[music playing]
NARUTO: Am I glad to
see you, Bushy Brow!
‐That is right.
Now that I am here, you
all have nothing to fear.
‐Hold on.
You're not alone here, pal.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
‐Huh.
Well, it looks like you
can relax now, Sakura.
‐You talk a big game, as
always, but you're still
just a medical ninjutsu amateur.
‐Hey, what did you say?
For someone who's only
studied a little more than me,
you sure are cocky.
‐Well, at least you acknowledge
that I've been studying longer.
‐Not that it's made
any difference.
‐Even with your head
start, I'm way more
advanced‐‐ Billboard Brow.
‐Wha?
Nobody's had the
nerve to call me
that in a long time, Ino Pig!
‐Oh, no you didn't.
SAKURA: Back off!
‐So their nicknames are
Billboard Brow and Ino Pig.
Huh.
Huh?
[both growl]
[both giggle]
‐Yah!
SAI: Unh!
Ow‐‐ what did I say?
[thud]
[both giggle]
‐Lady Tsunade briefed us on
the basics of the situation,
but I'll need you to fill
in some of the details.
‐Well, there's been
a new development.
‐You were saying, Sai?
‐Do your best.
[all chatting]
‐We'll explain over there.
KAKASHI: We encountered
four shinobi
who can all move freely
inside a smokescreen.
Then there's the
big guy I fought
and a Crystal Style user.
‐We found them at
the lake, and we
suspect they were dealing
with the Three‐Tails.
‐Thank you.
We had gathered as
much from our intel.
Well then, we'd better get to
work on sealing it quickly.
If the enemy gets the
Three‐Tails' power,
we're all but finished.
‐Actually, there's
something else.
A new wrinkle in things.
‐Huh?
‐Naruto witnessed a child
while he was at the lake,
and he claims that the child has
control over the tailed beast.
‐Impossible.
A human who can
control a tailed beast?
‐What's more, Naruto later
encountered the child
alongside the
Crystal Style user.
SHIZUNE: What's
their relationship?
‐They're close.
Like Naruto said, the
Crystal Style user
is the place where
that child will return.
‐Just who exactly is this child?
I thought the Three‐Tails
didn't have a jinchuriki.
‐Well, not yet.
After all, this is Orochimaru.
His goal may be to make that
child into a jinchuriki.
‐This thing just keeps
getting worse, doesn't it?
[music ‐ Joe Inoue, "Closer"]
[water lapping gently]
RINJI: We knew we had
to deal with human foes,
but no one said anything
about a tailed beast.
‐Yeah, no kidding.
That thing caused a massive
flood just by appearing.
What the hell are they
trying to start here?
‐Doesn't matter.
It's too late for
us to run away now.
‐Man, I'm telling
you, we need to think
of a way we can make a
break for it, and quick.
‐It's too much.
We were lucky to make it
out of that hideout alive.
I'm not about to give up
my life to some damn beast.
NURARI: Think of
something, Rinji.
We're counting on you.
RINJI (VOICEOVER): [groan]
What a bunch of buffoons.
‐Listen, I'll work it all out.
You guys have nothing
to worry about.
‐Thanks, Rinji.
I knew it.
RINJI: Where are you off to?
If you're going to
make a report to Guren,
I guess I'll tag along with you.
GOZU: You lie.
I can't trust you.
‐That so?
Well, I can't change
how you think of me.
‐Just tell me, you
gonna betray Guren?
My next move depends
on your answer.
‐Gozu, despite
what you may think,
my loyalties are with Guren.
GOZU: How do I
know that for sure?
[water lapping]
‐This is just
between you and me,
but what do you
think I'm doing here?
I left my sick kid sister
behind in the village.
And in order to keep
her safe and healthy,
I need to have money.
So as you can see, if I don't
survive, she won't, either.
Then again, whether you
think you can trust me or not
is completely up to you.
‐Ah, you're awake.
‐Where did Guren go?
‐Huh?
Oh.
Hey, how would you like to
return to Lord Orochimaru?
‐Is Guren coming, too?
‐Guren?
She's merely a sacrificial
pawn to our powerful master.
‐[gasp]
‐Remember, young man, you
belong to our lord Orochimaru.
‐No way.
The only place I'm go to is
wherever Guren is right now!
Aah!
Unnnh!
‐Aaagh!
‐Step away from
Yukimaru right now!
‐Guren.
‐What do you think
you're doing to him?
‐‐[laughs] Just giving the
boy a little discipline.
If anything truly
bad happened to him,
I would suffer the most.
And I don't intend on making
Lord Orochimaru angry.
The boy wasn't even
able to talk properly.
I'm astounded at how
much you've taught him.
‐If you ever lay so much as
a finger on Yukimaru again,
I will show you no mercy.
You understand?
‐Hmff.
Just be sure and keep a good
eye on our test subject.
[chuckles]
‐Are you all right?
‐Yep.
And I can stay here
with you, right, Guren?
It‐‐ it's just‐‐ I don't want to
go back to that hideout again.
[wings flapping]
‐Hello, Rinji.
‐Huh.
You believe her?
At first she was totally
hung up on Lord Orochimaru.
And now it's the
same with this kid.
I just hope it doesn't
interfere with her mission.
I'm worried she's getting
a bit too attached to him.
‐I'm certain Lord Orochimaru
will know how to handle her.
But just in case, I want you
to continue watching the girl.
Make sure she's
not up to anything.
‐Huh.
I spy for you, huh?
Wouldn't it make more sense if I
were the one reporting directly
to Lord Orochimaru?
‐Hm?
What are you saying?
‐Just that I've done a
lot of undesirable tasks
under your command.
I posed as a convict
at that prison,
got all friendly with
those inmates to send you
information on the outside.
That was pretty dangerous work.
And even this current job.
The only reason they're
getting all of this data
is because I'm putting
my life on the line
to acquire it for you.
‐What are you getting at?
‐Come on, you're a smart guy.
It's simple.
I just want to be
valued a little more.
‐Looking for a deal, are you?
‐Not at all.
I don't want anything.
You may give me my orders, but
I don't work under you, Kabuto.
The only one I serve
is Lord Orochimaru.
‐Ahhh.
‐Yeah.
All I want is for
Lord Orochimaru
himself to recognize
my diligence.
Besides, in this
situation, I'm the only one
can get Kigiri, Kiho,
and Nurari to act.
I'd even venture to say that
I have more power than you.
What I mean is if something
awful were to happen to you
and a Leaf Ninja somehow
managed to kill you,
wouldn't you want me to
report it to Lord Orochimaru
right away?
‐All right, then.
I'll take you to him.
But I suggest you
limit your expectations
if you plan on
surviving the meeting.
‐Now listen, in a
little while, it's
going to get noisy out there.
Just be a good boy and stay put.
‐What about you?
‐I have to take
care of business.
Then I'll hurry back.
Don't worry.
All you need to think
about is resting your body.
‐But I'm fine, Guren.
I actually feel back to normal.
‐No, not yet.
You need to heal completely.
‐Hey, wait.
I wanted to ask you for a favor.
Could you fix this for me?
‐Oh, that‐‐
rather than fixing it,
why don't I make
you a better one?
‐But I‐‐
GUREN: What is it?
‐But I want to keep this one.
This is the first flower
you gave me, remember?
‐All right.
Here, it's all fixed up.
‐Thank you, Guren.
You're not gonna
go away, are you?
‐[gasp]
‐Where I want to be
is here with you.
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
This is stupid.
What is this?
What am I doing?
[loud cawing]
[wind howling]
‐Naruto.
‐Hey, Kakashi Sensei.
‐What's the matter?
Something on your mind?
‐It's just‐‐
SAKURA: That moron.
The strategy meeting was
supposed to have started.
What's his excuse
going to be this time?
‐(QUIETLY) When it comes to
Naruto, she is always upset.
Huh.
‐Huh?
‐What do you see, Sakura?
Did you finally find Naruto?
‐Shh.
NARUTO: That kid, what are
you going to do with him?
‐I find it interesting
that you're
so concerned with him, Naruto.
‐He's being used
and you know it.
He believes there's
someone out there
he can go back to,
someone he can trust.
But he's gonna be betrayed.
And when that moment comes,
he won't have anywhere
left to turn.
If wherever someone
thinks of you is a place
you can call home,
well, then I am not
going to stop
thinking about him.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
He wasn't talking
about Sasuke after all.
‐Sure, it's important to
keep people in your thoughts,
but is it that simple?
Your feelings might conflict
with the other person's.
‐No, you're wrong.
It is that simple!
‐(SOFTLY) Naruto.
‐Everyone listen.
I'm going to go over Lady
Tsunade's plan of attack
and review the new
team formations.
First of all, the
search and rescue
mission to Orochimaru's secret
hideout is now complete.
Sakura, Hinata, and
Ino, from now on,
you'll be under my command.
‐Yes.
‐As for the rest of you, you'll
be forming a new unit that'll
be under the
direction of Kakashi.
‐All right.
Our team's new assignment is
to locate the Three‐Tail beast
and seal it by whatever
means necessary.
What's more, as that child
seems to be connected to this,
we must protect
him at all costs.
‐Huh?
‐It's not the Akatsuki alone
that covet the tailed beast.
If it becomes known that
a tailed beast exists
with no jinchuriki
the other nations
are bound to join
the hunt for it.
‐So that young boy
was brought here
to be transformed
into a jinchuriki.
Is that correct?
‐Hm?
‐Sai!
‐Ohhh.
I guess I forgot
you're a jinchuriki.
‐You dummy.
You always say stuff
without thinking, don't you?
But still, I bet you're
right about that.
Sealing the Three‐Tails
and protecting
that kid, that's so he doesn't
end up just like Gaara and me,
isn't it?
Right, Shizune?
‐Yes, that's our intention.
But the plan is not to
capture the tailed beast.
If we manage to seal
the beast, we're
going to send it to
another dimension.
That's Lady Tsunade's‐‐
the Hokage's will.
‐All right!
What are we waiting for?
‐One thing.
The tailed beast has a huge
reservoir of chakra, right?
I don't see how we
can put a seal on it.
‐Yes, it will be
extremely difficult,
requiring amazing
amounts of chakra control
and concentration.
Sakura and Ino, you've
trained in medical ninjutsu.
Your experience
will be very useful.
As well, Hinata's.
‐Um, but I don't
have any training
in medical ninjitsu, ma'am.
‐Actually, I was speaking of
your ability to control chakra.
You may not be a medical
ninja, but your Byakugan
can see the flow of chakra.
That and your mastery of the
gentle fist will come in handy.
You'll be very important.
‐Yeah, Hinata, you're amazing!
‐No I'm not.
[whimpers]
Mm, I'll do my best.
‐Yeah, I guess the girls
might be a little better
at delicate chakra
control than us guys.
Mm‐hm.
Huh?
Hey!
What about Tenten?
How come you didn't pick her?
All the other girls are
on the sealing team.
‐Well, I guess it's 'cause my
chakra control is rough, right?
Rrrrrnngh!
‐No, I‐‐ I didn't mean
it like that at all.
‐The rest of you will work
under Captain Yamato and myself
to provide protection.
I'm sure I don't need to
point this out to any of you,
but the people who are
after the Three‐Tails
won't wait around for us to
finish sealing the beast.
They'll hit hard.
The Crystal Style
user and the rest.
‐I say bring them on.
‐But how will our
team be structured?
‐Yeah, about that‐‐
I have an idea.
‐Well?
Come on, don't hold back.
Tell us already.
‐As I see it, the most
critical part of this battle
will be to stop the
Crystal Style user.
However, if all of us
fight her, the sealing team
will be left without
protection, which
is why I'm thinking of splitting
this team in two, with one
half concentrating on her.
Naruto, Sai, Shino.
‐Sir.
‐All right!
‐You three will operate
under my command
to confront the
Crystal Style user.
And all the others‐‐
Yamato, you know what to do.
‐Yes.
Understood.
OK, those of you whose
names weren't called before,
gather round.
TENTEN: He makes us sound
like we're the rejects.
LEE: Do not pout.
Where is your youthful
spirit and vigor?
‐Lee's right.
[Akamaru barks]
‐What were you doing?
‐Come on.
Isn't it obvious?
I was reporting back to
Kabuto about the movements
of the Leaf.
Actually, Kabuto
told me he was going
to return to Lord Orochimaru
at the hideout immediately.
‐That's strange timing.
‐Well, I guess he has
a lot on his mind.
‐Of course.
And Rinji?
‐Yeah?
‐What you said before,
I do trust you.
‐Ah?
RINJI (VOICEOVER):
Stopping the Three‐Tails
from being sealed and
destroying the Leaf‐‐
it's turning into a busy day.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): The
Hidden Leaf have come.
First we have to take
them down, and after that,
the Three‐Tails.
[gasp] No, I can't
worry about the boy.
Lord Orochimaru has
high hopes for me
and my only wish is to
be with Lord Orochimaru.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
She follows Orochimaru,
and Orochimaru's a
guy who thinks only
of his own twisted ambitions.
He'd sacrifice anything and
anybody to get what he wants.
And as far as I'm concerned‐‐
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Damn it!
What's wrong with me?
RINJI: Look who's here.
What are you doing?
Thinking up strategy?
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Rinji.
Where's he come from?
‐Yeah, sort of.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): And
how long's he been there?
‐Hm.
Look, the mist is clearing.
‐Right.
It's time to move.
‐Everyone, have you all
memorized the plan of action?
And remember, if that
child is discovered
during our operation, we must
do anything to protect him.
OK then, let's begin.
Tenten, show us what you have.
‐Right away.
Lady Tsunade specially
prepared this giant scroll
for the moment when we
seal the Three‐Tails.
Naruto, here.
[grunts with effort] Yaahhh!
Whoaa!
Wait, we're really going to
use this humongous scroll?
‐Exactly.
After all, we'll
need to suppress
a massive amount
of chakra energy.
Kakashi, we're counting on you.
‐No problem.
Both teams, fall into formation.
ALL: Yes, sir!
‐Naruto, guess we're
going our separate ways.
Good luck out there.
‐Leave it to me!
I won't need luck!
[MUSIC ‐ DEV PARADE,
"BACCHIKOI!!!"]
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): We'll
maintain this chakra balance
and slowly expand the
diameter of the opening.
When the Three‐Tails
is below the barrier,
we'll get a reaction.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Wait a minute.
If the enemy attacks while we're
maintaining the chakra balance,
we won't have a chance.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
That won't happen.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): We
won't have to fight them.
Trust your comrades to
take care of the enemy.
We just need to focus
on our chakra control.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time‐‐
"Four‐Corner Sealing Barrier."