-Where in the world could
he have gone off to?
It's like he just disappeared--
[breaking glass]
-Huh?
-Hold it!
Slow down, Sora!
-Oh!
Oh, no.
[crowd murmuring]
-Lady Sunned, there's someth--
-Sakura.
Sorry, I can't talk now.
I've called an emergency meeting
of all the team captains.
-What happened here, my lady?
-Sora tried to kill me.
-No.
-Has there ever been a power
outage this big before?
-This might not be
your ordinary blackout.
-Yeah.
Something's not right.
-Mmm.
-Oh!
-What are you talking about?
Everything's fine.
We have the Hokage looking
after us, don't we?
You don't think the
Hokage can handle this?
Stop whining and calm down.
-Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
-That's right.
As long as the
Hokage is with us.
[background chatter]
-Well, it's not the
main circuit breaker.
That means we stand by
on Area Three, right?
-Right.
Just like it says
in the field manual.
Meanwhile, the
off-duty team leader
should be meeting
with the Hokage.
-Well, then.
-Huh?
-Grr!
[chewing]
-Woah.
That is too delicious.
There we go.
I'm all fueled up
and ready for action.
You coming, Shikamaru?
-Yeah.
-No you don't!
-What the heck's going on?
-All the power is out.
-Oh, man.
I really don't
like the dark much.
-Something strange is going on.
It could mean trouble.
-What?
-Close and secure the main gate!
-The signal system
is secure, my lady.
You'll be able to
communicate instructions
if an attack should come.
-Excellent work.
(VOICEOVER) So now it comes.
Just when I've dispatched
so many of our Shinobi the
to Hidden Rain border.
-As you're probably
aware, the entire village
is without electricity.
There's always the possibility
that this power outage
occurred by accident.
However, since we've been
unable to make contact
with the main power
station, the safest course
is for us to assume that this is
an act of deliberate sabotage.
Therefore, I'm placing the
village on Level Two emergency
security alert.
-Huh?
-Company Three, fan out
and cover the east, west,
and north gates.
Company Two, go
to the main gate.
Company One will go
to the power station
and find out what's going on.
Asuma.
You'll remain here.
Keep your eyes open, everyone.
Dismissed!
-Sora tried to kill me.
-He what?
-Fortunately, he
was interrupted.
-Just a minute.
You-- you were
attacked, Lady Tsunade?
By Sora?
-Naruto is pursuing him now.
Go after them.
Hard as it is for you
to believe, it happened.
Find Sora and take him prisoner.
-Right.
-Huh?
-What is it?
-I thought-- it was like
the forest moved just now.
[birds calling]
-Is it an earthquake?
[shivering]
-Sorry, travelers,
but this village
has been cordoned off
for security reasons.
I'm afraid we can't
let you proceed any--
[gasps]
[laughter]
-Ahhh!
-What's that?
-It's confirmed, my lady.
We're under attack.
An attempt is being
made on the main gate.
Our security units
have engaged the enemy.
-And so it begins.
-Hmm.
-Move out!
Keep them away
from the main gate!
-Status report.
-Idiot!
Don't order them to
approach head on!
-Grr.
I'll take over from here.
Engage them only
from a distance.
[theme music - in japanese]
-The enemy is still approaching.
Our units have now engaged.
They're one kilometer from
the main gate and closing.
-Naruto.
-They headed that way.
-Cut it out!
Wait, damn it!
-Augh!
[grunting]
-What were you trying to do
by attacking Grandma Tsunade?
-Leave me alone!
This has nothing to do with you.
-It has everything
to do with me.
Huh?
[grunting]
-Hmm?
-Barrier Defense Seal Jutsu.
Eight Gate Lock-up!
-What the hell?
-Huh?
Hey!
-There's another one
at the east gate.
-The west gate, too.
-Huh?
-Lady Tsunade.
What is happening?
-Raise the alert to Level One.
We're on maximum alert.
All reserve units to
the main gate at once.
-Yes, my lady.
-Find Shikamaru.
Tell him to start working
on defense countermeasures
immediately.
-Right.
-Sakura.
Get yourself ready
to move out, too.
-Yes, my lady.
-What the-- what's
going on down there?
-It's them.
They've come.
-Huh?
Wait a minute.
Who has come?
What do you know?
-A defense barrier?
-What?
That doesn't make sense.
-Enemy appears to have erected
some sort of defensive barrier
around us.
-A defensive barrier?
-Wha-- what's that?
-He means a defense barrier.
-Huh?
-Ugh.
Don't you see?
It's a barrier used for defense.
Like a wall for defending
against enemy attacks,
or to keep an enemy
outside from getting in.
-But the enemy is outside,
so why would they put it up?
It's like defending
against themselves.
It's weird.
-No.
Maybe not.
-Huh?
-Maybe it's not intended to keep
them out, but-- to keep us in.
-That's right.
For some reason, they
want that barrier
to keep us trapped
here in the village.
-Now what do they have in mind?
-We are four individuals,
made one by a common resolve
to pursue the cause
of the Land of Fire.
It is this indomitable resolve
that has brought us here.
Lend us your ears for
but a brief moment,
for there is not much to say.
We have only one purpose.
The greater glory
of the Land of Fire
with the Feudal Lord Supreme.
-The existence of the
Hokage in this village
poses a lasting threat
to the supremacy
of the Land of
Fire's Feudal Lord.
There can only be one true King.
Don't you understand?
There is no longer any reason
for this Hokage of yours
to exist!
-Why, you--
-We didn't expect your approval.
Nevertheless, you will help
us achieve our purpose.
Even after you die.
-But I remember
learning that there's
no way to get in or out
of a defense barrier.
-Yes, quite right.
The enemy must be employing
some kind of special jutsu
to penetrate the barrier.
The situation is this.
We are trapped inside, while
the enemy can come and go
as they please.
Now that they've been allowed
to infiltrate the village,
we go to Stage Two, as
outlined in the Sneak Attack
Countermeasures manual.
-You name it, we're
ready to fight right now.
-Right!
-Yeah!
-Not yet.
-Before we can counterattack,
we must evacuate the civilians.
Your job is to round up
everyone in the village
and guide them calmly and
swiftly to a safe place.
Are you up to it?
This is your first
A-Rank mission.
-You bet we're up to it.
-Go.
I'm counting on you.
Meanwhile, I'll do what I
can to stall for time here.
-It's going to take
more than words.
-We won't let you
touch the Hokage.
-(VOICEOVER) If we can just hold
until reinforcements get here.
-Hmm.
Fudo.
-Yeah.
-Earth Style.
Impermanence!
-What?
Get back!
-Lady Tsunade.
I'm ready.
-Now that the
battle's been joined,
there's going to
be desperate need
for medical ninja
such as yourself.
Go.
-Right.
-(VOICEOVER) It
hasn't gone perfectly,
but we've done just
about all we can.
Why, then, do I
still feel so uneasy?
[grunt]
-It's just one
thing after another.
These guys are too much.
Huh?
-Earth Style.
Ultimate Revival Jutsu.
Soil Bodies.
Rise, fallen Shinobi.
Rise and live again!
[groan]
[laughter]
-You are about to die facing
our army of dead Shinobi!
-You don't know
anything about me.
-You're right about that.
Who are those guys?
What have you done?
-The Leaf tried to eliminate me.
What do you expect?
-Grandma Tsunade would
have never done that!
-Yes, they did!
I just tried to get
them before they got me!
-I finally found you.
-Asuma-sensei!
-It's the backstabber Asuma!
-Huh?
-Sora.
Why did you attack the Hokage?
She is not the one you're after.
[laughter]
-The one you want
revenge on is me.
-Let go!
I'm only doing the exact
same thing you did.
You chose to side with your
king by killing my father.
-King?
-I'll return the
favor by killing her.
-What are you talking about?
You're not making sense.
-No.
It's true.
-What?
-Sora.
You called Lady Tsunade
"king" just now.
-(VOICEOVER) The Land of
Fire doesn't need two Kings.
The Leaf is just
a military asset.
The Hokage is superfluous.
We already have a
man at the helm.
The Feudal Lord.
-According to Toschi's
reports, the Hidden Rain
was not involved in the
attacks on the border villages.
More significantly, it appears
that the mission assigned
to him by Danzo was
to track and monitor
the movements of those
four grave robbers.
The ones who violated the hidden
tombs near the Temple of Fire
recently.
-It is just as you all
feared, I'm afraid.
What those four were
really after all
along was that boy, Sora,
from the fire temple.
-(VOICEOVER) Now I understand.
But that means--
[gasp]
-This is bad.
-What is it, Asuma-sensei?
-If my guess is
right, the village
is in even greater
danger than we feared.
[groans]
-No pushing!
Everyone stay calm,
and keep moving!
-The enemy's objective is
more than just conquest.
It's mass slaughter.
-Say what?
-Nonsense.
What makes you think that--
-It must be.
-Why did the grave
robbers steal the bodies
of the four Lightning
Style Shinobi?
It's because they
sought the power
of those particular Shinobi.
They wanted the power of
Lightning Style Jutsu.
They've hit upon the means
of harnessing that power,
and using it to wipe out the
village and everyone in it.
-Wipe out the village?
-Sora.
Is this really true?
They'll destroy
the whole village?
Thousands of villagers.
You want their
lives on your head?
-I don't know.
I don't know anything!
-Sora!
-I must join the others.
-Huh?
-I have to stop this
before the worst happens.
Naruto, you'll have
to deal with Sora.
-Got it.
-(VOICEOVER) Finally,
it all makes sense.
What Sora said.
His use of the word "king."
There's no doubt about it now.
The one who attempted that
coup in the Land of Fire
is the same one
who's behind this.
-Charging process, complete.
[theme music - in japanese]
-What did you say?
-These guys attacking us.
They're Shinobi from
the Land of Fire?
-Yeah.
Those markings mean they
belong to the Kohaku clan
from that village on the border.
-But I thought most
of the Kohaku clan
were supposed to
have been destroyed
in that attack on their village.
-Maybe they've been raised
from the dead through some kind
of reanimation jutsu.
-That's horrible.
It's unforgivable.
To take all these people's lives
just to turn them into weapons?
-Next Time.
Revived Souls.
[theme music - in japanese]