Captain Kakashi.
What's the intel on the
enemy?
There aren't any signs of
life anywhere, including
from the enemy.
The battlefield's
completely quiet.
I wonder what's going
on. I seriously doubt
that they'd just give up
the fight.
Psychological warfare is
key to winning a shinobi
battle.
I really don't like doing
exactly what the enemy
wants us to dÄ6
... but we should use this
as a chance to rest.
All right, everyone, rest
up! Take time to recover
your chakra!
However... Stay on your
guard! We'll keep
scouting the area every
half an hour!
We must make sure we're
ready to begin fighting
again at a moment's
notice! Okay! That's all!
Guy, you should rest a
little, too.
Ha! Get real, Kakashi!
You really think I could
sleep at a time like
this?!
I understand how you
feel, but...
Captain Kakashi.
We finally received the
item from Headquarters.
Good.
This jutsu... it
really is unforgivable.
Sai, next up we'll use
the Foundation's Sealing
Jutsu.
So follow me!
But Kakashi, I
haven't mastered that
jutsu yet.
Isn't it true that Danzo
valued you very highly,
Sai?
You don't have to
suppress your emotions
anymore!
Hmm--
Hey, Sai. Sorry to bother
you while you're
resting...
It's okay.
This just arrived from
headquarters.
You need this for your
Sealing Jutsu, don't you?
Mmm.
Lee.
[panicking]
Is it the enemy?!
Well, looks like you can
still fight.
Of course, sir! Because
I, Rock Lee, the Blue
Beast of the Leaf, do not
know the meaning of the
word "exhaustion!"
I want you to be Sai's
bodyguard.
He won't be able to
defend himself well while
he's preparing his
Sealing Jutsu.
Leave it to me, sir!
I will risk my life to
protect him!
[grunting]
Better get
to it, Sai.
Yes, sir.
Okay! I look forward to
this!
Do not worry one
bit, Sai. No matter
who the foe may be...
I will not let them lay a
single finger on you!
Lee...
Sai!
It is okay! You can skip
the formalities and call
me by a nickname the same
way you do with Naruto
and Sakura!
Listen, Lee. Could
you leave me alone
for a while?
Yes, I understand! Just
call me right away if
something happens!
Sorry... But do you have
a moment, Kakashi Sensei?
Sure, what is it?
It is concerning Sai's
Sealing Jutsu.
Do you think it would be
possible for you to tell
me a little bit more about
it?
Yeah, I guess so.
I've just got to figure
out where I should
start.
You know that he used to
be a member of the
Foundation, right?
I suppose that it all got
started back when
Orochimaru attacked the
Hidden Leaf Village
during your chunin
exams.
Sai, it is imperative
that you learn and become
proficient with this
Sealing Jutsu.
Yes, sir.
The Third Hokage was
unparalleled in his use
of jutsu.
But when Orochimaru used
the Reanimation Jutsu to
bring back the First and
Second Hokage, the Third
Hokage had to seal them
away with the Reaper
Death Seal...
...and sacrificed his
life in doing so.
In order for things to
work in our favor, the
Foundation needs to
possess a powerful
Sealing Jutsu without
that limitation.
But... can I actually
master a Sealing Jutsu
that will work against
someone as powerful as
Orochimaru?
I believe that you can.
Uh!
You've been taught that
emotions merely hinder a
shinobi, isn't that
right?
Yes.
All of the feelings that
you've suppressed have
created a massive
reservoir of energy
somewhere deep inside
your heart.
And by releasing
that pent-up emotional
energy, you will be
able to imbue your
Sealing Jutsu with great
power.
But be careful...
Releasing your emotions
can make you susceptible
to the effects of your
negative feelings. And
that can be very
dangerous.
"The Helmet Splitter:
Jinin Akebino!"
Shift change.
Right.
So how's everything going?
Nothing's changed.
It's morning and the
enemy still hasn't shown
their faces. It sure is
quiet.
It feels like the calm
before the storm.
I hope it means that this
whole thing is gonna be
over soon, know what I'm--
They're here! The enemy's
attacking!
They're here.
Over here!
He ran away?!
[screaming]
Damn it! Where is he?!
Huh?!
Hey... What just
happened....? Where'd
they all go?!
[grunting]
They're here. This way!
It appears that even
though they're cornered,
they aren't gonna fight
us.
The enemy's moved their
weaker forces in.
It seems that their main
tactic is going to be
guerrilla warfare.
They want us to chase
these targets and get
split up so they can pick
us off one by one.
I hate to admit it, but
they wanted us to become
overconfident after
defeating Zabuza.
Now what? Things are
going downhill fast.
We need to regroup our
forces. Send a message
out to each team!
Tell them to join up with
at least two other teams
and stick together!
Okay, you got it! What
are you gonna do?!
I'm worried about the
squads behind us. If I
were the enemy, I'd use
this confusion to cut off
our support squads.
The rear guards are
battle-hardened... and
they have the restraints
and seals to fight
against the Reanimation
Jutsu.
Well... I don't really
understand. I'll just
leave it to you!
All right, you heard him,
right?! Send a message to all
the teams! Do not pursue the
enemy if you see them.
Tell them to stick
together and that we'll
destroy the enemy one at
a time!
Yes, sir!
Guy Sensei! Sorry I am
late!
Forget it.
Sai! Lee!
Perfect timing. Follow
me! We're going to
prepare a seal!
Sir!
You can count on me!
We won't let them dictate
how this war goes!
So, Sai... it takes some
time for you to prepare
your Sealing Jutsu, is
that correct?
How do you know that?
It was quite simple. I
just asked Kakashi Sensei
whether you need to stop
and concentrate in
order to use emotional
energy.
I will protect you,
however long it may take!
Earth Style! Mud Wall!
Ensui, prepare your
Shadow Paralysis Jutsu!
You got it!
Huh?!
[yelling]
I found ya.
[gasping]
One more time!
Defending yourself
against Kabutowari...
...the Blunt Blade Helmet
Splitter, is utterly
meaningless!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Get in formation,
now!
Trying to block me is
meaningless, too!
It seems you fools still
don't understand!
[gasping]
My next attack will end
you!
Not yet!
Wait, is that...?
Captain Kakashi!
I hope you don't think
that this will be over so
soon.
All right... You should
begin, Sai!
I agree.
I am very eager to see
what it is like! Show me
what your Sealing Jutsu
can do!
Mm!
But be careful...
Releasing your emotions
can make you susceptible
to the effects of your
negative feelings. And
that can be very
dangerous.
I've made up my mind.
But... I've been told to
suppress my emotions ever
since I was a child.
Is it really possible for
me master this Sealing
Jutsu?
And more importantly,...
can I overcome this sense
of fear I have when I let
my emotions go?
[grunting]
You've succumbed to your
negative feelings.
They're consuming you.
[coughing]
[gasping]
You're back now.
Lord Danzo, what...
What happened...?
You must assimilate the
mass of negative feelings
you have pent up within
you and train carefully
to use them.
This jutsu is the reason
why I raised all of you
from the time you were
young.
Keep going until you gain
complete control over
your emotions.
Learn to release all your
negative feelings. You
have to master them, Sai!
I couldn't suppress my
emotions that time.
Will I really be able to
suppress them any better
now?
If anything... it seems
to be even harder!
But...
I have to do this!
So there's still someone
left in this world who's
at least a little bit of
a challenge.
Even if you are one of the
Seven Ninja Swords Men of
the Mist, we won't let you
win this fight so easily.
[chuckling]
I'll silence you!
That eye looks dangerous.
But...
If I can simply thrust my
sword toward you, then
I'll win!
There is no way to
block the helmet
splitter!
Who said anything about
blocking?
Uh!
Your defense is weak!
That's one down...
[cheering]
Ensui!
Yes, sir!
Hold him with Shadow
Paralysis until the
Sealing Jutsu is
ready to go.
Right! Understood!
The rest of you will meet
up with the squad in front.
You'll all follow me.
Now let's go!
Shadow Stitching Jutsu!
Ah, I see. That is the
same kind of Secret
Ninjutsu as Shikamaru's.
It's just a stopgap
measure. If I release my
jutsu, he'll be free.
So you guys need to
seal him away as soon as
possible.
Impossible.
Run away, little brother.
We're indestructible.
There's no way you can
win!
Shin. Brother...
Brother! Snap out of it!
Uh--
Now. Secret Black Technique!
Salamander!
Brother!
[struggling]
You okay?
I heard it was difficult,
but he looks like he is
suffering greatly!
Are you all right,
Sai?
Lee...
Incoming!
An Explosive Style User!
Not good!
Sai!
Hurry up with the seal!
Lee can't handle this
alone. I need to go back
him up!
There is no reason to
worry!
I will not forgive the
Akatsuki! They are
controlling the dead with
the Reanimation Jutsu.
And that makes me
seriously angry! Is there
any reason I would let
myself lose this fight?
No way! There is not!
[yelling]
[grunting]
How...? I don't sense any
negative feelings coming
from Lee as a result of
his anger.
Why? Why doesn't anger
come with negative
feelings for him?
[yelling]
This is bad!
How dare you!
How dare you harm my
friend! You will not get
away with that!
The enemy is on the move
now. We should head out
so we can regroup with
the main company!
Sai... If there is
anything I can do, please
let me know!
I will do whatever I can!
'Cause I am your friend!
I see. Then the origin
of Lee's anger is found
in his strong feelings
for his friends.
But... that will not work
for me...
No...! I'm different from
how I was back then...
I have friends now.
And...
What's more, I also
have strong feelings
towards those friends.
Uh!
A sealing jutsu that
becomes more powerful
when I release my
emotions.
But those emotions don't
have to be negative ones
that come from anger or
sorrow!
[yelling]
Quick, Sai!
Lee!
I realized something... I
never gave you a
nickname...
But once this war is
over, I'll think of one.
Now, Sai! Do it!
Sealing Jutsu.
Crouched Tiger Bullet.
[roaring]
Okay! Got him!
Return!
[grunting]
[struggling]
No matter what defense.
Uh!
Wait! No, don't go after
him!
Sai!
[chuckling]
Hm.
What a pathetic sight,
Maki! You're actually
protecting a Mist
Shinobi!
She's my comrade.
Your comrade?! What are
you talking about?! She's
from the Bloody Mist. They
kill their own kind!
We're part of the
Allied Shinobi Forces!
An alliance? Whatever,
you idiots!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: User of the
Scorch Style: Pakura of
the Sand!
You'd sacrifice yourself
for an enemy shinobi?!