[music playing]
-I predict that the Hidden
Leaf will emerge victorious
from this battle.
Therefore, I'll let
the three of you live.
-Keep your sympathy.
We could still fight you.
-No, Jiraiya, stop!
-You three are very strong.
You survived even
this battleground.
And so I, Hanzo, hereby christen
you three the Hidden Leaf's
Sannin in exchange
for your lives.
Tell me your names.
-Will all this really
end with the Hidden Leaf
being victorious?
Did Hanzo speak the truth?
-If it does end
that way, are you
gonna leave on another journey?
-Well, maybe I will.
Set out on yet more travels
and write another book.
-Why don't you just settle
down in the village?
-I feel as though I
haven't quite found it yet.
-You mean your
destiny, don't you?
-Shh.
[thunder cracking]
-I can sense they're just kids.
-Don't let your guard down.
Even these little mice are
from the Hidden Rain Village.
-We know you're hiding.
Show yourselves.
[music playing]
All right.
What is it?
-I want you to
give me some food.
-Where are your parents?
-They were killed by ninja
because of this stupid war.
JIRAIYA: Here.
Have some hardtack.
-Nagato, Konan-- come on out.
They seem like they're OK.
-We already gave you guys food.
Stop following us.
-Thank you all.
This is for you.
-It's origami.
It's made from the
hardtack wrapper.
-And this is a gift for us?
-Please, will you
teach us ninjutsu?
You're all ninja from the
Hidden Leaf, aren't you?
-These kids-- shall I kill them?
We've seen so many war orphans.
It's always so pitiful.
They'd be better off if
we simply put them out
of their misery right now.
-Enough, Orochimaru.
You go on ahead with
Tsunade for now.
I'm going to stay here and look
after these three for a while.
-What?
-Only until they're
truly able to take
better care of themselves.
It's the least I can do
after what they've suffered.
-Yeah, but--
-This is also part
of my destiny.
ALL: Thank you for the food.
-Grilled fish in an instant
thanks to my fire style jutsu.
Delicious!
-Hey, I think I've gotten
the hang of fishing, sensei.
-Nagato, what's the matter?
-Nothing.
I just remember my family.
-Stop crying and be a man!
It's because of
little wimps like you
that men of the Hidden
Rain are called cowards!
-Things may be unstable now
among the three great nations
that surround the
Hidden Rain Village.
But I don't think that this
war will last much longer.
I'm confident that by the
time you are all grown up,
there will be mutual
understanding and peace
will finally--
-No, that's not fair!
-Huh?
-All of us have lost our
whole families to this war.
For mutual understanding, they
had to go through what we did.
That's which sharing
the pain is, right?
[music playing]
But I know now that's just
never going to happen.
And that's why wars
will never end.
I hate rain.
It's like this land
is always crying,
like the whole land is a coward.
But I'm going to change this
land, you just watch me.
I'll protect everyone.
That's why I ask,
Jiraiya sensei-- please
teach us ninjutsu.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
I can't seem
to come up with any ideas
for my novel at all.
-For mutual understanding, they
have to go through what we did.
And that's why wars
will never end.
I'll protect everyone.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): I
want the hero of my book
to wipe away hatred and somehow
bring peace to the world.
Now, how can I do that?
-Jiraiya sensei, come help!
It's Yahiko and Nagato!
-Lead the way, Konan.
-I brought Jiraiya sensei.
-What happened?
-It was him.
A renegade shinobi attacked us.
He told us to hand over
our food and our valuables.
And then Nagato--
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): He's a
chunin from the Hidden Rock.
How did Nagato ever--
those, those eyes.
Don't tell me
he's-- it can't be.
[music playing]
That shape, that ripple pattern.
I can't believe it.
That eye, said to
hold the most noble
of the three great visual
jutsu-- the Rinnegan.
It originated with
the Sage of the Six
Paths, the father
of all shinobi.
It's said that the
Rinnegan-eye-possessing sage
developed all the jutsu
known to us today.
He's rumored to
reappear whenever
the world becomes corrupt.
He's capable of being both
a godlike force for creation
or an all-obliterating
instrument of destruction.
I always thought it
was a myth, but here's
someone who actually
possesses it.
-I shall now tell you--
I will relate my dream.
You, who are singularly pervy
shall become a great ninja.
And once you do,
you shall acquire
an apprentice of your very own.
That apprentice
will become a ninja
who will bring about a great
change in the ninja world.
That is what I
foresaw in my dream.
You will be the one to guide
this revolutionary change.
And eventually,
there will come a day
when you will be forced to
make a critical selection.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Could
Nagato be that revolutionary?
Perhaps I've found my destiny.
-I've decided that I will
teach all of you ninjutsu.
-Really?
-It's a possibility
you could encounter
another life-threatening
situation like before.
So I'll teach you ninjutsu,
but only for self defense.
-Yes, all right!
Listen, I owe you a bit
thanks for saving us
last time, Nagato.
And I'm sorry that I
called you a coward.
And the next time that
anything bad happens,
I'll be the one to protect you.
-Thank you, Yahiko.
-What?
But Nagato is totally
stronger than you are, Yahiko.
-Yeah, but I'm gonna train now
and become stronger myself.
You always talk too much, Konan.
-All right.
Let's just get started.
The first lesson is on
manipulating chakra.
ALL: Yes, sensei.
[crying]
-Huh?
Nagato, what's bothering you?
Talk to me.
-Sensei.
-Is it that incident?
-That day when that
ninja hurt Yahiko,
I was just so angry with him.
Everything went
blank in my head.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Before I realized
it, the guy was dead.
After that, just
became so frightened.
That hatred made me
go blind with rage.
And I killed somebody
because of it.
It was wrong.
I know it was wrong.
-Nagato, I don't know.
I can't really say whether
what you did was right
or it was wrong.
But still, thanks to your
actions, Yahiko is still alive.
You saved your friend.
So I believe that's always
the right thing to do.
No one can fault you
for helping a friend.
Once you've been hurt,
you learn to hate.
But if you hurt another
you become hated,
and you shoulder
a sense of guilt.
But it is because one
understands such pain
that generosity towards
others becomes second nature.
That's what makes us human.
-I don't-- what do you mean?
-It's a process
called growing up.
-It's called growing up?
I still don't get it.
-It's about being able to think
and make your own decisions.
-Konan and I would cry
because we were so hungry.
And then Yahiko saved us.
He stole food from
other people to feed us.
All I want to do is protect
those two, no matter what kind
of pain I may be
forced to endure.
-I understand.
[music playing]
-Water Style Raging Waves!
-Paper Shuriken!
-Wind Style Gale Palm!
-Yes.
How's that, sensei?
JIRAIYA: You're able to take
down my shadow clone now, huh?
Well then, I can return
home without any worries.
-What?
-You three are all on
your own from here on out.
You've all done a great
job these past three years.
Hey, don't cry, Yahiko, or
people will call you a coward.
Konan, you're going to grow
up to be a real beauty.
I know it.
I hope we meet again someday.
This land is destitute, so
there will be hard times ahead.
But from this point
forward, you three
can change the
fate of this land.
Nagato, you three have really
grown up, wouldn't you agree?
Thank you, sensei.
NARRATOR: Even when Jiraiya
returned to the village
after so long, the Third Great
Ninja War still raged on.
-Ready?
Tsunade, Orochimaru.
-Yeah.
-Summoning jutsu!
The Hidden Leaf Sannin
distinguished themselves
in many battles, leaving
countless legendary tales
behind them in their wake.
TSUNADE: All this fighting--
how long must it go on?
Is there nothing that can
be done to stop this war?
-You say that as
though there really
might be a way to stop it.
Hate just breeds even
more hate, and that's
the way it will always be.
-That's not true.
-I don't know how to stop this.
But without a doubt, we
will have peace one day.
As long as there are those who
believe that peace is possible,
there still is hope.
-Hmph.
JIRAIYA: What's the matter?
-What's wrong?
JIRAIYA: Those three have died.
I've tried-- I've tried my
absolute best to always make
the right choices.
I really believe
that that was what
destiny had in store for me.
-Jiraiya.
JIRAIYA: In the end, I
thought that what I did
was the right thing to do.
But I guess I was
wrong yet again.
[music playing]
TSUNADE: You will find it, as
long as you keep believing.
JIRAIYA: Yes.
Perhaps I will.
I guess I'm still in the
middle of my journey, then.
NARRATOR: The Third Great
Ninja War continued to drag on,
and the one who ultimately
guided the Hidden Leaf
Village to victory was another
outstanding pupil of Jiraiya's,
a prodigy named Minato Namikaze.
[music playing]
TSUNADE: It was long.
Too long.
What'll you do now?
-Well, let's see.
Maybe I'll set out
on another journey.
Perhaps at last I can
find the apprentice
who can change the world.
TSUNADE: Is that your destiny?
The destiny of
the great Jiraiya?
JIRAIYA: I suppose
you could say that.
-Huh.
You're a strange one.
-But you also walk
the path of the ninja.
Don't you want someone
to take over after you?
-To gather all of the
jutsu in this world
and master every one of
them-- that is the only
go I care about.
-Even if you could
master them all,
human beings aren't
immortal, you know.
-She's right.
-Hmm.
I wonder if that's really true.
[music playing]
-Just give up.
-Can I say one thing?
ASSASSIN: I don't
care what you say.
Just die already.
-Give up, huh?
Huh?
-Yeah, about that.
ASSASSIN: Even if
you take me down,
another assassin will
attack the village.
As long as we're cursed to
live in this ninja world, then
there can be no peace, ever.
-Well, then, I'm going to
break that curse one day.
If there's truly such a thing as
peace somewhere in this world,
then I am going to find it.
And I'll never stop looking.
-Who-- who are you?
-My name is--
-Hey!
So you're reading my "Tales of
a Gutsy Ninja" book, are you?
Well, it's only my
first published work
so the stanzas can
be a bit childish.
It's not a great, really.
But--
-Oh, no.
I don't believe that at all.
I think that this
tale is wonderful.
-Oh?
-Every chapter reads like one of
the numerous legendary exploits
you told me about.
It's like it's almost
autobiographical.
-Yeah, but it
didn't sell at all.
Ha.
For my next one,
I think I'll add
some spicy elements
to pep it up.
-The main character in here-- I
thought that his determination
to never give up
was pretty awesome.
He's actually quite a
lot like you, sensei.
-Yeah?
You think so?
-So I was thinking.
I really hope my soon-to-be-born
child can become an amazing
shinobi, just like the main
character in your book.
So that's why I'd like
to ask your permission
to name my son after him.
-You what?
Are you sure about this?
I mean, I randomly came up
with it while eating ramen.
KUSHINA UZUMAKI: Naruto.
I think it's a wonderful name.
-Kushina.
Wow.
So would that make me
his godfather then?
Are you really sure
you're sure about this?
-You are my sensei, Jiraiya.
You are a great ninja who
possesses true talent.
There's no one else like
you in the whole world.
NARRATOR: Even
after that moment,
Jiraiya continued his journeys
in search of his destiny.
So it would be some
time before Jiraiya
would meet Naruto in the
Village Hidden in the Leafs
and begin their
journey together.
[music playing]
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
What is going on here?
It's great that I got
in here so easily,
but just who is this Pain that
everybody's talking about?
All I ever get from
these villagers
are vague descriptions
like god or angel.
And I can't seem to
locate the former village
leader, Hanzo of the Salamander.
But there's no time to waste.
I guess that I'll have to
just go with that one plan.
Next time-- Infiltrate!
The Village Hidden in the Rain.