This is really bad...
He's merging all the scattered
chakra into one.
Quite well, too! Almost
unrivaled....
Old Man Six Paths' level. Except
it's in reverse. With no Gedo
Statue, the Susano'o's the
receiving vessel.
Something incredible's going to
emerge! Stay alert!
That jutsu again, huh?>
Naruto... that jutsu of yours is
a symbol of your weakness.
Yeah... It's a jutsu that only
covers up your loneliness!
[attacking yell]
[grunts]
[struggling grunts] Why that-!
You only hold a little piece of
each Tailed Beast's chakra...
[heavy breathing]
You can't win against me now.
Nor can you hope to stop this...
Ya ready yet...? Kurama?!
I might've amassed too much, in
fact. It's everything that's
avaliable. Here it comes!
Got it!
(SASUKE) I can feel it! How'd he
suddenly gain so much Nature
Energy?
Let's do this!
Alright!
Finally decided to kill me, huh?
We've taken a lot of
responcibilities upon our
shoulders...
But you see... I...
You're one of the ones I want to
fight the most.
[gasp]
I actually do wanna fight
against you! And I wanna win
fair and square!
Although...
...not against the current you!
But you already know that, too,
don't ya Sasuke?!
This fight with you right now,
will be my last.
Indra's Arrow... Currently the
most powerful jutsu in my
arsenal...
Just die!
Just be gone already!
[gasp]
[pained coughs and groans]
[pained breaths]
[grunt] Damn it... You're
still--!
(KURAMA) Naruto!
If my Nature Energy hadn't
reached you, you'd've been toast
just now!
And your chakra's already been
drained from the war...
Amaterasu!
Only a diversion, huh? I can't
actually take him down with
this. I need the Tailed
Beasts...
[pained grunt]
[pained grunts]
I've used too much chakra. I
can't maintain control! At this
rate, I can't use my left eye's
abilities either!
[grunts]
[pained grunts]
[grunting]
[gasp]
[pained grunt]
[heavy breathing]
[attack yell and grunt]
[gasp]
[annoyed grunts]
[grunt]
[pained groans]
[sniffle and exhale]
He's still not--!
[pained grunts] Give it up
already...
[weak inhale]
Sasuke! / Naruto!
[wet cough]
[pained grunt]
[yelling]
[pained grunts and groans]
[grunt] Damn it!
Sasuke wins.
Now, make the Unison Sign...
[grunt] Hey, come back!
You weren't even looking at me!
That didn't count!
You're a turd! No, you're
crap! Hard and runny! You're
stupid...
Got something to say to me, you
hard and runny crap-turd?
[grunt]
Ow!
I told you, Hand-to-Hand Combat
is a sacred tradition!
Now make the Unison Sign!
[gasp]
(KAKASHI) You're finally awake.
Huh?
It's dusk already...
[gasp] Where are Sasuke and
Naruto?
They're fighting their final
battle right now in order to...
...settle things for good.
[gasp]
[heavy breathing]
[weary exhale]
Hang in there! It's not much,
but I've got some chakra-!
[gasp]
[weak gasp]
This is just one of the many
abilities of the Rinnegan.
As somebody who possesses the
eyes of the Uchida... my victory
is inevitable.
[pained grunt]
Now...
Now, I can finally... be alone!
[heavy breathing]
Farewell...
...my one and only...
...friend!
[pained grunt]
That was a nice counter! You
noticed that his Visual Prowess
had weakened!
Over...
...and over and...
...over...
...and over...
and over and over and over and
over again! [inhale]
Just give up...
...and let me cut you down,
already!
[chuckle] Sorry, can't do that.
'Cause I'm your one and only
friend. That's what you said,
right?
[angry growl]
[inhale]
As I thought... Sasuke took the
chakra that I got for you and
made it his own...
Flame Control. He's planning to
settle things with one blast.
Naruto, I will give you what's
left of my chakra...
That'll put me to sleep. Hold
your jutsu till the last minute,
so he doesn't steal any of it.
Well, not that he is even able
to use his Rinnegan to absorb
chakra while putting out his own
jutsu...
[gasp]
Who are you to be so confident,
when you couldn't even save
Sasuke?
Once you question your
beliefs...
...that's it; it's all over.
I will find a way to save
Sasuke... [chuckle]
Hey, ya know what?
I believe... I'm gonna come
after all of that hate that's
inside of you, too, someday!
Now go... You're the one and
only for us, too...
That's why... Sasuke's...
[attack yell]
Am I... dead?
Everything feels strange, so...
Yeah that must be what happened.
Well, probably.
Sorry, Grandma Tsunade... I know
that I promised I wouldn't
die...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Unison Sign"
...till I became Hokage...