[water lapping gently]
[wind howling]
[splash]
[loud wailing call]
[drip]
[gasp]
[sighs]
[wind picks up]
‐Quite the beast, this one.
It seems ordinary
methods won't work.
Doesn't matter.
We'll just move on to Plan B.
[music ‐ joe inoue, "closer"]
[music ‐ Joe Inoue, "Closer"]
[grunts with effort]
‐Everyone OK?
‐Yeah, more or less.
[squelching]
‐I don't think those Leaf Ninja
are around here at the moment.
But everyone stay on your guard.
So what was that
huge wave just now?
Somebody kept crying out.
What the heck are Guren
and that ogre doing?
‐I don't know, which is
probably for the best.
[splashing]
[panting]
‐Hey, Gozu, you made it.
‐Yeah.
Where's Guren?
‐Not sure.
‐You should be able to find her.
‐Trust me, if I could, I would.
But there's nothing I can do.
My bats have gone silent.
I know as little as you.
You going somewhere?
GOZU: She may be injured.
Wait a minute.
You don't even
know where to look!
[grunts]
‐Oh, well, no stopping
a man in love.
NARUTO: Ow!
Man, I'm gonna feel
this in the morning.
Wonder how far I was
washed downstream.
Oh, wait!
The kid!
How'd he get mixed up
with Orochimaru's people?
Listen, follow that person
and never let them go.
‐Mm‐hm.
‐‐[gasp] Could it be my fault
he's fallen in with them?
Perfect.
Fog again.
Huh?
Where the hell am I?
Sasuke!
‐Stop interfering, boy.
‐Why, you‐‐ what are
you doing with Sasuke?
OROCHIMARU: [laughs] Beginning
the transference ritual.
‐What do you mean?
OROCHIMARU: That is his wish.
He'll have the power he so
desires, and I will have him.
‐Like hell you will!
We're taking him back to the
Leaf Village, you rotten snake!
‐[laughs] Nonsense.
Returning to that place is
the last thing he wants.
‐Even so, home is
with the people
who care for him, not with you.
Nothing'll ever change that!
‐You really believe
that, do you?
‐Shut your mouth.
‐Forget him, or you'll
come to regret it.
‐I said shut up!
Yaaahhhh!
KAKASHI: Naruto, stop!
‐Huh?
‐Aahhh!
That was close.
‐Kakashi Sensei!
‐Watch it, will you?
I bust my tail looking for you
and that's the thanks I get?
‐But Orochimaru was right here.
‐Are you nuts?
I'd have picked up
his scent by now.
‐I'm guessing this
was an illusion.
‐But‐‐ but it felt‐‐
[dog barks]
‐Huh?
‐You all right, Naruto?
‐Everybody's in one piece.
‐But that doesn't mean
our problems are over.
‐Hm?
SHINO: Look.
‐Wait, they're‐‐
‐Yeah, they're acting strangely.
Something is messing with
their sense of direction.
They'd be useless
for recon right now.
‐Wait, are you serious?
‐Their behavior began to change
as soon as the fog settled in.
‐And Naruto just got
caught inside an illusion.
This is no ordinary mist.
Naruto, what exactly
happened out on that lake?
‐Huh?
Mm.
Well, there was sort of
a giant rampaging turtle.
It was going after
those guys from before.
[gasp]
‐Say what?
A turtle?
What, are you pulling our chain?
You're telling us
a giant turtle's
putting out all that chakra?
(SHOUTING) Aw, shut up!
I'm telling you what I saw, OK?
Something had to cause that
giant wave a minute ago,
didn't it?
And worse, Gamakichi said it was
the Three‐Tails when he saw it.
‐What?
‐Are you sure?
One of the tailed
beasts appeared here?
‐Yeah.
Didn't get a chance to
count the tails, though.
‐Kakashi.
‐I thought we'd figured
out their objective.
This makes things a
little more complicated.
At any rate, we need to make
our way out of this fog.
Then we can hash out what we've
learned and plan our next move.
OROCHIMARU: Well?
‐[gasp]
‐Why didn't you kill her?
[footsteps crunching in snow]
[gasp] [screams]
[thud]
[splurt]
[gasp]
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
What was that?
‐You're all right.
‐Yukimaru.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): That's right,
I was fighting the Three‐Tails.
I must have lost consciousness.
Its power was more
terrible than I imagined.
The others were probably
lost in the swell.
If the Leaf are on
the move, I'd better
find Rinji and the others.
But in this fog‐‐
‐Yukimaru, what happened
to the Three‐Tails?
‐I don't know.
Everything just went
quiet after that.
‐I see.
‐I'm glad, though, that
you finally woke up.
You were moaning the whole time.
I kept saying your name,
but you wouldn't wake up.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Huh.
He was watching over me
the whole time I was out.
‐Well, then, what do you say
we catch up with everyone?
‐Sure.
Although, actually‐
‐What is it?
‐Well, it's strange, really,
but I'm feeling kind of weak.
‐You‐‐ you have a fever.
Since when?
‐Mmph.
[wind howling]
‐Byakugan!
Amazing!
‐What is it?
Do you see something?
‐Yeah.
We should head back.
‐OK.
[wings flap powerfully]
KAKASHI: Well, what's the word?
HINATA: You were right, Sensei.
There's nothing
ordinary about this fog.
The whole bank's teaming
with chakra, a huge amount.
What's more, the entire
lake has been enveloped.
It's everywhere.
‐I suppose our
conclusion was right
that the Three‐Tails
was responsible for it.
‐Looks that way.
And based on
Naruto's account, we
know the fog brings
on illusions.
It might be acting as a barrier.
‐Probably meant to keep us
from the lake, I'll bet.
NARUTO: We gotta do something.
That little kid
is still in there.
‐Huh?
What do you mean?
‐I was telling you about him.
Remember, Sakura?
You know, the guy
I ran into when
I was heading out this way?
‐Yeah, that's right.
‐Oh, that.
I thought you were delusional.
(SHOUTING) Listen,
I'm not an idiot!
I met him before
we even got here.
He's out there, all right?
I know what I saw!
‐On the lake.
‐Please believe
me, Kakashi Sensei.
This kid isn't even a ninja.
I gotta see if he's OK.
‐Sorry, Naruto, but it's
out of the question.
‐Kakashi Sensei!
‐I have no choice.
You were just caught in
the Three‐Tails' illusion,
almost killing one
of your comrades.
I can't allow you
to fly solo anymore.
‐I‐‐ I see what
you're saying, but‐‐
‐Even more importantly,
what are we
going to do about the
mission now, Sensei?
I mean, forget about this mess.
We still need to
figure out where
Orochimaru's hideout is located.
‐I don't know.
The situation is starting to
spin out of control a bit.
It's not really my call anymore.
I've already sent Pakkun
back to the village.
Until we get orders from
Lady Tsunade, we wait.
For now, just steer
clear of the fog
and keep an eye out for the
Three‐Tails or those others.
Got it?
ALL: Got it.
PAKKUN: That's pretty much it.
‐Huh.
The Three‐Tailed
beast disappeared.
No one has seen it since
the last great ninja war.
For it to resurface
again in this form‐‐
‐I'll bet Orochimaru is
cooking up trouble again.
I can smell it.
‐Well, at least the good
news is the Akatsuki
haven't checked the
Three‐Tails off their list yet.
This could turn out to be
a blessing in disguise.
Hopefully we can get
to it before they do.
‐True enough.
But if the members of the
Akatsuki get wind of this,
the beast will likely be
caught up in a tug‐of‐war.
We can't let any of
them lay claim to it.
‐We'll capture it, then?
‐I don't think
it'll be that easy.
But there must be some
kind of precedent for it.
I'll start digging in
the archives in a moment.
‐Right.
‐In the meantime, you can
start mobilizing the squad
members I've laid
out for you there.
‐Right away, milady.
‐[sigh] All done.
‐You were a
tremendous help today.
Thank you so much.
‐Do you really mean it?
‐You bet.
Keep up the good
work, all right?
‐Will do.
[bird chirping]
‐‐[panting] That's‐‐
that's it for me.
I'm out.
‐We've only just begun.
This is where the real
challenge will come.
‐Excellently put, Lee.
[laughs] There's no quitting
in the springtime of youth.
‐That is right!
We must sharpen our
awareness of one another
to better keep each other safe.
We will own our
taijutsu together
and form an unbeatable duo!
[both grunting with effort]
‐You're wearing me out with
all of your showboating,
you lunatic!
Knock it off!
‐Uh, Lee, do you remember
the point of this exercise?
‐[frustrated yell]
It is partner coordination.
Increasing synchronicity
through training‐‐ I think.
‐That's right.
And tell me, how's
it going there?
Would you say you're
in harmony with Tenten?
‐Uh?
LEE (VOICEOVER): She
is breathing hard.
Oh no!
‐I understand, Sensei.
I was focused on the goal
and not on my partner.
‐That‐a‐boy!
That's my student.
You catch on quick.
‐[sigh] Enough is enough.
We've been at this for five
hours straight already.
I can't do it anymore.
‐Well, I still have
energy to spare.
‐Right on, Lee.
As soon as Tenten's
caught her breath,
I'll come at you with
a little taijutsu.
And I'll be coming full
force, so don't you hold back.
‐What?
‐Yes, Guy Sensei.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): [groan]
When's it going to end?
Huh?
Wait a minute, you guys.
Look!
[bird calls]
Lee: Are they calling us in?
GUY: OK, team.
To be continued.
[bird calls]
GUY: Now get going.
Show them the fruits
of your massive amount
of training today.
‐Right!
‐[sigh]
‐And that's pretty
much where things
stand for the time being.
I want you to find
Kakashi and the others
and lend your support.
I'm sure I don't
have to tell you
your most critical objective
is sealing the Three‐Tails.
‐To do it will require extremely
delicate chakra control.
Ino, you'll be a member
of the sealing unit.
Between the two of us,
and Hinata, and Sakura,
we shouldn't have a problem.
‐Right.
Count on me.
‐Tenten and Lee, you'll
be filling the gap
that Hinata and Sakura
will be leaving.
With the Three‐Tails
being in play here,
there's bound to
be a confrontation.
‐Don't worry about a thing.
‐We will fight with the
full power of our youth.
‐I'll lead you back
to their location.
Try to keep up.
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
If I have to keep
nursing the sick like this,
I'm going to collapse myself.
This is the second time I've
had to play nurse for the boy.
If you give him that
much medicine, he'll‐‐
Could those pills be the cause?
In any case, I can't go running
into battle now with him
in tow like this.
[coughing]
‐Hey, Yukimaru, snap out of it.
‐You know, I‐‐ I found a
place where I can return to.
It's with you.
[gasp]
‐Finally, I found it.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Oh,
Naruto, our shift isn't over.
We're still on watch.
‐Hm.
Quit slacking off, will you?
‐Huh?
Hey, Sakura.
I've, uh, been thinking
about something.
‐Huh?
‐But I‐‐ I can't figure
it out on my own.
During Pervy Sage's training,
he used to say something to me.
‐You mean Jiraiya?
‐A place where people
still think about you
is a place you can call home.
‐Has a nice ring to it.
‐Yeah, but I wonder
if it's actually true.
If it is, then all you'd have to
do is keep thinking of someone,
and then they'd come back.
[wind picks up]
You'd think.
But I'm not so sure
about that, either.
All the longing in the world
won't bring some people back.
Sharing your true
feelings with someone,
it's not all that easy, is it?
‐But if you put them out of
your head and give up on them,
there'd be nobody
left to remember them.
It's terrible.
‐That's true.
If you and I give
up, there really
will be no place for
him to return to.
Yep, no matter what
the others say,
we just have to keep
putting our faith in him.
That way there will always be
a place for him to call home.
‐Yeah?
You think so?
‐'Course I do.
‐Yeah, you're right.
Giving up isn't an option.
We just have to hang in there.
Hm, I'm feeling a
whole lot better now.
Thanks, Sakura.
‐Any time.
I guess I'll be heading
back to my position.
The next two‐man team
will swap in for us
in another 30 minutes,
so stay alert, OK?
‐Thanks again, Sakura.
OK, then.
‐So if somebody somewhere is
thinking about me, wherever
that person is is
where I belong.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No
matter what anyone says, just
keep thinking about him.
And if he has no
place to go, then I'll
be the one he can come home to.
[MUSIC ‐ DEV PARADE,
"BACCHIKOI!!!"]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Sakura,
I'm here to relieve you.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Thanks.
Everything's quiet so far.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Um, excuse me.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Sai, your post is over there.
What's up?
SAI (VOICEOVER): Well,
I don't see Naruto.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): What?
Did that idiot head
for camp before someone
could switch with him?
SAI (VOICEOVER): Well,
I‐‐ I'm not sure.
Wouldn't we have crossed paths?
KIBA (VOICEOVER): We're
talking about Naruto here.
He's probably out sleeping.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
Could Naruto have‐‐
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Everyone's Feelings."