Thank you so much for
letting me become a mother.
And thank you for letting
Minato become a father.
Thank you for
being born to us!
Thank you...
...so much.
Thank you.
Mom...
From now on...
I promise that I'll eat my
veggies, and not just ramen.
Don't worry about me bathing.
I like it! I go to the hot
springs a lot, too.
And I'm getting plenty of sleep.
Tons, in fact! I probably sleep
too much, ya know!
As for friends, I have lots of
them! Really good ones, too!
I sure wish that you
could've met them, Mom.
Although, there's one
that I'm not getting
along with right now.
As for my studies...
well, you feared right, Mom.
But I don't get
depressed over that,
ya know!
A lot happened with my
teachers and upperclassmen
when I was in the Academy.
But we respect
each other now.
Master Jiraiya taught
me all about the Three
Shinobi Prohibitions.
He was just like you
described him, Mom!
You sure were right about him!
But, he also taught me how
a shinobi should live!
He was a truly great shinobi.
I am Naruto Uzumaki,
ninja of the Hidden Leaf!
My dream is to
become Hokage!!
And to surpass all of the
Hokage who came before me!
And what's more, to become
an even cooler guy than dad!
And also, To be a
stronger shinobi
than you, Mom!
"Battle in Paradise!
The Odd Beast vs. The Monster!"
[gulp]
Yeah!
Heh!
What happened?
Did you do it?
How did it go?
A lot of this.
A lot of that.
Yo!
Huh?
I can see it! I get it!
And I totally understand!
Your face is calm,
completely bland!
So what about the
Nine Tailed fox?
Were you able to
control it?
All right!
Good for you!
'specially when you used
it in that situation!
Heh ha ha!
Whoa! No way! Don't tell me
that you mean you know what!
Yup!
I sure do!
That's right, ya know!
Listen, would somebody
just explain to me what
happened, already!
Words like "this" and
"that" don't mean anything!
I can tell! You guys're
doing this to me on purpose!
Don't you two try to deny it!
[Guy]
What?!
I had no idea Naruto
was undergoing such
strenuous training!
Well, I can't ignore a man
who's struggling in the
springtime of his youth!
Take me to Naruto
right away!
This man can be a
bit over the top.
So, uh, sorry about that.
No problem.
It's okay. Relax,
Captain Yamato.
I've stored Nine Tails' chakra
inside of me in a place
different from my own chakra.
That way I'm not using
it all the time.
This is how it is when
I tap into the Nine
Tails' chakra that I've
stored away in there.
[Yamato]
Wow! It's so full
of life energy!
Whoa.
It's even affecting
my Wood Style.
I can't believe it!
Huh?
Hmm?
What is it?
You really think...
...that you can
hide from me now?
You mean that... you're sensing
some other chakra here?!
Yeah, he senses
another presence,
that I didn't
was careless of me,
I must do penance.
[Kisame]
Impossible!
My chakra's the
same as Samehada's!
No one should be
able to sense it!
No, it's not chakra!
It feels hazy, but
it's something else,
something sinister,
and it's coming right
from your blade!
His blade?!
Hrh? Huh??
[Kisame]
It appears you can sense hate,
and other negative emotions.
That ability doesn't fit
any known Sensory Type.
It must be a power of a
Jinchuriki who's achieved
control over the Nine Tails.
Hold on! You're the
Akatsuki shark guy!
But how? I thought
we chopped his head
off a while back.
Let's do it.
Okay, my Brother.
Water Style! Super Shark Bomb!
[Raikage & Bee]
Double Lariat!
So how in the world did
you evade me and my
brother's tag-team attack?
It was quite simple! I merely
switched places while we battled
inside the bubble of water.
It's ink.
A smokescreen, huh?
He really is an octopus lout.
However...
With my body merged to
Samehada like this, I can
detect chakra through my skin.
You only cut off the
head of my clone.
[White Zetsu]
Don't you think
you're overdoing it?
No, I used just the
right amount of force
for the Eight-Tails.
All right.
Well, I guess
it's my turn now.
Yes. The rest is
in your hands.
But clones simply
disappear when you
hit 'em hard enough!
And the corpse still remained
post-mortem, no question.
If someone else had transformed
into you, then my buddy Cee
would have sensed it for sure.
A perplexing
consternation.
It was a very special
kind of clone.
A Parasitic Clone that
can be operated remotely
by the caster.
Well, we'll leave
it at that for now.
But this situation.
To be facing two Jinchuriki
and a Wood Style user.
That's tough, even for me.
No way! How'd you ever
figure out the way to open
the door to this room?
Now that's a silly question!
After all, I did come here
to act as a spy, you know.
[gasp]
Uwaagh!
Teleportation Jutsu?
First up at bat, the
first smash, just like
the Yellow Flash!
Grrh!
So fast.
Unbelievable!
[wet cough]
Uh?
Huh?!
Agh! My leg!
I hit the wall too hard!
Now I'm stuck here!
Looks like, he doesn't have
Lord Fourth's skills yet.
Please, go after the
spy, Master Bee!
I'll help Naruto.
Right!
Just leave the chase to me,
and I'll catch him in a jiffy.
Auggh! Damn it!
[Guy]
What? Your true self appears
inside that waterfall when
you meditate here?
Is that
for real?
Yes.
And Naruto also
faced and defeated
his true self here.
Well, Guy? Why
don't you try it
out for yourself?
Don't be foolish!
We have to go help
Naruto first!
That's much
more important!
I came here as his
mentor, to try to
protect him!
All right, You don't
have to get so upset,
you know.
or are you just too afraid to
step up to that waterfall and
face your true self, Guy.?
Well, are you?
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
What?!
Do you really believe
that I'm scared?!
No problem!
Oh, no, I was
only joking!
Although I have a
feeling that your true
self isn't even human!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Lighten up!
You're so serious!
[gasp]
Honestly, you really
shouldn't be going on about
"youth" so much, should you?
A man past his prime like you
will get hurt if he overdoes it!
I know that you have to keep
up appearances for Lee's sake.
But face it: you can't
keep yourself young just
by wishing it so, old man.
Come out! Show yourself!
Don't just hide and say
what you want!
Very well, then.
Know thy true self.
What?! That weird thing is
supposed to be my true self?
An Odd Insect?
Isn't that that Odd Beast?!
What?!
[gasp]
Seems I've forgotten
what springtime is.
I'll remind myself
by defeating you!
No, Guy!
That isn't your true self!
No! Watch out!
Leaf Rock
Crushing Square!
Yagh!
Graagh!
Huh?
What do you mean,
that wasn't my true self?
Go on and take a good look!
That is clearly not you!
The moment you open your
eyes, you leave the
Waterfall of Truth!
Huh, You know, actually,
Isn't that...?!
Nngh...
Grr...
Ohh!
It is!
It's a puffer fish!
No, wait, maybe it was
called a porcupine fish?
Well, there sure are a
bunch of strange
creatures living here, so
I guess that it could be.
Is that really a puffer
fish? They're supposed
to be super tasty.
Are all of you
deliberately pretending
to be idiots?!
I see that you haven't
changed one bit!
you're still dumber
than a beast.
This guy's an Akatsuki spy!
So, If he gets away, they'll
have Intel. Shameful, oh my!
Hrrh?
Damn you Samehada!
He's that shark man!
He was the one teamed
up with Itachi in the
Akatsuki!
He appears to
be weakened.
How did he even
get here?!
Yes, I see, I see;
he forced you.
Boy, that must've
been awfully rough
for you, huh?
Man, that thing's
really creepy.
Hrrgh!
[chuckle] Hey, now!
Your affection is a bit rough.
But what can I say?
I'm popular, life's tough!
[Aoba]
Oh, no! He's escaped
into the water!
And he's a Water
Style user!
Yes, I know!
Bee! Watch out!
He's stealing
your chakra!
Huh?
Why is it always that the
stronger they are, the
denser they are, as well?!
Ugh!
Hmm...
Huh?
Cut it out stat! But you're
so cute that I'm getting
weak in the kneecaps.
[weary]
Ohhhh...
Ah! Guy, quickly now,
please back me up!
I'll take Intel
from him instead!
Hidden Jutsu!
Stone Needles!
Got him!
A jutsu where the caster sends
his chakra to paralyze the
target, huh? Perfect!
Agh!
No! He's draining
my chakra instead!
Ohhh!
So much pull!
Leaf Hurricane!
Huaah!
My chakra is completely
recharged now!
Water Style!
Shark Bomb Jutsu!
Huagh!
Whoa!
Damn it,
he's getting away!
He's fast! If he gets past the
island's barrier, it's over!
We've got to stop him
before then or even I won't
be able to sense him!
Don't worry,
I'll stop him!
Watch!
Huaagh!
Eight Inner Gates!
Sixth Gate of Joy: Open!
Hm?
Haaghh!
Come on, noble beast, just
hop onto my hand, and then,
I'll toss you after him, in
the clock direction of ten!
Don't sacrifice
the truth just
for a rhyme!
He went towards two o'clock!
Okay!
Whee!
[woozy]
Aaahh...
Lord Bee!
Are you all right?!
I'm okay.
I'll bounce back
right away.
I really doubt it.
You've had too much
chakra stolen from you.
But we may be able to stop
him before it's too late.
Naruto and Yamato are behind
this waterfall, aren't they?
[Naruto]
Dagh!
Agh, I twisted my ankle.
You have to be careful
about keeping your
power under control!
All right.
Let's go, then!
Hm!
[gasp]
I'm counting on you!
I don't see you
forever, and then you
summon me in midair?!
I need to borrow your back!
Huagh!
Yaahhhh!
Aiiyaaghh!
Damn it, Guy!
I'm not just a
stepping-stone!
Huh?
Oh! Hello, there!
Good. Looks like I managed
to give them the slip.
Summoning Jutsu!
Hmm?
My, aren't you the
persistent one.
So the scroll you gave to
that shark contains the
Intel you gathered, does it?
I won't let it get away!
I wouldn't be so sure.
I have the topographical
advantage.
Water Style!
Thousand Hungry Sharks!
Augh!
I can't tell which
shark it is anymore!
In which case!
Hyaaaahhh!
Asakujaku!
Where's the scroll?
Damn it. Still too many!
It can't be helped.
I've got to expand
the blast radius!
Won't let the sharks
in the water get by,
either, huh?
Very well. Then I'll just
let them all tear you apart!
Seventh Gate of Shock! Open!
Ah, yes, I see.
Your fist moves so fast the
friction causes flames to erupt.
A taijutsu that destroys
opponents with fire and the
shock wave of punched air.
You really are a beast.
A shinobi this skilled
in taijutsu is rare.
Although I have known
two other ones.
This next taijutsu is far
beyond even my last move!
It's a special
single-blow attack.
Hardly anyone has
ever seen it.
It's impressive that
your blue chakra is
pushing the water away.
Water Style!
Super Shark Bomb Jutsu!
[clap]
Hirudora!
[growl]
Hyaaaah!
Hwaaah!
This Super Shark Bomb
is no ordinary jutsu.
It starts out strong
and gets even stronger
by absorbing chakra.
So the stronger my opponent is,
the stronger it gets.
Wait, what's going
on?! I know the jutsu's
absorbed his chakra.
But it's not
getting stronger!
I'm certain that I
absorbed his chakra.
Was that not a
chakra Energy Bomb?!
Now my youth, roar!
Yeaaggghhhh!
[Kisame]
In the Hidden Mist, there
is a great obstacle
one must overcome
to be considered
a true shinobi.
It really is
indescribable, isn't it?
Killing your comrades is
quite a sensation,
wouldn't you say so, Itachi?
There is only one thing that is
clear to me: that I felt I was
trapped in a false existence.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Man Named Kisame.
[Kisame]
This world really is
full of lies.