Rgh!
Why am I so different!?
Why am I always... Argh!
[wet stab]
I will never back down again
and let someone else rescue me.
I'll never run away.
Upon this wound,
I make this pledge!
[Naruto]
Damn it... Ahhg.
Look at you.
you're hopeless,
Naruto!
Hmph. You really are
just one big problem.
Rrgh!
Hey!
Sasuke! What
did you say?!
Augh!
Keep this up,
I'll finish you off myself!
Gah! But,
Sakura!
Hmph.
[sigh] Guess we're not
making a lot of progress on
the teamwork thing, huh?
That's right,
our teamwork's
all messed up,
and it's all because
of you, Sasuke!
You think you're
better than
everyone else?
Not everyone,
just you.
Listen, if you really don't
want to owe me anything,
Then just become
stronger than me.
Nh!
[seething]
[Naruto]
[frustrated punching]
Damn it!
[panting]
Just watch!
I'm gonna make that
stuck-up jerk admit that
I'm a worthy rival!
And I won't stop
till he does!
I'm gonna catch up
to him in no time!
And then I'm gonna become
even stronger than he is!
Whoaa!
[crash]
Hey, keep it down!
Do you know what
time it is?!
[Naruto]
Uhh! Um!
Sorry about that!
Now, I'll explain what
you'll be doing on this test.
It's in this confined
area that you'll undergo
the survival test.
The test consists of,
An anything-goes battle to get
your hands on these scrolls.
All together, twenty-six
teams will be taking
part in this test.
So half of those teams...
will be going after
the Heaven Scroll.
And the other half
will be trying to get
the Earth Scroll.
I'll hand over one kind
of scroll to each team.
And that's what
you'll be vying for.
Your entire squad must
bring both a Heaven and
Earth Scroll to the tower.
[gulp]
I get it. So none
of us can drop out,
even if we wanted to.
This is gonna be one serious
test of our teamwork as a
three-man squad.
And this is gonna be the
day that I pay Sasuke back!
Well, all right!
Here we go, guys!
[panting]
[Sasuke]
That wound's deep!
Will you be all right--
Got to move!
Got to get way from her!
But how?
Where?!
Man, I've never seen Sasuke
like this. He's got me scared.
[gasp] Sasuke,
watch out!
Unbelievable, I
didn't even notice!
I'm losing it!
Aiiyahh! No! Stay awaay!
[panting]
Huh?
I sense your fear
and desperation.
It's only natural. The prey
must never let down its
guard, not even for a moment,
in the presence
of its predator.
[gasp]
[Naruto]
Looks like I came
just in time!
What was that
password again?
[chuckle]
[Sasuke]
Naruto!
Get out of here!
What are you thinking?
You don't know what
you're up against!
He doesn't get it. He doesn't
know what he's dealing with.
What do I do?
It's no use. There's
only one way.
You do want the
scroll, don't you?
All right then. Take it,
and leave us in peace.
Huh?! Are you serious?!
We're gonna just hand
the scroll over to
the enemy?! No way!
What's wrong
with you?
Very wise.
Sometimes the helpless
prey, to survive,
Realize that they must
distract the predator with
something a bit more precious.
Take it.
Huh??
Stop being the
hero, Naruto!
Just stay out of this
and leave it to me!
Rrrgh!
You're a stupid fool!
You don't know
what you're doing!
I may not know the password,
but I know who I am!
You're the one I'm
not so sure about.
How are we supposed to
believe that you're really
who you say you are!
What sort of nonsense is this?
It's me, you loser!
Liar! You may look
just like him,
But there's no way you're
the Sasuke I know!
I don't care how tough a
fight you've been through.
Surrendering?
Giving up the scroll?
When did Sasuke
become a coward?!
You keep saying I don't
understand what's going
on, but I do.
You've choked,
that's what it is!
[chuckle]
Sad.
But it's true.
[gasp]
It doesn't matter.
I could simply kill
you and take it.
Ahh, let's see you try it!
Don't! Naruto, no!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto!
Ahh!
Agh!
Ahh ha ha. Enough playing.
Finish him off.
Yeah?!
Eat this!
Is that Naruto??
But how?
It's impossible.
Daagh!
Unhf!
It seems that things have
gotten very interesting.
Let's see how you do, Sasuke!
Ah!
Hey kid, you're
not hurt, are ya?
You scaredy-cat!
Naruto..!
Hey, kid...
You're not hurt are you?
Little girl!
Standing there frozen
like a frightened rabbit.
No way, you're not
the Sasuke I know!
All I cared about was surviving,
in order to defeat my brother.
What a fool I've been!
I see the truth now.
If I haven't the courage
to face this demon,
how can I ever
hope to face him?
For crying out loud!
Sakura!
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
It would seem we've
been spotted.
Somebody is playing
games with us.
[Sasuke]
Well, Naruto?
You wanted
a fight.
Four against forty.
I like those odds.
Clones, from the look of it.
And a whole lot of them.
Heh heh heh heh heh.
Like cornered rats.
cornered rats,
are we?!
Huh??
Agh. What are they?
What's really going on here?
Sharingan!
Naruto!
Sasuke!
Ah! Down!
Rrrgh!
Come and get it!
It's no use!
You'll only be
fighting illusions.
Huh??
It's Genjutsu,
all right.
That gash
on Kabuto's
arm is real
enough.
That's true. But still,
Sasuke's right.
Could be the real
enemy's in hiding.
Launching real attacks from
behind a smokescreen of
illusions, and coordinating
their movements with them,
so that we're fooled
into thinking these
"Genjutsu Shinobi" are
the ones attacking us.
Well what are we gonna do,
just stand here?
Let's go find these clowns
and take care of 'em!
Just hold on, Naruto.
They'd like nothing more
than for us to go searching
blindly for them.
U-Uhh!
All that we can do
is hold our ground
and fight them off.
But if we get rid of them,
if we take out all the
illusions at once,
When the caster throws their
kunai, then we'll be able to
see where they're hiding.
I'll show 'em two can
play at this game.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Huh? Shadow Clones!
Raaaagh!!
[fighting]
Yaahhh!
[panting]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
We've crushed their spirits.
Now all that's left
is their bodies.
Lucky us.
You. I know you.
You're the one who cut
me on the shoulder.
Oh well, now I can finally
pay you back, with interest.
Hrrm.
Huh??
[Sasuke]
Now who's the cornered rat?
Huh??
Worked like
a charm,
Naruto!
What?! It can't be!
If they're over there,
then who are they?
Are you
confused?
Sorry, it was was
the only way to get
you to come out.
Don't tell me that
little brat--!
It's not possible!
The Shadow Clones
were only the
first part of it.
My real trick was coming
up with clones for the
rest of my squad.
While our doubles did
all the fighting and
took the beating,
we were safe and
sound, waiting for
you to show yourself.
What do you think, guys?
I think our little plan worked.
Now, it's our turn!
Egh! Unh!
Huh??
Naruto, take a break for now;
you've used up too much Chakra.
Don't worry. I've got 'em.
After all the work I just did,
I'm not gonna let you guys
have all the fun!
Whoa. Is this
the same Naruto?
To be able to pull off a Multi
Shadow Clone jutsu, transform
three of them into clones of us,
and still come out fighting.
And on top of that,
to do all of this
on the fifth day.
[Anko]
First of all, congratulations
on finishing the second exam.
Alright, now pay attention!
Lord Hokage is going to
explain the third exam to you!
What happened? When
did he get this good?
Without him, we wouldn't
have made it out of the
Forest of Death.
I can't just dismiss
him anymore.
Sasuke,
quit now before--
Huh?
Please.
I'm scared.
Come on, you know as well as
I do you're in no condition
to keep on fighting,
Shut up, Sakura!
You think I'm blind
or something?
You think I don't see the
suffering you're going through?
This has nothing
to do with you.
Listen, Sakura.
I already told you all
of this once before.
I am an avenger.
For me, this is something
far more than just an exam.
Whether I become a Chunin or not
means less than nothing to me.
"Am I as strong as I can be?"
I can only find out by
fighting the strongest.
The best.
And the best of the
best are all here.
This is my path,
and neither you nor anyone
else can change that.
Man, you don't
know when to quit!
What're you biting her
head off, for, you idiot?
It's just 'cuz she
cares about ya!
Naruto.
Huh?
You're one of the ones I
want to fight the most.
Huh??
Huh?
[Sasuke]
What's up?
Heh. So you finally showed up.
Kakashi Sensei!
I want your help.
I need to get stronger!
[Kakashi]
Hmm. This determination
of Sasuke's.
He's dead serious.
It's Naruto. He became
so strong so fast!
I just can't waste
any more time.
I see, so that's it. He finally
took notice of the immense power
that Naruto has at his disposal.
I have a goal, and to
achieve it, I need to
have more power.
Okay.
Well, Sasuke, you know
about the five types of
chakra and about Change
in Chakra Nature, right?
Yeah.
Members of the Uchiha Clan
most often possess Fire Nature
and specialize in Fire Style.
I already know that.
What's this about?
Some shinobi are able to
affect more than one
Change in Chakra Nature.
My Chakra Nature is lightning.
Sasuke, For a long time now,
I've had a suspicion that
you may be similar to me.
First, I'd like to
verify what your
Chakra Nature is.
Looks like I may be able to pass
my jutsu on to you after all.
The unique jutsu,
of Kakashi the Copy Ninja.
[angry crowd, boos and hissing]
- Come on!! Boo!
- What's going on??
- We've been waiting all day!
Dagh! What could
he be doing at a
time like this?!
Where is that
idiot, Huh?!
Hm?
Whoaa!
Sorry we're late.
We hit a ton
of traffic.
And you are?
I'm Sasuke Uchiha.
Sasuke!
Huh, so you decided
to show up after all.
I was betting you wouldn't come,
'cuz you knew sooner or later
you'd have to face me.
Well, don't get too
full of yourself.
You're still a loser.
Anyway, what
about you,
Naruto?
Tell me.
Did you win?
You know it!
Sorry if we kept you waiting.
But, um, how late are we?
I mean, it's not like
Sasuke's, well, disqualified
or anything, right?
You know, you were so
late that we extended
the deadline for you.
No, he's not disqualified.
Oh, ho ho. That's a relief.
Listen Sasuke,
don't lose to him.
Got it.
You're one of the ones I
want to fight the most.
Don't lose. 'cuz I want
to fight you myself.
Got it.
[Sasuke]
I had no idea. I didn't
know Naruto fought
Orochimaru and the others.
Or that he learned a new jutsu.
Or that somehow, he's
gotten even stronger.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Rift. The rivalry between Sasuke
and me continues to grow.
[Sasuke]
Naruto. Come on, fight me!