-These tracks, it's not them.
-I see.
Then let's move.
-Hm?
-Huh?
Bandits!
-You shouldn't be
out here, old timers.
Didn't you get the emergency
bulletin from the Land of Fire
about the temporary curfew?
-Yes, but well, we
thought we might
be of some use in
the fighting ahead.
-Yeah, you won't
see us two getting
into whippersnappers
on our land.
-Hmph.
-That was scary.
-Yeah.
[theme music]
-Milady, I have an update.
We've sent 20 platoons to form
a perimeter around the Fire
Temple with a 150
kilometer radius.
Even an ant couldn't
get past us.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
We have received a report
from third platoon.
Border areas C and E are clear.
No sign of the Akatsuki.
-Then where are they?
-New report has come in.
Areas F and G, all clear, ma'am.
We still haven't
found the Akatsuki.
-I can see that.
Why can't we find them?
Have we heard from Team
Asuma at the Fire Temple?
-No, Milady.
Nothing reported yet.
-Ugh.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Chiriku.
-What's this all about?
-You've come from the
Leaf Village, correct?
-Yes.
-I see.
We were contacted by the monk
who has been in your care.
-Greetings to you all.
I am the head monk in
charge of the Fire Temple.
I had been away from the
temple for quite some time.
But when I heard
what had happened,
I rushed back as
quickly as I could.
It was a terrible sight indeed.
We asked neighboring temples
for help recovering the remains.
-This is awful.
-Excuse me, sir.
Where's Chiriku?
-Well, actually, we've been unable
to find Lord Chiriku's remains.
IZUMO: Um, Captain Asuma.
Well, sir, as much as I
hate to bring this up,
Chiriku does still have a 30
million ryo bounty on his head
on the black market.
-30 million ryo?
That's quite a large bounty.
If the Akatsuki knew,
they'd try to collect.
So that means the enemy
is carrying his body along
with them.
-Izumo, where are the
collection offices?
-Including the
one closest to us,
there are five
locations in total.
Now the other teams can head
to the exchange points closest
to them.
-All right, let's hurry.
-Please wait a moment,
Lord Asuma Sarutobi.
-Hm?
-For those of you who are
about to enter a fight,
allow me a moment to
offer you a prayer.
Please.
-It would be an honor.
[prayer chant]
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Chiriku.
-Oh.
I'm the only member of
the Guardian Shinobi
Twelve left now.
I wish we could
have shared just one
more of our all-night talks.
There were still so many things
I wanted to talk to you about.
Things I wanted you to hear.
-Please be safe on your journey.
-We cannot thank you enough.
And sir, we'll do our
best to find Chiriku.
-Please don't push things
too far in your quest.
As a former member of the
Guardian Shinobi Twelve,
you have a bounty on your
head, just like Chiriku.
Please be careful.
-Well thank you, but you have
no need to worry about me, sir.
You know the bounty on my head?
It's 5 million more
than his for a reason.
-Hmph.
Yeah, the only thing to
worry about with Asuma
is that he smokes too much.
-Hey, what happened
with the training?
I went to all that trouble
making more food pills.
SAI: Nobody's here, huh?
-Oh, Sai.
Let me guess, you came to
check in on Naruto like I did.
-No, I was just
taking a brisk walk
to make sure I didn't get out
of shape because of my injury.
I take that back.
Actually, you were
absolutely right.
-Mhm, see, it's
good to be honest.
-Naruto's training,
was it postponed?
-Well, he probably went
off somewhere to refocus.
His body and mind can't keep
up such intense training
without taking a
break now and then.
NARUTO: Ramen.
Ichiraku Ramen.
-Yeah, yeah, I hear you.
Keep going.
We're almost there.
-Hey, I've got an idea.
While we're here, why don't you
give one of these babies a try?
-What is that?
A mudball?
-Don't be rude.
No.
This is one of my
homemade food pills.
It's super special.
-Special, huh?
-You know, I suppose it's more
like medicine than a food pill.
It's chock full of all kinds
of nutritious goodness mixed
with a bunch of fast-acting
digestive agents.
All of which were
hand-picked by yours truly
and rolled up into a convenient
ball packed with energy.
In fact, in addition
to helping you recover,
I'd venture to say
the pill might even
add some healthy color to that
pale, sickly skin of yours.
They say the best
medicine is always bitter.
So the food pills might
taste a little strange.
But when you consider the
benefits of taking them,
tiny details like flavor
will be of no-- hm?
Sai?
Hm?
-I feel dizzy.
That stuff tastes and smells so
bad, there's no way it'll work.
In fact, it's making me sick.
NARUTO: Pork ramen.
-See, Naruto?
We're here.
Hello?
-Welcome, customers!
-Uh, hi.
-Listen, old man.
Extra large pork
miso with extra pork.
On the double.
WAITRESS: We have a new menu.
Take a look.
-That's great.
But I still want an extra
large pork miso with meat,
noodles al dente.
-Hey, come on.
You didn't even
look at the menu.
-Give it a look see, Naruto.
As of today, we've made
some pretty big changes
to the lineup.
-That's right.
We serve dipping noodles.
-Oh, wow.
I'm sticking with extra
large pork miso with meat.
And go ahead and throw in
some pickled red ginger.
-Would you listen?
We don't serve ramen
here any longer.
-Huh?
-Wait a second.
So this is a dipping
noodle shop now?
-See, my daughter
Ayame went off to get
some professional training
as a noodle maker.
She came home and said,
(HIGH-PITCHED VOICE) dad,
the age of dipping
noodles has arrived.
We need to take Ichiraku in
a new culinary direction.
Yep.
Now my girl's got all kinds
of fancy business knowledge.
-The customers'
likes and dislikes
are constantly evolving.
If Ichiraku doesn't change too,
we'll fall behind the times.
-See?
Ha ha.
-What the hell are
you talking about?
All I wanted was a simple
pork miso and meat.
-It'll be fine.
Dipping noodles are pretty
much the same as ramen.
-No they're not.
Dipping noodles are served
separate from the broth.
You dip and eat, like soba.
-Well, it all goes
to the same place.
-The concept is
totally different.
-He's absolutely right.
Ramen's not the same
as dipping noodles.
And I really want ramen,
so let's get it going, huh?
-We've only prepared
dipping noodles.
So I'm sorry.
-Oh, come on.
Switching back to
ramen would just
be tweaking the soup
a little, right?
-You'd be satisfied with
phony ramen like that?
I thought you of all
people would have standards
for quality pork
miso and meat ramen.
-No, it's not like that.
I'm just really--
[stomach growls]
This food talk
makes me so hungry.
I-- I don't care anymore.
We'll take the dipping noodles.
-Three orders of
dipping noodles.
-Right, three orders coming up.
Here you go.
Fresh out of the pot.
-All right.
Finally.
AYAME: Just a minute.
-Huh?
-The noodles are
a tad undercooked.
They need to boil
for one more minute.
-They do?
-And check the
water temperature.
-OK.
-Wait, you're going to
make them over again?
-Orders up.
Ichiraku dipping noodles.
-All right. Huh?
Where's the soup?
-It's a bit too strong.
The product in Yugao
Village was slightly more
on the refreshing side.
Start it over again.
-Right away.
-Hey.
-In that first bite,
we must make our mark
on the customer with perfection.
-That's the spirit, Ayame.
Show me the results
of your training.
-Oh, so hungry.
-Here you go.
Ichiraku's very own
dipping noodles.
And this time, it's perfect.
-Well, it's about time.
Old man, can I get some pork
slices, and pickled bamboo
shoots, and some
fish cake toppings?
Please?
-Uh, sure, I suppose.
-Heh.
-What are you doing?
-Ha ha!
If I eat it like
this, it's ramen.
-That's quality dipping noodles.
You can't do that.
-No, Ayame.
Somehow you have forgotten the
most basic guiding principle
for a restaurateur.
You're getting caught
up in the small details.
But what's most important is
that the customer is satisfied,
right?
-That's why I put
my heart and soul
into making these
dipping noodles.
It's the restaurant's
responsibility
to advise the customer, to
act as their culinary guide,
making sure they experience
only the finest of ingredients
and modern methods
of preparation.
-But I want to eat ramen,
and you won't let me!
-Save your yelling for after
you've sampled our noodles!
You'll see.
And you'll never selfishly
ask for ramen again!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
That was delicious.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Huh, dipping
noodles are lighter than ramen.
I think I actually
might prefer it.
TEUCHI (VOICEOVER):
Maybe I'm getting old.
My shoulders get
really stiff when
I do something I'm not used to.
I know, I'll hire some energetic
youngster to work part-time.
-Ah, at the end of
the day, anything
tastes delicious when
you're hungry enough.
Thanks for the
dipping noodle ramen.
My belly is full.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Even
though he complained about it,
he drank every drop of that
heavy dipping noodle soup.
-I may not agree with
how he ate our cuisine.
But he did wolf
down three bowls,
so I guess I should be proud.
-All right.
Let's get back to the
training, right fellas?
-Not yet.
Before we do, Naruto,
I want to show
you something very interesting.
-What did you have in mind?
-After eating all that
food, you should rest.
I'll explain everything then.
-Ah great.
More complicated explanations.
-It'll be fine.
You know I can
sweet talk anyone.
I promise, it'll be interesting.
-Thank you, and
here is your bill.
-Yamato, you've got this, right?
-Who, me?
Shouldn't the most senior member
be the one to take care of it?
-There's no rank
distinction when
it comes to mutual respect.
Besides, you're
probably my only junior
I acknowledge as a true equal.
But you're right.
If you want me to pay, I will.
[cash register ding]
TEUCHI: Thanks again.
YAMATO: And uh, keep the change.
-You can really sweet
talk, Kakashi-sensei.
-I'm really getting sick of how
lousy you are at conversation.
You know, an otherwise
pleasant trip
can be completely
ruined if you get
stuck traveling with
some boring companion.
-We're not exactly on
a vacation here, Hidan.
-I've also had enough of
searching for Jinchuriki when
we don't have a clue
where they might be.
Put yourself in my position.
I've been forced to go along
with all this extra work.
A little sympathy would be nice.
-Just shut up and keep walking.
We're late.
-Huh?
We're only late because we
have to stop at that collection
office or whatever it is.
For crying out loud, you're make
this tedious trip even longer.
I'm telling you, it's
getting really annoying.
Huh?
-This is annoying?
This is part of an
important mission.
-Whatever.
I know you're in
charge of making money
for the Organization.
But this bounty?
It's a pittance, barely
enough to cover the after
party for a tailed beast hunt.
Huh?
Hey, wait up.
I'm sorry.
That body must be
pretty heavy, right?
I don't mind
carrying it for you.
-And what do you plan to
do with my valuable bounty?
-What?
Hey, I was only trying
to be nice here.
-You want to discard it.
-What are you talking about?
-Don't play dumb.
I can see through you.
You would rather get rid
of this body, wouldn't you?
-All right, you got me.
Let's forget that guy and
get to the Jinchuriki.
See that?
I finally made you mad.
-You damn bastard.
-Hey, come on.
What?
No fight then?
-I don't have time to spend on
your pointless distractions.
And besides, after
this mission, I'll
be sending you to
the next world,
so I won't have to listen
to you in this one anymore.
-Ah, not that again.
Man, I sure hope whoever
our next opponent
is, they have
enough fight in them
so I can finally
let off some steam.
-Well, sensei, what was this
thing you had to show me?
-This is what I
wanted to show you.
It's very cool.
Watch this.
-Wait, is that-- Ra-- Rasengan?
Kakashi-sensei, you
can use Rasengan too?
-Hmph.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
the Rasengan is an
incomplete jutsu.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Adding
a change in chakra nature
to the Rasengan
is something even
the Fourth Hokage
couldn't accomplish.
In other words, whatever
comes next, I can't teach you.
You'll have to discover
it for yourself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No way.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, do you
understand why I'm
telling you this?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Why?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
It's because I believe
that you are the
only shinobi who
can surpass the Fourth Hokage.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- The Next Step.