Man, that sure was
a relief!
You certainly took long
enough. Naruto's gotten
way ahead of us now!
Look, I couldn't hold it
in any longer. Don't go
losing your composure!
But now i'm feeling good
and dandy. My rhymes are
sweet like cotton candy!
So don't worry, be happy!
Instead of wasting time
on your silly rap, let's
catch up to Naruto!
Lord Bee!
[grunt]
I've finally caught
up with you!
Yo! What's on your
mind, Brother Motoi?
Lord Raikage ordered
me to come here.
I'm supposed to assist you
in any way I can.
Great! Thank you,
Brother Motoi.
Hey, how come your
hand is all wet, Bee?
Not to be gruff, but
don't sweat the
small stuff.
By the way,
where is Naruto?
Well, I was off a-pissin'
and he went a-missin'.
He's beyond our
reach at this
juncture.
Man, it's hard being
a young kid's teacher.
I see. So he
went on ahead.
Wait, pissing?!
Hold up! Master
Bee, wait for me!
That's the Eight Tails!
He's really come this
far already?
I guess that we'd
better try to delay him.
[hum of approval]
It seems Bee and
Naruto are getting
closer.
I was told to leave
Naruto alone. However,
not Eight Tails.
I can't wait to conduct
Lord Orochimaru's tests
on him!
Bee, I'm going to
prepare the perfect
reanimation for you.
This will be so much fun.
Lord Bee, seriously, why
was your hand wet?
Now come on! Don't
make a big deal out
of nothing, Brother.
That's the thing, it
wasn't nothing!
[startled gasps]
[loud shouting]
Damn it! It's
the enemy!
What was that
all about?
[gasp]
No way, could
that be...?
Huh?!
Wait, he's...
You're the Eight Tails'
former Jinchuriki...
Fukai!
It certainly has
been a while, Bee.
And you are...Motoi, right?
Yes, but why
are you here?
Because someone used
the Reanimation Jutsu
on me.
Listen, Fukai...
That day thirty years
ago, I mean the day
that you died...
...We tried to stop
the Eight Tails' rampage,
and eight shinobi lost
their lives.
Among them, was
my father.
I see. I'm
very sorry.
But I know apologies
won't bring him back.
He's definitely Fukai.
But why?
No matter how hard I try,
I can't remember much
about that rampage back then.
Bee, this chakra that
I'm sensing from you...
Ah, so you did
become a Jinchuriki.
[snoring]
He'll probably be
next, the Jinchuriki
of the Eight
Tails after me.
Have you heard for sure
if that's going to be
the elders' decision?
No. No one's
said anything.
Both my old man and
my uncle failed.
And I'm not
compatible either.
Listen, as your
cousin I think-
Oh, come on. You've
kept the Eight Tails
under control up until
this point, so.
Just, listen to me!
Only a Jinchuriki would
understand. Even your close
friends look at you differently
after the process.
Well...They might
believe that they're
treating you the same...
But still they
aren't, not really.
You can never look back,
only toward the future.
But that future is filled
with darkness and loneliness.
Have you achieved
compatibility, if you've
walked through life with
the shadow of your death?
It fills your whole mind
day in and day out until you
become so consumed you don't
know who or what you are.
It feels like someone
made a hole in your heart.
And the Tailed Beast
constantly waits to pounce
on that weakened heart,
and run a muck.
And you live with
the constant fear of death.
You'd soon rather just die.
But, still...
You have a knack for
ninjutsu as well as skill,
ancestry, virtue-everything!
True. That's the exact
reasoning that they used when
they chose me to become
the Eight Tails Jinchuriki
But...To be honest,
none of those things
are necessary to be
a Jinchuriki.
Oh? So what is, then?
Having something
that can fill that
hole in your heart.
And, what is it?
That something?
It can be anything.
You'll know it when
you find it.
Because it will keep
you strong.
So, make sure
that Bee finds it.
Bee! I can't control
my own body anymore.
So run!
But check it, if the Eight
Tails isn't inside you
anymore, then you can't fight
like you did before.
You're wrong!
[shocked reaction]
Alright now, Fukai. Why don't
you show the two of them
that you mean business?
Bee! Motoi! Get away!
No way! He has a
Tailed Beast Cloak!
His chakra...It's
unmistakably mine!
When did he...?!
What's going on here?!
But how?! Eight Tails'
Chakra in a Reanimation...?
You're witnessing one
of my finest secret
weapons.
Lord Orochimaru's
laboratory was full of
interesting things like this.
Of all the places,,,
I have something
very precious hidden
away in here.
Is that...?
The horn from Eight Tails.
Eight Tails?!
Once I obtained some of the
Eight Tails' cells, I was
finally able to grow this
after many years.
When were you able
to produce this?!
Long before you were born.
What I had to go
through to obtain this!
But now that I have it, all
sorts of experiments become
possible for me.
[low growling]
That Kabuto!
If he can revive something
like this with the Reanimation
Jutsu, why would he bother
capturing the Eight Tails?
He could've just sealed
this chakra inside the
Gedo Statue!
Dodge this, Bee!
[growling]
Damn it! Bee,
get away!
[painful cries]
No! He's caught us in
his attack, too!
[growling]
Nice, Samehada. All right!
Now that's some appetite!
He ate the chakra
of the Tailed Beast Bomb?!
Now it's my turn to
make an appearance!
You're going to take him
on in Eight Tails State?!
[battle cry]
Lariat!
[grunt]
All this force from
just that one collision!
Why do you still
possess my chakra?!
When you died, I
extracted myself
from you entirely!
It's been a while, Eight
Tails. To think we would
reunite in this situation...
I'm disappointed, too.
I had very high hopes
for you.
The both of us were
completely fooled
back then.
By whom?
Thirty years ago...
[startled breath]
Oh, Ay.
You should be more
careful how you
approach me.
What's the matter?
Trouble sleeping?
That's right.
Especially during
a full moon.
It's like...the
immense hole in
my heart.
So you still haven't
found the something
that you need to fill
it, then?
I doubt I ever will.
Even if I'm still
physically here...
my heart is dead.
I wander the
desert alone.
Besides, if I can't ever
leave here, I'll never
find it.
Is there anything that
I can do for you?
My heart is completely
immersed in the darkness
now.
But when the time
comes...I'm counting
on you, Ay.
[curious reaction]
Alright, this
should do it.
But, these aren't
the usual ones,
They're new. I think
that they'll help
you sleep even better.
I see. Thank you.
I will fill that
gaping hole in
your heart.
[muffled sounds]
It's useless.
The medication that
you took...was
really my special
genjutsu pill.
Why you...!
Life is difficult
for you, right?
Well, then I shall liberate
you from the pain and
suffering of being
a Jinchuriki!
And I'll guide you
back from the land
of the dead.
[yelling in pain]
All right, it's time now
Eight Tails! Come out!
[painfully screaming]
Back off,
accursed humans!
[grunt]
[battle cry]
[angry roar]
Orochimaru?!
So, that's what
happened.
It's no wonder
that I don't
remember.
I was trapped inside
of Orochimaru's genjutsu!
Then...that means my
true enemy is Orochimaru!
Bee! Just run!
His power right now
isn't a problem.
We can handle it, Bee!
I got it!
Reanimation means different
form but easy annihilation!
Yeah!
Tailed Beast Bomb!
Will this work?!
Huh?!
He revived?!
It's useless.
Run! The only way to
stop a reanimated body
is to seal it!
Bee, let's prepare
to seal him.
Retreat for now!
Yeah! All right, then!
There's no escape,
Eight Tails!
[startled breath]
What is that?!
I'm sensing chakra from
two Octopops!
Don't tell me that
there's another
Eight Tails!
Don't go back, Naruto!
[startled gasp]
Old Man Raikage!
Just let Bee handle this!
But-
Bee won't lose.
Besides, even if you go,
you can't bring down
what Fukai has become.
Huh?!
Only Bee can fill the
hole that's in Fukai's
heart.
What do you mean?
A hole?
You got it, Old
Man Raikage. I'll
put all my faith
in Octopops!
[grunt]
This is not good!
We're in a real quandary!
What a calamity! But still,
escape is my specialty!
How can you rap
at a time like this?!
Wouldn't you rather jump
into a hole if there
was one?!
A hole...A hole
in the heart!
Woah! Just look
at them fight!
My father always
courageously stood
up to fight against
guys like them!
What am I waiting for?!
I'll hold him off!
You make a run
for it, Bee!
Brother Motoi!
Lightning Style!
Spider Web!
[growling]
No! Stop!
[painful scream]
Brother Motoi!
I told you to
get away!
[snarls]
I'm not gonna
lose here!
At one time, you
might've been my teacher.
But this time, I'm gonna
give you the lecture!
I owe you that, Fukai.
[scared gasp]
No! Bee!
Listen Bee, you know
why Ay is so strong?
[shaking head effort]
Ay has been raised very
carefully...
...to ensure that he
doesn't become pampered just
because he's next in line
to be Raikage.
Ay has accepted the
responsibility placed on his
shoulders by Lord Raikage
and the village.
And fulfilled
everyone's hopes.
A sensitive boy
once prone to tears...
...has grown up to
become mighty and strong,
and capable of incredible
deeds.
All while being a very
special person to the
Raikage.
He's a special person...?
That's the way I
found it.
Yo, what's up, Bro?
Hm?
Hm...
In a little while,
you're going to
become a Jinchuriki.
Everything is going
to change.
Your life is going
to be very hard.
Oh! No sweat, I
kinda figured that
might happen!
Maybe I'll name the
octopus while I do
my own rappin'.
I'll get all eight
tentacles clappin'!
Listen up, Bee. Always
tell me everything, you
understand me?
No secrets. Because you're
very special to me.
You and I are the
ultimate tag team!
I surround myself with
special people who
support me no matter
what happens.
I see...So you were
able to find it. For
you, it was the bonds
of friendship.
That's the something you
needed to fill the hole
in your heart.
And you're one of those
who are special to me.
That hole in your heart,
I'm gonna fill it up
completely. Yeah!
I wish that I'd been
able to find what I
needed back then, too.
Bee! Stop this war!
[frustrated grunt]
Are you okay, Brother?
[heavy groan]
Yeah, I'm fine.
Tell me...Did I fight
as courageously as
my father used to?
Oh, yeah! You had
mad courage out there!
I'll take you to the
Medical Corps right away.
No, I'll be alright.
[painful grunt]
Just carry out
Fukai's wishes and
end this war.
All right! You got
it, Brother!
Fukai, your sadness ran
so deep, it makes me weep!
But that's over, 'cuz
this I vow: my real war
is just starting now!
There's a special
way that Puppet Users
fight against each other.
I'm the only one
here who can do this.
Isn't that right,
Granny Chiyo?
After meeting Naruto,
I was able to do the
right thing in the end.
I thought that I'd died
leaving some hope for
a brighter future.
But...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Soul
Living Inside the Puppet."
Sasori, I...