Can you... share
your chakra with
everyone... again?
Not right now. Kurama
isn't done recharging
his chakra, yet.
To take down the main
body, we need to mow down
the big ones, or find
some way to slip past them.
It's too far to reach
in a single leap.
We'll need time to weave
signs and repel the
enemy's attacks.
Without your chakra,
Naruto, we could suffer
heavy casualties.
And the Medical Corps
can't come here.
We need to mow them down
and slip past, huh?
That'll be easy.
This guy can clear the distance
in one leap. And repel any
enemy attacks, too.
I can now stay near, and
heal anyone who suffers
serious harm! At any time!
-Summoning Jutsu!
♪
Hold on... huh?!
This color..!
Wait... You're-
You're Gamakichi!
Pops was tied up with some
negotiations, so I came
in his place instead.
What, you surprised!?
No! No, not really!
But, man, you got
big all of a sudden!
I'm even more shocked
than I was about Akamaru!
It's just that you humans grow
too slowly, that's all!
So, tell me, what's
the deal here, anyway?
Right! Do you see that
giant way in the back there?
Can you get me closer
with some leaps?
You mean the
biggest one?
That's right.
[growling]
(Aoda)
Lord Sasuke,
your desire?
I need you to just
keep advancing forward.
I'll get the real
body in the back!
Oh, Sakura, my dear! You're
able to invoke the 100 Healings
Mark! Lady Tsunade would be
so proud!
Lady Katsuyu, we
don't have time...
Please divide and attend
to each of the Allied
Shinobi, now.
Our role will be
to heal everyone.
How impressive! I never
imagined that I'd see
the Three-Way Deadlock
Summoning again!
[chuckling]
(Third Hokage)
It is a new era!
Now, let's go!
Aoda! Attack!
Lady Katsuyu,
please proceed!
Now, jump,
Gamakichi!
So this is the
original Team 7...
Nice, Gamakichi!
You're size isn't
just for show, huh?
Never mind that! Will
ya just hurry up and
weave some jutsu signs!?
C'mon! Get on with it!
You want me to shake
you off my head!?
His attitude's gotten a
lot bigger, too...
Yeah, I know, I know!
What the--!?
It's alright. These
slugs are part of
the Fifth Hokage's
Healing Jutsu.
Please, do not worry.
My strength's...
being restored!
My wounds are...
It's healing me!
Her 100 Healings mark was
just activated...
...and yet, she's
already performing
Lady Katsuyu's long-
distance healing!
(Shizune)
Sakura, you are
something else.
(Aoda)
Lord Sasuke?
Just keep moving
forward!
Sasuke!
Go for it!
Do it!
Hang in there!
Aim well!
You can do it!
Give it to 'em!
Chi'ya!
Wind Style: Massive
Rasen Shuriken!
Inferno Style:
Susano's Flame
Control!
So, then I'm... a
perfect match for
Sasuke...
Well, yeah. Wind
beats Lightening
certainly.
No. That's not
what I meant...
What I meant was, that only
my Wind can assist... and
magnify his Fire...
[roaring]
Whoa, it hit him!
Yeah, it really hit!
I've never seen such
Flame Control before!
(Tobirama)
And they combined jutsu
with matching chakra ratios!
That's hard to do,
even for a seasoned
duo!
A shuriken like a windmill..
.and an arrow that's
blacker than lacquer!
We'll call it Scorch Style
Nimbus Gale Jet Black
Arrow Formation Zero!
[chuckle]
Nah. Never mind.
Heh!
Now just burn up...
[growling]
You heard it, didn't
you? What Sasuke said
earlier?
What do you think
his true intentions
are?
[growling]
No idea.
Damn it! Why did we branch
off from Sasuke!? This
wasn't the deal!
At least I'm still safe!
Of course, it's no thanks
to being on the front lines!
Hm? There
they are...
What a sorry state
you're in, Tsunade.
Ugh, what a humongous
slug! I wonder how
much salt it'll take
to take it down!
That's just a piece of Katsuyu
that was summoned from
Shikkotsu Woods.
I'd say it's pretty
tiny, actually.
Oh...
I thought we came for the
Five Kage, not slugs!
C'mon, Lord Orochimaru! You
gotta stop paying attention
to Suigetsu and get to the
task at hand already!
Are you actually that upset
about me dragging you away
from Sasuke?
That's totally
not the case!
Let's just do this!
Damn you, Suigetsu!
Hey, why are
you attacking me?
I mean doesn't everyone
who sees a slug want to
sprinkle some salt on it?
Tsunade is first.
Let's go.
Lady Tsunade!
Wait, was... the Hokage
always a granny?
[gag] It isn't like she
had a really long torso,
either, did she?
It seems that you
were reckless, Tsunade.
Orochimaru...?
Katsuyu... I only
came here to aid
the Five Kage.
I am not a foe.
I don't have any reason to
believe you. ^ And besides, I
thought you were dead!
If I do anything that strikes
you as suspect, you're welcome
to take me down with your acid.
[screaming]
[weak groans]
Very well then. I
believe you. I will
trust you.
You are quite sensible,
unlike Manda.
Now then, first
of all...
...where are
the other Kage?
They're recovering
inside my fragments.
They've all been heavily
injured. It's quite
difficult to heal them.
(Orochimaru)
But still, Katsuyu... with
you here, why is it taking
so long for them to heal?
I can only use my power in
response to the strength of Lady
Tsunade's 100 Healings Jutsu.
But she's extremely weak right
now,... so I'm not able to
activate my strength fully.
Is that the way the
system always worked?
Well... then again, as far as I
can remember, I've never seen
Tsunade this weakened.
It must be true.
I've been trying to persevere
and remain focused on healing
even though the Summoning is
beginning to unravel now.
Thus, I haven't been able to
fully reattach Lady Tsunade's
body.
Suigetsu, go get Tsunade's
lower half and join it to her
upper half.
Ugh! What!? I'm better
at cutting things up
and taking them apart!
Ugh, these slugs are
all slimy and wriggly!
This is totally gross.
Yeah, well, so are you,
Suigetsu! In fact, you're even
grosser and weirder because
you have a human form!
Karin... Let Tsunade
bite you so that she
can heal.
What? But I don't want anyone
but Sasuke biting me! Come on!
Hah! You just admitted
you're in love with Sasuke!
No way! You're completely wrong!
How could I hate- I mean like
that damn Sasuke?
That wasn't a sentence...
[flustered] He tried to kill
me and it was irresistible!
No it wasn't...
You were covered in bite marks
long before Sasuke bit you!
Shut up! I'm for Sasuke's
exclusive use now!
Don't freak out you
denture mold model!
And besides, how exactly
does your body work, anyway?
You're the real
weird on here...
Say that again!!
You two... hurry up!
[gulps]
Both of you are weird, okay?!
Now stop your squabbling!
'Cause otherwise... I'll have my
snakes tie you up, and then I'll
crawl into your mouth and
possess you both!
[Thinking]
You're the weirdest
one out of all of us!
[Thinking]
Now that's weird
AND abnormal...
[sucking]
[Thinking]
She's taking so much that I
might age into a hag.
Lady Tsunade! You're
going to be okay!
Tsunade, you could
be a little more
grateful.
You betrayed the Leaf Village,
so why do this? And why now?
The range of things that
interest me has just expanded.
In the past, I wanted to
become the wind and turn
the windmill myself.
But now I know the pleasure
of waiting around for
someone else's wind...
...one that is unpredictable.
I don't want that wind to get
sealed away before I can enjoy
it...
You still don't make one
bit of sense whatsoever.
Although, seems
you've changed a bit.
I never imagined that
you would save me...
Stranger things
have happened.
Do you remember it? That
Three-Way Deadlock?
Our summonings...
No! Just like how it's
written! The Three-Way
Deadlock?
Earth Style Stone
Pistol Jutsu!
[labored breathing]
Hm?
It's useless, Tsunade.
The Hidden Stone's Earth
Style will most likely
collapse this mountain.
If we're to escape, we can't
wait. The two of us must go.
No. Jiraiya, too!
We cannot bring Jiraiya
and still expect to outrun
the Hidden Stone!
That's why I'll use Medical
Ninjutsu to help him-
Tsunade! We are
at war now!
We cannot let emotions get
in the way and reduce the
chance of success.
And what is success?
It's to survive, of
course! What else?
One alone can't. Two probably
can. But with three...
...it's certain death.
[gasp]
Quickly, you go on
ahead, and I will
take care of Jiraiya!
Make one move...
and I'll kill you
in a heartbeat.
Seems we're in a
Three-Way Deadlock.
What's that mean? This whole
situation just boils down to
who will act first.
Jiraiya is already--
[labored breathing]
[gasp]
You see? Jiraiya trusts
you completely, Orochimaru.
So much so, it even
freezes you in your
tracks.
[gasp]
What foolishness!
I shall just...
[explosion]
Over here! Jiraiya, Tsunade,
Orochimaru! I've brought
reinforcements!
People really can
change. Or they die
before they have a
chance to.
Although he passed away
without changing...
And you know what? He probably
trusted you until the very end.
Orochimaru! If you'd become like
this sooner, then Jiraiya...
might not be dead now!
Yet if I had... Jiraiya
may have also changed.
Just like it was with
us, the Legendary Sannin,
things don't always go
the way you want them to.
We're not made of stone.
Distortions will appear
somewhere.
[Thinking]
Perhaps that's why I want to
observe Sasuke's future...
...while patiently
waiting for his
wind to blow.
Fine... I give you thanks
for helping me heal.
So, I take it you
know all about the
war?
Of course. That's why
I'm helping you out
like this.
Don't you see?
How long have
I  been...?
I can report on the
battle situation.
Katsuyu? How'd you end
up on the battle front?
[Thinking]
I see... Sakura
Summoned her!
Right about now,... a new
Three-Way Deadlock is
probably making their debut.
Well then, we should
be heading back now.
Tsunade, you should
get to work on healing
the other Kage.
[Obito]
So there is still doubt
in your heart, is there?
[Kakashi]
Won't you stop this?
[Obito]
I want to negate
everything he desires!
[Kakashi]
I'm certain you must
understand Naruto's
feelings!
[Obito]
There's nothing
in my heart!
[Kakashi]
Do you think... such
things can fill the
hole in your heart?
[Obito]
Just like how it
was with me! Right,
Kakashi?
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Kakashi versus Obito."
(Kakashi)
This is all that the
current me can do.