[giggles]
Forehead! Forehead!
Forehead!
Hmf! Hey! Knock it
off! Leave me alone!
[giggles]
Okay!
[gasp] ...It's
snowing...
Kon, kon, kon,
it's snowing, kon!
It looks to me
like Yota really
likes you, Sakura.
Or your forehead
at least..!
Perfect!
Listen..! What's
the deal..!?
Kon, kon, kon!
Well... I guess
this could be fun!
All I wanted to do was
give Sasuke a bouquet of
flowers from our shop...
...but he just ignored me
and walked off without so
much as a look!
So so sad.
Poor Ino-Ino...
Ino... I... sorry.
Yota..! You're so nice
that I'll give you one!
(Thinking)
Ino is so forward...
I can't believe she'd
act that way with Sasuke!
You having
fun, Sakura?
Huh?
If Sakura happy,
then Yota happy, too!
Sakura...!? What are
you so happy about!?
Oh...! That's
not it...!
[giggle]
[annoyed groan]
That yota is
so fickle!
When he's sad, it
starts raining. And
when he's happy, it
snows... Hm...
[groaning]
Huh?
(Ino)
Those flowers...
(Shikamaru)
Did Yota...?
He was here?
Huh...
No, you can't go
there, Yota...
You're supposed to
be a secret from the
rest of the village.
If someone discovered
you, then there's gonna
be trouble for sure!
So you can't let
anybody see you,
okay?
Sure! But don't
worry, no one's
seen me.
Are you sure?
You bet! Well,
maybe one kid...
Who!?
He seemed like kind
of a weird one...
He was the only
kid sitting outside
at lunch.
He was on
an iron rod.
Iron rod?
...Naruto?
Hm... Wait, you
mean... that kid?
Oh! I know! He's
always alone! And
looks really angry.
Angry? Really? 'Cause
every time I see him
he kinda smiles at me.
You know what,
maybe he likes you!
What!? Cut it out!
Did Naruto notice
you, or not?
Maybe... I dunno.
Listen, Yota. Don't
go into the village
ever again, okay?
If you're caught, you
might get taken away
and we wouldn't see
each other again.
Oh no, not that!
I don't want to be
apart from Sakura!
Just Sakura?
What gives?
Thank you, Yota.
I gotta say, that
was really pretty
funny, though.
Sasuke is always
so "cool," but he
looked like a
flower garden!
[laughter]
[grunt]
[panting]
So, does this mean we
have to fight Yota?
It's just like with
Asuma. We have to
fight and seal him.
...We have to fight!
Yeah, but...
How can we!?
(Choji)
How do we defeat
someone who can
control the weather?
I don't know yet!
[shouts]
[panting]
(Thinking)
Come to think of it, we
really don't know much of
anything about Yota...
...How do we...?
(Telepathically)
Dad, connect me
with Sakura.
[gasp]
You got it.
Sakura!
[gasp]
(Ino)
Sakura! You there?
(Telepathically)
Ino? Sorry, I'm in the
middle of something
right now!
Do you remember...?
You have to-- You
just have to!
(Ino)
...It's Yota!
Wait... Yota? Ino...
He's in front of me
right now!
[gasp] What..!? He is!?
[gasp]
Huh!?
(Kiba)
He's here, too!
[gasp]
...And he's really
really mad about
something...!
What?
But, how can Yota be
with you guys, too!?
Three Yotas...?
What is going
on here!?
[♪Whistling]
Whistling...?
So, who are you?
[♪Whistling]
What's this?
Huh?
[gasp]
Hold on...
Yeah, you're...
Yota!
[giggle]
[♪Louder Whistling]
[grunt]... Yota..!
Naruto.
[♪Whistling]
Yota...
Huh?
[groaning]
What's up?
What did you do with
Yota!? Did you take
him somewhere, you-!?
Ino, putting him
through an
interrogation
won't work.
Naruto, you know
though, don't you?
Know what?
[groan]
You saw something,
right? I mean...
maybe not...?
If I didn't see
anything, how could
I have seen something?
You know, you're a
lot shrewder than
you look.
Mmmhm!
Are you kidding!?
Why would that
impress you guys
so much?
Come on! Let's go!
Hey! What--!?
Now, what did you
do with Yota!?
Uh... Yota?
You met him in the
schoolyard the other
day, didn't you...!?
The only other person
who knows about Yota
besides us is you!
[gasp]
Come on! Don't deny
it! You met Yota,
didn't you!?
And then you blabbed
about it to everyone!
I don't know
who Yota is.
He was a kid who
got lost near the
Village...
We all felt bad for
him so we started
taking care of him.
But then, today, when we
came here, everything was
a mess and Yota was gone!
So, this kid is some
kind of an outsider then?
[gasp]
Why would you guys
protect an outsider...
...but still look
at me that way!?
[grunt]
What kind of thing
is that to say!?
He's so stuck up!
[groan]
Well, maybe we did
question him kinda
hard without having
any proof...
Huh?
Maybe he really
doesn't know anything
about Yota.
[guilty sigh]
This really stinks!
Why's it always
have to be me!?
Ugh, now I'm lost.
(Yota)
[crying]
[gasp] Huh?
Are you...?
[crying]
Hey, could it be...?
Hey! Whoa! Just calm
it down, would ya!?
What is it!?
What's the matter!?
[crying]
Who are you
anyway?
I'm scared!
I'm so scared!
Okay... but
what's your name?
I'm... Yota!
Huh!? So you're the
one they were talking
about!
(Yota)
[crying harder]
ARGHHH!
Huh?
Weird, a sun shower?
Yota, is this...
your jutsu?
Wow, that's cool!
Man, I can't even do
stuff like Clone or
Transformation Jutsu.
And Iruka Sensei is
always getting on my
case about it, too.
You're an outsider
like me, but everybody
likes you...
What a joke...
that's so unfair,
you know?
Boo!
Ahh!
Wait! I know you!
You are...
[blowing air]
Right? You were sitting
up on the iron rod the
other day and doing that
whatchamacallit-- Whistling!
Oh!
[♪Whistling]
Whoa...! [♪Whistling]
Can you teach me
how to whistle, too!?
Huh?
When you started whistling
like that, it was like you
weren't all alone anymore!
It cheered you up!
I was just pretending!
I only started
whistling to
distract myself...
Then that's what
Yota's gonna do, too!
Look, you're already
friends with everyone-
Uh... Huh!?
Are you...?
[gasp] Hold still!
[hissing]
[gasp]
Will you teach me how
to whistle like you,
now? Pretty please?
Sure!
All right, watch me.
First blow out without
pursing your lips, ya know?
Then, you slowly
narrow them...
...and make wind
sounds like "wooosh!"
Hm!
[♪]
(Thinking)
He's happy now...
So his happiness
turns into wind!
Listen!
[whistling melody]
What's that?
[whistling melody echo]
(Yota)
You. Are. My. Friend.
Huh?
You are my
friend! Ya know?
Hm?
[laughing]
(Akamaru)
[Barking]
Hm.
(Akamaru)
[Barking]
Hey! There he is!
Come back, you!
[barking]
Hey! Wait!
No! No! Noooo!
Ahhh!
That kid!? Again!?
Yota!
Ow!
No doggies! No
doggies...! No!
Ahh! Whoa!
What did you guys
do to Yota!?
I have no idea!
I was just taking
Akamaru out for a
walk... ARGH!
And I saw that guy!
[lightning zap]
(Kiba)
Then thunder and
lightening started
goin' off everywhere!
He's the one doing
this, isn't he!?
Argh!
Yota?
Yeah! It's him!
Yota...!
Peh-peh-peh-peh!
So when Yota gets
angry, he makes
thunder and lightening?
[screams]
[giddy chuckles]
[grunt]
[laughing]
Here, puppy!
One... two... three...
Four... five... six...
Seven... eight... nine...
Ten... eleven... twelve...
Thirteen...
I'll hide with
you, Naruto!
You can't Yota!
They're gonna find
us both right away!
[giggling]
No, come on! You've
gotta stop acting
all happy like this!
Otherwise the weather
will change, and then
they'll find us!
Now you're angry
with me, Naruto?
Oh no! Not
crying! Just get
out of here! Shoo!
(Kiba)
Ninety-eight,
ninety-nine....
one hundred!
Ha! Found you, Naruto!
Ugh! That Yota
got me caught!
Isn't anyone gonna
come and kick the
can to save me...?
Come on... anyone?
[grunt]
Shikamaru, Choji, Ino,
Akamaru, Sakura...
That means Yota's
the only one left.
Yota?
Yota...?
That means
Yota's crying!
Yota...!
[gasp]
No! Yota!
[grunt]
We're taking him into
custody. He'll be  kept
under strict observation
and interrogated.
But Yota isn't a
danger to the Village!
We'll determine that.
Besides, all outsiders
are forbidden inside the
Village boarders.
You'll be summoned
later to give evidence.
Until then, return
home and stay there.
No way! 'Cause
Yota is my--!
[running breaths]
(Thinking)
That was it. That
moment marked the end
of our days with Yota.
And then...
We all let Yota die...
(Naruto)
Yota! Get a grip!
It's all okay!
(Yota)
You guys... time
to go...
(Naruto)
What are you talking about?
From now on we're gonna be--
(Yota)
No matter what happens,
I will never forget
about you guys...
(Yota)
But every last one
of you will forget
about me...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Lingering Snow"
(Naruto)
How could we
forget you!?