(Kiba)
Ugh! I still
ache all over!
You just can't sleep
on the ground without
the right gear, or
you'll pay the price!
[bark]
Sorry guys!
It's not the end
of the world.
'Least we'll be
back in the
Village by the
end of the day.
Hm? Kakashi
Sensei?
Where'd
he go?
I'm counting
on you guys!
Kakashi Sensei,
What's up?
I've just sent
messages to every
Hidden Village.
We want a
united front.
We need to share
critical intel as
early as possible.
(Earth Lord)
The Akatsuki possess
Tailed Beasts!
(Earth Lord)
There's no time
to waste amymore!
They're led by the
Madara Uchiha. He's
capable of anything!
We must do all we
can to stop him.
Yes, I know that.
Then just give
your approval!
Do you want to lose
this war before it
even begins?
But this... Allied
Shinobi force...
What if we're giving
shinobi too much power?
This decision might
come back to haunt us.
Do you really distrust
the people of your own
nation that much?
First of all--
If I may... I
suggest that
you decide now,
noble sirs...
(Tenga)
The battery's almost
depleted... It's such a
long distance to transmit.
[clearing throat]
Then let's conclude this.
Lightning approves
this measure.
Earth, too.
Just as before.
Wind will give it's
approval as well.
Sure, okay, why not?
Yes, Fire approves
it, too.
[sigh] Very well.
Water votes yes.
Then now, with this
vote... The formation
of the Allied Shinobi
Force is ratified.
Monitors on record...
I, Tenga, shall serve
as witness to this
momentous decision.
Thank you very
much for your
time, sir.
The transmition
has ended.
Finally..! That
took so long...
We must notify the
Hidden Leaf Village
at once.
(Ino)
Sakura...
I wonder what's
goin on... Where
is she now?
You think she
got Naruto to agree
with our descision?
Kiba and Lee are
still with her.
I'm sure that
everything's ok.
Yeah, but...
Look, Ino. Us sitting
around worrying about
it isn't going to do
anyone any good.
Hm?
[hawk cry]
Did something
happen?
(Shikaku)
Hey, Shikamaru...
...can I
talk to you?
Sure, dad.
(Announcer)
Lord Kazekage
has returned!
Tell me, did you get
Tobimaru's message?
Yes ma'am!
You receive any word
from the Feudal Lords?
Yes, sir. We
just did.
We've been informed
they all gave their
approval.
Huh. That came much
sooner than we all
thought.
Given the
situation...
...those Lords had no
choice but to act quickly,
even if normally they
drag their heels.
It's gonna get hectic.
Call a council
at once.
Send for all of the
officials immediately.
(Mist Shinobi)
Welcome home, Lady
Mizukage. We just received
word from the Feudal Lord.
Go on. Let's
hear it then.
The Five Great
Nations' Lords
approved the Allied
Shinobi Forces.
Is that so?
It's finally time.
We must hurry to
prepare ourselves
for the coming
war as well.
It's a good thing we were at
least able to secure Eight
-Tails before it fell into
the hands of our enemies.
And as a welcome bonus
Kisame Hoshigaki of
the Akatsuki fell in
that fight.
We were able to weaken
the enemy's might
before the war even
began, so that's a plus.
Lord Raikage
sure delivered.
[thinking]
Kisame Hoshigaki?
Really...?
[thinking]
The one who's been
called the Tailless
Tailed Beast?
What's the
matter, Chojuro?
Oh, no! Uh,
it's nothing!
Where's your
energy!?
Are you hungry
or something!?
You know...
I'll treat you
to a meal later.
Uhh... what?
How about some
breaded fried pork
chops? To bring us
good luck in battle!
[thinking]
"breaded fried..."
Wedded bride...
Thanks but, I
hate oily foods.
Sorry!
How pitiful! Keep
that attitude, and
you'll fail just when
it matters most!
[thinking]
As a wedded bride...
you'll fail....
At times like
these, accept
your elders'
advice!
Huh?
[giggle] Shut
up, or die.
[grunt]
(Kurotsuchi)
Already!? That
was fast!
It was, but -
- the Feudal Lords probably
reached a quick decision
'cause Madara and the Tailed
-Beasts were mentioned.
I understand the Tailed
-Beast part, but isn't
Madara something out of
the history books?
He's gotta be
really old by now.
I don't know,
he didn't look
that old to me.
Alright, who looks
older? Him, or our
Old Man?
Ya know, the
ignorant sure do
have it easy, I'll
tell ya that much.
Well, I think it's
just that the whole
idea of going to
war seems so unreal.
All I can say is,
Heaven help us.
If all our Shinobi
are young kids who
know nothing of
war whatsoever!
Of course, a certain
someone got dressed
down by one of those
snot-nosed kids.
[grumble]
When did all of you
forsake yourselves?
Hmf. Well I guess
we'll see just what
you young ones are
made of.
The reports suggest
there was quite an
uproar at the conference.
The Sixth Hokage's
attempt to twist
events in his own favor
was highly unusual...
The venue was kept
top secret, and security
was as tight as a drum.
And yet the site was
breached so easily.
Who would have thought?
Just what you'd
expect of the
Akatsuki.
They gained access
to the Summit without
difficulty, and threw
us all into an uproar.
Tell us everything.
Right as the Summit began,
they suddenly appeared out
of nowhere, just when we
all least expected it.
Well hello there!
One problem after
another, now what?!
Is he Akatsuki?
Seems so!
Guess what!
Sasuke Uchiha
has snuck in
here!
I wonder, where
do you think he
could be hiding
right now!?
Any guesses!?
(Sasuke)
I'm very
irritated
right now!
Attack, and I
doubt I can
hold back.
We could say
the same to you!
[attack yell]
Good! Now...
Gale Style!
Laser Circus
Sasuke!
(Karin)
[gasp]...What
is this...?
Gara, I've got an
ultimate defense
even greater than
yours...
It can't be! An
ultimate defense
greater than the
Kazekage's?!
That's what
Sasuke told us.
Must be an Ocular
Jutsu of the
Mangekyo Sharingan.
And then...
They told us to
withdraw, and
they headed for
the Summit room.
He's here.
Above us!
[gasping in pain]
I'll admit to you that
it does leave quite a
pain in my heart to see such
a handsome man melt away...
But you must die.
So you'r the
brat that took
down Deidara, huh!?
Well, I've got
no grudge
against you..
But many shinobi
want you dead!
So, goodbye!
Particle Style:
Atomic Dismantling
Jutsu!
My name is
Madara Uchiha.
Sasuke!
I am here to
explain something
to you all.
And once you
understand it,
I'll ask you a
question.
To think that even
together, four Kage
weren't able to take
down Sasuke Uchiha!
Such is the power
of the Akatsuki...
But why did they
attack the Five
Kage Summit anyway?
Was it merely
to put on a show
of strength?
Judging from their
individual actions...
...it is difficult
to say whether Sasuke
and Madara's objectives
were the same.
However... it
seems that Madara
thought, if luck
were on his side-
-he could take the
five leaders hostage
in order to advance
his own plan.
What gall! Seizing
the Five Kage!?
What is this
plan of Madara's?
He said it was
called "Project
Tsuki no Me"
(Gaara)
He already has possession
o seven Tailed-Beasts,
including my One-Tail.
(Gaara)
Madara wants to collect
the last two, and
resurrect the Ten-Tails-
(Gaara)
-The combination of
every Tailed-Beast...
(Gaara)
...in order to
make himself the Ten
-Tails Jinchuriki.
(Gaara)
Then using it's power, he
would place the world under
the infinite Tsukuyomi.
He'd rule over everyone
everywhere, and control
them completely.
A world free of
conflict and strife,
isn't that how he
described it?
Absurd! Such a
plan would mean
the end of the
world!
Exactly. That's the
very reason why we
must stop him.
That's the Allied
Shinobi Force's goal.
(Official)
In that case, I worry
about the whereabouts
of Danzo Shimura.
I hear he's been
controlling the Hidden
Leaf from behind the
scenes for a while now.
I certainly wouldn't want to
get stabbed in the back at
a time when we're all trying
so hard to build solidarity.
Yes, we're working
on that. Every hidden
village has men out
there searching for him.
Some of the Mizukage's
men came in contact
with him, but... hm?
What is it? We're
still in conference!
Come in.
Just now, Kakashi
Hatake of The Leaf
sent us a message.
He and two others ran into
Sasuke and Madara Uchiha
and there was a skirmish.
They confirmed
the death of
Danzo Shimura.
[gasp]
Danzo's really
dead!?
What happened!?
Someone so skilled
that he became the
Hokage?
Madara and Sasuke?
(Anbu Messenger)
Sir! It seems they
used the Transportation
Technique to disappear.
While the Akatsuki
are certainly strong,
their ability to wage
war is unknown.
(Gaara)
But the true strength of
our Allied Shinobi Forces,
is also unknown.
(Gaara)
Earth, Water, Fire,
Wind, Lightning...
...if we unite the power
of all our shinobi, I
believe we can counter
the Akatsuki effectively.
Above all, we must
win this battle, or
this world will end.
Begin stockpiling
ninja tools and
rations!
Halt all official
missions in
preparation for
battle.
Prepare a list
of all shinobi
belonging to
the Village.
Tell each platoon
to start preparing
their tactical
plans, now!
No way! Are you
serious!? Sasuke
attacked the Five
Kage Summit!?
I hear they're
just about to
make an official
announcement.
There's still lots
of confusion among
the officials.
So it's really true then!
Sasuke is with the
Akatsuki who attacked
the Hidden Leaf Village!
This mess is turning
out to be a real drag.
Lady Mizukage's orders!
Inventory all our ninja
tools! Make a list of
anything we're short on!
[grumble] I don't
know about this
Allied Forces thing.
There's no way I'm
gonna join up with
those guys from the
Stone.
The Akatsuki's a despicable
group that brought the
nightmare of the Fourth
Mizukage upon our nation.
And the Hidden Stone
has used the Akatsuki
again and again--
until now.
The higher-ups may
order it, but there's
no way Ganryu will
accept it...
(Temari)
You're sure being
careful with them...
(Kankuro)
They're the
masterpieces of a
legendary puppeteer!
(Kankuro)
I'm not gonna allow myself to
be bested by the generations
of puppeteers who came before
(Kankuro)
How about you?
I had to send off messages
to every one of the ninja
who are currently away on
missions.
To think... he'd
actually kill a
Hokage...
You mean
Sasuke Uchiha?
I knew he'd fallen,
but I didn't think
he'd fall this far...
However...
Naruto, you once
told me that you
would become
Hokage one day...
...Well, I've
become Kazekage.
And if you've
truly resolved to
become a Kage...
...then you're going
to have to do what
needs to be done, as
Sasuke's friend.
[grunt]
Naruto didn't
seem to be too
convinced, did he?
It's because he
never gives up.
Naruto was the one
who changed Gaara,
when even we couldn't
get close to him.
However lost in the
darkness someone is
Naruto will hold out
his hand and try to-
-save him...
...that is
his way.
Gaara...
But it's Sasuke
himself who's
seeking the darkness
this time. I don't--
It has to be
Naruto's decision.
What he must do as
a friend.
I will give my
friend's all that I
have to keep them safe
and protect the world.
[hawk cry]
Hey look. There's
another hawk flying
around. How many
does that make?
Who cares? Come
on Konohamaru,
forget about that!
What I really
wanna know is
where Naruto
has run off to,
We still have
to finish the
Leaf Hero
Newspaper!
And I haven't
snagged the
critical interview
with him!
Yeah. And when he and
I had that sexy Jutsu
contest, he told me that
he'd be coming right back!
What?! Sexy
Jutsu!? Don't
be so lude!
Yuck!
Hey! It's not
lude! It's my
secret lethal
move, ya know!?
Hey Konohamaru!
I just heard that
Naruto is coming
back home!
(Both)
[gasp & happy laughter]
Sakura...
We're home!
I heard from
my father
about Sasuke.
Yeah.
We talked. And not
only that but I
fought with him, too.
[gasp] You fought
against him? Really?
Against Sasuke!?
I'll give you all the
details. But first, will
you do me a favor and get
everyone together for me?
I have something
that I wanna say
to all of them.
Sure. Okay.
(Konahamaru)
Naruto! We've
all been waiting
for you!
Hey you guys...
I just need to get an
interview from you and
then the Leaf Hero
Newspaper will be finished!
Yeah, Naruto! It's
time for your big
interview!
Oh, right. I
almost forgot!
But I have to
make a report
now, so we'll
do it later.
(Moegi)
What!? You always say
that! It's always later
and it never happens!
(Udon)
Yeah, Naruto...
You promised us!
Oh you always make
us wait! You're so
mean, Naruto!
So, when are
you gonna do
it then!?
(Moegi)
Yeah we've been
waiting a long time!
We can't wait forever!
(Moegi & Udon)
Hey! Don't just
walk away! Talk
to us!
Go on! Why don't
you say something
too, Konohamaru?
I think something
happened.
What do you mean?
It seems like...
there's something
different about
Naruto now.
There is? What
are you talking
about Konohamaru?
I don't see
anything different
he looks the same
to me!
Yeah, I know,
but...
(Udon)
So when are we
gonna do the
interview Naruto!?
(Naruto)
Man they're fast!
What's going on?
(Sakura)
It's Kakashi-Sensei
and Guy-Sensei.
(Neji)
Those two... Is
it "that" again?
(Tenten)
No doubt about it!
They've rekindled
their rivalry contest.
(Tenten)
Guy-Sensei probably
challenged him... Of all
the times to do this!
(Neji)
No, that's exactly
why  he's doing
this now...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Kakashi
Hatake the Hokage!"
(Rock Lee)
What a splendid
contest Guy-Sensei!