(REAL ZETSU) That pesky traitor
vermin's finally dead, huh?
Though as insects go, his
persistance was like a roach's!
[laughter]
Don't laugh at Obito!
Naruto...
Naruto... If you keep resisting,
you're only going to end up
pitifully crumbling to dust just
like him!
As someone who tried to become
Hokage...
...Obito is...
[gasp]
...nothing but awesome to me!
No way!
[pained groan]
Can't move!
I don't even have much strength
left. Guess I was left behind
again...
[groggy moans]
(OBITO) You guys alright? Rin?
Kakashi?
[gasp]
Obito!
[grunting]
No, don't. It's okay, Kakashi.
I don't- I don't think I'm
gonna make it.
My right side is completely
crushed. I can't even feel
anything there anymore.
[grunting and panting]
No!
I'm... giving you my...
Sharingan.
[gasp]
Whatever the village or anyone
else may say...
I think.. that you're a great
Jonin...
It's true. That's how I really
feel.
Please accept this...
Kakashi...
[coughing]
[quivering breaths]
(KAKASHI & OBITO) Rin!
Again, you...
Thank you, Rin.
Obito and I will be joining you
shortly.
We can catch up then, all three
of us together once more.
[grunt]
Rin...
This time, let's...
...spend some alone time
together... just you and me.
Kakashi would just be in the
way. So I'll leave him here.
That was... Kamui!
[gasps]
Obito! What did you do?!
Kakashi...
...you stay here a little
longer.
[gasps and quivering]
Don't you rush to follow us!
[heavy breathing]
But why?!
Why save someone useless like
me?
[chuckling]
[chuckle] This is
embarrassing... I mean, messing
up in front of you the way that
I did...
It looks like you've managed to
calm down a little,
C'mon, Obito.
Rin... do you mind waiting just
a little longer?
Obito...?
Just a bit before we move on...
You see, I'd kinda like to make
just one more detour along the
way...
[sigh] Alright, who do you wanna
save this time?
Kakashi.
Huh...?
I've just finally gotten alone
time with you, and... it'll be
wasted if he comes here right
away.
Besides... it's kind of annoying
seeing him all stiff and
useless.
His name may mean scarecrow, but
that doesn't mean...
...he should be acting like one!
(RIN) [giggling]
Despite all that's happened, you
two are still close, huh?
[fumbling] No, no way! Come on!
Give me a break! We're like oil
and water!
[chuckle]
You can go... just like that?
That's right. The energy that we
call chakra connects both of the
worlds.
I'm gonna go see Kakashi!
I'll be waiting here.
Sorry, Rin! I promise I'll be
right back!
[gasp]
Obito?!
Before I move on to the next
world, I thought I'd emphasize
to you not to come running after
me so quickly.
Huh?
And besides, it's gonna keep on
bothering me that this eye I
gave to you...
...the one to celebrate your
promotion to jonin came back to
me.
Obito...you...
Then again, it's not like I'll
be springing back to life
anymore...
But, froget that... More
importantly, you know how I
told Naruto to become the
Hokage?
I meant to say, as
the Seventh.
Huh?
Because the Sixth Hokage...
should be you, Kakashi.
[gasp]
(OBITO) I know you haven't taken
office yet... but I'm giving you
your gift now.
It has a fixed time limit, but
it isn't useless. Do you get
what I'm saying?
I mean, you haven't actaully
forgotten your famous nickname
that's known throughout all the
lands, have you?
The name Kakashi of
the Sharingan!
[pained grunt]
Hm?
Let's do it, guys!
Hm!
Yes!
Yup!
Alright!
Roger.
Sure thing!
Gotcha!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Sage Art! [grunt]
Super Tailed Beast...
...Rasen-Shuriken! [grunt]
[pained grunt]
[grunts]
Nice one, Naruto!
There's no way they can come out
of that unscathed.
[grunt]
[worried groan]
Oh no! Don't tell me Mother's-!
What is that...?!
[weakening groans]
[roar]
Another...
...humongous creature thing?!
what is it?!
A wolf, or... 'Tanuiki? Badger?
Look, it doesn't matter... but
now we can get near it...
...and seal it more easily!
It's not humanoid? Mother didn't
transform into Ten Tails of her
own will.
Are the Tailed Beasts within her
resonating in response to
Naruto's attack and startting to
split apart? They're not stable!
[roar]
Sasuke, don't let that white
hand get hold of you! It'll
absorb you in an instant! And
it's really fast, too!
Yeah, I know!
[scared grunt]
[worried grunt]
Sasuke! Protect Sakura with your
Visual Prowess!
Ah!
Yeah, Sasuke! Nice!
A Susano'o?!
But whose?
Huh?! Wait... What?!
That wasn't you just now?!
[gasp] What's going on?!
(SAKURA) Kakashi Sensei!
Thanks... Obito.
This can't be... It's
impossible!
No it isnt Sauske!
They don't call him the Copy
Ninja, Kakashi of the Sharingan
for nothin! Know what I mean?
But he shouldn't even have the
Sharingan anymore...
I don't understand it, but you
saved me!
You watch along with me...
...as this time... I will
protect them... and the world.
Watch out!
[grunt and groan]
How about this...? Combining the
Kamui's power... with
shuriken!
Kamui Shuriken!
[roar]
Just as I thought... Gaining Six
Path's power enhances one's
Visual Prowess, too!
This power, is it Obito's
Sharingan?
But why does Kakashi Sensei have
it?
Whoa! That's more awesome than
yours Sasuke!
But this chakra is--!
[roar]
[pained roar]
(REAL ZETSU) This Root
Time-Space is Mother's exclusive
domain...
where she can directly extract
chakra from shinobi trapped in
the Infinite Tsukuyomi!
The Tailed Beats are now stable,
plus Mother's even produced a
Truthseeker Orb...
...an Expansive Kekkei Moura
Truthseeker Orb containing every
nature: wind, fire, earth,
lightning, water, shadow...
and light.
It's the start of a new
Time-Space. And you will become
its sacrifices!
[gasp] That thing is... it's
just like the spheres that're
behind me!
Yeah, except it's
a lot bigger!
And it's still growing- fast!
I definitely can't teleport away
such a giant object with the
Kamui.
Even if we were able to escape
this place and get to a
different Time-Space...
...if that thing gets too large,
we won't be able to return to
this place.
Then to stop it we'll have to...
I know... We're gonna have to
find a way to seal that Rabbit
Granny away right now.
You're right.
Listen up. I've got a plan.
This is going to be our very
last mission as Squad 7!
Let's go! We're saving
the world!
That's right.
Yeah!
Roger that!
I am immortal.
And if either of you were to
die, you cannot seal me away.
Now then...
...which shall it be?
Forget that! You're mine, damn
it!
No, we attack together.
She's scared of being sealed, so
her attention will be divided.
Get us in closer. Then we can
strike.
Right!
[gasps]
So fast!
Mother just gained more power.
Her might and speed are now
exponentially greater!
Huh?!
It really is a nifty ability,
Obito, to be able to pass
through things.
And now I can resurrect this
move, too!
Kamui Lightning Blade!
[pained groan]
Mother!
This is bad! Her right arm!
There's not enough time to
escape into another Time-Space!
Then...!
[pained groan]
So they were both Ashura's
reincarnante, after all.
They must have switched back
then.
So... the one on the right is
the real one!
Kamui!
[worried grunt]
Not good...
I'll go to the Ice World...
No... Indrea's reincarnate
possesses the Amaterasu, so that
would be no good!
Don't forget about me! We're
both women, so don't you mock
me!
[gasp]
Naruto... Sasuke... Sakura...
[grunts]
[giggling]
[gasp]
A silly prank...
But if this prank was the result
of teamwork...
[laughter] I gotcha! You fell
for it!
So Naruto's the perp...
I'm really sorry, Sensei. I
tried to stop Naruto, but he
just wouldn't!
Sakura makes excuses and tries
to protect herself...
Hmph!
And Sasuke just minds his own
business. He probably doesn't
even cosider them comrades.
Not one shred of teamwork...
Hmmm, how can I put this? My
first impression of this
group... You're a bunch
of idiots.
Okay, I'll go first. My name's
Naruto Uzumaki!
I like instant ramen in a cup!
I really like the ramen that
Iruka Sensei got for me at
Ichiraku.
But the thing I hate is waiting
until the ramen is done.
And my future dream is...
...to be Hokage!
Then the whole village will stop
disrespecting me and start
treating me like I'm somebody!
Somebody important.
My name's... Sasuke Uchiha...
And I hate a lot of things.
I don't really like anything.
What I have is not a dream...
because I will make it a
reality... I'm going to restore
my clan...
and destroy a certain someone.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
What I like, uh... I mean, the
person I like is...
My hobby is...
And I guess that my dream for
the future is...
[giddy squeal]
They're all just so...
scattered!
They're a long way from working
together as a team.
[sigh]
But then again, we were just
like that, too...
Well, I'll just have to do what
I can.
Yup... What a nice picture you
guys make right now...
Do it!
Oh Yeah! Cha!
Alright!
(KAKASHI) I really love you
guys!
We finally made it out! Kuruma,
that Jinchuriki of yours is
pretty good!
(NARUTO) And now it's happily
ever after, the end!
(SAKURA) You're right. Great
news.
Wait a sec! What about us?!
How're we supposed to get out of
this Time-Space?
You're right! This is bad!
(MINATO) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Congratulations."
(FOUR TAILS) But I gotta say,
he's still a tad dumb, isn't he?