What's up with
Minato Sensei?!
He tells us to
assemble and then he's late!
[sigh]
Give me a break!
You're one to talk!
Hey?!
You heard me!
Come on you two, stop it!
Hey, you wanna go?!
[scoff]
Hey, hold up!
Did you just scoff
at me, Kakashi?!
So what if I did?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're all here, I see.
Minato Sensei!
Do we have
a new mission?!
No, sorry, not today.
What are those?
Applications.
I've recommended you three
for promotion to Chunin.
Minato Sensei,
you're the best!
Hey...
Listen!
Just hold on a minute!
You'll have to get through
the Chunin Exams first.
Aww...
The Exams are divided into
three separate parts, and
each one of them
is quite difficult.
Are you kidding me?
[giggle]
You'll never pass 'cause
you aren't capable of making
it to a rendezvous on time.
What did you say?!
Hey, you guys, calm down!
So, anyway...
You've worked together
well and earned
the right to take
the Chunin Exam.
That's why I
recommended you for it.
However, it isn't
compulsory to participate.
It's entirely up to you if
you take the exam or not.
[chuckle]
Let's do it!
[nervous groans] The hell!
I thought for the Chunin
Exams were for stuff like
ninjutsu and taijutsu,
not some lame written test!
I'm the worst at
stuff like this!
Finished already?!
Yes.
Damn that Kakashi!
Aw, man!
I'm totally done for.
[gasp]
I'm always
watching you...
Rin...
There it is!
I did it!
[giggle]
Damn Kakashi!
Well...
Huh?
What'd you expect?
Shut up!
That was just a
written test!
Just wait!
You'll see!
I'll find my name!
I know I passed!
I guess not...
[gasp]
Obito!
Look!
There!
I did it!
Lucked into an open slot.
That's so like you.
What was that?!
Come on, you two.
Don't start this again!
There's no time
to celebrate!
If you passed, find
your assigned class.
We'll explain the
next part of the exam.
Part Two will
begin in three days.
It'll test your
physical skills.
You'll need to use
everything you've learned
about taijutsu and ninjutsu
or you won't pass this exam!
All right!
I got this!
Also, this test will pit
your team against
several other teams.
[gasps]
It's not an
individual test?!
Kakashi!
You'd better not drag
us down, you understand?
[sigh]
Right back at ya.
You're usually the one
doing the dragging.
What?!
Enough, you guys!
Just stop it!
Above all, don't be
late this time, all right?
Yeah!
I know that!
Kakashi Hatake's also
participating, right?
Yes.
He's part of the next team.
Ah.
I look forward to it.
All right!
Five minutes
left, Team Minato.
You positive
he'll make it?!
Yes!
I'm sure he's gonna be
here any minute now.
You realize that if
time runs out, you'll be
automatically disqualified.
[sighs]
I knew it!
Didn't I tell you
this would happen?!
You're too easy on him, Rin.
That's why he'll never break
this habit of being late!
He'll be here soon.
I bet that something must've
happened to hold him up a
just little bit, that's all.
He'll make it in time!
I know he will!
Hmph, I
wouldn't be so sure.
Oh, thank you!
Here, have some candy.
It's three p.m.
It's time to begin now.
We're going to fail
this all because of him!
I know he'll...
Sorry I'm late!
You see?!
I told you Obito would
make it no matter what!
Hurry, before
we're disqualified!
C'mon!
Close one...
Now we'll start part
two, the team competition.
Preliminary qualifiers...
Begin!
[attacking yell]
[gasp]
Fire Style!
Fireball!
[choking]
I'll make you pay me
back in full for the
last time that we fought!
The last time we fought?
What?!
Don't tell me you
don't remember?!
Just who are you?
And what have I done
to earn your wrath?
Why you!
Don't treat me like a fool!
Do your best!
Obito!
All right!
Just watch me!
Begin!
Huh?!
The winner is Might Guy!
What was he doing?
Do your best!
Go!
Kakashi!
Stop!
The winner is...
Kakashi Hatake!
He did it!
[chuckle]
You passed the Chunin
Exams on your first try?!
Kakashi, you're amazing!
Right, Obito?
Obito?
[sigh]
So this is
where you've been!
Oh, uh, it's you.
It's only natural
that Kakashi would pass.
But we can do it,
too, I know we can!
We'll just practice
hard for next year!
But it's hard to get
motivated after
watching Kakashi.
What are you saying?!
Huh?!
You're gonna be
Hokage, right?
Obito, I'll always
be watching you.
Okay!
Obito?
[chuckle]
I did it!
I'm a Chunin now!
Wow, nice job!
Meet me later at the park
underneath the cherry tree.
Today for sure!
I'm going to tell Rin
how I feel about her!
I know!
I'm late!
Sorry...
No, it's okay!
Everyone!
Everyone?!
Why are?!
Why are all of
these people here?!
I asked them to come
here so we could all
discuss the
gift, of course!
Huh?
What do you mean?
What gift is that?!
Well, Kakashi's being
promoted to Jonin, right?
So!
I figured we should give
him some kind of present to
celebrate!
"Mission to get gifts
for Kakashi's promotion?"
Kakashi's a Jonin?
That's right.
Didn't you know
about it, Obito?
I think it's something
that we should all be
proud of as his classmates.
Uh, yeah...
So what do you think Kakashi
would appreciate getting?
Well since we're talking
about Kakashi, it
should be something useful.
Now it's time for us to
do some combat training.
It might just be
training, but if you don't
stay alert, it can be fatal.
Got it?
Yes!
Uh... Well...
I guess that's that, huh?
Show me your left hand!
Oh...
Uh, it's nothing,
Rin, I swear, really!
It's just a scrape.
A little spit'll
take care of it...
Enough!
Show me!
I just messed
up a little bit.
Got some dust
in my eyes and...
[laughter]
Well, a guy's gotta have
a scar or two to get some
cred, like a badge of honor,
you know what I'm saying?
I was just thinking how I
needed a little something
cool like that!
So really this
wound's kinda- Oww!
Don't act tough and
hide your wounds!
I am always
watching, you know.
You promised me you'd
become Hokage, Obito.
Listen, I want to
stop this war, too.
Just like you, I truly
want to save the world!
And that's why I've decided
I'm gonna stick by your side
and watch over you.
You told me that saving you
was pretty much the same as
saving the whole
world, remember?
Mm-hm!
Well then, since I'm keeping
an eye on you, you can't
hide anything
from me anymore.
Go for it, Obito!
Become Hokage and
show me just how
you're gonna save
the whole world.
And that's another
promise for you to keep!
Let's go!
[giggle]
Obito...
You told Kakashi
Sensei you'd discard
all your memories and
all your feelings
about your comrades.
But when you became Ten
Tails' Jinchuriki and were
about to be
taken over by it...
[discomforted yell]
Didn't you try back then to
suppress Ten Tails because
you didn't want that?
[screaming]
The reason why you won
against Ten Tails and could
manipulate it was because
you stood firm on not
throwing away the past
and stayed yourself, right?
You just couldn't discard
all the memories of my Dad,
Kakashi Sensei, or
this Rin, could you?
That's how you were able to
stay Obito even after you
became Ten
Tails' Jinchuriki.
Am I wrong?
But dragging everyone onto
your path and continuing
down it with all of them
just cannot be allowed!
I'm bringing you
back as Obito Uchiha,
a shinobi of the Leaf.
And you're going to
atone for your sins.
You tried to run
away from everything.
The only thing that awaits
you is your worst nightmare,
which you know very well!
Solitude!
So why keep living
in reality, huh?
Now come join us, Naruto!
I bet I know what this Rin
person would say this if she
were still alive...
Don't act tough and
hide your wounds.
You know that I'm
always watching.
Because you're no one
else but you, damn it!
Stop running!
Come join us, Obito!
I will never go
over to your side!
I have no
regrets with my path.
I said I saw everything.
So don't keep imagining
yourself as Hokage!
The person Rin
wanted to watch over
isn't the current you.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Promise
That Was Kept."
It's Obito Uchiha!