Wind Style:
Massive Rasen Shuriken!
Inferno Style:
Susano'o Flame Control!
No.
That's not what I meant...
What I meant was, that
only my Wind can assist
and magnify his Fire.
[roaring]
[chuckle]
Now just burn up.
You heard it, didn't you?
What Sasuke said earlier?
What do you think his
true intentions are?
[growling]
No idea.
Though still incomplete, Ten
Tails has been revived and
is battling the
Allied Forces.
It's become quite a
complex situation.
It's that bad?
In that case, we all
ought to hurry, too!
I can carry all of
you with my sand.
Please,
preserve your chakra.
But we all came
in mid-story!
I want more details!
Why don't we hear
about it on the way?
Yes, let's just go!
To the battlefield!
[roaring]
So you don't know.
And yet you keep
working with Sasuke.
Why's that?
The answer's simple,
it's because I exist
to protect him.
Hey, Sasuke!
There are still other
Tailed Beasts inside
that gigantic one!
So douse those Black
Flames when it's weakened!
Then Kurama and I
will pull them out!
No, I won't.
They all burn.
Listen!
Don't you understand?!
If we don't save them now,
we're going to have a lot of
trouble later on!
I'm going to put an end to
this failing system that's
currently in place!
And then a new...
[gasp]
It detached the piece of
itself that was on fire!
[angry roars]
Sakura...
May I ask you something?
I don't know him well, so I
can see it impartially...
Sasuke can't be trusted or
considered a true comrade.
What are your
actual feelings on
the matter, Sakura?
Don't worry.
It's just that Sasuke
has come back to us again!
That fact makes me
sincerely happy.
And I do fully believe him.
Your words may
not be lies...
But...
I can already tell
that your smile is fake.
What's up, Shikamaru?
It's nothing.
Obito...
Enough of these tricks.
I'm over it now.
No more genjutsu.
It looks to me like
I can't find anything
that will change you.
Right now, all I can
give you is just death.
Then I shall do the same.
Now...
Shinobi Hand-to-Hand Combat.
Well now that
you're ready...
Begin!
Lemme borrow this.
Fire Style Fireball Jutsu!
Earth Style Mud Wall!
This is the real one!
Hand-to-hand combat's over.
The win goes to Kakashi.
Okay, make the Unison Sign.
Obito, your once-strong
will is still alive today
right next to me!
The only thing the
current me can do is
protect the current Naruto!
You...
No, everyone, actually
shall eventually just
end up like me.
Sasuke's a Rogue Shinobi.
Standard operating
procedure is to erase him.
You're going back to the
Leaf if I have to drag you!
But I'm not worthy of
being Hokage if I can't
even save a friend.
And I am going to become the
greatest Hokage of them all!
I'll never let
my comrades die!
No matter what happens!
Naruto, you never waver.
You're stronger than me
and have many things
that are solely yours.
This is all I
can do right now.
And that is...
...to protect this world.
My comrades...
...and the Obito
of the past...
...by killing...
...the current Obito!
It's over, Obito.
[laughter]
[coughing]
Very well, I'll let
you win this battle.
However I am not
conceding the war!
I thought I told you
I have no intention
of fighting a clone.
They give no resistance.
I respect the effort,
but it's pointless.
You're concentrating
too much power
in your real body.
So Madara, you too, were
holding back something.
Huh?
What is that?
Looks like that is of
no use to me anymore.
I had wanted to fight
Hashirama before I
became a Jinchuriki.
I guess I have no choice.
M- My body!
It's time to make him bring
me back with Rinne Rebirth!
[screaming]
That's--!
Obito...
Do you finally realize
that you are merely a
backup that I had
cultivated for my rebirth?
Are you saying that
you saved me, Gramps?
[chuckle]
Well, thank you.
It's too early to
thank me just yet.
And besides, I still
intend to have you
repay your debt to me.
It's time to have you
repay your debt right now.
[screaming]
He's being controlled
by Madara's chakra!
Is that the Six Paths'
Forbidden Rinne
Rebirth Jutsu?!
Madara!
He must not be allowed
to fully return to life!
Lads!
You're all closer!
Go stop the jutsu of the one
atop Ten Tails right now!
Okay!
Got- Sasuke!
I see...
So that's the
way it is, huh?
Is this the maximum
number I can muster
inside this barrier?
Tobirama!
Right!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I can only make
two of them?!
This is so
embarrassing.
We'll just have to make
do with what we have!
Predicting that those after
Obito won't be in time,
they're going to
attack me instead.
But they must realize
that clones aren't
enough to stop me.
Aoda!
That's enough!
Get going!
Yes, Lord Sasuke!
[chuckle]
You won't always be
like this either, right?
Don't give up.
Rin...
...you love her,
don't you?
We're both gonna
become Hokage.
Right, Obito?
Sensei...
Obito?!
So...
That was you?!
[gasps]
Well?
Which one?
[chuckle]
What a failure!
But oh well!
Did they succeed?!
All right!
That's Lord Fourth Hokage!
He teleported a
Shadow Clone.
Had he marked
the enemy already?
A Flying Raijin
marking never disappears.
I didn't teach you
that, did I, Obito?
If you were alive, I
would have wanted you
to become Hokage.
So why did you-?
That was anticlimactic...
So now all that's left to do
is seal the un-reborn Madara
and this war will be over.
Well, plus this giant thing.
What exactly makes
you think that the war
is over, my
fellow traitor?
[gasps]
No!
Dad!
Sasuke!
Go, Gamakichi!
All right!
What is going on?!
Is the Ten Tails changing
form again or something?
No, that's not
what's happening!
Obito repelled
Madara's manipulation
and he's been weaving the
signs necessary to do this
right from the beginning!
He's become...
Ten Tails' Jinchuriki!
Oh, man, I really want
to find out what happens!
But the next episode
will be a little breather.
It's an "Extra Edition!"
Pain and Itachi are
gonna appear again!
What's more, Deidara and
Pervy Sage show up and
cause a big ruckus in
the Leaf Village!
What kind of a
story is this, anyway?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Extra Edition:
The Directive to
Take the Nine Tails!"
Just what in the
world are you?!