[bird wings flapping]
[thwogg]
-Nnngh!
Aaugh!
[breathing heavily]
[zapping]
-Huahh!
[thwack]
[coughing]
-Nngh! [breathing heavily]
-Forgive me, Sasuke.
This is my reality.
Give me your light.
-Ahh!
[screams of anguish]
-Nngh.
Aaugh.
-I told you, Sasuke.
You don't possess the
Mangekyo Sharingan.
You'll never be able to win
against these eyes of mine.
[sighs]
[gasps]
-And now I'll take
the other one, too.
-Keh.
[growling] [roaring] Nngh.
Aaugh.
[breathing heavily]
-So that's the power
of the curse mark.
-Nngh.
[breathing heavily] Keh!
-This is the difference
in our strengths.
And the difference between
your eyes and mine.
[snakes hissing]
[kring]
[shattering]
-[breathing heavily] Nngh.
[thud]
-That ended quicker
than I expected.
Itachi has won this.
-How can you tell?
-Sasuke's caught
under the Tsukuyomi.
He's completely paralyzed.
Itachi can do whatever
he wants to him now.
[thunk]
-[gasps]
--[breathing heavily] You
broke through my Tsukuyomi?
[gasps]
-Oh my.
Sasuke was under a
Tsukuyomi, so why isn't he
down for the count?
-No.
He didn't get hit
with the Tsukuyomi.
He actually broke through it.
-What?
Someone who only has
an ordinary Sharingan
isn't supposed to be able to win
against the Mangekyo Sharingan.
-Ah, but the ordinary
Sharingan is still a weapon,
and a weapon can either
be strong or weak,
depending on the ability of
the person who is wielding it.
Someone's shuriken might be
taken down by a mere pebble,
if it's thrown by a master.
The difference is in the power,
the variance in strength.
It means that
Sasuke's skills far
exceed Itachi's expectations.
-Like I told you,
no matter how much
you use your eyes,
with all of my hatred
I'll turn fantasy into reality.
--[chuckling] Turn fantasy
into reality, huh?
Some strong words.
And let me throw them
right back at you now.
[theme music]
-Like I told you,
no matter how much
you use your eyes,
with all of my hatred
I'll turn fantasy into reality.
--[chuckling] Turn fantasy
into reality, huh?
Some strong words.
And let me throw them
right back to you now.
Just a few moments
ago, you so your eyes
gouged out during the Tsukuyomi.
Well, allow me to make
it that a reality.
--[gasping] The air around
Itachi has shifted!
-It seems he's finally
gotten down to business.
So now we might get to see
the Amaterasu in action.
-What?
The Amaterasu?
I can't wait to see it!
I'm so glad we came
to see this battle.
[clap]
-Continuing to use
genjutsu will lead nowhere.
Once Sasuke broke
through the Tsukuyomi,
the genjutsu battle became
completely pointless.
-Which means it's going to be
a direct ninjutsu slug-fest
from here on out.
-If the Mangekyo Sharingan
in Itachi's left eye
possesses the most
powerful genjutsu,
then his right one must
possess the most powerful
physical attack.
Amaterasu produces black
flames said to never extinguish
until they entirely
incinerate whatever
the caster has sighted.
-Is this it?
The Amaterasu?
-He wants to prevent
Itachi from weaving signs.
[whoosh]
[blades whirring]
-This is the Shadow
Shuriken Jutsu.
[zapping]
[wind rushing]
[cranking and reeling]
[clink]
-A rigged shuriken?
[clang]
[thwogg]
[kring]
-Huh?
-(TO HIMSELF) Ha.
Those last shuriken
did the trick.
[rip]
[clang]
-That's funny.
-What is it?
-It's just that
Itachi should have
been able to dodge
something like that easily.
-You feeling the backlash
from your Tsukuyomi?
Hmm.
Well, it's a nice
feeling for me.
-From the moment Sasuke
nullified the Tsukuyomi,
he seized control of
the flow of this battle,
and he slowed down Itachi's
movements even further.
You know, Sasuke might
actually win this thing.
-No.
It's still too early to tell.
[clap]
-Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
[blasting flames]
[gasps]
[zapping]
[blasting]
[flames blasting]
-Keh.
These wounds are nothing.
They won't slow me down at all.
-Ah!
We almost got caught up in that.
ITACHI AND SASUKE: Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
[flames blasting]
-Mmm.
Sasuke has the upper hand.
I really think he's
going pull it off.
Amaterasu.
-Ahh!
Here it is!
-Nngh!
[wind gusting]
-Incredible!
He put out fire with fire!
-With that jutsu, one need
only sight one's target,
and then the black flames
will burst into life,
right on point.
Those black flames cannot be
extinguished until they have
burned their target to ash, even
if that target happens to be
other flames.
[rushing wind]
-Aaugh!
[thud]
[flames blasting]
[labored breathing]
[footsteps]
-It seems Itachi is
the winner after all.
-He's put out the Amaterasu.
He's planning to
take Sasuke's eyes.
[fizzing]
-Hmm?
-He escaped underground?
[dripping]
-These wounds are nothing.
They won't slow me down at all.
Until he releases
the Amaterasu, I
can't use the
substitution jutsu.
[buzzing]
[rocks crumbling]
[splat]
-This is what I've
been waiting for!
[clap]
[coughs]
[labored breathing]
-Huh?
-Fire Style!
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
[earth cracking open]
[flames blasting]
[blasting]
[flames roaring]
-Hey, not bad!
-Oh no.
[whimpering]
[blasting]
[clay crumbling]
-[labored breathing] Nngh.
-Nngh.
[labored breathing]
That Amaterasu of yours.
It seems to have taken
quite a lot out of you.
-Nngh.
[thud]
-They're both totally exhausted.
They're probably out of chakra.
-So it appears.
-(TO HIMSELF) This will
probably be my last jutsu.
[thunder rolling]
-The Sharingan can
assess your chakra level.
So stop bluffing.
I can tell just by looking
that you're out of chakra.
You used the
Orochimaru-style substitution
jutsu to evade my Amaterasu.
It's a good trick to
deceive your opponent,
but it uses up an
enormous amount of chakra.
-That's right!
Because Sasuke
absorbed Orochimaru.
-Ah, so that's it.
[thunder cracking]
-Yeah, you're right.
I don't have any
more chakra left now.
I used up every bit of it in the
last Fire Style Jutsu attack.
[raindrops]
-However, do you really
believe that I would come here
to kill you and be unprepared?
[thunder clapping]
-It lasts only an instant, and
this jutsu cannot be blocked,
dodged, or evaded.
Just like the Amaterasu.
Now, Itachi.
You asked for it, so
here it is at last!
[lightning]
-I'll make your death a reality.
[thunder clapping]
[theme music]
WHITE ZESTU: Wow!
Am I glad we chose to
come see this battle!
I never imagined that
we'd get to witness
such an incredible fight.
BLACK ZETSU: Sasuke's
jutsu have been impressive,
but to think Itachi was hiding
a jutsu like that up his sleeve.
Looks like it will also come
with a heavy risk, though.
I wonder who will
win this battle.
MALE SPEAKER: Next
time, "The End."
WHITE ZETSU: Either
way, the next attack
will be the last
for one of them.