[growl]
[roar]
Huaagh!
[screaming]
Iruka... Are you all right?
Mom, what's the matter?
Dad, look, it's mom!
She's been hit!
[growling]
Why didn't you stay at
the shelter, Iruka?
Leave your mother to me.
You hurry up and get out
of here, now!!
No Dad! I'm not just going
to run away, and leave you
and Mom behind here!
I'm going to stay
and protect mom!
Don't you dare
push me, son!
It's a parent's duty
to protect their children!
[roar]
We have to protect the village!
We need to drive the Nine Tails
outside the village walls!
Right!
Buy me some time so I
can ready my jutsu.
Do not let up
the attack!
Yes, sir! Let's go!
[roar]
Yaagh!
Ninja Art!
Summoning!
Monkey King Enma!
Appear!
The Nine Tails, huh?
So the seal was broken?
[growling]
We'll drive it
from the Village.
With the Adamantine Nyoi!
Transformation! Gotcha!
Now Enma!
Let's go!
Right!
Extend!
[roar]
Good, it's been driven
out of the village!
Now keep at him,
one after another!
Minato. Where are you?
You're worthy of your
title, Fourth Hokage,
injuring me and separating
Nine Tails from me.
But he will be mine one day.
I shall rule this world!
There are plenty
of ways to do it.
Given his tone,
he's not joking around.
[growling]
[roar]
Yaagh!
Hold the attack, all of you!
Wait for the Fourth Hokage!
Iruka...
[gasp]
No let me go! My Mom
and Dad are both still
fighting back there!
[roar]
Listen up. You younger shinobi
stay away from Nine Tails.
What?! What
do you mean?
This is domestic trouble,
not a war against other
villages.
There's no need for all
of you to put your lives
on the line for this.
You've gotta
be kidding!
Stop it, Kurenai.
Just calm down!
You are also a shinobi.
You aren't going to live
forever, you know.
But, my daughter,
you're a woman, too.
Bequeath the Will of Fire
upon my future grandchildren!
Please make that your oath
to me your father.
For I do
believe in you.
[gasp]
This is bad.
He's going to
do that again?!
Lord Third Hokage!
Summoning Jutsu!
Is that?
It's the Fourth Hokage!
I shall rule
this world.
Kushina.
Forgive me.
Hold the Nine Tails!
Just for a little while longer!
I'll give it my best. But that's
going to be tough, even for me!
[Minato]
I'm going to need a lot
of chakra to transport
such a large object away.
Minato...
He transported the
Nine Tails with him?!
Over there!
[angry growl]
[panting]
I must erect a barrier now!
But I don't have much chakra.
I can still do it, Minato.
[growl]
[cough]
Kushina!
[cries]
[soft]
Woke you up, huh?
Sorry, Naruto.
Kushina.
I'll take the Nine Tails
with me to my death.
Because that way,
we can reduce the interval,
between now and when
he emerges again.
It's all I can manage now with
what little chakra I have left.
but I'll be able
to save you both.
So thank you, for
everything you've done.
[gasp]
[Minato]
Kushina... you're the one...
It was you who made me the
Fourth Hokage.
You made me a man!
And you made me this
baby's father!!
And yet...
Oh, Minato! Please don't
give me that sad look!
I... I'm happy!
Because you love me.
And what's more,
Today is the birthday
of our beautiful child!
But most of all,
if I were to
imagine me, alive,
and our future, the three
of us together as a family,
I can't really picture us...
as being anything...
but truly happy!
I guess, if I were
allowed just one regret,
I wish I could've
seen Naruto...
...all grown up.
I wish I could have seen that!
Kushina, there's no
need for you to die,
in order to kill
the Nine Tails.
Preserve what little
chakra you have, for your
reunion with Naruto.
Huh?
I'm going to seal the rest of
your chakra inside Naruto.
It'll be part of an
Eight Signed Seal.
And then I'll take the
Nine Tails with me.
[growling]
Since I'm not a Jinchuriki,
I'll have to use the
Reaper Death Seal.
You can't!
If you cast that,
then you'll...
And there's one other thing.
I'm only going to seal half
of the Nine Tails.
[growling]
It's physically impossible
to seal this much power.
But it's also
strategically unwise.
If you take the Nine
Tails with you, there
will be no Jinchuriki
until he reemerges.
This will upset the
balance of power between
the Tailed Beasts.
With the Reaper Death Seal,
we can at least seal away half
of the Nine Tails forever.
And, the other half
of the Nine Tails.
You know, perhaps,
It could be that you are
the Child of Prophecy!
Huh? The what?
In the future, terrible
things are likely to
befall the shinobi world.
The savior that will emerge
is the Child of Prophecy.
I'll seal it inside
Naruto with the
Eight Signed Seal!
[gasp]
I know what you're
going to say.
But remember what
Master Jiraiya said
about world upheaval.
And also, all of
the calamities that
would accompany it.
I've become convinced
of two things today.
First: that masked man who
attacked you will bring
catastrophe to the world.
And second: the one who will
stop him Is this child!
This infant,
whose godfather is
Master Jiraiya,
He will open up the
future as a Jinchuriki.
I know it.
Somehow, I'm sure of it.
But, Minato!
Reaper Death Seal!
[Minato]
Let's believe in him!
After all, this
child is our son!
Those signs.
Don't tell me!
Yes, it's the
Reaper Death Seal.
After I've completed this seal,
I'm going to seal your chakra
inside of Naruto, too.
You won't have much time,
but I want you to help him
try to control Nine Tails
power as a Jinchuriki.
But he's our son, Minato!
[Kushina]
...which is exactly why
I don't want him to bear
such a heavy burden!
And tell me...
Why use the
Reaper Death Seal?!
If it's just so I can meet
Naruto when he's grown up,
especially if it's only going to
be for a short time...
Then there's no need
for you to die!
I'd rather you stay with him...
and watch over him...
I just don't understand why
it has to be this way!
Why does Naruto have
to be sacrificed...
for the balance of
power among Tailed Beasts...
For his nation...
for his Village?
Why do you have
to sacrifice
yourself at all?!
Just for me?! Please!
To forsake one's nation,
and one's village,
is exactly the same as
forsaking one's own child.
Your very own homeland
was destroyed, so you
should know that.
A harsh life awaits
those without a land
to call their home.
Besides, our family,
Is shinobi.
Finally, even if I were
to live, I could never
be a substitute for you.
Huh?
You won't have much
time with him.
But there's something that
only you can tell Naruto.
Something that I just can't.
That's a
mother's role.
I'm not doing this just for you.
I'm doing it for Naruto!
I will die for my son.
It is my duty
as his father.
Rgh!
Lord Third!
What's wrong?!
It's no good.
We can't get
in any closer.
This barrier is preventing
the Nine Tails from escaping.
Seems the two of them are
planning to take care of the
Nine Tails all by themselves!
Damn you,
Fourth Hokage!
Seal!
[roar]
My body...
is going numb.
Can't believe how
heavy his chakra is.
[growling]
Damn you!
It is the Reaper
Death Seal after all.
I can't believe he used it!
The Nine Tails is
still alive, though!
Couldn't he seal
all of it away?
It appears
smaller, but...
All right, now for the
Eight Signed Seal.
I'll seal the rest of
the Nine Tails in Naruto.
[growl]
A Ritual Altar?
He's planning to
seal me up again!
Not inside that baby?!
[wheeze]
[coughs]
Kushina! Are you okay?
[big roar]
There you are!
[wet impact]
[Nine Tails]
[roar]
[Minato]
I said I was his father.
Dying for him
is my duty!
Yes, but I'm his mother.
it's mine, too.
There's a child
in there, too?!
Yes, and they
saved it!
[growl]
Why you!!
[labored breath]
I think this may be
the first time that
I've lost an argument.
I Guess it proves
just how serious you
are about doing this.
I thank you, Kushina.
Summoning Jutsu!
Yaagh!
The Nine Tails?!
And Lord Fourth, too!
What is going on here?!
Gerotora, I'll give
you the Sealing
Formula's key.
When I'm done, Take
it to Master Jiraiya
to store it.
So that's it.
Minato plans to make his own
child the Nine Tails' Jinchuriki
to save the village.
I confirm I received the key.
All right, I'm off now.
And now we're safe.
Kushina, I'm not going
to last much longer.
I'll start the Eight
Signed Seal, right now.
I still want to put some
of my chakra in Naruto.
We won't see him
for quite a while.
So let's tell him
what we want to say.
Naruto. Don't be a picky
eater. Just eat a lot so you
grow up big and strong.
And make sure that you
bathe every day and that
you stay warm, too.
Also, don't stay up too late.
Make sure you get
plenty of sleep.
Don't forget to make
friends as well.
You don't need a
ton of them, okay?
Just a few is fine.
As long as they're ones
that you can really trust.
And... heh...
Your mom wasn't
very good at this;
make sure you study hard
and learn your ninjutsu.
Always remember:
everyone is good at
some things and not so
good at others.
so even if something
doesn't go well, don't
get depressed, okay?
When you're at the Academy,
respect your teachers and
the upperclassmen.
Oh! Now, this
is important.
Regarding the Three
Prohibitions of the shinobi.
Be extra careful about
lending and borrowing money.
Take your pay.
Put it in a
savings account.
No alcohol, not
until you're of age!
Too much sake is bad for
you, so practice moderation.
And, another Prohibition,
is women.
Remember, I am one,
So I don't know too
much about it.
Keep in mind, that this world
is made up of men and women.
And so at some point,
you'll notice girls,
and that's normal.
Just be careful, don't
fall for the bad ones.
Just go out there and find
someone who's like me!
Oh, uh,
that reminds me.
speaking of the Three
Prohibitions, you should be
wary of Jiraiya Sensei ya know.
[heavy breathing]
Naruto, I'm sorry to say,
there will be plenty
of hardships and
painful times ahead.
Just be true to yourself.
Make sure to have dreams,
and the confidence to make
those dreams come true!
Oh, Naruto... There's so much...
Oh, so much more.
There are so many things I wish
I had time to pass on to you.
So much more I want to tell you!
I wish I could stay
with you longer...
I love you!
Minato, I'm sorry!
I used up your time!
No, it's all right.
Naruto, my
words to you.
Well, I guess your
talkative mom,
said it all.
[softly]
Eight Signed Seal!
I'm sorry, for making
you the Nine Tails'
vessel, Naruto.
For making you bear what should
have been our burden to carry.
For not being able to
stand by your side.
And for not being there
to give you love.
You don't have to apologize.
Yeah, sure, in the past, I went
through a lot as a Jinchuriki.
But I would never blame
you or Dad for that.
[gasp]
So, yeah... I never
really had parents...
or felt a parents' love.
After all, you and dad
weren't around.
But still, I had a feeling.
And besides, now I know
it for sure. Because you
and Dad both sacrificed
yourselves just for me.
So now I realize, there's more
than Nine Tails inside me;
there's your love, too!
That makes me really happy!
Mom and Dad,
I'm glad I'm your kid!
[Kushina]
Minato, did you hear that??
Our hopes really did get
through to reach our son!
Naruto...
Thank you so much for
letting me become a mother.
And thank you for letting
Minato become a father.
Thank you for
being born to us!
Thank you...
...so much.
Thank you!
[Aoba]
Naruto faced and defeated
his true self here.
Well, Guy? Why don't you
try it out for yourself!
[Guy]
Don't be foolish!
We have to help
Naruto first!
[Aoba]
Are you just too afraid
to face your true self?
[Guy]
What?! Okay then,
I'll try it out!
[Aoba]
I have a feeling your true
self isn't even human!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Battle in Paradise! The Odd
Beast vs. The Monster!
[Guy]
That thing is supposed
to be my true self?!