[Messenger]
Captain Mifune! We've just
received word from HQ!
The enemy force appears to
be marching right past us,
deep underground!
The shinobi in the
Sensory Unit weren't
able to detect them?
That can only mean that
they must not be human.
Well then, considering
our elongated
deployment formation,
we'll have to mobilize
a few of the platoons.
Take some from our Fifth
Company closest to Kitsuchi's
Second Company and send them
over as reinforcements.
And hurry!
I'll keep them coming!
The flare, now!!
Okay!
A red flare.
It's the Commando Unit.
Let's go!
Mm.
Are you all right after that,
Master Zabuza?
Looks like you
wasted a jutsu,
Haku.
This Reanimation Jutsu.
We can't die;
we're already dead.
I don't like this jutsu..
That was a good catch, Haku.
That species of giant
bird really does fly
in pairs like that.
They work together
to catch their prey.
However, that's only in
winter when raising young.
Plus there's that beacon
that looks like a cloud.
I have no doubt that the enemy
who attacked us is up there.
Please leave them to me.
Huh?
Snow?
Cold air?
Huh?
Secret Jutsu:
Crystal Ice Mirrors!
Waagh!
Yahhhh!
[groans]
Wait...
Isn't that...?
What is this? What's going on?
They're just children!
Our bodies are immortal now.
A mutual strike will be
sufficient.
Damn it! All of our
enemies are shinobi who
possess Kekkei Genkai!
Well, except me.
We don't have anything
personal against any of you.
But we're not in
control of our
actions right now.
Here they come!
Huh?
[Haku]
Kakashi?!
"An Old Nemesis Returns"
[Sai]
Kakashi!
You're a lifesaver!
Don't start celebrating yet.
All of these guys are going to
be difficult shinobi to defeat.
I knew we'd have to fight,
but I never imagined it would
be against you, Kakashi.
Hrm.
Lightning Blade!
That day back on the bridge,
you were supposed to finish
me off and send me to hell.
When I came to, I was in
the same place as Haku.
It seems that this is
neither heaven nor hell.
This is the world of the living.
You shouldn't be here. You're
under the Reanimation Jutsu.
The... Reanimation Jutsu?
That's right.
The Akatsuki brought
you back from the
world of the dead.
What? They know
each other?
Wait for Captain
Kakashi's signal.
Zabuza. Haku.
Oh! You've grown
up, Kakashi's
little kunoichi.
And is the other
lad doing well?
Ah!
Yes.
Uhhn.
[Naruto] [half asleep]
Who the heck are you?
[Naruto]
Wait, is this it? Is this one
of the ones I should pick?
[Haku]
Yes.
That's a medicinal
herb, huh?
Thank you again
for helping me.
You start work
early, huh, sis?
I like the calm of the
morning. I didn't think
I'd find someone sleeping.
I'm training!
I'm developing skills
so I can get stronger!
Mm?
To me, you seem
pretty strong now,
isn't that enough?
No, no, I need to get
stronger and stronger!
I have to keep practicing!
How so?
Why's it so important?
So I can become the
very best ninja in my
whole entire village!
And then everyone will know
who I am and respect me!
There's also a certain person,
a kid, that I have to prove
something to.
So are you doing it for
this "certain person",
Or are you doing
all this training
for yourself?
Huh?
[chuckle]
Why are you laughing,
what's so funny!?
Tell me, is there anyone
who is precious to you?
Huh?
So you see, when a person
has something precious
they want to protect,
that's when they
become genuinely strong.
Hmm?
Hmm...
Yeah! I hear you.
I know exactly what
you're saying!
Huh?
You will get strong.
And we will meet again.
Hm!
[Zabuza]
He defeated us.
He must be all grown up now.
And probably famous too.
Yeah, they named that
bridge after him:
the Great Naruto Bridge.
To everyone in our
village, he's a hero.
They call him the kid who
makes miracles happen.
[giggle]
Hmm?
Thanks to both of you,
Naruto was able to
find his Ninja Way.
He pledged to follow it at your
graves. He's quite the splendid
shinobi now. And he's grown
into a fine young man, too.
Then, he will become
even stronger.
[Kabuto]
Have you reminisced enough?
Because now we need to get to
work. It's time to get serious!
Power's
flowing
into me!
The main act starts now!
Kakashi...
You must...
stop us.
Retreat!
Kakashi...
Aren't those two...
Yeah. There's
no mistake.
The Demon Zabuza Momochi!
And Haku of the Ice Style!
Kakashi Sensei!
I am your opponent, Naruto!
Haku!
Let's finish this. Now!
I wanted to see your face
when you realize that your
Sharingan's worthless.
Ninja Art: Hidden Mist Jutsu!
Too late!
This is his Silent Killing,
which brings down a foe
only with sound.
Why, Zabuza?! You were known as
the Demon of the Hidden Mist!
How could you stoop so low
as to become a hired thug?!
Stop kidding yourself!
Don't be so naïve!
In this shinobi world,
the choices are either
to use or be used!
Shinobi like us are
merely tools, weapons
in the hands of others.
We cannot afford to
stand on principles!
A weak ninja has no
place at all in
this world of ours.
Zabuza. Why
that guy,
anyway?!
I live only to protect
and serve him.
Do you know what it's
like to feel unwanted?
Do you?
Zabuza. He came along and
made me necessary again.
Nh!
When I grew into my powers,
my father tried to kill me.
After years of the horrors
of civil war, nearly all
of the people who still
lived in my homeland,
had come to harbor great fear
and hatred against anyone who
carried the Kekkei Genkai
in their blood.
And back then, at that time,
I thought of myself thusly:
In the entire world, no one
needed me. I was unnecessary.
[gasp]
Just like... me!
But Zabuza. When he looked
at me, his eyes weren't
full of hate or fear.
He made me necessary again.
I was happy.
[Young Haku]
I am yours, Zabuza.
Think of me as a weapon
to be kept at your side
and used as you see fit.
But that isn't what
it's all about!
And there are other ways of
showing strength than just by
beating someone in battle.
Nh... My mind's...
growing foggy.
(disoriented reax) Damn...
The inside of my head,
it- it's burning!
Dgh!
That aura.
So that's the
Demon Zabuza!
And that
Ice Style
child!
Prepare yourselves!
Don't let your
guard down, Guy.
He is unparalleled
at silent killing.
Please, Kakashi.
I'm begging you now.
You must stop us once again.
You must!
My dream was always to be an
instrument of Master Zabuza's,
a weapon for him to use.
And to die
protecting him.
However, The fact
that Master Zabuza is
now under this jutsu,
means that not only did I
fail to protect him from
you that day, long ago,
But also means, that I
can't protect him now.
And worse, I can't even
do his bidding anymore!
No. you did indeed
protect Zabuza.
[Kakashi]
No. you did indeed
protect Zabuza.
He died from a
different cause. Plus,
Zabuza never thought that
you were merely a tool.
Uh!
Kakashi. just shut
your mouth, already.
Naruto. He dug deep
into Zabuza's heart and
carved out the truth.
Hmpf. He talked big,
and this is how he
ends up, huh?
Turns out you're
just a weakling!
Haku!
You scum!
Get away!
Stop!
Use your head.
We're outnumbered!
But...
Are you really gonna
let him do that?!
Be quiet, you fool;
Haku's dead, what
does it matter?
Gato's right; he died
'cause he was weak.
What?! How can
you say that?!
He saved you!
How can you let him
be treated that way?!
You don't understand
the Way of Shinobi.
I merely used him,
just as Gato used me.
I thought I'd told you:
in the shinobi world,
it's either use or be used.
We Shinobi are
tools, mere weapons.
The loss of his strength
and skill, yes, that
means something to me.
But the boy? Nothing.
If you really mean that,
you're just a rat.
Naruto, stop!
Why you ungrateful...
After all he did
for you?!
Haku lived for you!
Tell me, is there anyone
who is precious to you?
You were the most
important thing to him!
So you see, when a person
has something precious
they want to protect,
that is when they become
genuinely strong.
He meant nothing? He seriously
meant nothing at all to you?!
Really?! He gave
everything for you, and
you felt nothing for him?!
But I will do anything to see
that his dream is fulfilled.
Even become Shinobi if I must.
And if I become stronger, does
that mean, I'll become as
cold-hearted as you are?
He threw his life away.
For you and your dream!
You never let him have
a dream of his own.
And you just toss him
aside like he was nothing.
A broken tool.
that's so wrong,
so wrong!
Kid...
That's enough. You talk
too much, you know that?
While he fought you,
his heart was breaking.
You see, Haku was always
too soft and too kind.
I've known that all along.
I'm glad he fought you
in the end.
And kid,
it's as you said.
Even Shinobi are human.
No matter how hard we
try to escape that fact,
We always fail.
Zabuza, you...
You guys stay out of this.
This fight is for me alone!
Raaaaggh!
Snowing, at this time of year?
Haku?
Is that you weeping?
You were always at my side.
The least I can do is to
be beside you at the end.
I know it cannot be,
but I wish that I could go
to where you have gone.
How I wish.
You never know, Zabuza.
Maybe you will join him there.
Zabuza and Haku, huh?
They're both being
quite stubborn.
I can't believe they
still aren't bound.
[chuckle]
But have no fear, I'll make
you mere killer puppets soon!
Because both of
you are MY tools!
Kakashi. Don't
hesitate or hold back.
Use whatever means
necessary... to stop me.
Remember, I
already died once.
And, I died human!
Yes. I know.
Master Zabuza.
I thank you.
Here they come!
Captain Kakashi!
That Hidden Stone
shinobi is Gari.
Master of Explosion Style
Kekkei Genkai and, like
Deidara, a former member
of the Demolitions Unit!
[Maki]
And that woman is Pakura,
a Scorch Style Kekkei Genkai
master from the Hidden Sand.
Be careful!
All Kekkei Genkai users, huh?
Ninja Art: Hidden Mist Jutsu.
Assemble battle groups
with sensory type ninja
at the center!
The other members cover
twelve, three, six, and
nine o'clock positions
in Manji Formation!
Zabuza can locate targets
using sound only!
[Guy]
The mist is getting thicker.
Visibility is low.
It is okay! Do not be
afraid, Sakura!
Because I will protect
you with my life!
Last time he attacked from
this formation's blind spot,
the center.
So watch your
backs, everyone!
Leave it to me!
Huh? Oh. Yes! Right!
Mist, and then, cold air?
Augghh!
Aggh!
It's begun!
It's different than the
last time, after all.
I can bind them so much
more tightly, now that I
have Orochimaru's chakra.
Though it's overwriting my
personal control tags.
However, I deliberately
kept their emotions
intact to psychologically
shake up the enemy.
That left the binding weaker, so
their souls could rebel against
me, which allowed them to die.
This time, I will
suppress their emotion.
Right now, I don't know how many
pawns I can actually affect.
Well, at least this war
will show me my limits.
As for the rest of the pawns,
I'll bind them to the point
where they follow orders, and
leave them to their own devices.
I think it'll be to my
advantage to let some
of them retain emotion.
[explosion]
[gasp]
He's mummified!
This jutsu...
Here she comes!
Scorch Style!
Super Steam Kill!
My insides!
They're burning!
Explosion Style!
Land Mine Fist!
No way! That guy
just blew up Tajiki!
You bastard!
[Guy & Lee]
Leaf Hurricane Whirlwinds!
Master Guy!
Comrades die on
the battlefield!
You must prepare
yourself for that fact!
If you lose focus, then
you'll cause more to die!
Don't allow their
deaths to be in vain!
You got that, newbie?!
Yes! Right!
[pain]
Hnggh!
It's okay. Hang on.
I'm beginning to understand
the enemy's strategy.
But now it's gonna
be my turn!
[chuckle] I'm not so naïve
as to allow the enemy time
to catch their breath.
[both]
Summoning Jutsu!
Huh?
This is unbelievable.
No way!
Is that?!
[Kakashi]
Former members of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist!
[Naruto]
It was something that
Haku said to me.
He told me that when people
are protecting something
that's precious to them,
that's when they can
become genuinely stronger.
[Kakashi]
I see. And you agree
with him, do you?
[Naruto]
You bet! After watching Haku
with Zabuza, I know he's right!
[Kakashi]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The First and Last Opponent.
[Naruto]
I kinda liked those guys!