-Lady Tsunade.
The defense barrier and
the reanimation jutsu
have been defeated, and the
area around the main gate
is beginning to
return to normal.
Furthermore, the lightning
jutsu that Asuma spoke about
in his report, the
one that threatened
to incinerate the
village in an instant,
has been disabled before
it could be activated.
-Very well, then.
What's that?
That red light?
[groaning]
-Sora!
[theme music]
-What is it, Asuma-sensei?
What's happening to him?
-I don't know.
[laughter]
-That's right, Sora.
Get angry.
Get angry!
Channel all that
anger into real power.
Use your hate to smash
the people of the Leaf.
To crush them into dust.
-Stop saying that.
I'll never do these
things you want me to do.
I wasn't brought into
this world for that.
-Of course you were!
Your life's purpose
is to serve the cause
of unifying the Land of Fire.
And the time has
finally come when
your powers are required, Sora.
-I don't understand
a word of this.
What's this guy talking about?
-Wait a minute.
-Asuma!
-Kazuma!
-It is you.
But it can't be.
[laughter]
-Asuma-sensei.
Tell me, what is it?
Do you know this guy?
-I do.
He was one of the
Guardian Shinobi 12.
-Well, whatever.
I don't care who you are.
What did you do to Sora?
-I just made use of this
scraps you left behind.
That's all.
-What did you say?
-You see, Sora is
a lot like you.
-No!
Stop!
[screaming]
-Sora!
-Naruto!
-What is this?
What is this pain?
Is it true, then?
Am I really turning into
the-- the Nine Tails?
-But how?
How on earth did
you do it to him?
-Heh, heh, heh.
You should know
about it far better
than I. Have you forgotten the
Nine Tails' attack on the Leaf
that ended with the
Nine Tails being sealed
in the body of an infant, at
the cost of the Fourth Hokage's
life?
This meant the Leaf possessed
the power of the Nine Tailed
Fox.
Not wanting to be outdone,
we seized the opportunity.
We gathered up all
the scattered remnants
of the chakra left behind
after the Nine Tail's rampage.
We nurtured it, and
then, five years later,
implanted it in Sora.
-Monster!
But Sora is your own--
-Yes.
What of it?
Were we to sit by
while the Leaf gained
such an advantage in power?
No.
We needed to find
such power ourselves,
in order to protect our king.
Is that so wrong?
-Naruto, what are you--
-I knew it.
That's right.
All along.
Yeah, I knew it.
And yet I-- that
voice-- I knew it
had to be Sora's
voice, crying out.
So why?
Why didn't I do anything
about it back then?
After all, I was the one,
the only one who could really
understand the pain
behind those cries.
It was the same back
at the temple, too.
Eyes all around
him, watching him.
Those cold, hateful eyes.
Silently saying, go away.
Get out of here.
It was the same for me.
I know what it's like.
I felt those same
eyes, watch me.
-Naruto.
-Grown ups' eyes, with stares
that stab you like daggers.
Those eyes.
I know those eyes really well.
-What does all of
that matter now?
-Eyes like those,
looking at us like
we're not human, but freaks
that belong in a cage.
And all the time, you're
trying to exploit us
for your own twisted ends!
It was the same way with Gaara.
You people-- don't you ever
stop to think how we might feel?
And now Sora.
Sora.
Who gave you the right to put
that monster inside of him?
Why?
Why did you have
to do that to Sora?
-Enough of this.
-Naruto!
-Sora.
-Stay away from me!
All of you, stay away from me.
It won't work anymore.
I won't be fooled by you.
Killing my father, and then
thinking you can be my friend?
And all your talk of
my special powers.
You tricked me!
-Sora.
-I told you, stay away!
No matter what you say,
you're still just another one
of the Leaf, aren't you?
I can't trust you!
-Wait.
What's happening now?
[screaming]
-Wait a minute.
What's going on?
This is impossible.
Why is Sora-- That's
the Nine Tails Cloak.
-Can it be?
His cells are
actually becoming one
with the cells of
the Nine Tails.
[screaming]
-What is this?
-Something terrible
has been set in motion.
-Unlike the case
with your Jinchuriki,
the Nine Tails' chakra is
too powerful for Sora's body.
For the past 10 years, I've
had to maintain the balance
by suppressing the chakra
with a sealing juts.
But now, the seal
has been released
and the balance has been lost,
with the inevitable result
that Sora's body is
being taken over.
Once the ninth tail appears,
he'll no longer be Sora at all.
Our simulated Nine Tails will
have become the real thing.
-Why, you--
-That's right.
I forgeit my body to the Fox.
And I do it gladly!
-Sora--
-A small price to pay for
the power to smash the world.
-Stop this!
Sora!
-Wood Style!
Dome Wall!
SAKURA: Naruto?
-It's Sakura.
-Naruto!
-Asuma.
-Captain Yamato.
-What on earth was
that red light we saw?
Is that-- it looks like--
-No doubt about it.
It's the Nine Tails cloak.
-Not only that, it's Sora.
-What did you say?
-Good.
Well done, Sora.
Show them more.
Give them a taste
of your real power.
-Fight it, Sora.
Fight it!
Don't let it out!
-Why don't you shut up?
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Naruto!
-Where ya been, Shikamaru?
-You're sure about this, then?
-Is Akamaru's nose
or mine ever wrong?
It's not just Sora out there.
Asuma-sensei and Naruto
are with them as well.
And there's the trace
of another scent.
Someone not from the village.
-The enemy?
What in the world was that?
-Watch out!
Naruto, are you all right?
-Yeah.
-That was a little too close.
-Do I really have
to do everything?
-You fight me now, Kazuma.
-Hey, Captain Yamato?
Can't you control that
Nine Tails chakra,
like you did with
me on the bridge?
-I was able to restrain the
chakra in you because you're
wearing the necklace
of the First Hokage.
I can't do that with
Sora, because he's not.
[screaming]
-Sora, no!
-No?
It's still like that, huh?
You never wanted
me, or needed me!
-It was never like that!
We just don't want you
to let that power loose.
We can't let you do it!
-And why is that?
Only because I'm
the one who has it?
This power you fear so much
is the only thing I trust now.
-Sora.
-At last, I'll have
revenge on everyone
who ever made me an outcast!
-Naruto?
-I'm so tired of this power.
Of so many people
getting hurt by it.
[groaning]
-Not that long ago, I even
hurt Sakura with it once.
-The person who injured
Sakura, it was you, Naruto.
If you continue to
rely on its power,
not only will you
hurt yourself, Naruto,
you'll be endangering the lives
of those around you, as well.
-And that's why I
can't let you do it.
I can't let you hurt anyone
else with this power of ours!
-What do you mean, ours?
You don't know the
first thing about it!
-I know everything about it!
You really didn't know that
the Nine Tails within you
was created from the
Nine Tails within me?
-Within you?
What are you saying?
-That I'm the Jinchuriki.
-What are you talking about?
No.
-Sora--
-No.
Stay back.
All your words--
you can't trick me.
You won't trick me!
-Shadow Possession
Jutsu complete.
-Shikamaru.
Choji.
-Ino!
-They're here.
-What's this?
More friends come to save you?
-Go for it, Choji.
-Right.
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Both hands!
-Get off!
Get off me!
-Yeah!
He got him!
-Now he won't be
able to get away.
-It can't be right.
Doesn't make sense.
If you've really got the
Nine Tails inside you,
how can you have
so many friends?
You should be an outcast.
Why aren't you alone?
Like I've been?
Like I've been all these years?
-It was the same with me, too.
Once.
When I was little, for the
most part I was left on my own.
But even then, you see, I didn't
have the time to be lonely.
I was too busy getting
people to notice me.
And it finally worked.
Yep.
I made friends like these.
Good friends.
-I have no friends.
I have no friends at all.
-You're wrong.
I'm-- I mean, all of
us are your friends.
-Huh?
[groaning]
-Too hot!
-Choji!
Ino!
-Right, I'm on it.
Ninja Art, Mind Transfer Jutsu!
-Did she do it?
[scream]
-What is it?
-Are you all right?
-Ino!
What happened with
the mind transfer?
-There was-- there was no human
consciousness left in him.
-What?
-I'm afraid I've
hit the wall, too.
[growling]
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
The third tail.
[theme music]
SAKURA: Captain Yamato,
something's wrong with Naruto.
YAMATO: Don't tell
me his Nine Tails
chakra is starting
to emerge, too?
SAKURA: Oh, no.
YAMATO: That's all we need,
him going on the rampage again.
SAKURA: But how can
this be happening?
He's still wearing the First
Hokage's necklace, isn't he?
YAMATO: Something's
different this time.
The necklace isn't helping.
Blast!
What's going on?
My jutsu won't work!
NARUTO: Next time, Resonance.