-Eh!
Ah, Zetsu.
-So it's done.
Have you finished your
long-winded ritual?
--[grunts] Aw, don't tell me,
you're going to start now, too?
I'm surrounded by blasphemers
and ignorant heathens.
-Sorrow begets solitude.
The only thing you can
have faith in yourself.
KAKUZU: You're wrong.
The only thing you can
have faith in is money.
-There you go again.
This side job of yours
has made us fall behind
in our Jinchuriki hunt.
And that's not all.
-Listen, I only
teamed up with you
because you said
religion was profitable.
As holder of the
Akatsuki's purse strings,
I'm the one who
should be complaining.
-Money is indeed important.
More important is that
you two stop wasting time
and get on with the hunt.
Leave the Two Tails to me.
-You sure you're ready for this?
You just got out of
the hospital yesterday.
-Nah, that whole thing was
blown out of proportion.
-So you're good to go.
Full speed ahead, right?
That's what you'd like
to think, at least.
But first, let's
go over the basics.
-Forget that!
Come on!
Let's skip to the part where I
work on my new, killer jutsu!
-Mm.
-You know, the super secret,
deluxe, special Naruto Uzumaki
Rasengan, or
whatever it's called.
-Uh.
-Oh boy.
-Before that, let's review
the change in chakra nature,
all right?
Fire, Water, Wind,
Lightning, and Earth
are the five chakra natures.
And in your case--
-I know.
I've got a wind chakra nature.
-OK.
Just show us you remember
what we've done so far.
-Right.
Multi-shadow Clone Jutsu!
Uh!
[exhales]
OK.
Finely and sharply,
that's the key!
Uh!
[all clones copying]
Huh? (ALL TOGETHER) We did it!
Well?
What do you think
Kakashi-sensei?
Not bad, huh?
Uh, (WEAKLY) I think.
-Good grief.
He's always pushing it,
even when he's not 100%.
-The multi-shadow
clones were helpful
before as a way of
accelerating the training time,
but there's no need for
him to knock himself
out using them now.
KAKASHI: Naruto likes to
do things in a big way.
[theme music]
-How much farther is this place?
KAKUZU: We're almost there.
-[scoffs] Yeah, right.
That's what you keep
saying, but-- Uh.
You're kidding!
More climbing?
There'd better be a
Jinchuriki at the end of this,
because if there's
not, I'll get mad.
And you know what
happens when I get--
KAKUZU: I don't give
a damn what happens.
And if you don't stop
whining like a spoiled brat,
I'll kill you.
-Oh, come on.
What's that about?
You trying to scare me or what?
[huffs] You really are an
antisocial jerk, you know that?
-So putting aside any
variables that might arise,
you feel this is the best
assessment of the situation?
SHIZUNE: Yes.
TSUNADE: Put it all in order
within two or three days
and have it ready
for distribution.
I'm counting on you.
-Understood, M'lady.
-(THINKING) Sorry to put
you through this, Shizune.
But we can't just sit
around and do nothing.
KAKASHI: Welcome back.
-Was I-- Did I
fall asleep again?
KAKASHI: You need your rest.
That multi-shadow clone
method of training
can really wear
you out, can't it?
Why don't we resume after
you've rested a bit more.
-What'll the next step be?
-The next step?
The next step will be
to cut that waterfall.
-Wh-what?
-Press your hands to the
water and cut the flow
by slamming it with wind chakra.
-C-cut the flow?
But it's a waterfall!
-That's right.
And that means in
order to be successful,
you'll need a large amount
of change in chakra nature.
KAKASHI: If you're
able to pull it off,
it's something you'll always
be able to use in battle.
-Uh.
Kakashi-sensei, are you guys
saying if I can pull this off,
I'll have achieved my first
change in chakra nature?
-Mm-hm.
-Excellent!
So I'm getting even
better than I thought!
-(THINKING) I never could have
imagined that clumsy little
Naruto would achieve change
in chakra nature so quickly.
This training method
was a brilliant success,
if I do say so myself.
-OK.
Break time's over.
Let's get back to training!
YAMATO: Wood-style Jutsu!
KAKASHI: That will be
your training area.
-Got it!
KAKASHI: Whoa!
Not so fast.
-Huh? Why?
What is it?
KAKASHI: You're going to
need Yamato's chakra control
at all times during
this exercise.
He's in your hands, Yamato.
-Right.
Hup!
Ah, ho!
I'm ready when you are, Naruto.
-Multi-shadow Clone Jutsu!
(THINKING) I've got to form
a mental picture of the wind chakra.
-Now listen up.
To activate it, imagine
your chakra splitting in two
and grinding against each other.
-Grinding them?
-Just as if you were
finely sharpening
the blade between the two
halves of your chakra.
-Sharpening the blade
between the two halves, huh?
-Exactly.
Finely and sharply,
that's the trick.
-Finely and sharply!
OK. Let's do it.
Right!
Hup!
Ugh!
What is going on here?
Cut the flow?
We can't even budge it.
Come on.
Let's try again!
All right.
Hup!
-As we expected, this will
probably take a while, huh?
-Nothing we can
do but be patient.
-Hup!
Hup!
-I think that's
Everything I need.
Yup.
Now I can make some of my own
special Sakura food pills.
If I know Naruto and the
way he pushes himself,
he's going to need them.
(THINKING) That idiot.
He doesn't understand that
willpower is enough anymore.
If he's not physically
ready for it,
this training could
have the reverse effect
of what's intended.
On top of that, because
of his special abilities,
he's always in danger of
pushing it to the limit anyway.
I've just got to do
whatever I can to help him.
-Hup!
Hup!
[panting]
[gasps] Ahh!
Huh!
Hup!
Darn it.
Darn it!
Hup!
-(THINKING) He'll probably start
losing his patience right about
now.
HIDAN: [sighs] A temple?
Are you sure this
is the right place?
KAKUZU: We'll see this
is no ordinary temple,
so the odds are good.
-What's going on?
-Someone has broken through
the iron wall's seal.
Alert Lord Chiriku!
HIDAN: These guys don't
look like they'd willingly
convert to the way of Jashin.
Nope. No converts here.
-Look at those robes!
Could it be that
these two are--?
-There can be no doubt.
They're from the Akatsuki.
MONK: Intruders!
CHIRIKU: Who are they?
MONK: Members of the
Akatsuki, My Lord!
-(THINKING) I knew they'd
come calling someday.
But--
All right.
I will go.
Tell the others to stand by.
-Uh.
-Huh?
Ah.
Here goes another
highly virtuous fellow.
KAKUZU: This one's more
than just virtuous.
According to our bingo book,
his head's worth 30 million.
-Heh.
Hey, we're not doing this
just for the bounty, are we?
Killing a monk for
worldly gain is
a ticket to
damnation, my friend.
-Well, after all, they say that
money talks, wherever you go.
-I don't know what your business
is here, but turn around
and keep moving.
-You wont kill us without
a cause is that it?
Charming.
However, that's not
one of my beliefs.
-This fire temple is the
most famous Shinobi temple
in the Land of Fire.
They say all it's monks
wield a special power known
as the Gift of the Sages,
especially this one
worth 30 million.
He's an elite ninja who was once
one of the Guardian Shinobi 12
that protect the ruler
of the Land of Fire.
The proof is there
on his waistcloth.
The Fire emblem.
-Really?
Guardian Shinobi, huh?
KAKUZU: Take care
Hidan, or you'll die.
-Give me a break.
Not that again.
Shut up, Kakuzu.
Move it!
-Wh-what the devil is that?
-I don't care what it is.
Just keep pressing the attack!
[bodily impacts and blows]
-Now you're mine!
[body impacts and blows]
[thud]
MONK: Yes!
He did it!
[monks cheering]
-I will grant you a funeral.
-(THINKING) I couldn't
bear having another
religion's funeral
rites spoken over me.
Jashin would surely punish me.
Now I'm mad.
Hey, Kakuzu.
Since this one's
no Jinchuriki, I
can go ahead and obey
Jashin's commandments, right?
-Do what you like with him.
But remember, his head is
worth 30 million to me.
So don't go overboard.
I want him recognizable.
-Trading a human
being's life for money.
That's no way for
people to behave.
(ANGRY) Disgusting!
Just stay out of it, Kakuzu.
(YELLING) Leave this one to me!
Yah!
[metallic clang]
-Chiriku of the Fire
Temple will never
be defeated by the likes of you!
Raigo!
Thousand Hand Strike!
Yah!
-Well, I guess there
weren't any Jinchuriki hosts
to be found here after all.
When I'm done with
my prayers, let's
move on to our next thing.
KAKUZU: No.
I'm taking him to the
collection office.
I want the bounty.
Money comes first.
-Huh?
You know something?
In case you hadn't
noticed, you're
really beginning to irritate me.
-(THINKING) I must
inform the Leaf Village.
HIDAN: Great.
So you're saying more delays?
-The Land of Fire is vast.
We are going to take our time.
-Fine.
But like I've always
said, if we fall behind,
it's because of you!
Damn it, that hurts.
Ah!
Uh!
Will you wait for me?
Hold on!
NARUTO: Kakashi-sensei!
Hey, maybe, unh, maybe I
need more shadow clones, huh?
KAKASHI: What you
need is to transform
a massive amount of chakra into
wind to cut that waterfall.
Make too many clones,
and each one's chakra
will be that much weaker.
Besides, that waterfall's barely
wide enough for the 10 of you.
-Ah, come on, Kakashi-sensei.
[clones all protest]
There's got to be
a trick to this.
Are you going to teach me, or do
I have to stay up here forever?
KAKASHI: You're not
storing the chakra
you create inside
yourself long enough.
Take more time,
be more thorough.
-But if it takes that long, what
use is it on the battlefield?
-You're still in
training, Naruto.
Don't worry about
the battlefield.
Once you get used to
it, it'll flow faster.
-Yeah, but--
-Oh, for crying out--
Listen, the change in nature
usually takes years to perfect.
Even leaf-cutting normally
takes six months, at least.
YAMATO: You mastered
it in only a few hours.
-Mm?
-You don't need to rush.
You're progressing much
faster than we expected.
KAKASHI: Even Sasuke, when
I taught him the Chidori,
took quite a few days to achieve
the lightning change of nature.
-That's just it.
Sasuke's the one I
want to catch up with!
KAKASHI: OK.
Tenzo.
[whispers]
-[soft laugh] Very well.
[clones panicking]
[thundering roar]
[tree trunks crunching]
-Hah, huh huh.
-Wow.
That was tough even
for you, wasn't it?
-No, not at all.
[coughing] It was nothing.
[coughs] I'm fine.
[coughs again]
-(THINKING) That was tough.
How's that, Naruto?
Now you've got nothing
to gripe about.
--[laughs hysterically]
Multi-shadow Clone Jutsu!
[ending theme music]
TSUNADE: What?
Attacked?
The Fire Temple?
SHIZUNE: It must have
been the Akatsuki again.
They're probably
searching every location
that might hold a Jinchuriki.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): So
they're here at last.
We'll see they never
leave the Land of Fire.
Alert all 20 newly-formed teams.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Yes, M'lady.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): I'd like
to find out what they're after,
but they're dangerous.
If they can't be
taken alive, so be it.
Go!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Under the Starry Sky"!