Before he died...
Jiraiya told me to store
myself inside Naruto.
Have you lost your mind?!
You're well aware that
the key that corresponds
to Naruto's Eight-Signed
Seal is transcribed on my
belly!
Each and every year, the
Fourth Hokage's seal
grows weaker! We keep
the key in order to
retighten the seal if we
should ever find the
need!
To place a key right next
to the lock it opens is
unheard of!
Yes, and yet, Don't
forget that it was
entrusted to us by
Minato.
It was always meant to be
returned to Naruto one
day.
But it's too soon!
Once already you
sweet-talked me into
loosening the Tetragram
Seal, and you know just
as well as I do what
happened that time!
You haven't forgotten,
have you?
No.
But... I believe that
Minato entrusting me with
this Jutsu Formula...
Indicates that his will
was for Naruto to complete
that Jutsu for himself one
day.
Great Lord Elder! Are
you absolutely sure that
this is the right thing
to do?
Jiraiya tested Naruto. He
was confident the boy would
be able to fully control
the Nine-Tails' power.
But it didn't
go well at all.
Jiraiya was still
convinced that Minato
wouldn't have sealed half
of Nine-Tails' chakra in
Naruto if it weren't
controllable.
Oh, boy...
Great Lord Elder,...
Gerotora himself is the
key to Naruto's
Tetragram Seal.
Would it really be safe
to give him to Naruto? Tell
me. What are you thoughts?
Summon Naruto Uzumaki
here to me...
And I shall peer into his
future.
Our choice will hinge on
that.
Wait, are you serious?!
Well, it hasn't been
officially announced yet,
but judging by the
activity near the hut
where she's resting, I
think it's gotta be true!
All of her attendants had
been in such low spirits,
but now they're all smiling
and laughing together.
It looks like all of our
wishes have been granted
at last!
[gobbling]
Uh...
Goodness! Slow down!
It's not enough! My
chakra hasn't returned
to normal!
[exhaling]
Go get me some more
food, quickly!
Relax, and I'll turn into
an old hag!
[gasping]
Oh, no! It's happening!
We have completely
depleted the Hokage
Quarter's supply stores.
But don't worry; I'll
just go and requisition
some more provisions for
you.
Please, take a
short break!
Oink!
Oink! Oiiiiink!
No, absolutely not! What
are you thinking, Lady
Tsunade?! You cannot have
Tonton!
What are you saying?!
Nothing...
Oink?
[gasping]
K- Kakashi!
Huh.
I'm glad to see
you're looking well.
I'm not there yet.
I'm just getting started.
After all you've
eaten?! I can't believe
it...
I'm quite relieved. I
was dangerously close to
becoming Hokage.
But I'm not really the
Hokage type. Given our
situation, we need
someone with more
influence to be Hokage,
like you Lady Tsunade.
I'm shocked about the
Allied Shinobi Force.
I'm amazed the Tsuchikage
Raikage agreed to cooperate.
Yes, I know, but that's
how bad the situation
seems to be.
Madara Uchiha.
Is he really still alive?
We don't have proof yet.
But considering what
they're planning to do,
it seems that way.
It's another
war, huh?
I can't believe the
Uchiha misfortunes now
torment all shinobi.
[sighing]
I will call a meeting
of the council. We must
prepare for war!
"Prophecy of the Great
Lord Elder"
You must rest.
It takes time to become
accustomed to the
Mangekyo. Are you in
pain?
No.
They fit quite nicely.
I feel Itachi's visual
prowess.
I can tell that I've
already become so much
stronger.
Orochimaru
forced me into cruel,
harsh labor!
And then Sasuke took over
and kept ordering poor,
weak me around.
His demands were
unreasonable!
[sobbing]
In the end, he just
treated me like trash!
[sobbing]
I'm a victim
here, too!
I see! It must have
been so hard.
Oh, please.
I don't need your life
story!
Say what?
Give us everything you know
about the Akatsuki, Sasuke
and Kabuto.
And you! Don't get
emotionally involved!
You're no good if you're
biased!
Right. Yes,
sorry, sir!
Fine. I'll tell you,
but first, you have to
meet my conditions.
What conditions
are those?
Well, first of all,
I'm completely famished.
I want a fried pork
cutlet bowl or no deal!
What are you talking
about?!
Hm, you know, I didn't
think there was a fried
pork shop in the village.
And even if there were,
would it still be in
business under these
circumstances?
You know, I heard that
Ichiraku started back up
again in a temporary
location.
Is ramen okay?
No, it has to be a fried
pork cutlet bowl.
[sighing]
Hey, wait a minute. What
if we got a delivery from
outside the village?
Okay, but can't you get
a fried pork cutlet bowl
from a noodle shop?
Mmm... it would
take two days.
Can it! You two are
quite a pair.
Uh... Sorry, sir.
Hm.
They're the same...
You two better get your
act together--
I don't get it. What is
this? This entire village
is cheerful and warm.
Just like him...
Hey, Naruto! Haven't
seen you around for a
while. Where you been?
Oh, you know, just around
I guess!
It gets lonely when we
don't see you. Your
enthusiasm gives the whole
village the energy to recover.
[chuckling]
Thank you,
Naruto. Thank
you so much.
Really, guys--
Did you guys
see that?
Mm-hmm.
His head's gonna swell up
really big, I just know
it!
Just look at him, smiling
like that. Yuck!
This is a problem.
We in the mass media
have created some sort of
terrible monster.
If we don't take Naruto
down a peg or two, the
whole Leaf Village is
going to suffer!
Mmm-hmm!
I wonder where he's
headed right now...
Wherever it is, I'm sure
that it's nowhere good!
All right, now, let's
get ready to capture the
moment, 'kay?
Mmm!
[chuckling]
I've been wanting to see
you, my love! Wait no
longer!
Ha! I knew it!
Huh?
[gasping]
Them again. Do they
really think that I
haven't noticed them
by now?
[thanking Naruto]
They're shadowing me
wherever I go...
Uhhh!
[chuckling]
Naruto.
[grunting]
You're the village
hero. Aren't you,
Naruto?
Huh? No, I'm no hero!
So... where you
headed now, big boy?
Hold on! You're
Konohamaru!
I'm so not Konohamaru!
[grunting]
Darn it!
[grunting and groaning]
Hey, wait up!
[panting]
[chuckling]
In that case,
I'll do this!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You can't get
away that easy!
Harem Jutsu!
Huh?!
I just want to talk with
the big hero, Naruto!
What are you running
from? What, are you
afraid of little old us?
You going to meet
someone?
On your way to a hot
date or something,
Naruto?!
[screaming]
Oh, boy.
The village hero, huh?
However...
Aw, come back! Where are
you going?!
That time when Naruto
stood up to Pain to
protect me...
The Nine-Tails began
to emerge from Naruto's
body.
[screaming]
What's that?!
Do you hate
me now?!
I could feel its intense
anger.
But I- In that moment I
couldn't feel anything
of Naruto's will anymore.
It was like...
Its anger had taken
over.
Naruto's heart
lost in the Nine-Tails.
[sighing]
Well, the First Hokage's
necklace that Naruto got
from Lady Tsunade is
gone...
If the Nine-Tails were
to emerge and run loose
now...
Let's be honest, I
don't think even I
could stop it anymore.
True... it would be
tremendously risky to
take on the Akatsuki with
the Nine-Tails inside of him.
But...
[panting]
Yeah, hold up!
He's Naruto.
He's not the
Nine-Tails.
For this battle, we
don't need the
Nine-Tails... we need
Naruto's strength.
If it looks like the
Nine-Tails is taking
over, we'll have to stop
it.
That's right. This is
also a battle to protect
Naruto from the Akatsuki
and the Nine-Tails.
That's how I- No,...
I'm sure this is how
all of my classmates
feel.
We protect Naruto.
And we will fight
with him.
I wonder what Lady
Tsunade thinks.
All right, is
everyone here?
Then we'll begin the
war council to discuss
our strategy.
Assemble ninja tools
and stock reserves of
food.
Assign all shinobi to
a main battle unit or
support groups and ponder
how to further group
platoons within the main
unit.
And bring me a full list
of all our shinobi!
It's war, then. So
it's finally come to
that.
You were appointed to the
war council, but you're
still young.
Just watch and don't
miss a thing.
Yeah, don't worry.
I know.
I'll use every brain
cell. And hammer
everything in.
Guess I finally lost
them.
And now at long last I
can enjoy my love to the
absolute fullest!
Old man! One large
tonkotsu with extra pork!
[panting]
Naruto!
Huh?
What?! So Granny
Tsunade's all right?!
Mm-hmm!
Yes!
That's great! What good
news about Lady Tsunade!
Right! To celebrate,
the ramen's on me!
What?! For real?!
You too, Sakura; pull up
a seat!
Thanks, but no. I can't
stay. I've got to tell
everyone!
Well, I'll see you
later, Naruto! Bye!
[giggling]
Wow, with that load off
my mind, I'm hungrier
than ever!
All right! I am gonna
eat today!
One bowl, two bowls,
three bowls!
Here you go! A special
tonkotsu miso with BBQ
pork to celebrate the
Hokage's recovery!
Whoa! Cool!
Thanks, Teuchi, for the-
He just disappeared!
--Food!
[eager to eat]
Wow, I'm amazed! He just
dug right in!
Aw, you make me so happy
with how much you love my
arthropod cooking!
[gagging]
[retching]
[groaning]
What--what am I
doing here again?
I did a Reverse Summoning
on you. The Great Lord
Elder will divine your
future, Naruto-boy!
Mmm?
Divine?
Come along now...
[gagging]
[retching]
Don't you dare hurl!
On my floor...
I have brought him.
Hey, there! Long time
no see, huh, Giant Gramps
Sage?!
It was indeed I who
summoned you.
Er, uh... Uhhh....
What was
your name again?
[groaning]
Naruto Uzumaki!
C'mon! Could you remember
my name already, Giant
Gramps Sage?!
Oh, yes, that's right,
that.s right, it's Naruto,
of course!
[groaning]
Do we have to go through
this every time?!
Now, Naruto... I've had
a prophecy about you...
A prophecy? Okay,
let me have it.
Very well, then... Listen
carefully.
Soon you will be
meeting an octopus.
What?!
An octopus?!
But... Why would I be
meeting an octopus?!
I'm not certain. I
couldn't see too clearly,
but I'm sure there were
octopus arms.
Okay...
And then, after that...
You will come to battle a
lad whose power lies in
his eyes.
And then...
Yeah... I know.
Wait. What do you mean
you know, Naruto, boy?
I'm not going to change.
I don't want to
understand you.
I won't die!
You're the one who's
going to die.
Then we'll die
together... Sasuke.
Heh.
Fine by mean, but at
least I'll take you
down first.
No problem... since it's
clear that you still
don't respect me at
all...
Enough, Naruto. I'll
handle Sasuke. You have
to pursue your dream of
becoming Hokage.
I won't let Sasuke take
you down with him.
But I'm not worthy of
being Hokage...
...if I can't even save a
friend.
Fine, Sasuke...
I'll fight you!
Have you seen it, too?
Yeah.
And he whose power lies
in his eyes...
Do you know who and what
he is as well, then?
Mm-hmm. And I've
made up my mind.
Gerotora. I dreamt that
you stored yourself in
Naruto.
Wait a minute,
you did?!
Give him the key to the
Fourth Hokage's seal.
All right...
But only because you say
so, Great Lord Elder.
What is this?
The key left by the
Fourth Hokage to lock and
unlock the sealing jutsu
on your belly!
With this, you could even
let the Nine-Tails out to
run free, if you wanted.
Mm.
Just press your hand down
on that square area.
Once you do, you'll also
have obtained the means
to perfect that jutsu. The
one Jiraiya told you about.
That's the key to release
it...?
The Nine-Tails
seal?
Are you having some
doubts, Naruto?
In real battle,...
feelings of hate are
bound to come out.
So I thought I didn't
want Nine-Tails' power
anymore.
But then again... I need
the Nine-Tails' chakra in
order to fight Sasuke.
I can't hide from that
forever.
Well... no use getting
depressed!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Storage.
Dad, I'm gonna
conquer this control
thing!