-What's that?
-Looks like the boss finally got
ahold of the forbidden jutsu.
-Take a good look, Hotaru.
It's magnificent.
This is the forbidden
jutsu's power.
This is the art that
we've honed together.
[laughter]
-(VOICEOVER) No.
It can't be.
No, I didn't do that.
No.
-No!
[sobbing]
-No, I-- I can't believe it.
I killed Sir Utakata.
-All right, enough.
This is so pathetic.
I can't have a vessel with
feelings that get in the way.
-Now then.
Once more.
This time, get the entire
Tsuchigumo Village.
All those worthless villagers.
We'll get rid of them all.
-Wood Style Jutsu.
-It's useless.
Heh.
You can't harm all
these villagers,
but you can't get to me unless
you go through them, first.
But we couldn't care less what
happens to people like them.
-This ends right now.
Cho.
-Gu.
-Vu.
-Cho.
[grunt]
-Ah!
-We got them all.
[laughter]
-What?
-Hm.
-Benten!
-Ah!
-But how did you guys do that?
-Just like this.
-Ah!
-That jutsu you created
was quite formidable.
But with just two of you left,
you're no match for all of us.
[growls]
[laughter]
-With this jutsu, I'll
divide and conquer.
And make the five
great nations tremble.
-No.
No way.
Never!
There's no way that I'd ever
let you get away with this.
Hey, Utakata!
Come on.
Get up.
This is no time to be
lying down on the job.
-Right.
We have to get Hotaru
away from this maniac.
-Hm.
You just don't know when to die.
Fine.
I'll give you another taste
of the forbidden jutsu.
-Not going to happen.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go!
-Oh, no you don't.
Word Bind Jutsu.
Explode.
-Utakata!
Now's your chance to get Hotaru.
-Not so fast.
Word Bind Jutsu.
Flame.
[laughter]
-Oh, what's the matter?
Is that all you've got?
[laughter]
-No.
What have you done?
-Can't form signs now.
-Hotaru.
Damn it.
-Now I'll pay you
back, big time.
-Hotaru.
-Knock it off.
Stop the forbidden jutsu.
-It isn't me.
I mean, look.
My hands are completely bound.
-OK, but, then
what's going on here?
-I don't know.
It could be the result of
absorbing too much chakra
energy.
-Well, whatever it
is, just stop it.
-How can I with my
hands like this?
-Release.
[laughter]
-Now, then.
-What?
Damn.
-Come on.
Stop it, already.
-(VOICEOVER) The
Word Bind Jutsu.
It isn't working.
This is bad.
-What's wrong?
-Would you do something?
It's getting worse.
-If it keeps collecting
natural chakra like this,
it will explode and take
the village with it.
-Are you kidding me?
-Huh?
Hotaru.
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
-Damn it.
-The revival of the
Tsuchigumo clan.
The wishes of En no Gyoja.
By taking on everyone
else's selfish goals,
she's pushed herself
to the breaking point.
-Shut up.
What the hell would you
know about Hotaru, anyway?
She kept the
forbidden jutsu safe,
even sacrificing her own body.
The whole village rejected
her, but she still
worked to restore her clan.
She shouldered the
entire burden herself.
But then she met Utakata.
And even though you
tricked her, she
came with you because
she looked up to you.
[laughter]
-Don't you see?
She'd finally found
a true friend.
Somebody that she could
form of real bond with.
But you took all of
that and crushed it.
-Hotaru found a true
friend, a real bond?
That's just a bunch of nonsense.
I'm the same as her.
For the forbidden jutsu,
any master, any person,
would sacrifice a student.
Anyone, without
hesitation, saying it's
what a good shinobi would do.
It's just survival.
I went through it, too,
until I got sick of it.
That's why I went
on the offensive.
I killed my father,
who had been my master.
And I tried to steal the jutsu.
-You did what?
-You're shocked, Utakata,
but that's just what you did.
-No, it wasn't.
I didn't.
-You're wrong.
-What?
-My master, he
always-- he cares.
About me.
About all his students.
So even if we're not
together, I can always
feel his thoughts,
and our connection.
He's in my heart every
minute, and that's
why I believe in him.
Hotaru has people
like that, too.
Her grandfather and
Tonbei, and now Utakata.
Your thoughts should have
reached her, Utakata.
They should be within her heart.
She just wants a
friend, a master.
A bond.
But you can't see that at all.
You don't know a
single thing about her.
Don't pretend that you do!
-Give me a break.
Word Bind Jutsu.
Split.
-Ah!
-I got you.
-Thanks a lot.
-Oh, no.
I'd better escape before
the vessel explodes.
[sigh]
-Hotaru, no!
-I'll bring Shiranami
back to stop it.
-I'll come too.
-No.
You're Hotaru's master, Utakata.
Your place is here with her.
I'm counting on you.
-Very well.
-NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Hotaru
has people like that, too.
Her grandfather and
Tonbei, and now Utakata.
Your thoughts should have
reached her, Utakata.
-UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): My
feelings are within her.
And in my heart as well.
Yes.
My anger.
It prevented me from listening.
But I did hear-- no.
I felt my master's thoughts.
They were there.
-All his thoughts.
All his feelings for me.
They reached me.
And yet--
-Now, Utakata.
Go live side by side
with this power.
Back then, I swore that I'd
never use your power again.
But now, for Hotaru, I must.
Please, I need your help.
[crying]
-Hotaru.
-I never wanted to hurt anyone.
And yet, I hurt Naruto.
And Sir Utakata with
my very own hands.
-But look, I'm right here.
Naruto and I are fine.
-I saw it happen.
-But Hotaru--
-I'm sorry.
I betrayed you, Sir Utakata.
Somebody like me should just
disappear along with the jutsu.
-Don't say that.
I will not allow it.
A good student should
always listen to her master.
-Did you say "master"?
-Come on.
Let's go.
-Thank you.
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-No!
You must leave.
Sir Utakata, please.
Just get away from me.
Go.
Run as fast as you can.
-Hotaru.
-I've done all I can.
I can't suppress it any longer.
Anyone with the
forbidden jutsu is
going to tear me
apart and explode!
-It's all right.
-Sir Utakata?
-Just trust your master.
-Let the village be destroyed.
It deserves it.
He'll be eradicated.
[laughter]
-You again?
-I got you.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-You're a persistent bastard.
Word Bind Jutsu.
Flame!
Fool.
You can't stop me.
Huh?
-I won't let you get away.
No matter what!
-Word Bind Jutsu.
Slice!
[shouts]
-What?
No!
Augh!
-Now to get you back
to Hotaru right away.
-[gasp]
-What is that?
-Hey!
Utakata!
Are you guys all right?
-We are.
-My Master.
-My, what a troublesome
student you are.
-Wait, hold on.
What happened to the jutsu?
-It seems to have disappeared.
-Disappeared?
Well, as long as Hotaru
is safe, I'm glad.
-Naruto!
-Huh?
Hey, Sakura!
-Right.
The mission negotiated
between the Tsuchigumo Clan
and the Hidden Leaf has
been completed successfully.
-Thank you for everything
you've done for us.
-Well, the forbidden
jutsu was destroyed.
However--
-Yes.
I think that it's
for the better.
Lady Hotaru is safe, and now
no one will come after her.
-The townsfolk are
happy, finally.
They'll welcome Hotaru
and not fear her.
At last.
-Are you still going, Hotaru?
With Utakata?
-Yes, I am.
I still have so much more
to learn from my master.
But after I've trained
with him, once I've
achieved the strength
I need as a ninja,
and I can restore
our clan's glory,
I promise to return here.
-Hey, good for you, Master.
-Hold on.
Are you trying to mess with me?
-No way.
I'm just glad that you finally
accepted your role as a master.
It took you long enough.
Just take care of Hotaru.
Got it?
-Well, everyone, take care.
-It's nice to have a master.
You know what I mean?
-Hm?
-To be honest, I
even find myself
kind of missing the Pervy Sage.
-This is it, Master.
This is the place
where I first met you.
-Hotaru.
Will you wait here for
me, for a little while?
-Is there a problem?
-I'm meeting the ANBU Black Ops.
I'm tired of all this running.
I want to get permission
to travel and train you.
-Great.
-(VOICEOVER) No response.
Strange.
Did something happen to them?
[gasp]
-The Six-Tails, jinchuriki host.
-Are you the ones who
killed Tsurugi and his men?
-I'm going to build
an entirely new world.
And for that, I need you.
Well, really, I need the
tail piece that's inside you.
-So, that's it, then.
-Now, Six-Tails, you are mine.
[humming]
-Please, Hotaru.
You have to-- you have to live.
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
-(VOICEOVER) Out of the
blue, shocking news arrives.
A terrible message that rocks
the Leaf to its very core.
People are left shaken, unable
to cope with the awful news.
A storm of despair is about to
sweep across the Hidden Leaf
village.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden-- Somber News.
-Naruto.
Lady Tsunade has summoned you.