-That came a lot
closer than I thought.
[laughter]
-Fuen needs lessons in
how to set a good trap.
-Their skill's unbelievable.
We may be out of our depth here.
-Did any of those get him?
-Not quite.
-Come on, then.
-Laughable!
You can't run forever.
Earth style.
Stone plate coffin.
That's the end of that.
Well, you've earned a
grave marker, at least.
Dammit, Fuen.
I broke a sweat 'cause of you.
-You should never
overestimate your own jutsu.
Always make sure
that the job is done.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): But
what's their game here?
After stealing the
bodies, they deliberately
attract attention
as they escape.
-Maybe they're after one of
us from the Leaf Village.
That could mean Danzo
has a hand in it all.
[theme song]
-It looks like we're trapped
in the middle of the enemy's
jutsu, huh?
First thing we should
do is locate the others.
They've probably
regrouped nearby.
-I'm gonna go find
your idiot friend.
-Hey, wait a second, will ya?
-I'll be fine on my own.
You'll just slow me down.
-Oh, boy.
So much for working together.
We're all off on our own now.
Oh, well.
Can't be helped.
I doubt he's had the team
training that Naruto and I have
had.
Come to think of it, Naruto
flunked that course, didn't he?
-All right.
What's her deal?
-Ugh.
Manual labor.
Not really my cup of tea.
The traps in this place were
supposed to do the work for me.
I guess I have no choice.
Let's make it a
quickie, shall we?
-Don't worry.
It'll be quite, all right.
I guarantee you that.
Let's go!
What in the blue
blazes was that?
-Oh, my.
The taste leaking from
your chakra network.
Who knew?
So you're one of the rare
few with wind-based chakra.
-What about it, you lunatic?
-You'll make for a nice
addition to my collection.
-What?
-What do you prefer, kid?
French or traditional?
-What do you mean?
Like food?
-Cutie.
I meant kissing.
-Wait, you're saying-- ahh!
You saying you want
to make out with me?
-That's right, hun.
You think you can handle it?
I mean, you have been
kissed before, haven't you?
-Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Don't be ridiculous.
Of course I have!
I know it was a guy, but still.
-Really?
Whatever.
Anyway, how about having
a little fun with me?
-Yuck.
No freaking way, lady.
Women like you are
nothing but trouble!
-I don't believe it.
He turned me down.
-What the heck is
wrong with this chick?
I've heard of easy,
but this is ridiculous.
-You never want to disappoint
a lady, sweetie-pie.
Now, you are mine.
-No way.
Can't we talk about it?
-Reaper kiss.
What?
-Not bad.
A little on the
cold side, maybe.
But you've got soft
lips, that's for sure.
-Your last moments would
have been sheer bliss
if you had just held
still for a minute.
-Good luck finding the real me!
-Well, now you've gone
and ticked me off, kid.
-This isn't merely
some genjutsu.
I designed this
terrain and summoned it
into being, calling it forth
from another dimension.
Run, if you wish.
However, escape is impossible.
-I'm not stupid enough to
fight in a terrain created
by the enemy.
-There's no point in hiding.
Skulk about all you want.
My eyes will be on you.
After all, I've already
left my mark on you.
I know where you're going.
Almost before you do.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Am I safe?
-I need to find the others fast.
I'd better get moving.
-Off in that direction, are you?
-What?
How could they possibly
know where I am now?
And why are there traps
waiting everywhere I go?
-I think this little game
has gone on long enough.
How unfortunate.
Every move you make
shows up on the design
plans I carry with me.
Earth style, spears of stone!
Farewell.
-Ninja art, super beast scroll.
-Spears of stone!
Clever boy.
He got away.
But don't I look the fool.
Well, I guess if he's
capable of outmaneuvering me,
perhaps he might be more of a
challenge that I first thought.
-Hm?
Hardly the time to be standing
watch over an old man.
-Huh?
A message at this hour?
[oinking]
-Shizune, what have you got?
-An owl, ma'am.
A Blakiston's fish owl, I think.
-That's not what I meant.
What is it doing here?
-Oh.
Uh-- it's an urgent message
from the Fire Temple.
Team Kakashi was ambushed
while pursuing the enemy.
-Why didn't you say sooner?
-I've already dealt
with one of them.
-Well, unlike your
opponent, mine
was a young man with
some actual fight in him.
-Did he get away?
-The labyrinth that I created
is absolute perfection.
They'll never make it out alive.
-You sure about that?
-They've barely had a
taste of what's to come.
If anyone survives they'll
deserve a standing ovation.
-This smell-- it's sulfur.
It doesn't seem to be poisonous.
Sai!
-Ninja art, super beast scroll!
-Sai, you all right?
Sai, try not to move.
Looks like your arm's broken.
This is gonna hurt.
Try and bear with me.
That should do it.
Now, for the spider venom.
Don't worry.
It's not that toxic.
I'll neutralize the poison, OK?
-So, were you moved just now?
-Huh?
-You were moved, weren't you?
Enough to save me.
-What's that?
Guide to self-sacrifice?
-Yes.
It's been a help to me.
According to this book, if
you want to endear yourself
to people, nothing works more
than laying down your life
for them.
Particularly when
it comes to women.
Perhaps it'll work
on Naruto, too.
-Huh?
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
Zip it.
[scream]
-You've had some luck, but
now I'm angry, little boy.
-Ready to fight now, huh?
OK.
Now you're talking.
-Yeah, show us
what you got, lady.
-You don't think you can
lock lips with all of us,
now, do you?
-Fire style, phoenix
flower jutsu!
Like I said.
Just a boy.
Now, I wonder where
the real one is hiding.
-Wait.
Did I get her?
What the-- oh, hell.
Where'd she go?
I don't get it.
I'm almost positive
I tagged her.
[laughter]
-Earth style, hidden
in stone jutsu.
You're plucky, that's for sure.
And your wind
chakra's formidable.
Can't wait to make it mine.
-Jeez, what are you, immortal?
Nobody gets up after I blast
them with the Rasengan.
-Your attacks are sloppy.
I can read them like a book.
But enough banter.
Those lips of
yours need kissing.
You ready, handsome?
-Sorry.
I don't think I'm
as easy as you are.
-First I'm gonna
knock the words out
of that smart little
mouth of yours.
-Shadow clone jutsu!
-Oh, please.
More clones?
Not very creative.
Then I'll just go with-- water
style, mouth of the serpent.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): She can use
earth, fire, and water chakra.
How can she have three?
-Lightning style, earth flash!
-Lightning?
What the-- four kinds of chakra?
Come on!
-What in the world is that?
Who are you?
-You're Sora, aren't you?
I've been waiting for you.
[music playing]
NARUTO: A woman's hair.
Feminine mystique.
Please.
What do I care about
any of that stuff?
At any rate, she's got earth,
fire, water, lightning,
and wind chakra.
That's all of them!
I've got my wind, too.
Time to put all that
training to good use.
Ah-- wait!
I haven't mastered any
wind-style jutsu yet!
Next time-- Contact.