(angry roar)
(startled gasp)
Mina?
(frightened whine)
(sobbing)
I'll just ask him
myself about what we
discussed earlier.
His genetic data is
still slumbering here.
The sacrifice...
...is still
alive, too.
(painful scream)
I don't think
it's a cold.
Is he all right?
It wasn't the
breakfast, was it?
(chuckle)
No, no way!
He's been feeling
off since yesterday.
Brother Naruto!
Time to train!
Ninjutsu!
Yeah!
You guys, Naruto's
not feeling well.
What?! But you told us
that you were gonna
teach us self-defense!
And you call yourself
a hero of the Hidden
Leaf?
(annoyed grunt)
All right, you guys!
Now, to overcome the
hardship and challenges
you'll face...
...you'll need to build
up your strength and
physical fitness!
Of course, just diving
right into training
without a plan in mind
isn't gonna work!
So, I put together
all my years of-
Man, he's just
so eager!
And the name of this
plan is, Naruto's Miracle
Power Training! Make it
through this, and you'll
be ready for anything!
Hah! Looks like
this might be fun!
Wanna try, Brother?
Nah...
It sounds hard.
I don't really want
to get all tired out.
Agh! Don't be such a
wimp! Whatever you do,
give it your all!
Right?!
Yeah! Right!
Good! First we'll run
down to the lake!
Let's go!
Man, this is
the worst!
No kidding!
Hmph!
What's this diversion
about, anyway?
You don't even know
what it means?! What
are you, stupid?
Hmph!
Hey, watch it! I'm
just trying to say
that being used by
Kabuto is the worst!
Immortality was your
best trait! But look
at you, you're in
pieces. How pitiful!
Oh, yeah? What about
you? Didn't you blow
yourself up or
something?
Shut up! It was my
Ultimate Art, idiot!
I scattered, and it
was sublime! Hmph!
That's nothing to brag
about! So you died!
Don't get high and
mighty! You're the
same!
That's it! That
concludes our
training!
(exhausted sigh)
(heavy breathing)
Whew! I worked up a
nice sweat! But still,
that was too easy!
You all did just
great! How 'bout I
go buy some drinks
for everyone?
Just wait here.
(disappointed sigh)
Naruto...
How embarrassing!
I know... I'm
not feeling...
...a hundred
percent today.
(shocked gasp)
(scared gasp)
(laughter)
C'mon! A real hero
could get free!
You must be lying!
You keep harping
on about art!
It's always art this,
and art that! But all
the explosives you
design are so trashy!
You're just an idiot!
Well, your ceremonies
are always too long!
You know what it's like
having to go after you?!
You don't need to go
after me, 'cause I
finish what I start
you phony artist!
Shut up! You can't do
anything if you step
out of that curse symbol
of yours, so there!
Ah-ha! You know what?!
Maybe I should curse you!
Go ahead and try it!
I'd blow you up with
my art first!
(angry growl)
(attacking yell)
(throwing grunt)
Enough warm-up! Time
for the main event!
(giggling)
No escape for
you, Naruto!
Huh?
Mom, dad!
Can I get an ice
cream from the
store?
Yeah, sure!
(giggling)
Oh, you're gonna
get it now!
Is it good, honey?
It's awesome!
(giggling)
(crying)
Papa...
Mama...
Mama!
Oh, Daddy!
I wish I could
see them!
Me too!
I miss them so much!
I can't stand how
much I miss them!
Why are you
so lonely?
Look! You're
not alone.
Hm?
You're really not
trying to lose that
weight, are you?
That's not true!
Once I heal up, I'll
start exercising for
real!
Well, maybe I'll
supervise your
training!
(chuckling)
Uh... Hi, there!
Uh...Wh-What's
wrong, you guys?
(giggle)
(shy chuckle)
Naruto?
You pushed yourself
too hard!
I'll be fine...
...after I get
some sleep.
(scared gasp)
Take it...
Take it!
Get out!
Huh?
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
That's enough, Mina!
Stop it! What's
the matter?
Get out!
Please, don't say
such rude things
to Naruto!
Stop, Mina!
Get out!
Mina!
(stunned gasp)
Guess she doesn't
like you.
(confused sigh)
Why? Did I do something
wrong? I don't understand
it...
Hey, seriously. Do
you feel all right?
Don't worry,
I'm fine.
Let me examine you...
Huh? No, not like that!
Hey! Stop it, Sakura!
That tickles!
Stop wiggling around!
Ow!
Why do I even bother
worrying about you
anyway?!
Isn't that the Chief
of the village?
I wanted to let
you know personally,
so I rushed over just
as quickly as I could.
This man standing here
beside me came into the
town hall this very
morning.
(shocked gasp)
It's the Chief!
Grandpa!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
You're both all
right! Oh, thank
goodness!
I'm so happy you're
okay, too, Chief.
Yes, aside from my
eyes. I was wondering
across the wilderness
when somebody came
along and saved me.
Dokku, I put such
a burden on you.
No. It's fine.
By the way, I have
something important
to ask you.
Okay...
On that night, do you
remember the items that
I gave you?
Now, you may already
have guessed what I'm
about to tell you, but...
They're a part of the
treasure that was hidden
in the village altar.
To ensure that the
treasure remained safe
from the invaders, I
entrusted parts of it
to another guard, just
as I entrusted you
with yours.
Regrettably, however,
five of the parts,
including my own...
Are now in the hands
of the enemy.
The remaining two pieces
must be protected at
all costs.
And that is why I
would like, Disonasu
here, to take custody
of them and help us
keep them safe.
(affirmative grunt)
But Chief, you're
sure about this?
Yes. That is
my decision.
I understand.
So...
Where are they?
Give them to me,
(frightened gasp)
Yes, sir. Of course.
No!
Grandpa isn't right!
Huh? He's been...
Reanimated?!
She's quite sharp.
Huh?
She must be
very special.
Kabuto!
(angry growl)
We've been tricked!
(evil chuckle)
I'm going to take fatso
over there and squeeze
information out of him!
And after that...
(evil laugh)
(attack yell)
(shocked gasp)
Chief!
Grandpa!
So, a sacrifice that's
almost dead is useless.
(fighting grunts)
Sorry!
Agh!
(shocked gasps)
(painful grunts)
What is it, Naruto?!
What's the matter?!
(painful screaming)
Take it...
Take it!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Mina, please, you
have to stop this!
Ahh!
Get out! Get out!
Mina!
Get out of
Brother Naruto!
(evil laughter)
(angry growl)
(angry roar)
The Nine Tails' power.
Ah!
(painful grunts)
(gasps)
(angry roar)
(struggling breaths)
People like you who
possess such immense
power. However you
choose to use that
power, for good or for
evil, you still must
bear the weight of such
a big responsibility.
Why become stronger?
Why did you desire
such power? Tell me...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Power-
Episode 4."
That strong conviction
you have inside. I'm
sure it will guide you.