-There.
The sealing of the Six
Tails is at last completed.
Phew.
It certainly takes longer
with just five of us.
-Now that it's done, there
are only two tailed beasts
remaining.
-Yes.
I've sent Sasuke and his
team to go and retrieve
the Eight Tails.
-But can he be trusted?
-I can vouch for Sasuke myself.
-I know that you're out
here all by yourself.
So why aren't you running?
-Whatever.
I can be any number
from 1 to 1,000.
Besides, why would
I want to run?
If I capture you right now, then
I'll get to see Sasuke again.
-Why are you so obsessed
with my brother?
He's just a rogue ninja.
It's true that we
may not be blood,
but he's more of a brother to
me than you ever were to him.
ITACHI: You're already
under my genjutsu.
I'll say it again.
I just want to talk.
I know that you've been
trying to take Sasuke back
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
However, what if it doesn't
go the way you want it to?
-I'll do anything
to make it happen.
-Even taking him by force?
Sure, if you're lucky,
Sasuke will just obediently
return with you to the village.
But tell me, what if the
opposite were to happen?
-What are you talking about?
-You just said you consider
Sasuke to be like a brother
to you.
What if Sasuke were to attack
the Hidden Leaf Village?
What would you do then?
-Why would-- no,
there's just no way
that Sasuke would ever
do something like that.
-Sasuke is still a blank canvas.
He can easily be
dyed into any color.
If he resists, would
you be able to stop him?
Or even kill him, if need be?
Could you weigh Sasuke
against the Hidden Leaf
on a set of scales?
-I would defend the
village, and I'd
find a way to stop Sasuke
without killing him!
-You're such a child.
All your tales are nothing
but mere fantasies.
Shinobi must be capable of
making very harsh decisions.
-The first thing is for
you to give up on Sasuke.
What happened was always
destined to happen, Naruto.
Dismiss him from your
mind, and move on.
To be a shinobi, you need
more strength and jutsu.
You must acquire the judgement
to make the right decisions.
You must become smarter.
So the longer that
you remain a fool,
the harder it is for you
to live in this world.
-Fine, then.
If being smarter means
what you say it does,
I'll remain a fool
my entire life.
I'm going after him, and I'll
do it alone, if I have to.
I'll create my own
incredible jutsu.
Someone else once tried
to tell me the same thing.
But for me, there is no choice.
I gave my word, and
I'll never back down.
That will always
be my ninja way.
ITACHI: I have shared
some of my power with you.
Though I hope the day
when you will have to use
it never comes.
-What is this?
What's going on here?
I thought you said that
you weren't after me.
Then why are you doing this?
-I'm going now.
I have an important
matter to attend to.
-What did Itachi
mean by all of that?
Why did he--
-Sasuke triumphed in the battle.
Itachi Uchiha is now dead.
Sasuke is down right now, too.
So what's next?
I think he's in
pretty bad shape.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What
are you doing now, Sasuke?
I hope you're OK.
-Are you all right, Sasuke?
-Yeah.
Let's hurry.
We're almost at the
rendezvous point.
As promised, I've delivered
the Eight Tails to you.
-Excellent work.
I knew you could do it.
Where are you going?
-First to tend to my wounds.
Then to the Hidden Leaf.
-Sasuke, I need to ask
you something important.
After learning the truth
about Itachi's life,
there is a chance that you
will carry out his wishes
and protect the Hidden Leaf.
So tell me the truth.
What are your intentions?
-Itachi's life shows
how he sacrificed
himself to protect the village.
But my grief at losing him
is deeper than any desire
to follow his path.
Inconsolably so.
The peace that Itachi
sacrificed himself for
doesn't appeal to me.
Now that I know the truth,
following in Itachi's footsteps
to protect the Hidden Leaf
is the last thing I would do.
Most of all, I will never
forgive the three elders
of the Leaf Village.
I believe everyone
in the Leaf who's
enjoying the peace paid for with
Itachi's life is guilty, too.
-I thought you were only
going to kill the elders?
-No.
What I want is to slaughter
the entire Leaf Village.
But only by myself.
I was just lying in
front of the Taka.
-Are you sure about that?
You can truly ignore
Itachi's will, his sacrifice,
as well as all of those
he strove to protect?
Are you really serious?
-Look, you told me so yourself.
The reason why Itachi couldn't
bring himself to kill me
was because my life was
more precious to him
than the village itself was.
I have similar feelings
that Itachi's life
is more precious
than the Hidden Leaf.
That's all.
They shunned the Uchiha clan.
They ordered my brother
to kill own parents.
It wasn't just the elders who
chased Itachi to his death,
but all those in the Hidden
Leaf who abide by the Senju.
To me they are the
scum of the earth!
They are all objects
of my vengeance!
If you want to ridicule me as
a brat swayed by his emotions,
go ahead.
To accept and adopt Itachi's
intention would be childish.
The foolish sputtering of
those who don't know hatred.
If anyone who criticizes my way
of life were to come forward,
I'd turn around and kill every
single one of their loved ones,
so that they too
could grasp what
it's like to experience
this hatred of mine.
MADARA: When a man
learns to feel love,
he must also bear the
risk of feeling hate.
-What?
What do you mean,
Killer B's been taken?
-Among the assailants is
someone from the Hidden Leaf.
An Uchiha.
My partner is tailing
them right now.
-Lord Raikage, what
are your orders for us?
-The Akatsuki.
They won't get away with this!
Just you wait, little brother.
This isn't done.
[theme music]
[knocking]
-Huh?
Oh.
It's you.
Hey, Kakashi-sensei.
-Lady Fifth has summoned you.
Let's go.
-Chief Toad and Gamakichi?
What gives?
-Yo.
What's up, Naruto?
-What are you guys doing here?
What's going on?
Did something happen?
-Well, actually, uh--
-Gamakichi, keep your trap shut.
Let the boss and
Tsunade handle it.
They know what they're doing.
-That's weird.
What's going on here?
-Don't worry.
Let's go.
-Hm?
-So this is Jiraya
boy's student, is it?
-Yes.
This is Naruto Uzumaki.
The child of prophecy
you spoke of.
-What's with the
old geezer frog?
Who's he?
-Pipe down.
Watch your mouth, Naruto.
He is one of the two
great sages of Mt.
Myoboku, Lord Fukasaku.
He traveled all the
way here just so
that he could speak with you.
-Well, to be more accurate,
I'm a Great Sage Toad,
but never mind that.
It doesn't matter.
Answer me this.
Are you really Jiraiya boy's
student, or aren't you?
-Jiraiya boy?
A boy?
Don't treat the pervy
sage like a kid.
Who does this geezer
frog think he is, anyway?
-I told you already,
watch your mouth!
-Naruto, he's the one who taught
the Sage Jutsu to Lord Jiraiya.
He's Jiraiya's master.
-Huh?
[laughter]
-So you call him the Pervy Sage?
I've never heard a more
fitting name for Jiraiya boy.
-What does this
geezer sage want?
What did he come so far
to talk to me about?
-I'm not exactly sure
where to begin this.
But let me see.
I suppose the most
important thing
is I'm afraid Jiraiya
boy has died in battle.
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
-I know that this
is very sudden,
so I understand if
you don't believe me.
For some time now, rumors
had been circulating
that the leader of the
Akatsuki was operating out
of the Village
Hidden in the Rain,
so Jiraiya boy went
there in person to verify
whether these rumors were true.
-The leader of the Akatsuki
was in the Hidden Rain Village?
-As I recall, that village
is difficult to infiltrate.
It's entirely closed off
from the outside world.
-Yes.
But Master Jiraiya was
exceptionally skilled
in infiltration and
espionage tactics.
-Yes.
Exactly.
-This is what I've
thought through on my own,
and that is that,
Jiraiya-sensei.
FUKASAKU: Jiraiya
boy encountered Pain,
the leader of the Akatsuki.
However--
-We'll, your appearance
has changed quite a bit.
But those eyes--
so I guess you're
the ones who became
Pain, Nagato.
It appears you've strayed
from the path of goodness.
What happened to you?
-You don't need to know.
After all, you are an outsider.
-Pain was a former
student of Jiraiya boy's
from many, many years ago.
-He was his student?
What do you mean by that?
-I don't know the
particulars, but Jiraiya boy
called him Nagato.
-That goes way back to
a time during the chaos
of the Third Great Ninja War.
The Hidden Rani Village
had become a battlefield,
and Jiraiya took some war
orphans under his wing.
Who would have
imagined those kids--
-But to defeat a
shinobi as powerful
as Jiraiya-- how did this
Pain accomplish such a feat?
-It was because Pain
possesses the Rinnegan.
-What did you say?
-Rinnegan?
-It's an ocular jutsu said
to have been possessed
by the father of all shinobi,
the Sage of the Six Paths.
But I believed that it was
nothing more than a legend.
-The fabled occular
jutsu, the Rinnegan.
Its power was supposedly beyond
anything you could imagine.
But there's more.
-There were six of
them with the Rinnegan?
How can that even be possible?
-I don't know.
Perhaps there's some
trick behind it.
I believe that Jiraiya
boy discovered the secret
behind the six of them in
that final terrible battle.
But--
-Jiraiya boy!
-Even after he had his
throat crushed by Pain,
and he knew the end
was near, Jiraiya boy
left a message
before collapsing.
This is his message.
-It's a code.
-I'm sure he did this to
prevent Pain from catching on.
And that's everything I know
about Jiraiya boy's efforts.
-I wonder what he was
trying to tell us?
Maybe we can decode this.
Then, hopefully,
we'll understand.
-You let him go.
Is that right, granny?
-That's right.
Why would you ever let
him do something so risky?
You knew Pervy Sage better
than anyone, granny!
How could you send him
somewhere so dangerous alone?
-Stop it, Naruto.
You of all people ought to
know Lady Tsunade's feelings.
-It's too dangerous.
-I'm one of the Leaf's
legendary Sannin.
You know what that means
just as well as I do.
You were so beautiful back then.
And now, you're a
50-something granny.
But it does pain
me to see how you
hold all the memories
of your lost friends
and loved ones inside
that ample bosom of yours.
As you know, number will
only continue to rise.
Well then, we'll simply have
to keep our emotions in check.
The job that we must
give to ourselves
now is to set
examples, and to aid
the next generation, Tsunade.
And to achieve that,
I'd gladly risk my life.
Wisdom is the one thing that
makes growling old worth it.
-Dammit.
-Naruto, wait.
Where are you going?
-If the Pervy Sage had
been the Fifth Hokage,
he wouldn't have let granny
Tsunade take a risk like that.
Never.
-Naruto!
-Don't Sakura.
-Enough.
Just let him be for now.
-But milady--
-My apologies, Lord Fukasaku.
I'll arrange for Naruto to--
-No need.
That's quite all right.
But about that child
of prophecy vision
I mentioned earlier-- I can
see that this child truly
loved and admired Jiraiya boy.
It makes me hope
more than anything
that he is the
child of prophecy.
-First I'm going to
show you how it's done.
Now, watch me carefully.
[scream]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This is it.
Summoning Jutsu!
What?
No way!
I mean, come on!
Why do I have to
tag along with you
while you do research
for another one
of your pervy books?
-Look, kid.
This isn't just
another research trip.
See, there's this
woman I have to find.
A very remarkable woman.
-Come on, come on, come on!
Why'd ya choose me, huh?
-Well, the truth is,
kid, a long time ago,
the Fourth Hokage used
to be a disciple of mine,
and you bear such a striking
resemblance to the Fourth
that it's almost laughable.
Not a minute will be wasted.
-Huh?
-All of our time
on the road will
be devoted solely
to you, Naruto.
-But how come?
-We've got to get you stronger.
Time to train!
[theme music]
NARRATOR: The boy
wanders the village,
lost in despair,
immersed in anguish,
reminiscing about
his late master.
The end of his childhood
approaches quickly.
When at last he lets
go of all of his grief,
the boy will raise
himself up once again.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
Following the Master's Shadow.
-After all, we can't
stay brats forever.