Good job, Yamato.
No. That wasn't me.
Naruto stopped it
all by himself.
But, listen, is it
really okay to leave
things like this?
Hmm.
♪ Naruto and Nine Tails
are in confrontation.
I hope it's settled soon
and will meet our expectations.
♪ But I know all this waiting
can feel very drawn out!
So to pass the time,
why don't you and I work out? ♪
Would you knock it off!
This isn't the time to
be doing a rap!
Oh really? Shadapp!
[gasp]
Look, right now, Naruto
is locked in an internal
battle with the Nine Tails.
There's nothing
more that we can do
to help him out.
I know you care about
Naruto's well-being, but the
only things we can do now,
are wait and have faith that
he's gonna get the job done.
[growl]
[Kushina]
I love you.
What is this?
I feel so calm...
I love you so much.
I feel so happy!
Hyaaaahhh!
Damn you, Kushina!
Yaahhh!
[Killer Bee]
Yeaaa-eeaah!
What?!
This is real nice!
For now keeping
watch will suffice!
My chakra can't suppress the
Nine Tails for much longer!
So go get him while
you have the chance!
All right!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You brat!
Let's go!
He's as strong
as I thought.
Let 'im have it!
[growl]
[roar]
Rasengan Super Barrage!
You haven't won yet!
I can keep going, ya know!
Rrrgh??
Raaaaaahh!
This is it!
Is that?
[Yamato]
Sage Mode!
All right.
You're done! Sage Art!
Massive Rasengan Barrage!!
Auggghh!
Once more!
What kind of
power is this?!
Rauughhh!
Pull!
Get out!
[Kushina]
You did it! You pulled out
the Nine Tails' chakra!
No way. This is really
the Nine Tails'.
Naruto. How dare you!
You have infuriated
me! Naruto!
You still have
this much power?!
[growling]
Wow. You really
are amazing.
Raaagh!
Isn't this the Six Paths?!
You'd better watch out...
Naruto.
[Naruto]
Sorry, Nine Tails.
I promise I won't
do wrong by you.
So just hang in there
for a little while.
You pulled it off, Naruto!
Yeah.
Mom, what are you
going to do now?
Well, at long last I can
finally go and join Minato.
Before I go, there are a
few things that I'm going
to need to tell you.
Uh?
It's about the incident that
happened sixteen years ago,
when you were born.
I'm going to tell you the
truth about that day.
About sixteen years ago?
What do you mean?
To start with, I'll tell
you about the Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki before you.
That person was me.
"Target: Nine Tails"
You were the Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki, Mom? Seriously?!
I was.
Before I can tell you what
happened sixteen years ago,
I need to tell you
more about me.
Back then, I was chosen to
be the second Jinchuriki
host of the Nine Tails.
In fact, the only reason I
came to the Hidden Leaf
Village in the first place
was for that very purpose.
All the way from
the Land of Eddies.
But why?
Why'd they choose you as a
Jinchuriki?! You were a
stranger from another land!
Yes, I was. A stranger.
From a different Hidden Village.
But it was also a
different time.
Back then, the Land of Fire
and the Land of Eddies had
a close relationship.
They shared a deep bond.
The shinobi of the Leaf's
Senju Clan and the shinobi of
the Eddy's Uzumaki Clan were
distant blood relatives.
Full of shinobi brimming
with vitality, the Hidden
Eddy Village was also known
as the Village of Longevity.
My clan excelled
at sealing jutsu.
It was their specialty.
But they were also
a bit savage.
The Tetragram Seal on
your belly was based on a
jutsu that was originally
developed by our village.
I taught it to Minato,
your father, along with
several other sealing jutsu.
Naruto. that symbol
there, on the back
of your jacket.
It's the crest of the
Hidden Eddy Village.
Even today in the Hidden
Leaf Village, it's a
symbol of friendship and
camaraderie, isn't it?
I've never heard of the
Hidden Eddy Village.
That's 'cause it
doesn't actually exist
as a village any more.
During the era of war and
unrest, our sealing jutsu
abilities were greatly feared,
so we were targeted
and destroyed.
The survivors fled,
and they hid themselves
throughout the other lands.
But I still don't get it.
So why were you chosen, mom?
I was born with very strong
chakra even for my village.
It's powerful enough to
suppress the vast might
of the Nine Tails.
Do you know
about the battle,
between the First Hokage
Hashirama Senju and
Madara Uchiha?
Mm-hmm.
The Jinchuriki before me
was the woman who became
the wife of the First Hokage.
Her name was Mito Uzumaki.
During that battle, to lend
strength to Lord Hashirama,
who had obtained Nine Tails,
Lady Mito sealed the Nine Tails
inside herself with a Sealing
Jutsu and became its Jinchuriki.
And ever since that day,
the Leaf has possessed
the Nine Tails.
When Lady Mito approached
the end of her life,
I was brought to the Hidden
Leaf to become the next
vessel for the Nine Tails.
But they weren't even treating
you like you were a real person!
When I was brought to the
village, I wasn't told a
single thing about why I
was really there.
Of course, I was completely
shocked when I found out.
Everything about it
was top secret.
The only ones who knew
were Lord Third Hokage
and a few of the elders.
Not even the Legendary
Sannin knew.
I was so lonely.
The responsibility
almost ruined me.
But then Lady Mito, the
previous Jinchuriki,
summoned me.
Please, come closer,
my dear.
We are alike,
you and I.
I was brought here to
be the Nine Tails'
vessel, too.
I can only imagine the
shock you felt when
you learned of it.
How sad you
must have been.
How you've suffered.
My dear, you can
tell me the truth;
you don't have to hold
everything inside.
Yes.
Listen closely.
Neither of us could
escape our fate as the
Nine Tails' vessel.
However...
There is something that
you must understand:
There is a way to find
happiness even if you must
live as a Jinchuriki.
And the first step is...
...to fill ourselves...
The first step is...
to fill ourselves with love.
Then, even if we had to live
as the  Nine Tails' Jinchuriki,
we could still find
a way to be happy.
That is what Lady
Mito taught me.
So you were actually happy
even though you were still
the Jinchuriki, Mom?
Mm-hmm!
[sniffs]
[sympathetic chuckle]
Naruto, there's no need
for you to cry, is there?
[chuckle]
Hold on.
What is it?
So what happened when Nine Tails
attacked the Hidden Leaf Village
sixteen years ago?
Dad told me that the entire
thing was all because of
that guy from the Akatsuki,
the one who wears the mask.
How come you had
the Nine Tails, Mom?
I don't get it!
Your father left just a
few things out when he
talked to you, I suppose.
But it wasn't his fault.
You see, he keyed the sealing
jutsu to give me more time
with you than he got.
And there was so much
going on back then, anyway.
However, he was right.
When the Nine Tails attacked
the Hidden Leaf Village
sixteen years ago,
that masked man
from the Akatsuki
was behind it all.
But right up until
the moment that the
attack happened,
the Nine Tails was still
sealed inside of me.
Then what happened?!
It was that masked man.
I have no idea how he
discovered it, but he
knew the secret.
What secret?
Somehow he found out about
the one and only time that
a Jinchuriki's Tailed
Beast seal weakens.
He timed it perfectly
and stole Nine Tails
from me.
Hold on a second,
the one time that
the seal weakens?
When does that happen?!
Please, tell me!
In childbirth.
During the nine months
between when a female Jinchuriki
gets pregnant and gives birth,
the seal holding back
the Tailed Beast
weakens proportionally.
as the energy that's normally
used to maintain it is instead
diverted to the growing baby.
So, then...
It was on October tenth,
sixteen years ago.
[female doctor]
Congratulations!
Huh?
Your due date works out to be,
let's see, October tenth!
Oh, that's great!
What?! A baby?!
That's right!
I'm gonna be a
mother, ya know!
And I'm... gonna be a father...
I'm gonna be a mother,
ya know!
And I'm really going
to be a father!
I'm gonna be a
mother, ya know!
[giggle]
Wow, imagine that,
I'm going to be a father!
[both laugh]
[Third Hokage]
Kushina.
There is something
important that I must
explain to you about giving
birth as a Jinchuriki.
It was the same way
with Lady Mito.
When she gave birth,
Nine Tails' seal almost
came completely undone.
I apologize, but considering
the worst-case scenario,
we've decided to have you
give birth inside a barrier
away from the village.
I'll be there, too.
I do have to
monitor the seal.
Minato and Taji of the Anbu
Black Ops will accompany you.
As will my wife, Biwako.
This must be done
in utmost secrecy.
Mm.
You'll have bodyguards as well.
They'll all be Anbu Black Ops
directly assigned to me.
I'll go on ahead and make
sure everything's ready.
And I shall guide you
to the location.
Kushina!
Ah! Oh, yes.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
[Biwako]
We should leave soon.
[Kushina]
Right.
Oh!
Ah!
Wow!
You had a girl?
[chuckle]
No, he's a boy.
What a
lil' cutie!
Hi there, little guy!
What's your name, handsome?
It's Sasuke.
[Biwako]
Oh!
He was named after the father
of Lord Third then, was he?
Yes. So he will grow up to be
a strong, splendid shinobi.
You're due pretty soon,
too, aren't you, Kushina?
You ought to start thinking
about baby names, as well!
Actually, I've
already decided!
We're going to
call him Naruto.
He'll be classmates with
little Sasuke, here.
I hope you two
get along!
By the way...
Does it really hurt
like they say?
Wow, so there's actually
something that scares you!
Shocking!
Ah!
Come! Let's go, Kushina!
Yes, ma'am!
[chuckle]
The details of your
birthing are supposed
to be secret, remember?
Until we get to our
location, you must avoid
all contact with anyone,
even friends.
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry about that.
[Biwako]
Also, although we'll be
outside the village,
this is to remain covert.
So when your labor pains
start, do not cry out,
understand?
[Kushina]
Oh. Yes, ma'am.
Aaaahh!
It hurts, ya know!
[struggling with pain]
[Minato]
I've never seen Kushina in
so much pain before that
she's cried out like this.
Is... Is she really
going to be okay?
Yes, she's going
to be fine.
Now forget about that
and just stay focused
on the Nine Tails' seal!
Hnnn... Aaagh!
Okay... But she's so...
You're the Fourth
Hokage, Minato!
Now act like it
and get a grip!
Most men would have dropped
dead from such pain long ago!
But women are
much stronger!
[roar]
He's so strong!
The Nine Tails is
writhing to get out!
Hang in there, Kushina!
Naruto! Come on!
Hnnnhhh...
I can see the head now!
You're almost there, Kushina!
Just hang in there!
You're doing great!
[roar]
Naruto! Hurry up! Come out!
You stay in, Nine Tails!
[struggling with pain]
[baby crying]
[Biwako]
Hot water! Now!
[Taji]
Got it!
[frightened villagers]
No! No!
[Third Hokage]
Why is the Nine Tails loose?!
Was Kushina's seal released?
[shinobi]
Do not falter! Even if we can't
defeat the Nine Tails, we must
allow the villagers to escape!
[Minato]
As Hokage, I must protect
the village, my family.
This is what I have
to do right now.
[Third Hokage]
Next Time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Fourth Hokage's Death Match!
[Minato]
I won't let you do this!