Huh?
He he he he he!
[chuckle]
[splash]
[crashing]
[Suigetsu]
For whatever reason, there are
a lot fewer guards around.
We might be able
to escape now.
Let's look
for Sasuke.
You go on
ahead of me.
I'm going to go look
for my blade before
I do anything else.
I found the key to this
place easily, but I can't
find my blade anywhere.
Well, the samurai did
confiscate it from
you, didn't they?
So we should look
for an armory first.
Let's go.
Wow, you're going
to help me?
You're all right,
you know that, Jugo?
Unlike that Karin.
Where is she,
anyway?
Want to look
for her?
Hmm. You know, ironically,
it's almost too quiet
without her around.
Decisions, decisions.
I'm beginning to understand
the enemy's strategy.
But now it's gonna be my turn!
[Kabuto]
[chuckle]
I'm not so naïve as to
allow the enemy time
to catch their breath.
[together]
Summoning Jutsu!
[gasp]
This is unbelievable.
No way...
Is that?!
[Kakashi]
Former members of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist!
And out of all the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist,
these are the most
powerful ever!
They chose well.
[Kakashi]
The Seven Ninja Swordsmen.
Ready, Ensui Platoon?
I still need a
bit longer!
[Kakashi]
What about you,
Maki of the Hidden Sand?
My team is ready to roll, sir!
All right. We need to buy
time for Ensui's platoon.
We'll all attack as one!
Aw man, it doesn't
look like my sword
is here, either.
You said you wanted to
collect all the lost
Hidden Mist Blades.
But why are you so
obsessed with this
quest of yours?
Hey, come on! You offered
to help me with this.
You giving up on me already?!
No, you're the one who
always gives up, Suigetsu.
But when it comes
to those blades,
you're very focused.
Tsh.
I just gotta have
something that keeps
pushing me forward.
And, well, I've always had this
dream of resurrecting the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist and
then becoming their new leader.
Resurrect them?
Yeah.
Right now, the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist
consists of just a single
brat named Chojuro.
Traditionally, the ninja
blades are handed down from
generation to generation.
But other than the Great
Twin Sword Hiramekarei,
the rest have gone missing.
I assume Kisame has Samehada,
but he's a rogue ninja. And the
Executioner's Blade that I'd
found is gone again.
So officially, that unit
doesn't even exist today.
For now, anyway.
"The First and
Last Opponent"
It's no use. No matter
how many times we attack,
it has no effect.
What can we possibly do
against an enemy like that?!
They're the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen, plus they can't die!
The longer we fight,
the greater our
disadvantage.
Look, quit
worrying so much!
The Reanimation Jutsu can still
be stopped by sealing away the
soul or immobilizing the body.
And other than Zabuza,
none of them have weapons.
So that means all of them are
at half strength right now.
No.
[Kakashi]
It looks like they brought
their blades, all right.
But they're not
at full power.
[Guy]
The mist is getting thicker.
Visibility is gone.
And there isn't any sound
with Silent Killing.
So we can't even hear them.
We must get rid of this mist,
or our forces will be at a
disadvantage.
Do you have a plan
to get rid of it?
I'm preparing
one as we speak.
All right, then I'll
leave you to handle it.
Lee, you go after
Scorch Style!
I'll take Explosion Style!
Understood!
Captain Kakashi!
Shadow Possession and
Shadow Paralysis ready!
Good, then
fasten it to me.
Ensui, I need you to
start by following my
moves with a loose Shadow
Posssession Jutsu, okay?
Right!
Santa Yamanaka, use your
Mind Transfer Jutsu to
trade places with me.
With your sensory skills,
you should be able to
track and find Zabuza,
even in this mist!
Got it!
Once you locate Zabuza,
Santa, Ensui will get my
body within visual range
using Shadow Possession.
Get me behind him
as close as you can.
Santa, once you see Zabuza,
release the Mind Transfer
Jutsu to return my body to me.
While fighting Zabuza,
I'll step on his shadow
to connect it to mine.
At that point, Ensui, you'll
immediately power up Shadow
Possession and Shadow Stitching
Jutsu in order to bind him.
Then Maki, completely
immobilize Zabuza with your
Cloth Paralysis Jutsu!
[Maki]
Yes, sir!
Let's do it!
Right!
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Now! The rest of us will
guard Captain Kakashi!
Yeah!
[Suigetsu]
Anyway, there are lots
of other blades, too.
And throughout
all of history,
there have been Ninja
Swordsmen other than only
Kisame, Zabuza, and Chojuro,
who have wielded
those blades.
The first one,
With the sharpest cutting edge
and swathed in lightning is the
Lightning Blade the Fang, "Kiba"
and its wielder Ameyuri Ringo.
And the wielder of
the Blunt Blade,
the Helmet-Splitter,
"Kabutowari" that smashes
through any defense,
Jinin Akebino.
Stabbing and piercing
through anything,
and sewing them together,
is the Long Blade, the
Sewing Needle, "Nuibari",
and its wielder
Kushimaru Kuriarare.
Adding the power of
explosion to swordsmanship,
The Explosive Blade,
the Spatter, "Shibuki",
and its wielder
Jinpachi Munashi.
Next, just like Kisame
Hoshigaki, a previous wielder
of the Great Blade Shark Skin,
"Samehada" Fuguki Suikazan.
And he who could handle all
seven blades, the man known as
the second coming of the demon,
my older brother.
Mangetsu Hozuki.
So hopefully,
If I have my way, I'll
get to become captain of
the new generation of the
Seven Ninja Swordsmen.
And then--
Enough.
You're talking
too loudly, and
far too much.
Aw, come on! I was
just about to get
to the best part!
But the sword you were carrying
around is broken, anyway!
Why don't you just get a
new one, or make a new
one for that matter.
You have no idea what
you're talking about, Jugo.
you know that blade has
a very special ability!
The Severing Sword, the
Executioner's Blade, cannot
be chipped or nicked.
A better way to put is
that it can heal itself.
as it slices up people
and absorbs their blood.
It uses the iron it takes
in to regenerate itself!
Found him!
Mind Transfer
Jutsu, release!
Good luck, Captain Kakashi!
Nice. He hasn't noticed me.
I got him!
[chuckle]
Well done, Haku.
The boy threw himself
in front of my attack!
He saved your worthless life,
at the cost of his own.
Zabuza's Hidden Mist style
keeps them concealed and
is the keystone to this
battle of numbers.
So I knew that Zabuza
would be their target.
The rest can just be
shields to defend him.
And of course Haku will
protect Zabuza as if his
life depends upon it.
[chuckle]
Even though he's
just a puppet now.
I bet it's turning out to be
quite an interesting production
out there on the battlefield.
He'd hack right through
the boy to take me down?
Captain Kakashi, no!
Agh!
Yagh!
Huagh!
Damn it. How do we fight
the enemy if we can't
see or hear them?!
Isn't Captain
Kakashi here yet?!
I've got the shadow
of one enemy!
But there hasn't been
enough contact time
with the second one!
So I can't freeze
his movements yet!
There hasn't been
enough contact time?!
You mean that
Zabuza has cut down
Captain Kakashi?!
Kakashi
Sensei!
I really wanna
go on another
A-rank mission!
Oh, no. Not a chance.
I still can't believe that we
all made it through safe and
sound against such powerful
enemies as Zabuza and Haku.
Aww.
Listen, don't worry,
you're going to get
to A-Rank eventually,
after you learn more
jutsu and do some
training to get stronger.
I guess so.
You're right about
learning more jutsu.
But I've also got to
find more things I
want to protect.
Hm?
It was something that
Haku said to me.
He told me that when people
are protecting something that
is truly precious to them,
that's when they can
become genuinely stronger.
I see. And you agree
with him, do you?
You bet! After watching Haku
with Zabuza, I know he's right!
[chuckle]
Hey, um, wait a second,
Kakashi Sensei.
Tell me something.
What do you think?
About what?
I'm glad that you two were
Naruto's first adversaries.
Maki, until I give the signal,
stay behind me. Get the Cloth
Paralysis Jutsu ready!
Yes, sir!
[panting]
Why? Why can't I
keep up with him?
Haaaaah!
I knew you didn't
have what it takes
for the long haul.
What did you say?
[Kakashi]
You have no idea what
real strength is.
Zabuza. you hesitated in
slicing through Haku
that day on the bridge.
You simply couldn't hide
the unrest in your heart
over Haku's death.
But things are
different today.
You're just an
emotionless tool.
So let's just get this
senseless fight over with!
[Naruto]
Hey, um, wait a second,
Kakashi Sensei.
Tell me something.
What do you think?
About what?
Well. I know that
those two were our
enemies and all.
But you know what?
Actually...
Well, I...
I kinda liked those guys!
Huh?
What is it? Is that
weird or something?
Heh heh heh heh.
[Kakashi]
No.
I feel the same way.
Ensui! Bind him!
That's my signal!
All right!
Shadow Paralysis Jutsu!
The way you died
and your tears.
They demonstrated your
bond to each other.
As a shinobi, I've got
plenty to protect, too.
Protecting the way that
Zabuza and Haku died,
is one of those things.
Especially since I was-
and am again-
their final enemy.
Naruto. What do you think?
Now, Maki!
Do it!
Right!
Mh!
Damn it!
Look!
Is it...?
Yeah! The mist
is clearing up!
Yes! We can see
the enemy now!
[Maki]
As long as these tags remain,
they can't be summoned.
And I will watch over
these two personally!
All right.
This jutsu.
It really is
unforgivable!
Sai, next up we'll use the
Foundation's Sealing Jutsu.
So follow me!
But Kakashi, I haven't
mastered that jutsu yet.
Isn't it true that Danzo
valued you very highly, Sai?
You don't have
to suppress your
emotions now!
Well, It takes a quite
lot for me to lose my
temper too, you know.
But after this mess,
I've reached my boiling point.
I'm Kakashi the Copy Ninja;
I know a thousand jutsu.
And now, I'll use them all,
And live up to my name!
Attack!
Haaaa!
[barks]
Fang Over Fang!
Hidden Jutsu! Beetle Sphere!
Eight Trigrams Air Palm!
Eight Trigrams Palm Rotation!
Agh!
No! He's got Neji!
Egh! There are
just too many of them!
And they absorb
chakra, too.
Gentle Fist Technique!
Body Blow!
They just keep coming!
There's no end to these guys!
Quit whining!
And move!
These forces are so
strong and persistent!
This is going to be
a war of attrition.
Captain Kitsuchi!
There's a message from HQ!
Several thousand of the
enemy soldiers have
apparently gotten past us!
Dad, we
gotta--!
Be quiet!
I know!
Here they come now.
[Ao]
Who are those two shinobi?!
They possess the
Nine Tails' chakra!
And They have a lot of it.
[Raikage]
No, there's no mistaking it.
The Gold and Silver
Brothers of the Cloud!
[Tsunade]
Even Dan has been revived?!
[Raikage]
Now that it's come to this,
I must go join the battle!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Brilliant Military Advisor
of the Hidden Leaf
[Tsunade]
So, what do we do?