-Go to the Tenchi
Bridge in the village
hidden in the grass 10
days from now at noon.
One of Orochimaru's henchmen
is working for me as a spy.
And that's where I'm supposed
to rendezvous with him.
However, I don't think I--
-Why has it grown so
quiet inside the cave?
Could it mean that
the fight is over?
Neji, can you hear me?
Neji?
-What is going on in
the enemy's hideout?
-Hang on just a minute.
I'll check.
-Looks like it's been settled.
The fight's over.
-Did you say the fight's over?
Well, who won?
-Is Sakura-- Sa-- Sakura!
Where is Sakura?
What has happened to her?
-Sakura's all right.
I see her and Lady
Chiyo walking out.
-Excellent.
That means they beat
that Akatsuki swine.
NARUTO: I would expect
no less from Sakura.
-Unfortunately, that's doesn't
mean our problems are over.
MIGHT GUY: What do you mean?
-There were two of the
Akatsuki in that cave.
Even though one of
them's been defeated,
this jutsu is still in effect.
Which means--
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
Which means either
it was the other
who cast the jutsu--
-Or else.
-This jutsu can't be broken,
even if the one who cast it
is beaten.
NEJI: It's a
definite possibility.
-Huh?
-That just means we will have to
defeat these clones on our own.
[theme song]
-Lady Chiyo.
Here.
Let me heal you.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): But
this is only a stop-gap.
It won't save her.
I still have to do something
about the poison that
got into her system.
All of the antidote I made
in the Hidden Sand is gone,
and I can't make more
because I used up
their limited supply
of the herbs I need.
If I can arrange to have
the ingredients transported
to the Sand quickly enough we
might just make it in time.
-Hurry.
You and I have to quickly
get back to the village.
I'll make another
batch of the antidote.
-No.
-Why not, Lady Chiyo?
We have to get back and
neutralize that poison.
And quickly.
Our job here is finished.
We beat him.
-But more than that--
there's something I must do.
My job isn't done.
Yet.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
A new Sharingan.
-Hm?
What is it?
-Kakashi-Sensei, don't sweat
it if this doesn't work.
Because if it doesn't, I'll
make sure to settle things
once and for all.
-Yeah.
I'm sure you will,
if it comes to that.
-Right.
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER):
What's this?
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
Just as I feared.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER):
How can this be?
-How can these guys be even
stronger than they were before?
-It is true.
If anything, his blows have
even more force than they did.
-No.
Our enemies aren't
getting stronger.
That's not it.
-Exactly right.
The fact is that
we're getting weaker.
-We've gotten weaker?
Do you know why, Neji?
Why?
-Yes.
Why do we grow weaker
and they do not?
-It makes sense when
you think of it.
It was that jutsu.
-All right, everyone.
Get ready to remove the
tags on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three!
-By breaking those seals we
created clones of ourselves,
not only identical
to us in appearance
but possessing all
the physical abilities
that we possessed at the
moment the seals were broken.
That's why defeating
them is so difficult.
But of course, we are all
made of flesh and blood.
Unlike them we grow weaker the
longer the fight continues.
We get less precise
in our movements,
and in executing our jutsu.
And the weaker we get,
the stronger they seem.
-We get tired, and they don't.
So, basically, the longer
this fight drags on,
the bigger our disadvantage is.
-That's about it.
-No way.
-Well, if that is the
case, the only thing to do
is not let this fight drag on.
We must beat them now!
-Oh, no!
-Damn you.
What now?
-Sakura.
-Lee?
Are you-- what's going on there?
-The answer is so simple.
-What do you mean?
-I just figured it out.
I know how to defeat them.
It is so obvious.
-It is?
Really?
-All right, let's hear it, then.
-You really mean it?
You're not just trying
to keep our spirits up?
-No.
I have a sure-fire method.
We just need to make
ourselves stronger
than we were when our
clones were created.
These clones have the
same strength levels
that we had at the moment
we removed the seals.
Now do you get it?
If we increase our
strength levels
from what they were
at that point in time
it is reasonable to think
we will defeat them.
-Brilliant deduction, Lee.
Brilliant.
Then again, you're my student.
-Hold it.
I guess that all makes sense.
But how are we supposed to
make ourselves stronger all
of a sudden?
-Tenten, have you forgotten?
The motto we learned
during our training?
Stronger than we were yesterday.
Remember?
It was those words in our
hearts that kept us going,
that got us through
our darkest hours.
-What's the matter?
Are you giving up already?
The three of you got no
further than you did yesterday.
-Give up?
No.
-We're not going to stop yet.
Not 'til we beat
yesterday's mark.
-That's right.
We all have to get stronger.
-Stronger than we
were yesterday.
-Stronger than yesterday.
-Stronger that we
were yesterday.
-Stronger than we
-Thanks to that training,
Tenten, you and I became Juni.
And Neji became a Jonin.
All because we
worked hard every day
to be better than we
were the day before.
But are we satisfied with
how far we have come?
Do we stop now?
No!
No, that day will never come
when I do not strive to be
better than I was--
yah!-- yesterday!
Better than I was an hour ago!
Better than I was a minute ago.
-Yes, making Jonin
meant a lot to me.
But I've never believed
it was my final goal!
-And I've no
intention of retiring.
At least not any time soon.
-It's not like I'm ready
to give up, either.
Not by a long shot!
Hya!
-Feel this!
The full power of youth!
-Eight trigrams-- strike!
-Weapon control, tensesai!
-Great leaf blast!
-All right.
[music playing]
NARUTO: Sorry we're late,
but I told you not to worry.
Kakashi-Sensei's here, and
he's got a new jutsu that's
gonna finish
Deidara permanently.
SAKURA: Good old
Kakashi-Sensei always
likes to keep us in suspense.
NARUTO: Plus he never gives us
a straight answer to anything.
But he always comes
through in the end.
SAKURA: You bet.
He hasn't been around all
these years for nothing.
NARUTO: He's a wily old veteran.
SAKURA: And experience
beats youth every time!
KAKASHI: Uh-- thanks, guys.
Was that supposed
to be a pep talk?
NARUTO: Next time--
Kakashi Enlightened!
[music playing]
KAKASHI: A thorough
knowledge of hand signs
is indispensable for the
effective casting of ninjutsu.
Today we're going to
study these signs.
While there are some
special exceptions,
there are essentially 12
basic sign combinations.
Naruto, will you demonstrate?
-OK.
Ne, Ushi, Tora, U, Tatsu, Mi,
Uma, Hitsuji, Saru, Tori, Inu,
I.
-Let's try combining some of the
signs to cast the clone jutsu.
It's made by combining
the Hitsuji, or sheep, Mi,
or snake, and Tora,
or tiger, signs.
-Everybody paying attention?
Here we go.
Hitsuji, Mi, Tora.
Hm?
Ahh!
What the--
-Oh, boy.
-What happened?
The shadow clone
jutsu's my specialty.
-Well, were you able to do it?
I sure hope so.
We'll see you next time.