We've been waiting
for you, Sasuke.
It had already been decided
that the moment you abandoned
the Hidden Leaf Village you
would become our new leader.
I hope you can
forgive the rudeness
we displayed earlier.
(Sasuke)
Like I care.
Let's go.
It begins now.
(Shikamaru)
Naruto!
Hey, Naruto!
What is it,
Shikamaru?
Seems Sasuke has left
the village. And he's
headed for Orochimaru's.
[groan]
No way!
You gotta
be kidding!
There's a strong possibility
that Orochimaru's men are
guarding Sasuke. Our mission
is to bring him back.
Hold on a second!
I'll go get dressed!
Oh well,
at least
I got five
and a dog.
Alright!
C'mon!
Follow me!
Wait.
[grunt]
I saved the
most important
thing for last.
For as long as I've known
him, Sasuke and I haven't
exactly been close...
in fact I don't like him.
[gasp]
But all the same,
Sasuke's a comrade
he belongs to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
I'd trade my
life for his.
That's the way
of our Village.
That may be.
But to me,
Sasuke is a
close friend.
I don't say that just
because the two of us
were both in Squad Seven.
Even before
that, I...
Sasuke...
..has been a friend
of all of ours from
way back in the day.
Yeah. After all,
we were in the
same class.
I know one thing, that Sasuke
is talented. And I'm not going
to let the enemy take him.
[chuckle]
Thanks guys.
So let's go!
We're gonna get
him back for sure!
Okay, I'll explain
the formation we're
going to use.
Hang on,
Sasuke!
We're all on
our way to
rescue you!
Lord Orochimaru gave
us an important task
to take care of when
we reached this point.
I'm afraid you're
going to have to
die, just this once.
I must die,
this once?
You will take
one of these.
Awakening pills.
And just what'll
happen after that?
Not to
worry
Sasuke.
Why do you
think that
we're all
here?
We'll cast a Barrier
Ninjutsu to minimize
the transition.
Instead of dying,
you'll only be
suspended in a
state of half-death.
One thing's for sure,
I can't afford to die.
Not yet.
All right,
then...
[pained groan]
Now!
[grunt]
Four Black
Mists Formation!
And now!
Black Seal!
There. That'll
hold him for
now.
[struggling]
You're weak,
Sasuke.
Damn it!
[grunt]
"Parting"
Sasuke!
[heavy breathing]
Are you gonna
run off again?
Hopeless little
knucklehead.
Just leave
me alone.
Sasuke.
[grunt]
[chuckle]
Look at you.
What's with
the angry face?
But why?
Why're you
doing this
to us?
I don't get it.
Why're you doing
it?!
Why should you
care what I do;
it's my concern,
not yours!
[grunt]
I have my own path
to follow now. And
neither you nor anyone
else can steer me from it.
Is that right, huh?
I will tell
you this much.
That my days of
playing ninja with
all you Hidden Leaf
brats, are finished.
Choji...
Neji...
Kiba...
Shikamaru...
Bushy-Brow...
All of those guys
risked their lives
to try to save you!
Well, wasn't
that nice of them.
(Naruto)
Not so fast!
You gonna tell
me your comrades
risked their lives
for nothing?!
Choji...
I'll handle 'em.
This guy is mine.
Yeah but Choji,
this is...
Shikamaru,
just take everybody
and get out of here!
What are you
talking about!?
This isn't the kind
of guy you can take
on your own!
What did the five of us join
together for? If we lose
Sasuke. We'll be just what
this guy says we are..
..a stupid idiot of
a leader, and his
band of rejects!
Yeah, okay.
But you'd better
catch up with us,
Choji.
[grunt]
Alright.
Let's move!
[chuckle]
Once I finish you off
here, kid, your friends
are gonna be next!
Choji!
[pained groan]
Go already!
Neji...
(Neji)
Go on you guys.
I'll take care
of him.
[whimper]
Huh?
Well, looks like
this guy's stronger
than that big guy
we fought before.
Much stronger.
We're going to have
to go one-on-one to
have any chance for
success.
Isn't that what
you said?
Yeah.
That's what
we agreed.
If we all stay here
we won't be able to
catch up with Sasuke.
Naruto.
Sometimes your
eyes are even
better than mine.
Huh?
Wherever he is...
Sasuke is in
the darkness.
Now go! I'll
follow soon.
Hm.
[grunt]
Let's do
this thing.
When you catch up,
make sure you bring
Choji!
[bark]
Oh, no you don't!
[grunt]
Kiba...
Shikamaru...
Here, catch!
[grunt]
Good work, Kiba!
Okay, got it!
Don't worry,
I'm coming!
Little punks.
Do they really
think they'll get
away with this?
You heard him,
Shikamaru! It's
time to pull out
now!
You think
it's that easy!
Man! He's fast.
Akamaru!
[bark, bark]
Once you've
set the bombs,
get moving!
[jump grunt]
That's the last
time you'll bark
at me, you mutt!
[pained yelp]
[whimper]
Akamaru, no!
[grunt]
[scream]
Kiba!
Akamaru!
No! Damn it!
You're mine now!
There's no other way.
I'll have to take care
of this one. You take
the coffin and carry
on with the mission.
Shikamaru...
Just get going!
What?
Kimimaro.
You were taking
too long, Tayuya.
Why have you
come back here?
I understand much more now.
The strength of my life force
has increased since I escaped
the prison of human flesh.
I've had a taste of
Lord Orochimaru's
magnificent dream.
Orochimaru...
This vessel,
is an important
part of his dream...
I've had just
about enough of
this nonsense!
I'm takin'
Sasuke back
now!
[pained yell]
[groan]
[grunt]
I'll just leave
those two pieces
of garbage to you.
Look, I've got this;
you go after Kimimaro,
all right?
Are you
serious?!
Trust me. I'll
take care of this.
Bushy-Brow...
The moment I've
been waiting for.
It's come,
at last.
The first step
toward achieving
Lord Orochimaru's
design.
[grunt]
Sasuke...
Hey, Sasuke! What're
you hanging out with
these losers for?
C'mon! Let's
go home now!
[chuckles]
[grunt]
Talk to me!
What, have you
gone deaf or
something?!
Hey, wait!
Sasuke!
It's no use.
Die!
Leaf Hurricane!
Who's this?
The rejuvenated
Leaf Village's
Handsome Devil.
Rock Lee!
Bushy Brow?
But- What about
your injuries?
Do not worry
about me, Naruto.
Go get Sasuke!
Go on, get going.
I can take care
of things here.
Not so fast!
You gonna tell me
your comrades risked
their lives for nothing?!
Sasuke!!
Don't you have any
idea at all about
what being a comrade
actually means?!
[grunt]
Wake up!
Before it's
too late!
Yeah.
I have woken up,
don't you see?
That guy who dreamed of a
happy future full of peace
and friendship, he was the
one who was asleep till now.
If I'd stayed with
comrades like you
I'd never would have
gotten this strong.
Huh?
That's why I
left the village.
Now I'm
going to where
Orochimaru is.
All he wants is
to use your body
like a new suit
of clothing!
[struggling]
I couldn't care
less what you
want.
[grunt]
[pained groan]
I do not dream
of the future
any longer...
Only the past.
That's where
my dream lies.
Naruto... You can't
possibly understand
my dream of exacting
revenge on my own kin.
Like me, you may
be one of the few
who can use Mangekyo
Sharingan.
But there
is a catch.
Take the life of
your best friend.
You must kill him.
Brother!
No matter what darkness may
await me, if it means killing
you, I will meet it head on.
And whatever happens,
I will get that power.
[gasp]
Neji, it's just like you said.
Sasuke is in depths of darkness
right now...
He seriously wants
to kill me! I can't
believe it!
You finally get
it, huh? Yeah,
I'm going to
kill you!
What am I
to you now?
We were comrades,
or did you forget
that?!
Are you tellin' me that all
the things we did together
in Squad Seven, mean absolutely
nothing to you now?
They weren't
meaningless.
One thing was
worthwhile...
We became
best friends.
Then why are
we fighting?!
Because we're friends,
there's far more meaning
in destroying you.
Sorry, I can't
understand that..
But I guess for some
reason you want to
destroy me, right,
Sasuke?
Chidori!!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!!
Sasuke actually came out and
said that we're friends. And
now, I'm gonna put it to the
test with this Rasengan!
Damn it!
I don't believe it.
He was able to counter my
chidori at its full power.
That's it. There's no
mistaking it now...
You're dead serious
about this, aren't you.
You really
mean to...
Sasuke...
...the truth is...
you and I are friends!
Maybe I was the only one...
who thought... who thought
that we were friends...
The Mangekyo Sharingan..
I have to kill my closest
friend...
[grunt]
What is?
What's this
red chakra?!
Sasukeeeee!
I'm not letting
Orochimaru take
you away!
I'll break every single
bone in your body if
that's what it takes
to stop you!
Enough of this!
What in the
heck are you?!
I'm your friend.
[struggling]
Snap out of
it already!
If you don't come to your
senses, then I'm just gonna
hafta break all your bones and
drag you back to the village!
Shut up
for once.
What do you know
about it? You never
even had a family in
the first place.
You were on your own right
from the beginning! What
makes you think you know
anything about it, huh?
I'm suffering because
I have those ties...
[grunt]
How on earth could you
possibly understand
what it feels like to
lose all that?!
It's true. I have no
idea what it's like..
having parents, or a
brother.
But..
..when I'm with you...
I wonder... if this is
what it feels like to
have a brother...
Why, Naruto.
Why would you go
so far for me...
It's the first time...
That I've ever had
a bond like this...
[gasp]
That's why I'll do
anything I can to,
to stop you.
A bond, huh?
You're right, Naruto.
I felt it from the very
beginning too.
Come on,
Naruto!
If that's how it is, then I
guess I have no other choice.
I'll just have to sever that
bond.
just like
that, huh...
Then why bother
with that headband
anymore?
I'll admit it.
You're definitely
strong.
Huh?
It's because you
know the pain that
solitude brings.
Just as I do.
Naruto, that
pain makes
you and I
stronger.
Which means if I can just break
that bond... I'll be able to
achieve even greater strength!
It's time you and
I had this out.
As equals.
But you're still not gonna
be able to lay even a single
scratch on my forehead. I know
that hasn't changed at least.
Fine. Guess there's
no point in talkin'
anymore...
Sasuke!
Enough. No more words.
From here on out, we
stick to fighting.
Come!
[attack yell]
Hurry!
He's in really
bad shape.
It's the Medical Corps!
Please, tend
to him first!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine;
now just go look
after the others,
all right?
I wonder if Naruto
was able to catch
up to Sasuke.
Please, just let me
make it in time.
I guess we're
at the end.
The end of
this fight.
Rasengan!
Chidori!
Naruto...
I am...
...an avenger.
Kakashi-sensei?
You're awake.
Where's Sasuke?
He's gone.
I'm..
sorry,
Sakura.
I've been waiting
for you, Sasuke.
I'm glad you've
finally arrived.
I want more power.
Of course...
Just follow me.
Itachi...
I will get my hands on that
power. But not the way you want
me to. I'm going to surpass
you, but I'll do it my way!
(Naruto)
I'll never give
up on you, Sasuke.
no matter what.
Whatever you
may say, we
are friends.
Now and forever.
Madara's Akatsuki army of
Reanimated Shinobi and White
Zetsu troops numbers one
hundred thousand.
Opposing them, the Allied
Shinobi Forces, led by Gaara
and comprised of shinobi from
the Five Hidden Villages..
..as well as the samurai,
numbers eighty thousand.
The Fourth Great
Ninja War is about
to begin.
Next Time on
Naruto Shippuden:
"For My Friend."
I want to protect
my friend, Naruto!