[wind rushing]
And now this world
shall know Pain.
Almighty Push!
[blasting]
--[coughing] [gasping]
What happened?
No!
But why?
How could--
[tears splashing]
-Naruto.
Hurry.
[crying] Please.
Naruto!
[blasting]
-Wait, I don't get it.
Where are we?
-Where's the enemy
we're supposed to face?
-What's going on, Ma?
Why didn't you summon us to
the Hidden Leaf, like we asked?
-I'm afraid this is the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-I don't understand.
What you mean, Granny Shima?
-Just take a good
close look around.
[wind gusting]
-Huh!
There's no way!
-It's obvious to me
who did all this.
I sense the same
energies as when
we rode atop
Jiraiya-boy's shoulders.
[theme music]
[wind rushing]
[rocks crashing]
-Lady Tsunade,
are you all right?
-Nngh.
Aah.
Huh?
What is all this?
[growling] Damn you.
You will pay.
This is unforgivable!
[gasping]
-The mark on her
forehead's gone.
She's already released her
Mitotic Regeneration Jutsu
and given her chakra
to Lady Katsuyu
to protect the villagers
from Pain's jutsu.
So now she's powerless.
-Nngh.
-You all right, Iruka?
Talk to me.
-Please forgive me.
It took everything that I
had just to cover all of you.
-You're not to blame
for this, Lady Katsuyu.
(TO HIMSELF) I just hope
everyone else is all right.
[insects buzzing]
[rock cracking]
[clanging metal]
-Lady Shizune.
-[coughing] Wait!
Is Pa--
-Don't worry.
Choza is going to be OK now.
-Ah, thank goodness.
Huh?
Aah.
Kakashi-sensei.
[cryiing] Pa!
You tried to save me!
-Cry later, Choji.
If you can still move, you
must report Pain's abilities
to lady Tsunade and have
her set up countermeasures.
-I did it, Kakashi-sensei.
Your last orders were
carried out like you said.
I completed the mission, Sensei!
[rock cracking]
KIBA: Damn.
-Hang in there, Kiba!
--[grunting] Aw, you
gotta be kidding me.
Aah!
[thud]
-[chuckling] Piece of cake.
[barks]
-Are you doing all
right, Lady Hinata?
-Mmhmm.
But you're hurt.
-If you were injured during
Lord Hiyashi and Lady Hinabi's
absence, then I'm sure
I'd never be forgiven.
So you need not concern
yourself with me.
-Of course I do.
If anybody's injured while the
head of the family is away,
I will be the one who's scolded.
-Lady Hinata.
[fabric tearing]
(TO HERSELF): But this
attack-- it's unspeakable.
-Aaugh!
-Ah, Shikamaru!
Are you hurt?
Are you OK?
-Nngh, yeah.
What was it that hit us, anyway?
-You OK, Shikarmaru?
-Well, I'm still alive.
Although I think
my leg is broken.
-Then I think you should
count yourself lucky,
if that's all you
suffered in that attack.
-The thing is,
frankly, Shikamaru
was trying to protect me.
And he got hurt.
-All right, now.
It's not the time
or place for tears.
-They possess a jutsu
that's this powerful,
but they didn't
use it against us
when they first attacked
the village, which
means they had a
purpose in coming here.
They must have finally
fulfilled that purpose.
So they changed their approach
from guerrilla hit-and-run
tactics to an all-out offensive
on the village as a whole.
-But who are they?
-Well, it's someone who can do
this much damage to the Leaf
Village.
And all that I can think
of is the Akatsuki.
-I agree.
And that means that
their target must be--
-Yeah.
Naruto Uzumaki.
-Seriously?
Naruto?
-Mmhmm.
I sure wouldn't survive
very long if I relied solely
on luck, but it was
lucky to survive that.
Don't bother crying.
Just hope we don't get
hit by another attack.
(TO HIMSELF) Naruto.
-Wait, is that-- Naruto!
-Naruto?
[footsteps]
[gasping]
-Good.
Now I don't have
to hunt you down.
[footsteps]
[blasting]
[crunching]
-Why go to such extremes?
-Because this is
my form of justice.
-When all the chakra is
focused Intendo Pain,
his jutsu's effectiveness
is tremendous.
But so is the risk.
And the other five are
recovering more slowly
than the last time as well.
From here on out,
I look after you.
No more paper clones.
[rustling paper]
-Summoning Justu!
[poofing]
-All six Of them have
assembled together.
Tsunade?
--[breathing heavily]
I am the fifth hokage!
-Lady Hokage!
-How dare you trample
upon the jewel,
the dreams of my predecessors?
I won't forgive you.
I'll settle this now as hokage!
-It appears you understand
a little about pain.
However, I have no
need of you right now.
The one I seek--
[blasting]
-Is me!
-There's no need for
the Leaf's hokage
to bother herself with
the likes of them.
You just sit back and
sip some tea, Granny.
-Naruto--
-What's going on?
I can't tell from here.
-Amazing.
He took down one of the
Pains with one blow.
(TO HERSELF): Naruto, you--
-Well, grandfather.
What do you think?
Doesn't he remind you a
lot of those other two?
-Indeed he does.
(TO HIMSELF) Naruto-boy has
surpassed his predecessors.
-So you are Naruto Uzumaki.
-That's it!
Let's settle this.
(TO HIMSELF):
Tendo's powers won't
be fully recharged for quite
some time, which means--
-Gamakichi!
[thud]
-I want you to take Grandma
Tsunade someplace safe.
-Gotcha.
-Granny, I'll take
over from here.
Keep the rest of the
village out of this.
I can't be worrying
about everyone else,
not during this fight.
-All right.
But here.
Please take Katsuyu.
I'm sure she'll come in handy.
She has Intel on
all of the Pains.
[squishing]
-Go, Katsuyu-girl.
Just keep yourself hidden
inside Naruto-boy's clothing.
-I-- I probably shouldn't
bring this up right now,
but now that I've
mastered nature energy,
I'm able to sense
everybody's chakra.
Is Kakashi-sensei on a
mission away from the village?
I see.
Go, Gamakichi!
-Summoning Jutsu!
[thud]
[gasps]
-My lady.
Lady Tsunade!
-Sakura.
It's all right now.
[breathing heavily]
-Yes.
Thank you for your
labors, Lady Tsunade.
-Hwah!
-Summoning Jutsu!
[blast]
BOTH: Let's go!
Sage Art, Frog Song!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
[poof]
-Sage Art!
Giant Rasengan!
Bunta-boy!
Ken-boy!
Hiro-boy!
-Hey.
-Naruto, ninjutsu doesn't
work on the Pain right
in front of you.
He will merely absorb any and
all ninjutsu-based attacks.
-OK, Frog Kumate it is.
[thwap]
KATSUYU: All the Pains
are visually linked.
A blind-spot attack is
useless, unless you're out
of the other sight line.
[thwogg]
-Well, then.
I'll show them an attack
that they can't see.
-You insolent mutt!
[thwogg]
-And stay down, dog!
-As you see, I'm ungraceful.
-Nngh!
Hungh!
[thwogg]
[slice]
[poof]
[thudding]
-Just lie down, ya mutt!
(TO HIMSELF): I
thought we dodged that.
-Frog Kumite utilizes the nature
energy all around the wielder.
That energy became
part of Naruto
and attacked Pain
alongside Naruto's strike.
In Sage Mode, both threat
perception and attack capacity
are enhanced well
beyond the ordinary.
-That's it.
I can't waste anymore time.
I'll finish this
with my new jutsu.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-I see.
So you've become a sage.
Then you've mastered the
same jutsu as Jiraiya-sensei.
-Jiraiya.
You called him sensei?
-That's right.
I also learned
jutsu from Jiraiya.
He was once my master as well.
And that makes us
sibling students.
Sharing the same
sensei, we ought
to be able to
understand each other.
Our master desired peace.
-Just shut the hell up, already!
-What a massive
amount of chakra.
Did you teach him, that, Pa?
-No.
First time I'm seeing it, too.
He never did that
during our training.
I wonder what Naruto-boy's
planning to do now.
-What's that jutsu?
-What's happening?
-Naruto's chakra
is forming a-- I
think it looks almost
like a shuriken.
-Wind Style Rasen Shuriken?
Naruto, what're--
-Everything you've done
here, all this destruction,
what part of all
that is peaceful?
-You simply cannot see
the forest for the trees.
You're not able to comprehend
the true meaning of peace
or what I'm trying
to accomplish.
Just let yourself be captured.
Surrender, and your
death will lead to peace.
-I already told you,
shut the hell up!
-He threw it!
-He what?
[theme music]
SHIMA (VOICEOVER): Pa!
The lad's Sage Mode has run out!
It's going to be dangerous,
but merging with him
is our only chance now.
FUKUSAKU (VOICEOVER):
Except we can't.
The Nine Tails prevents
us from merging.
SHIMA (VOICEOVER): Then
what're we going to do?
FUKUSAKU (VOICEOVER):
Naruto-boy's
come up with his own unique
solution to this problem.
That's what he's about to do.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time
on "Naruto Shippuden," "Danger,
Sage Mode Limit Reached."
I'm counting on
you, Geezer-sage.
-Man.
Who'd ever thought that
you'd master Wind Style?
-Mmm, why do you say that?
-Ah, I was just
thinking out loud.
-Yeah, who woulda
guessed just back then
you'd end up being so strong.
[gulp]
-Huh?
-Wind Style, huh?
-It does have a pretty nice ring
to it, don't you think, Naruto?
-All right!
I am absolutely gonna
master this one.
-Yeah, right.
You can't even clone yourself.
-Just shut your mouth!
You--
--[laughing] Actually, I can
kinda use Wind Style right now.
Check it out, guys.
[humming] Here it goes!
Wind Style Grave Suction!
[vacuuming]
-See?
-Ahhh!
Come on, what kind of
lame Wind Style is that?
Even I could do
something like that.
Here goes.
Wind Style Fart!
-You idiot!
-Aah!
CROW: Idiot.
Idiot.
You're an idiot.
[theme music]