Wow, that place is
pretty impressive for
a building stuck out in
the middle of nowhere.
Well, I'm not sensing
any shinobi chakra in
the area nearby.
We going in?
No way. We're going
to the Hidden Leaf.
We don't have time for detours.
[panting]
Haaaaa!
Naruto!
How much stronger are
you going to get?!
Naruto!
No, I'm not done yet.
Huh?
"A raccoon dog, lived in a log,
high up on Senba Mountain.
"But that beast got caught,
by a hunter's shot,
And that raccoon dog was done."
The creature was grilled,
the hunter ate his fill,
And packed the rest in
leaves to keep it--
Oh!
Nngah!
Ah! Aaahhh!
[terrified squeaks]
What do you think
you're doing?!
You almost got
yourself killed,
you know!
Don't lecture me!
Just hurry and
pull me up!
Do you have any
idea who I am?!
Tcheh.
Oof!
How dare you!
I don't know who you are,
But you should be more careful.
Wait, come back here!
What is your name?!
Sasuke. Sasuke Uchiha.
Bye, Sasuke Uchiha...
Drive Toward Darkness
[Tsunade]
I have a mission for Team 7!
We've just gotten word that
some ninja on the national
Most Wanted Criminals list
have entered the Land of Fire.
Your team is to learn what
their objective is and
track their movements.
But there is one hitch.
I take it that things
aren't going well?
No.
Naruto has always been the one
trying to catch up to Sasuke.
He wants Sasuke's approval
more than anything.
Sasuke, on the other hand,
has seen Naruto's abilities grow
and has come to feel inferior.
Being rivals can be quite
difficult.
It reminds me of the
relationship between
Jiraiya and Orochimaru.
Well, all right.
I guess we should just
let them cool off a bit.
Just you and Sasuke will
go on this mission, then.
What about
Naruto and Sakura?
I happen to have the perfect
baby-sitting assignment for
them!
Baby-sitting?
[Tsunade]
The two of you have
been assigned to a
mission as bodyguards.
You can count on us,
Granny!
So, where is this person
that we're supposed to
protect, anyway?
Oh, did I forget
to introduce you?
This is Miss Naho.
That's me!
Huh?!
Seriously,
we're guarding--
[Tsunade]
This young lady.
What?! I thought that we
were gonna be bodyguards
for some VIP!
Don't be insolent,
short stuff!
Short stuff?!
You're shorter
than I am!
Enough, Naruto,
quiet down!
Miss Naho is related
to an important
feudal lord!
Augh.
Lady Hokage,
Are the two of
them really my
bodyguards?!
That's right;
they're the very ones!
There's no way I'd
feel safe with them!
Go and get me
Sasuke Uchiha!
D'ohh!
I'm very sorry, Miss Naho.
But Sasuke is away on
another mission.
I don't care! Have them
go on that mission instead.
I want Sasuke now!
Look, I assure you that
these two are full-fledged
Leaf ninja, too.
Just like
Sasuke.
But I'm making a
personal request here!
What's the deal with that kid?
Going on about Sasuke...
Maybe they know
each other?
[slamming on table]
Naruto! Sakura! Listen up!
Lady Naho has to get to
Shizume Village today to
inspect one of her properties.
Move it! On the double!
Go on! Go!
Get Lady Naho there!
If anything happens to her,
I will personally...
[crack]
[in unison]
Right, we got it.
Oh, I wanted Sasuke...
[Naruto]
I guess we have no choice;
we can't turn down a mission.
But don't worry;
we'll get you there,
I promise!
Bleh! That doesn't really
make me feel safer!
No! I refuse to go
anywhere unless
it's with Sasuke.
But you heard what
Lady Hokage said,
Sasuke's on another
mission and won't be
back for a while.
Then I'll just wait
until he does come back!
Huh!?
But what about
that whole
inspection thing?!
I don't really
need to be there.
But you do!
Look, why do you
have your heart set
on ~Sasukeo anyway?!
[dreamy giggle]
Aah, ha ha!
Because Sasuke actually
saved my life once already!
If Sasuke hadn't been there,
then I would have died.
But besides that,
He treated me like
a regular woman,
not just the relative of
some big Feudal Lord that he
hoped to get something from.
Oh really?
I trust Sasuke far more than
I'd ever trust the two of you!
I won't go anywhere
without Sasuke,
and that's my final word!
hmpf!
Well? What should we do?
Our assignment is to
get her to Shizume
Village by today.
I know. Plus,
Granny said,
If anything happens to her,
I will personally...
[crack]
[chuckle]
Naho! I promise you!
I will keep you safe!
Yes! There's no
one I'd trust more
than you to do it!
Hm hm!
You gotta act more
like Sasuke would,
all right, Naruto?
Hey, don't worry; I got this!
Stop doing things that
are out of character!
If Naho figures out that
we tricked her and demands
that we turn back, we'll
be in big trouble!
Yeah! I know that!
But just remember, she
doesn't actually know how
Sasuke usually acts, right?!
Hey, what are you
two guys whispering
about over there?
Are you trying to hide
something from me?!
Just shut up, already!
Ohh, Sasuke!
What are you doing?!
You don't have to get
all angry with her!
Give me a break! That's exactly
the way Sasuke always talks,
at least to me!
Sasuke, you're so cool!
It's practically enough
to melt a girl's heart!
Oh... Yeah?
Just keep acting cool!
She likes it!
Oh, good grief...
You know, now that
I think about it,
it does seem like something's
been bothering Sasuke lately...
Sasuke, I gotta
thank you!
I mean, you know, it's just
that, you protected me from
the Sand, right?
No.
It wasn't me
who rescued you,
it was Naruto.
What!?
[Naho]
I didn't feel safe with just
that goofy-looking kid.
Oh, thank goodness
you came, Sasuke.
Goofy-looking?!
Is she really
talking about me?
Damn it! How come Sasuke
is so popular, anyway?!
Sasuke, is something
the matter?
No, nothing's wrong!
[shivering]
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
Just a shiver,
that's all.
Our mission is to track
the movements of some
wanted criminals.
Don't let your guard down.
Got it.
[Sasuke(Naruto)]
Are we getting close to
Shizume Village yet?
I think it's just on the
other side of this forest.
Good, almost there.
You're the best, Sasuke...
[Sakura]
You know, when she's
asleep, she's actually
really cute.
I mean I still don't get it, But
I guess Sasuke is her hero.
Seems so.
[Sasuke]
Hardly anybody's here.
Yeah, it looks like
they've gone somewhere.
But the question is,
where, exactly?
Ah! Is this a plan for
a kidnapping?
This says it will take place
near Shizume Village...
Seems the target is a girl
named Naho, who's related
to the Feudal Lord.
Ah! Wait, I know that girl!
Who are you guys?!
Naho, I'm gonna have
to put you down.
Why? What's
going on now?
Get lost. We have no
business with you two.
What do you mean?
Target confirmed.
Hand over the girl
and we'll let you leave.
No way; I won't hand her
over to people like you!
That's right, Sasuke,
you tell 'em!
And if they won't listen
to you, then make
mincemeat out of 'em all!
That's just what I'm gonna do!
Sakura, keep Naho safe!
All right! Multi-Shadow
Clone Jutsu!
Whoa! There's so many!
Wow! Look at all those Sasukes!
Right! Let's do this!
Sasuke Punch! Ha!
Sasuke, you are just so awesome!
Sasuke Kick!
How wonderful!
Sasuke Chop, Chop, and Chop!
Mesmerizing!
Heh heh!
Haup!
Oof! Augh! Hoo!
Gimme a break.
Earth Style! Mudslide Jutsu!
[Sasuke Narutos
getting slammed]
Augh! Whoa! Wahh! Yahh!
Ah!!
Don't worry,
I got this.
Let's go!
U - zu - ma - ki!
Uh, I mean...
Lions Barrage!
He did it!
Huh?
A jutsu like that, Heh!
is useless against me!
You don't know when to quit.
Sasuke, go beat
that guy up for me!
Naho, Stay back!
It's dangerous!
This time, I'll make sure
you don't get back up!
Take this!
Rasengan!
Hauuugghh!
[heavy breathing]
Aww yeah!
How's that?!
Hey, Naho, Sakura, that was
pretty cool, wasn't it?
Huh?!
Sasuke! Please help me!
No! Naho!
Keep getting in our way,
and this girl will die.
But, I got you!
No, your attack failed.
That jutsu's strong but
it's incomplete.
Oh, yeah?
Augh!
What?!
No! Sasuke!
Wait a minute...
You're not Sasuke at all!
Sasuke, please,
come and help me!
Help, Sasuke!
[Pakkun]
I followed the trail
the ninja left...
[sniff sniff]
But the scent's mixed up here.
They must have gotten into a
scuffle with Naruto and Sakura.
We just missed them.
Why is Naruto even
involved in this?
Naruto and Sakura are both
currently on a mission as
bodyguards for that girl, Naho.
What was that?!
They're not here. So it must
mean they've been taken captive.
This is bad.
Summoning Jutsu!
We don't have much time.
Sasuke, I'm leaving
Pakkun with you.
We'll split up and
search for them.
Right, understood.
I don't get it.
We can ransom
the girl for money,
but not those ninja.
shouldn't we just've
gotten rid of them?
If we're up against ninja,
then having more hostages
couldn't hurt.
You guys are gonna
regret doing this to us!
When I get loose, you're
all toast!
A ninja who can't weave hand
signs isn't much of a threat.
Rrgh! You just wait;
you'll see!
Aum!
Hey! Cut that out!
Even if I can't weave
signs, I'll stop you!
Quick, Naho, run!
Aah!
[panicked cries]
Ah! Ahh! Yah!
Naho!
You can't escape.
Kids who try to run are naughty
and have to be punished.
Sasuke, please help...
I need you, Sasuke!!
[echoes]
Sasuke... Sasuke...
Yell all that you want. It's no
use; no one's coming to help.
[landing on dirt]
Huh?
[Sakura]
Sasuke!
huh, You're not bad.
So you're the real
Sasuke, then,
is that right?
The real one?
That brat over there
has been impersonating
you this whole time.
He did what?!
I had to because you were late!
Hey kid, we're here to help.
Pakkun!
Your friend actually
fought pretty well when
he was disguised as you.
So how about the real thing?
I'll show you right now.
Come on, let's go!
He's fast!
Sasuke!
Come on, bite through, already!
I'm doing my best,
you know!
What's taking so long?!
I'm working on it!
You're pretty tough.
And you're pretty lame;
an attack that weak
won't work on me.
Well, then how about this one?
Fire Style! Fire Ball Jutsu!
Sasuke!
Heh heh heh heh.
This just won't do at all,
will it?
I have to admit that I'll miss
the protection it gives me,
though.
Ahh. My original skin is
much more comfortable
anyway. It's lighter.
Unbelievable! He was
armored by Earth Style!
So that's it! That's why my
Rasengan didn't work before!
Now that you know the real me,
let's start over again,
shall we?
He's gone!
You didn't even try to dodge!
You're really not much of an
opponent, are you?
Sasuke!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Back off!
This guy is all mine!
Ooh, Sharingan.
So you're an Uchiha, then!
You know about the
Sharingan, do you?
As shinobi for hire,
my people have worked
in many places for
various employers.
In the last great war, members
of the Uchiha clan were among
the people we faced in battle.
Oh, that's right!
I do remember hearing that there
was one Uchiha named Itachi,
who betrayed the Hidden
Leaf Village and slaughtered
his entire clan!
But it appears that there
was a survivor among the
Uchiha after all...
Or could it be that perhaps,
you simply weren't
worth killing?
Oh, don't worry;
you're not even
worth killing.
You don't interest me
at the moment.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatsuki are after,
And we will have him.
Just shut up!
Oh, my, it seems that I've
touched a nerve and upset you.
That's exactly why...
Hyeaa!
...you're a fool!
Wha?!
Haauugghh!!
Sasuke, don't you
think that's enough?
Are you trying to tell me
what to do, now, Naruto?
Just stay out of it.
Stop, Sasuke...
You're scary.
Hmph.
Please,
spare me!
Kakashi!
[Naruto]
Kakashi Sensei!
You can stop now. We still
have a lot of questions that
we need him to answer for us.
Hey!
I'm going back
to the Village.
[sigh]
But why, Sasuke?!
I'm sorry.
He just, He's got a
lot on his mind now.
But he really
is a good guy,
I swear!
Just try to forgive him, okay?
Mm.
Yeah, that-a girl!
And one day when he's back
to his old self, I'll take
you to visit him.
Sasuke... I promise I'll
bring you back home...
[Sakura]
Did you say Danzo?!
He's the new Hokage?!
[Naruto]
And he approved
Sasuke's elimination!
[Kakashi]
Sasuke is a Rogue Ninja. It's
only because of Lady Tsunade
that he's been allowed to live.
[Naruto]
I'm going to
talk to Danzo!
[Sakura]
I'm going with you!
[Kakashi]
Calm down,
both of you!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"The Sixth Hokage Danzo"
[Naruto]
How are we supposed
to stay calm?!