[shattering sound]
‐What the?
‐Huh, they broke
down the barrier.
These Leaf ninja
aren't that bad at all.
‐Guren.
‐Hey, what are you?
Hmm.
‐Kakashi Sensei.
‐Reinforcements, huh?
‐Is everyone OK?
‐Naruto, was that?
‐Yeah, the collaboration
ninjutsu we've
been working on
with Pervey Sage.
‐Really?
‐Now it's my turn
to have some fun.
OK, you.
Don't try to escape.
‐Huh.
So another big
talker has shown up.
Are you all like this?
‐Hinata, you lousy.
Just what have you
done to her, huh?
‐Hmm hmm.
NARUTO: What's our next
move, Kakashi Sensei?
KAKASHI: As you can see,
Hinata's been taken hostage.
So we've got to keep our cool.
We can't just rush
in against her.
Besides, any shock, and
that crystal might shatter.
And Hinata with it.
‐A tricky situation.
‐Ha ha ha.
(VOICEOVER): We we will look
for an opening from above.
(VOICEOVER): Right.
‐You will realize that
you have only one option.
‐Hey, Gamatatsu, you
ready for one more?
(VOICEOVER): If you
return to your village,
and leave me alone,
I'll release the girl.
‐Yeah.
But just one more, OK.
‐I've got to control my chakra,
so Hinata doesn't get hurt.
‐Don't move.
‐Now Gamatatsu.
(VOICEOVER): Wait.
‐Wind style.
Tall water pistol.
‐Huh.
‐My crystal style can
crystallize anything.
You'll need about ten more years
experience to challenge me,
boy.
Crystal style:
Burst Crystal Falling Dragon!
‐Run, Gamatatsu.
‐Is everybody all right?
‐Yes sir.
(VOICEOVER): Man, what
the heck was that?
‐She not only
crystallized your jutsu,
she turned it against you.
Listen Naruto, I'll
get her attention.
When you see your
chance, grab Hinata
and get her away from here.
Got it?
‐But‐‐
(VOICEOVER): Naruto,
Hinata's safety
is our top priority right now.
‐All right.
‐What are you hiding for?
There's nothing you
can do as long as I
hold your little friend hostage.
Huh, it looks like
they're giving up.
‐Let Hinata go.
Take me as a hostage instead.
‐Nice try.
Huh.
‐Naruto, now.
‐Go, Gamatatsu.
[squeaking]
‐Oh no, you don't.
Uhh.
Dammit all.
Just look at my clothes.
(VOICEOVER): Guren.
Are you all right?
‐Yeah, yeah.
(VOICEOVER): I'm so
relieved to hear it.
‐Huh, they can sure move fast
when they're running away.
Rinji, keep an eye out.
Don't lose them.
‐Will do.
[theme music]
‐Way to go, Gamatatsu.
OK, you can spit her out now.
‐Be careful.
Gently now.
Nice and easy.
‐That's it.
That's the way.
Put her down slowly.
Slowly.
[fly buzzing]
‐Huh.
‐Hinata.
‐Unbelievable.
How could you do
that, you blockhead?
‐Oh.
Oh no.
No.
Stop cracking.
‐Hinata.
‐It stopped.
‐Damn.
Guess I'm too late.
‐Pakkun.
‐They finished analyzing
that insect of Shino's.
There's no mistaking it.
The enemy uses some kind
of crystal style jutsu.
‐Yes, we know.
‐The researchers say the effect
on the insect was thorough.
That thing was crystallized
inside and out.
‐So it was true what she said,
that her crystal style works
on anything.
‐Even Sai's super beast scroll
was completely crystallized.
This jutsu is a problem.
‐That's putting it mildly.
It's like I said, its
effects are thorough.
‐You mean‐‐?
‐Yeah.
They found that even the
insect's bodily fluids
were crystallized.
‐What?
But then‐‐
‐Hinata.
She's going to be OK,
right Kakashi Sensei?
‐Uhh, yeah.
We need to get her back to
the village immediately.
‐That's right.
Grandma Tsunade.
Grandma Tsunade
will fix everything.
‐OK, calm down Naruto.
[crystal shattering]
‐No, Hinata.
‐Sakura.
‐It's all right.
She's alive.
‐What a relief.
‐Yeah, I'll say.
‐Phew.
I was scared for a minute.
‐Idiot.
Dropping her for a lousy fly.
‐Huh, what is it, Shino?
‐I was remembering what happened
to one of those insects.
After it was captured by
the crystal style jutsu,
it shattered in my hand.
And yet, Hinata survived.
‐It's true.
The same thing happened with
those crystals we encountered.
They shattered.
What do Hinata and the
insect that was sent back
to the village have in common?
‐Uhh.
‐Be careful, Hinata.
Take it easy.
‐When I saw that I was going
to be hit by her jutsu,
I released chakra from all
my chakra points at once,
and surrounded myself
with a barrier.
‐I see.
So her crystal style doesn't
work on everything after all.
It can't crystallize chakra.
Hmm, quick thinking
in a tight spot.
Well done, Hinata.
‐Thanks.
‐Yeah, that was awesome.
Of course, I expected as much.
‐Woof.
‐Well, I'm glad you're OK.
‐I'm sorry, Naruto if I, well,
if I caused you any worry.
‐Hey, you don't
have to apologize.
Don't be silly.
‐Naruto.
‐All right, then Kakashi.
What do we do now?
Any thoughts?
‐Well, that depends.
‐Uhh.
I'm all right, sensei.
Really.
‐Don't push yourself.
‐We're lucky Hinata was the
only one hit by that jutsu.
‐Since we don't have any
countermeasures to this crystal
style, caution's the
best policy for now.
‐We should have gone after them.
Why'd we let them go?
‐I share your
frustration, Naruto.
We certainly don't want
to lose track of them.
‐He's right.
Remember how much trouble
it was finding them?
If we let them go, who
knows if we'll ever
be able to pick up
their track again?
‐All right, then.
Here's the plan.
There are enough of us
to split into two groups.
So, Sakura and Sai, you two
will stay here with Hinata
until she's recovered.
‐Right.
‐The rest of us will try
and pick up their trail.
Of course, since they
leave no scent behind,
it's impossible to
track them that way.
Even for Akamaru.
‐They don't make it
easy for us, do they?
‐But, how are we
going to track them,
if they're impossible to track?
‐I think we might be able
to use those surveillance
bats of theirs.
But we can't get too close.
We don't want them
spotting us first.
However we go, we have to move
deliberately and cautiously.
‐That makes sense.
‐Doesn't sound like fun,
but I guess it's a plan.
‐One more thing.
We have to be very
careful if we run
into any more of those
crystal barriers.
If you do find
any of these guys,
don't try to attack
or capture them.
After all, remember our
mission is to investigate them.
Got it?
‐Got it.
‐If you're done with us, I
guess we'll be on our way.
‐Thanks.
See you next time I need you.
‐I'll be heading
home too, Kakashi.
That all right?
‐OK, Pakkun.
Thanks for your help.
‐Well, see you later.
‐Bye, bye everybody.
‐All right then.
Let's move out.
‐Guren.
‐What is it?
Is everything all right?
‐I met somebody that I know.
‐What?
‐So, who was it?
‐The boy with the headband.
‐Headband, huh?
Could it be that
kid we just saw?
‐You say you knew
this boy from before.
Tell me how.
‐Oh yeah.
I met him when I was with
Kabuto the other day.
He told me about how we all
have a place to go home to.
He even asked me if I
wanted to go there with him.
But then I decided
not to go, because I
think there's somewhere else
I'll go home to some day.
‐A coincidence, you think?
‐Must be.
There's no way
they could possibly
know that Yukimaru has
anything to do with us.
All right, Guren, what's
our next move going to be?
‐There's only one move.
You're a good boy.
You did the right thing.
There's no where for you to
go home to with those people.
Your home is with me.
‐Yeah.
‐But this boy.
If he's a friend of yours,
I'd like to meet him.
Do you remember where you
saw him this last time?
(VOICEOVER): You
going to track him?
‐Yeah.
Once I decide to go after
something, I stick with it.
That's just the way I am.
(VOICEOVER): That's a
dangerous habit, Guren.
‐Kabuto.
‐If you're not careful, it
can get you into trouble.
‐What do you mean?
‐You don't feel even
a little bit guilty?
Because from what I
just heard, you're
very lucky they didn't take
this boy away with them.
And you know what would happen
if you were to lose Yukimaru.
Guren, you would also lose
Lord Orochimaru's trust.
‐I'm sorry, but the
rest of you will
have to stay here
and keep an eye out
for those meddlesome leaf ninja.
The last thing we want right
now is any kind of distraction.
‐Hold on.
You're really planning
on leaving us here?
‐Rinji, just shut up,
and do what Kabuto says.
‐If you say so.
Very well, I will obey.
‐Nothing personal.
All right, let's go.
From this point forward,
the fewer witnesses
there are, the better.
‐Why do you say that?
Is there something you
don't want people to see?
‐Well, it's not something
most people see every day.
That's for sure.
Just keep rowing.
You'll find out.
Is anything wrong?
‐Kabuto.
I, I have a bad feeling.
The last time I took the
medicine it made my head
hurt a lot.
‐Don't worry.
Everything's going to
be perfectly all right.
And if anything
does happen, Guren's
here to take care of you.
‐You are?
‐Yeah.
Of course I am.
‐I knew it.
It was a big mistake taking
our eyes off those guys even
for a minute.
And now we have to try and
pick up their trail again
from scratch.
‐And what's even
worse, we've got
to watch out for
those stupid bats.
‐There is another option.
Risky perhaps, but.
‐Sounds to me like you've
got an idea, Shino.
‐As Naruto said, keeping
away from the bats,
only makes our job
more difficult.
Perhaps we should reverse
our way of thinking
and, instead of avoiding
them, we use them.
‐Eh, how do we do that?
What do you mean?
‐If we continue to stay out of
the range of the bat's sonar,
they won't detect our presence.
And if they don't
detect our presence,
they won't report
back to their master.
‐Yeah, of course.
I think I get it now.
‐Now that You mention
it, you're right.
Good thinking, Shino.
‐Hey, wait.
What's the plan?
Does everybody get the plan?
‐What do you mean, do we get it?
Who wouldn't get it?
We're all chunin and
jonin here, aren't we?
Oh, I forgot.
One of us is only genin.
‐Shut up.
You trying to pick a
fight, or something?
Anyway, I get it.
I get it.
I was only making sure
everybody else did.
‐You sure about that? huh?
‐To get back to my
idea, what do you say?
‐I say we try it.
Naruto, create
three shadow clones.
Spread them out about
10 meters apart,
and send them running
through the woods.
‐What?
But if I do that,
‐Just do it.
‐OK, fine.
I'll do it.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
But aren't those bats sure
to detect us if I do this?
‐That's just what we want.
‐Huh?
‐I see one.
It's working.
A bat wouldn't be
flying in daylight
unless it had somewhere
important to go.
‐All right.
After it everyone.
‐So, what's the deal?
Why are we following
a bat, any way?
‐I knew it.
You never understood
the plan, did you?
Think about it.
That bat's going to make a
beeline back to it's hideout
to let the enemy know
that he found us, right?
‐Mm hmm.
‐So that means if
we follow the bat,
it will lead us to
the enemy's hideout.
See?
‐Huh, I get it.
That's a good plan.
‐Man, you're always two
steps behind everyone else,
aren't you, genius?
‐Oh, yeah.
You think you're so smart
just because you're a chunin.
Well, just take this.
[screaming]
‐Aww, seriously dude,
what have you been eating?
‐Ha ha.
Catch you later, sucker.
‐I get a strange feeling
every time I come here.
‐What happens now?
‐What happens is I perform
a little test, with him.
And with help from Guren.
Here, put this on, will you?
‐Wait.
If you give him
that much, he'll‐‐
‐Do you really want to question
Lord Orochimaru's plan?
‐Uh.
‐Call it a mission.
A mission that would benefit
from your unique talents.
In fact, you're the only one
who could possibly do it.
‐I'm the only one.
‐And afterwards, who knows?
I might even reconsider.
‐Huh.
‐I might change
my mind about who
is best suited to be my vessel.
‐No need to be worried.
It's going to be so
much fun, Yukimaru.
You'll see.
This medicine's
different from the last.
This one shouldn't cause
you any pain at all.
Besides, you can't go home
until you've taken it.
Now it's your turn, Guren.
‐Stop bossing me around.
Crystal style:
Jade Crystal Hexagonal Column.
[Yukimaru panting]
‐What is it that's
about to happen?
[Yukimaru screaming]
‐What is it?
‐Careful now.
It's coming.
‐What is?
‐The test was successful.
It's about to appear.
‐What's about to appear?
‐A tailed beast.
‐A tailed beast?
‐Ha ha ha.
[Yukimaru screaming]
(VOICEOVER): A three
tailed beast, to be exact.
[theme music]
‐I'm sensing something.
‐What is it, Shino?
‐My insects have
detected a strange chakra.
‐A strange chakra?
‐Very.
In fact, I've never sensed
so much chakra in one place
before.
‐I think Akamaru's picking up on
the same thing as your insects.
‐What could it be?
What's going on over there?
‐Let's find out.
Full speed ahead.
Hurry.
(VOICEOVER): Next time,
the Rampaging Tailed Beast.