Now! Hurry!
[gasping]
No!
[gasp]
Kamui!
"The Infinite Dream"
[groan]
(Kakashi) Sakura!
[groaning] Kakashi Sensei.
[gasp]
(Sakura) Sasuke?!
Why are you popping up here,
Sakura?
She was in the Time-Space
plane...
Sakura, what's going on there?
(Sakura) [gasp] Kakashi
Sensei, your left eye!
It happened in a flash...
But it appears that Madara has
stolen my Sharingan.
Let me see, Sensei!
(Kakashi) Thanks.
(Kakashi) But, never mind me.
What about Obito? I'm sure
Madara used the Kamui to
teleport himself there!
(Sakura) Huh? I blinked, and I
was back out here...
Then that means...
I want you to destroy my left
eye, the one with the Rinnegan.
(Obito) I can't move much at all
now...
If I let down my guard,
even just a bit, Black Zetsu
will take over my body, Rinnegan
and all.
He'll use my right eye's Visual
Prowess to go back outside,...
...and then the Rinnegan will
fall into Madara's hands.
If he gets both eyes, terrible
things will happen.
What do you mean, "terrible
things"? How much worse can all
this get? Hasn't he done enough
already?!
(Obito) I wasn't able to implant
both Rinnegan myself.
The chakra and Visual Prowess of
just this one eye are so
strong,
...I nearly lost myself.
I'm not even its original
owner, yet I accomplished this
much.
If both Rinnegan are restored to
their true owner, I fear no one
can stand against him.
(Sakura) But-!
Full powers unleashed in
Visual Prowess only when both
eyes are together.
Quickly! There's not much time.
Please destroy this left eye!
[gasp]
What is it, Sakura?!
We're in serious trouble now!
Obito had reached his limit and
couldn't move...
Which means that Madara will get
Obito's Rinnegan!
(Six Paths Madara) The Cursed
Seal Tag I placed on your heart
is gone...
How did you manage to remove it?
You shouldn't have been able to
damage it yourself.
I had Kakashi stab me, that
destroyed it.
(Kakashi) This is all I can do
right now.
Since it was in the way of me
making myself into Ten Tails
Jinchuriki,
...I had to gamble my life on
it...But I wasn't going to keep
doing what you wanted!
[chuckling]
No, actually, you did exactly
what I'd intended you to do.
Even exceeded my hopes.
(Obito) Huh? What's so funny?
A Curse Seal Tag that was meant
to turn you into a puppet...
One that would restrict your
movements should you try to
remove it from inside the body
that it's implanted in.
Looks like you knew about it,
Obito.
About those Cursed Tags I
implanted in the two of you...
Naturally you couldn't have
killed yourselves, either,
...since you both were my
previous pawns.
"The two...of you"?
Call it fate or karma,
but it's ironic that both of
you ended up getting rid of them
in the exact same way.
[gasp]
Rin!
(Six Paths Madara) That's right.
The plot to make that girl
into Three Tails' Jinchuriki
and have her rampage through the
Leaf Village was mine, not the
Hidden Mist's!
She took advantage of Kakashi's
move toward the enemy to foil
it, at the cose of her life, but
that too was part of the plan...
In order to pitch you into
darkness and make you my pawn.
(Obito) You bastard, you
deliberately had me see-!
I targeted a time when Minato
was on another mission,
...and then I simply
manipulated the Mist Shinobi
into kidnapping Rin,
leaving Kakashi so he'd be sure
to come after her.
Its other purpose was so I could
see the extent of your unleashed
power.
You really thought White Zetsu
stirring you up and your being
able to get out from
underground, right then,
...was simply some sort of
coincidence?
Hey! Listen! I was outside just
now! Your friends Rin and Stupid
Kakashi are in trouble!
What?! What's going on?!
They're alone and completely
surrounded by Hidden Mist
Shinobi!
What's the status of Rin and
Kakashi?
(Swirly) Well, according to
the others,...it sounds pretty
bad.
(Swirly) They're talking about
some Hidden Mist test
subjects,...but I don't really
understand.
Some test subjects...?
(Swirly) Anyway, it seems that
Rin and Kakashi are totally
surrounded.
Sounds like all of the Mist guys
appear to be jonin or ANBU Black
Ops.
(Obito) What's Minato Sensei
doing?
(Swirly) Who?
(Obito) I'm asking what the
Yellow Flash of the Leaf is
doing!
(Swirly) Hm...It seems that he's
on some different mission.
(Obito) At a time like this?!
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) The girl
dying by Kakashi's hand was more
than I could have hoped for.
[gasping]
(Obito) [growling yell]
(Six Paths Madara) Either
way,...I would have had my
Puppet Shinobi kill her.
I taught you to use the darkness
in people's hearts to manipulate
them, didn't I, Obito?
[growling]
If there's no darkness, you
create it.
Don't you think it's
presumptuous to consider
yourself any different?
Why me?! Tell me why you chose
me?!
Because you were genuinely
devoted to and kind to other
people, of course.
Wasn't elder care your specialty
back then?
[bitter choking back tears]
(Six Paths Madara) Your deep
love for Rin,...for your
comrades,...for the Hokage, and
for all other shinobi...
Once you fell into darkness, it
would all conversely transform
into an equally profound hatred
for this world.
That's just the kind of guy you
are.
[gasp]
There's just one more thing that
I need to know for all of this
to go completely my way.
I'm going to be taking back that
left eye of mine.
He's caught now. I'm leaving him
to you, all right?!
Sure! You can count on me!
It seems that Madara has
appeared there now.
(Kakashi) I see...So that's what
Obito said, huh?
We have no idea when they might
emerge. Stay alert.
So what did you do about his
shadow?
(Naruto) My Shadow Clone and I
immobilized him with Six Paths
Rods.
Naruto?!
Hey there, Sakura! Let me do it!
What're you trying to do,
Naruto?
Hey!
No, it's okay.
Open your eye, Kakashi Sensei.
[groan]
[gasp]
What?! But how'd you do that?!
[chuckle] Well, the thing is,
it's really kinda hard to
explain with words, but,
basically,
I took a part of Kakashi Sensei
and then I kinda, well, I used
that part to, um, uh...
Naruto, I told everyone to stay
alert.
Huh? Really, well this is the
first time I'm hearing about it!
Come on! Quit talking back for
once, Naruto! Anyway, you'll
just have to explain about the
eye later!
(Sasuke) Madara took Kakashi's
eye and wen to where Obito is.
The next time he appears, he'll
have both Rinnegan!
(Naruto) What?! For real?!
(Kakashi) Alright, why don't you
introduce yourselves, one at a
time.
Okay, I'll go first. My name's
Naruto Uzumaki!
I like instant ramen in a cup!
I really like the ramen that
Iruka Sensei got for me at
Ichiraku.
But the thing I hate is waiting
until the ramen is done.
(Naruto) And my future dream
is...
...to be Hokage!
Then the village will stop
disrespecting me and treat me
like I'm somebody! Somebody
important!
(Sasuke) My name's Sasuke
Uchiha...I hate a lot of things.
And I don't particularly like
anything.
My dream...isn't really a dream
at all because I'm going to make
it a reality.
(Sasuke) I'm going to restore my
clan...and destroy a certain
person.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
What I like, uh,...I mean, the
person I like is...
My hobby is...
And I guess that my dream for
the future is...
[squeal]
(Kakashi) You've already
surpassed the Hokare, Naruto.
You've been acknowledged by all
and become a hero. But being
Hokage is still your dream.
And Sakura, I bet your feelings
for Sasuke have changed from
what they were back then.
You still love him but on a
totally different level.
He tried to kill you, yet you
still care for him.
You won't cut him off, no matter
what. And you think it's your
duty to save him from the
darkness.
That's how kind you are.
Sasuke...Your dream was to kill
Itachi.
Now that he's gone, what do you
desire? What are you heading
toward?
I was your teacher,...but it
turned out that I didn't
understand you at all. Even
now...
Sasuke...What is your current
dream?
Huh?
What's the meaning behind saying
that you'll become Hokage?
I feel that it might be
fate...that the former Team
Seven has reunited like this.
If you don't wanna tell us what
you're thinking right now,
Sasuke,...that's fine.
(Kakashi) But,...that we were
all once a part of Team 7 is an
irrefutable fact,...isn't it?
In front! He's coming!
You haven't forgotten the
lesson from trying to steal
the bells have you?
Nope.
Hm.
(Naruto) Of course not! The
answer...
...is teamwork! Right?
(Six Paths Madara) Then,...
...you all dying together could
also be considered teamwork,
right?
Madara,...you have both
Rinnegan, huh?
(Kakashi) And his lower body's
regenerated already...
(Naruto) Obito!
(Black Zetsu) Sorry, but...Obito
is no more. I've taken over his
body now.
It seems that he was hoping to
have his mistakes rectified and
be redeemed.
He was praying in his heart,
like a child,...that he could
just leave the future to you
all.
How convenient that would have
been for him, don't you think?
Like a spoiled brat.
[gasp]
(Kakashi) I can't blame her,
...given the power of those
eyes.
Hm.
(Sakura) Lady Tsunade,...it
looks like I've finally caught
up to them!
I'm not retreating anymore!
I'll be the diversion.
Follow me!
[gasp] Wait!
[gasp]
(Naruto) Sakura!
(Six Paths Madara) Oh?
Rule Four says: ...A Medical
Ninja who masters the Art of
Mitotic Regeneration, the 100
Healings,
...may break the first three
rules!
(Six Paths Madara) The same
Regeneration Jutsu as
Hashirama's granddaughter,
eh...?
[gasp]
(Sakura) An invisible wall?! I
can't reach him!
(Kakashi) What's going on?!
[groan]
Sakura!
No, don't worry, Naruto.
(Sakura) Sasuke...didn't even...
(Sakura) I'm all right.
Naruto!
[gasp]
Yeah, yeah...I know already.
There's more of them out there.
That left eye's a Rinnegan?!
(Sasuke) Madara's got four
shadows now.
(Six Paths Madara) Enough with
the sideshow.
[gasps]
What is he up to?
(Six Paths Madara) Catastrophic
Planetary Devastation!
[gasps]
(Gaara) We're retreating for the
time being!
(Rock Lee) What about the
others?!
They'll pull through, no matter
what!
[gasp] This is Six Path's power?
They're way bigger than Pain's
and there's a lot more of
them...
Forget about what's above.
His shadows are here on the
ground with us!
They're just a bit more solid
and larger than raindrops, but,
still...
(Naruto) Here they come!
And the shadows, too!
(Naruto) Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Leave the shadows to me!
(Six Paths Madara) [chuckling] I
think I'll record their final
moments!
Kurama...
(Shadow Kurama) Yes!
(Sasuke) Susano'o
(Naruto) Tailed Beast Bomb Rasen
Shuriken!
[grunting]
(Sasuke) Gah! There's no end to
them!
[gasp]
(Naruto Clone A) You bastard!
Damn you!
(Six Paths Madara) According to
that stone tablet...
When the one who possesses the
power of Rinne should draw near
the moon,...
...the eye that can reflect off
the moon and grant the infinite
dream shall open.
Shine upon the world...
...Infinite Tsukuyomi!
(Yamato) Where am I?
What...happened to me?
(Hiruzen) Are you all right,
Yamato?
(Yamato) Lord Third! That's
right! Kabuto captured me...
The war...! What's happening
with the war? And Naruto? Is he
all right?
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Infinite
Tsukuyomi."
(Hiruzen) Control yourself,
Yamato!