We have to reach the oasis today
or we'll be low on provisions
and in trouble.
We have the water I extracted
from that giant scorpion. We
can still get by on that.
Well, I for one refuse to "get
by" on something as gross as
scorpion water for the
rest of the Chunin Exams!
[grossed out]
(Kouji)
It's just like you planned.
(Ameno)
Not quite. I didn't
account for this.
[gasp]
Wait, you're...
♪
Please hand over your scroll.
Once you do, we'll allow you to
access the water in the oasis.
We'll even give you medical
treatment if you want.
What?! We don't need
to be treated by
the likes of you guys!
We have our own medical
specialist right here!
Ino...
Besides, nobody told us that
the oasis's water was yours!
That's right! You
tell 'em, Choji!
And Sakura,
you tell 'em too!
We don't need treatment, but
we definitely need water.
Think weak like that, and we'll
lose even before we fight!
(Sakura)
Ino!
Sand Formation: Shisa!
[grunts]
Ino!
You okay?
(Shishio)
She's a sacrificial pawn...
I mean Jumping within range of
my attack like she did without
taking any precautions at all...
I was curious when I
heard that this team
had two Medical Ninja...
But she clearly doesn't possess
the cool-headed judgment
required to be a Medical Ninja.
Disappointing. I
had expected more.
[groans]
This means we don't have to
negotiate anymore, right?
Looks that way.
You just got us fired up!
Now Choji and I will
break past you!
Medical Water Style!
Water Praying Mantis!
[grunts]
Don't worry,
it's okay!
After we defeat you and take
your scroll, I'll make sure to
treat all your injuries.
(Thinking)
That's not an ordinary
Water Style blade...
It's as sharp
as a Chakra Scalpel!
She's really strong!
Saganken:
Sand Stone Fist!
Damn! I missed!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
This Sand Stone Fist of his is
equal to my size and power...
But...
...it's incredibly hard.
And it's gotta be heavy...
But even so, he wields it
so easily!
Now let's see who's
stronger, shall we?
[grunt]
That's amazing! She's
evading all of my attacks!
What..?
[attack yell]
[grunt]
Your attacks are
really boring me...
[gasp] He just took a blind
swing, and he landed it!
Having a rough time?
Not as rough as you are.
The two of you...
stop fooling around!
Done infusing chakra?
Polarized... Sand
Formation...
Burning Sand Camouflage!
Huh?
They vanished!
Huh?... [grunts]
Choji--!
[grunt]
This isn't the time
for you to be worried
about the others...
[grunts]
It's going to be hard to
fight an enemy you can't see.
Choji... If we scatter,
we'll be at a disadvantage.
Let's watch each other's backs.
Right.
Ahhhh!
Sakura...
Choji...
Distance, ten: eight o'clock.
Distance five: Three o'clock.
There's two.
Distance, thirty:  Six o'clock.
[whistle]
Ugh! Darn! No good,
Chakra's disrupted.
(Ino)
I can't tell!
What a joke. If my concentration
lapses even a little, my Sensory
Perception won't work.
[sigh] There's no way that
I can use this in battle!
Sorry, Choji.  I really wanted
to get this down by the Chunin
Exams, but...
It's fine. The fact that you can
even do Sensory Perception is
amazing.
Well, you can't use it in a real
battle, that's for sure.
[groan]
Sometimes these tricks seem
useless, but you find you can
use them in a surprise attack.
[grunts]
Not yet...
We're not done,
mister...
Wrong again.
We'll finish this
up right now.
Choji! Stay alert!
How can I watch out for a
foe that I can't even see?
You're going to
have to find a way!
Toward six o'clock!
[attack yells]
Yeah! All right! I owe
you one, Shikamaru!
I found all three of them! I can
sense their chakra. They're on
the move!
The enemy's heading this way.
Hey! since when do you
have sensory powers?
That's amazing!
I know! Cool, right?!
I'm trying to get
comfortable with it.
But in actual combat,
it's still difficult.
If I don't have the
time to concentrate, then
I can't really do it.
Oh. I understand. Too bad
no enemy is willing to give
us the luxury of time...
If there's no spare time,
you have to steal it!
I became a pawn to buy time
and use Sensory Perception.
It's not a bad trick, but don't
be so proud of yourself.
You fooled us, too! We
thought that he got you!
I guess he
didn't... Huh?
But we're still going
to take your scroll.
You can't buy much time
by inflicting such a
small amount of damage.
What? What are those?!
What the hell's going on?!
I didn't know you had a
Sensory Perception user.
(Sakura Thinking)
That counter attack was
perfectly executed...
I can't believe it didn't work!
And she undid the damage so
quickly!
Heh. I prepared chakra earlier
for this Medical Water Style
Water Jellyfish.
If it weren't for this
self-healing...
We would've been in trouble.
Kouji, Shishio... I'm
out of Water Jellyfish;
can you go on?
Sure... And I'll block
her sensing!
Choji, Sakura! I'll
track 'em with-
A sensory barrier?!
(Shishio)
Blinding Sand Formation: Noise!
I won't let you
sense us anymore!
Ino!
[groan]
(Shishio)
You should be grateful to Ameno.
She gets really upset if I do
too much damage.
Inoichi, what's the matter with
you?  You're acting so antsy!
Are you that worried about your
daughter's Chunin Exams?
I won't make excuses, but, my
daughter's what you might call a
jack-of-all-trades and master of
none.
Almost before I was really aware
of what was going on with her,
she turned her back on
training in our Secret Jutsu...
She's just been such a burden
to you, Lady Tsunade...
Oh, don't worry.
Besides, to tell the truth, I
don't actually intend to make
her a Medical Ninja.
Huh!?
I just thought the
training would be handy.
Since she skipped out on your
Secret Jutsu training to come
learn under me...
If I can't sense them, I can't
get into Mind Transfer mode.
So I'll have to contact them
both with Mind Transmission...
(Ino)
Sakura, Choji! Can
you hear me?
Yeah! I hear you!
Ino! Can you do something
to sense the enemy?!
My Sensory Perception's
blocked. But their attack
seems to follow a pattern!
Yeah, I know!
That's obvious!
[grunt]
The enemy attacks
from our blind side...
Right now, I can see Choji's
opponent when they're attacking.
But it's too late by the
time I see one coming.
Thought so...
You can communicate with several
people at once.  This is the
Mind Transmission Jutsu.
Intel transmission is a basic
part of battle strategy.
As long as the enemy doesn't
find out, it's a huge military
asset.
Wow, Ino! You sure
learned an awesome jutsu!
I guess...
Useful jutsu tend to be risky.
That's true for this one, too.
If you misjudge your level of
skill and carelessly increase
the jutsu's intensity,
in the worst case scenario,
you'll die.
[gasps]
By increasing the intensity, do
you mean widening the scope or
increasing the number of people
involved? 'Cause knowing that
would change our strategy for
using this jutsu...
Yes. In the Mind Transmission
Jutsu the user's skill sets
its levels.
Transmission speed, scope,
number of people in the
conversation,
all these change according
to the user's level.
And when it's truly mastered,...
you're able to transmit the most
precious thing of all.
What's the most precious thing?
What's held inside your
comrades' hearts.
The Mind Transmission Jutsu
can communicate that.
On the battlefield, when you can
feel the intensity of your
teammates' thoughts for you
that gives you more
courage than anything.
I've really only barely
scratched the surface
of this jutsu...
If only I'd spent
more time training...
If only instead of spending time
studying Medical Ninjutsu I'd
trained more with Dad!
(Lady Tsunade)
That happened because your
chakra control is too rough.
You must learn to control your
chakra more carefully and
delicately!
Lady Tsunade...
Hey! Sakura,
Choji, listen up!
But can you do that?!
Doesn't matter if
I can. I have to!
I've gotta do more! And
raise my levels up!
All right, here goes!
Mind Transmission Jutsu!
I'll try relaying Sakura's
thoughts to Choji!
Got them! Now I just
have to send them on!
[gasp]
Yes!
I saw something, but...  there
just isn't enough time!
Transmitting everything through
me takes too long.
I'll have to send Sakura's
thoughts directly to Choji.
I'm not gonna give up!
I gotta level up!
Gotta level up my
Mind Transmission Jutsu.
More... more,,,
more...! More...!
[grunt]
Now my thoughts this time!
Gotcha! Cha!
But...  how...?!
[heavy breathing]
How did-?! No way!
Intense feelings decided the
outcome of this battle.
You still up
to this, Ino?
Yeah! Of course!
Good. Then let's finish
this together. Now.
Right!
Wait! Hold on!
-No excuses!
Ahhhh!
All right, that
should do it.
We're in the middle of the
Chunin Exams and on
opposite sides, so thank you.
I'm a Medical Kunoichi.
This is what we do.
[laughs] Is it really
any wonder why all guys
love medical Kunoichi?!
Why are you spewing that
nonsense again, Choji?!
[laughter]
(Choji)
You're so cute!
Let's get going.
But are you sure
about this, Sakura?
We're sure. We already
have both of the
scrolls that we need.
Just the water's fine.
Okay...
Well, you sure beat
us, but still, we'll
get the scrolls.
and avenge this in
the Third Exam.
Hm!
I don't consider this
a victory either.
We'll settle it
next time we meet.
Your barrier against my Sensory
Perception was tough!
No, we underestimated your
skill.  That was our downfall.
Yeah, he's right! When did
you learn how to do that
kind of thing, anyway?!
Huh? Oh, well, you know!
[giggles]
How's that saying go?
"A skilled hawk hides
its talons."
I was Lady Tsunade's
apprentice, too, you know!
I wanted to prove it.
Well said, Ino! Thanks,
guys! we'll be going
in this direction.
And we'll go this way.
The Yamanaka Clan's Secret
Ninjutsu takes finesse. I'm
sure the chakra control skills
required in Medical Ninjutsu
will come in handy with that.
Lady Tsunade...!
It may seem like she's taken a
detour, but trust me... she's
learning what she needs to.
And you, as the caring father
you are, must be well aware
of that.
[gasp]
In time, you will
surpass me...
In fact, I have faith that you
will become the foremost shinobi
of the Yamanaka Clan!
Those guys were seriously
formidable!
I'd hate to think what
would have happened if you
hadn't been here Ino.
Oh, no, don't say that! You two
bought me time, that's why we
won.
If you guys hadn't given it your
all, who knows what would've
happened?
Dad, I'm sorry for skipping out
on my training.  And please
forgive me, Lady Tsunade...
I thought that Medical Ninjutsu
was an easy way out.
But your guidance and training
in Medical Ninjutsu really
helped me grow.
The ability to make decisions
under pressure, more delicate
chakra control...
Everything I learned is
pushing me in the direction
I'm destined to go.
All right, let's do our
best and reach the goal!
Yeah!
(Sakura)
What? A doll? Is it an enemy?
(Ino)
Sakura! How are you
doing physically?
(Sakura)
Good, since you let me rest.
(Ino)
She's... a Puppet User!
(Sakura)
Ino, he's coming this way!
(Ino)
Since she's a Puppet User, if
we bring down the jutsu caster--
Sakura! Guard my body!
(Sakura)
I'm on it!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Cursed Puppet"
(Choji)
This guy's trouble!