I'll keep him trapped so
that it's easier for me to
cast my usual genjutsu on
him.
So, then right now, Kabuto's
caught in the loop you've
created?
And that's the Izanami?
When did you cast it?
The very first time Kabuto
stabbed me with that blade.
Way back then, huh?
But how?
You said that it was a
Visual Jutsu that worked
even without vision.
How can a Visual Jutsu
work without eyesight?
Izanami is a Visual Jutsu
that works with the physical
senses of you and your
opponent.
The physical senses of both?
As you are battling
your opponent...
You use your Visual Prowess
to take a record, like a
picture, of the sensations
you and your
opponent are feeling
in an instance.
We'll call that "Exhibit A."
As time progresses, you find
that "Exhibit B" is a more
important moment.
Then you record "Exhibit C"
and so on with Sharingan.
Then you recreate those
exact feelings. So you're
using your powers to create
a perfect copy
of Exhibit A. We'll call
this "A Prime."
By overlaying and connecting
A to A Prime, the Izanami
also links a path
including B Prime
and C Prime to create
fluctuations within
a fixed time.
Thus, you can create
an infinite loop.
All in exchange for one's
sight, of course.
Just like the Izanagi.
So Kabuto's consciousness
is trapped inside the loop
that you created.
He'll be fighting a phantom
you and a phantom me for all
eternity, then.
Not quite... There's an escape
route built into the jutsu.
He could feasibly disengage.
You see, the Izanami was
developed to admonish and
salvage an Izanagi user.
[surprised gasp]
What does that mean?
You know a little bit about
the Izanagi already.
It's a perfect Uchiha Visual
Jutsu designed to change
destiny.
If something doesn't go the
way you want, you can just
erase that outcome and start
over.
Ultimately, you can pick and
choose the most desirable
end result.
What I'm about to tell you
is the story of the Uchiha's
Izanagi and how the Izanami
came to be.
I want to be sure
you know this.
Izanami...
...and the story of
it's creation...
A long time ago, there was a
great battle the Uchiha Clan
couldn't afford to lose.
The Izanagi tuned out to
be an invaluable jutsu.
Move in!
[battle cries]
No, damn it! They
set a trap for us!
What?!
Now you die!
As long as we Uchiha possess
the Izanagi it is impossible
for us to lose!
[maniacal laughter]
However, a jutsu that
allows the caster to choose
their own ending carries
with it a bigger
risk of only the loss
of one's vision.
Most who used that overly
powerful Visual Jutsu
couldn't handle it and
abused the power
that they held.
If there was only one
Izanagi user, there
was no problem.
But when two or more
used it, there was a
scramble within the
Uchiha Clan to see who
could get the best result.
You know, you're not the
only one who can use the
Izanagi!
I don't like you
bossing us around!
But I am the one who
achieved it!
In the shinobi world,
only results matter!
Well, then... It seems my path
is clear. I'll just have
to rewrite that result...
...with my own Izanagi!
You fool! You're all talk!
I shall rule!
Not just over the Uchiha,
but the entire shinobi
world!
All thanks to my Izanagi!
I'll take your wish and
I'll make it mine!
Thanks to the power
of my own Izanagi!
[triumphant laughter]
The Izanagi's ability to
influence outcomes caused
much inter-clan rivalry.
The Izanami was ultimately
created to control its
power.
Normal vision-based genjutsu
is powerless against Visual
Prowess...
If you intend to oppose me
too, then I'm afraid that I
have no choice.
There has to be a way to
settle this without more
fighting.
[om harrumphing chuckle] My
hands are already deeply
stained with blood.
You think I would stop now?
What would be the point?
You don't know yourself
anymore!
You don't know what your
true strength really is!
Oh, be quiet!
There's still time
to turn back!
If you have the will to
change, then take my hand!
You can't fool me!
If you continue to refuse
to listen to me, then I'm
prepared, as well.
First-rate work sneaking up
behind me like that!
However, while I have the
Izanagi, you won't be able
to beat me!
It's over for you!
What is this?!
My right eye... I should have
gone blind after activating
the Izanagi!
The Izanagi that you depend
on so much will not protect
you now.
Quiet!
No! Not yet...
Not yet!
Reality is a product of
chance that we call fate.
We cannot predict it.
But Izanagi can twist around
an inconvenient reality and
lead it to a new fate.
At a whim, the user can
change the original reality
into a new one.
A fallen opponent can just
revive, so to an enemy, it's
an intolerable jutsu.
If someone is using the
Izanagi to change an
outcome for their own
benefit, the Izanami
causes them to circle
endlessly in a loop.
I believed that the Izanagi
was the ultimate Visual
Jutsu...
But this means the Izanami
is a far superior one...
Izanami forms a loop using
physical sensations, even
stopping Izanagi from
warping reality.
Since the Izanami is a jutsu
meant for stopping the
Izanagi...
There's an escape route
that's built into the loop.
Originally, the Izanami was
designed to keep the Uchiha
humble and honorable.
It's to stop you from taking
the easy way out and
avoiding inconvenient
outcomes.
[heavy breathing]
But how?!
There is no destiny that
Izanagi isn't able to alter!
Simply stop what
you're doing.
Take my hand and grab hold
of the future that awaits
you!
I can never be forgiven for
all the blood on my hands.
Even still...
Take hold of it!
[battle cry]
I won't use Izanagi anymore...
I'll accept reality
and will move forward.
Once one accepts the
original outcome and stops
trying to run from it, the
loop will stop.
This jutsu guides you toward
accepting your fate instead
of relying on jutsu to
change it.
A jutsu with an escape is
too dangerous to use in
combat.
That is why the Izanami
is a Forbidden Jutsu.
If Kabuto stops trying to
transform himself, then
he'll be able to bring the
loop to an end.
The Uchiha Clan and their
history of conflict.
The arrogance and
recklessness displayed by
those who misused the
Izanagi...
As well as the clashes
between them and how they
were stopped by the Izanami.
I understand why Izanagi and
Izanami became Forbidden
Jutsu.
And I also see how one must
learn from the past, accept
one's fate, and then find a
way to move on afterward.
But, why?
Why'd you even bother
casting this jutsu on
Kabuto?
If he could still escape...
He reminds me of the old me.
He thinks by
getting everything,
he can accomplish
whatever he wants to.
And he makes himself believe
that he can't fail, even if
that really amounts to lying
to himself.
I stopped listening to
what anyone else said.
And I stopped letting
myself trust anybody.
In his case, Kabuto is so
deluded that he thinks all
of these powers are his and
his alone....
I understand him too well.
Both of us were used
by the shinobi world.
He can't forgive himself or
accept himself for what he
truly is.
It's clear that what he's
doing is wrong.
But he's not completely to
blame for not realizing
that.
My chance has passed me by,
but he can still forgive
himself.
But why, Big Brother?! Why
would you feel you needed to
help him do that?
He is not like you.
No, you were perfect!
Sasuke...
You know I was going to
control you. I planned to
use the Visual Jutsu Koto
Amatsukami.
I treated you as though you
were a child. I thought you
needed my protection.
I was unable to
trust your strength.
It may be that a perfect
being does not exist at all
in the whole world.
Sometimes two people
who appear to be complete
opposites are actually two
sides of the
same coin and can only
succeed when they work
together.
Like the Izanagi and
Izanami....
Look at me and find in
yourself what I couldn't
find in me.
However...
Do not ever say
that I was perfect.
First off...
No! It's impossible! I've
already become a perfect
being!
But this isn't the real me!
How long will you
imitate Orochimaru?
If you want to exit this
loop, you must reexamine
your mistakes!
Shut up!
I know he's going to
use a Fire Style Jutsu.
Water Style! Water Dragon--!
Water Style! Water
Dragon Missile!
He saw that coming
with his Sharingan!
But how did I get
any of this wrong?
Where have I ever make a
mistake in all this?!
All I ever wanted was for
someone to be there for me!
Someone to acknowledge me!
Someone to appreciate me!
Tell me, where is this
mistake in wanting that?!
First off, I should
have acknowledged
and appreciated myself
for the person I was.
If I'd just done
that, I never would've
had to lie to anyone.
To myself or to you.
If you lie to yourself, how
can you have friends or be
trustworthy?
In the end all these lies
will keep you from seeing
your true self.
If I wasn't trapped here...
I'd have won this war.
I would have been
sleeping by now!
Damn you, Itachi!
It's 9 o'clock already.
Something wrong?
No, I just wish we could
wrap up this war so I could
finally get a good night's
sleep!
They never tell us rear
guard shinobi what's going
on. We're kept almost
completely in the
dark on everything.
That's true.
So, what are you gonna do
when this war's over?
Well, I'll start
by going home.
If the war ends and the Five
Great Nations continue to be
friendly allies...
Then maybe my little
brother, who's been on a
mission forever, can finally
come back home.
Boy, I envy those who have
a home to return to...
Yeah well, you could come
home with me?
I mean, my home is
just an orphanage.
But if my little brother's
there, he can take a look at
your wounds for ya.
Wow, Urushi! Thank you!
I really hope you'll
come home this time.
Kabuto.
I'll stop the Reanimation
Jutsu now.
All the reanimated
shinobi will be gone.
And that should bring
the war to an end.
But Brother.
You'll go, too.
But I will have protected my
village. I'm Itachi Uchiha
of the Leaf once again.
I have no more regrets.
But why?!
Why help the very village
that did this to you?! That
put you where you are?!
You may be able to forgive
the Leaf, but I can't!
You have no more regrets?!
What about what you've made
me become? What about that,
huh?!
[heavy breathing]
I will let you
deal with Sasuke.
I tried to do everything
myself, too. And I failed.
So this time I will leave
that task for a comrade to
handle.
I'm not the one who can
change you, Sasuke.
But I can stop this. This
reanimation jutsu is
something I can affect.
In doing so, I'll fulfill my
promise to Naruto, at least.
It's time to end this. Tell
me the signs to stop the
Reanimation Jutsu!
Tsukuyomi!
I've kept my promise. I
leave the rest up to you...
Naruto!
I hate the Leaf Village for
causing you so much pain!
I hate it more than I've
ever hated it before!
It's because I'm your
brother that no matter what
you say, you're not going to
stop me!
Even if you protect the
village now, I will still
destroy it someday.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "I Will Love You
Always."
Goodbye, Big Brother.