‐Are you saying Naruto's
inside of the Three‐Tails?
‐Uh‐huh.
[blasts]
‐Like a bunch of
kids‐‐ so excited.
‐[laughing]
Are you feeling as good as I am?
‐Yeah.
I feel like a whole new person.
‐All the fatigue
and pain is gone.
And as a matter of fact, I
feel more powerful than ever!
‐Terrific.
But all I care about is getting
Yukimaru back from the Leaf.
‐[laughs]
You worry too much, Four‐Eyes.
‐Right now, I feel like
I could take on anyone.
‐Anyone at all, even Guren!
KUBOTA (VOICEOVER): Hm,
I'm not so sure about that.
But you never know.
‐What?
Could this really be true?
‐Well, yes.
According to Yukimaru,
he really believes
that Guren woman is still alive.
‐And he says Naruto
and she ended up
being swallowed by
the Three‐Tails.
‐Well, stranger
things have happened.
It would explain why
we haven't found them.
But if it's true, what makes
you think Guren survived?
‐Guren made this crystal
especially for me.
If anything would
have happened to her,
it would have shattered.
‐I see.
‐But even if that proves that
Guren's still in one piece,
it doesn't indicate whether
Naruto's all right as well.
‐True.
There is no way of
knowing what it's
like inside that
beast's stomach.
‐And anyway, if he
is all right, he's
stuck with that woman
and her Crystal Style.
Chances are, they've
already fought it out
and settled things
one way or the other.
‐Taking her own by himself?
‐Stop.
Let's just work
on the assumption
that Naruto is fine, that
we have to find the beast.
‐All right.
I'll look for it.
‐The Three‐Tails?
You can find it?
‐Yeah.
I'm not sure how exactly,
but I‐‐ I can feel it.
‐OK, but even if we do find
that thing, what do we do then?
‐Then my team and I will try
one more time to seal it.
‐And we'll rescue Naruto
while you're doing that.
And in case the Three‐Tails
starts acting up,
Yamato, we'll send
Shino with you.
He'll also come in handy if
we find Guren with Naruto.
Sai, you're on
airborne surveillance.
The rest of you will
secure the perimeter.
[theme music]
‐Remember, Kabuto is
capable of anything.
Watch yourself.
‐Just find Naruto.
‐We will.
Take care of yourselves as well.
‐Shino, time to go.
‐Right.
‐OK, Sealing Team, we
must keep our distance
till the time is right.
Move too soon, and we'll
only enrage the Three‐Tails.
TEAM: Got it!
‐Naruto.
‐Uh!
Agh!
Aah!
Uh!
Ya‐ah!
‐Huh!
‐What is it?
‐My clones.
Those things got
every one of them.
‐Every one?
[rattling noise]
Uh!
‐That sound.
They're coming this way.
We're seriously outnumbered.
What now?
Ugh!
Like all those little
ones weren't bad enough!
‐We'll have to fight.
‐There's no way
you can fight them.
Not in your condition.
‐Have you found an
escape route yet?
‐You're right.
We have no choice.
‐Crystal Style,
Hexagonal Shuriken!
[gulps]
‐That stuff's not going to work.
It just bounces right off him.
Listen, I'll draw his attention
while you make a run for it,
OK?
Get ready!
[grunts]
Oh, yeah?
Ya‐ah!
Ugh!
Ugh.
Huh?
‐Hrrh!
Aah!
‐Guren!
‐Heh, how is that?
Huh?
Ugh!
‐Are you OK?
‐Yeah, I'm fine.
Hm.
‐All right, that's it.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Come on, climb on my back.
‐What?
There's no way I'm doing that.
‐And why not?
‐Because I still
have some pride left.
NARUTO: Oh, shut up!
This is no time to be
talking about that!
‐[gasps]
Put me down, you fool!
‐Just hold still.
[growling]
‐Come on, hurry!
‐Right!
Ugh!
Going up!
Ugh.
‐We did it!
Aah!
‐Aah!
[growls]
‐I wonder how Sakura and
the others are doing.
‐Is Naruto OK?
That's what I'm wondering.
‐Naruto?
Well, of course, he is!
And why?
Because he still owes me a match
to find out which one of us
is best!
‐Hm.
[snarls]
‐What is it, Akamaru?
Looks like the enemy is finally
putting in an appearance.
‐Perfect timing.
My fighting spirit
is all fired up.
I will use them as practice
for my match with Naruto.
Uh?
Heeyah!
So it is you again!
‐How did you recognize us?
‐I do not need to
see or smell you
to recognize your evil intent.
You've failed before.
And you will fail again.
‐We're not the same now.
I think you're in
for a real surprise.
Dark Smoke Sphere!
‐I cannot get close enough.
‐I can throw things, too!
‐No, you don't!
‐What happened to them?
‐Come out, come out!
Smoke Dragon!
‐Huh?
[growls]
‐What is it?
‐They're here, right below us.
‐All right, Sealing
Team, get ready.
‐Wait.
They're trapped inside.
Guren and Naruto are
trying to find a way out.
‐A way out?
‐If we can make a
hole from the outside,
that can be their
way to get out.
‐What's the boy talking about?
‐I suggest we
investigate and find out
exactly what's down there.
‐Camellias!
I will need a lot of
camellias, quickly!
‐Camellias?
‐So why did you save me?
‐Well, I was thinking
the same thing.
Why the heck did you save me?
‐For one simple reason.
I need you to get out of here.
‐Oh, really?
So you need me.
You admit it.
Uh, how's that wound?
‐Ugh, don't touch me!
Once we're out of here, you
and I will still be enemies.
‐Yeah, whatever.
But I'm not letting
you have Yukimaru.
‐Why do you care so
much about him anyway?
‐It's like I said before,
Orochimaru's evil.
Whatever reasons
you've given yourself
for remaining loyal
to him, you've
got to know he's just using
you, like he's using him.
‐Used who?
‐Forget it!
The point is that
Yukimaru definitely
doesn't belong with you
and your boss, Orochimaru.
Well, since my clones
are out of commission,
I guess I better do some
reconnaissance on my own.
It's a long way down, but
it's the only way out.
Here goes nothing.
Ugh, huh.
A fog?
Oh, no.
Not them again.
Huh?
Wait!
Hold it!
Who are you?
What are you doing down here?
Impossible.
Sasuke?
What the hell are you
doing in this place?
Ugh!
Huh?
Knock it off, Sasuke!
Listen, there's something
you need to know!
What are you doing?
Sasuke!
‐Uh!
That Three‐Tails' fog again.
I see.
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
This fog senses
the weakness in the hearts
of anyone caught in it
and manifests them as illusions.
If I go down there,
I'll have to face mine.
NARUTO: Sasuke!
Stop it!
‐Um!
[groans]
Uh.
It's you.
I know that I can't atone for
what I've done, but forgive me.
There's nothing I can
do to make amends.
But I promise you, I will
protect your child always,
even at the cost of my own life.
[sobs]
‐Aagh!
Ugh!
Sasuke, why are we fighting?
Why have you turned your
back on the one place
in the world where you belong?
Why, Sasuke?
Ugh.
Let go of me.
Let go!
Ah!
‐Get a hold of yourself!
What you've been
fighting is an illusion.
‐Uh.
Ugh!
You just saved my life.
‐Was it Sasuke Uchiha?
‐Yeah.
Hold on, how come
you know Sasuke?
‐I have seen him
with Lord Orochimaru.
He frightens me.
‐You've seen him?
Tell me, is he safe?
Is he all right?
‐I think so.
Why are you so interested?
‐Why am I interested?
Because Sasuke's
always been one of us.
It's important that I find
him so I can tell him, make
him see that we're his home,
the place where he belongs!
‐Wait a minute.
Are you really going to
try to take Sasuke back?
‐Of course, I am!
‐But...
Sasuke Uchiha?
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Is
he out of his mind?
This boy really thinks
he can rescue Sasuke?
Uh, of all the‐‐
‐[giggles]
‐What?
What is it?
What's so funny?
‐Oh, Naruto, you're
an even bigger fool
than I thought you were.
‐Hey, where did that come from?
‐I could die laughing‐‐
oh, uh, literally.
‐Take it easy.
You OK?
‐That must be it, the
dimensional barrier Yukimaru
was talking about.
If we can punch a hole in it,
we might give Naruto a way out.
Here goes.
Lightning Blade!
‐The fog is starting to lift.
It's like it's
leaking out somewhere.
Where did they come from?
‐They've got us surrounded.
‐Give me a break!
Not again!
Persistent, I'll give them that.
‐One more time.
Ugh!
Come on home, Naruto.
Ready?
‐Do it now!
‐Naruto, there is something
I need to tell you.
‐Right now is not
exactly the best time.
‐I told you that Yukimaru's
mother died, right?
‐Yeah.
‐I was the one who killed her.
‐Huh?
What did you say?
‐At that time,
Lord Orochimaru was
intent on creating
the Sound Village.
And I was ordered to
attack Yukimaru's village.
But I had exhausted my powers.
I collapsed.
That woman, I was her enemy,
but she saved my life.
Go now.
Get out while you can.
‐You weren't going to
betray me, were you, Guren?
‐You see, I
couldn't‐‐ I couldn't.
Back then, all I wanted was
to please Lord Orochimaru.
And so I‐‐
and I'd
almost succeeded
in forgetting all about
that terrible time.
Then I met Yukimaru and the
memories came flooding back.
‐That's why you protect him.
‐You were right about me.
I've hurt Yukimaru in ways I can
never hope to make amends for.
I have no right to
be his protector.
‐Guren.
‐It's too late for me.
But I'll see that you
make it out of here,
if it's the last thing I do!
You have to escape and live.
Protect Yukimaru.
‐I've got to say, that
sounds weird coming from you.
But that just proves that
you're a different person now.
‐Naruto‐‐
[water flowing]
Huh?
‐Camellias?
[grass‐whistle music]
‐Yukimaru.
‐It's him.
He's trying to show us
the way out of here.
Watch out!
Agh!
Ugh.
‐Ugh.
‐OK, up you go!
Agh!
No way I was going
to leave you in here.
We're getting out, both of us.
Now!
Aah!
[music playing]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): If
things continue to go wrong
and those fools from
the Leaf actually
succeed in sealing
the Three‐Tails,
it could seriously
jeopardize Lord Orochimaru's
whole strategy.
I can't allow that to happen.
If I ever had any pity for
Yukimaru, it's gone now.
I will squeeze every ounce of
power of the boy if I have to
and stop the Leaf shinobi.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Counterattack
of the Curse Mark."