[music playing]
‐Steady now.
The seal is almost complete.
Maintain your focus everyone.
‐(ALL TOGETHER) Right.
‐Huh?
Ahh!
What in the world?
Tenten, there is a
monster behind us.
‐Huh.
What the heck is that?
‐You recognize them, Kakashi?
Our persistent friends again.
‐Now is my chance to
get even with them.
‐A physical attack won't work
against that tower of goo.
‐Yeah.
Neither will my insects.
‐Man, these guys are a pain.
‐Maybe we should let the
two jonin take care of this.
‐I wonder if this is what is
meant by the word "disgusting."
‐Happy to see us again?
‐Yep.
That's disgusting all right.
[theme music]
‐What happened to Rinji?
‐Rinji?
Oh, I made him part
of my collection.
‐Your what?
‐He had become a
bit of a nuisance.
‐I spy for you, huh?
Wouldn't it make more sense if I
were the one reporting directly
to Lord Orochimaru?
‐What are you saying?
‐Just that I've done a
lot of undesirable tasks
under your command.
‐I alone serve Lord Orochimaru.
He needs no one else but me.
‐I see.
So everything's working out
just the way you planned, huh?
‐Yes.
But of course, I'm not the
one who deserves the credit.
Everything has happened just
as Lord Orochimaru predicted
it would.
He knew Guren and Yukimaru both
needed someone to belong to,
and so they'd form
a powerful bond.
And when the truth about
Guren was revealed,
this bond would be shattered,
and Yukimaru's anger
would unleash the
explosive force within him.
At least, it should have.
However, even when he
discovered that Guren
was the one responsible
for his mother's death,
no explosion was unleashed.
Why was that?
The human heart's a
funny thing, isn't it?
There's just no predicting it.
‐What you've done,
it makes me sick.
You think you can treat Guren
and Yukimaru like puppets.
Who gave you the right to
mess with people's feelings?
Just what are you after anyway?
‐You'll see.
Right now, it's just the
Leaf and the Akatsuki
who are fighting each other.
But soon, all the Hidden
Villages will be at war.
Lord Orochimaru is
waiting for the time
when the world is
consumed by war.
That's the reason he needed
Yukimaru and the Three‐Tails.
‐I don't understand a
freakin word you said.
[laughing]
‐Guren, if you meant what you
said, get him out of here fast.
‐I will defend
Yukimaru with my life.
‐Not a chance, four‐eyes.
First, you've got
to go through me.
‐Dead Soul Jutsu.
‐Guren.
‐Rinji.
Don't worry.
I'll keep my promise.
I will protect you.
‐No, Guren.
Don't!
‐Crystal Style.
Crimson Fruit.
‐Guren, wait!
‐Yukimaru, you wait right
there till I come back for you.
‐What?
‐Just wait right there.
‐I'll be back for
you, I promise.
‐Wait.
Don't leave.
If you leave, I'll
have no one left
in the world I can come home to.
‐I'm not leaving you.
Don't you worry.
‐How did‐‐
‐Forget that trick.
You may be able to form
thousands of tiny uniform
polyhedrons and then fuse them
together in a solid structure,
but my bats' ultrasonic
waves cause vibrations
that attack that
structure at the seams
and shatter it to pieces.
Yeah, now, you know your jutsu
was never any use against me.
I told you.
It's useless.
‐You're annoying,
even when you're dead.
‐Well, so much for Guren.
Now for you.
‐No you don't.
I swore to defend
him with my life.
‐Guren!
‐Your jutsu wouldn't
work when I was alive.
It certainly won't
work against me now.
‐You can't summon
your bats, can you?
Crystal style.
‐No.
No.
‐There's a place
waiting for you in hell.
[screaming]
‐No!
‐What's she doing?
‐No, Guren.
No!
Guren!
Don't leave me.
‐The jutsu's been broken.
‐She couldn't have.
She said she'd‐‐ she promised.
You swore that you'd
look after Yukimaru.
What happens to him now?
No.
Yukimaru!
‐The Three‐Tails will
be getting tired soon.
Then we'll finish it.
‐What's happening?
No, it's impossible.
Where is this sudden surge
of strength coming from?
I don't know how, but its chakra
level has definitely increased.
No.
The seal.
‐Yamato, restrain it
with your wood style.
Let me get one clear shot.
‐Got it.
‐Lightning Blade.
‐Kakashi.
‐I know.
Find the sealing team
and make sure they're OK.
‐(GROUP) Yes, sir.
‐It's here.
‐Not quite the way we expected,
but it worked all the same.
Losing Guren unleashed the
dormant forces within him.
I never realized that the
feeling of belonging to someone
could be so powerful.
‐Yukimaru, stop it.
[screaming]
‐You've got to.
No.
Yukimaru, listen to me.
You've got to stop.
Hey, it's me, Naruto.
It's no use.
He's not listening.
Dammit.
Hey.
If I could just get through
this barrier and get to him,
then‐‐ hey, Yukimaru!
Yukimaru.
KABUTO: That's right.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
‐I've got to stop this thing.
Multi‐Shadow Clone Jutsu.
‐Yeah.
Yeah.
Come on.
‐My Rasengan won't
work against it.
And it isn't like I can use
the Wind Style Rasen Shuriken.
Damn.
There's only one option left.
Summoning Jutsu!
‐Huh.
‐Tell me that's not the
Three‐Tailed Beast, brother.
‐Hm.
It looks to me like things have
gotten a little bit out of hand
around here.
‐No kidding.
You think I would have
summoned you guys otherwise.
Gamatatsu, time for
the Toad Water Pistol.
‐Roger.
‐Wait.
Hold on.
‐Huh?
‐What are you doing?
We don't have time for‐‐
‐Use your head, will you?
Your opponent's an
amphibious type beast
that lives in a lake
for crying out loud.
No matter how much you
increase the strength,
a Water Style jutsu won't do
any good against a Water Style
opponent.
‐Huh?
GAMAKICHI: To beat a Water
Style you need an Earth Style.
‐Well, it will all be beside
the point if we don't hurry up.
We'll just have to hope my Wind
Style's enough to‐‐ hold on.
So then I'm a perfect
match for Sasuke.
NARUTO: Well, yeah.
Wind beats lightning certainly.
‐No.
That's not what I meant.
What I meant was that only my
wind can assist and magnifying
his fire.
Yeah.
Fire Style.
‐What are you mumbling about?
‐If only one of
us had Fire Style.
‐Lucky for you, I do.
‐What?
You do?
You've got it?
‐Fire Style.
Yeah.
‐What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you say so before?
‐Because you never asked me.
So anyway, what about it.
‐Well, with Fire Style we can‐‐
‐What is it now?
What's wrong?
‐Dammit.
Well, so much for
that plan, I guess.
‐Spit it out.
Stop mumbling to
yourself, will you?
‐I thought it might
work if we magnified
the power of your Fire
Style with my Wind Style,
but then I remembered, fire
is always weak against water.
‐Hang on.
Not always.
Not if we could find a way
to make the fire so intense
it would evaporate
any Water Style.
Hey, Gamatatsu.
‐What is it, brother?
‐Get on back to the
village and fill your belly
with all the toad
oil you can swallow.
One minute.
That's all you've got.
Then we'll summon you back.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Get hopping.
‐On my way.
‐I get it.
We use oil not water in
the Toad Water Pistol,
then squirt the
stuff all around.
Then we set it on fire
with the Fire Style
like a flame thrower.
‐The best part is, it's the
same as the Toad Water Pistol,
so we don't need practice.
We got it down.
‐Genius!
It's going to work.
Yukimaru!
Guren, I'm going to keep
the promise you made to him.
I'll give him a place
that he can call home.
‐That's it, Naruto.
A minute's up.
‐Right.
Summoning Jutsu.
‐Did you get it done?
‐Yeah.
I think so.
‐Ready when you are, Naruto.
‐Gotcha.
All right.
Let's try this new
collaboration ninjutsu.
Aim for its eye.
That's its weak spot.
So are we ready to do this?
‐Make the first shot
a bullseye, because we
won't get a second chance.
‐Understood.
‐Right.
Gamatatsu.
‐OK.
‐Collaboration Ninjutsu!
Wind Style Toad Flame Bombs.
Now.
[roaring]
‐We did it!
Way to go, brother!
‐Yeah, you weren't bad either.
‐Looks like it's over for
the time being at least.
‐I guess that means
we're done here.
‐Yeah.
Thanks.
‐Any time.
‐Yukimaru?
Yukimaru, come on.
Let's go home.
[theme music]
KABUTO: Forgive me.
I wasn't expected a
Hidden Leaf to interfere.
OROCHIMARU: So, Guren is dead.
KABUTO: I'm afraid so.
It's a pity.
She had interesting abilities.
OROCHIMARU: Don't pretend
you didn't detest her.
KABUTO: As for Yukimaru, well‐‐
OROCHIMARU: It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters once
his body is mine.
You know whose I mean.
NARUTO: Next time, "A
Place To Return To."