High-Level Shinobi
Danzo...
He took Shisuis eye
before he died.
And from that day on,
you've been my goal.
At the beginning, I had
nothing, but I built bonds.
Like with Team 7.
On the missions with
you and Sakura...
Yaaah!
So Ill have to throw
him off guard.
Wha?!
He's after Naruto!
Ive got to stop him!
[Naruto] [coming to]
Nngh...
[Sasuke]
Ngh... You always...
...get in the way, Naruto...
it never fails...
You beat him, Sasuke!
Huh?
Why...Why did you...
save me?
Hrgh.
You should see the
look on your face.
You look like
a total loser.
But why?! Why'd you save me?!
I didnt ask for this!
Chyeah. I dont know.
My body just moved.
[faints]
Ahhh...
You know that I...
I always hated
you, Naruto.
Sasuke...
Dont let your... dream die.
Sasuke!
Aaaahhh!
Hey...
Yeah!?
Youre not hurt are you,
little girl?
Grrh!
Hyaaah!
Hn?
Hm!
Huh? What?!
Eat this!
[Naruto]
It's your fault our teamwork's
all messed up, Sasuke!
You think youre better
than everyone else?
No, not everyone else,
just you!
Rrrgh!
Listen, if you really don't
want to owe me anything,
Then just become
stronger than me.
[pants] Hey kid,
youre not hurt, are ya?
You scaredy-cat!
Augh!
D'yeeaaahhh!
Hyaaaaah!
Here! Thanks for waiting!!
The three of you
treating me to lunch?
I wouldn't be surprised
if it snowed on me.
D'ohh!
Nnnnh!
[in unison]
He fell for it!
Chidori!!
I'll beat you into oblivion
if that's what it takes,
to bring you back!
Haaaaaaa!
[Naruto]
I wanted to be
strong like you,
cool like you.
I guess thats why I kept
chasing after you.
No matter what happens,
I'm really glad that I
got to know you.
Naruto...
No matter what you
may say to me now,
I'm not changing.
Im still going to kill each
and every person in the
Hidden Leaf, including you!
I'll get revenge for
the Uchiha Clan!
But, is that really
the only way, Sasuke?
Yes.
Your only choices are to kill
me and become the hero who
saved the entire village,
or get killed by me and
be known as a loser!
Sasuke...
I just don't believe that.
I'm not going to be a loser,
but I'm not going to be the
hero who killed you, either!
Neither ones gonna happen!
[Naruto]
I...
Whoa!
[waterlogged gasp] You?!
When did you--?
Oh, I've been tagging along
for quite a while, now.
Tobi told me to observe
you and to make sure that
you didn't see me.
But it seems like you
were in a crisis, and
you needed some help.
[panting]
I should probably summon him.
It doesn't seem like Sasuke's
going to retreat.
Naruto, I told you to
go back to the Village.
Its...
...all clear to me now.
I really should collect the
Rinnegan before the war begins.
Hmm?
Sasuke. He's in a real bind.
What now?
"Its all clear?" What do
you mean by that, Naruto?
[panting]
Ah!
What's going on, Sasuke?
I told you to
go home and rest.
Madara!
[panting]
The Nine-Tails huh?
It seems that when you
two see each other,
you just cant suppress
the urge to fight!
Ill arrange the proper time
and place for you to fight
and capture the Nine-Tails.
But for now, we retreat.
And Ill stay and
fight for you.
After all,
We need to capture
the Nine-Tails
Jinchuriki anyway.
Madara and Zetsu.
They're sticking
close to Sasuke.
[Kakashi]
This is going to be
tough all by myself.
What to do?
No, Zetsu. Capturing
Naruto is beyond you.
The Nine-Tails is too tough for
a non-battle type like you.
We'll let Sasuke get the
Nine-Tails. I will enjoy
watching that.
Oh... Is that so?
[Madara]
Our bigger concern now is
Kisame. Go check on him.
And rendezvous with
your Black half.
Yes, yes, all right;
I understand.
Huh?
Naruto!
I know. But don't worry;
I'm all right.
There's just one thing I
want to make sure I say to
Sasuke before he leaves.
Let's go, Sasuke.
Not yet.
Sasuke.
Do you remember?
Do you remember what you said to
me long ago at the Final Valley?
The thing about
high-level shinobi?
When two shinobi are powerful
enough, they are able to read
each others thoughts simply
by an exchange of fists,
without ever uttering
a single word.
Youve always been
naïve, Naruto.
Tell me...
Do you know what I'm thinking
right now, at this very moment?
Can you read my mind?!
Trading blows just now...
I learned a lot about you
and what youre thinking.
It means we've become
high-level shinobi, Sasuke!
Both you,
...and me.
So, Sasuke...?
How about it?
Can you tell me what it is
I'm thinking right now?
Can you...
Read my mind?
And can you...
..understand...
That if you and I
fight each other,
...we'll both die.
Sasuke.
If you attack the Hidden Leaf,
I'll have no choice. I will
fight you, don't doubt that.
Until that day,
save your hatred.
Then you can throw
all of it right at me.
I'm the only one who can
handle all that hate.
Do you understand?
I'm the only one who
can fulfill that duty!
So, Ill bear the
burden of your hatred,
And I'll die
with you!
What is it with
you?! Huh?!
Just what in the hell
do you want from me?
Why are you so
fixated on me?
Because you're my friend!
[Naruto]
Sasuke.
From the moment we met,
I knew it would take a lot
of work if I was ever
going to understand you.
Exchanging punches is the way
we can understand each other.
I know that!
Like I said just now,
It means that both
of us have become
high-level shinobi!
Once we really understand each
other, your hatred will go away.
Just like mine when
I met Iruka Sensei.
I haven't given up on you!
Not yet.
I will take you back to
the Hidden Leaf Village!
I'll never
change my mind!
Naruto... you...
Heh, All right, I guess
that I'm done nagging
you for now, Sasuke!
Damn it, this is ridiculous!
I'm not any good with words;
I shouldn't try to lecture you!
[chuckle]
Well, I guess if the
worst does happen and
both of us end up dying,
You wont be an Uchiha and
I wont be the Nine-Tails
Jinchuriki anymore.
We'll be free of our burdens.
And we'll understand each
other in the afterlife!
I'm not going to change.
I don't want to understand you.
I won't die!
You're the one
who's going to die.
Then we'll die together, Sasuke.
Hmph.
Fine by me. But at least
I'll take you down first.
No problem, since it's
clear that you still
don't respect me at all.
Enough, Naruto. I'll handle
Sasuke. You have to pursue
your dream of becoming Hokage.
I wont let Sasuke take
you down with him.
But I'm not worthy
of being Hokage,
if I can't even
save a friend.
Fine, Sasuke.
I'll fight you!
Naruto stands here
with clear resolve.
So Ill bear the burden of your
hatred, and I'll die with you!
While my courage and
determination do nothing
but continue to waver.
I'm a shinobi, too. But I'm
always crying and relying
too much on Naruto.
I came here thinking that
I was past all that.
But still, I hesitate. I havent
really prepared myself at all!
I cant do anything,
I can't say anything.
All I can do,
...is to trust them!
[Kakashi]
All right. I'll leave
Sasuke to you, Naruto.
However, Watch over
my body, Sakura.
I'll get rid of
Madara right now!
Kamui!
Don't bother, Kakashi.
That jutsu won't work on me.
Huh?
Let's go, Sasuke.
Madara.
[Sasuke]
I want to talk to you later.
I'll be waiting,
Sasuke.
What did you
want to discuss?
I want Itachis eyes.
So, you're finally ready.
You've used the Susano'o
too much. Im aware that
your vision is almost gone.
Ngh!
Its perfect timing.
Transplant them
immediately.
Such a sudden change.
What's brought this on?
I will crush Naruto
with all I've got!
I'm going to eradicate
him completely!
And that's final!
[Sasuke]
Naruto. as always, thank you.
Because of you, I still
don't have to give up my
dream that team 7 will laugh
together again one day.
What?!
Huh?!
Naruto!
It must have
been this wound.
Aaagh! You mean
that... this is...
Uuggh...
Naruto?!
Naruto...
[Sakura]
It's because of the poisoned
kunai I used earlier?!
I'm afraid so.
[Kakashi]
You need to administer the
antidote right away, Sakura!
[Kakashi]
I'm taking you to
the Hidden Leaf.
Please behave yourself.
I wouldn't try anything
at this point, anyway.
Oh, boy.
I still feel
really sick.
Uh, are you all right?
Are you gonna throw up?
Hold on.
Thats him, huh?
That's Naruto Uzumaki.
Are you ready?
Just do it.
[Sasuke]
Itachi...
I will destroy the Hidden Leaf!
[Killer B]
Yo! It's been a while,
Omoi, Karui!
Ya been getting by cheerfully,
carefully, merrily?
[Omoi]
Of course not! Not since you
disappeared from the village!
[Karui]
Hey, he was alive,
so it's all good now.
[Omoi]
Whats that, Lord Bee?
A prize from my fight with
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist.
Its taken a liking to me.
[Naruto]
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
Infiltrator.
[Omoi]
Wow, thats one of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmens Blades?!