[music playing]
-Iruka, Sensei?
-Hmm?
-Tell me, did you hear the news?
-Hear what news?
-Apparently last night
there was a battle
in the forest in the back hills.
-And what happened?
-Well, the rumor is that enemy
spies were discovered out
there.
A patrol unit was able
to kill one of them
and bring the body back here.
-If that's the case, we
should warn the students
that they shouldn't go
near the back hills today.
-That's a good idea.
There might still be
more spies out there.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): I hope
nothing's happened to him.
-All right, I got
to find that corpse.
I wonder where it could be.
I've played here
so many times, I
know the place like
the back of my hand.
But I should have asked the guys
exactly where I should look.
-Naruto?
-Huh?
-Sensei?
-Come on, you have to get
back to the academy now.
-No!
I don't want to go to
The Academy anymore!
-You don't understand.
There are still dangerous
enemies out here.
-I won't go back
even if you beg me!
-Just do as I say.
I'm your homeroom
teacher Naruto.
-Oh, shut up!
You only act like a teacher
when it's convenient for you.
You don't get it.
You don't know what I
go through every day.
And none of that
is going to change
just because I go
back to school.
I'm always alone.
I'm always left out.
Look, don't you see?
Nobody wants me around.
Nobody cares!
-I--
-But this time
it'll be different.
If I bring something
back from out here,
then I'm finally going
to have some friends who
will accept me.
If I do that I won't
be alone anymore.
And I won't feel like
an outsider anymore.
That's why I'm going
to stay out here
until I can find something
good to bring back.
-Please listen.
I know that you
have your reasons.
But as your teacher, I
can't just walk away.
I won't allow you to stay
in such a dangerous area.
-You can't even try to
understand my feelings.
Well then, Sexy Jutsu!
[moans]
[screaming]
-Ha.
-Huh?
No, wait!
-Ha, grown ups are
so easy to trick.
It's not even funny.
Huh?
These are signs of a fight.
That means it's close.
[grunting]
Ah!
It's not here.
[stomach growls]
-Come of think of it, I haven't
eaten anything at all today.
Maybe I can find
something out here.
Aha!
Well, it looks like I
just found my lunch.
Huh?
What's that?
Whoa, I've never seen a kunai
shaped like this before.
[laughing]
The enemy ninja
must've used this kunai
during the battle yesterday.
I found something that I can
bring back to my friends.
-That kunai, it has the secret
documents we're looking for.
I see.
She must have placed it in that
nest before she was defeated.
-All right!
-Don't let him escape.
-Where did he go?
I hope he's OK.
-Well, he sure is a handful.
Listen, take my advice.
Don't give him any more
attention than you have to
and you should be fine.
-Leave him alone?
Just ignore him?
Naruto's right.
I've never really made an
effort to understand him
or what he might be feeling.
After the death of my
parents, there was no one
left to care for me or give
me the support that I needed.
I did a lot of stupid
things in class.
I wanted to get
people's attention.
Naruto, he's just
like I was back then.
[theme music]
[music playing]
-Hmm, hey Shikamaru, can I
borrow some money from you?
-Come on, not again.
Don't tell me you're spending
all of your allowance
only on snacks?
-Huh?
Shikamaru, snacks
are the only thing
in the world worth
spending money on.
-Oh, all right.
If that's how you feel,
I'll lend you the money.
-Hey, you two.
-Huh?
-Aren't you supposed
to be in school?
-Who are you?
I'm not supposed to
talk to strangers.
Otherwise my dad
will get mad at me.
-Well, you must be Shikamaru
Nara and Choji Akimichi.
-Hold on a minute,
how do know our names?
-You both look just
like your fathers.
You're Shikaku and
Choja's sons right?
Perhaps I should tell them
you've been skipping class.
-You're going to tell our dads?
But we both have a free period
right now, right Shikamaru?
-Why is that?
-It's because of Naruto.
He went to look for a
corpse in the back heels.
Iruka Sensei had to
leave class to find him.
-Iruka Sensei went after Naruto?
Is that true?
-Yeah, I'm positive.
-Listen, having a
free period doesn't
mean you get to leave school.
Go back to the
Academy right now.
-OK.
Uh.
-Now I'll be able to
make some real friends.
Huh?
-Hey, kid.
-Oh great, what do you want?
I'm in a hurry.
Had over that kunai
nice and easy.
-Hmm?
No, forget it!
This is mine!
I'm not giving it to you!
-I see.
Well then, we'll just
have to take it by force.
-What?
Just wait a second.
[gulps]
[screaming in distance]
-Naruto.
[yelling]
-Sexy Jutsu!
Ooh.
Ah!
-Too bad that technique
won't work on us.
Huh?
No way!
You're all women?!
Ah!
No fair!
In that case, Clone Jutsu!
-Unbelievable That's got to
be the most pathetic excuse
for a clone I've ever seen.
Now go and get him.
No mercy!
[screaming]
-If Ninjutsu won't work
don't let them get away.
There are traps all
over this forest
and I know exactly
where they're hidden.
-Hurry.
-Here they come.
[laughter]
[grunting]
-Ugh, how'd we get caught
in such a simple trap?
That brat is mine.
-Got to hold on.
I know there's another trap.
IRUKA: Naruto!
-Huh?
Sensei?
I'm over here Sensei!
[screaming]
-Ah!
[groans]
-Hey!
Are you all right?
Come on, wake up.
Wake up.
-Huh?
-Good, at least you're awake.
-Sensei?
-All right now, we have to
get you back to the academy.
-It's them.
-You're not from here.
What are you up to sneaking
around The Leaf Village?
-Hmm, and just who're you?
Leave the kid with
us and get lost.
I'm in charge of
this child's safety.
He's going home with me.
-What are you, his teacher?
-Ha, you're unfortunate to
have such a lame student.
Now you'll pay for his
stupidity with your life.
-Difficult children are
just more rewarding.
Besides, you won't be able
to defeat me that easily.
Naruto-- hang in there.
-Quickly, surround them!
-Die!
-I will not let you hurt Naruto.
[grunting]
-Don't let them escape.
Scatter.
Multi Phantom Shuriken Jutsu!
Can't dodge them.
What?
-Hey, you two all right?
-Kakashi, what are
you doing here?
-Your students told
me what happened.
And I got a little concerned.
Dammit, he's got got backup.
-So what?
We'll get rid of
them with Fire Style.
Synergy Jutsu.
-Go Iruka.
ALL: Karura.
-Kakashi!
-That's one down.
What?
-Lightning blade!
[screaming]
-Thanks a lot Kakashi.
I don't know what
would've happened
if you hadn't shown
up when you did.
-I'm confident that you
would have kept Naruto safe,
even if I hadn't been here.
-Mm, you gave me good advice.
I think I understand it now.
-Hmm?
-You were right.
I should have tried to be honest
with him right from the start.
I probably tried to
turn my back on him
so I could avoid
my own feelings.
But I think that I can
finally face him now.
-I see, that's good.
-Thanks.
-This map details The Leaf
Village's patrol network.
So this is what they
were trying to get then?
-Yes.
-Excellent work.
I'll have the patrol unit
reexamine their village sentry
patterns right away.
-Please do.
-It was coincidence.
But even so, it
appears that Naruto
has saved the entire village.
You may leave now.
-Yes sir.
-What is it?
-Lord Hokage, I
just-- I just wanted
to thank you for placing
me in charge of Naruto sir.
-Hmm?
-It's because of
that assignment I
remembered why I
wanted to do this,
why I wanted to be a teacher.
It all started
with something you
told me, Lord Hokage,
a long, long time ago.
[sobbing]
-It's hard to believe
it's been a year already.
You're very brave.
It's hard to do that, to
hide sadness behind laughter.
Your instructors
have been telling me
that you're among the most
playful of all their students
and that you're
always so full of fun.
-You're wrong!
I'm not sad about anything!
It's a noble thing to die in
the line of duty, isn't it?
My parents both gave their
lives to protect this place
from the fox demon!
They're heroes!
I'm the son of those
revered heroes.
I'm not even sad because they
went and left me all alone.
If I cry it's
because I'm proud--
-It's all right Iruka.
I know that somewhere
inside of you
there's a boy curled
up in a ball of pain.
But remember this,
you are not alone.
Inside every ninja
of The Hidden Leaf,
there burns the Will of Fire.
-The Will of Fire?
-It's what gives us the
strength to defend our village.
It's the unbreakable bond
the ties us all together.
It's what makes us a family.
(LAUGHING) I wonder, do you
have it yet, young as you are?
-I think so.
I wish to pass on
the Will of Fire
to the children of the future,
to children like Naruto.
-Huh.
-Aw, come on Sensei,
give me a break.
How could you have
lost that kunai?
-You
-Idiot
-Ah!
-Are you kidding?
You almost lost your life
today because of that thing.
-Yeah, that's true, but--
-Huh, you seem quiet today.
-That's because this
is the first time
that you've actually
yelled at me Sensei.
I'm just surprised.
-Yelled at you?
I guess I did.
That's because I
decided I'm going
to be more honest and
upfront with you from now on.
Starting tomorrow, I'm going
to be harder on you than ever.
-Huh?
If that's how it's going to be
I'm never going back to school.
-Naruto, do you have
the Will of Fire in You
-The Will of Fire, what is that?
It's the strong
will to do whatever
it takes to protect the
Leaf Village no matter what.
If you have it, then
you can become as strong
as the Lord Hokage.
-The Hokage?
Is he really as
strong as they say?
-He is.
But he's got more
than just strength.
Lord Hokage has the respect
of everyone in the village
because he's a great leader.
The fourth Hokage was a hero
who protected the village
from the Nine-tailed fox.
-A hero?
That's it then.
I'm going to be an even stronger
Hokage than the fourth Hokage.
And then everyone
in the village will
have to acknowledge
how great I am.
-Hmm.
-Well, my guess is, that by the
time you're about this tall,
you might be able
to become Hokage.
-OK, then I'll work just as
hard I can until that day comes.
-Naruto-- I believe you really
might become Hokage one day.
-Iruka Sensei, could you
give us a hand with this?
-Yeah, sure thing.
I'm on my way.
[sighs]
-Where had Suigetsu gone?
-Suigetsu?
huh, he went out two
or three days ago
and hasn't bothered
to come back yet.
To tell you the truth, I don't
care if he ever comes back.
-I heard that, you know?
-The executioner's blade?
You went all the way back
to get that old thing?
-Well, you left it behind.
It was a real pain to get back.
-I had better things to do
than worry about your stuff
when we fought the
Eight-tails, OK?
-Yeah, well, I carried the
two of you out of there
when you were dying.
So quit fighting.
-Oh, patronize me why don't ya?
-Yeah, whatever, I'm just
glad I have this baby back
where it belongs.
I'm incomplete without it.
-Now that all of
us are here, it's
time to get ready to leave.
-Huh?
You're all healed up?
-Yeah.
-We're heading to The
Hidden Leaf Village.
-And that's it.
-I never imagined Pain
would be defeated.
-This is most unexpected.
-And Konan's not coming
back here either.
-What should we do?
So many of our members are gone.
-We need more palms
to synchronize
with the Gedo statute again.
Kisame, you go track
down the Eight-tails.
-What about you?
-I have some other
business to attend to.
-This is much worse
than I imagined.
-You're late.
-Did Naruto do all this?
-No, it was all Pain's doing.
-What?
Pain?
-Yeah, but Naruto handled it.
He defeated pain by himself.
-He did?
What about the Nine-tails?
-Naruto was able to
control it all on his own.
[sighs]
-Well, that's good news.
Oh, wait-- Naruto controlled
the Nine-tails on his own?
-There's no time to
worry about that now.
We have to focus on
rebuilding the village.
It's going to be hard work.
Yamato, we're going to need
all the help you can give us.
-Right.
-What is it?
-An emergency
council's been called.
As Jounin squad
leader, you're required
to be there, Lord Shikaku.
-Already?
All right then.
[theme music]
KAKASHI HATAKE: So this
is where Naruto lives.
-He's a fool.
But it would be best if
you looked after him.
-Sure.
-He'll be on your team,
along with Sakura and Sasuke.
KAKASHI HATAKE: I'm
not naive enough
to go easy on them because
of personal feelings.
-I wish you the best of luck.
You're Going to need it.
NARUTO: Next time on Naruto:
Shippuden, Kakashi Hatake,
the Jounin in Charge.
-This looks like it's
going to be troublesome.