♪
[crickets chirping]
[groan]
Argh! Brother! How can you sit
and read all this stuff?
And Father, too...
Why does he have to
write so much?
All of it has to
do with Ninshu.
Every word has meaning.
Yeah, I know all
that, but still!
[quiet snore]
That's not it...
Like this, maybe?
(Hagoromo)
My two sons studied together
and played together.
This one's huge! Ashura,
quick! Get the net!
Uh, yeah!
Be careful!  Slow and steady!
Gotcha!
Ashura!
[splash]
Hey, look!
Damn it, Ashura...
You're so impulsive.
It looks like you've
got a bite, too!
You're right!
It might be even
bigger than yours!
[shouting]
[barking]
(Ashura)
Oh, it's just driftwood.
Whoa! That's amazing!
It's a huge fish!
Nice one, Ashura!
Uh huh!
Hey, wait... hold on...
What did you just do,
Elder Brother?
(Hagoromo)
At the time, Ninshu did not yet
have a practical application for
fighting.
My original intent for it was
to help bring souls together.
We needed healthy bodies to
sustain wholesome spirits.
But I didn't feel the need for
any martial arts training that
went beyond that goal.
However... due to the
innovations that Indra
introduced... the course of
Ninshu was changed drastically.
[gasps]
Whoa!
Elder brother! What'd
you just do, huh?!
A while ago when I was infusing
chakra to release power, I
noticed that the formation of my
hands created differences.
I think that you can invoke
different powers by how you
shape and combine your hands.
Wow, really?
I call it a "sign,"
and the manifestation of
the power is a "jutsu".
Sign and jutsu?
How cool! That's
awesome, Elder Brother!
(Hagoromo)
I inherited powers from my
mother, Kaguya.  So I don't have
to weave signs to invoke jutsu.
But that wasn't the case for my
pupils with whom I'd shared my
chakra.
When Indra was merely ten years
old, he was inventing jutsu even
I couldn't do.
He was one worthy of being
called the "Genius of Ninshu."
The invention of invoking jutsu
by using hand signs changed the
foundation of people's lives.
Eventually... it came to pass
that anyone who trained hard
enough was able to use jutsu.
But... I was a foolish father.
I didn't notice the powers of
darkness targeting Indra...
...and I didn't see that they
were already beginning to make
moves to manipulate him...
[scream]
Ashura!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm all right,
Elder Brother.
When releasing chakra, you have
to be very careful.  Or you'll
get hurt badly.
Plus, we possess more chakra
than most other people do.
Yeah, sorry...
Your invention has transformed
Ninshu an incredible amount.
I know... Although, I don't know
if that's a good thing or not...
Why is that?
Training used to be a much
more spiritual experience,
but now it's become focused
on just honing the jutsu
themselves.
In time, they could become
weapons, and that, in turn,
would create chaos throughout
the world.
Your astuteness is almost
frightening, my son.
I didn't realize you'd
thought so deeply about it.
Yeah, well...
(Hagoromo)
But then again, what
will be will be.
No one can stop the
flow of time.
If you hadn't invented hand
signs, then eventually, someone
else would have.
If chakra is to become a weapon,
then we must simply train the
soul even harder to control that
chakra.
Yes...
(Zetsu)
So it was you, huh?
rited Mother's powers!
You're the
one who inherited mother's power
Who's there?! Show yourself!
(Zetsu)
I'll be watching you. Always.
(Futami)
Very impressive, Master Indra!
...Now, Master Ashura...
All right!
Uhh...
[grunts]
[grunt]
That's enough.
You okay, Ashura?
Yeah, sure.  But you're really
strong, Elder Brother!
[knocking]
That means training's over!
I'm going to play with
Taizo and the others!
Oh, good grief...
Father, I'm going to go
train a little more on
the hill in the back.
Well, it appears that Master
Indra has gained great command
over the powers that you passed
on to him.
That's fantastic!
Why's that?
(Futami)
Oh... well, if you're to name a
successor one day, it's
customary to select the
first-born son.
Having a younger son inherit
could sow the seeds of
discontent.
Nobody would object to Master
Indra. He's naturally gifted
with Ninshu.
The future of Ninshu
is now secure.
[groan]
Hey, guys!
You're late, Ashura!
Yeah, sorry! But I'll have you
know that I came as soon as I
finished training.
Anyway, what's up?
Check this out!
(Ashura)
What are they?
(Edashi)
Wild boar tracks.
A lot of the fields around here
have been damaged recently.
Oh, yeah? Well, that's
not good, huh...?
I know! So why don't we
just go and hunt it down?
Huh?!
Uh, but won't
that be really
dangerous?
We'll all be just fine!
If worse comes to worst,
we've got Ashura with us.
You can just use your Ninshu
to bring it down, right?
What...?
That's right!
Yeah, so let's go!
There you are!
(Zetsu)
I'm so happy that you're
able to sense my presence!
A child...
Look, what do you want?  Why do
you keep following me around?
You will grow strong.  You have
the desire, potential, and
talent for Ninshu.
However... You're still not
aware of your true power.
My "true power...?"
An even greater power lies
dormant inside you.
But there is one condition
for awakening that power.
[chuckle]
Listen, just who are you?  How
do you know all of this, anyway?
It doesn't matter. But if you
do manage to awaken your true
power...
...my wish will come
true one day...
But never mind that.  We were
talking about awakening your
power, weren't we?
Do you want to know how?
It has nothing to do with
training, you know.
Hm.
You must lose love...
And what does that mean?
It's like... having someone that
you love deeply... die.
Let's test it out, shall we?
Wait, what? Hey, what
are you gonna do?
Wait!
[gasp] Ashura!
Over here! The
tracks go this way!
[barking]
Hey, wait... is that...?
[screaming]
Oh, no! It's coming
right for us!
[angry snarling]
All right!  I can use that rock.
[grunt]
[scream]
What's up with this guy?!
(Thinking)
That boar's not acting normal...
[scream]
[groan]
Ashura!  Quickly!
Use Ninshu!
Uh, yeah, right...
Um, let's see...
(Gasuka)
Watch out, Ashura! Run!
[snarling]
[bark bark]
Huh!?
Shiro!
[injured whine]
[grunt]
[nervous panting]
(Indra)
Ashura!
Huh?
Elder Brother!
Hurry!  Go on!
How dare you! My
younger brother?!
[attack growls]
Elder Brother!
Are you all right, Ashura?
Mhm...
But, look... Shiro's...
Shiro gave his life to protect
you.  Give him a proper burial.
[sob]
Elder Brother!
Look!  Your eyes!
This is...
[grunt]
Elder Brother?
Come out!  I know that you're
there!  Tell me, what did you
do?
(Zetsu)
Oh nothing. That's just
your true power.
From now on,... you'll be able
to use those eyes to see the
truth.
See you later!
What are you...?
[grunts]
[frightened gasp]
Amazing! [grunt]
You have to give it your all!
Uh... right!
And Ashura,...  you, as well!
You can't expect to succeed
at Ninshu like this!
Sorry...
Since he awakened his Sharingan,
Master Indra's progress has been
nothing short of phenomenal.
He's has good discipline, and
it's clear that he has the right
temperament to guide others.
He can take over Ninshu anytime!
[slurp]
(Apprentice)
Man! Master Indra is
absolutely amazing!
When he glares at me with
those eyes, I can't even move!
He's so young, and he's
already an instructor.
He's the one who invented
hand signs and jutsu!
Although recently he's
been really strict...
Of course, it's not like he
went easy on us before at all!
If Master Indra becomes the
successor, I don't know if I
want to follow him...
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Sometimes the way Master Indra
looks at us seems almost... I
don't know, hateful.
Master Ashura is much
easier to approach, but
he has no skills at all.
Well, nothing's ever
perfect, is it?
[groan]
Elder Brother! Are you going to
train in the mountains again?
Yes, that's my plan.
You think maybe I
could come with you?
I'm sorry. But I'd
rather train by myself.
Besides, with you there.
Yeah, you're right, of course.
Our skill levels are
just too far apart.
Elder Brother...
I think that maybe during
practice with everyone. Um, you
could go a bit easier on all of
the others...
It's just that... Well, when
you're all serious, then they
end up getting hurt, you know?
Yeah, good point.
I'll think about it.
Just come out. I can
sense that you're here.
(Zetsu)
Impressive... It's been a
while, hasn't it?
Yeah, and I've changed.
So it seems.
Have you gotten used
to those eyes?
(Zetsu)
Don't glare at me like that.
you could at least show
me some gratitude.
And why exactly should I
be grateful to you?
Well, I am the one who awakened
those eyes, after all.
By the way, did you see
something with those eyes?
Like the future of Ninshu?
Or your dreams?
You've already sensed it,
haven't you? That you're
special?
That you possess the power to
change the entire future of
Ninshu?
The power you possess is
overwhelming.
You've inherited most
of what Hagoromo has.
Ashura can't hold a
candle to you.
[gasp]
In time, your power will rival
your father Hagoromo's.
No one will be able to compete
with you then! [chuckle]
[thud]
(Indra)
Next!
What's the matter?!  Isn't
anyone here willing to spar
against me?
Cowards.
Elder Brother!  Why'd you do
that?  You said you'd think it
over!
Look, Ashura.  You don't have
the Sharingan, so you wouldn't
understand.
Power is what rules the world.
Power maintains order.
In time, I'll take over Ninshu
and fulfill my dream.
[horrified gasp]
(Ashura)
Elder Brother...
♪
(Villager)
Hey, did you hear?
Seems Lord Hagoromo is finally
going to name the successor to
Ninshu!
(Villager)
Master Indra or Master
Ashura, huh?
(Villager)
I wonder which of them it's
going to be...
There's no doubt!  It just has
to be the elder one, Master
Indra, since he excels at
Ninshu!
(Hagoromo)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Tumultuous Journey."
(Hagoromo)
And now, I'm going to
pick my successor...
♪