We've received word
from the Fourth Company.
It seems Lord Danzo's
ANBU bodyguards
have been reanimated.
Do you mean Torune and Foo?
They were listed as missing
in action.
I believe so.
So they were killed, then.
Yes.
Really? Both of them?
Only Torune has
been confirmed.
Notify every company!
When he is found, he
must be sealed immediately.
Is he actually
that formidable?
Shikuro Aburame's son...
If he's under the Reanimation
Jutsu, he might use a
Forbidden Jutsu.
Get word to
Naruto as well!
I wonder what happened
to Danzo's other
bodyguard, the one who's
called Foo.
That's right. He belonged
to the Yamanaka Clan,
didn't he?
Yes. I didn't want
him to join the
foundation, but...
What's the matter?
[frustrated gritting]
Even if it is a
Forbidden Jutsu, why
do you resist it?
No one from this
point on will
prohibit you.
Jar of Poison Jutsu!
[sinister chuckling]
You certainly know
your stuff.
Now go on, finish it.
Damn it! Being forced
to use this jutsu...
[surprised breath]
Excellent, good
job finding me.
My insects led me.
Wait...Shino?
Torune? Is that you, Torune?
Yes.
Judging by your appearance,
I can only assume you've
been reanimated.
Yes.
Which means...that you died.
That's right, unfortunately.
What happened to
Lord Danzo?
I heard he died.
I see...So Madara
killed him in the end.
The facts are slightly
different, but nevermind
that.
Please tell me what
you're doing here.
The Jar of Poison Jutsu.
What is that?
Insects are rapidly
multiplying in this chasm.
Do you remember
my Venomous Beetles?
I could never forget them.
Remember, you and I, we
both grew up together
like brothers.
Gotten used to the
Academy yet?
Not yet. It's because
my class is so rowdy.
I prefer playing with
insects, like this.
That's not gonna do.
In time you're going
to start being sent
out on missions.
And when you do, having
friends or not will make
a huge difference.
Torune, you didn't go
to the Academy, did you?
I didn't, because I'm
special, even within
the Clan.
Special in what way?
I guess it's time that
I told you about it.
My body is host...
To nano-sized
Venomous Beetles with
very toxic poison.
My body produces
antibodies for
the poison.
But if the beetles infect
another host...they will
destroy its cells and kill it.
But if the beetles infect
another host...they will
destroy its cells and kill it.
Don't touch it!
These Venomous Beetles of
mine thrive inside
of living cells.
They multiply and
destroy them.
If their host dies,
the Venomous Beetles
will also die.
Like a virus?
Yes. These insects can only
survive for any length of
time inside me body.
That's why I can't
touch anyone.
It's not that you didn't
go to the Academy, it's
that you can't go, that's
because...
Yes, you're right.
But you're different
in that regard.
You must get used to
the Academy quickly,
and make friends.
[mischievous giggling]
Wahoo!
Huh?
Hey! There's a whole
lot of bugs on your
desk, you know!
Yeah, he's right!
Just leave them alone.
These are my insects,
they're very special.
Oh! So you collect
bugs, huh?
Don't most people collect
rhinoceros or staghorn
beetles?
Say, you know what we
should do? Throw these
bugs at the girls in class!
"Ahh," they'd all say.
Wouldn't it be fun
watching them scream?!
These insects aren't
for that purpose.
Aw, come on!
Bugs are bugs!
Let's just do it!
Let's make them
scream, "ahh!"
And who are you
gonna make scream,
Naruto?
[distant yelling]
I don't understand
friendship.
The reason is because
everyone is so different.
Even if people are different,
if they spend time together,
aren't they friends?
Well then, I'd have
to consider my entire
class friends.
But it's not like that.
You know, you
analyze things
too much.
Dad...
Is that boy holding
the net your son?
Yes.
He's now at a suitable
age to enter the foundation.
Pardon?
As you know, the
Foundation is where
ANBU agents are developed.
Those who show great
promise are selected
when they're still
very young.
The Foundation's being
reorganized, and I would
like the Aburame Clan to
send us a candidate.
Has Lord Third
approved this?
Recruiting for the Foundation
is wholly under my jurisdiction.
Every Clan that possesses
a Hidden Jutsu, including the
Uchiha and Yamanaka Clans,
has sent someone to enlist.
Yes, but...Shino-
If he is your son,
then he must be
exceptional.
[conflicted reaction]
What is this all
about, dad?
Let me clear about it.
This is not a request,
it's an order.
But that's...
If this man's looking
for someone exceptional,
will I do?
Torune...
You, boy?
From the looks of you,
you aren't even a genin yet.
I'm the son of
Shikuro Aburame.
I wasn't aware Shikuro
had a son.
As fate would have it,
we're his guardians.
Hmm. Now I know
why you kept him
hidden. Interesting...
I have a few reservations,
but the foundation will
take this boy in.
I should tell you,
I can't be teamed
with anyone.
Don't be arrogant.
You're not the only
shinobi who possesses
a Secret Ninjutsu.
In the morning,
you will come
to visit me.
Understood.
Torune, you
sure about this?
It's not like joining
the Foundation
will kill me.
But we won't be
able to see each
other anymore.
This is goodbye.
But why, Torune?
Entering the Foundation
means abandoning
your past, as well
as your future.
I wanna say...
[surprised breath]
Thank you for
everything
until now.
Those Venomous Beetles are
lethal, but only transmitted
by touch.
What is the point of
a jutsu such as this?
The Jar of Poison Jutsu
requires a large amount
of flesh.
That's why it's
considered a
Forbidden Jutsu.
But I was able to
gather many bodies
from the battlefield.
With this many cells,
the insects won't die.
They'll just keep
multiplying.
And then, as the decaying
flesh releases gases...
Of course...The gas.
In the next phase,
the gas will be ignited.
The cells carrying my
Venomous Beetles will
scatter on the wind...
...and infect everyone
in the surrounding area.
That's the Forbidden Jar
of Poison Jutsu.
So it doesn't discriminate
between friend and foe.
Hurry, call for
reinforcements.
You can't stop
me alone.
You're wrong. I'm
probably the only
one who can.
It's useless. I underwent
very rigorous training
at the Foundation.
Yes, I know that all
of you in the Foundation
are quite skilled.
I never thought it possible,
but I actually made a friend
in the Foundation.
Hidden Jutsu: Beetle Sphere!
Foo...
[determined breath]
Did you ever make friends?
[shocked gasp]
Shino...?
I don't really know
if I have any friends.
That's because I'm not sure
that they consider me to
be their friend,
You're still
over-analyzing.
To me, it's merely
viewing things
accurately.
I think it was good
that I joined the
Foundation.
With my physical constitution,
I couldn't be an ordinary
shinobi doing ordinary
missions.
However, the Foundation's
ANBU was quite a good
fit for me.
As someone who uses a
Secret Ninjutsu.
Making contact with your
opponent is the basis of
your jutsu.
I want to see your
taijutsu skills.
So I'm going to
have you spar with Foo.
But sir...my body
will be-
Lord Danzo told me
about you.
The main thing is just
to avoid touching
your skin, right?
Not that you'll
be able to touch me.
What's that?
Just remember, you joined
the Foundation today.
Don't think you're
my equal.
[frustrated reaction]
Begin.
[battle cry]
You call that
being on guard?
If I were fighting
seriously, you'd
be dead.
Lord Danzo needs to assess
you. He wants to know your
true strength.
So you have to
fight seriously.
Now come on!
You're nothing but talk!
You may show him.
Sir!
[yelling in attack]
There you go.
[defeated reaction]
Stop. That's enough.
Damn!
From this moment on, the
both of you are going to
form a two-man cell.
Foo, teach Torune
everything about the
Foundation.
Yes, sir.
I'm with him?!
The Mind Transfer Jutsu
and the Venomous Beetle
Jutsu should pair well
with each other.
[surprised gasp]
Shino, do you know
what has happened
to Foo?
I don't.
You were both listed as
being missing in action.
I see...
Maybe Foo's been
reanimated as
well, then.
We have no reports
about that.
Shino, why waste time
listening to my old stories?
You haven't called for
help. Just how do you
intend to stop me?
I know you're only
trying to buy time.
The reason is because
the insects require more
time to multiply.
You intend to die here
with me...But that's futile!
You cannot attempt
close combat with me.
If I can't use my
beetles, then I must.
Get men skilled in
long-distance
fighting! And
Sealing Jutsu!
I don't know anyone
like that nearby.
Shino!
[grunt]
Naruto!
Well, kinda. I'm a clone.
I came over here because
I sensed your chakra.
Is that the guy HQ
sent the message about?
I'm impressed that you
recognized my chakra.
Yeah, I learned how
in my training!
No, I didn't mean
it that way.
Shino, don't let
him attack recklessly.
All I have to do is
pulverize this guy, right?
The Venomous Beetles would
scatter everywhere. And our
opponent's reanimated.
We must seal him
to beat him.
Don't touch him, the reason
is because his Venomous Beetles
will infect you.
But not only by touch...
Poison Cloud Jutsu!
[inhale]
Get back! Don't
inhale no matter what!
Touching or breathing
them does that.
Naruto, do you posses
a Sealing Jutsu?
No, I don't. You don't
have one either?
I've been given some sealing
tags. But, what I don't have
now is a way to apply them.
Get rid of those
tags, Shino!
I'll be forced to
destroy anyone who
gets in my way.
My body will just
attack on its own!
I'm not gonna let you
lay a single finger
on Shino.
I'm gonna stop all
your attacks!
You're the one who can't
lay a single finger on
him, Naruto.
That's because-
I get it, and I'm
sure you're right.
You had better watch
out, Jinchuriki.
The Assassination Jutsu
of the Foundation.
Like I care!
[angry grunt]
[battle cry]
Rasengan!
[attack yell]
Not good!
[shocked reaction]
Dodge this!
Naruto!
Shino!
[gasp]
[grunt]
No!
Jinchuriki, quick!
Take me down! Seal me!
Otherwise...I'll
continue to-
[nervous breath]
Shino, are you alright?
[painful struggle]
Stay back, Naruto.
Shino...?
Now as insect users, let's
settle this, just the two
of us!
Shino, how did you manage
to survive that?
You...You touched the
Venomous Beetles!
No, I didn't touch them.
Your beetles touched mine.
You were like an
older brother to me.
I wanted a keepsake of
you, so I nurtured and
bred my own Venomous
Beetles.
I raised them by
feeding them my
insects.
Years later, after many
generations of offspring...
...insects with antibodies
against the Venemous Beetles
were born.
These are those insects.
With the antibody they
possess, touching your
Venomous Beetles won't
kill them.
You may be an Insect User,
but no one can host an
insect as unique as that.
Especially not in this
large quantity.
Yes. At first I only
carried about ten with me.
But when I got here,
I made them multiply.
Maybe it was the jutsu
barrier, but it took
less time than
I calculated.
Shino...you...
I know you're only
trying to buy time.
The reason is because
the insects require
more time to multiply.
You never miss a detail.
But it's different now.
You see...I'm not alone
amymore.
Forgive me. For
this seal.
No, you don't need
to apologize.
Hey, Shino, what do
we do with everything here?
Don't worry. The Jutsu
User has been sealed.
Eventually these insects
will die.
You mean this
is all over.
Please go, Naruto.
Kiba and Hinata
are that way.
Right!
Torune, I'm grateful.
I'm glad that I didn't
have to join the
Foundation.
It's because...
Hey! What about
you, Shino?
Come on, hurry it up!
It's because, I got
to make friends.
I've been told to leave
Naruto alone. However...
not Eight Tails.
I can't wait to conduct
Lord Orochimaru's tests
on him!
Bee, I'm going to
prepare the perfect
reanimation for you.
Wait! He's...
You're the Eight Tails'
former Jinchuriki! Fukai!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"A Hole in the Heart:
The Other Jinchuriki"
It certainly has
been a while, Bee.