You once told me
that you're nobody.
That you don't
want to be anybody.
No, stop it!
Don't step into my thoughts!
But the truth is that
you wanted to be
Hokage, just like me.
It could've even ended up
being the case that I was
chasing after your shadow
since becoming Hokage has
always been my dream.
I threw away the
past and my naïve self!
Don't say-
Then tell me why I'm
able to see this!
You can hide behind a
mask, but it's pointless.
You were Kakashi
Sensei's friend, my dad's
subordinate, an Uchiha like
Sasuke, my senior, and a
Leaf shinobi who shared
the same dream as me.
What is all this?!
Just tell me...
What is it that
you want with me?!
I want to remind you
that you're Obito Uchiha.
I told you that I'd tear
that mask right off your
face, remember?!
Obito Uchiha?
What meaning is
there in that name or
in that existence now?
I've merged with Ten Tails.
And I have transcended
and attained enlightenment.
I am no longer human.
I shall lead mankind
into its next stage.
I possess the same
will and body as the
Sage of Six Paths.
I am the Second Sage!
Wrong!
You are Obito Uchiha!
When our chakra
touched earlier, I saw
into your past.
Our personal histories
and our dream of being
Hokage are the same.
Almost exactly the same...
Neither of us knew our
parents, and we both lost
people precious to us.
Which is why you tried to
scare me by saying solitude
is my worst nightmare.
At the start, you wanted
to be acknowledged
and praised by others, too!
I bet that's why you
wanted to be Hokage.
I mean if you're
the same as me...
But look at you now!
You've made all shinobi
your enemy and spout
nonsense that it's for
the world's sake!
When really, you're
only doing it for yourself!
Not one person, not even
those precious to you, would
ever acknowledge this
current dream of yours.
You used to have
the same dream as me.
Now you're the
opposite of a Hokage!
It's 'cause you're
just like me that-
No, it's because of that.
That's why I wanted
to see you despair
about this world.
Or I suppose I wanted to
feel again for myself that
the path which I've chosen
for myself is not a mistake.
When I was battling against
you, you made me recall
myself from my youth.
That's why
wanted to test you.
To see when you would fall
into despair and reject your
feelings and past...
It's because we're so alike
that you really annoy me!
Get it?!
You're just abandoning
everything and running away!
No...
What I'm doing's
no different than
a Hokage's actions.
More, in fact.
For I can truly
bring about peace.
Are you serious right now?
You?
You really,
truly believe that?
Hey, you know, Rin, if you
really think about it, you
saving me is pretty much
the exact same thing as you
saving the whole world!
Huh?
'Cause I mean, I'm gonna
become Hokage and I'll bring
this war to an end, right?
And for me to do
that, I have to stay
alive and healthy.
Get what I'm saying?
Mm-hmm!
It kinda makes sense...
So, it's like this-
How do I put it...
I mean, if you don't
stay close and keep
a watch over me.
Well...
It's just- [gasp]
Y- You got so close
to me all of a sudden!
Don't scare me
like that, Rin!
You said to stay close
and keep watch over you!
[giggle]
Yeah, I guess I did.
So watch over me!
'Cause I'm gonna wear
the Uchiha crest...
And become Hokage!
Right!
Yes, I do...
That's how I feel.
There's no need to
voluntarily walk a rugged
path, whose destination
isn't even clear.
And step over
comrades' corpses.
So, any person who's
sensible would choose a
shortcut with a
fixed outcome.
That's right...
The goal a Hokage
should seek is to
create world peace.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
What I want to know isn't
the shortcut or the easy
path, but how to
navigate the rugged one!
Would you still say that
even if both of those paths
led to the same place?
But in the beginning, how
can you tell which one is
the rugged path?
I mean, you never really
know until someone
starts walking down it!
A Hokage is the one who
walks ahead of everyone
else, enduring
their own pain.
So that's why a Hokage
never walks over
his comrades' corpses.
There's no shortcut
to becoming Hokage!
And no way out for the
one who becomes Hokage!
Correct?
Oh man, oh man, oh man!
This is the one
day I can't be late!
You're even late to
the entrance ceremony?!
Someone like you has
no business being
in the Academy at all.
You'll fail out.
It's okay.
Huh?
Since you weren't there,
I picked this up for you.
For me?
Yeah!
Just submit this packet, and
you'll be able to enroll!
Wow, thank you!
You're a lifesaver!
You know, if you keep
pampering him, then he'll
never get over
his tardiness.
Hey, shut up!
You wanna fight?!
Say that again!
What?!
It's your own fault!
[chuckle]
What did you say?!
Stupid Kakashi!
A perfect score!
[cheering]
Are you trying to kill me?!
Sorry, sir!
[laughter]
Now begin!
Stop!
Yes, sir!
Um, uh, hold on,
let me see here...
I didn't call on you.
What's the matter?!
[laughter]
What?!
Kakashi's taking
the graduation exam?
Mm-hm!
But he's the
same age as we are!
He's so brilliant that
they're going to
let him skip a level!
He should be taking
the exam right now!
Damn it!
[gasp]
-[gasp]
-He did it!
Yes!
Excellent job, Kakashi!
Hey, what's
with the headband?
That means that
you passed it!
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Well?
Aren't you going
to congratulate me?
Yeah, right!
I'm gonna catch up
with you in no time!
Just you wait!
Hmph!
Obito...
Class is going
to start soon.
Let's go.
Rin...
Please, just-- just keep
watching over me, okay?
Uh, what?
I...
I'll catch up to him.
And then I'll
surpass him and...
I'll become
Hokage, no matter what!
Don't worry.
I'll be watching.
All right!
I'll do my best!
It's no good...
What's the point?!
Of course I totally failed!
Damn it.
I still can't
catch up to him!
[sigh]
What am I going
to say to Rin?
Ah, so this is where
you ran off to, huh?
I had no idea
where you went!
Oh, sorry about that.
Got something for you.
Here!
Huh?
Does this mean?
Congratulations!
This means that
starting today, you're
a full-fledged shinobi!
I did it!
However!
The difficult days as a
Genin are just starting!
Right.
Yes, sir!
Hereafter, you will be
part of a three-man squad.
Each group has a Jonin in
command, and you'll fulfill
your missions as a team.
Pardon me, sir?
You summoned me?
I want to ask a
favor of you.
The one who just left here.
Isn't he Kakashi Hatake?
That's right.
He's the orphaned son of
Sakumo Hatake, the White
Fang of the Leaf.
Is there some kind
of issue with him?
Kakashi's an
extremely talented shinobi.
However, he can be much too
fussy about sticking to the
rules, and on top of that he
also frequently clashes with
his superiors
and his teammates.
He may excel in technique.
But as a person, I'm
afraid he has much to learn.
His father broke the rules
to protect his comrades and
then took his own life.
Seems his death
has cast quite a long
shadow over Kakashi.
You want me to
supervise him?
I know what you
want to say to me.
But our village has lost
many Jonin and Chunin due to
the long war in which
we've been embroiled.
I can only make so
many allowances.
But now I must send the
young ones off to war.
I understand.
Good grief!
How long are you going
to keep me waiting?!
I'm so sorry!
He'll be here shortly.
He's late.
As usual!
Oh, don't worry!
He'll be here soon!
You're too easy
on him, Rin.
Sorry I'm late!
Rin?
[giggling]
No surprise there!
How is it that
you never learn?!
What's that?!
Whoa, there!
Okay, guys.
Cut it out, all right?
Mr. Genzou is
tired of waiting, so
hurry and line up.
All right, now look at me!
[annoyed harrumph]
[chuckle]
Come on. It's a
commemorative photo.
Look at the camera!!
You just couldn't discard
the memories of my dad,
Kakashi Sensei, or
this Rin, could you?
You tried to run
away from everything.
I bet this Rin person
would say this if
she were still alive.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "I'm Always
Watching."
"I am always
watching, you know..."