[humming]
-Those are called cat tails.
-Huh?
-Why don't you try
squeezing the top?
See?
This is the lake
I told you about.
[humming]
[theme music]
-So it's true.
Lake water doesn't
taste salty at all.
Not like the ocean.
Course, I've never
seen the ocean, either.
Did you--
-Hm?
-There This should
be far enough.
[laughter]
-What's so funny, then?
-I have a feeling we're
about to do something fun.
-That's right.
We're about to
have a lot of fun.
Will you put this on for me?
This pill will draw
out your power.
No-- what I mean is it will make
something interesting happen.
[groan]
[scream]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): It's coming.
That was the threshold.
So it's there.
In this lake.
No doubt about it.
Yes.
We can definitely use this
child, Lord Orochimaru.
-You called, Kakashi?
-Thanks for coming, Pakkun.
Take this back to
the village and tell
Lady Tsunade to
have it analyzed.
-Huh?
What on earth is it?
-It's a jutsu that was cast
on one of Shino's insects
by a follower of Orochimaru.
We think.
-Orochimaru again?
-From the footprints
they left, we're
looking for five, maybe six.
Anyway, we're going after them.
Get back to the village quickly.
-Leave it to me.
-I know I can count on you.
All right.
Let's get after them,
whoever they are.
But not all together.
We'll spread out,
widen our search area.
We cannot afford to
let them slip through.
-Right.
[bark]
-Got it.
-No problem at all.
I'll take care of everything
here while you're away.
Don't worry.
-You'd better.
-Could she make
it anymore obvious
that she doesn't trust us?
She doesn't want us finding
out about Orochimaru's hideout,
so she shows us in this dump.
-She's extremely cautious,
no doubt about it.
That's why she doesn't
make that many mistakes.
And that's also why
we can trust her.
-Yeah, but those
poor slobs she killed
were running away because they
didn't want to see Orochimaru.
Are you sure we can trust her?
GAMARIKI: 1, 2, 1, 2.
NARUTO: 1, 2, 1, 2.
-It's perfect, Naruto.
Gamariki's stern discipline
will soon harden and temper you
like a steel blade.
And then you'll--
[giggling]
-And then your body and
spirit will be tough enough
to resist the temptations
of the world, and-- ah!
I hope to be able to
resist them too, someday.
-What You can't even learn a
simple little move like that?
-Hey, it's not me!
I can learn it fine!
You just don't know how
to teach it, that's all!
-I get it.
It's me.
I suppose you could do better?
-Just forget it.
I've had enough of this.
I quit.
-Well, we'll just
see about that.
Love tap!
-Hittin' me from behind, huh?
You cowardly toad!
-No-- just-- get off me!
[screaming]
[shouting]
WOMAN: Oh, my goodness!
WOMAN: What happened
to the water?
WOMAN: Let's get out of here.
-No!
-You call that training,
slobbering all over me
like that?
-It's not slobbering,
it's a love tap, you--
-I don't care what you call
it, this partnership is over!
-Well, that suits me fine.
-That is enough, both of you!
Knock it off!
-Hm?
-Coming from Naruto,
I'm not surprised.
But you too, Gamariki?
I must say, I'm
very disappointed.
-Forgive me.
I really do understand, Jiraiya.
Really, I do.
It's this boy.
He's--
-This collaboration
ninjutsu will never
work unless the two of you
get your hearts and bodies
working in perfect sync.
-Exactly.
But in order to achieve that,
we have to be, uh-- well, compatible.
-Yeah!
And we're not compatible.
And things will go
a lot faster if you
let me find somebody
I am compatible with.
-Heh.
That may not be such a bad idea.
There's just one problem.
How can you summon anything
with that arm of yours?
-Heh.
You're forgetting how fast
my body can heal, Pervy Sage.
See what I mean?
-Hm?
-Summoning Jutsu!
What the wha--
-Long time no see, pal.
-Hey, Naruto.
How's it goin'?
-Gamakichi?
Tatu?
Wha--
-Well, Well.
You two sure have grown.
-Yeah.
I almost didn't recognize you.
You've gotten a lot bigger.
-Of course we have.
-It's on account of we
both ate a lot of snacks.
-So anyway, Naruto, what
did you summon us for?
-Right.
Here's the plan.
How do you feel about
perfecting our synchronicity
and compatibility?
-Huh?
-What's that?
Does it taste good?
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
Lord Orochimaru.
That's--
-You're late, Guren.
Lord Orochimaru has
chosen Gen'yumaru.
And that was Sasuke
Uchiha just now.
Lord Orochimaru's next vessel.
-So, Sasuke, let's see how
your training's coming.
Show me all that you've learned.
-You're going to be my opponent?
-Course not.
Very impressive.
You stand there facing
a thousand opponents
without batting an eye.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): That
man-- how strong could he be?
-Let it begin.
Yes, Sasuke.
You truly are the one.
-What is it?
His power-- I've
never seen such--
-OK, then.
But I gotta warn
you, we're going
to really put you
through your paces.
-Yeah.
You do that.
-And a one, and a two.
Hit it.
(SINGING) Can you
hear the froggy song?
Yes, I hear the froggy song.
Can you hear the froggy--
-Hey, wait a minute.
What are you guys doing?
-Yes, I hear it and I
see yummy fly to eat.
-Heh, heh.
Boing, boing, boing,
boing, boing, boing, boing.
-Gotcha!
Boing.
-Get with the program.
You're not trying to connect
to his heart and soul, Naruto.
-Come on!
This can't really
be part of training.
[sigh]
-When will you
ever learn, Naruto?
-Did I get 'em all?
-You defeated them all
without one fatal blow.
You are still naive.
-They're not the
ones I want to kill.
-You must learn to be heartless,
or you'll never defeat Itachi.
-When I come face
to face with him,
I'll be heartless, all right.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Not a drop of blood on him.
They called me a genius,
but compared to him,
there's no comparison.
Just a little longer.
A little more patience--
and he's mine.
-It's been a long time, Guren.
I'm so glad you've come.
Yes.
That young man is destined
to be my next vessel.
You still want to be my
vessel yourself, don't you?
You haven't given
up on that dream.
Your skills are
indeed very enticing.
I was so impressed
when we first met.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Lord
Orochimaru-- you're wrong.
-These powers of yours,
they intrigue me.
Come with me, child.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): You're wrong.
I was the one who was impressed.
By you.
Your power.
I wanted nothing more
thing than to be like you.
-And now for the reason
I summoned you here.
I have something special I
need you to do for me, Guren.
-Anything.
You know I live only to
serve you, Lord Orochimaru.
-Call it a mission.
A mission that would benefit
from your unique talents.
In fact, you're the only one
who could possibly do it.
-I'm the only one?
-And afterwards, who knows?
I might even reconsider.
I might change my mind about who
is best suited to be my vessel.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
He's getting tired.
Perhaps we should
rest for a bit.
[giggling]
-What a joke.
Trying to keep up with a
bunch of stupid dance moves.
It's embarrassing.
Trying to connect heart and
soul is crazy, especially
with a toad.
CHILD: Can you really do that?
-Huh?
Hey?
Who said that?
Who's there?
-Where'd you come from?
-What does that mean, to
connect heart and soul?
-Uh, well, uh, it's
when you can feel
what someone else is feeling,
and they feel what you feel.
-Can anyone connect like that?
-Well, yeah, I suppose.
Hm.
If you stay focused
and keep working
at it, one day-- one
day it has to work.
And then even Sasuke-- 'cause
wherever someone is still
thinking of you, that
place is your home.
But you wouldn't know what
I'm talking about, would you?
Sorry.
I was kind of rambling.
-So if somebody somewhere is
thinking about me, wherever
that person is is
where I belong.
-That's right.
Wherever it is,
that place is home.
-I've learned something.
-Yeah, I know lots of stuff.
[laughter]
-So tell me, what's
your name, anyway?
Huh?
Weird kid.
Where'd he disappear to?
-Kakashi-sensei, is
this really the right
time for us to be kicking
back and taking it easy?
-We can't do anything until
my insects locate the enemy.
We might as well rest up.
-He's right, Kiba
-Yeah.
Until we find out exactly who
they are and where they are,
there's no sense in
us jumping the gun.
Besides, there's
that crystal jutsu.
Until Pakkun gets back with
word from the Hidden Leaf,
we've got to move with caution.
[knocking]
-Enter.
-Lady Tsunade, Kakashi
sent us a messenger.
-Well, well.
Pakkun.
-Before I give you
Kakashi's message,
do you think I could
have some water?
-Feels good.
Nice and hot.
-Huh?
What the-- you
shrunk, Gamakichi.
What happened to you?
-Of course I shrunk.
If I hopped in here
full sized, there
wouldn't be room
left for anyone else.
I used ninjutsu to
make myself small.
-Really?
Whoa, that's a
pretty cool ninju--
-Nothing like a hot
bath, is there, brother?
Especially after a
hard day of training.
-Please, you call that training?
All you guys did was
chase flies all day.
-No.
We were working
on the foundations
of the collaboration ninjutsu.
-Get out of here.
You really expect me to copy
those wacky moves of yours?
-Who said anything
about copying?
This training's about
learning to feel
what's in Gamatatsu's heart,
and how to respond to it.
-Gamatatsu?
-This feels so nice.
-Forget about copying
his every move exactly.
Feeling what's in your partner's
heart, feeling it in yours,
that's the essence
of collaboration.
That's how you get two
beings in perfect sync.
-Your partner's heart.
Feeling it.
Now I see.
I get it.
Yeah, I finally get it.
Let me try one more time.
I'll master this collaboration
ninjutsu, even if it kills me!
-Yay!
I love training.
-Huh?
Oh, no!
Wait!
[shouting]
WOMAN: Not again!
-Get a grip, Gamatatsu.
-My tummy hurts.
-Ah, yes.
The sweet voices of
bathing beauties.
-All the bathing
beauties just left.
-Ah!
No!
[theme music]
GAMAKICHI: Naruto,
you'll never get it
if you keep getting
distracted by what you see.
GAMATATSU: I'm hungry.
NARUTO: What else is new?
GAMATATSU: Look, grasshopper!
GAMAKICHI: Don't focus
so much on his moves,
but where they're coming from.
GAMATATSU: Snack time!
NARUTO: That's what
I'm trying to do!
GAMATATSU: Oh, caterpillar!
GAMAKICHI: Try and feel
Gamatatsu's emotional vibes,
then channel them
through your own style.
NARUTO: Will you shut
up for a second, please?
Think I'm finally on
to something here.
Next time, Connecting hearts.