-Eh?
-Ah!
-Focus.
You're still moving.
Even if it's just a little.
Remember, don't move.
-Doing this stuff
without the toad oil
is a lot harder than I
thought it was going to be.
-Well, of course it is.
Just want did you expect when
you stopped using the shortcut?
-Hm?
-Not even the slightest quiver.
-You know, I just
thought of this, but--
-What is it?
-Why can't I just
take this oil with me
and use it when I fight?
Then I wouldn't even have to
learn all this stuff about how
to take in nature
energy without the oil.
-That isn't possible.
-Huh?
Why?
-Outside of Mt.
Myoboku's climate, this oil
evaporates almost immediately.
It just vaporizes.
-What?
Are you serious?
-I already told
you, the oil is just
a tool to help you
grasp the concept.
-Yes, sir!
-But the way you
transform into a frog
so quickly-- your
powers of concentration
are still lacking.
Now be serious.
-I am.
I promise I am.
Despite how it looks, I did
learn the tricks to focus.
-That is enough.
You just come along with me now.
-What's this?
This isn't what I
think it is, is it?
-Yes.
Exactly.
This is where you're
going to be training next.
Balance a stone slab
atop the highest point
and begin meditation.
If your concentration wavers
and you move even slightly,
you'll fall to the bottom.
-I'd fall from way up there?
-OK.
This should do just fine.
Follow me, Naruto boy.
Stay still.
You must learn to stop
your motion as an animal.
You need to find your
center of balance
and motionlessly synchronize
with nature around you.
NARUTO: Ah-- whoa-- whoa!
Whoa.
You saved me.
-You have to wait on
taking in nature energy
until you learn how to
perfect being still.
[stuttering]
[scream]
-Uh-oh!
-Naruto boy, maybe it's time we
took a little break from this.
-Damn.
I can't believe how difficult
it is just to stay still.
Doesn't this training
seem sort of ridiculous?
-That is utter nonsense.
Your master,
Jiraiya boy, managed
to learn this very
same exercise himself.
-What?
Are you serious?
You're telling me Pervy
Sage trained here, too?
-That's right.
The two of us came here to
train together quite often.
-Thanks, Lord Fukasaku.
-Jiraiya boy, I think that
we should call it a day.
What do you think?
-Naw, I'm fine.
I can keep going like
this all day long.
-But Jiraiya boy--
-I think I'm just on the
verge of really getting this.
So can you help me
a little longer?
-I'll give him this, he had more
guts than anyone else around.
-Hey.
About how long did Pervy
Sage take to learn this?
-Well, he could only come here
to train when Jiraiya boy was
in between the many missions
that the Hidden Leaf sent him
on.
So it took him quite some
time to master it all.
-I see.
-Naruto boy?
-Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu.
I don't have time,
so I guess I'll just
have to pick up the pace.
If Pervy Sage did the same
training, I'll do my best, too.
[theme music]
[scream]
-That sucked.
-You simply have to
focus harder, Naruto boy.
-So colorful.
It looks tasty.
-Ah.
Hey, would you like
one, Naruto boy?
It's my favorite,
larvae rice balls.
-No thank you.
-Can't watch.
FUKASAKU (VOICEOVER):
It's going well.
He's rapidly amassing
nature energy.
Yes.
He's finally got it.
I'm impressed at how far he's
gotten without using the oil.
He's displaying the
rings around his eyes,
proof of successful sagehood.
And no frog aspects, either.
This could mean
that Naruto boy will
become a sage, one that
surpasses Jiraiya boy.
It seems he's able to build
up even more Sage Jutsu
chakra than when he was
using the oil, tool.
-Well, how does it feel?
-You know, I think I'm
finally getting it now.
How to become one with nature.
Ah-- ah--
[scream]
-Wait, hold on.
It hardly hurts at all.
-Exactly.
That's because of Sage Mode.
Your body has become
activated in a whole new way.
-Oh, wow!
That's amazing.
That's Sage Mode, huh?
-And now that we have mastered
Sage Mode and nature energy,
we have come to one final step.
-What?
There's one final step to go?
You mean we're not done yet?
-A type of sparring
sages perform
using Sage Jutsu chakra.
Now I shall teach you how to do
Frog Kumite to spar with frogs.
-You are so useless.
Why did you leave behind
my executioner's blade?
-Shut up, Suigetsu.
You should just be thankful
that we didn't leave you behind,
too!
-How dare you?
You know, you were knocked out
just as much as I was, Karin.
-I ended up that way trying
to protect all of you.
-All of us were protecting
each other, you guys.
We're like fish in water.
We can't do without one another.
So stop your quarreling.
-Yeah, all right.
Fine.
But anyway, are we really
going to get the Tailed Beast's
power now, Sasuke?
-Who knows?
Maybe.
But actually, we no longer
need to depend on such things.
-Why's that?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Because
I have obtained new powers.
Powers strong enough for me
to take down the Hidden Leaf
Village.
-Is something wrong, Sasuke?
-It's nothing at all.
-What is it, Karin?
-I sense a chakra outside.
It seems we were followed.
-Go now.
Please forgive me,
Lord Raikage, but it
appears my tail
was unsuccessful.
-Not only Yugito,
but now B, too.
I can't believe that
B has been taken down.
-We have received several
messenger lizards.
J's been sending them
to us frequently.
When we locate the enemy,
we'll send in four teams.
They'll get Lord Killer
B and wipe out the enemy.
-So, I heard it was an Uchiha.
One from the Hidden Leaf
who took my little brother.
Why is an Uchiha
in the Akatsuki?
-It was Sasuke Uchiha.
He went rogue from the Hidden
Leaf Village quite a while ago.
-And why isn't the
Hokage doing anything
about their rogue ninja?
They were quick to react
to the Hyuga incident.
-Something's going wrong.
The messages have ceased.
I don't like this.
-Well, Naruto boy,
let's call it a day.
-No.
Not yet.
-It's not you.
I'm the one that can't go on.
However, you are starting
to get the hang of it,
I'm glad to say.
-Yes, sir.
-What did you say?
What are you talking about?
The messages from J
have stopped coming in?
-It would seem that J has
either been killed or captured
by the enemy.
So now we won't be able
to locate their position.
-Figure out as much as
you can from the intel
he's already sent back.
And start combing the area.
Send the whole battalion,
if you have two.
-Yes-- yes, sir.
-And summon Samui's
platoon, as well.
They'll take a document
of intent to the Leaf,
saying that we'll take
care of Sasuke Uchiha.
And get their intel on him.
-Yes.
Right away, sir.
-Furthermore, I'll convene a
Five Kage Summit conference
with the five great nations.
The Akatsuki will
not be forgiven!
-Omio, Karui.
I've just received
word that Lord Raikage
has summoned all of us.
-Summoned, huh?
-What in the world could it be?
Maybe some kind of
crisis has occurred?
Or could it be we're
going to be reprimanded?
Does he know that my
body mass index spiked?
Hm.
Maybe putting mayonnaise
on my potatoes
wasn't such a good idea.
-Stop.
You always think too much, Omoi.
Why would he scold you
for something like that?
At most, you'd just be sent
out to buy protein drinks.
-Being around you
guys is really tiring.
Oh, my shoulders.
-Your shoulders
are probably sore
because of your
well endowed figure,
but there's a chance
it's something else.
What you thought were
still shoulders could be--
-Oh, just shut up!
Quit your yakking and
let's go, already.
-You really should think
things through more carefully.
Your shoulders aren't sore
'cause you're so flat.
-Shut up!
-Ow!
-You got something else to say?
-That kick's the just beginning.
It'll cause--
-You two.
If you're really ninja,
you should act like it.
Let's go.
-I did it.
I pulled it off.
Even though it's still
far from perfect,
I'm gonna have to
try it in Sage Mode.
And I have to make sure
that nobody catches me.
-It's J.
-We didn't make it in time.
-Yes, sir.
Mission acknowledged.
-I'm counting on you.
-I knew.
I knew this was bad news.
Man.
-Don't worry about it.
There's no way Lord Killer
B would mess up like that.
I bet it's just a bad
prank, or something.
-How can you be so optimistic?
He could be suffering
right at this moment.
Or even worse.
-Just shut up!
Don't want to hear any of
your pessimistic theories,
all right?
He's our master.
We're talking about Lord Killer
B. There's no way he'd lose.
-Aren't you worried about
Lord B at all, Karui?
-Being worried
doesn't mean I should
rush to crazy conclusions!
-Stop it, you two!
Listen.
We shall rescue
B, no matter what.
We will save him.
-Lord Raikage.
-Ha!
You have made great progress!
Impressive jumping ability.
Nice one, Naruto boy.
Your Frog Kumite is
going quite well, too.
-Yeah.
And that's not all I can do.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Eh?
-I'm not done!
I'm just getting started!
-Then come at me
with all you have.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: The sudden appearance
of six figures shocks
the Leaf Village.
Cries of fear, people
fleeing in panic.
Pillars of smoke arising
one after another.
Outclassed, the
Leaf's shinobi are
engulfed by the
spiral of suffering
set in motion by Pain.
And amidst the
merciless invasion,
Tsunade is convinced that
the fateful day has finally
arrived.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
Assault on the Leaf Village.
-Hey, everyone.
How are you all doing?
Today I brought Neji, who hasn't
been in the show much lately.
-What do you mean by that?
That's only because
I'm almost always away
on important missions.
-Let's see.
The last time you were here
was a month-- no, s months.
Wait, how long?
-I don't remember.
It's not something I
do just to be noticed.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, people sure did notice
Lee and Tenten last time.
-What?
Why, those two-- Hmph.
They have free time
on their hands,
unlike a Jonin such as me.
-Right.
'Cause it's so tough being you.
Ha ha ha.
-Damn you.
Hey, why don't you
come along with me
on my next mission, Naruto?
We'll call it The
Neji Chronicles,
and air it as a spectacular
one hour special.
-No way, ain't never
going to happen.
So everybody, please
continue to watch.
But only my
adventures, ya got it?
-That is just not right!
I object, I object, I object!
-Overruled!
[theme music]