I know how hard this
must be, Yugao.
Even so, you're the one best
suited for this mission. You
have to go.
But, Sukui...
It might seem cruel, I know...
But in order to reduce the
casualties on our side, we need
as much intel on our enemy as
possible.
It might even help
you save lives.
Now, go. I'm giving
you an order.
Mhmm.
You think she'll
be all right?
This is like
a nightmare...
It appears they've erased any
trace of their scent.
Bringing a Sensory-type was a
good move.
Yugao, can you locate the
targets?
They've detoured around the
battleground to the forest
ahead. They're at about two
o'clock.
If we go around, we could
confront them head on.
You've gotten better.
I know. Not bad, right?
I can win about half of our
bouts now.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's really more like one out of
three.
That's only because you can
use Transparency Style.
But just wait, I'll catch
up to you in no time.
You're gonna have to work
way harder to do that!
You're open!
Hmph.
Huh?
[Chuckles]
I lost.
You don't get off that easy.
But don't worry. I'll
always protect you.
All right then, before the
battle begins...
We should know more about
who we're up against.
He's Hayate Gekko, an expert in
the Hidden Leaf Sword Style and
the Transparency Jutsu.
He is highly skilled.
We'll want to avoid close
quarters combat.
We better hurry.
How boring! That was over too
fast! I wanted to do some more
damage!
Are you kidding me? I'm already
sick of being used like this!
Come on, we just got brought
back to life! We should be
enjoying ourselves, right?
To meet again like this...
But you could...
Hey, I'm talking to you. Are you
trying to ignore me, you
bastard?!
They're coming.
Hmph.
[Screams]
Oh! So this is what they mean
when they say we have bodies
that can't die. Well, that's
convenient!
Don't speak so soon!
[Laughing] A posse, huh?
This is more like it!
Still two left, I wish we could
have stopped at least one more
but...
[Chuckling] That other
reanimated guy didn't last
long...
But still, this is perfect! You
and I can share this prey,
fifty-fifty!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
We'll take that one.
All right!
Yugao, you've come...
Just stay back.
Sorry, but I'm the one
you're going up against!
Earth Style: Flying Stones!
Huh!
Now you're mine!
[Sigh]
[Grunts]
Please! Just keep your
distance from me!
If you want me to do that, then
return the scroll you took!
No way! [Grunts]
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Iou!
Pay attention!
[Grunts]
And now I'll take
care of you!
I'm so sorry.
I'm an enemy of the Leaf. And
I'm an enemy of yours, as well.
And that's why I want you to
stop me.
I don't want to hurt you!
So, please!
[Grunts]
Yugao! Take this!
Huh! [Gasp]
Please, Yugao stop me!
[Gasp]
I can't do it!
[Groaning] I just can't.
If you don't...
Yugao!
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Back off!
[Screams]
[Chuckles] Is that
seriously all you got?
[Grunts]
[Sigh]
It's just down to you now!
I have to go.
Wait! Damn it!
[Gasps]
Iou!
[Grunting]
[Wincing In Pain]
This is...
This'll hurt a bit. I'll close
the wound.
In his condition, Iou won't be
able to continue the pursuit.
You're in no condition to
continue, either.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
It's not.
But what you said before,
is it true? That you...
That you can't fight?
I apologize.
I always wanted to be an ANBU
Black Ops, so when I heard you'd
left them, I lost my head.
Huh?
I'm going to get water.
Please, don't go.
Hayate's course
hasn't changed.
You'll catch him, even if
I'm not here to help.
If I stay there's still
nothing I can do.
Why exactly did you leave the
ANBU Black Ops, anyway?
Hayate was the love of my life.
And at the time, years ago, we
were both studying the Leaf
Sword Style.
As training partners, we honed
our skills together.
There!
Quite impressive.
The Hokage himself certified my
Transparency Style.
My Sensory skills and my
swordsmanship are why I was
chosen to be ANBU.
But you still need some work.
I'm almost there!
[Gasp]
Hayate?
I should be happy that your
strength was acknowledged.
But real missions are
extremely dangerous...
...far riskier than mere
training sessions like this.
Please...be careful.
ANBU Black Ops were killed in
this hospital?!
Hayate, I'm okay. But...
Huh.
The culprit was Kabuto Yakushi.
It seems that he was actually
Orochimaru's spy.
You mean the one who was taking
part in the Chunin Exam?
He had us all fooled.
It appears that their goal was
to go after Sasuke, but that
alone doesn't explain all their
actions.
There is no doubt in my mind
that they're up to no good.
Our path is clear, we must learn
more about whatever plans
they've now put into motion.
It's way too dangerous.
I mean, he held his
own against Kakashi!
But still someone
has to do it.
And with my Tracking Jutsu,
I'm the ideal choice.
Yes, but...
I have to go.
[Sigh]
[Crowing]
We've learned that Hayate Gekko
has been killed.
[Shocked Murmurs]
No...
Not Hayate...
Earlier, his remains were found
on the rooftop of Kikyo Castle.
Thats...
[Sobbing]
The attack on the Leaf Village
happened a month later.
Hayate...I am going to
avenge you!
It was my way of avenging
Hayate. So I fought, and I
fought...
But when the fighting ended, my
emotions, already stretched
thin, just snapped.
I wasn't even able to hold a
sword anymore.
Hayate and I shared a
connection through our swords.
So now, because of that, it
inevitably reminds me of his
death.
But Yugao...
How can I?
How can I kill him and relive
his death once more?
I'm sorry. But I still can't let
you go. Especially not when we
have wounded to care for.
Hmm.
We need your help, Yugao. And I
do understand, you see...
...I couldn't fight the one that
I used to love, either.
Now, please!
I leave it to you.
Sakura...
Kakashi Sensei once said, this
jutsu's unforgivable.
It tramples on a person's death,
our memories of them...
I feel the same way!
Don't you have to go?
Yokaze...
Sorry I was rude to you earlier.
But about this Hayate person, it
seemed to me that he really
wanted you to stop him.
[Heavy Breathing]
What's the matter?
Just call for me, and
I'll come running!
However tough things are, if you
need me, I promise I'll save
you!
Then let us make a vow, with the
moon as our witness.
I'll swear an oath to you,
and you to me.
We'll love and protect each
other above all else.
Stop him, we'll be fine. Backup
will arrive soon.
Hmph!
[Heavy Breathing]
Hayate Gekko! You must stop.
Wait, I know you...Sakura
Haruno.
It seems you've grown up to
become a fine shinobi.
Please, I don't want to have to
kill you.
I can't let you go. I have to
get that stolen scroll back from
you.
Hmph!
I'm not gonna waste any time
talking.
It's over!
[Grunt]
Ahh!
Right there!
Where did he go?
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Please! Run!
It's Yugao...
Huh?
Hmph.
[Gasp]
I'm here now.
I'm sorry I took so long.
I thank you.
I'll back you up!
No. Just go and get
the Sealing Corps.
Even a lethal blow won't truly
stop him.
Hmph.
Okay.
Crescent Moon Dance!
[Grunt]
[Grunts]
[Both Grunting]
Hmph.
Please, Yugao...
Hayate...
Moonlit Night!
Secret Sword, Tsukikage!
[Grunts]
[Groaning] Like I said all those
years ago, you've gotten better.
I wish it weren't for this,
though...
And I also wish...
...we'd never made that
promise!
You're wrong about that, Yugao.
I had wondered what could be
taking you so long out there.
Come on, hurry up and do your
work already, would you?!
[Groaning]
I'm being called, he's taking my
consciousness away now!
[Groaning]
Huh!
[Grunts]
Hayate...
This is pitiful but, it's
the best I could do.
Yugao!
So Yugao, goodbye...
[Sighs]
But, the moon always
changes shape.
So a promise made on it is
bound to get distorted.
All that changes is our
perception of the moon.
Whatever its shape or name, the
moon itself remains the same.
That will never change.
Yokaze and the others
have all been rescued.
Oh. That's good.
Yugao, I...
You know in the end, he
protected me.
Thank you, Hayate.
And also...goodbye.
Who is he?
He's a reanimated samurai, and
he's really strong!
Samurai?
Get back, shinobi!
Old man? Don't tell me you're
Old Man Tatewaki?
Naruto?! So you're still alive,
are you?
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The A-Rank Mission: Food
Fight!"
Please tell me what
happened to those two!