If only I knew where
their souls were now,
I'd be able to save
Neji and the others...
[Shino Collapsing]
[gasp]
Shino! No!
[grunts in pain]
Shino! Are
you okay!?
...please, stop!
You're a true asset to
our military strength!
...we can't afford
to lose you!
Shino, please
listen to reason!
I will not give
up, Hinata.
But, Shino, you...
We're just one step from
saving Neji and Kiba...
I cannot stop.
The reason is because if
I do before we can even
reach them, the flame of
hope will be extinguished!
We can't give up!
If the only was to save them
is to find out where they are,
then we'll keep searching
for them until we do...
I won't quit...
[small gasp]
Shikaku, are you there?
Are Shikamaru and the
others still okay?
A little while ago,
I suddenly stopped
sensing their chakra!
If there's anything
I can do, tell me!
(Naruto)
Hey! Say
something!
Shikaku...
Hmm.
All right. Connect
me to Naruto.
(Shikaku)
Naruto, can
you hear me?
(Naruto)
Shikaku, what's
going on!?
What happened to
Shikamaru and the
others!?
(Telepathically)
We're not entirely
sure, but we know the
jutsu the enemy used.
It's called the
Underworld Transfer
Jutsu...
(Shikaku)
It extracts the soul
from a victim and places
it into a special barrier.
Seriously!? It
extracts their soul?
Yeah, but... they're all
still alive, aren't they?
We can just track down
their souls and save them!
We can just track
down their souls
and save them!
Unfortunately,
that's impossible.
There's no shinobi
with the ability
to locate souls.
So, what do you
need me to do?
Right now, Naruto, you're
the only shinobi who can
mitigate the chaos within
the Allied Shinobi Forces.
You may have immense
reserves of chakra, but
there's no way you can
cover every battlefield.
Even as it is,
you're stretching
yourself too thin.
We've now reached
a critical point:
The Allied Forces can't
spare a vital asset like
you, not for just four
shinobi.
What!? Don't
be an idiot!
They're not just
shinobi! I mean,
Shikamaru is your
own son!
And that's not all! I
heard Shino and Ino are
desperately trying to
save them--!
(Naruto)
How can you turn your
back on all of them!?
As our chief strategist,
I must coordinate every
one's actions.
I cannot allow
people to go off
on their own.
Your duty right now
is to identify the
enemy by sensing
their malice.
You must focus on
doing your very
best in that role.
Come on! Give
me a break!
(Inoichi)
Naruto!
[gasp]
Shikaku's right.
You must put all
your efforts into
your mission.
Got it!?
Roger that!
I'm on it!
Hm.
[laugh] Give it up!
LIke I said earlier,
we're immortal...
(Tayuya)
And even if you losers could
defeat us, it still wouldn't
make this barrier come down!
Ha! Face it! There's
nothing you can do!
Huh?
Hm.
Heh.
What an idiot!
You're wide open!
Eight Trigrams!
Air Palm!
[grunt]
[♪ flute music]
Fang Over Fang!
[gasp]
Huh?
[♪ flute music]
That's it! Eat up all
his chakra so that he
can never get back on
his feet!
Ahh!
Now, Sakon!
Shadow Pull Jutsu!
Ahhh!
That fool! What
is he doing!?
Yes! It worked!
That gate is enormous.
So I wondered what would
happen if its foundation
were weakened...
I was right!
Why you jerk! You
tricked us into
attacking that spot!
That's what you were
after all along!
Damn! You bastards!
"We're trapped," "We have
no hope of escape?" You really
think anything like that
would make us give up?
Don't underestimate
us, you piece of crap!
Actually, you're the ones
who are underestimating us!
I could've sworn that
you were stronger the
last time we faced off.
Well then, you think that
means all of us have improved
but you guys stayed the same?
(Kiba)
Sounds right to me!
(Akamaru)
[bark]
I'm gonna shut that
big mouth of yours!
Listen, Shikamaru...
Does it really seem
wise to rile them up
like this?
You know, come to think of it.
You & all the other reanimations
were called back to become tools
of war, weren't you..?
(Shikamaru)
So what's with your ridiculous
obsession about getting revenge?
And why are you directing
it all at us, anyway?
Didn't the Sang
Siblings kill some
of you, too?
What? We're "tools of
war?" Is that what you
called us? [laugh]
Huh?!
(Jirobo)
[derisive laughter]
You ignorant fool!
We have nothing to
do whatsoever with
this war!
Our reanimation is
simply because of
our loyalty to Lord
Orochimaru!
He made us a promise
long ago, and this is
the result of that!
[fighting]
Yes. That's it.
Kill each other off.
And if you're not taking
this battle seriously, then
I'll just kill you myself!
[panting breaths]
(Orochimaru)
The feeling that's born
when one transcends the
dear of death...
Yes, that's it.
That's what I
wanted to bring
out in you...
Just look at those
fine eyes of yours...
(Orochimaru)
Now I shall bestow upon
you even greater power...
And you shall carry
out my bidding... as
my favored ones...
(Jirobo / Tayuya
Sakon / Kidomaru)
Ninja Art! Four Flames
Formation!
(Sakon)
Standing at Lord
Orochimaru's side, we've
been witness to many jutsu...
But the ultimate is...
The Reanimation Jutsu!
(struggling breaths)
That old geezer...
How dare he!?
[labored breaths]
What? Do you have
something to say?
No...
In the condition I'm
in now, you four might
be able to kill me.
This is your chance
if you dare to try...
Well, it seems that as long
as the Curse Mark binds you,
you cannot bring yourself to
raise your blade against me.
Although the attempt
failed, you did make
yourselves useful in the
attack on the Hidden Leaf.
For that, I shall
reward you...
What do you
wish for...?
There is only one
thing, Lord Orochimaru.
Power. Power as
a shinobi...
...We wish for nothing
more than that...
So it shall be. That's
quite impressive, all
of you...
I commend you
on your choice.
Kabuto, be sure to
add each of them
to the sample.
I understand, sir.
To access the next level
of power within you, you
need a vengeful heart.
...possessing an extreme
desire for revenge will
rapidly increase the power
of the Curse Mark...
What's the connection
between that and the
Reanimation Jutsu?
The emotions your four
learned from overcoming
the dear of death at
that laboratory...
...are resentment and
hatred towards me...
No, an even stronger
feeling...
I'm sure you swore to
get back at me one day,
even if you were killed
in the process...
That emotion... When you
can hate someone as
strongly as that...
Once you're actually
killed... you take it
with you...
...that hatred towards
the one who put you to
death...
You die thinking that if
you could be resurrected,
it would be to only seek
revenge...
Yes... through the
Reanimation Jutsu, you
will return as ones
seeking vengeance.
You will attain power
unlike anything you've
ever had before...
The source of your
newfound strength will
be your consuming desire
for vengeance...
Embrace that power!
Take pleasure in it!
Revel in its might!
Today, just as in the
past, we belong to
Lord Orochimaru!
[gasps]
We are Lord Orochimaru's
very own seekers of vengeance!
The intense hatred and
resentment that we harbor
towards you allows us to release
the full depths of our power!
The way it stands now,
no one can stop us!
Don't you even dare to think
of lumping us in with all
those other damn reanimations
you big piece of trash!
Th- thats...
What? They were seriously
reanimated only to get
revenge against us?
They're all
insane.
If what they said is
true, then they're only
starting to get serious.
Hm.
Ahhhh!
[groans]
(Jirobo)
It's too soon...
Huh?
You can't quit on
me this early!!
[screams]
Fool! Against my improved
Gum Style Spider Thread,
your Gentle Fist is nothing!
[gasp]
[evil laugh] Besides!
I've always been better
at grappling than
shooting, anyway!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
Did we get him?
Yeah, right! You've
gotta be joking!
Like that amount of
power would do any
thing to us!
Now, it's our turn!
[gasp]
[pleased laughter]
The power of this
Curse Mark is amazing!
With this, super
fast cell fusion
and cell division
is now possible!
[gasp]
So being bound by
shadows, means stuff
like this is possible?
Argh!
[grunt]
You guys are too
weak, you pieces
of trash!!
Gimme a sec, I'll
prove you wrong!
They've progressed to
a superhuman level!
(Shikamaru)
[laughs]
Hm?
All right, then.
Did you get it out
of your system?
Don't act so smug.
The only reason you're
still here is that we've
been going easy on you!
But I'm only barely
holding back my urge
to kill you!
Oh yeah? You know
what, about that...
Let me go. Come on.
Let me outta here.
Boy, you've got some
big balls, I'll give
you that!
My hatred just grew
a hundred times!
[♪ flute music]
[grunt] So you really
hate me that much, do you?
(Tayuya)
Yeah, I do!
Why do you insist
on provoking her
so much?
(Shikamaru)
Choji...
Huh?
Do you remember what we
talked about shortly before
all of us got brought to
this place?
[gasp]
Fortunately for us, HQ
has a strategy for
identifying the fakes.
What? They already
came up with a plan?
I do. At least, I
think. What about it?
(Shikamaru)
HQ's strategy is to
utilize Naruto's power!
[gasps]
It seems the sensory power
that Naruto now possesses
allows him to sense evil.
Not many people know
about it, but if they
don't, they will soon.
Because right now, Naruto
is heading to every one of
the battlefields with his
Shadow Clones.
[grunt]
Shikamaru!
What are you
rambling on about?
[grunt] Sorry, guys.
But this time, I'm really
only going on intuition.
I bet it'll happen
soon, though.
Huh?
(Shikamaru)
This is the third reason
why we don't need to
fight these guys directly.
Because knowing him,
he's definitely going
to find this place!
That's what I've
been betting on.
[nervous gasps]
Ahhh!
[grunt]
Inoichi! You
were right!
I went towards a pitch-
black aura of evil, and
I found a giant barrier!
Leave the rest
to us, Naruto.
As long as we know where
Shikamaru and the others
are, we can save them.
Right, Shikaku?
(Shikaku)
I leave it up to you...
All right! Got it!
(Neji)
I see. You kept provoking
them to make it possible for
him to sense their malice.
(Kiba)
You had faith that Naruto
would get what's going on!
(Choji)
Yeah!
There's no doubt
about it, you guys
are really strong...
...But you made the
same mistake as you
did the last time.
Just like when we faced
you before, we aren't
fighting alone, now.
Back then, we had comrades
who rescued us when we were
backed into a corner.
And now that we're in
another one, we have
faith that they'll come
to help us once more!
We know that as long
as we stand firm,
there's always hope.
That's the bond that
exists between true
comrades, and that's
what defeated you guys!
The last fight, and
this one as well.
Yeah? Well we
haven't lost yet!
But you are about to!
You won't be able to
break or counter this
power! It's impossible!
Shikamaru!
Yeah!
That's good!
We're connected!
Release!
[gasp]
Wait! You're--
(Kidomaru)
That brat from
last time!
(Sakon)
No way! He tore apart
the barrier from the
outside!?
(Ukon)
This is bad, Sakon!
If the barrier's broken,
our souls will..
So what!? Before that
we can at least get our
revenge on this guy!
[attack cries]
Nothing worthwhile is
ever born out of vengeance!
(Sakon)
No! Our... souls...!
The influence of the
Curse Mark on the dead's
desire for revenge...
Well, at least the
data I collected about
that was worth it.
I think that pretty soon
I'll be able to send him
out onto the battlefield...
And when that happens, all
of these "opening acts"
will be inconsequential...
[happy sobbing]
This time, I was able to
use the enemy's malice to
our advantage...
But the malice of war is
spreading like wildfire.
I have to put an
end to this, quickly!
(Hinata)
Are you doing all
right now, Neji?
(Neji)
My eyes have recovered a
lot, but I still have some
blind spots...
(Hinata)
Then rest assured, until
your eyes have healed, I'll
be sure to protect you!
(Hinata)
...just as you
protected me back
then...
(Neji)
When I protected you?
(Hinata)
It was when Sasuke
was still in the village.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Heart's Eye."
(Hinata)
I've always wanted to
tell you this... to say...