[wind gusting]
[wings flapping]
[owl hooting]
[crashing]
ALL: Augh!
Nngh!
Aah!
Whaa!
[slashing]
[wind slicing]
[cracking]
[labored breathing]
[blasting]
[roaring]
-Hueh!
[panting] [sighing] A dream.
Man.
[footsteps]
[door opening]
[sighs]
[breeze blowing]
-What was that about?
Crazy.
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
-In order to be more quickly
understood by others,
one must first draw them in
and warm them to oneself.
For example, when
addressing others,
if you persist in
maintaining formality,
a reserved air develops
and never allows
the gap to be bridged.
Have confidence.
Just take the plunge and
call out to people casually.
Or you could come
up with a nickname
or a term of endearment.
By doing so, those you speak
to will feel closer to you
and begin to see you
as more of a friend.
That make sense.
-Ah, here it is.
-Hmm?
(TO HERSELF): What's
Sai doing here?
-For more information
consult Make-Out Paradise--
-Looking for an art
book or something?
-Huh?
Miss Sakura.
-Hmph.
I never pegged you as a reader.
-Well, I guess I am.
-(TO HERSELF): Hmph.
So Sai does have a
human side, after all.
Naruto and I were on our
way to visit Kakashi-sensei
in the same hospital.
If you're free, you wanna come?
-Kakashi-sensei?
-Well, I mean, you are
part Team Kakashi now.
Don't you think you
should meet the leader?
-I don't care what happens.
Only one thing matters, and
that's getting my revenge.
So long as I get that
nothing else in this world
is important.
However, if I can
obtain the power
to defeat Itachi by giving
myself to Orochimari,
I'll give him my life
a thousand times over.
I can see everything.
So this is where all
that power's coming from.
Interesting.
I never would have guessed
you had this inside of you.
[squish]
[bursting]
[roaring]
--[gasping] Why did
I have that dream?
-Naruto!
-What?
Aw, what's the deal?
Why'd you bring Sai with you.
--[chuckling] I bumped
into him at the library.
-Aw, man!
I spent all this
time working it out
so it would just be the
two of us alone together.
You know, like a date.
-If you've got time to
daydream about that,
you should be studying ninjutsu.
-Yeah, like I'd study.
I can't believe you two hang
out in that stuffy old library.
-Naruto, you can't just
train your body all the time.
Your mind needs to get
some exercise, too.
Ugh.
Sometimes you're such a dummy.
-(TO HIMSELF): I knew it.
Sakura is calling
Naruto by a nickname.
-So harsh.
Man, you really got me there.
-Na-- Naruto?
Sa-- Sakura?
Do you do you mind if I
join your conversation?
-Hmm?
-Well, I read in
a book about how
to make others feel
at ease around you.
The book said to call
out to people casually
or to use nicknames and
terms of endearment.
It said doing that
would breed familiarity
and might even
lead to friendship.
-Hey.
Gee, Sai.
I never knew you thought
about stuff like that.
-So that's what you were
doing at the library.
-Mmm.
I've been trying to come up
with some nicknames for the two
of you, but I just couldn't
really think of any.
So I'll try to be more casual.
-(TO HERSELF): Wow.
I can't believe Sai cares so
much about our friendship.
-Listen, you don't need to
put so much thought into it.
Just let that stuff
come naturally.
-A lot of times, a
nickname or pet name
will refer to someone's
personality traits.
Let's take Naruto for example.
-Hmm?
-You could go with Dimwit,
Bird Brain, or Stupid Naruto.
-Enough, Sakura.
Come on, you're killing me here.
-(TO HIMSELF): I see.
Personality traits.
-Hmm.
(TO HERSELF) This is Sai?
He's so different from
when we first met him.
-Uh, Sai?
Why are you staring
at me like that?
-Ah!
I understand.
Thanks for the advice, Ugly.
NARUTO: Aw, boy.
SAKURA: Let me at him!
NARUTO: You might have crossed
the line with that one.
SAKURA: Who you calling ugly?
Why you little--
SAI: What do you mean?
NARUTO: Aah!
SAI: Nngh.
Sakura!
NARUTO: Why'd you hit me, too?
-So, you're the new team member.
Sai, was it?
Nice to meet you.
-Sir.
-Hey, Sakura.
Come here a second.
-Hmm?
-Those two seem hurt.
Did they fight or something?
Knowing Naruto's
temper, I can imagine
what must have gone down.
--[gasping] No, it's
nothing like that.
We're all getting
along just dandy.
-Oh.
OK.
Well, if you say so.
[nervous laughing]
-(TO HIMSELF): So this
is Kakashi Hatake.
Legendary even to those
in the foundation.
-Naruto?
-Hmm.
Kakashi-sensei, on
our last mission, we--
-I know.
Yamato told me everything.
About Sasuke, too.
-We're running out of
time to get him home.
At this rate, we-- we
could lose him for good.
But with my power
there's just no way.
I wouldn't be able to
bring him back now.
Sasuke has gotten way
too strong for me.
-Well, in that
case, I guess you're
gonna need to get even
stronger than that.
[gasps]
-Yeah, but, the way he's grown--
Sasuke has developed so fast.
His growth isn't natural.
I spoke with Lady Tsunade.
She thinks they might be
using forbidden jutsu or even
drug enhancement.
After all, they do
have Kabuto with them.
No book in the world could
explain the kind of person
who performs experiments
on human beings.
-Which is why the
only thing we can do
was accelerate our own growth.
-But how can we do that?
-Do you think I've
just been lying here,
doing nothing the whole time?
I've been brainstorming
and I have an idea.
[gasps]
-However, what I came up with
is more suited to Naruto.
-Huh?
-Or rather, I should
say it's something
that will only work with Naruto.
In fact, if this
training pans out Naruto,
your power may
even surpass mine.
-Hold on.
I'd surpass you, Kakashi-sensei?
-That's right.
I'll be working with you
one on one the whole time
and it'll be training
like you've never
experienced before.
-Um.
What're we gonna be working on?
-We're going to create an
ultimate ninjutsu just for you.
[gasps]
-A brand new jutsu, even more
powerful than the Rasengan.
But in order to obtain
that kind of power,
you'll have to put in an
enormous amount of time
and intense effort.
You can't get that kind of
strength in a couple days
like the hero of
some pulp novel.
And it won't be like
learning a preexisting
jutsu like the Rasengan that
can be broken down and taught
in stages.
-An enormous amount of time?
Are you people listening to me?
I just said we're
almost out of time!
Sasuke's gonna--
-If you'd let me finish.
I figured out a way
to do it faster.
-How?
-Well--
[door sliding]
ASUMA: How you feeling
today, Kakashi?
-Asuma-sensei, you really should
try knocking first, you know.
CHOJI: What's up, guys?
-Look who's here.
It's Naruto and Sakura.
Guess your mission
must be-- hmm?
I know you.
You're that guy
from-- [growling]
-Doh!
-Huh?
What guy?
-(TO HIMSELF): Why is
all this happening today?
Relax.
Remember, start with a smile.
Hello there.
-Thank you for your report.
-Of course.
I'll head out now.
[poof]
-It sounds like the
Akatsuki are really
starting to make
their move, my lady.
Which means it's
only a matter of time
before they venture closer
to this area, maybe even
assault the Leaf Village.
-True.
This is a dangerous development.
But it could also be our
chance to smash them.
We've got no time left to lose.
-Oh, I see.
So that's what
that was all about.
I guess I guy that. [munching]
-My name is Sai.
You can feel free to be casual.
-Hey, that new guy's pretty
cute, don't you think?
He even kind of
looks like Sasuke.
-On the outside, maybe.
But inside?
No way.
He can't read people's emotions.
[chomping]
-Lady Tsunade told me
what happened with Sasuke.
Next time something
like that comes up,
I'll be around to help.
Especially now that I'm
done with the chunin exams.
Oh yeah, you missed out on
becoming a chunin again, huh?
-That's right.
-Well, I guess that's the
least of your problems.
-Why'd you bring the whole
gang in here, of all places?
This isn't a rec room, you know?
-You have a point.
Why don't you guys head on over
to the barbecue restaurant.
And Team Kakashi, you're
more than welcome to join us
if you'd like to.
-Barbecue!
Woohoo!
-I second that.
(TO HERSELF) [giggling]
And I'll sit next to Sai.
-I need to talk to Kakashi
alone about some business.
In the meantime, the
barbecue's on me, OK?
-Hmm?
-Hey, wait a sec.
Sensei, what gives?
What happened to that
whole conversation
we were just having about
my special training?
-Oh, that's right.
Hmm.
We'll get back to it later.
-Eh?
What?
Later?
But it was getting good.
-Well, we can't start
anything while I'm still
in the hospital.
Don't be so impatient, Naruto.
[growls]
-What took you so long, Sakura?
-What?
Where's Shikamaru?
-Oh, he said he had to go
home and help his father find
antlers to use as
some kind of medicine.
-Huh?
That's weird.
He always showed up to celebrate
successful missions with us
before.
This is a first.
SAKURA (TO HERSELF): She's
ignoring what I told her.
CHOJI: All right!
Then I get Shikamaru's share.
INO: Knock it off, Choji!
-Eek!
INO: We should be
polite and introduce
ourselves to Sai before we eat.
-Oh yeah.
Of course.
-Word is, things
are really starting
to heat up outside the village.
-I figured.
As long as their objectives
are the tailed beasts,
we can be certain they'll
come here sooner or later.
They want Naruto.
[door sliding open]
-Hmm?
-You guys don't need to
leave me out of this.
I'm just as concerned about
the Akatsuki as you are.
And Naruto-- is
he going to be OK?
What if those guys from
the Akatsuki attack?
Even Gaara couldn't--
-You're right.
He wouldn't be able to do it.
[gasping]
-Well, not yet.
-Mmm. [giggling]
-Well, then.
(TO HIMSELF) First impressions
are very important to people,
so I've got to come up
with some casual nicknames
as fast as I can.
-So, uh, hi there.
I'm Choji Akimichi
of the Akimichi Clan.
And uh, your name
is Sai, isn't it?
-That's right, you
uh-- (TO HIMSELF)
personality trait,
personality trait.
[gasps]
-(TO HERSELF): On no!
-(TO HIMSELF): He's not gonna
say that forbidden word, is he?
-Fat--
--Hmm?
-Eek!
[slap]
-Sai, fatso is absolutely a
taboo word in front of Choji.
Ya got it?
-Mmhmm.
-Hey, where you about
to say something?
--[giggling nervously]
No, it was nothing.
Forget it.
-OK.
[sighs]
-(TO HIMSELF): Coming up
with nicknames is tough.
-Anyway, I'm Ino Yamanaka.
My family owns the
Yamanaka flower shop next.
Nice to meet you.
-Heeyah.
SAKURA: Let me at him!
SAI (TO HIMSELF): When
it comes to women,
stating their personality traits
too bluntly might anger them.
So perhaps I can
avoid that if I just
say the opposite
of what I think.
SAKURA (TO HERSELF):
Don't say it, Sai.
DARK SAKURA: Come on, say it!
Let her have it good,
just like you did to me!
-A pleasure, you uh,
you um, beautiful.
[sighing]
--[growling] You
call her beautiful?
Why, you-- haiyah!
[plates breaking]
NARUTO: Aah, take
it easy, Sakura!
[twhogg]
[thud]
[footsteps]
[chanting in japanese]
[crashing]
-Keh.
It's the wrong one.
[theme music]
-OK, time for some training.
[giggles]
-What is it?
-Well, it's been pretty
long since the last time
I trained with you.
I don't really know why, but I'm
psyched to be back in action.
-I see.
[giggling]
-Well, you better laugh
it up while you can.
-Hmm?
-The purpose of this training
is to create a new ultimate need
ninjutsu just for you, one
that will surpass the Rasengan.
-No way.
Surpass the Rasengan?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time, "Wind."
[theme music]