You're saying the Fourth
Great Ninja War is about
to start?
Even though we're talking
about Madara Uchiha.
Can he really take on the
Five Great Nations?
You need to wake up and
face the facts! Madara
Uchiha leads the
Akatsuki!
Just one of them was able
to destroy the Leaf
Village!
Have you already
forgotten that?!
I agree with Lady
Tsunade. The Akatsuki
already have the other
Tailed Beasts, from
One-Tail to Seven-Tails.
If they intend to use
them as military weapons,
we must consider their
strength to be far
greater than even
Nagato's.
And if that's the case,
the Five Great Nations--
no! The entire world is in
danger of destruction!
We cannot delay action!
Very well... But where
should we strike? Do you
know where Madara is?
We do have a general idea
of the location.
The Mitarashi Unit
recently reported in, and
they've confirmed spotting
someone who fits.
the description of Madara
Uchiha.
What? They have...?!
Right now they're working
to gather more conclusive
intel.
Nah, it doesn't rhyme.
What a crime. There must
be some phrase that'll
earn some praise.
Without knowing the
enemy's precise
location...
The success of a surprise
attack is doubtful, so
first we must organize
scouting parties.
Know you... to maximize
their efforts, we'll need--
"Know you..." Eh. No
originality.
But switch around the
words... you get "you
know."
Then all you got to do is
add a little nuance...
and make it... "You know
it!"
You know it, you know it,
now come on and show it.
Now I have a pretty clear
picture of the Hidden
Cloud's military
strength...
Luckily, the Eight
Tails is a fool.
Nah, this phrase just
seems... to rub me the
wrong way. Ya know?
No, it's not working.
Right now, we have very
little intel on the enemy.
So we must rely on the other
four villages.
Are you serious? We're
just supposed to sit here,
empty-handed and depend
on them?
I mean, are they even
gonna share their data
with us?
If they won't divulge it
to us, then the Allied
Shinobi Force is
absolutely meaningless.
We're just gonna have
to trust them.
We don't have any more
time to waste now.
Because out there, right
at this very moment...
Madara Uchiha is
preparing for battle.
All right!
I'll have the Allied
Shinobi Force meet here
in three days! Send a
summons to each village!
Very soon, I'll announce
to the entire village the
coming Fourth Great Ninja
War.
The Fourth Great
Ninja War?
You haven't heard this
yet, Sakura... But Madara
Uchiha has declared war.
This time, the Five Great
Nations aren't battling
each other but have
joined forces for a
conflict unlike any seen
before.
Then who-?
We face the Akatsuki.
The Akatsuki! We're
really going to battle
Sasuke.
When the fighting breaks
out, many will wrestle
with doubt and with fear.
It will be your job to
keep a close watch on
their mental state.
Circulate among the teams
and report anything
unusual. Do not hide
anything, understood?
Yes, m'lady.
And one other thing: make
sure you keep an eye on
Naruto.
I cannot have him acting
recklessly. In this war,
Naruto is the Akatsuki's
goal.
Hmm? Yes,
Shizune?
Lady Tsunade, Naruto
suddenly disappeared from
Ichiraku Ramen just now.
What?!
Wait. You don't think
the enemy could've--
It's impossible for
Naruto to be kidnapped
from this village! I
want him found right now!
"The Five Kage's
Decision"
See ya, Giant Gramps
Sage!
All right, off you go!
[gasping]
Huh?! Oh, I'm back
home.
Where'd you go?! First
you disappear and then
you just reappear again!
[chuckling]
Stuff to do...
Wow! Naruto!
Huh?
Man, they said you
were gone and everyone
nearly went out of
their minds!
They did? Seriously?
Yeah! Wow, I never
thought I'd run into
you, here!
Oh, that's right! Can I
get your autograph?
And could you make it out
to my kid, please? He's a
real big fan!
Autograph...?
You're the hero of the
Hidden Leaf! Naruto, the
kid who makes miracles!
Can I please have
your autograph, too?
What? Can't you do it?
No, it's not that; I'm
just not used to this
celebrity thing...
I've never given
an autograph before.
Everyone's making a
fuss over him lately as
the miracle kid. What an
about-face from not long
ago. Can't blame him for
feeling the way he does.
Listen, guys, just let
him eat his ramen before
he signs anything, okay?
Oh! Sure!
Bring it on!
I finally get
to eat real food!
Naruto!
Hey, Sakura,
what's up?
[panting]
We've been looking
everywhere for you!
Oh, well, I got summoned
suddenly and I-
Look, just come with me!
Lady Tsunade and everyone
else are worried sick
about you!
Aw, come on, Sakura! Let
me eat my ramen!
That can wait!
You saw the Great Lord
Elder?
Yeah, he used a Reverse
Summoning Jutsu.
And we went through all
that trouble...
Lord Fukasaku could have
at least let me know
beforehand.
Yes, but still... it's a
relief you're okay,
Naruto.
Hey, I'm more than okay!
I'm doing great!
I'm glad. But why did the
Great Lord Elder summon
you?
Giant Gramps Sage had
something he wanted to
tell me, a prophecy he
had.
Like the one that he
foretold to Jiraiya?
So what did the Great
Lord Elder have to say
to you?
Uhh-- Well,
I--
What is it?
Well, I'm gonna go
to some cool resort
and meet an octopus
there!
Huh!? You're
gonna what?!
Uh...
And what's that supposed
to mean, exactly...?
Well, uh this octopus is
supposed to cooperate
with me somehow...
Giant Gramps Sage didn't
know all the details
either. And...
He said that I'm gonna
end up fighting Sasuke.
Fight Sasuke?
But I'm ready now. I've
already prepared for it.
But, Naruto...
It's all right.
Don't worry.
Let me handle Sasuke.
This is my task.
It sure is quiet.
Yeah, I'll say.
So peaceful.
What? No, it's not! Not
at all!
Uh?
Sure, the Village is
being rebuilt after
Pain's attack,
and Lady Tsunade's
come out of her coma...
But as for Sasuke,...
there's only talk that
Naruto is gonna do
something.
And there's gonna be a
full-out war, isn't
there?
What?! How'd you know
that?!
I'm not stupid, you know.
I can tell by watching
the jonin prepare.
Hm.
I guess so.
[grunting]
It's true. War is
right at our doorstep.
[sighing]
I kinda figured.
Yeah. This fight is
something-
I mean, this is something
unlike any other shinobi
has ever experienced
before.
Just imagine, to crush
the Akatsuki, the Five
Great Nations are joining
forces for the first time.
It's the start of the
Fourth Great Ninja War.
The Fourth Great
Ninja War...
Man, aren't you
scared, Shikamaru?
Yeah. You'd better
believe I am.
Huh?
But this time, it doesn't
matter how scared we are
or how hard it'll be.
Our enemy, the Akatsuki,
is made up of members so
skilled that it took just
one of them to destroy
the Hidden Leaf Village.
And the abilities of
their leader, Madara, are
completely shrouded in
mystery.
And even worse than that,
he has Seven Tailed Beasts.
If he unleashes all of
them at once, who knows
if even the Five Great
Nations together can win.
Now, the entire ninja
world is at stake.
So each and every shinobi
will have to do their
absolute best or we'll
have no chance to win.
Choji, I'm counting on
your strength, big time!
Uhhh...
Shikamaru, I hope
I can do my best.
Man... it's hard to take
this all in...
[gagging]
Are you okay...? You
wanted to know what to
expect from war.
Yes. I'm fine.
But nothing can prepare
you for the real
battlefield.
The wounded's cries, the
smell of blood.
It's almost impossible
not to be affected by
it all.
But regardless, a Medical
Ninja must maintain their
composure, no matter what
happens.
Everyone fights hard,
counting on us to be
there to save their lives
if need be.
Yes, I know...
That's why I wanted to--
To know, I guess.
Heh! All right. I guess that
I'm done nagging you for
now, Sasuke!
Damn it, this is
ridiculous! I'm not any
good with words; I shouldn't
try to lecture you.
[chuckling]
Well, I guess if the
worst does happen and
both of us end up
dying...
You won't be an Uchiha
and I won't be the
Nine-Tail's Jinchuriki
anymore.
We'll be free of our
burdens.
And we'll understand each
other in the afterlife!
Naruto. You--
If both Naruto and Sasuke
get seriously wounded...
Who will I save first...?
Found ya!
Tadah!
Keep it
quiet, now.
Master, what's the
meaning of this?
Don't scare us like that.
[coughing]
I'm Killer Bee quiet!
Nice cadence...!
Well?
What is it?
Hm?
What?! These are for
us?!
We're supposed to sell
these tickets?!
My brother interfered
during that last concert
of mine.
This time, I'm gonna make
sure that I nail it, baby!
They're tickets
for a concert?
Uggggh, who's gonna
wanna buy these?!
[beat-boxing]
You saying you got a
thing against hearing me
sing?
You fools! You big
idiots!
No, it's not that!
Okay, Master, relax!
We'll sell 'em, even if
it kills us!
Yeeeaaaahhh!
I'm countin' on you.
You all came quickly.
The situation calls for
swift action.
Listen, Princess Tsunade.
Are you sure you're up to
this?
You know, you should've
handed the reins over to
someone a little younger.
You're getting way
too old for this.
You should really
speak for yourself,
you old fence sitting
geezer.
Setting aside the Danzo
mess, I'm so relieved to
see that you're back as
Hokage, Lady Tsunade.
Let us be done with the
greetings and just proceed
right to our main business.
First on the agenda are
the Eight- and Nine-Tails
Jinchuriki.
And then we'll move onto
information on the
enemy's stronghold and
battle strength.
Some of my shinobi found
a location that may be
the enemy's base. But it
could also be a trap.
I think it's best to
gather more intel
first.
And we've also organized
multiple scouting parties
which are collecting data
as we speak.
We must pool and share
the intel from each
village with each other.
Well, what about forming a
separate unit within the
Allied Force that only
handles intel?
Now that's a good idea!
Share and share alike,
that's what I say!
Yes, of course!
If our nations become
driven by greed and self-
interest, the Akatsuki will
pull the rug from under us
before we even start!
So... where will we hide
away the two crucial
Jinchuriki?
Hide them away?!
What's the problem?
Naruto and Bee can lend
battle strength! Why
hide them away?
At first I thought so as
well, but our enemy's
goal in this war is to
possess those two.
Considering what could
happen, we can't let them
participate.
That's what we all
decided at the last
meeting.
Of course, you were
still unconscious,
Princess.
Our enemy is Madara!
Hold back strength and
we'll lose our chance to
win and we won't get
another!
We must hit them hard-
The Five Great Nation's
aim in this war is to
protect those two.
Your sole dissent as
Hokage is not enough.
Majority shall rule.
Listen, you stripling!
Naruto is--
I know him quite well.
Ya sure had us worried
there..!
He takes too many risks,
especially when it comes
to his friends. That is
why.
Before we discuss
military strength, the
five Kage must reach a
consensus.
Or no victory
will be possible!
I must agree with the
others, Lady Tsunade.
All right! Fine!
The Slug Princess is back
to her impudent self.
That retort is proof
she's well!
Let's decide where to
hide Eight- and
Nine-Tails.
Any objections,
Lady Hokage?
None at all. Just hurry
it up so we can move on.
I've got just the place
in mind.
It lies inside the Hidden
Cloud, which so far,
hasn't produced any
Akatsuki members.
I set it aside in case.
And why do you need to
speak privately?
Because I need a favor.
Heh. A favor?
I understand that your
younger brother Bee has
the Eight Tails under
control.
My hope... is that Bee
can train Naruto....
And teach him to control
Nine-Tails.
Hm. Wouldn't that
be convenient...
If that brat named Naruto
gains complete control
over the Nine-Tailed fox--
He'll be the ultimate
weapon for the Hidden
Leaf.
Do you actually believe
that I would ever agree
to that?
I understand your
concerns.
But this isn't the time
for us to be arguing
about our own interests!
Hmph.
We're facing Madara
Uchiha!
Eventually, we're going
to be forced to use Bee
and Naruto's powers!
But if we wait, it'll be
too late!
You shouldn't shout. Is
that any way to ask
someone for a favor?
[sighing]
I'm sorry.
Well, I have to admit,
you do make a good point.
I know, because I
considered it a
long time ago.
You did? What
are you saying?!
Where I'm sending those
two isn't just some secret
place where they can both
hide.
I said I set
it aside, didn't I?
A long time ago, when we
were younger...
Bee and I trained
on that island.
An S-rank mission?!
No way! You're giving me
a big assignment like
that?
That's right. It's a
mission that only you
can undertake.
You and Yamato will go to
a site in the Hidden
Cloud.
Mm?
So is that the resort?
The Great Lord Elder's
prophecy was correct. It
seems that is the place
he foresaw.
So then, you're saying I
am gonna meet the octopus
on this island?!
I gotta say, I kinda feel
bad! Everyone's so busy
and I get to go to a
swanky resort and---
Quiet, you fool!
You're going on a
mission!
Yeah, I know, granny! I
was just jokin' around.
But if I'm going to the
place from the prophecy,
Is the other one true, too?
Was the Great Lord Elder
right about me having to
fight Sasuke, as well?
I'm afraid I don't know,
Naruto. However, I do
know we stand on the
brink of war!
Hence, this S-rank
mission. Now, when you
reach the location, you
will follow Yamato's orders.
Okay! I understand!
You can count on me,
granny. I'm on the job!
Dress casually for
enka.
I'm looking pretty good,
all right...
Where's Bee?!
What up, Bro?
You nearly gave me a
heart attack!
You're going on a
mission! You leave
immediately!
What?!
Huh?!
Ah!
What the hell
are you wearing?!
[struggling]
Let's go!
But my concert's
in three days! Ow!
Not so tight!
There's no way that we
can sell these now...
Yeah, but if we
don't sell them,
he's gonna be all,
"Ya fools. Ya idiots.
Ya worthless jerks."
And then what'll happen?
We'll end up both tied to
a chair...
And then we'll be
forced... to listen to
Master's singing... for
forever.
Ahhhhhhh!
We'll get calluses
on our ears!
We have no choice.
We just have to sell
all the tickets!
Yeah, but if we do sell
all of them... then he's
gonna be so grateful...
That he'll give us both
first-row seats!
And we'll still have
to listen to him sing
forever and get calluses
on our ears!
Ow!
So do we sell the tickets
or not?!
How the hell
should I know?!
The time has come! Just
like Giant Gramps Sage
prophesied.
I'm going to go look
for an octopus and train
to control the Nine-Tail's
power.
And meet Sasuke once
again.
Naruto, are you ready?
Yeah!
Now, young one,
time to go!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Young Man
and the Sea.
Set sail for the Land of
Lightning!