This landscape brings
back so many memories...
The Tsuchikage and Kazekage
are especailly
persistent.
What should we do?
Huh?!
It's them! They're
toward four o'clock!
Wood Style! Deep
Forest Emergence!
He's able to use
Wood Style?!
I guess this is
it for us then...
[low grunting]
Damn it! I don't
have much chakra
left at all!
What am I gonna do?
Naruto, this time I'll
lend you my power.
[irritated breath]
And I guess you're
gonna tell me to hand
my body over to you again?!
No...I'll just give
you my chakra.
I do not care
for Madara.
If he's going to try to
control me again, I'd
rather stick with you.
If I can utilize Madara
to my advantage, I can
control the war.
I never imagined he'd
be such a powerful player!
Naruto! Wait!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Giant Rasengan!
[surprised breath]
Go for it, Naruto!
Giant Rasengan Barrage Line!
Just as you said, he's
quite an impressive
shinobi.
Isn't he?
[heavy breathing]
I used up the chakra
Nine Tails gave me in
one shot.
I'm at my limit! I'm
gonna disappear at any
moment here!
[panting]
Naruto, that's enough.
I'll take over this
battle for here on.
Lord Tsuchikage you're
too injured! You're in
no condition!
[grunt]
I have a chance to
reclaim myself now.
I've still got enough
energy left to do that,
believe you me!
I'll fight him!
What?! That's crazy!
You're already
falling apart!
[heavy breathing]
[alarmed grunt]
That's too bad. I wanted
to try out some more jutsu...
But I don't think
you can dance anymore,
Ohnoki.
[angry growl]
What is that look for?
I already showed you how
different our strengths
were long ago, remember?
What?! But why?!
That wasn't the agreement!
Lord Hashirama said...
There is no alliance now.
You will merely bow
down to the might
of the Hidden Leaf!
And also...never mention
that shinobi's name in
my presence again!
[scared quivering]
For all these years,
we shinobi have done
nothing but do battle.
We have continued to
fight for the sake of
our nations and our
villages.
We just take what we
want from our enemies
without a single care!
We take from them, and
they take back from us
again in an endless
cycle!
Three times now our
hatred has caused
all-out war!
But that is simply the
way that life is.
I can't believe you've lived
as long as you have without
learning a single thing
from the pain of the past.
I've lived longer than you...
And been around the block
enough to learn twice
what you have!
It's because I've experienced
pain in the past, that I can
even consider what would be
best for the future!
And yet this is the
Fourth Great Ninja War.
Is this what's best?
This war is different
than the others!
This time, we're all
fighting the battle
together.
In order to achieve
something more than the
petty differences we've
fought over before!
By watching youngsters like
them, I've learned that
time doesn't just flow
and pass us by.
Though slow in pace, the
world does accrue its past
experiences...and grows
steadily towards peace.
[heavy panting]
That is where you
are wrong.
The world does not need
to grow any further.
It should slumber in peace
under the genjutsu of the
Eternal Tsukuyomi.
Madara...Long ago
you forced me to
foresake myself.
However...I shall win
against you here. I
will reclaim myself!
And you shall be the
one who will slumber!
Lord Tsuchikage!
[surprised reaction]
Come with me, and
I'll help you
reclaim yourself.
I've found that the aged
usually complain when those
younger than they are
dote on them too much.
Don't you think
that's true?
[chuckle]
I'll allow all of
you to meddle this
one time.
Hmph.
Still have some dance
left in you?
For my soul's sake,
and for the future!
I shall take you down
here and now!
Damn it!
Lady Tsunade!
Your name's Mabui, right?
Prepare your Ethereal
Transmission Jutsu
and come with me!
The Ethereal Transmission
Jutsu is for transporting
objects!
It's not like the Summoning
or Reverse Summoning Jutsu;
it's not meant for people!
There's no time to argue!
We won't know until
we try it, right?
We do know!
The transmission rate is so
fast the body can't keep up
and it just gets torn apart!
It's certain death!
The only one who has
ever successfully
traveled using this jutsu
is the Third Raikage.
But he was able to
achieve that feat only
because of his
superhuman body!
Perhaps it's possible for
the Fourth Raikage, being
of the Third Lord's blood...
But certainly not for you,
Lady Hokage. Please,
reconsider!
I've got an idea that
just might work.
We'll use the Flying
Raijin Jutsu.
We could summon Genma's platoon
here, put jutsu formula on a
Katsuyu clone, and then have
Mabui transmit her to the site.
Well I do have the
ability to survive
being split into
pieces,
There's no need. I'm just
going to use this.
Yes, of course, I
should've known.
[nervous reaction]
It's still a very dangerous
gamble. And you tend to be,
shall we say, unlucky with
bets, Lady Tsunade,
That's only when
I bet money.
It's completely different
when I wager my life.
That's why I'm
still alive.
[uneasy groan]
Lord Raikage, sir. Please
ask Lady Hokage to
reconsider this!
[humming]
Mabui, go prepare the
Ethereal Transmission
Jutsu. You're sending
both of us!
Lord Raikage, not
you, too!
Shikaku, please!
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
that we have no other
options left.
It's time for the
Supreme Commander's
entrance!
[grunt of approval]
Madara belongs to
the Uchiha Clan,
If we don't shut down
his Fire Style, we have
no chance.
We'll save the Flying
Raijin Jutsu...
...until we're able to
use it against him.
[battle cry]
[struggling grunt]
[attacking yell]
[grunt of pain]
The more of them I cut
down, the more confidence
I'll gain.
That's why I gotta
keep slicing!
[pleased reaction]
Yeah!
I thought that was
a lot of chakra you
were gathering.
I had no idea that
sword would be so huge!
I...can't move!
I had no idea...he could
transform the shape of
his blade so fast!
Woah! That guy is
seriously good!
Genma! I'm sorry, but
could you just do as
I say?
Shikaku?
It's an emergnecy
situation. Don't
interrupt me no matter
what I tell you!
First of all, the real
Madara has been brought
back with the Reanimation
Jutsu.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but...what was that?!
I said no
interruptions!
[gasp]
Do it now!
All right! Here it goes...
Ethereal Transmission Jutsu!
[struggling reaction]
This is a surprise.
So it's instaneous
transportation? Wasn't
that the Fourth Hokage's
jutsu?
That's right. The three of
us were formerly assigned
to the Fourth Hokage's
Personal Guard Platoon.
And now we're there
for the Fifth.
The Lord Fourth taught
all of us his Flying
Raijin Jutsu.
Unlike Lord Fourth, who
could do it alone, it
takes all three of us
together to make it work.
I'm sorry about the
close quarters.
Lady Mizukage...
Please go and
take Madara down
hard!
I'll defend this place
with my life as one
of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen!
[pleased reaction]
Oh, Chojuro...
That boy...he's
grown so much since
leaving the village.
Prepare yourself! Lady
Tsunade bears the Jutsu
Formula on her.
As soon as she reaches
the battlefield, we'll
fly right there ourselves.
Roger, understood. I'm
already late for the alter,
I'd hate to be late for more.
Unruly Ay and
Princess Tsunade!
I had already relayed
our coordinates to HQ!
Reserve Seal! Release!
Ninja Art Mitotic
Regeneration Jutsu!
Are you okay, Tsunade?
Yeah...
Granny Tsunade is here?!
That's her Regenerating
Jutsu!
Hmph.
[startled yell]
Well, seeing that everyone
here is still alive, I
guess we made it in time.
Now I can finally let
loose! And it's about
damn time, too!
All right, I'm ready
to go now as well!
I must say, it is truly
worth living a long life.
Imagine, seeing the day
when the Five Kage would
unite and fight side by side.
This is perfect! You
all will make this
test of mine
worth while!
Thank you for
this, Princess.
I'll heal the two of
you. Raikage, Mizukage!
You buy me some time
while I finish this up!
Here we go, Mizukage!
Right!
Lava Style: Lava
Monster Jutsu!
Jutsu this pitiful isn't
even worth absorbing!
He's fast!
[shocked reaction]
Lateral Bolt of Pain!
Chop!
I feel so out of
place here next
to them.
What do you think?
Is he still okay?
Doubt it.
You've seen what
they're capable of.
Keep watching!
There's no way for us
to join the fray and help.
Look, why don't all
three of you come
with me, and we'll
go after the other one.
Help me out!
Is that the guy?
Follow me! Let's go!
How much longer, Hokage?
Just a bit!
But Granny Tsunade,
are you okay?
Whenever you use that
forehead mark jutsu, you
get really old and you
fall down!
It's different than when
I fought Pain, Naruto.
I only healed myself
so far, and none
of these wounds are
very troublesome.
I have more than
enough chakra!
Great! So does that mean
you can heal me too,
Granny Tsunade?
I may be a clone, but
I can't afford to
disappear yet!
I can join you!
That's not necessary!
[taken aback reaction]
Why not?!
Naruto, you must understand.
This war is no longer being
fought only to protect you!
Lightning Style
Teleportation as
well as Lava Style
Kekkei Genkai...
Most impressive attacks.
You know, I normally
prefer men who are hard to
melt. But in your case,
I think i'd have to pass.
He can counter me
even at my full speed.
I'm gonna have to get
faster...and thus up the
power to crush your
defense!
How is your defense?
[shocked reaction]
A Stone Golem...and
a Sand Shield!
Do you understand now?
This war has become a
battle to protect each
other!
I wanna fight Madara,
too! I can help you!
A defensive wall of
Sand and Stone?
Also quite impressive!
Right! It's time to
go on the offensive!
Now, Mizukage! Raikage!
Listen to me well!
You! Hold it!
How pesky!
[struggling grunt]
Right. I understand.
Mizukage!
Water Style: Hidden
Mist Jutsu!
Hidden Mist...They're
trying to block the
Rinnegan's field of
vision with it.
Let's do this, Raikage!
Right!
Huh?!
That Tsuchikage...He
made the Raikage lighter,
which increased his speed,
but even so...
What a lousy punch!
Not to worry. It'll
turn out the same
as before.
Huh?!
Super-Lightened
Boulder Jutsu!
[shocked grunt]
[painful groan]
Granny! Come on! Would ya
heal me already?!
Just calm yourself and
listen to me, Naruto.
You see, this war
that we're now
fighting...
In the beginning, I only
agreed to join the Allied
Shinobi Forces in order to
get rid of the Akatsuki.
But as I battled alongside
all of you, I started feeling
quite differently than I had
in the past.
Now, I want to be here
as the Tsuchikage of the
Allied Shinobi Forces!
In the exact same manner, some
shinobi villages which used to
be disparate and autonomous, are
now changing.
They are becoming one.
So perhaps this shinobi
world system, which thus far
has only bred hatred, can
change as well!
Naruto...
Please, let all of us
deal with this Madara.
I swear we'll finish
him off!
It'll be our first step in
stopping the curse of hatred
we've all been under
until now.
Like Madara, we Kage are
also guilty of stirring
up hate in the past.
It's our responsibility
to make things right!
Rest assured and
leave this to us!
And you...You
go and take
care of the other
Madara, my boy.
That act will become
the first step in
promoting hope for
the future.
The old one or the
new one, it doesn't
really matter.
Only by defeating both
Madaras will we be able
to bring this war to an end!
We will all defend you
by fighting on this
battlefield.
So protect us through your
actions by fighting over
there on that battlefield!
Now, Clone Naruto...
I entrust you with this
message from all
the Five Kage.
We'll win!
Yeah!
We'll win for sure!
Damn it! That thing
is really hard! I didn't
even crack it!
Just chill out, Naruto!
Fool, ya fool.
I could've simply passed
through you, but I guess
it doesn't matter if you
can't even crack the mask.
With the power to control
the Nine Tails, I hope
that's not all you can
manage!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Unbreakable Mask and
the Shattered Bubble!"
This jutsu...
This chakra!