(Ashura)
My chakra's reacting
very strongly.
(Kanna)
What is that?
It's the same thing that was
growing on all of those sick
people.
I see!  The Divine Tree's sap
has seeped into the soil.
The sap acts like a fertilizer,
making this area a lush oasis in
the middle of such a barren
region.
The power of the Divine Tree is
what's making the land fertile?
Yeah...
So, then that means the Divine
Tree's getting its power back?!
No,  or at least it hasn't
completely revived yet...
But... in time it
probably will...
The real problem is...
Is what?
The villagers are becoming
contaminated.
Contaminated?!
Yeah. The people and animals eat
the produce that was grown on
this land...
...which has accumulated
the sap of the Divine Tree.
Wait... does that mean, if you
eat the food here, you're gonna
get sick?!
(Asura)
Probably.
Blargh! But... I ate
so much yesterday!
It'll be okay.
With my jutsu I can take
care of a small amount...
But if you've eaten
it for many years.
Hey, wait... since the Village
Elder ordered this place to be
kept under watch...
...does that mean he
knows everything about
what's been going on here?
So it would seem...
♪
I see, You went to
the Divine Tree.
That's right.
Tell me, traveler, why is it
that you insist on digging for
our village's secrets?
Forgive me. I
was sent here.
I was told to come by
the Village of Ninshu.
Ninshu? What destroyed the
land twenty years ago?
You are a pupil
of that discipline?
Yes.
That tree is a remnant of the
specter that almost destroyed
our entire world.
That's why it's so powerful.
I've been ordered to do
something about it.
Lord Elder, to be blunt,
that tree is a narcotic.
The power of the Divine Tree
is indeed making this land
fruitful...
But... it's also making
the villagers ill.
...At this rate...
Yes, Traveler, I am
already aware of it.
But I cannot authorize
that tree's destruction.
Why is that?
Several decades ago... that tree
began to grow dramatically...
Prior to that, this land
was arid and barren.
We had terrible droughts
nearly every year.
I've lost count of how
many starved to death.
Why don't you just
try digging a well?
It was futile.
Futile?
We tried that ages ago.
One could dig for years, only to
hit the solid bedrock that runs
beneath this entire land.
If we cut down that tree now,
what will happen to us?
I cannot tell the villagers that
we'll return to those days of
hunger and suffering.
Besides, even if I told
them the truth, the villagers
wouldn't believe me.
Traveler, please... don't get
involved any further...
It would be best if you
were to leave soon.
Kanna, what do you think?
Think about what?
In time, you'll become infected
by the Divine Tree, as well.
I know. And?! We have
no other choice!
Even if we wanted to
leave, there's nowhere
else for us to go!
We just have to endure
and live with it!
All of you! Please,
listen to me!
Do you know the truth
behind the Divine Tree?
[gasp]
Hey, Ashura...!
(Ashura)
The Divine Tree is the
ruins of a specter.
It's the cause of the illness
afflicting those at the clinic.
And if you keep relying on its
power you'll all fall victim to
the same thing!
Ask yourself: are you
okay with that?
Everyone! You don't have
to listen to this guy!
The two of them came here
from the Village of Ninshu!
Yeah!  They ravaged the world,
and now they want to try to take
the Divine Tree away from us!
We can't let them do that!
Just leave!  Get outta here!
What do you think would happen
to us if the Divine Tree was
gone, huh?!
Ashura, let's go!
[angry shouting]
Yeah you better run!
Yeah, good riddance!
Don't come back!
I certainly hope...
Masters Indra and
Ashura are okay.
Brother, to what kind of places
did you send those two?
Simply put, two villages that
were burdened with the same
problem.
I want to see what choices they
make, and how they resolve the
problems.
Ah, yes, I understand.
But be honest, have you already
decided which one'll succeed
you?
No, I haven't.
Indra's abilities are
extraordinary...
...but he's too quick to try to
resolve everything by himself.
Ashura is truly kind
to others ...
... but hesitates to
take the lead.
If this journey that they've
been sent on helps to them
mature and learn to support each
other
then I would have no complaints.
Gamamaru, have you
had any new dreams?
Dreams about your
sons' futures, you mean?
If I did, would you
want me to tell you?
That'd be cheating.  You must
name your successor by yourself.
[cough]
Well, then... Guess it's
time for me to be leaving.
Hold on... I hope you're not
planning on visiting them,
Gamamaru...
[grunt]
Please, do not
interfere with this.
I won't!
[grunt]
I doubt that all of you will
ever be able to reach a
decision.
Come on, Ashura.
Let's go, already!
Let's just head out and have
a carefree journey, okay?
[groan] If you're really that
concerned, just sneak over
there and destroy the tree!
I mean, you do have the
power to do that, don't you?
But if I do that, then all of
the villagers will...
They'll suffer, sure!  But
everyone dies eventually!
You know...  now that I think of
it...  Father didn't tell me to
destroy the Divine Tree.
Huh?
Indra, Ashura. You are to go to
those lands and fix whatever
problems may have occurred
there.
Wait, that's right!  Father said
to resolve the problem...!
Hey, hold on, now. I hope that
you're not getting any crazy
ideas.
To solve the problem,  there's
no other way but to dig a well.
What?! You heard that village
elder! There's bedrock under
here!
It'd take years!
Yes. But a little while
back, Father told me.
The power of Ninshu that you
have inherited. I'm afraid
there's no handbook for its use.
It's up to you to decide
the right way to employ it.
It's up to us.
I've decided!  I'm going to do
what I think is right!
Huh?
Even if it takes me years!
(Apprentice)
Master Indra's returned!
[gasps]
(Villager)
Ha!  Leave it to Master Indra!
I can't believe it!  He's back
already?
I'm glad to see
that you're well.
Where's Ashura?
He's not back yet.
He isn't?
Don't tell me... Is he-?!
[blast]
[gasp] Ashura!
Oh, hey, Kanna!
What are you doing!?
What, can't you tell? I'm
digging a well for your village.
[weary sigh]
Are you serious...?
Yeah.  If you guys have water,
then you won't have to rely on
the Divine Tree.
It's impossible. The villagers
have tried digging for water
for years. But they've never
found any...
Yeah, I already told him that.
But once he gets an idea in his
head, he won't listen.
It doesn't matter whether it's
possible or not.   Because I've
decided to do it.
See you later, Kanna.
[blast]
Are you guys... idiots?
Well, I just might be,
but he definitely is.
(Thinking)
Even if it takes years,
I'll make it happen!
I've returned, Father.
Yes. Welcome back.
So how did it go?
I did exactly as I was told.
And were there any problems?
No. Peace has returned
to the village.
Lord Hagoromo. Master Indra
has returned first...
Which means the successor
of Ninshu must be.
No... I'm not interested in how
quickly things were resolved.
I'll wait for Ashura's return.
And then I'll decide. Is that
all right, Indra?
Yes.
(Zetsu)
It's been awhile, Indra.
Oh?  You're in a bad mood.
Didn't you come to see me?
I'm aware of
everything, you know.
You did exactly as Hagoromo
wished.  But he's still not
satisfied.
The future Hagoromo envisions
for Ninshu is not the future
that you envision.
You've both improved.
No matter what may happen in the
future, Indra,  we'll always
follow you.
I will remember the
words that you've spoken.
Lord Hagoromo. It's been one
year since Master Ashura set
out on his journey.
And yet... he
still hasn't returned.
Your students are starting to
become restless.  So perhaps you
should decide on your successor.
Yes, I realize that.
No one would object if you were
to choose Master Indra.
Why keep waiting for
Master Ashura?
Please, don't be concerned.  I'm
certain Ashura will return very
soon.
Lord Hagoromo! Sir!
Huh? What's going on?!
(Apprentice)
Master Indra!
It's Master Ashura!
He's returned!
Hey there, everyone!
(Apprentice)
It's not just Master Ashura!
There are so many with him!
(Villager)
I recognize Taizo, but...
who are the others?
So he's back at last...
(Gamamaru)
You are quite astute
about your sons.
[grunt] I think that this water
pot has seen its last day...
My, my, that certainly
did take a long time!
You know, that younger one of
yours is very clumsy.
But his tenacity's
really something!
I thought that I told you
to mind your own business,
Gamamaru.
That's what I did! The only
thing I did was watch, that's
all.
However... I want to let you in
on something that happened...
It's about the village
Indra went to...
Welcome back to the village.
Thank you. Are you well?
Yes. I'm glad you're
well too, Master Ashura.
Please, go see Lord Hagoromo.
What?!  Elder Brother
wasn't...?!
So Father still hasn't?
(Futami)
He's been waiting all this time
for your return, Master Ashura.
Oh.  I see.
Father, I've come home at last.
You've become dignified, Ashura.
We've all been waiting...
I know. Forgive me,
Elder Brother.
With the level of power I
possess, I needed a lot longer
to resolve the problem in the
village where I was sent.
And who are those people?
Oh! Right! They're all
from that village.
They helped me resolve the
problems there.  And they've
become valuable friends.
We heard so much about your
village, and we all wanted to
see it,
so we came with Master Ashura
when he headed back here.
Welcome. It's good of
you to come.
Ashura, tell me your story.
The village I went to relied on
the Divine Tree for water.
So... I decided to dig a well.
Ashura! Are you really
doing to do this?!
This is what I've
decided to do!
[sigh]
[weary sigh]
What is it now?
Are they back to throw
rocks at us or something?
Hold on.
Everyone, please...
We came to help.
It's for our village, so
we want to do our part.
And if you can, do you think
that you could teach us Ninshu,
too?
[gasp]
Uh, yeah, sure!
♪
Everyone, wait!
Please be quiet!
Huh?
Is something the matter, Ashura?
Can you hear it?
You hear that sound...?
[crash]
It's water!
No way!
What happened?
[cheering]
Incredible!
We did it!
You did it, Ashura!
[small groan]
Mom...
Kanna...
[sob] Mom...!
We're finally free now from
the curse that has burdened
us for so long.
-I can't believe it!
-Amazing!
I see... So the Ninshu that you
spread has saved many people.
Yes!
I'll now announce the name of
the successor to Ninshu.
The one who'll take
over Ninshu is.
♪
(Hagoromo)
A bond is something that can
only be created after sharing
hardships together.
It overflows with
love and compassion.
As long as such bonds exist,
Ninshu won't be used for evil.
However, power without bonds
will bring great calamity upon
the world.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Successor."
From this moment onward, I
entrust my power to you.
♪