CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sasori.
[groaning]
-All right, break time's over.
-Guy-sensei, are you sure?
-Absolutely.
I feel perfectly fine.
All I needed was a little rest.
-Well, Neji?
-It's all right.
His recuperative
powers are amazing.
-But what about--
-Don't worry about me.
I'm ready to go.
-All right, everyone.
To keep to our
schedule, we're going
to have to move double
time from here on in.
-Aw.
-No!
Let us make it triple time.
Then we might actually
arrive ahead of schedule.
-Good thinking.
As a matter of fact, why don't
we make it quadrule time?
Eh, what's the matter?
-That's not even
physically possible.
-Would you guys please
stop getting carried away?
-Uh, Sensei, perhaps triple
time would be enough.
-Lee.
I think even that's pushing it.
-All right.
It's time.
That's enough rest.
We should get moving.
OK, you two.
Wake up.
We're heading out.
-Right.
-OK, in a minute.
Just give me a minute more.
-I thought you were
going to save Gaara?
-You bet I'm going to save him.
[theme music]
-Somewhere out there is
the Akatsuki hideout.
Gaara, I'm sorry.
[groaning]
-Now, we're entering
the final stage.
-What should we do about
these annoying pests?
-They're getting
closer, and more quickly
than we anticipated.
-Not a problem.
We delayed them just enough.
Ignore them.
In any event, we
have a backup plan.
-I think he means that in
the end it'll be up to you
and me, Sasori, my man.
-Well then, I suggest we hurry
up and finish our business
here.
We'll want a moment
to catch our breath
before greeting our guests.
-Oh, yes, indeed.
We must be ready to give
them a warm welcome.
-Blasted nuisances.
They're such a pain.
-I never thought we'd have
so much trouble finding
a Jinchuriki.
-Calm down.
We each just need to
fulfill our own part.
-Enough talk.
Concentrate, all of you.
There can be no mistakes
from this point on.
-Each squad understands how
and where it is to be deployed.
Our Kazekage is missing.
We've done our best
to hide that fact.
However, you must act under
the assumption that news of it
has leaked out.
At this very moment,
neighboring lands
might be planning to take
advantage of our confusion
by launching an
attack, so don't think
of this as standard
border patrol.
Very well.
Those squads ready to
leave will depart at once!
-What's wrong with you, Matsuri?
-Are we sure this is the
right thing to be doing?
-What do you mean?
-After all, Lord
Gaara's been kidnapped,
and instead of
trying to rescue him,
we're marching back and
forth on the border,
waiting for an attack
that may not even come.
-They're orders from on high.
Ours but to obey.
-No!
Lord Gaara is one of us.
He's our Kazekage,
no one else's!
-You think I don't know that?
Are you forgetting
Gaara's my brother?
-Please forgive me.
-This way.
-Right.
-Something's not right.
-Do you sense something, Neji?
-The enemy?
-Just the opposite, in fact.
I can't detect any
trace of the enemy.
That's what's so disturbing.
They were so intent
on delaying us.
Using such a powerful jutsu.
-So what do you think?
-Could it be that they--
-They're confidend they've
delayed us long enough.
-Yes, indeed.
I'm starting to
think the same thing.
-But that means--
CHIYO: What's he--
-Hang on, Gaara.
We're comin'.
-Naruto, not so fast!
Wait up!
Oh, brother.
-Why's that boy pushing
himself so hard to save Gaara?
He's not even from
the same village.
What is he?
What's that boy's story?
-Naruto is a
Jinchuriki, as well.
He has the Nine Tailed
Fox sealed within him.
It's not that he has any special
feelings for the Hidden Sand,
or its people, but he and
Gaara are both Jinchuriki.
Naruto knows how Gaara feels
better than anyone in the Sand
ever could.
After all, those
who are Jinchuriki
have been treated the
same way in every village.
That's why he feels this
desperate need to save Gaara.
It doesn't matter
whether Gaara's
from the Sand, or the
Leaf, or anywhere else.
He's a friend, the
only friend who's
felt the same pain
Naruto's felt.
Naruto's dream is to
become Hokage, so the news
that Gaara had been made
Kazekage hit him pretty hard.
-I see.
So Gaara was named Kazekage.
-He was frustrated, but at the
same time, deep in his heart,
he was profoundly
happy for Gaara.
-Well, I'm not about
to be outdone by him.
I'm still going to
be Hokage one day.
Just you wait, Gaara!
-You see, Naruto has
another remarkable gift.
He doesn't need
much time, or many
works to make friends with
almost everyone he meets.
-As for me, I've
lived a long life.
I've seen many things
over the years.
I thought I'd come to know
the ways of the world.
I knew that alliances
with foreign lands
were just for show,
and not to be trusted.
I knew that the only
way the Sand Village was
to be protected is
if I did it myself.
It was my jutsu that sealed
the Shukaku in young Gaara,
after consulting with his
father, the Fourth Kazekage,
of course.
I truly thought I was
helping my village,
but in fact I was jeopardizing
its very existence.
And now I find that my
peoples' survival depends
on one of those alliances with
a foreign land I never trusted.
I seem to have been
wrong about many things.
Perhaps everything.
I am old and weary.
I want nothing more
than to just give up.
Oh, Kakashi, when I look at
them and see their youth,
their potential, I
envy them so much.
-No, no.
Your life has only just begun.
You're still young.
[laughter]
-Perhaps you're right.
Maybe there is some
purpose for keeping
an old bag of bones
like me around.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): There
must be something I can do.
[groaning]
-It's almost finished.
GAARA: Whose hand is this?
It's-- it's mine.
Does this mean I've become
someone that people need?
Who's that?
Is that me?
Yes, it's me.
Me wanting to be
needed by someone.
Why?
Why did I want that?
Why did I yearn for that?
Those eyes.
That nose.
That mouth.
Why?
Why is that Gaara?
I was in there.
No.
What am I, anyway?
I'm only aware of being me.
So who am I?
Am I anything more than just
this small consciousness?
-It is complete.
-Finally.
-So in the end, it did take
three full days and nights.
Hm.
-It seems to get more
exhausting every time.
-My shoulders are stiff.
-Well done.
Good work, everyone.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): That
can't be a good sign.
Dammit!
If only there was
something I could do.
-So, this is the place?
-Gaara's on the other
side of that boulder.
-It won't be easy getting
past that barrier.
-What's the plan?
ROCK LEE: We smash our way in.
-No, Lee.
-Huh?
-Late as usual, Kakashi.
-Well, you see, we ran into a
little trouble along the way.
-Naruto!
Sakura!
-Wait a minute.
By a little trouble, you don't
mean me, do you, Kakashi?
-Well?
-Naruto.
-Looks like we were just
a step behind you guys.
-Yeah.
Who's that old lady?
-Oh.
This is Lady Chiyo.
She's an adviser from
the Sand Village.
-Very pleased to meet you.
-Well then, let's
do this, Kakashi.
-Right.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Hang on, Gaara.
Just hang on!
[theme music]
GUY: Listen up.
The title of the next
episode, Button Hook Entry,
refers to the ninja tactic
of breaking through a barrier
by deploying themselves to
the left and right of it.
This, of course, is not to be
confused with my own Dynamic
Entry, which is not a
jutsu, as some people
think, but an effective
technique when
speed is of the essence.
It also makes an excellent
diversionary tactic.
There.
Now you're ready
for a test, or maybe
even a mission of your own.
[LAUGHTER
NARUTO: Next time, Charge
Tactic, Button Hook Entry.
[theme music]
KAKASHI: The Leaf
Village fashion report.
Today we'll be taking a look
at some indispensable shinobi
accessories.
Number one, the Leaf headband.
It tells the world
you've been recognized
as a full fledged shinobi.
Not only handy in defense,
but a tasty fashion statement,
as well.
It's usually worn
over the forehead,
but it doesn't have to be.
Everyone has their
own individual style.
Next is this shuriken
and kunai set.
Very practical.
Useful in all kinds of combat.
Of course, no set's
complete without
a handsome and handy holster.
Finally, there's the
official Leaf vest.
With this vest's
convenient compartments,
you'll never have
to fumble around
for scrolls in the
midst of battle.
They're right there
at your fingertips.
-And if you act
right now, you'll
also receive this waterproof
ventilated form fitting action
suit!
-Thanks, but I don't think
anyone's really interested
in one of those--
-Not interested?
Are you crazy?
-Well, until next time.
So long.