SAKURA: Naruto, wait.
Where are you going?
-If the Pervy Sage had
been the Fifth Hokage,
he wouldn't have let Granny
Tsunade take a risk like that.
Never.
-Naruto!
-Please, Sakura.
Enough.
Just drop it.
Let him be for now.
-But milady--
-I can see that this child truly
loved and admired Jiraiya boy.
It makes me hope
more than anything
that he is the
child of prophecy.
[theme music]
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): I'm sorry.
You always seem to get such
unfortunate assignments.
-What's with the
sudden confession?
-Look, I'm really saying you
were supposed to become Hokage.
After all, the
Third Hokage always
wanted you to succeed him.
-I'm not cut out for
that sort of thing.
I like being free
and unfettered.
-You regretted not being
able to stop Orochimaru.
That's why you tracked
his movements by yourself
for so long, isn't it?
-Well, guess I no longer
need to do that, do I?
Of course, that also
means I get to release
the sequel to my
novel even sooner.
FUKASAKU: Tsunade girl.
Tsunade girl!
-Are you doing
all right, milady?
-Yes.
I'm fine now.
I apologize.
-You've received
some very sad news.
No one can blame you
for being distraught.
But that said, you have
a vital duty to perform.
You must protect the village.
It's essentially
that you stay strong.
-I know.
In any case, let's
discuss the clues
that Jiraiya boy left for us.
In addition to the message
he's put on my back,
he's given us other
leads, as well.
A Hidden Rain ninja that
Jiraiya boy managed to capture
is inside the
belly of that frog.
And one last thing remains.
Inside this toad is one
of the bodies of Pain
that Jiraiya boy
managed to kill.
One of the six.
-Pain's body?
[groan]
-Oh, there they are!
So many beautiful girls.
-Hey, what are you doin'?
Knock it off!
-Just taking in the sights.
And getting inspiration
for my next novel.
FUKSAKU: This is Pain.
SHIZUNE: The ripple pattern.
Is that the legendary Rinnegan?
-That's correct.
If we studied his
body, I believe
we may find clues on
how to defeat pain.
-A shinobi's corpse is
full of information.
We'll need skilled
medical ninja,
and then we'll launch a full
autopsy on him immediately.
Shizune.
-Right.
I'll take care of it.
-Hm.
The photo's very clear.
I have given you everything
that was entrusted to me.
-Yes.
Indeed.
-I will return home now, but
let me know what you find.
Since Jiraiya boy's
student is here,
you can send him to
contact me at Mt.
Myoboku.
-Thank you very much.
I promise you, we will find
a way somehow to defeat Pain.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Now listen, Naruto.
I only have three
years to get you
strong enough to
stand on your own.
We'll spend that time
training, but it won't be easy.
So be prepared to work hard.
-I'm ready.
Trust me.
And this time, I'm gonna
bring Sasuke back for sure.
There's no time to waste,
so let's get going.
Come on, I can't
stand this anymore.
This has gotta be the
lamest training ever!
-There's no such thing
as lame training.
And you'd know that if you
weren't such a complete fool!
-Gotcha!
[laughter]
-You aren't the
only one here who
knows how to use
the shadow clones.
Sometimes you're still so naive.
-Damn.
So close.
I almost had you had time.
-Oh, please.
It'd take you 100 years
before you could beat me.
NARUTO: No way.
I can't wait 100 years.
Just watch.
Next time.
Nice!
Man, this is a cool outfit!
-Well now, they do say
the clothes make the man.
IRUKA: Yo.
Naruto.
I hear you've been real
active on missions lately.
Everyone in the village
is talking about you.
Hey, you and I should go
somewhere and catch up.
How about we hit up
Ichiraku for some ramen?
-Maybe later.
-What?
You want me to do this now?
-That's right.
Take that over to
them right away.
-But the guys in the cypher
division don't work this late.
Lady Hokage--
-Then summon them and tell
them it's on my orders.
I'm putting you in charge.
Get that message decoded.
-Look, I know this is
an important encryption,
but can't you ask someone who
isn't on a mission right now?
Wait!
Where are you going?
I actually came here
on other matters.
I--
-Shikamaru.
-But--
-Lady Tsunade has been
very busy all day.
-Well, the same goes for me.
-Shikamaru, please don't.
-You know, you've become even
more beautiful than before.
-And you haven't changed a bit.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Betray that dream,
and you make all their
sacrifices meaningless.
If I thought you could, I would
stop you right here and now.
I know.
How about making a bet with me?
You gamble everything
on me dying.
After all, Tsunade, you
always lose your bets.
Isn't that right?
Promise me.
If I do actually manage to make
it back alive-- [laughter] I'm
only kidding, Tsunade.
You know, I'm really
quite grateful to you.
Well, hello there.
I'm Jiraiya.
You can send love letters later.
Nice to meet ya.
-You stupid fool.
-Naruto?
I heard what happened
to Master Jiraiya.
-All I ever wanted was to have
him keep watching over me.
I wanted him to see
me become Hokage.
But I only showed him the
worst, most uncool side of me.
I'm still so--
-Listen to me.
All Jiraiya ever had
was praise for you.
he always boasted about you.
He kept saying that you were
like his own grandchild.
It's true.
He had faith that you were the
one who you'd inherit his will.
And he truly believed that you
would become a wonderful Hokage
one day.
He's still watching,
and he always will be.
Even at this very minute.
No matter where he is,
I know that he wouldn't
be happy to see you
this upset and sad.
Naruto, just go back to being
the you he praised so highly.
Cheer up.
For you are a distinguished
student of one
of the legendary Sannin.
Acknowledged by the
great Jiraiya himself.
NARUTO: Thanks, Iruka-sensei.
-So, how's it going?
-Well, I checked it and
double checked it again.
This is definitely not a
code from the Hidden Leaf.
It doesn't correspond to
any of our algorithms.
But considering
that Jiraiya wrote
this in his final
moments, I wouldn't
think he could come
up with a code that's
too terribly complex.
It's a string of
numbers, so it has
to be a shared key encryption.
-I see, but can you decode it?
-Ahem.
-Hm?
-Frankly, without the key,
it's impossible to decipher
the code.
-The key?
-Yes.
Basically, without knowing the
rules that govern this code,
we simply can't decrypt it.
Unless we can find something
from Jiraiya's life that
could be the key, I doubt
we'll ever crack the code.
-So then, where do you
suggest we start looking?
-I wouldn't know
how, I'm afraid.
But perhaps someone
that was close to him
would recognize it.
Perhaps they would know the key.
-But, given the
circumstances of his death,
he could have come up
with this encryption
hastily, to prevent the enemy
from discerning his message.
We can be sure of nothing.
Consider who he could have
meant the message for,
and go and ask them.
Perhaps then you'll
find some clues.
-Well, that would
be Lady Tsunade.
Or Kakashi-sensei.
[yawn]
-Well, thank you very much.
If I find out anything,
I'll come right back.
-Sure, but I'll be home in bad,
so just come by the house, OK?
I'm heading home to sleep.
What about you, Shiho?
-Oh, well, uh, somebody's
gotta stay behind, right?
KAKASHI: 9, 31, 8,
106, 7, 2017, 15.
-Does anything come
to mind at all?
Did any of these
numbers ever come up
in a conversation with
Jiraiya that you can recall?
-Hm?
-This one.
106.
Master Jiraiya?
-It's easily 106.
-What is?
-106 centimeters.
-No.
That's not it.
-Huh?
-Nothing's coming to me.
Why don't you try Lady
Tsunade or Naruto next?
-I already asked Lady
Tsunade about it.
Well, I guess that
leaves Naruto.
-Aside from the code, I'm
also worried about him.
Do what you can to cheer him up.
-I will.
But don't get your
hopes up too high.
[doorbell]
-Terrific.
He's not home.
-Hey, Shikamaru.
What's up?
What do you want?
-Well, for starters, how
about letting me come in?
Do these numbers
mean anything to you?
Hey.
Naruto.
You still with me, or what?
Naruto!
-Oh, right.
Sorry.
So, uh, what'd you say?
-All right.
You're coming with me.
Let's go.
-To where?
-Just come on.
NARUTO: What?
Why did you bring me here?
-Just wait.
There she is.
-Huh?
Huh?
Kurenai-sensei?
-That's right.
-Were you hospitalized for
eating too much barbecue?
Your stomach's
bigger than Choji's!
-She's pregnant, not overweight.
Oh, boy.
You're still just as
obnoxious as you ever were.
-So, then, you mean she's--
-Shikamaru, you know, you
don't have to come every time.
-Sorry.
No can do.
Asuma made me promise him.
-Shikamaru, what did
Asuma-sensei ask you to do?
-Their child will be my student.
-Huh?
-I'm being serious.
He entrusted me with that.
I heard about Master Jiraiya.
Having lost my
teacher just like you,
I understand exactly what
you're going through right now.
But whining and sulking
won't make things better.
Face it, both of us are way
past that point in our lives.
-What do you mean?
-Asuma-sensei imparted a
lot of knowledge to me.
Some lessons were
important, some not so much.
It didn't matter.
The same for you, right?
An infinite number
of priceless things.
So I think it's time
for us to step up.
-How so?
-To stop being students,
and become teachers.
It's going to be a drag, but
we can't keep complaining.
Eventually, you'll be the
one paying for the ramen,
and someone will be
calling you Naruto-sensei.
After all, we can't
stay brats forever.
Not if we want to
become cool shinobi.
Like the type of shinobi that
Asuma and Jiraiya both were.
-You're right.
Shikamaru, thank you.
-So pull yourself
together, 'cause
you've got some work to do.
-All right.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Comrades move to
decode the message left behind.
Entrusted to Naruto, what is
the key to Jiraiya's encryption?
Shikamaru's intellect
and Shiho's experience
will lead them to
a clear answer,
and at last the hidden
mystery will be revealed.
Next time on Narruto
Shippuden, Decryption.
What was Master Jiraiya
trying to tell us?