Huh?
Hey! Hey Neji, are
you all right?!
(struggling breath)
Yes, I'll be fine.
Just take it easy. I
can use my nose to
sniff out enemies,
too. We aren't relying
on your eyes alone.
Let me take over
for a while. You
go see the Medical
Corps.
There's a medical tent
that's located in the
rear center of every
single company.
Coordinates...
(worried whine)
So, what do you know
of the Akatsuki?
I thought I knew more
than you did, but...
It seems that ultimately,
we were both shinobi
being used for others
purposes.
They only kept us
around because of
our Visual Prowess.
It's the same as now.
The caster of this
jutsu is using us.
Pain, with the Rinnegan,
the Six Paths' power that
you possess, and with my
Mangekyo Sharingan as well,
we could do anything.
The user of this jutsu
intends to take advantage
of my genjutsu power when
the time is right.
Itachi, you have always
been wrapped in darkness,
even back when you were
in the Akatsuki.
You two Jonin Medics
over there! Please,
lend me a hand! We
have to resuscitate
this man quickly!
Now!
Right!
Oink...
Oink! Oink!
But, are you really
sure you can carry
all this?
Oink!
Okay! Okay!
Just stop right
there! By order of
Headquarters, we
Sensory-type shinobi
must verify your
chakra signature
before you can enter!
No one passes without
confirmation!
Yes, I know that.
Hurry up and
check me out.
I'll bandage it.
There. Okay,
you're all set.
Great, thank you!
You take care!
Okay, please send the
next one in now-
Hey, Neji!
There you go! I've
taken care of your
external wounds.
Thank you.
But I think you could
use a break. You need
to sleep and to rest
your eyes.
You shouldn't
overuse them.
That's easier said
than done. My job
right now is to
discern things faster
than anyone else
can and then notify
Headquarters in order
to improve our chances
in battle. To achieve
that goal, I have to
put my eyes to work.
Yeah, I know. But
while you're here,
try to rest.
Thank you.
All right, we have to
begin our rounds now.
The next tents will
be F5 through G3.
Is something the
matter? If you're
still in pain...
(shocked gasp)
(heavy breathing)
Listen! Toyosa,
Takemaru, and Hino
were all found dead
inside their tent!
They were murdered!
This can't be!
What's going on?
We've been infiltrated.
It's the only explanation.
And it appears that
they're specifically
targeting our Jonin
Medics.
But how did they get
in? Everyone's chakra
gets thoroughly verified
prior to them being
allowed to enter
the camp.
A simple Transformation
Jutsu would be noticed.
And only Allied Shinobi
who've been positively
ID'd are let in.
Which must mean that
a shinobi on the inside
is somehow being
controlled by a jutsu.
It must be powerful.
What's happened here?
Neji...
Yes, I see...
If only Allied Forces
shinobi are here, it will
be hard to distinguish
who's responsible.
We don't know who
the suspect is.
Even someone standing
here right now, could
secretly be the killer.
This is sure to breed
suspicion among our
shinobi.
And that's the
enemy's aim.
We Medical Ninja
are critical.
Without us, our
battle strategy
can't succeed.
We're fighting those
under the Reanimation
Jutsu. There's just
no way to confront
them without medics
as backup to heal
the injured.
If we let this paralyze
us now, we'll lose the
battle that starts at
dawn.
Then I'll make sure to
find who's responsible
with my very own eyes.
In the meantime,
we can't neglect
our treatment of the
wounded. We'll continue
to treat them.
We'll just need to
watch our backs.
Especially the Jonin
Medics.
It's almost time.
We're going to have
to start going back on
rounds any minute now.
Yeah, I know.
So, uh, listen, tell
me something. Where
did you and I...
...first meet?
Huh?
Look, it's not that
I'm suspicious of you
or anything like that!
I mean, of course I'm
not! But, I, uh...
It's just... Well,
I...
You are suspicious!
(gasps)
Oh, it's only you,
Neji. Please don't
scare us like that!
Whatever. Where is
Sakura right now,
anyway?
Why? Did something
happen?
I just saw someone
suspicious skulking
around here. I was
tailing him through
the camp, but
then I lost him.
Thinking back, I
seem to recall that
he's been hanging
around Sakura.
Sakura's in tent
number three right
now.
The guy you followed
can you please tell us
what he looked like?
Let's see...
Well, actually...
(gasps)
He looks exactly
like me.
Oh! It's you. You
came back. Are your
wounds bothering you?
(nervous gasp)
No, I...
I feel just
fine now.
But, the thing is.
Well ever since you
treated me, I, uh...
To be honest, I
haven't been able
to stop thinking
about you.
What is this?
It's... a
love letter.
Uhh...
Next time, when I
go back into battle,
there isn't any
guarantee that I'm
going to return
alive...
So...
Thanks for this.
But, I... I have
someone else
already, though,
you see.
Hmm... Sure,
of course.
I suppose that
he's a Leaf, too.
Well, a rejected man
like me has no right
to pry into who you
love. Even a shinobi
like me knows that's
really rude.
All right then,
I guess I should
go now.
I'm sorry...
Good luck, I hope
everything works
out for you. If you
love him...
...then he must be
a good man.
(sigh)
What do you think is
happening? Why are
they going through
such pains to keep us
separate from
the enemy?
Are they not going
to use your genjutsu
after all?
Right now it's
nighttime with
both sides at a
stalemate.
But I'm certain that
soon enough, Madara
will use us to break
the silence.
He's got something
up his sleeve.
But this Reanimation
Jutsu has been brought
into play by Madara's
new ally.
It doesn't figure
into Madara's
original plans.
Is that what's
going on?
Probably.
You doing
all right?
Yes, Neji.
It's easy to get
discouraged. We don't
even know who it is
that we're supposed to
fighting right now.
It's troubling.
I know. We have
to be careful.
Yes...
Are you sure that you
don't need me to take
you to the Medical
Corps? It sure seems
like you could
use it!
You're getting on
my nerves Kiba!
I told you, I'm
going to be fine!
You totally overused
your Byakugan and
could barely stand up!
You don't need to try
and show off in
front of you
subordinates!
Just shut up, Kiba!
What the hell? You can't
tell the difference
between a dog and a man?
Your visual prowess
is supposed to be
your specialty!
Hinata, don't
overextend
yourself.
You don't need to.
My Parasitic Insects
have spread out to look
for the enemy, as well.
Thanks, Shino. I
really appreciate
your concern.
However, I need to
push myself now.
Because this war is
a fight to protect
Naruto! We cannot
lose, no matter what!
By the way, Sakura,
where is Captain
Shizune right now?
Huh? Why? Have you
figured out what's
going on?
Maybe, a little
bit. But I think
we should report
anything, no matter
how trivial. Until
we finally locate
the suspect.
Hm. I think she's in
tent B-2. She's still
busy treating Tonton
right now.
One leg is very
badly sprained.
Well, better it's
a leg than a hand,
I suppose.
Will Tonton be able
to rejoin the battle?
Probably. Tonton can
still weave signs,
since the hand
remains uninjured.
I see. That's good.
Can I ask you a
favor, Sakura?
Would you mind taking
a look at my arm again?
It's still bothering me.
Sure!
Take a seat
over here.
Ahh!
But, how did
you know?!
'Cause pigs don't
have hands! Ya
big fake!
(aggravated grunt)
Probably. Tonton can
still weave signs,
since the hand remains
uninjured.
Are you telling me
that Tonton is just
a pig?!
She tricked me!
Yeah, that's right!
And that makes you
the murderer!
(painful screaming)
Spill it! How were
you able to recreate
Neji's chakra?!
You better tell me
what kind of jutsu it
is if you don't want
me to hit you again!
This Transformation
Jutsu isn't anything
you can possibly
handle! Do you truly
believe that I am
the only clone who's
managed to infiltrate
your ranks?
(gasp)
This is what was in
Captain Yamato's
reports.
A note regarding
Parasitic Clones.
It was thought the
Raikage and Killer
Bee took down Kisame
Hoshigaki. But it now
appears he switched
places with a parasitic
clone or some type of
Transformation Jutsu.
This transformation
replicates the target's
chakra, so it's difficult
to detect. At the Five
Kage Summit, Zetsu of
the Akatsuki suddenly
emerged from people's
bodies. He had absorbed
their chakra.
So this guy transformed
into Neji, of course!
I get it. You use
the chakra that you
absorb from someone,
then copy them and
and their chakra!
Is that right?!
(struggling grunt)
There are just too
many of them!
And they absorb
chakra, too.
She's quite a
smart girl.
Uh, maybe, but then
again, maybe not.
You maybe able to
camouflage yourself
well, but you're not very
good at lying, are you?
What's going on?
We heard some
commotion in here!
Wha-What's this?!
Who's he?!
I have to contact
HQ immediately!
You two secure him.
You were transporting
too heavy a load, Tonton.
(embarrassed snorts)
What happened?!
Sakura has an
emergency!
We have to let
Lady Shizune know!
Finish up, already!
Remember, we're both
gonna be up next for
guard duty.
I totally had to go
more than you did. Look
at my ripples in the
water compared to yours.
Ripples? Are you
kidding me?
Tetsu, you really
'oughta go to, you
know. It's a long
shift.
Tetsu, don't stand
behind me when I pee!
Give a guy a little
privacy, would ya?
Well then, how
about instead, I
make you bleed?
Tetsu?! What the-
Another one!
We have reports from
all regiments! Our
comrades are falling
victim to multiple
surprise attacks!
It's chaos! We don't
know who the enemy is!
What could be going
on?! It's doubtful
that they'd launch
a night raid. Sensory
ninja watch each
camp, and we've
increased patrols.
So why can't we
detect the enemy?!
Is it some kind of
poison? What's the
condition of the
corpses?
All of them received
external wounds! So,
they're physical
attacks!
Someone from the outside
must be using some sort of
control genjutsu, on them.
(gasp)
Itachi...
Itachi Uchiha's the
only one that I know
of that my Sensory Unit
couldn't detect, but
could still use
genjutsu to manipulate
someone like that.
But controlling this
many people at once in
multiple locations is
impossible!
Even for Itachi!
Wait, hold on! There's
word from the Medical
Corps!
It seems that the
enemy is- White Zetsu
has been impersonating
various Allied Forces
shinobi! He's able
to mirror our chakra
imprints!
That explains it.
If one of our shinobi
had his chakra absorbed
during the daytime
battle...
White Zetsu can fully
transform into him!
Well, Shikaku? What
should we do? There's
no way that we can tell
friend from foe, now.
How do we prepare to
fight when dawn comes?
If we don't discover a
way to tell the difference
fast, we will lose
time, plus all our
men will be endangered!
In the end they could
wind up killing each
other by mistake!
So this was White
Zetsu's ability all
along, huh? The battle
during the daytime was
to set up these
secret nighttime
assaults.
That was the enemy's
true motive.
I need to think. Be
calm. I can solve this
if I calmly analyze the
situation!
Sort and evaluate.
Review all of the
intel I have on this
war. What's useful?
What's our counter plan?
Be cool, be calm, but
do it quickly. Calm,
cool, but quick.
Don't let them touch
you. That's because if
they do, they'll absorb
our chakra!
Easier said than done!
How can we take them
down without touching
them?
I just sent out a
messenger owl. So the
sealing corps should
arrive in just a little
while to seal up
this mine.
And what, we're just
supposed to wait
until then?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: White
Zetsu's Trap.
How many of them
are there?!