KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Asuma.
-No!
Asuma!
[theme music]
-Whoa!
Asuma!
-All done here.
How 'bout you?
-Just give me a minute.
-Damn you.
Damn you!
-You son of a-- you're
gonna pay for that!
-Heh.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Dammit.
It's no good.
I'm powerless.
Huh?
Feathers?
-Huh?
What's this?
Do you really think you can
beat me with a flock of crows?
What do you think I am?
-A pitiful attempt
at a diversion.
A black sword.
-Shikamaru.
We're here to help.
-Ino.
-Takes Shikamaru somewhere safe.
-Right.
-Don't let your
guard down, Choji.
-Got it.
-Reinforcements.
[coughing]
-Hey, are you all right?
-Yeah.
But forget about me.
What about--
-Asuma-sensei!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
It's faint,
but his heart's still beating.
-Choji, you've got to rush
him to the Leaf hospital.
Ino, go with them and
use your medical jutsu
to buy as much time as you can.
Get going.
-We're on it.
-Yeah.
-Huh?
-I'm not giving up my bounty.
-Is that right?
-Take Asuma and get
out of here now.
We'll keep these two busy.
-You can fight it all you want.
You're still going to end up
as part of my sacred ritual.
And that's why-- hm?
Come on.
I only need a little
more time, sir.
We're just about to get
to the good part, here.
-We're sealing the Two Tails.
Return at once.
This is top priority.
-Please, sire, just
a few more minutes.
Is that really so much to ask?
KAKUZU: Enough, Hidan.
-Huh?
EBISU (VOICEOVER): Are they
communicating with somebody?
-We'll be back in no time--
so prepare yourselves.
-Huh.
What troublesome
fellows they are.
-Let's go, Hidan.
-That blasted leader of ours.
One of these days, I'll
put a curse on him.
GENMA (VOICEOVER):
They're retreating.
What kind of strategy is that?
-Sensei!
-Asuma-sensei!
-Ino! Choji!
Let's take Asuma
and go right now.
-Oh, no you don't.
You stay right where you
are until we get back.
You hear?
Besides, he's gonna die, anyway.
-Don't worry, we'll be
back before you know it.
-Choji! Ino!
Hurry up!
INO: I'll start
medical ninjutsu.
CHOJI: Right!
-No.
Don't.
-Huh?
-Listen, don't even
bother trying to heal me.
I wouldn't make it, anyway.
I-- I can feel it.
And I bet you three-- you
can feel it too, can't you?
-You shut up, OK?
Just keep quiet.
Ino!
-Right.
-Ino?
INO (VOICEOVER): Here.
And here, too?
Four vital spots.
It's too late.
-I think that I finally
understand now what
the Third Hokage meant.
I was always slow
figuring things out.
I've got-- [cough]
Ino, Choji, Shikamaru,
I've got something I
want to tell you three.
-Stop it, Sensei.
Just stop talking, will you?
-Choji.
You too, Ino.
Listen closely to Asuma-sensei's
words-- his last words to us.
-Ino.
-Yes?
-You're bossy, but you can also
be a compassionate caregiver.
Choji and Shikamaru, they're
both so awkward and clumsy.
Watch over them.
-Yes, sir.
-And make sure that you
don't ever lose to Sakura.
Not in ninjutsu, or in romance.
-I won't.
-And Choji, you're a thoughtful,
loyal friend and a kind soul.
In time, you'll become
a stronger shinobi
than anyone else, so be
more confident in yourself.
-Got it.
-And another thing.
You might consider
losing a few pounds.
-I don't know if it's
possible, but I'll try to.
-And finally, Shikamaru.
With your razor
sharp intellect, you
have the instincts
of a great shinobi.
You are truly worthy of becoming
Hokage, though you'll probably
try avoiding it.
[cough] Since you'd find
the job such a drag.
All those games of Shogi, and
not once could I beat you.
Which reminds me, remember
when we talked about the king?
-If I were picking pieces
to represent Leaf shinobi,
you know what?
I'd say you were
most like the knight.
-OK.
Which one are you?
-Me? Oh, I'm nothing.
I'm just--
-The sacrificial pawn, huh?
-Then do you know
which one the king is?
-Huh?
Uh-- well, the Hokage, right?
-Yeah.
That's what I used
to think, too.
But it's not the case.
-Then who is it?
-You'll know the answer
when the time comes.
Now I'm going to tell
you who the king is.
Lean closer.
-But Asuma-- so then
that's why you--
-I'm counting on you, Shikamaru.
I know I said I
quit, but I guess
it doesn't matter anymore now.
Could you get me
one last cigarette?
They're in my pouch.
[coughing]
-Oh.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm Asuma Sarutobi,
and starting now,
I'm the leader of Squad 10.
I warn you, I'm
strict, so be prepared.
Now, don't start crying already.
So far all I've done is
barely even threaten you.
-It's the smoke.
It's stinging our eyes.
[crying]
WAITER: More rice over
here, and four more servings
of beef ribs!
Thank you for waiting.
-Woo-hoo!
-Slow down, Choji.
I wonder if you've ever heard
of humility or self restraint.
-Glad I'm not
picking up the bill.
-It's not that I'm stingy.
It's not a question of money.
I'm only saying this because
I'm worried about ya.
-Hm?
-If you keep creating this
way, you'll end up getting fa--
-You don't want
to use the f word.
-Fat?
Fat what?
What was he about
to say, Shikamaru?
-Oh, just said fa-- famished.
If you're famished, go on
and order the deluxe meal.
-Ah!
You said that, Sensei?
You mean it, really?
Wow, that is so cool!
Waiter, a deluxe meal over here!
Make that two!
And with extra rice, please!
Oh, man, I am stuffed.
[crying]
-Here Get go.
-Perfect. thanks.
-Who are they for?
-Oh, uh, no one in particular.
Well, uh, see you later.
-Say hi to
Kurenai-sensei for me.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): How?
How did she know?
[laughter]
[crying]
-Shogi?
But it's a such a drag.
ASUMA: You see, Shogi is a game
of countless variations, all
determined by how you
utilize the characteristics
of the individual pieces.
It's a perfect game
for someone like you,
who's always trying to
out think the other guy.
This book will give you
all the basic rules.
The rest you'll
learn as you play.
-What a pain.
Give me 10 minutes,
and I'll have it down.
-You-- you beat me.
-You know, you don't
have to go easy on me.
Really.
ASUMA: You're the only one who
was promoted from this term's
Chunin selection exams.
I don't mind telling you, as
team leader I'm very proud
of you.
Ino and Choji, it'll
be your turn next time.
Congratulations, Choji, Ino.
Well done.
Since Shikamaru
passed last time,
that means all the
members of Squad 10
are now officially Chunin.
And it also means
that I will no longer
be in charge of you guys.
From here on out, you're
leaders in your own right.
Each of you will be
given a new team to lead.
These earrings are my gift to
you, to celebrate your success.
Whatever the future
holds, never forget
you were members of Squad 10.
-Sensei!
[crying]
-It was an end
worthy of a shinobi.
-I still hate those
damn cigarettes.
I can still feel his
smoke in my eyes.
[theme music]
-I see.
-What about Kurenai?
Notify everyone else regarding
the funeral services.
I will inform Kurenai that--
SHIKAMARU: No.
I'll do it.
I'll tell her.
I have a message for
her from Captain Asuma.
NARUTO: Next time, Sad News.