[nervous laugh]
[groan]
Oh yeah... by
the way, Kakashi
Sensei...
(Naruto)
...Who's she?
One of Sasuke's
comrades.
Was. I'm
not anymore.
I'm going to
take her back
to the village
to question her.
Got it...
Back to the
Hidden Leaf
Village then...
(Kakashi)
Naruto! Not
that way.
What are you
talking about,
Kakashi Sensei?
You said we were
heading home and
the Village is
that way.
We forgot
something in
the Land of
Iron...
...Right,
Sakura?
Forgot
something?
Huh??
[gasp]
(Kakashi)
We better go
retrieve it,
don't you think?
Yeah...
Forgot what?
What's going
on?
Ahh!
Oof! I think
I'm gonna hurl!
What do you think
you're doing out
here, Naruto!?
You were supposed
to go back to the
Village with me!
And you made
a hole in the
Inn's floor!
Naruto...
Come on. Let's
get going.
Naruto...?
[gasp]
What!?
Oh, come on!
It was a clone
all along!?
[groan]
I'm so sorry!
You made me chase
you and apologize
to the Inn keepers
...again!!
[sheepish chuckle]
Naruto arrived
here just in the
nick of time to
save Saukra...
...but I guess
you didn't send
him over to help
us out, huh?
No! Of course not!
You ordered me to
take him back to
the Village...
...I wouldn't
disobey you!
Heh!
I see. So basically
Naruto outfoxed you
and left you behind,
is that it?
No! Well...
Uh...
It all worked
out for the
best, Yamato.
If Naruto hadn't
come when he did,
Sakura might be
dead now.
(Kakashi)
And perhaps
me too...
[sigh]
Sasuke's chakra...
It's different
than before...
It was incredibly
dark, and cold.
(Naruto)
Still...
Sasuke is
Sasuke.
You're right.
(Thinking)
Sasuke is
Sasuke...
(Thinking)
Yeah...
Hm?
(Kakashi)
Anyway, that's
what happened,
Yamato...
...so please
forgive Naruto
for what he did.
Ugh. Alright.
I understand.
Release!
[gasping]
(Yamato)
Okay, go on
ahead!
(Kakashi)
And you?
Me, I'm gonna go
back to the Inn
and repair the big
hole Naruto made.
[sheepish laugh]
I'm sorry
about that,
Captain Yamato!
Honestly, Naruto.
We should get
going as well,
you two.
(Thinking)
Sasuke abandoned
me...
(Thinking)
...and now I am
a Hidden Leaf
Prisoner of war.
(Thinking)
I wonder how
Suigetsu and
Jugo are doing...
(Thinking)
Whatever...
Why should I
care anymore?
(Lady Koharu)
Danzo should have
returned by now...
(Lady Koharu)
I wonder what's
going on.
What about the
Five Kage Summit?
Can you explain
the unfortunate
outcome?
(Shikaku)
May I enter?
What is it,
Shikaku?
There's been
some unusual
unrest within
the Foundation.
What kind
of  unrest?
Is it among
the membership?
Yes. They seem
restless and agitated
about something, but
I don't know the reason.
(Foundation Member)
Lord Homura, Lady
Koharu...
Well. speak
of the devil.
Has there been
any word from
Lord Danzo?
No.
We're waiting
for him to
return, too.
My...
Well, they are
restless indeed!
The higher-ups
don't know any
thing either.
What about
Sai? He went
to the Land
of Iron, too.
Find Sai.
Have him report
back on every
thing that's
happened.
We're home
at last!
Hey! Lord Bee!
Yo! It's been
a while, Omoi!
Karui!
Ya been gettin'
by cheerfully,
carefully,
merrily?
No! Of course not!
Not since you
disappeared
like that!
Do you know
how worried
we were!?
Hey, he made
it back to us
alive, so it's
all good now!
Welcome, Lord
Raikage. I'm
glad to see
you back home.
I know it's sudden,
but we must hold
council soon about
the Five Kage Summit.
[groan]
No down time?
We can't afford to
take it easy yet.
Everything's about
to really heat up.
What are you
talking about?
The Fourth Great
Ninja war.
What!?
An allied
Shinobi force
has been formed.
We'll go into more
detail at the meeting.
Also, we're going
to need to set up
an audience with
the Feudal Lord.
Yes, sir.
I'll request
a conference
with him.
Hold on...
Hey, Lord Bee.
What's that?
A prize from my
fight with one of the
Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of the Mist.
It's taken quite
a liking to me.
It never leaves
my side now.
Wow! That's one of
the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen's blades!?
Incredible!
Just as
expected!
As expected,
huh??
Well as expected,
I'm still at someone
else's mercy!
Mercy!
(White Zetsu)
Well, did you
record the battle?
Yes.
And Samehada?
Eight-Tails
took it
with him.
Oh yeah?
So then...
Yes... It
went perfectly.
(Black Zetsu)
You've got to
hand it to
Kisame...
I will declare the
start of the Fourth
Great Ninja War at
the Five Kage Summit.
So, the time has
come, has it?
Once I've declares
war, I suspect the
Eight-Tails freedom
will be restricted-
-and he'll be
confined to
his Village.
Then you'll be
able to hunt
him at your own
leisure.
I'm ready to
go after him
right now. But--
Infiltrate first.
I want you to
sneak into their
midst and obtain
any intel you can.
So, this is to be
an infiltration
mission then?
Use White Zetsu.
Once he touches someone, he
can copy their chakra, and
form an indistinguishable
clone of them.
Just leave
it to me!
But he's weak.
(Madara)
He's useless in
battle but he's
good for deception.
You realize that
if fighting the
Eight-Tails gets
too exciting--
--it's possible
that I could end
up killing him...
But I accept.
Good. I leave
the Eight-Tails
in your hands.
I'm on it.
I've been searching
high and low for
you, Eight-Tails.
You see, my great
blade Samehada
simply loves
powerful chakra--
--and it seems to
have caught scent
of a very
delicious chakra.
I'm sorry, but I
must feed Samehada,
and you're what it
wants to eat!
(Kisame)
But don't worry,
I won't let it
kill you...
(Kisame)
Now then, this is
where things start
getting tough...
(Kisame)
It was good to let
Samehada take a liking
to the Eight-Tails--
(Kisame)
--but I never
imagined it would
share chakra with him.
(Kisame)
Luckily, that ended
up working in my
favor as well.
Their Sensory-Type
ninja haven't
caught on yet.
It's not surprising,
since Samehada takes in
Kisame's chakra and
uses it for energy.
(Black Zetsu)
So they have
the same chakra
signature.
(Black Zetsu)
That's probably what
the enemy is thinking
too...
But I could
have taken on
the infiltration
mission.
You're too weak.
Ultimately, we are
going to capture
the Eight-Tails.
Kisame's the best
choice for this
mission.
Aww...
But you pulled off
that performance
quite well...
It wasn't easy
switching places
with Kisame under
water.
I'm really not
used to that!
(White Zetsu)
Don't you
think you're
overdoing it?
No. I used just
the right amount
of force for the
Eight-Tails.
Alright. Well,
I guess it's
my turn now.
Yes, the rest
is in your hands.
Water Style!
Super Shark Bomb!
Double Lariat!!!
(White Zetsu)
I can undo my body
substitution Jutsu
now, right?
(Black Setsu)
Yes.
It's almost
feeding time.
Come on!
Let's merge.
That's what
you forgot!?
I don't get it.
How can all these
guys just lie
around and sleep--
--while you
were in such a
bind, Sakura!
[nervous laugh]
(Kakashi)
Sakura...
Don't forget that
these guys were
going to help you...
...so apologize
to them after you
wake them up,
alright?
I will.
Wake them?
[groan]
Oh boy...
Naruto, it's my
fault that they're
all fast asleep.
So, please, be
gentle when you
wake them, okay?
Ugh, I'm
still sick...
You're going
to sleep too!?
Listen, isn't Naruto
like this 'cause
--Sakura, isn't it--?
Because of
your poison?
[groan]
[chuckle]
(Karin)
What a carefree
guy! He's
already out!
(Thinking)
He's sleeping
so soundly!
(Thinking)
Naruto seems to
have finally
let things go.
However, we don't
have time to waste
here.
Sakura, you're
gonna have to
wake them up.
[groaning]
Huh? What's
this? Sakura?
[nervous laugh]
Next up is Sai...
I'm awake.
It just wore
off.
I'm sorry, guys!
Hold on, why's
Naruto here?
(Kiba)
Tsk, and he's
fast asleep,
too!
(Kakashi)
I'll explain
everything on
the way home.
Hey! Get up!
Hey!
Uhh, Kiba! Be
a little gentler
with him, would
you?
But... why?
(Sakura)
Do you still
feel nauseous?
I'm fine.
Could you take
a look at this?
(Kiba)
What do you mean?
Looks fine to me.
Then the Curse
Mark really is
gone?
[gasp]
Lord Danzo put a
Curse Mark on my
tongue to keep me from
talking about him.
Danzo? That's
the guy who's
the new Hokage,
right?
Though he hasn't
officially taken
office...
...but what's
your point, Sai?
If the Curse
Mark's really
gone... [gasp]
It seems that
it's true.
Can it be?
Lord Danzo's
gone?
This woman would
know more about
it than me.
Yeah, that
Danzo guy...
Sasuke got him.
Sasuke did!?
Just hold on!
Are you telling
us that Sasuke
killed Danzo?
But why!?
He's Hokage.
That's all I
have to say.
C'mon! Give us
the details!
What is going on!?
I don't have a
clue about what's
happening here!
(Naruto)
[groaning]
Make it an
extra large bowl
of ramen...
I think it's
about time you
got up already!
Now tell us
what's going
on!!
Just wake up!
Naruto!
Okay, the next
step's the meeting
with the Feudal
Lord.
He's waiting
for you now.
Alright. None
of you waste
any time.
Especially you...
...Bee!
Yes, my brother?
Listen, you get
what I'm saying
don't you?
Sure! I got it,
man! I understand!
I'm down with the
plan! Yeah!
Things are
getting
really bad.
Yeah, I know.
A Great Ninja
War.
Basically, it's
just a big, all
out, fight.
They're going to round up
a bunch of newbies like us
who have no real experience
in actual warfare--
--and send us to
the front lines...
...surrounded by
Akatsuki guys that
no one knows much
about...
...it'll mean
certain death
for us!
(Omoi)
Of course we'll have
no choice but to
give it our all...
(Omoi)
...so I'll fight
as hard as I can...
(Omoi)
But the enemy's counter
attack will be relentless
and I'll end up crying...
...And then Karui,
when you die...
Jerk! Don't
kill me off!
Yo, don't
despair my
young ones.
But Lord Bee...
Now now, I'll put
your troubled hearts
at ease, just listen
to me, baby!
I'm gonna lay
down a little
sentimental rap!
Sentimental?
(Kiba)
Damnit! This whole
thing is ridiculous!
I did what you
said! I found
Sasuke, and for
what!?
Calm down.
Don't be
angry, Kiba.
(Kiba)
Well don't act like
you're the only
hero here, Sakura!
(Kiba)
You told us to
keep this a secret
from Naruto!
But Sai went and
babbled it all!
And on top of
which, then
Sasuke got away!
(Naruto)
Kiba...
Just shut it!
Man up and
stop whining!
Hey speak for
yourself! You're
the one who went
on a rant, Naruto!
Huh? What's
that!?
Yeah, Kiba's
right about
that!
You're way too
simple minded to be
trying to form such
complex thoughts!
Sai! What's your
problem!? When did
you ever develop
a sense of humor?!
Why thank you!
I wasn't
being nice!
(Rock Lee)
[laughing]
What Bushy Brow!?
Oh, nothing! You
just seem like
your old self
again, Naruto!
(Kiba)
He means you haven't
grown up at all! Once an
idiot, always an idiot!
(Naruto)
If anyone's an
idiot, you are
Kiba! You idiot!
(Kiba)
Hey! No idiot
gets to call
me an idiot!
Sai! Quit it!
I've had enough
of your laughing!
(Thinking)
Naruto is the
complete opposite
of Sasuke...
(Thinking)
His chakra... It's
so bright, and warm!
(Karin Thinking)
...So welcoming...
[gasp]
(Thinking)
What is that!?
Deep inside him!
A hidden chakra! It's
so dark! It's like...
Sai, you need to
tell us everything
that's happened.
What's up?
Who are they?
ANBU Black Ops
from the
Foundation.
It's as you,
my seniors,
already guessed.
The same reason
the Curse Mark
put on us by Lord
Danzo is gone.
Then Lord
Danzo,,,
is dead.
Yes.
That's....
And his
bodyguards?
Foo and Torune?
I have no
knowledge of
their fate.
They weren't
at the site
with Danzo.
Therefore, if you are
in agreement, I would
like us to discuss the
future of the Foundation.
With the new
Hokage, here.
What!? The
new Hokage!?
Kakashi Hatake
has been appointed.
We'll head back
before you.
(Sakura)
You're really going
to be the next Hokage
Kakashi Sensei?!
[sigh]
Mhm.
Looks like it!
I'm afraid that
I don't really
have a choice.
(Raikage)
I'll get right
to the point,
your Lordship--
--The Five Great
Shinobi Nations of the
Hidden Cloud, Hidden
Leaf, Hidden Stone--
--Hidden Mist, and
Hidden Sand, along
with the samurai of
the Land of Iron--
--have formed
the Allied Shinobi
Forces...
...I ask for your
approval on that.
(Feudal Lord)
But Raikage, Why
such haste?
Rivals have always
existed among Shinobi
from different nations--
--yet you want to
pull your strength
in a military
alliance?
For what reason?
The Tailed Beasts.
Tailed Beasts?
A group that's known as
the Akatsuki possesses 7
of the Tailed Beasts, and
has declared war on us.
(Cee)
The Fourth Great
Ninja War...
[gasp]
Continue...
The remaining Tailed
Beasts are the Hidden
Leaf's Nine-Tails, and
our own Eight-Tails.
We have no
choice but to
cooperate.
Raikage, this isn't a
case of a retainer
wanting to supplant his
Lord, now, is it?
Listen, your Lordship,
we don't even know if
we'll be able to keep the
Feudal Lords protected.
That's how difficult
this battle will be.
Hm?
I understand, Raikage.
I approve this alliance.
Then I request that
you convene a Summit
of the Feudal Lords!
You can't be
serious.
Arranging a summit
like that? Do you
know how difficult
that would be?
Please, Sir,
Alright, very well.
Since I have no
choice... I'll do
as you say.
Thank you.
We have approval from
the Feudal Lords.
Which means that
now we can officially
prepare for war.
Yes. I'll begin
all the preparations.
I just hope that
all the other Villages
are starting to get
ready right away, too.
I've got my
worries about the
Hidden Leaf...
...they may have
Hokage succession
issues...
And the Sand. The
Kazegage is too
inexperienced.
Don't worry about the
others. Just focus on
preparing our own people
for all-out warfare.
[crowd cheering]
What is going on?
I'm not sure!
Yeah!!!
(Crowd)
Yo all you young
ones out there! Blast
your worries away!
Knock em all out of sight!
I got a rap song
for y'all, and
it's filled with
passion, baby!
(Crowd)
Yeah!!!
Listen up! Master
Kinchan polished my
style and mixed in more
passion! It's enka rap!
And this one's
called "Gosaku"!
Thanks for
listening!
(Crowd)
Yeah!!!
Yeah!!!!
(Raikage)
Drop Kick!!
Ahhhh!
{grunting]
You haven't learned a
single thing, have you!?
No, I attest.
Your kick's the
best. Now let
me rest...
(Gaara)
The Akatsuki is
certainly strong.
(Gaara)
But the true strength of our
Allied Shinobi Forces,
unparalleled in history--
(Gaara)
--is unknown. If we
unite the power of all
our Shinobi, I believe
(Gaara)
--we can counter
the Akatsuki
effectively.
(Gaara)
Above all, we must
win this battle, or
the world will end.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Five
Great Nations Mobilize"
(Gaara)
Begin preparations
for The Great War!