What is it?
I see...
Huh? There's lots and
lots of shinobi?
Well, according to
these birds...
There's a war going
on, is that right?
[affirmative grunt]
We need to find Sasuke
before we get mixed up in
this whole ridiculous
conflict!
Hidden Leaf Home Watch
Unit One reporting. We've
completed our patrol
of the eastern sector.
No incidents to report.
Hidden Leaf Home
Watch Unit Two.
We patrolled the western
sector. No incidents to
report.
Roger that! Unit One will
now go and patrol the
northern sector.
Right! And Unit Two will
head for the southern
sector.
You all do your best,
Konohamaru.
We will! You guys,
too, Watase! See ya!
It kinda feels like we're in
the battle, too! It's sort
of exciting!
Yeah, it feels like
the real thing!
This isn't some kind
of game, you guys!
If people like those
wrestlers and boxers show up
again, we have to protect
the Hidden Leaf
Village, you got it?!
Yeah!
You bastard! I'm
going to kill you!
What was that scary
voice, Konohamaru?!
You're gonna pay!
That's the Intel Division
over there. Of course!
It's the prisoner!
Prisoner? Who is it?
Big Brother Sasuke's partner
from the Akatsuki or The
Taka or something.
But I'll forgive you!
Let's go. It's okay.
Come on, you guys.
You bastard! I hope
you suffer and die!
But you're so handsome!
[giggling]
But still!
Who do you think you are!
How dare you try to kill me!
[cough]
Karin... if you're slow enough
to get taken hostage, then
you're just a burden.
Why that little--!
You're an idiot!
But I still want you!
No!
That idiot tried to kill me!
There's no forgiveness for
that!
But he's so handsome!
What is she doing?!
It's that picture she
brought with her.
She's been in there talking
crazy to it again. Poor
thing...
She must've
suffered so much.
Oh, wait... Do you mean
that picture of Sasuke?
[giggling]
Aren't we supposed to
confiscate that thing?
We tried!
But she went nuts!
Completely wild!
She's a lot quieter with it,
so we let her keep it.
Anyway, it's just a picture.
Okay then, no harm done, I
guess. You want to play a
quiet game of cards?
Sure.
[giggling]
Boy, it sure would be great
if Sasuke were here at this
hideout.
After all this
place is special.
Orochimaru's favorite spot.
Hey! Sasuke! Are you here?
The size of this
hideout is ridiculous!
[painful grunting]
What's wrong?
It's nothing. My head
just started hurting.
Oh, man is he gonna go
on another rampage?
Sasuke, Karin and Jugo...
Hebi, Taka or whatever...
I'm the only normal
one among us.
Suigetsu...
Yeah, what is it?
You know, there's something
about you that's always
bothered me quite a bit.
Oh, yeah?!
Well, I'm always concerned
about you, Jugo. Your
presence is thrilling.
I'm here because I made a
promise to Kimimaro.
Why are you here? Are you in
Team Taka just to cause
trouble with Sasuke and
Karin?
Why, huh?
Yeah, why are you here?
You wanna know why?
It's you. I knew you'd come.
You being here must mean
that you killed Orochimaru.
That's right.
But never mind that for now.
Let's get you out of there.
Aaaah, free at last!
Thank you, Sasuke.
Suigetsu, you're the first.
Now come with me.
What do you mean, "the
first?" Who are the others?
There are two others: Jugo
of the Northern hideout, and
I'm also getting Karin of
the Southern hideout.
I understand why you'd pick
me, of course. But choosing
those two is making me
wonder about you, Sasuke.
Do you ever shut up? Come
on, get dressed. We're
leaving.
Can I ask you
something Sasuke?
What is it?
Why are you dragging
a team together?
Because I have a goal...
...and having a team will let
me reach that goal faster.
Since I joined with
Orochimaru...
I've been preparing for when
this would happen. I have
monitoring a number of
shinobi.
Carefully selecting the
most powerful ones who
catch my eye.
Huh...
Now that I gathered my
perfect team...
Here it is. This is my plan.
My ultimate goal is to kill
Itachi Uchiha of the
Akatsuki.
But to succeed, I'll need
help from all of you.
Of course, it's your choice.
Karin. You said you had
something else to do.
Decide.
Oh. Uh.
Well, on second thought...
That other thing isn't
really important.
Karin, just be honest and
tell the truth, would you?
The only thing you're really
interested in is being
around Sasuke, isn't that
right?
What?! No, that's
just ridiculous!
It's ridiculous how
ridiculous that is! No,
you're ridiculous!
What I am, is right! I mean,
why else would you get all
flustered like that?
How rich!
I know the truth, you know.
About how long ago you
wanted Sas-
Agh!
Suigetsu, don't get
Karin worked up.
Didn't I tell you to
try and get along?
All right, I will.
I'm sorry, Karin. Truly.
Now, look, you may hate it...
But I'm not going anywhere.
I'm sticking like glue to
Sasuke.
At least I am, until I can
locate one of the Seven
Hidden Mist Blades.
I'm on the hunt for Kisame
Hoshigaki's giant sword, The
Shark Skin Samehada.
Then it's all set.
Now that we're a team, we
all move together, as one.
And from this point on, we
four will be known as the
Hebi.
So, why?
Heh!
[chuckling]
I would love nothing better
than to break both of those
two losers up for good!
I just want to break
everything in two! I can't
help myself! Especially when
it comes to those guys!
I see. You're reprehensible,
you know that?
Huh?
Yeah, right. You kidding me?
You want to talk
reprehensible? Then Sasuke's
the worst of all!
What do you mean?
Come on! After he'd defeated
Itachi, I thought that he
had reached his goal and was
finished.
We are no longer the "Hebi."
From this day on, our team
will be the "Taka".
And Taka has but one goal.
Our mission...
...is to destroy
the Hidden Leaf!
I mean, give me a break!
Teaming up with the Akatsuki
to capture the Jinchuriki of
the Eight Tails?
He got us mixed up in a
ridiculous mission.
Are you the Jinchuriki host
of the Eight Tails?
That's "Lord Eight Tails,
sir" to you.
No, wait. You say, "Are you
Lord Jinchuriki, sir?" Got
it?
I'm here to capture you.
Suigetsu, take the right.
Jugo, take the left.
Karin, behind me;
cover my back.
Then I'll sting ya
like a killa bee!
Sasuke!
And end my flow
with a killer blow!
[gasp]
[attacking yell]
Sasuke, the three of us
will take care of him.
The fact is, this guy is
incredibly strong. So we'd
better go at him as if we
are trying to kill him.
That might be our best
chance of taking him while
he's still alive.
[roar]
A monster ox So this is
his true form, huh?
[roaring]
I'll take over, you guys!
Just run while you can!
Thanks, Suigetsu...
Let's go, Sasuke.
[angry growl]
Yo, I'm not letting y'all
get away this late in the
game, fools, ya fools.
[growling]
All of us nearly died! But
somehow, we managed to
finish the job.
But the next thing you know,
we're crashing the Five Kage
Summit and we're in a battle
royale with the Raikage
and the others!
He's trying to blind us!
No!
Jugo, relax. It's
just a genjutsu.
You saw through the
genjutsu, but it's too late!
And when the fist fight was
over, he brought down the
ceiling without giving a
damn about us!
Whoa! What the
hell's he doing?!
Thanks to him, we ended up
as prisoners of the Land of
Iron.
[annoyed sigh]
To be honest,
I hate you all.
I lead you idiots to water,
and you splash it in my face
instead of drinking it.
That's why--
[angry roar]
Agh! A rampage! Whoa,
is he out to kill me?!
Just die!
You know, I think I
hate you the most of all!
What is this?!
I've been here so many times
before, but... I never knew
this existed.
[gasp]
Is this... one of Orochimaru's
secret rooms?
Huh?
What?! This is?! Orochimaru
planned all of this?
This intel. It could change
the whole outcome of this
war!
[coughing]
What are you doing?
This scroll might be a very
nice little present for
Sasuke.
We've found something
incredible down here, purely
by chance!
[coughing]
That punch is water under
the bridge for right now,
Jugo.
[coughing]
Come on, Jugo,
snap out of it!
We've got to find
Sasuke, and fast!
The birds around
here are uneasy...
Over there.
Let's go.
You wasted no time
coming after me.
What are you doing out here?
Or not, as it seems to be...
[gasps]
I passed by two towns on my
way here, but they were both
completely deserted.
It seemed really odd to
me. Do you happen to know
anything about what's
going on?
First, you're gonna have to
answer our question! Now how
come you're outside?!
What happened to our
original that was with you?
If you hate it so much that
I'm outside now, then you
ought to capture me.
After all, you do
outnumber me this time.
Hold on, you didn't kill our
original, did you?!
With this many of you, now.
I hope it's more of a
challenge.
[attacking yells]
Susano'o!
[screaming]
Sharingan!
This is a war...
Our orders...
Take down the enemy...
So Madara's done it.
He's begun his plan.
Capture Killer Bee
and apprehend Naruto
Uzumaki, as well.
Sasuke...
If you attack the Hidden
Leaf, I'll have no choice. I
will fight you. Don't doubt
that.
Until that day,
save your hatred.
Then you can throw
all of it right at me.
I'm the only one who can
handle all that hate.
Do you understand?
[chuckle]
Fine by me. But at least
I'll take you down first.
If you don't hurry, more and
more will join up with him
one after another...
[chuckle]
It's because you know the
pain of solitude like I do...
It's that very pain that
makes you and I stronger,
Naruto.
Which means if I can just
break that bond, I'll be
able to achieve even greater
strength!
Did you forget, Naruto... just
what true strength really
looks like?
I feel the Uchiha at last
being freed from this
rotting Shinobi world.
And besides, isn't what I'm
doing exactly what you Leaf
Shinobi have wanted all
along?
You've always snubbed and
put down the Uchiha clan. So
I'll simply help erase the
Uchiha from your memories...
By killing all of you.
And then, by destroying...
The Hidden Leaf Village!
Severing all bonds with the
Hidden Leaf will be the
ultimate purification!
And that shall lead to the
Uchiha's true restoration!
I think that it's time for
me to come and find you.
It's time to cut you down.
You're not Hidden Leaf
Village shinobi. You're not
part of the promise.
[screaming]
These are good eyes. I'm
quickly getting used to
them, Brother.
When you possess
the same eyes...
Come back and face me!!
The scenes burned into these
eyes that used to belong to
my brother...
They're disgusting and sad.
They weigh me down. But
that's only fitting...
Just you watch, brother!
There's no shinobi alive
today who's as powerful as
the First Hokage, Hashirama
Senju.
Everyone says that.
Just like they think the
Sage of the Six Paths'
power was a fairy tale.
It's time to show them that
all the myths were real!
No one can stop
this Reanimation!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "A Will of
Stone."
I guess I'm too old
to do anything...