- Let's do this and shut up
this witless pain in the ear.
-That is the plan.
-Check it.
I'm not witless, yo.
I got super rhymes and
charming flow, fool.
-Oh, what a joke.
Not to mention, he's got
absolutely zero rapping talent.
-Hold up, fool.
No need to be cruel.
-Be quiet!
[mumbling]
-I'm feelin' hella fine.
I just wrote the fattest rhyme.
Thank you.
Now, I'll play with you tools,
you teensy weensy baby fools.
-Watch out, Sasuke.
This guy is clearly
used to handling blades.
He's no ordinary ninja.
-Ha ha ha.
Quickly take a look 'cuz now
I give you a taste of my hook.
[theme music]
-What...
-The hell... What's that stance?
-Sasuke, are you all right?
- What is up with
those moves of his?
I can predict his
line of attack.
-Hm.
SUIGETSU: The Chidori blade.
He's going to use
something that's
impossible to defend against.
-No way.
He blocked it.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): He can
stream his chakra too.
- First, I'm gonna float
and fly like a butterfly.
Then I'll sting you
like a killer bee.
-Sasuke!
- And end my flow
with a killer blow.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
He also uses
lightning style, my weakness.
-Hold on.
-Yah.
-Sasuke.
This is not good.
Here, quickly.
Hurry up and bite me.
Do it.
Ahhh!
KILLER B (VOICEOVER): He
funneled the lightning style up
through his body and
deflected my attack.
That's how he avoided
mortal injury.
And that woman
possesses the ability
to heal others letting
them suck her chakra.
-Thanks for that, Karin.
-Yeah, sure.
- Sasuke, the three of
us will take care of him.
The fact is this guy's
incredibly strong,
so we better go at them as
if we are trying to kill him.
That might be our best
chance of taking him
while he's still alive.
-This battle's not over.
Gotta stop these foes.
Check it out, yo!
-Gotcha.
Sasuke, now.
Just hit both of us.
-Chidori.
-Ahhh!
-He's gone.
Where is he?
- They're puny,
but so bothersome.
I'm done.
Goin' home.
Gonna get my drink on, son.
Yeah.
-Karin.
-I know.
He's over there.
KILLER B (VOICEOVER): So she's
also a sensory type, huh?
-Got no choice.
Here comes the Eight.
Woo!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Here it comes.
It's just like that day.
- Oh, he's the first to
dodge my Eight Tailed
form since my brother.
-Damn it.
He's after them.
-Yo, I'll squash y'all flat.
Split splat.
-You all right?
-I think, more or less.
- It definitely has
speed and power,
but he only moves
in a linear fashion.
So with my eyes, I should
be able to see him coming.
Karin,
I need you to read his chakra
and anticipate his
moves for me now.
Stay on him and keep
relaying his location to us
at all times, you understand?
- If you really think
you can keep up.
-No, look out!
KILLER B (VOICEOVER):
Those eyes.
The Sharingan genjutsu, huh?
Can't move.
-Lariat!
-Sasuke!
What?
What is this?
- His neck and chest have
been seriously injured as well
as the organs beneath.
He's beyond our help.
- In a way, Sasuke is
like my reincarnation.
-Hang in there.
-Karin, don't worry.
I'll do it.
You don't have enough
chakra to deal with this.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): What
are you going to do?
-I'm going to merge with him.
I'll share my body and chakra.
Since his body is compatible
with my curse mark,
it should work.
- In order to break the hold
of the genjutsu, what you need
is a partner that can agitate
their chakra and wake you up
from it.
My partner is the Eight
Tails that's inside of me.
Genjutsu doesn't work
on Jinjuriki hosts who
have control of
their tailed beast.
You're losing.
Then I obliterate, and then
y'all, I shall annihilate.
My true mode as the
Eight Tails abode
is now going to unfold, yo.
It's a monster.
See, I told ya.
Whole transformation, yo.
Oh ya.
Eight Tails will make you pee
your pants, you little ants.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Such chakra.
Is this even possible?
-That's Eight Tails?
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
A monster ox.
So this is his true form, huh?
-Just me and my bones.
I was born a glorious longhorn.
Wee!
KARIN (VOICEOVER): His
chakra's off the charts.
We'll die if we stay here.
-Jugo, are you done yet?
KARIN (VOICEOVER):
Thank goodness.
He's alive.
-Good, you're conscious.
Come on, you've got to get up.
Jugo, we need to...
KARIN (VOICEOVER): He
turned into a child?
Why?
-Jugo.
-I won't let you die.
You're a memento of Kimimoro.
-Come on, hurry.
We gotta run.
-Weee!
You're a water style shinobi.
I knew it.
You think you have
the advantage?
-I'll take over, you guys.
Just run while you can.
-Thanks Suigetsu.
-Let's go Sasuke.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
Who would have
thought I'd end up
sacrificing myself again just
to save their hides?
- Yo,
I'm not lettin' you get away
with that this late in the
game, fools.
You fools.
-That really doesn't look good.
- That looks like...
is that Lord Killer B's?
-Wh... what is it, Sensei?
-Let's go.
-Yes sir.
But that's...
- Killer B. Why'd he
transform into Eight Tails?
I thought Lord
Raikage had forbidden
him to take that form.
-Wait.
Look over there.
He's been fighting with someone.
-Those robes, Akatsuki.
The same ones who
kidnapped Yugito.
- I can't believe
Suigetsu's all messed up.
We can't escape now.
What are we gonna do?
Hurry up and bite me.
Do it.
-I won't let you die.
You're a memento of Kimimoro.
-I'll take over, you guys.
Just run while you can.
-Haaa!
KARIN: He's coming.
Amaterasu.
JUGO (VOICEOVER): So those
are the inextinguishable black
flames Sasuke spoke of.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
SASUKE: Karin, run!
Damn, the black flames.
-It's too late for her now.
We need to get
away from here fast
before we get caught in it too.
-Wait, Jugo.
-We can't.
SASUKE: Karin.
-What?
But how?
-Jugo, grab Karin.
Hurry!
- The black flames
have been extinguished.
How is that possible?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I
was able to extinguish
the black flames of Amaterasu.
Is this another power of
the Mangekyo Sharingan?
In which case... Ahhh.
- Eight Tails,
seems he's barely alive.
SASUKE: Then we did
manage to take him down
without killing him.
Let's grab him and go.
- No, don't tell me they
actually defeated Lord Killer B?
-It must be some mistake.
We've got to go help him.
- Those guys down there are
members of the Akatsuki,
don't be hasty.
Wait, is that...
-What is it?
A Uchiha crest.
-Uchiha?
- It would be useless
for us to engage them,
so we should report
this to Lord Raikage
and let him deal with it.
- When he here's what happened
to his younger brother,
knowing how he is,
he'll be furious.
- You must be
exhausted after that.
You've lost
Orochimaru's curse mark
and you haven't yet healed
yet from battling Itachi.
-I know.
I really didn't expect that we'd
have such a fight on our hands
today.
But it's done now.
[theme music]
LADY KATSUYU: I've been
waiting for you all to arrive.
KAKASHI: Lady Katsuyu,
what are you doing here?
LADY KATSUYU: It's an emergency.
Mount Katsuragi's
barrier has been broken.
KAKASHI: What?
What of the Tsuchigumo clan?
LADY KATSUYU: Time
is of the essence.
Under the secret treaty
made by the third Hogake,
Team 7 will immediately head
out to the location with Yamato
as team captain.
NARUTO: Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, "Wanderer."
It's an all new mission.