NAGATO: Yahiko died,
and from then on, I
took over as the leader
of our organization.
Since that day,
countless other comrades
have fought and died in battle.
So many others.
One by one, they kept dying.
The peace-obsessed citizens
of your Land of Fire,
they paid a small commission
to the Hidden Leaf,
adding to their war fund.
And the citizens of
the Land to Fire,
knowing full well the truth,
still falsely proclaimed peace.
But the peace that you
large nations enjoy only
exists because of the sacrifices
forced upon smaller nations.
What you all like to
call peace is only
won through violence against us.
In order for some
to live peacefully,
others must die in war.
As long as humanity
still exists,
then hatred will
also exist with it.
There cannot be true peace.
Not in a world as
cursed as this one.
All that Jiraiya-sensei
said about peace
is nothing more than
wishful thinking.
I've told you my story,
just as you asked.
Now let's hear your response.
[theme music]
-I've told you my story,
just as you asked.
Now let's hear your response.
JIRAIYA: But I truly believe
that eventually, the day
will come when all people
will understand one another
and live in harmony.
NARUTO: You may be right.
Truth is, I think
the same way you do.
-I see.
NARUTO: But even if
I understand you now,
that doesn't change how I feel.
There's no way that
I can forgive you.
I still hate you.
-Then you want to
settle things with me.
-I do.
But Pervy Sage believed
in me and wanted
me to continue his quest.
And for those reasons, I
choose to believe in him
and to follow what he taught me.
So that's it.
That's my answer.
That's why I'm not
gonna kill you guys.
-After everything
that's happened,
you still believe in
Jiraiya-sensei's teachings?
Very well, then.
You've given your answer.
And you expect us to wait until
you somehow magically transform
this world to a peaceful place?
No, never!
How can I believe in Jiraiya's
words after all of this?
There will never be such
a thing as true peace!
Not as long as we're forced to
live in this accursed world.
Peace is impossible.
Impossible!
-Well then, I'm gonna
break that curse one day.
If there's truly such a
thing as peace in this world,
then somehow, I'll find it.
I'll never stop looking.
-You're-- But that's--
-Nagato.
What's the matter?
-Those words.
It can't be.
-That's right.
You know them.
All of those words are taken
right out of this book.
The very first novel that
Pervy Sage ever wrote.
He was seriously trying
to change the world
with his message.
And in the back of it,
he wrote about a student
who helped provide
him with inspiration.
It was you, Nagato.
-But--
-Hm?
-Sensei.
-Yeah, what's up?
-Do you have a minute?
-Sure.
I was trying to do
some work on my book,
but I've come down with a
bad case of writer's block.
Yeah, I figured I'd
take a little break
and get a bit to eat.
Mm.
So, what's going on?
YOUNG NAGATO: Well,
I've been thinking
about all the
hatred in the world.
Do you remember when
we talked about it?
-Sure I do.
And what ideas have you
come up with so far?
-Real peace.
I still haven't figured
out how to attain that yet.
But I vow that I'm going to
break that curse one day.
If there's truly such a
thing as peace in this world,
then somehow, I'll find it.
But more important
than how to achieve it
is the power to believe
that it will happen.
-You know, that is
an excellent thought.
You may very well be right.
A-ha!
-What is it?
-Well, thanks to
you, I think I'm
going to be able to
write a brilliant novel.
-Now, first things first.
I've got to come up with a
name for the main character.
The hero of the story.
Hm?
Now I can return home
without any worries.
The three of you are all on
your own from here on out.
These past three years,
you've done a great job.
Hey, don't cry, Yahiko, or
people will call you a coward.
Konan, You're gonna grow
up to be a real beauty.
I know it.
I hope we meet again someday.
This land is destitute, so
there will be hard times ahead.
But from this point
forward, you three
can change the
fate of this land.
Nagato.
You three have really grown up.
Wouldn't you agree?
-Thank you, Sensei.
-Come on now, stop
crying, Yahiko.
I'm sure we'll see
him again someday.
-I miss Sensei.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-You ready to give up yet?
I'm starting to tire
of our game of tag.
A smoke bomb.
[clanking]
-Just give up.
-Can I say one thing?
-I don't wanna hear it.
Just give up now.
You give up on trying
to make me give up.
-Even if you do take me
down, another assassin
will attack the village.
As long as we're cursed to
live in this world of shinobi,
then there cannot be any peace.
Ever.
-Well.
I'm going to break
that curse one day.
If there is such
a thing as peace,
then somehow I'm
going to find it.
And I'll never stop looking.
-Who-- Who are you?
-My name is-- My name is--
-Perhaps, Nagato,
you're actually
the reincarnation of the
Sage of the Six Paths.
I have the feeling
that your eyes
may realize the
hopes of that sage.
Another sage once
gave me this prophecy.
He declared that
one of my students
would bring about a great change
to the world of the shinobi,
and that I would be the one
to guide that revolutionary.
I believe that you are
that revolutionary.
And also, I believe
in you, Nagato.
-You are the savior
of this world.
I know you can do it.
-More important is the power
to believe that it will happen.
JIRAIYA: Amazing, Yahiko.
Nice catch.
I'm impressed.
-I know, right?
-Tastes great,
doesn't it, Nagato?
-Yeah, it sure does.
-It looks delicious, dear.
-Now eat up, Nagato!
-OK.
-Instead of trying to rule
the world through pain,
I wish you'd move past
it and use your power
to create peace
in a positive way.
-And for those reasons, I
choose to believe in him
and to follow what he taught me.
The name of the
hero in this novel.
His name is--
-I'm going to break
that curse one day.
If there is such a thing
as peace, then somehow,
I'm going to find it, and
I'll never stop looking.
-Who-- Who are you?
-My name is--
-His name's Naruto.
-The name of the
hero in this novel.
His name is-- His name's Naruto.
-Listen.
My name is a precious
heirloom that
has been handed down
to me by my master.
There's no way
that I'm just gonna
give up and dishonor
my master's gift.
I will become Hokage, and I will
bring peace to the Hidden Rain.
I will!
I'm asking you to believe in me.
NAGATO: Why should I?
How can you stand
there and tell me
that you will never
change your mind?
Do you really think you will
never stray from that ideal,
no matter how much
pain befalls you?
You think you will always
believe in yourself?
Can you guarantee it?
How can you possibly
have that much faith
that life won't change you?
-I've felt pain too.
You're not the only one.
[music playing]
-There's still pain buried
deep down inside of me.
And there's no telling
what kind of pain
I may face down the road.
But if I stop believing just
because things get difficult,
if the hero in this book
were to change who he is,
then it would become a
whole different story.
It sure wouldn't be the
story our master left behind.
And it would be about Naruto.
The thing is, I can't write
books like our master did.
And so any sequel has to
come from the life I life.
That's why, no matter how
much pain my own path brings,
I'll keep walking.
because that's who Naruto is!
-If the hero ever changes,
it'll be a different story.
We are sibling students,
sharing the same sensei.
We ought to be able to
understand each other.
When I said that to you
earlier, I meant it as a joke.
You really are a curious fellow.
You remind me of myself
when I was much younger.
-Nagato.
-I wasn't able to continue
believing in Jiraiya's ideas.
Nor could I keep
believing in myself.
But, you give me a
vision of a future that
shows a different path
from the one I've walked.
I think I shall believe in
you after all, Naruto Uzumaki.
I'll use Gedo art
of Rinne Rebirth.
-Nagato-- You can't.
-No, Konan.
It's all right.
All I'm going to do
is make a new choice,
even though I'd all
but given up hope.
-What is it?
What kinda jutsu are you doing?
-Those who possess the
Rinnegan can perform
all of the jutsu the
Six Pains used and are
said to exist outside the
realm of life and death.
Nagato's visual prowess
itself is the jutsu
that presides over
life and death.
He is the Seventh Pain.
-Gedo--
KONAN (VOICEOVER): If
he performs the jutsu
with his current
level of chakra,
Nagato will-- He's willing to
go that far for this child.
This mysterious child
has changed Nagato.
-It appears to have ended.
-I see.
And how did it turn out?
-It's as my vision
foretold, although I never
thought two of
Jiraiya's students
would be the
children of prophecy,
and that the both of them
would become the ones to bring
about great changes
to the ninja world.
Perhaps it's possible that in
that moment, when Jiraiya chose
not to give up, all
this became preordained.
Who would have thought
that that book would really
become the key to
changing the world?
[theme music]
KONOHAMARU: Iruka-sensei!
IRUKA: Konohamaru!
Thank goodness you're safe.
-Glad you are too, sensei.
-Ebisu-sensei.
Are you hurt?
-It's nothing.
Konohamaru saved me.
But never mind that.
What is this strange phenomenon?
-I don't know what is happening?
NARUTO: Next time on
"Naruto Shippuden."
Hero of the Hidden Leaf.
What just happened?
[theme music]