‐Well, are we getting close?
‐At the rate we're
traveling, we'll
get there about noon tomorrow.
And will you please stop
asking me the same question
every five minutes?
‐What, me?
‐Come on, Lee.
Try not to be so
impatient, will you?
‐How can I not be impatient
when at this very moment
our comrades might
be in desperate need
of our assistance?
Let me remind you that our
mission is to provide them
with hot‐blooded backup
as quickly as possible.
‐You wasting all that energy
doesn't make us go any faster.
‐Shizune, can I
ask you something?
‐Hm?
‐It the enemy's
already made contact
with the Three‐Tails, that
means they must have developed
some kind of jutsu that
will control it, right?
‐That's right.
Most likely some
form of sealing jutsu
that we're not familiar with.
But if we get there in time, we
can use our own sealing jutsu.
We can't allow them
to beat us to it.
‐Then we all agree.
We should increase our pace
to twice, or even better,
three times our current speed.
‐Oh, brother, not
this speech again.
‐Actually, he has a good point.
We could pick up
the pace a little.
Pakkun, lead the way.
‐OK, if you insist.
Try to keep up, everyone.
[owl hooting]
‐Huh!
[rubble falling and crashing]
There.
That should do it.
Well, Kakashi,
what do you think?
‐(DISTRACTED) Yeah, looks good.
‐Hm.
You've, uh, been staring at
that page for quite a while now.
You want to tell me
what's on your mind?
‐Huh?
Oh, this and that.
Yamato, don't you
wonder just how
those guys were planning
to capture the Three‐Tails?
‐That's a good question.
It is a tailed beast, after all.
Our enemy's Crystal
Style is powerful,
but I doubt it's enough to
restrain a tailed beast.
But perhaps it
works in conjunction
with something else?
KAKASHI: Even so,
they didn't manage
to delay us for very
long back there.
It's hard to believe they could
have come up with something
so big in such a
short amount of time.
‐That's true.
But then, what about the little
boy Naruto saw by the lake?
‐Yeah, that's been
bothering me, too.
Almost as much as the prospect
of facing that Crystal Style
user again.
‐Where are you going?
‐It's time we came up
with a plan of action.
‐Kakashi Sensei.
‐Sorry to interrupt.
(LOUDLY) Hey, there's
something I want to discuss.
‐All right.
[music ‐ Joe Inoue, "Closer"]
‐‐[gasp] You know, I‐‐
I found
a place where I can return to.
It's with you.
‐Where you can return to.
Ah?
‐Where is he?
He's got to be around
here somewhere.
‐That one.
A Leaf Ninja again.
He could prove troublesome
if I let him get any closer.
Don't go anywhere, OK?
‐OK, we're here to relieve you.
‐Right.
Nothing unusual
to report so far.
SAI: Uh, Sakura?
‐What is it?
‐Sai, what are you
doing over here?
You're supposed to
be at your post.
‐Uh, yes, I'm aware of that.
But do you know where Naruto is?
‐Huh?
He's not on watch?
‐No, he isn't.
I was supposed to relieve him.
‐Don't tell me he headed
back to camp early.
‐I don't think so.
If he had, I would
have run into him.
‐That's right.
Even Naruto would
wait to be relieved
before [gasp] No way!
‐If that wave had
carried him off,
there wouldn't be any
trace of him left behind.
All right.
‐You should feel honored.
I've come here to take
care of you personally.
‐Why, you‐‐
‐Poking around all by yourself?
I'm the worst person
to could have picked
to try and spy on,
my little friend.
‐Just as I thought.
This is definitely
not another illusion.
‐You're right.
Jade Crystal Blade!
[shing]
‐Die!
Aaaaaaghhhh!
[clang]
‐If you really want to
know, I wasn't spying.
I was looking for
someone, that's all.
The kid who was with
you, where is he?
‐Nnnghhhh!
[crystal shatters]
‐Answer me!
What have you done with him?
‐Where is she?
I should‐‐ I have to go.
‐What?
Naruto disappeared?
YAMATO: Could he have come
under attack by the enemy?
‐Doubt it.
I didn't pick up the scent
of any intruders at his post.
As far as I can
tell, Naruto just up
and took off on his own.
‐Well, it did seem like there
was something on his mind.
But to go off like that‐‐
‐(SOFTLY) Naruto.
YAMATO: [sigh] Well,
whatever happened,
we have to find
him, and quickly.
‐We'll fan out and‐‐
‐No.
The worst thing we can do is
go wandering around recklessly
in this fog.
Yamato and I will
follow Naruto's tracks.
Summoning jutsu!
‐You summoning me?
Well, this is a surprise.
‐Pakkun's on a mission, so
it's up to you, Biscuit.
I need you to find
Naruto for me.
‐Gotcha!
‐Shino, Kiba, and Hinata,
search the perimeter of the fog.
Sakura and Sai will do
aerial reconnaissance.
ALL: Right.
‐And stay together.
Do not act alone.
NARUTO: So where is that kid?
Is he all right?
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Why is he
so interested in Yukimaru?
Of course.
He saw it all.
‐Stay out of it.
It's none of your business!
‐I'll make it my business!
[clang]
‐Pathetic!
‐Listen, you, I'm
taking that kid back,
so just hand him over!
‐Taking him back?
What are you talking about?
He never belonged to you.
He was always one of us.
‐No, he wasn't always with
you, and if he is now,
it's only 'cause of me,
'cause of my big mouth
and all the stupid
things I said.
‐What stupid things?
‐Hey, thank you.
You're the one who taught
me about going home.
‐Uh?
Hey.
‐Yukimaru, what are you‐‐
‐Wherever someone's
thinking about you,
that's the place you belong.
‐No!
Stay where you are!
‐I wanted to thank you
again for teaching me that,
because I found where it
is, the place I belong.
Right, Guren?
‐What have I done?
‐Get away from him!
‐Don't move.
‐So you had another shadow
clone up your sleeve.
‐What are you doing?
‐Hey, so what was
your name again?
Yukimaru?
My name's Naruto.
‐Naruto?
‐What's going to
happen, Yukimaru,
is that you're
going to come home
with me to the Leaf Village.
‐Why is that?
‐Because there's no way
you belong with this woman.
Trust me on that.
She follows Orochimaru,
and Orochimaru's
a guy who thinks only of
his own twisted ambitions.
He'd sacrifice anything and
anybody to get what he wants.
And as far as I'm
concerned, anyone
who'd serve a guy like that
is just as bad as he is!
‐But Guren's the one
who thinks about me.
She's always kind to me.
She always protects me.
This might be hard to
understand, but trust me,
all she's doing is using you.
‐Just shut up!
[smash]
‐I'd never let you take
him with you, you hear me?
‐Really, Guren?
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
Someone's coming.
More Leaf Ninja.
NARUTO: Well, I'm not leaving
him with you, no matter what!
[boom]
‐Hexagonal Crystal
Shuriken Wild Dance!
‐Take this!
[rubble flying]
‐Not going to let you‐‐ agghh!
KAKASHI: Naruto,
stay where you are.
‐[sigh] Subject secured.
NARUTO: I gotta get the kid!
Let me out of here!
‐Forget it.
Anyway, they're gone.
‐Huh?
Nngh‐‐ darn it!
[rumbling]
‐She's a follower of
Orochimaru, and he
would sacrifice anything and
anybody to get what he wants!
[smash]
‐Thank goodness, Guren.
Are you hurt?
Oof!
‐Will you stop pestering me?
‐There's no way you
belong with this woman.
Trust me on that!
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Little punk.
The next time we meet‐‐
GOZU: I'm sorry if I
upset you, but it's
just that I'm glad you're OK.
‐Uh‐‐ [whimpers]
‐Yukimaru!
[panting]
[wood creaking]
‐Guess I'll be heading back now.
‐Right.
Thanks, Biscuit.
[shoom]
What were you thinking, Naruto,
going off all on your own
like that when you knew the
woman we've been chasing
was still out there?
It was foolish.
‐But I was just‐‐
it was that kid.
I was trying to find him.
‐There is no excuse.
If we hadn't come along,
you might not even
be alive right now.
You put the whole squad at risk
by giving in to your emotions.
By sending you on this
mission, Lady Tsunade
put her trust in you, a
trust not given lightly.
‐OK, you're right.
It was wrong of me.
‐[sighs]
‐Listen, we're facing a
dangerous and unpredictable
enemy.
If one of us goes off
half‐cocked on his own,
it puts the rest
of us in danger.
Just try to remember that, OK?
‐I will.
‐So should we get
back to the others?
‐Sure.
By the way, Naruto, this boy
you say you saw by the lake‐‐
‐Yeah?
What about him?
‐Something's been troubling me.
Tell me more about
this encounter.
[water lapping gently]
‐Uh?
Guren, am I happy to see you.
You're OK.
Sorry I wasn't more help, but
I couldn't use my search net
so near the lake.
‐Just forget about it.
So I see we're all here, still
at full fighting strength.
I have to admit there's
at least one of our party
I wouldn't mind losing.
‐I'm blessed with the
luck of the wicked.
We have that in common.
He's a bit weakened,
but he be all right.
‐He's exhausted.
Let him rest.
‐Unfortunately we haven't
really got the time
to hang around here resting.
‐Hm.
‐I just can't figure
out why these guys would
be dragging a little
kid along with them.
They've already got
all they can handle
trying to snare that
Three‐Tailed beast.
‐What do you mean,
Kakashi Sensei?
‐Well, what if he possesses
some special power that
works against the Three‐Tails?
‐Wait a minute.
Come to think of it,
there was something
he did that seemed to make
the Three‐Tails stop moving.
‐Bingo.
‐You trying to tell me a human
was controlling a tailed beast?
‐Don't ask me how.
But remember, we're dealing
with Orochimaru here.
In any case, they're
obviously using this boy
to help them capture
the Three‐Tails.
‐If he's such a key
part of their plan,
it seems imperative that
we do something about him.
‐What do you mean, something?
Like what?
‐Like grabbing him at
the first opportunity.
‐Grabbing him?
‐Yeah.
I'm thinking if they
don't have the boy,
they can't capture
the Three‐Tails.
‐And I seriously
doubt that Orochimaru
will be satisfied with
merely capturing the beast.
He's trying to find
a way to create
a jinchuriki that
he can control.
The boy's ability to
interact with a tailed beast
will help him achieve that.
The boy's simply a
tool toward an end.
‐I won't let that
creep get away with it.
‐My sentiments exactly.
And what's more,
I'm sure they'd like
to study this boy's power
back at the Leaf Village.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Well, it all depends
on Lady Tsunade's reply
[shoooom]
‐Hm?
‐(SHOUTING) Naruto!
‐Sakura?
[pow]
[boom]
‐So is that what
they call tough love?
[rubble falling]
‐We could lecture him
all day, but her way
is probably more effective.
‐Don't worry, Sensei.
I gave Naruto a good talking‐to.
‐Did he say he was sorry?
(WEAKLY) Sorry.
I am so sorry.
‐Never mind him.
Good news.
‐There are more Leaf Ninja?
‐Our enemies are
quick to respond.
No doubt they're coming here
to seal the Three‐Tails.
‐That can't happen.
The beast belongs
to Lord Orochimaru.
‐I agree with you.
And that, Guren, is
why you must make
sure Yukimaru restrains
the Three‐Tails next time.
‐But the boy, he's still so‐‐
‐Don't worry.
If we just accelerate
his recuperation a bit,
I'm sure he'll do fine.
[low buzzing hum]
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Is he going
to give him that drug again?
‐Yukimaru still seems
awfully weak to me
from the last attempt.
Will he be all right if we
force him to do it again?
‐We'll soon find out.
‐Mmph.
‐Oh, don't look at
me like that, Guren.
The boy is just a
means to an end.
Unless we can make use of him
now to capture the Three‐Tails,
there's really no point
in allowing him to exist.
You know that.
On the other hand, what
if you push him too hard
and he collapses and
the whole plan fails?
How do you suppose
that will make me look?
‐Guren, I want the plan to
succeed as much as you do.
And that's precisely why I‐‐
[shring]
‐You annoy me.
You stick your nose in my
business once too often.
‐Guren, really.
‐If the main thing is to
keep the Leaf from sealing
the Three‐Tails,
well, then I'll just
destroy the Leaf and
all the Leaf Ninja.
[whoosh]
‐You two have an argument?
‐I don't like him,
and I don't trust him
either, the four‐eyed jerk.
Is he trying to kill Yukimaru?
RINJI: Hm?
‐What is it?
‐Nothing.
I'm just a little
surprised you care so much
about what happens to the kid.
‐The kid?
Don't be an idiot.
All I care about is successfully
completing the mission.
That's it.
‐Completing the mission, huh?
NARUTO: Reinforcements?
Here?
Who?
SAKURA: Huh.
Just you wait and see.
‐That's it, I can't
run another step.
‐This is what you meant
by reinforcements.
INO: So, Naruto.
‐Huh?
INO: I hear you messed up again.
‐It is all right.
Recklessness is a sign of youth.
‐Shut up, Lee.
Stop encouraging him!
‐Hey, hey!
Look who's here!
[MUSIC ‐ DEV PARADE,
"BACCHIKOI!!!"]
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): These are
Lady Tsunade's instructions.
Our new mission is to seal
the Three‐Tailed beast.
Additionally, we are
to secure and protect
this child, who's clearly
connected to the Three‐Tails
in some way.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): So we'll
be dividing into groups‐‐
a stealing unit, a
lookout unit, and a unit
to take on the
enemy's crystal style.
‐Sounds good.
But, uh, who's gonna
be on which squad?
‐Yeah, about that‐‐
I've got an idea.
Next time‐‐ "Regroup!"