[sigh] Whew! All done!
[chuckle] Everything's nice
and clean now!
Wow, you really cleaned
Naruto's room?!
That's right! Naruto's been
away for three whole years,
and it really needed it!
His place is spotless!
It's ready to welcome him
home and so are we!
[gasp]
Naruto, is that you?!
Hm?
[chuckle]
Been a while, huh, Sakura?
Hey! Naruto!
Sexy Jutsu!
[scream]
Well, what do you think? Not
too bad in the curves
department there, huh!
Konohamaru... I'm not that
scrawny litle kid anymore.
And you shouldn't be using
jutsu like that either.
Huh?
Just face it, that jutsu
is totally weak!
Now step aside and get a
load 'a my brand spankin'
new pervy Ninjutsu!
Are you kidding me?!
We don't see each other for
two years and you pull a stunt
like that?!
Oh man, I thought that you'd
be a little impressed, at least.
[laugh] Well, my training
involved way more awesome
jutsu than that!
That's just what I'd expect
from you! Everything's going
exactly according to plan!
Plan?
[chuckle]
Wow!
No way! What happened?!
Isn't it obvious? I
cleaned your entire
house until it sparkled.
Thanks, Konohamaru!
You're such a great guy!
Yup! And I don't even expect
you to teach me a new jutsu
in return either!
I have no ulterior
motives at all!
Right. Could you be
more obvious?!
But okay! I'll teach you an
absolutely amazing jutsu!
All right!
Hold on. First, let me
just put my things way.
Huh?
Isn't that your old outfit?
Yeah, it doesn't really fit
me anymore, but I just can't
bring myself to part
with it...
So you could say, it's kinda
like a treasure to you!
When you put it that way,
it's embarrassing.
[chuckle] Hm.
The new jutsu I'm gonna
teach you is like nothing
you've seen before; it's
totally different and cool!
I wonder what kind of
Sexy Jutsu it is!
Well, c'mon! Show
me already!
The first step's "rotation"!
Whoa! So we're going to
add motion to it, huh?!
That's right. And the
second step's "power!"
Oh, I see: attack with
the risqué! Awesome!
And then third, comes
the final step.
Seriously?! There's
still more?!
Containment!
Oh-ho! The most points go to
the best cute expression, eh?!
What are you talking about?!
Quit kidding!
But it's a Pervy
Ninjutsu, right?
No way! It's better!
It's an A-Rank jutsu, and
it's seriously hard to master.
This is a super advanced
Ninjutsu that combines
Chakra rotation, power,
and containment.
It's called Rasengan!
So awesome!
But I don't understand
what happened!
How'd you do that?!
[chuckle]
Don't you worry about that!
Because I'm gonna teach
you, Konohamaru!
And, you can do this jutsu
even if you're stupid!
No kidding?!
Huh?
Stupid?!
To complete this training,
you just have to make it
through three steps.
First, we need a
water balloon.
A water balloon?!
The "gaah!" is first you,
then you "bam" it!
Oh! Wow! So, how'd
you do that?!
What do you mean?
I just explained it.
First, you have to "gah" it,
then "bam" it to burst it!
Uh...
I said...
You just "gah" it and, then,
you "bam" it! Simple, right?
Uh...
Okay, do your best,
Konohamaru!
What, seriously?!
That's it?!
You're just gonna
leave, like that?!
I have to go train
with Sakura now.
Yeah, but...
Come on, Konohamaru.
Don't be a baby.
Uh...
Like anything, you've got to
learn by doing and feeling.
Oh...
And besides, I have faith
that you'll be able
to do it, no problem!
Big Brother Naruto...
All right, I'm gonna do it!
Just watch me!
The next time you see me,
Big Brother, you're going to
get a really big surprise!
Okay, first I go "Gaah"
and then "bam!"
"Gaaaah" and then "bam!"
Lady Tsunade!
Terrible news!
Now what is it?!
We've just received a
message! The Hidden Sand's
Kazekage has been abducted
by a group called the Akatsuki!
[gasps]
Gaara was...
Team Kakashi, I'm hereby
assigning you to a new mission.
You're to go to the Sand
Village at once, find out
what's going on, and
keep us informed.
You're to remain there and
follow their orders.
Give them any backup they need.
Right!
"Gaaaah" and then "bam!"
I can get the water
inside rotating, but...
There he is! Hey,
Konohamaru!
Huh? What? Oh, hey, what's
going on, you guys?
It's terrible! Some guys
called the Akatsuki
kidnapped the Kazekage
of the Hidden Sand!
The Kazekage? Big
Brother Naruto's friend?
Yeah! And Naruto just left
as part of the Hidden Leaf
Village support team!
Huh?
Isn't it awesome?! The
minute he gets back, he gets
picked for no less than
an S-rank mission!
Cool, huh?! Even though he's
only a genin, just like we are!
Hm?
[grunting]
"Gah" and "bam" ú aren't
enough to figure this thing out!
Hey! What are you doing,
anyway, Konohamaru?
How long have you guys
been watching?!
[giggle]
So this is the reason for
your weird yells, huh?
Come on! They're not weird!
Well, maybe they are a
little bit embarrassing.
I mean, "gah" and "bam"-
what do they mean?!
Maybe you just need to
take a step back from
it for a little while.
Huh? I don't understand...
Well, Naruto tends to do
things intuitively, by feel.
But not everyone learns
in the same way.
Mhm...
Yeah, you could try
it a different way.
I guess...
Okay, the first step is
rotation, and he said I'd
have to learn it
by feeling it.
That's it!
Okay! Konohamaru!
Let's just focus on
practicing that part first!
Uh, yeah, okay!
Anyway, that's what's up.
Can you please help?
To be honest, I don't really
understand what you're
talking about.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, absolutely!
Please, I have to do this if I'm
gonna learn this new jutsu!
All right, then, you got it!
You sold me with your
determination.
Come on!
[attacking yell] Huh?!
Fang Over Fang!
[screaming]
So did it help, Konohamaru?
Uh... Everything just...
Well, okay, then! On
to the next thing!
Please, help us!
All right, if
that's the case.
Bring it on!
Try this out! Human Boulder!
[growling]
Next one!
Okay! You ready, Konohamaru?
Go!
Wait a second!
Uh... Huh?
Aw, but Hinata this is to
help Konohamaru
learn a new jutsu!
No, it isn't that.
It's just I can't
use rotation!
Huh? Well, okay!
Hm.
I understand.
Hold on! Understand what?!
8 Trigrams Air Palm!
This doesn't make any sense!
Idiot! Idiot!
Next up is...
Hold on! I can't keep doing
this kind of thing, you know!
You're right. But have you
figured anything out?
Nothing. Not at all...
Did Big Brother Naruto tell
you anything else?
He said he taught me
everything I needed to know.
But the only thing that he's
ever really taught me was
the Sexy Jutsu.
Oh! Wait a minute.
What's up?
Well he dissed my Sexy Jutsu,
and he told me that it was
totally weak.
So maybe if I escalate the
sexiness, it'll all come
together nicely!
Konohamaru! That's
gotta be it!
Really? You think?
But the problem is how are
you going to go about making
it even sexier than
it already is?
There's only one man who
holds the key to that!
Anyway, that's it!
I see. So you're practicing
a new jutsu, huh?
Yeah, but I've hit
a really big wall.
Please, Sensei! If I'm gonna
be able to get over it, then
I'll need your help!
[whimpering]
It's so unlike Konohamaru to
be this determined. Well, I
have no choice but to do
my best to help him!
Of course I'd be happy to
help you, Konohamaru!
What exactly is it that
you want to know?
About sexiness!
I want you to teach me
everything that you know
about sexiness!
Oh. Yes, of course. All I
know about sexiness.
Wait, what?! Did you say
sexiness just now?!
Big Brother Naruto
told us...
[laugh]
If Old Man Jiraiya is the
all-out-in-the-open pervert,
then you're the closet
pervert, Ebisu Sensei!
Gah! That Naruto and his
big, dumb mouth!
You're the only one I
can turn to, Sensei!
I need that secret side of
you to come out in the open!
But, I, uh...
We found something,
Konohamaru!
What?!
Looks like a secret
textbook!
No!
Hey, look! There's more!
Here, too! Oh,
and over here!
Wow, there's so
many of them.
This is great! It's like a
secret library or something!
And look! There's stacks of
textbooks in the attic, too!
We should check under
the floorboards!
Thank you, Ebisu Sensei!
This is way more than
we ever imagined!
Now you can continue
your training!
That look...
Behind those eyes, the
eyes of an innocent girl.
The feeling lurking
there was contempt!
Awesome! There's so
many different kinds!
Boy, closet perverts don't
mess around, do they?
I think I'm starting to see
Sensei in a different light.
The problem now is that
there are way too many of
them to choose from.
How about this one?
[chuckle]
Well, it does have
the rotation part.
I'll try it! Here goes!
[giggle] Uh...
You're not good at that.
Anyway, time to do
the real jutsu now!
Right! Here goes!
This time...
I'll do it!
Idiot! Idiot!
[giggle] So?
How's this, huh?!
This time, I'm gonna
do it for real!
I saw something
go bloop just now.
You're right! It's different
than it was before!
Hm...
Wait, that's right, when
Big Brother Naruto burst it...
Oh! Wow!
The surface of his
balloon went bloop like
this one just did.
Then, go on! Try it again
but with some more finesse!
Okay! Yeah!
I'm gonna do this!
[grunting]
How was that?!
No way, you actually
did it, Konohamaru!
I mean, it's a little
different, but...
Okay, so we get to move on
to step two now, right?
Oh, man! [giggle]
It was worth it, training
hard while you were away in
the Hidden Sand,
Big Brother!
Yeah! On to the
next step, then!
Now, for the second step.
Use this!
A rubber ball?
Yeah, exactly! What you do
is "guh" it and then "boom"
it to burst it!
That's it!
Not this again! Although
I expected it!
That's really all I get
about step two?!
Now, don't be like that,
Konohamaru.
This jutsu...
Just has to be learned by
doing it, is that it?
See? You get it!
But I wish I could stick around
and supervise your training.
Uh... You just got back and
now you're going out on
another mission?!
From this last mission, we
learned that Orochimaru had
a spy embedded with Sasori.
Orochimaru?!
So, then?
If things go well on this
next one, we might find a
clue about Sasuke.
We're gonna lure the spy out
and make him talk!
He's so casual about it, but
this mission has to be an
A-rank or higher.
Big Brother really
is amazing.
Huh?
Don't worry! I've got
natural talent, so I don't
need your help, Big Brother!
Good luck on your mission!
[chuckle] Thanks!
I'm gonna keep
getting better, too!
I'm gonna do this!
This jutsu's really hard,
isn't it?
You've gotta get the power
right. You said that's what
this step's about.
[sigh]
Man, the rubber ball is a
whole lot harder! Because
it's empty, I can't
get the feel of it!
So what should we use
as a reference this time?
I'm positive that
this one's better!
No way! It's this
one for sure!
But my mom says that
guys have a weakness
for ones like these! They
can't help themselves.
Come on! For power,
it's gotta be this one!
Actually, I think this woman
looks like the strongest.
We just can't seem to agree
on this one, can we?
I think I get it. So, you
feel that you lost some
respect due to something
that happened recently.
That's right, and I just
don't know what I
can do about it now.
It's okay. Everyone
makes mistakes every
now and again!
You know, there's always a
chance to put things right.
Thank you, Iruka.
I say for now, we should
just calmly support
Konohamaru and his progress.
[chuckle]
There you are!
We've been looking for you!
Well, well! What perfect
timing! We were just
talking about you!
Please, Ebisu Sensei,
there's something else we
need you to help us with!
It's really important!
What, me again?!
This is perfect! What a
wonderful opportunity!
This is your chance to
regain their trust!
You guys!
Don't tell me!
Wha-?!
[giggle]
What do you think?
I'm not holding anything
back! [chuckle]
Which girl do you think...
...Is the best?
Please! You gotta tell us!
[screaming]
What?! Such depravity!
In public?!
I won't tolerate this, this...
...this, immoral behavior!
What in the world are
you fools up to?!
But we had to!
To master my new jutsu,
I had to find a way
to make it even sexier.
Is what he's saying true,
Ebisu Sensei?
I've no idea!
However, a jutsu is like a
secret weapon for a ninja!
It's not something
you use recklessly,
not even a Sexy Jutsu!
You hold it in until the
last minute, and, only then,
release it! And that's
how you get the
maximum result out of it!
Hold it 'til the last minute,
and only then release it?
Huh?
Ebisu Sensei!
What's the matter now?!
Is this what you're
talking about?
Hold it with "guh", then
burst it with "boom!"
[screaming]
Well, that definitely
looked powerful!
Awesome!
Leave it to Ebisu Sensei
the closet perv!
I can do this! Hold it,
with "guh", then
burst it with "boom"!
[power yell]
Boom!
Uh?
Hey! It expanded right
away that time!
Yeah! It's working!
But it still didn't burst!
Big Brother Naruto is just
so far ahead of me!
Even now, he's out there
trying to get stronger.
So I will, too!
Ouch!
Are you okay, Konohamaru?!
This is bad. Your hand is
a mess from all of that
compressed chakra.
I'll take care of
it right now.
It was bound to take its
toll on you. You've been
training for days
on end, you know!
Damn it!
I wasn't strong enough to
bring him back. Next time,
with my Wind Chakra, I'll be
able to surpass Sasuke!
You're so cool,
Big bro Naruto!
And that is exactly why
you're my rival!
So how are you
doing, Konohamaru?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Naruto's Rival"
Here I go! Hold it in with a
"guh!" and "boom"!