[street chatter]
[gasp]
Wood Style!
What?!
Stop!
That girl is crucial to
capturing Orochimaru!
How do you know?!
Gotta said so
before he died...
[gasp] Gotta is dead?!
No! You have to run!
But--!
Please, listen! Come with
me! We'll escape together!
Kinoe!
This is as far as you go!
[gasp]
Yukimi!
Yukimi, no!
Kinoe! Do you have any idea
what you're doing right now?!
Stop, Kinoe!
Will you break the rules
like Orochimaru and
betray the entire village?!
Just for her?
Why Yukimi?!
Why does Orochimaru
have to have her?
It seems getting a
transfusion from someone
with that ability
lets you become smoke
for a short time.
If that's true, it
would make it easy
to cross the border.
However...
Yukimi...
You are the only one who...
...can help Lord Orochimaru.
What are you talking
about?! Hey!
We are all of no use...
...we have to offer young
Yukimi's blood to Lord
Orochimaru.
He died right after
he said that.
That's so--!
Gotta...
[painful grunting]
[cheering]
Lord Orochimaru
helped our Clan survive.
But still, that doesn't mean
we live only for his sake.
No! Tenzo!
You must bear
it, Yukimi!
We are not able to
live for the present.
We live for the next
generation for their lives!
So they can bask in the
sun, feel the wind, and
laugh without worry.
We live for that day. That's
why Lord Orochimaru's
research is so important!
Tenzo! No!
Yukimi...
Are you seriously...
...betraying Lord
Orochimaru?!
Without the help of
Lord Orochimaru, our
clan has no future.
That's why Tenzo and
Gotta were willing to
give up their lives
for the greater
good of the whole clan.
Orochimaru will go to
that village to find her.
I'm sure of it.
Hm?
[gasp]
She's gone! Could she have
heard us? And gone back?
To her village?
To help Orochimaru?
If he gets hold of Yukimi
with her body being as
unstable as it
is right now...
She's prepared to die.
All that I wanted was
to keep her protected.
This time, I...
If that's the case, then
you didn't break the rules.
Huh?
Let's go and
protect that girl.
Tenzo.
All right!
Where is everybody?
[gasp]
Perfect timing, Kakashi!
Orochimaru's just up ahead,
and he's coming this way.
[gasp] Damn it! Let's go!
Lord Orochimaru?!
How disgusting!
Inferior things
are useless.
Well then, it must be
your blood or nothing.
[gasp]
E... Everyone?!
This happened
because you were gone.
These are the results of my
tests on the Iburi Clan's
bodily transformation
ability.
Only with the blood of the
young will this ability
manifest itself.
I've already gathered
all the other samples.
The only thing that now
remains is your blood.
And then that will
be the end of it.
But that's... You said
you'd help guide us
to the next generation.
[painful grunting]
No... No!
You cannot say no.
I'm going to have your
blood, and that's that.
[gasp]
[chuckle] Now, do not
waste any more of my time.
[gasp] Why can't I?
Did you intend to
wrap me up in smoke?
[chuckle]
Don't you know by
now the prey can never
truly defy the hunter?
[grunt]
[gasp]
[screaming]
Yukimi!
[gasp] Tenzo!
Agh! So you've come to
take her back, have you?
Too bad! [grunt]
[screaming]
[evil chuckling]
Damn it! Orochimaru!
[gasp]
He's losing blood fast.
He can't go far
in his condition.
He's bound to stop
somewhere in order
to take Yukimi's blood.
We'll split up and search!
All right! Leave
it to me!
Is that-?
No way... Are
they guiding us?
You noticed it, too, huh?
Over there!
[yell]
They're on the other side!
Lightning Blade!
Yukimi!
And Orochimaru!
You little brats!
How dare you.
How dare you!
I won't waver this time...
I'll look into your
eyes till the very end,
and bring you down!
You will only fail. Because
you are still inferior.
You will learn your place!
[gasp]
I must tell you... You really
need to grow up some more.
And when you do,
I shall fight you!
Stop, Orochimaru!
[groaning]
Yukimi!
Yukimi, no!
[screaming]
That's Orochimaru's
Curse Mark!
Kakashi, what
do we do now?!
The Curse Mark can only
be released by the caster.
But that's--!
Tenzo...
[gasp]
Ten...
Zo...
[gasp]
[angry yell]
Wood Style!
[growl]
[gasp]
[gasps]
It's Yukimi!
I didn't find Orochimaru.
Nor did I encounter
a strange clan...
Nor anyone from
the Foundation.
[chuckle]
You know what? I'm not
scared of the wind anymore.
I'm gonna walk
straight ahead.
Into my own future.
All I can really do for
now is live by the rules.
But that's okay.
Beause now I know
that I'm capable of
protecting someone.
It's been a while, Kakashi.
He knows how to fight
against my Sharingan.
This was his intent
from the very beginning!
Why do you want to kill me?
It's my mission.
Stop, Kinoe!
Abandon this mission!
To a shinobi, a
mission is absolute!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The
Targeted Sharingan."
I will complete my mission!