‐Wha‐‐ what is this thing?
Is it a jutsu?
‐It's a slug.
‐Lady Tsunade summoned her.
It's Katsuyu.
‐Oh, I'm sorry.
‐I had no idea.
‐Why have you come?
‐Why'd she send you, Katsuyu?
To help us out?
‐That's right.
You see, Lady Tsunade
had been concerned
about the effectiveness of
the sealing jutsu you were
employing earlier
against the tailed beast.
So she sent me along
to bring more chakra.
It should help
the sealing jutsu.
‐We could really use it.
‐Then I'll transfer
it to you immediately.
‐Whenever you're ready.
‐Very well then.
‐That damn Tsunade.
She had to send
Katsuyu, didn't she?
More, we need more
power, Yukimaru.
[screaming]
‐Naruto, stop.
‐Yeah?
What is it?
‐Will I be forgiven?
I mean, will he forgive
me when Yukimaru finds out
that‐‐ that I'm responsible
for killing his mom.
‐That's still weighing
you down, huh?
‐I'm fully prepared
to protect Yukimaru.
It's just that‐‐
‐Think about him, and only him.
He could push you
away, despise you.
None of that should matter.
Don't you see?
It's about him.
Who cares if I'm the
person he can call home.
The only important thing now
is to keep thinking about him.
‐Yeah, I think you're right.
I suppose if you're a fool,
that makes me one too, Naruto.
‐Hey, that's not nice.
Let's hurry.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Yukimaru.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I feel
the power of the Three‐Tails
beneath the surface.
‐It's too big.
I feel like the chakra's
going to explode.
‐Such energy.
Without Katsuyu's
chakra, my power
alone couldn't sustain this.
‐Listen, if the Three‐Tails
falls into Orochimaru's hands
or the Akatsuki's, it will
mean the end of the Hidden Leaf
Village as we know it.
But it won't.
Because the Three‐Tails
is in our hands now.
We're the only ones who
can protect our comrades
in the village from this power.
It's all up to us.
ALL: Right.
‐Listen, Katsuyu.
Is there a way you can amplify
your chakra even further?
‐Yes.
I will try my best.
‐We're going to send that
beast to the other dimension
right now.
‐I don't believe it.
They're still trying to
control the Three‐Tails.
[screaming]
‐Yukimaru.
Come on, kid, rile up
that Three‐Tails spirit.
Drive them wild.
Obliterate those pests
from the Hidden Leaf.
[screaming]
[theme music]
‐Hey, Sai.
Did those guys attack you too?
‐Yeah.
Unfortunately, they
got away with Yukimaru.
[barking]
‐What's this?
‐It must be them.
Let us attack.
‐Hold your horses, Lee.
‐What do you think you
are doing, Ten Ten?
We must go seek our revenge.
‐If we rush into
that smokescreen,
there's a chance
we'll hit each other.
‐Yeah.
Even Akamaru's sense of smell
will be useless in that stuff.
[whimper]
‐The best plan of action is to
just wait and see what happens.
‐Oh man.
I am so frustrated.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
It seems the enemy
is using Yukimaru to
stir up the Three‐Tails.
If it keeps up, Shizune's
sealing team is in danger.
A sticky situation.
And trying to defeat all
these clones is impossible.
It's no good.
I can't dodge them all.
[groaning]
‐It's time.
Binding Smoke Prison.
Well, imagine my luck.
I get to bring down the fabled
Kakashi of the Hidden Leaf.
It'll make surviving all
these years worth it.
What?
‐Although I'm not
as skilled as you,
I do know how to
use shadow clones.
Lightning Blade.
‐Huh?
‐This is bad.
‐You know what they say,
where there's smoke,
there's always fire.
Meet my Smoke Dragon.
‐Smoke has no real form, so Wood
Style is useless against it.
Then I guess I'll just
have to change up my style.
Water Style, Hand of Waves.
‐What the hell?
‐Smoke is a vapor, and by
adding moisture to the mix,
it's too heavy for
you to control.
That how to use Water Style.
Now your jutsu is worthless.
[screaming]
‐Take this.
Silly boy, you
must have forgotten
that I have a third arm.
‐Hm?
‐I'm afraid play time is over.
Don't bother.
‐Spindle Formation.
‐What?
But how?
‐I admit, your jutsu is quite
formidable against my insects.
However, the reason you'll
lose is because of your fight
with Hinata of the Hyuga Clan.
I'll explain.
Hinata, may we speak?
‐Shino, what's the matter?
‐I need you to
tell me everything
you know about that
Crystal Style user.
Any detail will help.
‐Well, unfortunately, her
jutsu had no weaknesses.
And if I hadn't surrounded
myself with chakra,
I wouldn't be here now.
And speaking of
huge chakra, Shino,
you have to be careful
of that slimy guy.
He'll be very difficult
for you to beat.
‐Why is that?
‐Because his entire
body is his jutsu.
That body suit he wears is
filled with pure chakra,
and it allows him to alter
his form whenever he needs to.
When I used my Gentle
Fist against him,
he just twisted his body
away like it was nothing.
‐He overcame your Gentle Fist?
‐When I grazed his
body with my hand,
I accidentally
touched that fluid.
His entire body is
covered by some kind
of dangerous
mucus‐like substance.
‐So you see, I was tipped off.
Which is why this
whole time, I've
been concentrating on
scraping that lethal fluid
off your body.
‐Since we started fighting?
‐Yep.
I focused my attacks
on making that membrane
as thin as possible.
I assumed if I could weaken it,
your jutsu would break easily.
And the way things
look, I was right.
[screaming]
‐It's over?
‐Yeah.
‐Took a while, but‐‐
‐Kakashi‐sensei, there you are.
[bark]
‐You are safe.
‐How about you guys?
Are you all OK?
‐Yeah, we made it.
And Naruto?
How'd he do?
‐We haven't found him yet.
‐I'm sorry about Yukimaru.
‐Mm.
All right then, we should head
out to assist the sealing team.
‐Yes, captain.
‐Yes.
‐Right.
‐Don't forget, we must
recover and protect Yukimaru.
But first, we'll check
on the sealing team.
It seems they're
in a tough battle.
[roaring]
‐The Three‐Tails, it's here.
‐Ino, you don't need to rush.
Just slow down and
focus your mind
on stabilizing your chakra.
‐Right, OK.
[roaring]
‐It's no good.
He's not doing it.
Damn it, it's not enough.
Is that all there is to
Yukimaru's massive power?
Oh well, I guess this
isn't working anymore.
Heh.
I really didn't want to
have to resort to this,
but it looks like
it's my only choice.
You ready to give your life
for the Great Lord Orochimaru?
Here.
‐Yukimaru.
‐Guren, is he all right?
‐You again.
So you two didn't die after all.
‐Wake up.
What's wrong?
Come on, Yukimaru,
snap out of this.
Yukimaru.
Hi.
‐You came back.
Oh Guren, you came back.
It's because I was
thinking of you.
Whenever someone
is thinking of you,
that's the place
you come back to.
‐Yes, that's right.
All you had to do was think
of me, and see, I came back.
‐Yeah.
‐When I was inside
the Three‐Tails,
trapped in some other dimension,
the only thing I thought
of that whole time was you.
And that's why‐‐
and that's why it's
your turn to return
to me, Yukimaru.
‐That makes me happy.
I'm coming back home.
You are my home, Guren,
the place I can return to
that always welcomes
me back with open arms.
[laughing]
‐Yeah, you're right.
At this point, Guren is the
only place you can run back to.
After all, your mother's not
around for you anymore, is she?
‐Stop.
I think you've said enough.
‐Actually, I wasn't
quite finished yet.
Yukimaru, listen to me.
‐Don't you say another word.
‐It's all right, Naruto.
‐What?
No, it's not.
‐It's OK.
We have to face the
truth, you taught me that.
‐Guren.
[laughing]
‐So you're prepared then?
How noble of you.
Listen up, Yukimaru.
One person destroyed
the place you
used to call home,
the same person who
turned that white camellia
red with your mother's blood.
The person responsible for
killing your mother is Guren.
She seems so nice, but
Guren is really a demon.
She hid the truth about
killing your mother
and pretended to be your
friend just to use you.
She's been using
you this whole time.
How does it feel?
Don't you loathe her?
Don't you want to
kill her yourself?
Well, no one's
going to stop you.
As if we could.
Do it.
Use the Three‐Tails
to vent your anger.
Command the Three‐Tails
to destroy everything
in your sight.
‐You bastard.
Shut your mouth.
‐Guren.
‐Yukimaru.
I'm sorry, but everything he
told you about me is the truth.
‐Listen to me, Yukimaru.
The Guren of the past might
have done lots of terrible stuff
in the name Orochimaru, but the
Guren you know is different.
I know for a fact, she regrets
the way she used to be.
She's so sorry, and now
she cares about you.
No matter how much
you hate her, she's
going to keep on
thinking about you.
She swore to me.
‐No matter what I tell
you, or what I do,
I realize that nothing
will ever erase the pain
that I've caused in your life.
If you want me to die
for what I've done,
I won't stand in your way.
But still, if you
could forgive me,
then I‐‐ I swear I'll
protect you forever.
‐Guren.
‐Yukimaru.
Are you saying you
don't despise me?
‐You're a nice person.
Why would I?
After all, we have a connection.
You're the one I can return to.
And don't you see?
I'm the one that you
can return to, Guren.
‐Do you mean‐‐ I promise,
for as long as live,
I will keep thinking about
you, and I will never
leave your side again.
‐And you'll never leave
my thoughts either, Guren.
That's my promise.
From today forward, forever.
I love you, and I always will.
‐Yeah, I love you too.
‐The two of you, together,
you'll never be apart.
‐What a complete farce.
You weaklings can
get all lovey‐dovey.
But a stupid bond like that will
be broken before you know it.
‐Kabuto, it's you.
‐Hello, Naruto.
If you interfere, well
then, I'll kill you.
‐Kabuto, you're behind
all of this madness?
You're going down!
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Kabuto, what
are you people trying to do?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): It's
not just the Hidden Leaf,
all of the Hidden Villages
will soon be thrown into war.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Lord Orochimaru
has set his sights
on a violent future.
That's the plan, anyway.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): You're
just talking gibberish.
Guren, go with Yukimaru.
Protect him no matter what.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): I
can't let you do that.
The two of them
must not be free.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time‐‐ Shattered Promise.