[music playing]
-Right this way.
-Wow.
Is this place for real?
-Careful.
You OK?
-Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
Why you.
-Divine retribution.
-That's it, pal.
-All right.
That's enough.
-You lousy, rotten, no-good.
Come here.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
A thousand pardons, OK.
-I'll kill him.
So help me, I will.
-Careful.
Don't mess with karma.
-(GROUP) Welcome
back, Lord Chiriku.
-Any progress?
-Sir, we've already sent
monks to the remaining three
hidden tombs, those of Lord
Nauma, Lord Tou'u, and Lord
Seito.
We've sent some of our
finest men, my lord.
They'll inform us immediately
if anything happens.
MONK: We've also
instructed several men
to search for the
remains of Lord Kitane,
and temple security has
been tightened just in case.
-Well, I suppose we
can rest easy then.
SORA: Took you all long enough.
CHIRIKU: Sora.
-Boy, nice attitude.
-The jerk.
CHIRIKU: We just got back.
Master, allow me to
introduce the shinobi
we requested from the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-Hello.
I'm Captain Yamato, and with
me are Sai, Sakura, and Naruto.
-Leaf ninja.
Well, that is reassuring.
-Yep.
We'll take care of this for you.
-We're ready to move
whenever you are.
So please just give us the word.
-Thank you.
But we're waiting to hear
from our monks in the field.
For now, you can just follow me.
[theme music]
-The bodies they stole, why
did they even want them?
-Hard to say.
It could be that they want the
information inside of them.
Or maybe.
-Summoning Jutsu Reanimation
First and Second.
So the third one failed, did it?
Oh well, no matter.
-Maybe what they want is to
use the bodies in the same way
Orochimaru did.
But a jutsu like that
takes great power,
and I doubt that's what
we're dealing with here.
-Wow.
So then the four shinobi from
those hidden tombs or whatever,
they must have really
been something, huh.
Hey, what gives?
-They were like no other.
But most of all, they
were good people.
The tombs of Nauma, Seito, Tou'u
, and Kitane lie to the east,
west, north, and south of here
with the Fire Temple resting
squarely in the middle.
They were each members of
the Guardian Shinobi 12.
-Guardian Shinobi, huh?
-I've heard of them before.
-I know the name.
-Are they famous or something?
-Well, the people in the
know are aware of them.
[groan]
-The Guardian Shinobi,
the 12 are an elite group
from all across the Land of Fire
who protect its feudal lord.
-Huh.
But protecting the Land of Fire
is what the shinobi of the Leaf
are for.
-That's true.
We do watch over
the Land the Fire.
That is our purpose.
The Leaf Village
exists to safeguard
the whole of the nation,
not just a single man.
-So you're saying--
-To protect the
entire country, one
must protect the man
who stands at its head.
And that's precisely
what the Guardian Shinobi
12 were assembled to do.
I was a much younger
man at the time,
but even then, I was willing
to put my life on the line.
I joined the 12
without any hesitation.
-Wait.
You mean you were--
-Well, I used to be.
-Just so you two
know, Asuma Sensei
used to be a member as well.
-Ah.
-Asuma.
He's doing well, I hope.
-Yeah.
He's fantastic.
He gave me some awesome training
advice just the other day.
-That's good to hear.
-So that would mean
these hidden tombs that
were broken into, for
you and for Asuma Sensei,
it's personal.
Your friends'
graves were defiled.
-All four of them
died when young,
giving their lives
for the Land of Fire.
Within the 12, a
faction began to emerge
that sought to stage a coup.
It ultimately splintered
the shinobi apart.
-A coup d'etat, an attempt
to seize power and bend
a nation's will closer
to one's own ideals
through any means
deemed necessary.
-Yeah, I knew that already.
-Extremists, all of them.
Their desire to
protect this land
became so all-consuming
to some within the 12
that a radical new
ideology began to form.
-Gotcha.
So you're saying--
-They just couldn't leave
the Land of Fire's well-being
in the more lenient hands
of the Hidden Leaf Village,
better in their minds to
create a new military order
with themselves at the center,
or something to that effect.
-Yeah, or something like that.
-Unforgivable.
-Naruto, keep quiet.
-You're correct.
They meant to dissolve
the Leaf and consolidate
all military force under the
command of the feudal lord.
They had laid the
groundwork for it.
All they needed
was his blessing,
all the while
making preparations
to invade our neighbors.
-What did you say?
-They had no interest in
maintaining the balance
among the five great nations.
They thought peace was
only attainable by uniting
the entire world under
the Land of Fire's banner.
-That's so selfish.
-No matter how many ballads are
written about it, war is war.
As expected, his lordship
became aware of their plotting.
And then--
the six who staged
the coup were eliminated.
However, that day, Kitane,
Tou'u, Seito, and Nauma,
they too fell in battle.
-How could something
like that have happened?
SAI: The people from
those tombs were
Chiriku's and Asuma
Sensei's friends.
Just think if it were
Sasuke, how you'd feel.
It would be like if
you two had lost him
and his body was stolen.
That's true, isn't it?
-We cannot allow the people who
took Kitane's body to get away
with it.
-Yeah.
You have our word.
It's time for the younger
monks' evening training.
-There's that little jerk again.
-Free sparring.
Begin.
-Hm.
-What is it?
-Something's off about him?
-What's the matter with you?
-I can't stand him.
-Bow.
-Thank you very much.
You again.
-So how about it?
Am I doing it right or what?
-Beat it.
Will you?
Don't waste my time.
-Please.
You're the only one
who's wasting time.
I don't know what passes
for training around here,
but it looked like
dancing to me.
-Oh yeah.
NARUTO: You really tick me off.
It's all just a joke to you.
And I don't really know why, but
it's starting to make me mad.
-Naruto.
That idiot.
-Your name's Naruto, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-Let me give you an even
better one for the after-life,
something for the world
to remember you by.
-Remember?
-Naruto, look out.
-Finally getting serious, huh?
That's the kind of
strength you showed me
the first time we went at it.
-Now, you're really
starting to tick me off.
-Hey, take it easy, will you?
We're just sparring here.
Quit freaking out on me.
-Not again.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's with this guy?
His power's lost
all sense of focus.
They're all staring at him.
Those eyes.
That's how they
used to look at me.
-Sora, that's enough.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
I can't stop.
-Oh well, no new name for you.
-What are you doing?
-I just thought
I'd wipe your brow.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
Hey, Sai.
-Yeah.
-What's a name
for the afterlife?
-Well, it's one you're
given after you're gone.
You know for people
to remember you by.
-Oh, I get it.
Kinda like a nickname, huh?
-Uh.
-So it's a sign of friendship.
-Sora.
Hey.
Huh?
-What's the matter?
MONK #2: Lord Nauma's tomb.
[grunt]
-Beast Wave Palm.
Best Wave Gale Palm.
NARUTO: Man, nice jutsu.
Are you working on changing
the form of your wind chakra
too then?
-What are you doing here?
-Huh.
Oh, right.
Thought you'd need a name
for the afterlife too.
How about it?
-All right.
Fine.
Just make sure you
give me a good one.
-Let's see.
What could we call you?
Sora the--
-You idiot.
Give it a rest already.
-What was all that
back in the temple?
-Seriously.
Are you always such a pain?
-Maybe.
I suppose people have
thought that about me
as long as I can remember.
It's the same with you, right?
-So what?
What difference
does it make anyway?
Sure.
People think I'm
a pain, but they
can judge me all they want.
I don't care.
None of that even matters,
because the person
who hates me most of all is me.
Yeah.
That's right.
My power has never been
anything but a nuisance.
-Sora.
-Anyway, nuisance or not, I
can't throw that power away.
I still need it to avenge
my father's murder.
-Revenge, huh?
-A patrol bird.
One of the tombs.
-Naruto, where have you been?
-Sorry.
-They've gotten word from
one of the shinobi monks sent
to Lord Nauma's resting place.
His body's gone.
The tomb is in shambles,
just like the rest of them.
-Are you kidding?
-At this rate, the
others will be.
-My team is ready.
We should go now.
-I'm coming too.
-All right.
-OK then.
I hope those grave
robbers are ready.
They're going to get the
pounding of their lives.
[theme music]
-We've heard from
the Fire Temple.
The last of the hidden tombs
has been compromised, my lady.
-They've got us.
So what's our status now?
-Team Kakashi's on route.
TSUNADE: So it's true then.
They were after the bodies
of the Guardian Shinobi 12,
weren't they?
SHIZUNE: Between
Orochimaru, the Akatsuki,
and Lord Danzo and
all his machinations.
TSUNADE: I know.
So why not start with
the one closest to home?
NARUTO: Next time,
"A New Enemy."