Did you hear? Sai of the
Hidden Leaf sealed away
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen!
Looks like you did well,
Sai. I just hope we can
keep morale up for the
whole regiment.
Sir, the information on
the Ninja Swordsmen we
requested from HQ has
arrived.
While the enemy has stopped
all activity, we should take
this opportunity to gather
as much intel as we can.
It's just as I suspected.
They're all quite
fearsome fighters.
We need to be very
careful with these
two.
We'll be at a
disadvantage in
a group battle.
Huh?
Help!
Help me!
What's wrong?
Ah! It's these strings!
They're controlling my
body! Ahh-ahh!
Strings?
Ahhh!
(struggling grunts)
(painful groan)
(painful moans)
(sinister laughing)
He's crucifying them
alive. And taking
pleasure in their
suffering.
(painful screams)
Stop!
Stop it!
Is this some kind
of game for you?
(shocked gasp)
Ran!
You are unforgivable!
I feel sympathy and pain
for the legends of past
generations who are being
forced to fight against
their will. But you...
You revel in killing.
I hate to think we're
both called shinobi.
Hnnh! Stop being so
full of yourself.
Who gave you permission to
wield the Executioner's
Blade!
That blade belongs
to the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist!
(painful grunt)
(shocked gasp)
An outsider wielding
the Executioner's Blade?!
I don't like
it one bit.
Back off!
He's mine!
Even though they
can't die...
...they don't even
consider each other...
...when they make
their brutal attacks!
I'm gonna kill you
and take back the
Executioner's Blade!
No, I will.
Stay back! I'll
kill you if you
get in my way!
(giggle)
I'm already dead!
(annoyed sigh)
Going up against these
two alone is going to
be rough, but...
It looks like you're
backed up against
a wall, buddy!
Severe...
...Leaf Hurricanes!
I'm Might Guy, the Hidden
Leaf's Noble Blue Beast!
So sorry I'm
late, Kakashi!
Guy, thanks.
Huh? You're the one who
wanted us all to regroup
because it was too dangerous
to work separately in small
platoons! So why are you
doing this by yourself?
And what's more! You're
up against two of the
Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of the Mist!
I wanted to protect
everyone, but I got
in over my head.
I figured as much. Anyway,
we should get her away
from here, fast.
Yeah, thanks.
You know, it's really
kind of creepy to see
you being as grateful
as this. But, still...
I guess you feel that
way because you opponents
are just that strong!
(sinister chuckling)
Where am I?
(gasp)
That man! He killed
all my comrades!
I know. I'm sorry. Listen,
we'll take care of the
enemy. You go regroup with
the main regiment.
But, the two of you!
We'll be fine. While
we're fighting them,
you're only going to
get in the way.
Be careful.
Now then, how dare you
treat our comrades like
they're mere toys for
you to play with!
Careful, Guy. That's
Kushimaru Kuriarare, who
wields the Long Blade
"Nuibari", the Sewing
Needle, and Jinpachi
Munashi, who wields the
Explosive Blade, "Shibuki",
the Splatter. One killed his
master and the other
his brother, along with
countless other cruel acts.
Yeah, and if you get
in my way, I'll kill
you, too!
(chuckling)
I guess you could call
them the cold-blooded
combo. We've got to
stay focused.
That's no problem at all!
You may call them the
cold-blooded combo, but
we're the comrade combo!
Oh...'kay.
And enemy's a match
for the Hidden Leaf's
invincible comrade combo!
(determined grunt)
They're full of openings
to attack. They've
underestimated my speed!
(attacking growl)
He takes big swings
because of that
gimmick sword, but...
(shocked gasp)
His Long Blade!
Guy, watch out!
Huh?
Ninja Art Long Blade!
Stitching Spider!
(painful grunt)
(struggling grunts)
No! This thing won't break!
Ahhhghh!
Explosive Blade Jutsu!
Multiple Explosions
of Death!
Guy!
Forget about me! Go
on, get out of here!
It looks like you saved
me again, Kakashi.
Earth Style!
Multi Mud Wall!
I was far too naive.
I'd read all the data on
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of the Mist, but I never
expected them to take
advantage of being
reanimated so effectively.
Kakashi, did they...
Yeah, they got my eye.
I think it's only
temporary, but still,
this is bad.
Two of the reanimated
Seven Ninja Swordsmen of
the Mist are our enemies,
and we're both in bad shape.
It certainly doesn't
look too good for us.
Guy...
It's okay. I've survived
a lot of tough situations
like this one before.
And there's something
I think of every time.
Three kunai knives and
one paper bomb. That's
all we have left.
And not only that, but
the Hidden Stone's elite
have us completely
surrounded outside.
Yeah, they're sure to
attack us first thing
in the morning.
But, guys! There's no
need for us to worry!
Even if we're short on
Ninja Tools, I still
have my two fists!
All we have to do is
break through the
enemy lines!
Guy, give it a rest.
Your overconfidence is
what got us stuck here
in the first place!
Did you forget already?!
Haven't you learned?!
Don't do anything on
your own!
Why are you being
such a wet blanket?!
I say that we just make
it our next rival challenge
to see which one of us is
able to break through the
enemy lines before
the other one!
Shinobi who defy
orders are scum!
I am your captain! If
you can't follow my
orders, it's time for you
to quit being a shinobi!
I-I just don't want
that to ever happen
again.
Kakashi...
Are you okay?
That's right!
Follow me!
Don't worry, guys.
I'll be a decoy.
If I draw the enemy
off, you'll have a
greater chance of
escaping.
I'm Might Guy, the Noble
Blue Beast of the Hidden
Leaf! I don't die that
easily!
(painful grunt)
I'm not finished yet!
Agh!
No, not yet! I need
to buy more time until
dawn!
(sinister chuckling)
Sorry, Kakashi. I let
you down. Maybe you're
right. Maybe I'm not
suited to be a shinobi.
Kakashi!
We'll talk later! Let's
just get out of here
for now!
I'm all out of chakra.
I can't use any more
big techniques.
Why did you
come, Kakashi?
Because you defied
my orders.
I'm not worthy of
being a shinobi,
am I?
No...
In the Shinobi World,
orders are absolute.
But you defied orders
to save the life of
your friends. And, well,
if I couldn't tell the
difference, I'd be a
failure as a captain.
You mean...
Besides which, I think
that your plan actually
could have succeeded. I
mean, we've been able to
draw the enemy away,
after all. Rin should
have regrouped with the
main squad by now.
So all that's left...
I have to take
care of him.
This is not good, Guy!
Stone Shinobi use jutsu
formulas that cover
a wide area.
Wait! I thought you
told me that you ran
out of chakra!
(powerful yell)
Chidori!
He cut through lightning
with Chidori? But I
thought that he was all
out of chakra!
You all right, Kakashi?
It's strange. I thought
I was all out of chakra,
but then... when I thought
about saving my friends,
it came out of nowhere.
(shocked gasps)
I'll tell you what,
why don't you rest
up a bit. I'll handle
these guys.
But you can't run on
those legs, let alone
fight.
If I can't use my
legs, I'll use my
arms. If I can't use
those, I'll use my
hands or mouth!
I'll struggle all the
way right until the bitter
end to save my friends.
Just like you did
now to save me!
Friends, huh?
You can't see right now,
so don't try to push
yourself, Kakashi!
If I can't see. I'll
sense things with sound.
Or I'll use smell, or
even my skin!
I'll struggle all the
way right until the
bitter end to save
my friends!
So you remember that
time, too, huh? All
right, then, let's go!
Yeah!
C'mon! Bring it on!
(annoyed grunt)
(swinging grunts)
(attacking grunts)
(throwing grunt)
Hm?
(attack yell)
All right, let's do this!
Don't underestimate me!
Ahhhghh!
Hnnh! Well, it seems that
repeating our rival
challenge wasn't actually
a waste of time, after all.
Hm?
Even if I can't see
you, I know exactly
where you are!
And by matching your
movements, I can tell
where the enemy is!
It's like I can see.
Move it!
You move! Or better
yet, disappear!
That's it! I've had it!
I'm going to take care
of you first!
You don't think of
your comrades as
comrades.
So in reality, you
two were never a
match for us.
Just shut up!
(forceful grunt)
Substitution Jutsu?
(shocked gasp)
(attacking grunt)
You idiot! Now
I can't dodge!
(painful grunt)
Did we do it?
Ugh! Damn it!
I'm completely done with
this stupid fight! Now
you're really going to
get it!
Watch out, Kakashi!
Get back!
I'm going to use my
Explosive Blade to
blow up this whole
area!
Hey! We may be
immortal, but if you
do that, we'll die!
Maybe, but we won't
know until we try it!
Shadow Paralysis
Jutsu!
What! Hey, I
can't move!
Captain Kakashi!
Don't worry! I've
brought the Sealing
Team with me!
Hm. So you're able to
see once again, huh,
Kakashi?
Yeah...
Get these two
sealed away
quickly!
Yes, sir!
I just knew it! I knew
you'd be able to avenge
their horrible deeds!
Retreat!
(shocked gasps)
Huh?
You made it just in
time, Guy and Kakashi!
When a shinobi takes the
power that's at his
command and uses it for
his friends' sake rather
than for himself, his
power becomes multiplied
beyond belief.
That's the lesson that
I learned on that day
long ago.
I'm able to produce
unfathomable power when
it comes to my friends.
It's strange...
Yeah...that's right.
I think that this war
is helping everyone
realize that very thing.
All right, come on!
We'd better go look
for the other platoons
now.
I agree.
We'll need everyone's help!
Yeah!
Ameyuri Ringo...
One of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen. She wields the
Lightning Blade, "Kiba",
the Fang.
Who is this Ameyuri
Ringo, anyway?
Stop hiding! Isn't there
anyone here at all who
can send shockwaves
through my heart?!
Ah ha! At last, someone
who isn't afraid to
face me!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Lightning
Blade: Ameyuri Ringo!"
And I won't let
you get away!