[explosion] [screaming]
-How dare those guys
just come in here
and mess up our entire
village like this.
UDON: Konohamaru!
MOEGI: Konohamaru!
KONOHAMARU: Udon.
Moegi.
Just in time guys.
Come on!
It's up to us to save the
Hidden Leaf from this disaster.
-What?
We just managed to get
away from all the trouble.
Now you want us to go back?
-Big brother Naruto
is away right now,
so it's our duty to protect
the village while he's gone.
-Yeah, but there's
nothing we could
do, not against monsters
as powerful as these.
[explosion]
KONOHAMARU: I'll just
blast it with the new jutsu
that Naruto taught me.
UDON: What new justu?
MOEGI: It's probably just
the usual sexy jutsu.
-No.
NARUTO: Konohamaru, I've got
this totally cool new jutsu
I want to teach you.
KONOHAMARU: What's with
you all of a sudden?
-Well, I uh-- what I mean is
it's time for me to step up,
time for me to become a teacher.
Huh?
-And what is that
supposed to mean?
NARUTO: Mm.
KONOHAMAURU(VOICEOVER):Don't
tell me he came up with some
awesome new sexy jutsu.
NARUTO: Anyway, look.
This new jutsu that
I'm going to teach you
is like nothing you've
ever seen before.
It's totally different and cool.
KONOHAMARU: Come on!
Just show me!
(VOICEOVER) I wonder what
kind of sexy jutsu it is.
-All right.
The first step's rotation.
Whoa!
So we are going to
add motion to it, huh?
-That's right.
And the second step's power.
-Oh, I see, attack
with the risque.
Awesome!
NARUTO: And then third,
comes the final step.
KONOHAMARU: Ugh, seriously?
There's still more?
NARUTO: Containment.
KONOHAMARU: Woah.
The most points go to the
best cute expression, eh?
-What are you talking about?
Quit kidding.
-At first, I thought
what he meant
was just another sexy jutsu,
but this is way different.
With this jutsu, I can
go on A-ranked missions.
-What do you mean
A-ranked missions?
We've got other things to worry
about at a time like this.
-Yeah.
Moegi's right Konohamaru.
Right now our duty is to
locate any civilians who
might need rescuing and then
evacuate them to safety.
[monster roars]
KONOHAMARU: We're supposed to
evacuate the children and those
who can't fight, huh?
-Mm hm.
I'll check out how
things are in block c.
-I'll check block e.
-All right.
I'm going to block b then.
I'll go see if
there's anyone there
who didn't make it out already.
-Just be careful, Konohamaru.
KONOHAMARU: Hello,
is anyone here?
Anyone?
OLD WOMAN: Help me.
-Where are you?
Can you hear me?
Are you all right?
Just hang on.
How could someone do
something like this?
NARUTO: If we can't merge,
I've got to figure out some way
to pull in nature
energy while I'm moving.
FUKASAKU: But I already told
you that it's impossible.
I never imagined this would
happen after coming so close.
-I'm not just going to give up.
There's no other choice, so
I'll find a way to make it work.
FUKASAKU: But I'm telling you
that there is no other way.
I'm sorry.
I know that this
is hard to accept,
but it's just not physically
possible to do that.
NARUTO: That code
on your back, that's
a message to me from Pervy Sage.
-Of course.
I know that.
And thanks to you it
has also become a key
to solving the
mystery behind Pain.
-Not just that.
That was also a
message to me directly,
telling me to never give
up until the very end.
-But it simply cannot be done.
NARUTO: Look, I'm
Pervy Sage's student,
and if that message was
my master's ninja way,
well then, I have no time
to waste whining and moaning
about this.
[music playing]
-Thank you young man.
-Sure.
You're going to
be all right now.
[screaming] That
crest, it's the gang
that killed uncle
Asuma the Akatsuki.
PAIN: Is Nartuto Uzumaki
in this village, or not?
Tell me now.
-You want Naruto.
No way!
Naruto is one of us, and we
would never sell out a comrade.
PAIN: The will of fire, hm?
-What of it?
-If you do not
answer my question,
then you will have no future.
So I will ask again.
NINJA: What the hell is that?
-Will I find Naruto Uzumaki
somewhere in this village
or won't I?
Tell me.
-I don't know anything.
Now get lost, will ya?
-We just told you we
don't know where he is.
Let us go.
-I see.
Then, I shall pas
judgement on you.
PAIN: It seems that
you truly did not know.
KONOHAMARU
(VOICEOVER):What's going on?
The enemy didn't do anything,
but the guy on the left
just stopped moving
all of a sudden.
What did the enemy do to him?
Was that chuunin
killed without being
able to fight back at all?
Whatever it is, I got
to get out of here now.
Did he hear me?
-It seems you've gotten too
used to having your own way.
Well, that ends right here.
I have no mercy
for thugs like you.
KONOHAMARU: Ebisu sensei.
EBISU (VOICEOVER): Go.
Get out of here Konohamaru.
EBISU: Your fight's right here.
It's going to take way
more than that to kill me.
-Ebisu sensei.
EBISU (VOICEOVER): I
have to buy some time
to allow Konohamaru to escape.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
What should I do?
How can I--
EBISU (VOICEOVER):
Good, he got away.
Let my guard down.
Big mistake, but at least I've
done what I needed to do here.
PAIN: Now is Naruto Uzumaki
in this village, or isn't he?
If you know, tell me.
-Wha-- Naruto?
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Big brother Naruto?
PAIN: It appears that you
do know Naruto Uzumaki so
tell me where he is now.
-I may not look it, but I'm
ranked an elite instructor,
and Naruto was my student.
Long ago, I considered
him to be nothing
but a nuisance who stood in
the way of Konohamaru's rise
to hokage.
I was absolutely certain of it.
However, Naruto didn't allow his
cursed fate to discourage him.
With unending optimism
and determination,
he faced one challenge after
another and overcame them.
The important lessons
I wasn't able to teach,
despite being an
instructor, Naruto
taught them to my student.
PAIN: Enough.
You've rambled on for
far too long already.
I'll give you one more chance.
Do you know where Naruto
Uzumaki is or don't you?
Answer me right right now or
I'll kill you in a heartbeat.
EBISU: Naruto.
You You will overcome
the death of you master
and carry on his legacy.
The indomitable will
that you possess
will teach Konohamaru-- no--
everyone in the Leaf village
many lessons.
Naruto is one of us, a comrade
of the Hidden Leaf village.
Ask all you want.
I have no intention of telling
you Akatsuki anything about him
at all.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Ebisu sensei.
PAIN: I see.
In that case, Naruto--
Because when they look at me,
they don't really see me.
They just see the
grandson of the Hokage.
I can't stand it anymore!
That's why I just got to
become a Hokage right now.
NARUTO: Sorry.
It's not that simple.
KONOHAMARU: Huh?
NARUTO: You keep
saying Hokage Hokage.
To really be a
Hokage, you're going
to have to defeat me in battle.
-From now on, we are rivals.
-Challenge accepted.
And, one day, we'll fight
for the title of Hokage.
Until then, let's both look
forward to that day Konohamaru.
EBISU (VOICEOVER): It
seems this is it for me.
I hope you were able
to get away Konohamaru.
PAIN: Die.
-Come on!
Fight me.
(VOICEOVER) I always taught
that in the ninja world,
there are no shortcuts.
EBISU (ANGRILY): No Konohamaru!
Why didn't you run when
you had the chance?
You have so much potential.
One day you could
even become Hokage.
You can't just throw
your life away like this.
KONOHAMARU: Long ago,
I made a promise.
I promised Naruto to fight him
over the title of Hokage one
day.
We both promised.
Big brother Naruto is my rival,
so I'm not choosing an escape
route because Naruto won't
be on that shorter path.
So fast.
(VOICEOVER) One thing's certain,
if he catches me, I'm dead.
If he catches me, he'll kill
me with that weird jutsu.
-Konohamaru!
KONOHAMARU: Se-- Sensei!
PAIN: Is Naruto Uzumaki
in this village, or not?
Tell me now.
KONOHAMARU
(VOICEOVER): I get it.
So this is what you
see if you get caught.
PAIN: Speak.
Answer me.
It seems that you
truly did not know.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
I'm starting
to figure out this
guy's ability.
I don't have a
clue if he's here.
-No, Konohamaru.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Brother Naruto.
NARUTO: Konohamaru, I've got
this totally cool new jutsu
I want to teach you.
It's an A-ranked jutsu
and hard to master.
PAIN: I see.
Then I shall pass--
a shadow clone!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A
super advanced ninjutusu
that combines chakra rotation,
power, and containment.
KONOHAMARU: Rasengan!
EBISU: What?
When did he learn--
I'm a genin honored
with the name of this village.
My surname is Sarutobi and
my given name is Konohamaru.
You will remember me.
-One more time.
We got to keep trying.
FUKASAKU: Sage jutsu is not
meant for everybody, not
by a long shot.
You could say it's
possible because it's
you and Jiraiya-boy.
Because, otherwise, I wouldn't
have even brought you here.
And unless you already possess
enormous chakra inside of you,
the nature energy would simply
take over and transform you
immediately.
And also, you must possess the
guts to never ever give up.
You are such a stubborn lad.
Let's take a little
break Naruto-boy,
otherwise, I won't
last much longer.
-No.
We can't stop.
I've got to work even
harder than I did just
to get to this point.
Now come on!
FUKASAKU: Just
listen Naruto-boy.
This sort of training has
never been tried not once.
I mean to try to gather nature
energy whose main principle is
stillness while
you're running, well,
it's just like trying to make
yourself look to the left
when you're already
looking to the right.
NARUTO: Ah ha!
-What?
What is It?
[music playing]
PAIN: All of you, you push
death out of your thoughts.
In battle, both sides suffer
death, injury, and pain.
Feel pain.
Contemplate pain.
Accept pain.
Know pain.
Next time, on Naruto
Shippuuden, Pain to the World.
Almighty push.
-My sexiness will get Sasuke
this time. [laughter] Now,
this ought to do it.
-What was that?
What ought to do it?
-I thought we could
just hang out.
May be sit around and talk.
-No thanks.
-Aw come on.
Don't be so uptight
and boring Sasuke.
-This is shear heaven.
-Just what the hell do you
think you are doing Suigetsu?
SUIGETSU: I could ask
you the same thing.
-What?
It's just that I
happen to be-- I
mean-- I-- none of you business.
Damn!
It was the perfect
opportunity to-- Oh well,
it's fine because at least
I got a hold of this.
-Sasuke have you seen
my toothbrush around?
[music playing]