-No way, you keep out of this.
I'll save Sora all by myself.
[theme music]
--[laughing] Seems like Sora
has intimidated the real
Jinchuriki.
-Restore him back to normal.
-It's too late now.
Soon the Nine Tails
will break free
and the Leaf will be destroyed.
-I'll stop it.
-You can try.
As for me, I wash my
hands of the mater.
-Oh, no you don't.
-Sora!
I got rid of him.
I told the Nine
Tails to get lost.
And I did it by
borrowing your strength.
Now listen, you can do it too
if I loan you some of mine.
So come on and get it!
-Sora, snap out of it.
Wake up already.
-Naruto.
You OK?
Hang on, Naruto.
Let me heal you.
-Damn it.
She doesn't have time
to be healing him now.
Sakura, look out!
-Everyone run!
-Is everyone OK?
-Yeah.
-We are all right.
But then, what about
Sakura and Naruto?
[growling]
-Naruto.
-Sakura, you OK?
-Yeah.
-That's good.
-Never mind about me now.
Please let me heal you.
-I'll be fine.
After all, aren't
you the one who's
always talking about what
amazing recuperative powers
I've got.
Sora is our main concern now.
I've got to get him back.
No matter what, you have
to heal him first, OK?
-Naruto.
All right.
-Sora.
-Naruto!
-I'm all right.
Sakura, go on, join the others.
This is between Sora and me.
-Right.
Ahhh!
-Any luck?
I couldn't get it to heal
with my medical ninjutsu.
-As I thought, it's the same
as when you were hurt, Sakura.
Wounds from the
Nine tails chakra
just take longer to heal.
That pain, like sharp needles,
will remain for a little while.
-I'll be OK.
-So what then?
Does this mean Naruto
is the only one who
can ever control that guy?
-That seems to be the case.
-No way.
-Naruto.
-If only-- if only I'd
finished the job back then,
this wouldn't have
happened to Sora.
-Really?
I would think you'd
be glad that wasn't
you who killed his father.
-Not this time.
That won't be the
case this time.
-The Hokage's orders again?
-No!
I can't forgive you.
For what you've done to your
son, you'll get no mercy.
-All of this father
and son nonsense.
You fool, there'll
be no need for that
in the new Land of Fire.
-Yes there will.
There will always
be a need for that.
-I will change this land,
this world, everything.
But to do that, there
needs to be one king.
-Wrong!
-You're the one who's wrong.
Terribly wrong.
-Ninja art super beast scroll.
-What the hell?
-So tell me?
The hospital let you
out for a stroll?
-I had trouble sleeping
what with all the commotion
in the village.
-Isn't that a shame?
Now then, you and I can have
a nice leisurely chat, Kazuma.
-Ha, save your breath.
We have nothing more
to say to each other.
-Sora!
Stop doing that.
It hurts.
Come on, Sora.
Try and remember.
Remember when we
first met each other?
Remember how you and I got
into it with each other?
Remember the time
in the cave when
you came and helped me out?
[crying]
-Sora.
Sora.
Sora!
Come on.
Both of us have been
mistaken from the beginning.
We were both wrong about
what a king really is.
-There was no mistake.
I made no mistake!
[moaning] But if
I die, what will
happen to the Land of Fire?
-Nothing at all will happen.
-That would be funny.
-I don't remember my
dad's face very well.
But still, I'll never forget
that spotted sash he wore.
To me, my father is that
dazzling white light itself.
Now, when I think back on
him, that's always what I see.
-Kasuma.
Your reasons were--
-Listen to me.
Sora.
Who is that?
-Sora!
-Oh, it's only Naruto.
-Calm down, OK.
Why don't we knock it off?
It's me that you keep
hitting, you idiot?
-Why does he always
have to be so damn loud?
-Are you all right, Sora?
-Naruto, why did
you-- you little
idiot, when are you
going to stop butting in?
-As long as I'm here, I
guess I'll give you a hand.
-Always meddling.
-OK, Sora, what's
this all about?
What's going on between
you and Asuma Sensei?
-Nothing.
Get off me, you jerk.
-The most annoying person ever.
-What it is now?
-What in the world
is going on up there?
-It must be-- Captain Yamato,
Sora looks different than
Naruto did when he--
-Yes, you're right.
It's only a theory,
but I suspect
Sora's body isn't strong enough
to hold the Nine Tails much
longer.
It's chakra has grown
far too powerful.
It's seeking to escape his body.
-But that means--
-Sora.
All that power.
That kind of power
won't do you any good.
That isn't real strength.
Let us be your strength.
Me, all of us in the Leaf, we've
got all the power you need.
-Naruto!
-Lady Tsunade.
-Shizune, we're going out.
-Right.
-What is it?
Is that the Nine Tails?
-What an incredible
amount of chakra.
-What now?
-What is it doing?
-Something's not
right, that's for sure.
-Captain Yamato?
-Although it freed
itself from Sora's body,
it apparently needs to find
another human vessel in order
to maintain its form.
-But then--
-Sora.
Sora, you OK?
Hey, can you hear me?
Come on.
Come on, wake up.
Wake up, Sora.
-What is it?
Who's there?
Is somebody-- is somebody
calling me again?
NARUTO: Sora!
--[cuckles] Don't you
ever shut up, Naruto?
-So you're finally awake.
-Naruto.
-Hey, are you ready
to go home or what?
-Are you joking?
I don't have a home anymore.
Where am I supposed to go?
-What are you talking about.
Here, of course,
the Leaf Village
is your home now, buddy.
-The Leaf?
You mean the same village
that I just tried to destroy?
-That's ancient history.
You're our friend.
Get that through your head.
That's right.
We're friends.
You got that?
Don't let anybody ever
tell you differently.
-I'm your friend?
-You bet.
-You OK?
-Sure, they're fine.
-Do you mind if I'm
a part of this too?
-No way, Sai.
Beat it.
-But I thought--
SAI (VOICEOVER): Now,
what was funny about that.
-Naruto, you're terrible.
-My friends.
-So you're really not going
back to the fire temple?
-No.
I think I want to see
a bit more of the world
and meet different
kinds of people,
and make, or try to make,
new friends like you have.
-Good plan.
-Be sure and come back
once in a while, K?
You know you'll
always be welcome here
in the Leaf Village.
Don't ever forget that.
-That's right any time.
-Thanks a lot.
So long.
Would you tell old
Asuma goodbye for me?
-Got it.
-Oh, and the next time you see
me, I'll have though of a name
you can use for the afterlife.
-Hey, wait a sec.
I found out that afterlife
means after your dead.
--[laughing] Took you
long enough, you idiot.
See ya.
-Really?
The climbing silver move?
Right off the bat like that?
Whoa, what's your hurry?
Let's take our time.
Why rush?
-To penetrate the enemy's
line, sometimes you
have to be willing
to risk a bold move.
-But I thought you always hated
risky moves like that, just
like me.
-To defend your king
from a superior opponent,
one must make some sacrifices.
-What's going on with you?
-Oh, nothing.
Nothing to speak of.
It's just that
I'm finally coming
to understand the true
importance of the king.
-Well, sure.
You lose the game if
your king is taken.
It's over.
-If I were picking pieces
to represent Leaf shinobi,
you know what?
I'd say you are most
like the knight.
-Why's that?
-It's not the most powerful
piece on the board,
but it can leap over
any of the others.
It's a unique ability.
It reminds me of how
flexible your mind is.
-OK, which one are you?
-Me, oh, I'm nothing.
I'm just--
-A sacrificial pawn, huh?
-Done.
Do you know which
one the king is?
-Huh?
Um, well, the Hokage, right?
-Yeah, that's what
I used to think too.
But that's not the case.
-Then, who is it?
-You'll know the answer
when the time comes.
HIDAN: Quick on your
feet, aren't you?
Hm, then again, my attack
speed is the slowest
and my aim is the worst
among all the Akatsuki.
-I see.
I knew you must be Akatsuki.
HIDAN: She's all yours.
-Still you're pretty
good, I'll grant you that.
-Careful, Hidan she's the
Two Tails Jinchuriki host.
Underestimate her
and she'll kill you.
-Oh honestly.
Come on, Kakuzu,
personally there's
nothing I'd like better
than to be killed.
[theme music]
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade,
we just received a report
from Kakashi who'd been
trying to make contact
with Master Jiraiya.
TSUNADE: Well, finally,
what does he say?
SHIZUNE: He's verified that
the same pair of shinobi
have carried out attacks
on seven different villages
in five neighboring lands.
TSUNADE: A pair, huh?
SHIZUNE: Yes, my lady,
and while there's
been no incursion into
the Land the Fire as yet,
Kakashi believes it's
only a matter of time.
-I see.
So they've shown their hand.
NARUTO: Next time, "The
Quietly Approaching Threat."