‐We're almost there.
‐Excellent.
Yukimaru, are you ready?
‐Do I really have to
do it all over again?
‐You know full well
it's your duty.
It's going to make me
worse, I just know it.
‐Well, Guren, if you
prefer, I can always
inform Yukimaru for you.
That the kind, gentle
Guren, who he believes
is the one he can come
home to, is actually
the evil villain that
killed his mother.
‐Stop it!
‐Fine, as long as you carry out
my orders without hesitation.
Time is short.
Come on, we need to hurry.
‐Well?
‐I'm not getting anything.
‐I see.
She used up a considerable
amount of chakra
during that last battle.
‐[grunts]
‐We have to find her before
she has a chance to recover.
‐I couldn't agree more.
I'll widen my perimeter a bit.
‐I'm so tired of waiting here.
Where the hell
did that woman go?
‐Patience is the key, Naruto.
‐Yeah, I know.
But if we let her
get away, Yukimaru
is going to‐‐ I
swear I'll find you!
[theme music]
[groans]
‐Look at the two of
you, it's pathetic.
Seriously, you guys
look like you could just
die at any minute.
‐[grunts]
Speak for yourself.
‐Oh, man, I think I'm
about to pass out here.
‐No way I'm dying on
this miserable lake,
not after we survived
Orochimaru's hellhole
of a hideout.
‐That's the seal for
capturing the Three‐Tails.
‐This is a problem.
Looks like they're a good
ways into the ritual.
Now then, Yukimaru.
‐Uh.
‐‐[sighs] We don't
have time for this.
Guren, do something, will you?
‐Guren, please.
‐Enough!
‐[gasps]
‐Huh?
Are you betraying us, then?
‐No, of course, I'm not.
But that jutsu is
going to harm Yukimaru.
Please, I know I can do it.
Just give me another shot.
‐The ones wasn't
punishment enough, huh?
This reluctance to
use them is foolhardy.
It's already cost
you some of your men.
And they roughed you
up pretty good as well.
You honestly think you
could survive another round?
‐Of course, I, uh‐‐
‐The most you could accomplish
now is‐‐ well, wait a minute.
There is one way to do
it without Yukimaru.
However, time will
be of the essence.
And mind you now, you're to
follow my orders to the letter.
Got it?
‐Understood.
‐If I sense even the
slightest bit of willfulness
or if you fail, I won't
hesitate to use Yukimaru.
‐All right.
‐Hm, very well then,
come, Yukimaru.
Don't worry, I'll take
him where he'll be safe.
‐So this plan, what is it?
‐I'll give all of
the details to Rinji.
You just do as he
tells you to do.
The Three‐Tails power
can't reach you here.
‐What about Guren?
Will she be OK?
‐She's the one who
wanted it this way.
She said she's going to do
it even if it kills her.
Now, don't move from this spot.
[rustling]
‐Let's hear this plan already.
‐Hello there, Guren.
‐Just get on with it.
You're wasting my time.
‐All right, according
to Kabuto, there's
a pair of shinobi
guarding the seal.
One's a weapon
user; one, taijutsu.
We already hit them pretty
hard with an ambush,
so they're being
especially cautious now.
‐I'm with you.
We need a diversion‐‐ something
flashy to keep them busy.
One of us will
have to be a decoy.
Hm, all right, then.
No point in delaying this.
I'll take care of
the two in front.
‐It seems a little risky.
Are you sure?
‐Don't worry about it.
I have enough chakra
to act as bait.
You just keep your eyes
peeled for an opening
and be ready to break the seal.
‐All right.
‐The Three‐Tails is completely
ensnared within the seal.
‐Perfect.
Now, we'll just have to narrow
the sphere of the Four‐Seal
Barrier until the Three‐Tails
is trapped for good.
ALL: Right!
‐Uh, Tenten!
‐I know.
‐Who is there?
‐A sealing this precious and
they got children watching it?
You're kidding me.
‐That jutsu.
You must be the
Crystal Style user.
‐Aren't the others supposed
to take care of her?
‐Poor baby, are you going
to run home and cry?
‐Nonsense!
If you are this Crystal Style
user, we welcome the fight!
‐You got a lot of guts, kid,
for a Leaf Village brat.
‐Stay with it.
Concentrate.
All right, we've
got him reined in.
Now, lock it from
all sides, and we'll
seal away the beast for good.
ALL: Got it!
‐Four‐Corner Sealing
Barrier, engage!
‐Hm?
‐Now, it's my turn!
Heyaah!
‐Ugh!
‐Agh!
Something is strange about her.
It is like‐‐
‐You're out of luck, kid.
‐Her whole body is
covered in crystal?
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
Ugh, normally,
I'd have finished a pair
like this in no time.
‐All right!
‐Ah!
GUREN (VOICEOVER): With
the chakra I have left,
there's only one or two
more jutsu I can use.
So‐‐
‐Ugh!
‐Nah!
Agh!
Aah!
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
I've got to end it now!
‐Huh!
‐Ino!
INO (VOICEOVER): My control!
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Hm, did we fail?
‐Sorry, Shizune.
‐The net hasn't been broken yet.
Just keep synchronizing.
It's not too late
to lock it up again.
‐Die!
‐Now!
Um.
‐That isn't good!
‐Oh, no!
BOY: Collaboration Ninjutsu!
Wind Style, Toad Water Pistol!
‐What the‐‐
‐Naruto!
‐That's awesome, we did it!
‐Of course, we did.
What did you expect?
‐So you're the
Crystal Style user.
‐Why, you!
GUREN (VOICEOVER): I'm
breaking that seal,
no matter what it takes!
‐Now, Shino!
[buzzing]
‐What the hell?
‐Uh!
‐The seal!
[shrieks]
MAN: Kakashi!
‐Hm?
‐Yamato.
‐We encountered the enemy's
diversionary team a moment ago,
exactly as you
predicted we would.
It didn't prove all
that formidable though,
and took off pretty quickly.
After that, I split
us up into two groups
and sent Lee and
Tenten over to the lake
to help the Sealing Team.
How did you do?
‐Not so good.
We found a way to counter
the Crystal Style,
but she gave us the slip.
‐Huh?
‐You guys should
go and help protect
the Sealing Team as
quick as you can.
[loud howling]
Damn it!
‐Ugh!
We'll never hold the
barrier like this.
‐[grunts]
‐Uh, it‐‐ it's gigantic.
‐What on earth!
[shrieks]
‐Agh!
‐[whimpers]
‐There, there, what the‐‐
‐Such chakra.
The Three‐Tails.
‐The barrier has been broken.
‐Woohoo!
Yeah!
Deidara!
I think we found our target!
[howling]
‐[grunts]
Hm.
‐[whimpers]
I'm scared, Gamakichi.
‐That shock wave
rattled my skull, kid.
This is getting ridiculous.
What the heck did you just
summon us into this time?
‐Listen, I'll explain later.
There's no time now.
‐Looks like we've
achieved our goal.
Your little jutsu for
sealing away the Three‐Tails
has been broken.
‐You people aren't
getting away with this!
‐Humph.
Rinji, we're leaving.
‐Not so fast.
‐Huh?
‐Aaah!
‐Aargh!
Aargh!
Grrarrh!
‐Oh!
‐No, no!
‐[gasping]
‐Guren.
Uh.
Ha‐ah.
‐Where is she?
Uh, huh?
Heh, uh!
Huh!
Guren, wake up!
Run!
‐Huh?
Where are they?
‐Over there.
[howling]
‐Oh, no!
Stop it!
Don't!
No!
‐Poor, Kabuto, it seems he's
having quite the difficult time
drawing out Yukimaru's power.
If you tried to
force the boy, we'll
never tap into his
true potential.
Real power is forged from the
desire smoldering in the heart.
It fans into a flame and begins
to burn with an intensity
one scarcely imagined
to be possible.
[whooshing]
‐Well, looky here.
‐What is that?
‐I don't know.
But it's not good.
It's the same thing
all over again.
‐[groans]
[gasps]
Huh!
Yukimaru!
‐Uh?
[music playing]
‐Guren, you're little
reunion over with yet?
‐Rinji, I blocked the
Leaf Sealing Jutsu.
Now, we just need
to get to Yukimaru.
‐Huh?
It was you all along.
‐Excuse me?
What are you talking about?
‐We should try to get along
for Lord Orochimaru's sake.
‐Uh, what are you‐‐
‐After all, you want to keep
a trigger on Yukimaru who,
in turn, controls the monster.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Red Camellia."