[gasp]
S... Sasuke?!
Why?!
[gasps]
[gasp]
You guys are still
annoying as ever.
Why the hell are you
here, you bastard?!
He's right...
What are you
doing here, Sasuke?
A whole lot has happened.
But I've decided to protect
the Hidden Leaf Village now.
Then, after...
I will...
...become Hokage.
What?!
[chuckle]
All right!
Team 7 is finally back
in action once again!
Sakura! Sasuke! Let's go!
That sight sure brings back
memories! Right, Shikamaru?
Well, okay. I guess that if
he's willing to help us take
down the enemy, I
won't turn him away.
But I don't accept him.
It's been a while since
our whole class was together
like this. Kinda feels
like the Chunin Exams!
I'm the one who's
gonna be Hokage!
Hey, are you
even listening?!
Kiba, no one's
paying attention.
Frankly, it's
pitiful. Quit it.
The reason is because the
impact of Sasuke showing up
suddenly and declaring
his intent to become
Hokage is much too great.
Um Kiba? Well, I
heard you loud and clear!
All of us should
aspire to be Hokage!
Come on, you guys!
Let's show 'em
what we're made of!
Sasuke...
What are you
thinking right now?
All right!
Just hold up...
We have another one?!
It wants to
break the barrier!
Fellow past Hokage!
Please focus and
prepare yourselves!
Yes, we know that!
Now, then.
The barrier held!
That thing's absolutely
amazing!
To be able to
keep him trapped!
But where is Ten Tails?!
[angry growl]
[chuckle] That Ten Tails...
...it seems that he
scorched himself!
That is not just
some simple barrier!
[impressed chuckle] Wow...
The past Hokage truly were
incredible individuals, huh?
Seems they
weren't just all talk.
Wood Style:
Wood Clone Jutsu!
I'll make four entry
points in the barrier,
so we can go in and out!
Now, follow me!
Right! Let's go!
Yeah!
[angry growling]
I'm not done! Sage Art!
Gracious Deity Gates!
Head Seal!
[attacking yells]
Now then, it's your turn.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Madara.
No way.
A clone's no fun at
all. I'll wait until the
real you shows up.
Quick, go now!
[attacking yells]
[attacking yell]
Those are Fission Beings!
It's trying to keep us away
from its real body!
[defiant roar]
[attacking yells]
Don't hold back!
[charging yells]
Yes... I...
I...
Sasuke!
Demon Wind Shuriken:
Windmill of shadows!
Eat this!
[grunt] Let's
see you try it!
Summoning jutsu!
Help!
[chuckle] Enough
playing. Finish him off.
Yeah?! Eat this!
But how? It's impossible.
Fire Style:
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
That's right. Ever since I
was a genin, I thought I was
a full-fledged kunoichi.
But I ended up hiding
behind Sasuke and Naruto.
And the two of
them always risked
everything to protect me.
I hated the way I was.
I swore that next
time, I would make
them stare at my back!
[growling]
Even I'm-- Even I'm...
Aaah!
A wall of air! My shiruken
just bounced off...
I know I made
that oath back then.
But both Naruto and Sasuke
kept staying ahead of me,
rushing ever forward.
So I gave up. I thought the
two of them were too strong,
that I'd never be able
to catch up. But...
Naruto!!
Sasuke!!
No, you guys!
Stop! No!
I didn't even think
about it. I put the entire
burden on you, Naruto.
I went crying to you, clung
to you, and expected you to
make it all better.
While I did nothing.
Sorry, Naruto.
It means you may have to
wait for me a little bit.
Next time I'm coming, too.
I would like to be
your apprentice.
Hmm?
[delighted laugh]
Take this! Cha!
Your movements are
getting much better!
By the way, do you
remember the first
thing I taught you?
Of course, ma'am!
Medic Ninja must never get
themselves killed. Thus they
must never force their
way forward in combat.
Yes, that is true...
At the same time, that does
not excuse you from learning
how to fight on
the front line.
First and foremost, you
are my student, a kunoichi
inheriting the
Legendary Sannin's power.
And Sakura Haruno,
you are also the
Fifth Hokage's pupil!
And I just reached
full capacity.
I can finally unleash it!
Cha!
I am never, ever talking
back to Sakura or making her
mad ever again.
She'll destroy me.
[chuckle]
Wow, what monster
strength! It might even
be greater than Tsuna's!
A continuous massing of
chakra over three years,
requiring extremely
delicate chakra control.
The 100 Healings Mark that
I couldn't even achieve!
And I don't have
to waste any on a
youthful appearance!
[angry growling]
Wind Style...
Inferno Style...
Rasen Shuriken!
Flame Control!
[attack yell]
Thanks, Sasuke!
Um, hello?
I'm here, too! You know
that? Right, Sakura?!
Look, don't drag
us down, Naruto?
That's right! Keep
complaining and I'll just
grab the Hokage
seat for myself!
What?!
Not you too, Sakura?!
We'll fight with
our backs together!
Lady Tsunade, it looks like
I've finally caught up to
the two of them!
So this is how Nine Tails
Chakra looks under control.
A new Sharingan
and black flames.
That Naruto! He's even
mastered changing the
Rasengan's nature!
[chuckle]
Sakura's holding
her own out there!
Come on, Team 8! Let's get
in there, too! We can't let
Team 7 show us up!
I've managed to work out a
new jutsu for myself, too,
Naruto!
Don't think you
have exclusive
rights to this jutsu!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!?
You only made one!
I could make way more!
Even back in the day!
Just watch, all right?!
There may only be one clone,
but this'll make me
three times stronger!
Come, Akamaru!
Plunge into the
enemy's midst!
Inuzuka Style! Man-Beast
Team Transformation Combo!
Three-Headed Wolf!
[angry roaring]
[harrumphing chuckle]
Sasuke's joke about becoming
Hokage was nauseating.
But it's revving me up!
[growl]
Tail Chasing Rotating Fang!
Parasitic
Gigantic Beetle...
[angry roar]
Infestation!
Eww gross! What
are those things?!
Parasitic Gigantic Beetles.
If you mistake the amount of
chakra to give them,
they'll devour your
flesh and grow rapidly.
They're incredibly
tricky to nurture.
Two Palms! Four Palms!
Eight Palms! Sixteen Palms!
Thirty-Two Palms!
I guess this really
is still my limit.
Not at all.
But Neji, I'm not like you.
If you set limits on
yourself, you'll never be
able to catch him.
You have to surpass your
limits. You must fearlessly
take a giant leap forward.
That is...
Sixty-Four Palms!
...the trick to
achieving Sixty-Four Palms.
Naruto is always striving
to get ahead. And I...
[growling]
...want to keep standing
next to Naruto forever!
I'll proceed to Eight
Trigrams Sixty-Four
Palms, like this!
Thus, I must continuously
move forward as well!
All right, come on
Team 10! Attack with an
Ino-Shika-Cho Combination!
We can use Formation E!
[exasperated sigh] This
isn't the Chunin Exams. We
don't need to compete
against the other teams.
We're in the
middle of a war!
But we still wanna
show them what
we're made of, right?
Expansion Jutsu!
Damn it!
Shadow Grasping Jutsu!
Twenty-five enemy
signatures picked
up and locked on!
Sensory Relay!
Human Boulder Yo-Yo!
[attacking yell]
I'm going to
expand some more.
Can you handle
some more weight?
No prob.
You're still light, Choji.
And besides, this isn't
quite flashy
enough to impress yet.
What? Who's being
super competitive now?
Actually, I'm
technically on Team 7, too.
I'll attack the main
body from the sky!
Sai!
You all right?!
Yes...
[growling]
It's no good!
The number of
enemies keeps increasing!
And some of them are huge!
These big ones
sure are heavy!
[angry growling]
Can you share your
chakra with everyone again?
Not right now.
Kurama isn't done
recharging his chakra, yet.
[eager roaring]
To take down the main body,
we need to mow down the big
ones or find some way
to slip past them.
It's too far to
reach in a single leap.
We'll need time to
weave signs and repel
the enemy's attacks.
Without your chakra,
Naruto, we could suffer
heavy casualties.
And the Medical
Corps can't come here.
We need to mow down
and slip past, huh?
That'll be easy.
This guy can clear the
distance in one leap and
repel any enemy
attacks, too.
I can now stay near and
heal anyone who suffers
serious harm at any time!
Summoning Jutsu!
You see that giant
way in the back there?
Can you get me closer
with some leaps?
I need you to just keep
advancing forward. I'll get
the real body in the back.
Lady Katsuyu, please divide
and attend to the entire
Allied Shinobi
Forces. Our role
will be to heal everyone.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The New
Three-Way Deadlock."
[proud chuckling]
It is a new era!