[attacking yell]
Retreat! Retreat!
The chakra threads wielded
by world-class puppet masters
are able to control human
beings as well as puppets.
But once the chakra threads
are cut, there's no lasting
harm to the person who was
being controlled.
I thank you.
I almost had to
slay an ally.
There's a special way
Puppet Users fight
against each other.
I'm the only one here
who can do this.
Isn't that right,
Granny Chiyo?!
Kankuro...
[gasp]
Hm?
Sasori...
Everything I've done in
my life has been wrong.
After meeting Naruto, I
was able to do the right
thing in the end.
I thought that I'd died
leaving some hope for
a brighter future...
But as I stand before you
now... I can't help but
fee regret at the
actions of my past...
Sasori...
Granny Chiyo? When
are mother and father
coming back?
Oh, they'll be gone a
little bit longer.
Oh, I see...
At the time, I simply
couldn't bring myself
to tell him the truth.
I felt that Sasori was too
young to know about his
parents' deaths. But...
[gasp]
Sasori...
Sasori was perceptive.
He'd already figured out
his parents were dead.
Sasori! How've
you been?
Granny Chiyo told me that
your last puppet was a
really big hit with
everybody.
Someday I want to be a
shinobi everyone praises.
Just like your puppets!
Hey! Are you
listening to me?
Hello? I'm right here!
Komushi's here
to see you!
Come on, already!
Answer me!
I didn't mean to lose
my temper. Sorry about
that.
It's just that you're
kinda treating me worse
than you'd treat a
puppet, you know?
Well, I guess I'm gonna
have to wait until hell
freezes over to get an
answer out of you!
Anyway, I have a
message from Granny
Chiyo.
She wants you to finish
those puppets earlier-
Crow, Black And,
and Salamander...
Huh?
Everything she
requested is complete.
So your new creations,
huh? Boy, you certainly
do work!
I don't like to
make people wait.
Uh... Of course.
I'm sure that
you don't.
Whoa...
Wow, that's amazing!
They look just like
real human fingers!
Hmm...
Oh! I almost forgot
to ask you...
About that new one. She
wanted me to ask you if
you'd finished the recipe
for the Crow puppet's poison.
Hm?
All these are really
rare medicinal plants!
You're gonna make a
mixture out of all
of them?
I'm gonna need to ask
permission about this.
All right!
I, Komushi, will
negotiate it!
Give me a little
time-
I don't like
waiting around.
Guess not... I'd
better go, then!
[excited laughter]
[knocking]
It's Komushi!
Hm? What is it?
Oh, did you relay my
message to-?
Granny Chiyo, Sasori
has a request to ask
of you.
What is it?
Oh. Well, there's not much
I can say without knowing
the blending ratio.
But since
it's you...
I foresee no issues. I'll
go clear it with the
Pharmaceutical Division.
But right now, I'm in the
middle of some research,
so please leave.
Man, Sasori! You've got
it made! I mean, you're
still young but you're
already contributing
to the village!
Granny Chiyo must
be really proud
of you.
Are you listening?
I don't know if you know
this, but Granny Chiyo
always seems really
worried about you.
I can't wait for the day
that I finally get
acknowledged as a full-
fledged shinobi just
like your puppets!
My own parents still treat
me like a kid! They keep
telling me that I'm not
suited to be a shinobi...
But guess what? I just
got assigned to work
border security!
I mean, yeah, it's
only guard duty,
but if I can
prove myself-
Komushi!
What are you up to at
this hour?! I've been
worried sick about you!
Mom, cut it out!
I'm gonna be working
border security from
now on!
Oh, you don't have to go
out on missions like that!
I'll just take care of you
for the rest of my life!
How's that sound?
Thanks, Sasori!
I heard...
...they said you were
injured while on guard
duty.
Yeah, I messed
up... But look!
Huh?
That's... a
puppet arm!
Yeah, and that's
not all, either!
I feel stronger
than ever before!
And the way this is
made, it fits just
perfectly!
It's like it's always
been a part of my body!
[screaming]
[groaning]
How could you ingest
your own poison?!
Granny Chiyo...
He's... It's
not his fault!
I'm the one... It
was me who messed
up!
[screaming]
Ah! Where is Sasori?!
What is the poison's
blending ratio?!
[screaming]
Please, heal him! Please,
I beg you! Heal him!
Please!
You attached his right
arm, didn't you? That
means his left arm can
be attached, too!
His legs, his body...
You can even fix his
soul, I know you can!
Please, just give him
back to me! Fix my Komushi
and give him back to me!
It was a painful
accident.
Komushi was my go-between
with Sasori... But even
more than that...
He was the only person
who truly treated Sasori
as a friend.
Hm?
So tell me, how has
Sasori been lately?
Eh, pretty much the same
as usual. But, recently
he's been working on these
really small
puppet parts.
And they look just
like real human hands.
Huh?!
What?! Can't be...
It's probably a
coincidence.
But something's
off...
I hope my fears
are ungrounded...
I don't like to
make people wait...
From what I can see. I
thought there'd be a
little more progress...
Sasori! What are
you doing?!
I've just barely managed
to get it to the standard
size...
Sasori!
What?!
It's Komushi?!
[grunting]
As requested...
This model is done.
[gasp]
I wasn't there for him
when he was suffering
the most.
When he desperately
needed love...
No, I made excuses and
distanced myself from him.
I'm the one who
warped him...
I'm sorry! Not that it
does any good. An apology
from a corpse to the puppet
you've become!
Your technique's just
as sharp as ever.
But you don't have
any fighting spirit.
I guess puppet masters
aren't any good if they're
being controlled, huh?
Hmph! Youngsters
shouldn't act
like smart alecks!
And don't take the
Reanimation Jutsu
so lightly!
If the jutsu caster
gets serious...
Speak of the devil!
Reverse Secret
White Technique!
Esematsu's
Ten Puppets!
Huh?
Wires?!
[gasp]
Sasori... and his
Mother and Father
puppets...
I recovered and
repaired all of
them...
Sasori, a human who
wanted to be a
complete puppet.
He said he was an
unfinished puppet
with a beating heart
at its core...
Do you think he wanted to
be closer to his parents?
Since both of them had
already become puppets?
To think someone would
want to be a puppet
with no soul...
It could be...
Although...
Actually, I can sense the
souls of Sasori's mother
and father inside of
these puppets.
I'd like to believe
that he sensed them
as well.
Granny Chiyo said Sasori
was able to anticipate
the Mother and Father
puppets' attack.
But he didn't even
attempt to dodge it.
He let his
defenses down.
Yeah... It must have
gotten through to him.
The cry that his
parents souls let
out...
I may well be
inexperienced...
But I'm not so ignorant
that I couldn't feel your
regret and sadness pulsing
through every last
inch of your Chakra
Threads.
You say whatever pops
into your head! That's
why your a youngster!
There are many things I'd
like to atone for, but it's
too late. I'm dead.
There's nothing
further I can do!
Sasori entrusted his
legacy to me...
I entrust you with the
"Father" and "Mother"
puppets.
Sasori?! He
did that?!
Puppets only Sasori
could create. Their
inner working's are
unbelievably delicate,
all the way down
to the fingertips.
So he shares a love and
passion for puppets,
just like Sasori did.
I believe Sasori's soul
still dwells inside
these puppets!
Thanks to his love, the
souls of his parents
have been instilled in
them, as well!
In the end, I think
that Sasori sensed
that for himself.
You speak of puppets
that have souls?
There's even more,
Granny Chiyo.
The love that you gave to
his Father and Mother
puppets, became a part of
their souls, as well.
Oh?
Sasori was aware of that.
And he entrusted all of
it to me.
Rather, he left it
behind for future
generations.
And passing it on has
become my duty, as well,
one that I take very
seriously.
Sasori did that?
I may still be a youngster,
and I suppose that to you,
I'm little more than a
stranger.
But my kid brother Gaara
received your soul and
came back to life.
So I'm not a
stranger at all.
That's not the only thing
I sense through the Chakra
Threads! Sasori, his mother
and father, their family's
thoughts and love...
Their souls are crying
out to me now...
They're saying, "Please
stop Granny Chiyo!"
Family...
Mother!
This is only a simple
family portrait. You
don't have to be so
stubborn about
the whole thing!
You're a fool!
The word "shinobi"
means "stealth"!
I'm not going to take
a photo to be put up
as a decoration!
Just so that people can
say, "Oh, what a fine
portrait" at parties!
Well, it wouldn't go
that far, I don't think.
Oh, please! Of
course, it will!
Granny Chiyo...
Is it that you don't
want to take a photo
with us?
No! It's not that! Where
would you even get such
an idea?
Heh! What are we
going to do with
you?
Oh... What are
you doing?
[groaning]
Ah-Ahh!
I must say, it seems that
they are in the hands of
a fine puppeteer now.
[gasp]
Granny Chiyo!
Ha! Ha! Just kidding!
Playing possum
for real!
[laughing]
Now let's see, Sasori
left his Mother and
Father to you as a
gift.
It seems only fair that
I should leave you with
something, too.
But the only things that
I have left to give you
now are my Secret Puppet
Techniques.
You'll learn by
experiencing them!
Wait, hold on!
Secret White Technique!
Army of Illusions!
Oh no! This is
seriously not
good at all!
[laughter]
When I was a kid, I
begged you to train me,
but you said you didn't
care about the future
of the village
and ignored me!
Well I guess I
was younger back
then!
You were already
an old hag!
[laughter]
Did you say that Omoi
deserted the battlefield?!
Is this true,
Kakashi?
I'm afraid it is. Reports
say he ran from his post
after stating that he
needed to leave for a bit.
Deserting under enemy
fire is a serious
offense in the Hidden
Cloud!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Run, Omoi!"
Damn it, Omoi!
What were you
thinking?!