-The person who injured Sakura?
It was you, Naruto.
[gasps]
-Naruto!
[choking]
-You-- you really don't
remember any of it?
-So.
The bridge, then?
And the giant crater?
-Yes.
It was all you.
-And Sakura's wounds?
-That's right.
She lied to spare your feelings.
To protect you from the truth.
But understand, I'm to blame
for her injuries as well.
This is not all on you.
The thing is, there's a reason
I was assigned to Team Kakashi.
You see, I possess
a unique power.
The ability to suppress the
Nine-Tails power within you.
So you needn't worry too much.
You'll be fine.
Well, as long as I'm
at your side, anyway.
-Huh?
-Let's be honest.
I'm not even sure if it's
right to be telling you
any of this just yet, Naruto.
But there's a reason I did.
There's no question this power
will get you to Sasuke faster.
But the strength you gain from
depending on the Nine-Tails
isn't actually your own.
If you continue to
rely on its power,
not only will you
hurt yourself, Naruto,
but you'll be endangering
the lives of those around you
as well.
Just as you did today.
[gasp]
-But you knew about all
this already, didn't you?
And you let your impatience
get the better of you
and unleash the power anyway.
I'll have to suppress the
Nine-Tails power completely
now.
But listen.
If you think that's
going to make you weaker,
you're mistaken.
I've witnessed what you can do.
You're powerful
enough on your own.
I really think you've
got the wrong idea, here.
The source of your strength
isn't the Nine-Tails chakra.
It's your own, which holds
the formidable energy
of the Nine-Tails in check.
If you want to save Sasuke,
then do it using your own power.
If you wish to see Sasuke,
then look with your eyes,
not the Nine-Tails'.
If you want to protect Sakura,
forget about the fox spirit.
Use your strength.
-All right.
[theme music - in japanese]
[birds singing]
-Kabuto, can't all that wait
until we get home again?
-'Fraid not.
You have to keep these clean.
If you don't, the blades
will go dull in no time.
-Hm.
-(VOICEOVER) Good.
The pain is starting to fade.
They're still at it over there.
Oh, yeah.
Gosh.
I almost forgot.
-(VOICEOVER) Gone.
-(VOICEOVER) Here it is.
-You can go on ahead without me.
I'll catch up as
soon as I've packed.
-Here, let me help.
(VOICEOVER) Huh?
This isn't a
printed copy, is it?
-Did you draw this, too?
-Yes.
-Wow.
Your own picture book.
Would you mind if I took a look
at it while we're on the road?
-I do, actually.
It's just, I haven't
finished it yet.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I don't show it to other people.
-Oh.
-It belongs to my older brother.
-(VOICEOVER) I lost it.
-It's a very intriguing story.
But give me one good reason
why I should believe you.
-Ah.
Ah!
-(VOICEOVER) I must have
dropped it back there.
-Is something the matter, Psi?
-No.
Not at all.
-Good.
-By the way, Lord Orochimaru.
-Hmm?
-Once we do get back, do
you think you could possibly
supply me with a
fresh male cadaver?
-You should still have some
in stock shouldn't you?
-I do, but none
between 15 and 16.
We used the last one, remember?
I'm going to need another for
this scroll to be completed.
I mean, you must know how
much of a perfectionist
I tend to be.
-Kabuto.
Your blood type is A, isn't it?
-Actually, no.
It's AB.
-Really?
That's surprising.
-No, I don't think so.
Anyway, we should
probably get moving.
We're not home yet.
-Hmm.
-Here.
Have a look at this diagram.
I think it lays out a pretty
good strategy for cornering
your enemy, which we'll need.
Now, in actual missions, things
can change up pretty quickly
depending on the
number of enemies
and allies in the field.
So, first off--
-I don't get it.
This book.
-Huh?
-And if things go in this
direction, we'll have to-- hey,
are you even listening to me?
-You guys, come here a minute.
-Hmm?
-Hurry.
You have to see this.
-What is it, Sakura?
Is something wrong?
-Look at this.
-Hey!
That's Psi's!
-It's the picture book we found.
The one that he drew, right?
What's it about, Sakura?
Can you tell?
It we figure that
out, we might be
able to learn
something about Psi.
-I know.
That's what I was thinking.
So I tried to read it, but--
-Well, what's it about?
What kind of story is it?
-Hmm.
Actually, I'm not all that sure.
-Huh?
Well, why not?
-Go on, Sakura.
-There aren't any words
or dialogue at all.
-Yeah, you're right.
-I don't know.
I mean, it seems like
it's about the two
boys on the front
and back cover.
Each of them has his
own story, starting
from either end of the book.
And then, if you read
them all the way through,
they eventually
meet in the center.
If you start on the side with
the black-haired boy on it,
all the pages are alike.
He's always on the right side.
-But the character
on the left changes
with every turn of the page.
See?
-Wait.
Sakura.
Go back, will you?
-Hm?
-I thought so.
Check out what he's wearing.
Now, go ahead and flip back
to the other page again.
He's got a different outfit on.
-You're right.
-And look at his weapon.
It's the same one
his opponent is
wielding on the previous page.
A sickle and chain.
[sigh]
-It seems like, like it's
the story of a young boy,
vanquishing his enemies.
-Looks like it.
And after each fight, I think he
claims their weapons and armor
for his own.
Every page, it just keeps going.
Oh-- wait a minute.
Yep.
The layout's in reverse.
But the boy with
the white hair has
been drawn in the
exact same way.
-So it's actually
a story about how
the boys mature with
each battle, then.
-Wait.
Hold on a second, though.
If they're both fighting
their way in from the cover,
what happens when they
meet in the middle?
-Yeah, I know.
That's the problem.
Look here.
-What's up with that?
I don't get it.
-Kind of freaky.
-I went through the whole thing,
and these pages at the center
are the only ones
that are incomplete.
-So, uh, anybody as
creeped out as I am?
-He said that he
hadn't finished it yet,
but why wouldn't the
face be drawn in?
[gasp]
-Look at that guy.
He kind of looks like Psi, huh?
Or am I crazy?
-You're right.
-Was he drawing himself?
-And then there's this
boy with the white hair.
Wonder who he is.
-Hmm.
[gulp]
-It's just, I haven't
finished it yet.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I don't show it to other people.
It belongs to my older brother.
-It could be his brother.
Don't you think?
-Hmm?
-If you have a brother,
try and imagine
what it would feel
like to lose him.
Surely you should
be able to do that.
-Hmm?
Oh, yes, that.
Well, you see, my
brother is already dead.
-So.
These pages in the middle.
And the boys on the cover.
They're Psi and his brother.
-Shall we, then?
-Yes, sir.
-It's in there.
-His older brother.
Do you think?
-Could it be?
-Hmm?
-My clone's reporting in.
Looks like we've got a location.
[gasp]
-So, this is it.
Ready?
-Mm-hmm.
-(VOICEOVER) It's him.
-You're late.
[theme music - in japanese]
-What?
I'm sweating.
But I've always been
devoid of emotion.
And yet, with one look in
his eyes, the sense of dread
is palpable.
Like nothing I've ever known.
This is who Naruto has been
searching for all this time?
-Sasuke Uchiha.
Next time, Infiltration--
The Den of the Snake.
[theme music - in japanese]
-Notable People in
the Leaf Village.
Welcome to the first
of our two-part segment
on Sasuke Uchiha.
The epitome of cool,
Sasuke is a genius
who graduated at the
top of his class.
But his only
ambition was revenge
on the brother who
wiped out their clan.
His polar opposite was Naruto,
and the two were often at odds.
-You are a complete loser!
-What the heck's your problem?
You should thank me for
coming in here to help you.
-At first, Naruto was no
match for Sasuke at all.
-You're not hurt, are you?
Scaredy-cat.
-But with his determination
and unpredictability,
he grew stronger.
-You're not hurt, are you?
You scaredy-cat.
-Until finally--
-You're one of the ones
I want to fight the most.
-Huh?
-And that's when the rivalry
between Naruto and Sasuke
truly began.
As for the rest of
their story, we'll
just have to wait
until next time.