What is this chakra?!
Interesting, they all
perceive the chakra, even
though none of them
are sensory types.
This chakra is...
Let's just go. Hurry up and
lead the way, Orochimaru.
It looks like he's a bit
concerned about Naruto.
[gasp]
That's Nine Tails'-
Wait, hold on.
No, it's Naruto's chakra!
Nice work transforming
and transferring
my chakra, Naruto!
I've got the hang of it now.
So, help me out, Kurama!
That Nara shinobi. He sure
analyzed my chakra exchange
capabilities extensively.
Sorry for the wait. You
can use a small number
of Shadow Clones now.
Great!
W- Wow! This is the chakra
Naruto's been handling?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Hey, Naruto! You're late!
Sorry! Here!
Choji! Ino!
Uh, okay!
What is going on here?!
Are these calories?
Hey Choji! You're
filling out again!
That brat Naruto...
Is he giving them the
Nine Tails' chakra?!
[grunt]
Eight Trigrams Air Palm!
I feel my
power surging!
Just an Air Palm did that?!
That girl down there,
she has gotten quite a bit
stronger after receiving
that power from Naruto.
Expansion Jutsu!
Ino! Shikamaru!
Are you both ready?!
-Yeah!
-You bet!
You all understand the plan,
right? Each of you beat it
into your heads!
First, start with Ino-
Shika-Cho!
And if this plan doesn't
work? What then?
Then you live on and
take the reins, Shikamaru.
[gasp]
HQ will soon be no more.
[grunt]
The only face time
I spent with you
as your father was
when we played shogi.
I haven't given
you a thing.
You gave me everything.
Huh?
I was able to grow up,
staring at your back, dad.
[chuckle]
Ino, you've grown up to
perfectly embody the
symbolic meaning of
the Yamanaka Clan's
crest, the purple
bush clover.
Optimistic love, right?
That's not the only
meaning of that flower.
What I am most
proud of about you
is your care and
compassion towards
your friends!
You have blossomed
into a beautiful bush
clover flower indeed.
Now, then our
time's almost up.
Do you have any final
words to share, Shikaku?
Could you tell your mother
something for me, Shikamaru?
Wait! First, throw out
that wooden box on the
left-hand shelf of my
closet without your
mom finding out about it-!
I already know all
about it. Don't worry.
Lastly, from me.
Never forget that we live
on inside of you forever.
Don't forget!
Don't mock me!
[gasp]
-Shadow Possession!
-Mind Transfer!
Jutsu!
I'm in!
Not again!
Whoa! Damn it!
[grunting]
They're faster than me!
Nice work, there, Ino!
[angry roar]
[grunting]
One after another.
Now it's the
Nara's Paralysis jutsu.
Don't underestimate
the Nara Clan!
Gotcha! It's immobilized!
You can stop now, Ino!
[weary groan]
Are you all right?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
[scoff]
[crying] Neji!
Lee, stop crying!
Lee...
Listen Lee, as long as
we hold onto Neji's
convictions, he'll
continue to live on,
connected, inside of us!
Let me share a little
something with you all.
It's those connections that
made me what I am today!
You should know that bonds
can be powerful curses, too!
Listen, Naruto. I
know that I was the one
who once told you
that "I will never
let my comrades die."
Those words are also an
admonition aimed at myself.
I haven't been able
to save many a comrade.
Which is why I keep telling
myself this time I will
protect them.
But then I end up having
to face the fact that I
couldn't once more.
I'll be confronting
those wounds for
the rest of my life.
But that's why we're
ninja. We're "those who
endure." Isn't that right?
They'll never
let you forget,
but it's those wounds
that prove your comrades
live on inside here.
Comrades that you only
create inside a dream so you
can't get hurt aren't real.
And that means
you're just erasing
your real friends!
Whether it's a
curse or not.
I want to keep
the real Neji
right in here!
The real Neji
right here.
[attacking yell]
Gentle Fist!
[groaning]
Give it up, Lee.
No matter how hard you try,
you'll never defeat me.
That's simply the way it is.
Look elsewhere for a rival.
So you saw me lose
back there, huh?
You know... I used to
believe that you couldn't
change the fate that
was handed to you.
One day, we'll fight
for real and see
which is greater.
Your Ferocious Fist
or my Gentle Fist.
However, I shall not lose as
long as my eyes are black!
Wait, Neji, don't
you mean so long as
your eyes are white?
Huh? Oh, yes, I guess.
Well, in any case, it
means you'll always
have me as your rival!
It's a lot stronger
and there's more of
it than last time.
I want to confirm something
about the intel from the
last battle sequence.
Kakashi, you said that
the reason why you
were able to travel
through space-time using
Kamui, plus pull Eight
Tails in and out almost
whole, was thanks to
receiving Nine Tails
Chakra from Naruto, right?
Yes.
Though to be completely
accurate, I received
that chakra directly
from the Nine Tails.
In reference to your choice
of words "Thanks to...", how
different was it
compared to using
Kamui without Nine
Tails' Chakra?
Could you explain it
to me in simple terms?
I would say more than three
times the power. I couldn't
really hurl things that
were very large or do
it very often before that.
Almost done, huh?
[chuckle] It's ended
up just as you wanted,
Fourth Hokage!
For the only one who can
link with my chakra right
now is Naruto, since he has
Kushina's blood and has
been with me for years
as my Jinchuriki.
And he's matured to the
point where he's skillful
enough to sense and
transmute my chakra
to be compatible with other
shinobi and give it to them.
Though I can help or use
Naruto as an intermediary to
give my chakra to anyone
just as you handed over
and inserted your chakra
into Naruto, Minato.
He's already surpassed
you both, a while ago now.
The amount of chakra we can
link and he can transmit is
on a different scale!
[laugh] Kushina, Minato.
You both pale in comparison
to your brat, Naruto!
[chuckling]
Though I suppose
this is the power you
wanted him to
have all along.
[harrumphing chuckle]
Perhaps I'll lend Obito a
little power, too.
[grunting]
Damn it! He's
pushing back hard!
Naruto, this is
your chance! Go now!
Tailed Beast Bomb!
Beam of Light!
Eight Trigrams
Air Wall Palm!
Wind Style:
Giant Casting Net!
[grunt]
I won't let Neji's
death be in vain!
[chuckle] A curse mark that
doesn't vanish till death, a
shinobi curse Hyuga's
main and branch families
gave rise to.
An existence where one can
only await death inside a
cage. Nice analogy
for this situation.
You're all like that
brat who just died
a pointless death.
No, Neji-
Neji's will isn't...
[battle cry]
Dead yet!
I will take the right side!
Gotcha!
Damn! My shoulder's
dislocated again!
Gentle Fist!
Go, Lee!
Right!
[attacking growl]
I'm not like you guys.
I don't want to
sever any of my bonds.
Or have them
cut off, either!
This is it?
This place seems
to be untouched.
It's in shambles.
Well, I suppose it is
way outside the village.
Which one?
Hm?
Let's see. Should be...
There we go.
Man, this place gives me the
creeps. If you've found it,
can we please
get out of here?!
Yes, lets go to the place
where all the secrets sleep.
This place has
changed a lot, too.
What is up with Sasuke now?
He's like me before I
wanted to destroy the Leaf.
How so?
You see, though both he
and the village have
changed, this place still
remainshis homeland.
He needs time to reconfirm
his decision and resolve by
immersing himself
in sentimentality
and retracing the past.
Huh, I see.
So you're over
it already, then?
That "immersion in
sentimentality to confirm
your resolve to
destroy the Leaf" thing?
Hey, you know, come to think
of it, all of us were your
cream-of-the-crop
top subordinates,
isn't that right?
And right now, we're here
inside the Leaf Village,
with all the strong folk
away fighting in the war.
So isn't this, like,
the absolutely perfect
chance for you?
[chuckle] Yes, perhaps...
Well, except for
one little thing.
Huh?
You are no longer
Hebi anymore.
Wow, you use a jutsu to
remove the entry stone?
There's not even a trace
left of the Uchiha's
Nakano Shrine.
The exterior doesn't matter.
What's important is
what's beneath. Let's go.
Well then, I'll get started.
It's best if you stand back.
[screaming]
[ghostly cackling]
In order to perform what
is written in that scroll,
first, the Death God's
Mask is necessary.
That is inside the Uzumaki
Clan's Noh Mask Hall on the
outskirts of the Leaf.
Then one must allow the
Death God of the Reaper
Death Seal to possess
oneself and guide it forth.
Slice open the Death
God's abdomen, and the
seal will come undone.
Although I shall then end
up as a human sacrifice.
[screaming]
However, it will also
allow me to retrieve my
arms from inside the
Death God's belly.
They're mine again!
If I regain the power in
those arms, I can perform
the Reanimation Jutsu.
Yes.
I can revive those four. Of
course in that case, you're
well aware of what
will then be necessary.
Agh! No! You're gonna
make us Reanimation
Jutsu sacrifices!
[chuckle]
A good idea but we've
actually got something
better than you all.
Though it's still
invisible to you yet.
Jugo, Sasuke, Suigetsu.
Get ready now!
Got it. Right.
Now Jugo, give Sasuke some of
your Curse Mark Sage Power.
And when you do, the
Zetsu that Tobi stuck
onto Sasuke to watch
him should respond and
rise up to the surface.
Damn it! How did you--?!
I know your Hashirama
cells inside and out from
all of my experiments.
[grunting]
And that includes how to
detect you, of course.
Six of you, huh?
Tobi sure wasn't taking
any chances, was he?
When I reclaimed and
reabsorbed my chakra from
Kabuto, his intel was
transferred into me, as well.
He'd thoroughly investigated
the six of you that'd been
attached to Sasuke.
I possess the DNA of those
four too, since I love
collecting and
storing knowledge.
Suigetsu, Jugo. Take
care of the remaining two.
Okey dokey, Lord
Orochimaru! You got it!
Reanimation Jutsu!
[screaming]
Now here goes!
Yes! They who
are all-knowing.
The previous Hokage!
That's the First Hokage? The
real Hashirama who's been
touted as a God of Shinobi?
No way! You solved how to
undo that Sealing Jutsu?
Lord First, it appears
we've been recalled into
the world of the living.
Huh? Who the hell are you?
Oh, uh, the
Fourth Hokage, sir.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The
All-Knowing."
Oh ho! The Fourth
Hokage, you say?!