-Kabuto, I can fill you in
about this child later on.
For now, why don't you signal to
the three baby rats behind you
to come on out?
[laughs]
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): So he
must have known all along.
-There's the signal.
-Well, it's you again.
-Mm, I know that
face all too well.
And it looks like the
nine-tails tagged along.
Well, we might as well
have a little fun together.
Let's find out who's gotten
stronger, you or Sasuke.
-Give Sasuke back.
You give him back.
-It's not as simple
as giving him back.
Really, you're way off here.
Sasuke came to us
of his own accord.
You can't dwell on
the past like this.
It's unbecoming of a man.
-Shut up, four eyes.
You don't understand
how people really feel.
You only understand cold logic.
-If you really want
to know about Sasuke,
then I'm afraid
you're just going
to have to force it out of me--
if you think you're up to it.
[theme music]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, what is this?
SAI (VOICEOVER): What is that?
-I see.
So it's just as I feared.
-Judging by the shape the chakra
was taking, the number of tails
will probably grow.
And eventually, they'll be nine.
-That about sums it up.
-Master Jiraiya, how
many tails have you seen?
-Hm.
In all my years of living, I've
come close to death only twice.
The first time, I broke
six ribs, both arms,
and ruptured a handful
of internal organs.
That was when I was caught
doing research at a hot spring,
and Tsunade beat me like a drum.
The second time--
the second was back
when Naruto and I were
off training together,
and the fourth tail appeared.
His anger acts like a trigger.
The number of tails increases
along with his rage.
He was able to
maintain consciousness
with the appearance of
the first three tails.
But after the fourth,
his mind was overpowered.
All that was left was a
hunger for destruction.
He was like a smaller version
of the nine-tailed fox.
-That far gone?
Even with the
fourth Hokage seal?
-I can't say what's causing it,
but one thing is for certain.
The fourth Hokage seal
formula seems to be weakening,
near as I can tell anyway.
-The fourth Hokage
sealing jutsu?
-Hard to believe.
-There's more.
When Naruto is cloaked in
the chakra of the nine tails,
I know it looks like
he's being protected,
but the truth is his
body is continuously
being harmed by
that same chakra.
When the fourth tail
emerged, his whole body
suffered severe injuries.
He ran amok covered in blood.
Once the cloak had
finally disappeared,
Naruto's internal nine tails
chakra began healing his body.
But if he continues this
cycle of egregious harm
and rapid recovery, his
body will pay the price,
and the span of his
life will be shortened.
-That's exactly why we need
you for this mission, Yamato.
After all, you carry
the cells of the First
Hokage in your blood.
-You alone possess the ability
to control the jinchuriki now.
It's in your blood.
Luckily, Naruto also wears
the First Hokage's necklace.
We're counting on you.
-Naruto, you've come a long way
as a jinchuriki, haven't you?
The power of the nine tails
gets stronger and stronger.
-Jinchuriki wield unimaginable
power thanks to their resonance
with the beast they carry.
-Naruto.
-You're starting to act
more like a jinchuriki,
aren't you, boy?
Now I see.
That's why he was chosen
to be your watch dog, yes?
Seems some of my experiments
came in handy after all.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Experiments?
-Honestly, the
Leaf Village really
ought to be more grateful to me.
[laughs] Wouldn't you agree,
my darling little test subject?
-Test subject?
Who exactly is this guy?
-Years ago, when I still walked
amongst the fools of the hidden
Leaf Village, I sought the
power of the shinobi, who
was not only the ultimate
wood style ninjutsu master,
but also the one person
who had total control
over tailed beasts,
the First Hokage.
[laughs] I extracted some
DNA samples from the First's
remains and conducted
an experiment,
implanting genetic
components into the cells
of 60 worthy children.
But their bodies violently
rejected the treatment.
They perished in rapid
succession, one after another.
Just as I was closing
the book on the subject,
someone stumbled onto one
of my other experiments.
I was forced to flee, leaving
my laboratory exactly as it was.
I thought all the test
subjects had succumbed.
I never dreamed there'd
be any survivors.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
So that's it.
-Four pillar prison jutsu.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): But-- but
isn't that wood style ninjutsu,
a secret ninjutsu known
only to the Hokage?
How is Captain Yamato
able to use it?
No wonder he can use
the First's ninjutsu.
-So that's his story.
How fascinating.
We are looking at the end result
of your work all those years
ago.
You can observe the
fruits of your labor.
-There's no question
he's intriguing.
But I wonder more about Sasuke.
He needs to stretch his wings.
Maybe we could put
his growth to the test
by pitting him
against Naruto here.
-You don't own him.
-Hm?
-Sasuke doesn't belong to you!
Don't you talk about
Sasuke like you own him.
Especially in front of
me, you rotten bastard!
-Oh, no.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What is that chakra?
SAI (VOICEOVER):
The air is stinging.
-Interesting.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
There's no question.
It's the nine tails
cloak, three tails.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): That's
the power of the jinchuriki.
I can sense it, this
terrifying chakra.
No one could ever control it.
SAI (VOICEOVER): So
this is his power.
No, the nine-tails'
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Such force
from chakra alone.
What's worse, he's letting
his emotions fuel his rage.
He is oblivious
to all around him.
This power of his, it
could be just the chance
I've been hoping for.
Failure will not be tolerated.
This is it.
My true mission for
Lord Danzo starts now.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
the top secret mission begins.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Anvu
intelligence report.
Profile on Kabuto Yakushi.
No one is closer to
Orochimaru than Kabuto,
a man shrouded in mystery.
An enemy survivor of the
battle at Kikyo Pass,
he was taken in by the captain
of the Leaf medical unit
and raised as a son.
Hence, little is known
of his real origins.
He hid his true
skill in the Leaf
by posing as an average genin.
But in battle, his masterful
handle of medical ninjutsu
proved a challenge
even for Tsunade.
Originally one
Sasori's agents, Kabuto
came to admire the man
he'd been sent to spy on,
and his loyalties
swung to Orochimaru.
But his intentions, much like
the man himself, are an enigma.
His case still remains open,
and further investigation
is recommended.