-I'm not done yet.
-Over here!
NAGATO: Fate had led
us right to them.
JIRAIYA: What do you want?
NAGATO: We finally found him.
Jiraiya-sensei.
-Huh?
-Damn, enemies.
YAHIKO: Run now.
get out of here!
KONAN: Nagato, go!
NAGATO: But I couldn't
truly accept a Hidden Leaf
ninja as a teacher.
I'm sure that you know what
that's like, don't you?
[theme music]
Please, will you
teach us ninjutsu?
You're all ninja from the
Hidden Leaf, aren't you?
KONAN: Thank you all.
This is for you.
-These kids-- shall I kill them?
We've seen so many war orphans.
It's always so pitiful.
They'd be better off if
we simply put them out
of their misery right now.
-Enough, Orochimaru.
You go on ahead with
Tsunade for now.
I'm gonna stay here and look
after these three for a while.
-What?
-It's the least I can do
after what they've suffered.
NAGATO: My parents were killed
by ninja of the Hidden Leaf.
ALL: Thank you for the food!
-Instant grilled
fish, thanks to--
NAGATO: But I started to
realize that Jiraiya-sensei
might be different.
-Hey, I think I've gotten
the hang of fishing, sensei.
JIRAIYA: Oh!
You're becoming more
promising all the time.
-The four of us began living
under the same roof together.
Soon after, a certain
incident took place.
-Incident?
[slap]
-Yahiko!
NAGATO: A renegade
shinobi attacked us.
When Yahiko was
almost killed, that's
when I struck out and
killed that ninja, instead.
I did it without even realizing.
-You all right, Yahiko?
Talk to me.
NAGATO: It seems I had a
special power inside me.
The visual jutsu
known as the Rinnegan.
After that, Jiraiya-sensei was
no longer hesitant to train us,
and began to teach us ninjutsu.
He said that he
just wanted us to be
able to protect ourselves.
But in terms of
me specifically, I
feel he wanted to
help me control
the power of the Rinnegan.
But I feared my own power.
Hate had caused
me to go berserk.
I didn't know who might get
hurt if it happened again.
I convinced myself
that what I had done
was wrong, and became
consumed with guilt.
But sensei pulled me from
the depths of despair.
-Is it that incident?
-That day, when that
ninja hurt Yahiko,
I was just so angry at him.
Everything went
blank in my head.
I didn't know what I was doing.
And before I realized
it, the guy was dead.
After that, I just
became so frightened.
That hatred, it made me go
completely blind with rage,
and I killed somebody
because of it.
I know that it was wrong.
It was wrong!
-Nagato.
I don't know.
I can't really say whether what
you did was right or was wrong.
But, thanks to your actions,
Yahiko is still alive now.
You saved your friend's life.
I believe that's always
the right thing to do.
No one can fault you
for helping a friend.
NAGATO: Before I realized
it, I'd accepted Sensei.
-Once you've been hurt, you
learn what it is to hate.
But if you hurt another,
you become hated
and you shoulder
a sense of guilt.
-However, it's because
one understands
pain such as that that one
becomes generous toward others.
Experiencing pain helps
us to grow up, to mature.
And growing up means
that one becomes
able to think for one's self
and make one's own decisions.
To know and to
reflect upon pain,
and then to come up
with one's own answer.
Jiraiya-sensei seemed
to be asking himself
the same question, but he hadn't
figured out a solution either.
Just like you haven't been
able to provide any answers.
Back then, I was able to come
up with an answer right away.
-All I wanna do is protect
those two, no matter what kind
of pain I may be forced
to endure for them.
-I understand.
-Tell me, sensei, what are
you always thinking about?
What has you so preoccupied?
-There's so much war and
hatred in this world.
Sometimes it seems like
they're the only things that
really exists.
I wanna do something about it.
And I'd really like to know
what the answer to finding
true peace is.
NAGATO: After we
trained for three years,
both my body and
soul grew stronger,
and I felt as if I had matured.
But Jiraiya-sensei's
words always
kept echoing back to me
from somewhere deep inside.
He told me that he wondered if
the solution to bringing peace
to the world lay
with my Rinnegan.
-Once, a really long time ago,
people did nothing but battle.
It was all just one,
big unending war.
That era was even worse
than what we have now.
Then, there came a day when
a mysterious monk appeared.
The first to discover the
inner workings of chakra.
And he tried to lead
the world toward peace.
It is said he traveled
across the world,
teaching ninshu,
the shinobi creed.
Time passed, and ninshu came
to be known as ninjutsu.
Ninjutsu wasn't originally
about fighting power.
It's a teaching intended to
guide people towards peace.
That monk was known as
the Sage of the Six Paths.
He was considered the
savior of the world.
And like you, he
possessed the Rinnegan.
I am he who shall
bring peace and order.
Those were said to
be the sage's words.
I think he believed there would
come a time when people truly
would understand one
another and live in harmony.
Perhaps, Nagato, you're
actually the reincarnation
of the Sage of the Six Paths.
I have the feeling
that your eyes
may realize the
hopes of that sage.
NAGATO: Sensei entrusted
me with his quest,
conferring his wish
for peace on me,
and then left the three of us.
We started gathering comrades.
With Yahiko as our
leader, our organization
quickly gained fame.
People approved
of our philosophy
of trying to construct a
peace that was minimally
based on military might.
However, the world was caught
up in a war between the three
great nations.
The Stone, Leaf, and Sand.
Hanzo, the leader
of the Hidden Rain,
heard rumors of our
organization and approached us.
He could no longer
ignore our existence.
He proposed to make us
a nexus in the effort
to launch peace negotiations
between the three
great nations.
Our power would be used to
illicit mutual agreement
from all the parties.
We decided to
accept his proposal.
But that decision would
lead us only to misfortune.
We were naive children.
-Misfortune?
What happened to
you guys after that?
-What happened is, Yahiko died.
-He died?
-It was all merely a trap
that Hanzo had laid for us.
He was paranoid
that we were going
to steal his power
over the Hidden Rain,
and for that petty fear, Yahiko.
The next day at the
rendezvous point
where the negotiations
were to occur,
Hanzo's subordinates and the
Hidden Leaf's ANBU Black Ops
were already there.
Hanzo had allied with
a man from the Hidden
Leaf named Danzo
to eradicate us.
Danzo wanted to usurp
the seat of Hokage,
while Hanzo wanted to protect
his own position of power.
-Your organization has
become a nuisance to me.
Yahiko, you're the
leader, so you must die.
Resist and I'll
kill her instead.
You.
Redhead.
Use that to kill Yahiko.
If you do, I'll spare
you and the girl.
-Don't, Nagato!
Forget about me.
Just get away, both of you!
YAHIKO: Nagato.
Just kill me.
-All I wanna do is
protect the two of them,
no matter what kind of
pain I'm forced to endure.
-Nagato!
-Don't do it!
-Hurry up.
Do you want this woman to die?
-Konan.
Yahi--
-You and Konan must
survive, no matter what.
You are the savior
of this world.
I know you can do it.
-Yahiko!
-I have big dreams, and I'm
gonna make them come true.
-Kill him.
-If all of this useless
fighting doesn't stop,
then I'll become a
god and make it stop!
-He repelled them.
-How?
-Did we get him?
-Nagato.
-Konan.
Hold onto Yahiko and stay still.
-Impressive, boy.
You escaped even while being
hit by my Fire Style Jutsu.
You're no ordinary
brat, are you?
Those eyes.
-Get him!
-Summoning Jutsu.
Gedo Statue.
-But that's--
-What?
What is that?
-Nagato.
No, don't use that.
-Run!
If it touches you, you die!
[shouting]
-It appears you were in the
shadows as the real leader.
That you possess the
Rinnegan is quite a surprise.
-Nagato.
-Teleportation Jutsu.
-Yahiko died, and
from then on, I
took over as the leader
of our organization.
I thought that I had grown up,
but nothing had changed at all.
It was the same as
when my parents died.
I was wrong.
I realized then that the
answer I had given Jiraiya
was worth nothing.
I owed Yahiko my life.
He gave me my dream.
He was an irresistible
friend for whom
I would've given everything.
Yahiko's loss.
That was my second great pain.
[theme music]
MAN: It appears to have ended.
MAN: And how did it turn out?
-It's as my vision foretold.
Although I never thought it
would turn out like this.
Perhaps it's possible that in
that moment when Jiraiya chose
not to give up, all
this became preordained.
NARUTO: Next time on
"Naruto Shippuden."
The Tale of Naruto Uzumaki.
That's my answer.
-Boy, it sure has been a really
long time since the three of us
got together, hasn't it?
-Yeah, you got that right.
-Not since we all reunited
during the invasion
of the village.
-Not to mention it's been
years since the Ino Shika Cho
trio was famous
across the nations.
-Hey, we're not has
beens yet, you know.
-Say, why don't we do it once
more for old times' sake?
-Sounds good to me.
-All right, let's do it!
-Formation Ino!
-Shika!
-Cho!
-We still got it.
-Yep.
-You just can't beat hanging
out with old friends, can you?
-Hm.
Wait.
Didn't we invite someone
else to join us today?
I could swear that we
just saw him yesterday.
-Oh, yeah.
We talked about
getting together.
-So who was it?
-Think hard.
They say the memory's
the first thing to go.
-Sir?
-Huh?
-Can I take your order?
-I ordered two hours ago.
-Sorry!
-I guess that being
forgotten runs in the family.
[theme music]