I'm sorry to cause you
shame, Lords Kinkaku
and Ginkaku,
It's also hard for me to
dishonor the two rays
of light among the clouds.
i'm sorry for the
disrespect, but I'm going
to have to shame both
of you a little
right now.
I'm afraid I might end
up stripping away the
shine from your
gold and silver.
With just a single strike
of my Gale Style.
Though it'll be
dull.
Hmm. Mm.
Just calm down,
Raikage.
You're supreme
commander, remember?
You don't know just
how fearsome the
Gold and Silver
brothers are!
I can't believe there's
actually something
that you're afraid of!
Hmph. No, you're
wrong. It's not
that I'm scared...
But those two... remain
the most reviled
criminals in the
whole history of
the Hidden Cloud...
A while back at the
formal ceremony to
cement our
alliance with the
Leaf, they staged
a coup...
... and launched
attacks against both
the Second Raikage
and Second Hokage.
(Explosions)
They wielded the five
Treasured Tools of the
Sage of the Six Paths,
and they drove the
second Hokage to the
brink of death.
Who are those two
Shinobi? They possess
the Nine Tails' chakra,
and they
have a lot of it.
But I'd never heard
that they possessed
the Nine Tail's chakra.
Yes, well, years
ago it seems that
the Hidden Cloud
made an attempt
to go and capture
the Nine Tails.
And during that
venture, the Nine
Tails devoured both
of the Gold
and Silver brothers.
[Growls]
(Raikage)
But they were so
unruly, thrashing
around in his belly
that the Nine
Tails couldn't stand
it. So he vomited
them both back
up.
Since then, they've
both borne the Nine
Tails' chakra.
Not surprising,
they were inside the
Nine Tails' for
more than two
weeks.
That's quite a
far-fetched tale. But
what are the rumors
that they were able
to wield the Treasured
Tools of the Sage
of the Six Paths? Is
there any truth to
them at all?
No ordinary human
can wield those
tools.
They drain away chakra
and massive amounts
of it. So most who
try, die.
Except for someone
who harbors the Nine
Tails' chakra like
those two monsters do.
They're shinobi with
enormous, fiendish
chakra who wreak havoc
wherever they go.
And they fear nothing.
Not even the Nine Tails.
So what really scares
me about them
is the thought of all
our subordinates
having to face both
of them in battle.
I gotta say, I really
don't like the tone
you're using towards
your seniors
but I'll shut you up.
It can't be helped.
It simply seems that too
much time has passed.
It's almost as if
our comrades have
never even heard of
us before.
Samui, Atsui.
If you two are
actually the Gold and
Silver Brothers we
read about in
our history books. Then
I'd rather not be
called your comrade.
It isn't cool.
Ha! The usually cool-
headed lady is feeling
red hot today, I see.
Those two really
must be something.
Let's do this,
Ginkaku!
Sure thing,
Kinkaku!
Hold up,
are those?!
There's no doubt.
Those must be the Gold
and Silver Brothers'
ninja tools that we
learned about years
ago. They have four
out of the five
ultimate ninja tools,
which the Hidden Cloud
collected long ago.
(Samui cont'd)
Kokinjo, the gold
rope squeezes out the
victim's spirit word.
(Samui cont'd)
Shichiseiken, the seven
stars blade severs and
curses that spirit word.
(Samui cont'd)
Benihisago, the crimson
gourd records it and
seals its speaker inside!
(Samui cont'd )
And Bashosen, the Leaf
fan conjures up all five
chakra natures.
Quite a lecture,
and I really hate
to interrupt, but...
(Atsui)
I got this!
Cloud style!
Flame slice!
(Atsui)
Those ninja tools
maybe flashy, but...
They're still only
tools!
They don't stand a
chance against our
ninjutsu, that's fueled
by our blazing hot souls!
No, Atsui, wait!
Just stay cool and
let me finish!
He's too hot
hot headed!
Heh. They talk too
much; this'll be just
perfect. Are you ready
yet?
I'll take the one
in the back.
You got it, Ginkaku!
Just leave the others
to me.
He avoids my hot
fighting spirit to
attack Darui instead!?
You really think you
can escape my hot attacks
by putting these guys
in between us?!
AHH!!
You have to stay cool
and pay attention
to what's going on
Atsui!
(Painful grunts)
Woah, that was a
scorching hot punch!
(Fighting Grunts)
Ah!
Damn it.
Atsui! Samui!
You guys all right?
Don't look away when
you're fighting me,
you brat!
Change places,
Kinkaku!
Right, Ginkaku!
(Grunt) I can't
even stop one enemy!?
Samui, Atsui, I'm
sorry!
Ha! I get to be
your opponent this
time!
I gotta admit, that
Kinkaku fellow packed
a pretty hot punch!
Now I'm up against
old man Ginkaku, huh?
I think it's time we
squeeze him, Kokinjo!
What is this?!
What's happening!?
Kokinjo here on my
left arm squeezes out
the Spirit Word of
whoever touches it!
Curse them!
Shichiseiken!
(Chuckle) Now
record them!
Benihisago!
All right! That's it.
I'm done here, Kinkaku.
Ha!
We're finished.
Too bad that we're not
done with you! it's our
turn now and we're gonna--
You should have let
me finish my
explanation..
Listen, you can't
speak carelessly from
this point on.
Why? What do you mean?
Atsui and I have a
cursed jutsu and sealing
jutsu cast against us.
Our spirit word have
been taken hostage.
And that means the
next time we utter the
word or phrase,
that we've said
most since birth.
(Samui cont'd)
We will be pulled into
that gourd and sealed
away inside.
My, my, aren't
we knowledgeable.
Seems that as time
passed, all sorts of
secrets have been
revealed.
The word that we've
said most since birth
is now forbidden
to us!?
Come on, we're
not playing some
silly word game here?
This is all getting
so dull.
(Kinkaku)
I see...
Bashosen!
What is it?
What's the hot word
that I say most often?!
What could it be?!
(Samui)
You shouldn't need
to think so hard. It's
pretty obvious.
Uh!
Scroll of fire!
Ahh-
Ah! It's so hot!
Ahh!
You fool!
Atsui!
You know there's
an old saying, that
silence is golden.
The tongue is a
source of misfortune.
Right, Ginkaku?
(Ginkaku)
Yeah, Kinkaku!
This is what happens
when you can't shut up.
Words are merely
tools and people use
them to trick each
other through lies.
Just wait until you
encounter Bee, You'll
rethink what words are
for then.
Who's this Bee?
I know of no such
person!
If you move then
I'll kill her. And
I'm not lying about
that.
I'm sorry, Samui.
Yahh!
Ah!
As I expected.
You've both proven
yourselves to be true
Hidden Cloud shinobi.
Gale Style!
(Darui)
Laser Circus!
(Ginkaku)
So fast.
And it's Precision
Ninjutsu?!
(Ginkaku)
Ahh!
Ah! Don't you
underestimate us,
brat!
(Grunt)
Good job hitting
him with the
Kokinjo, Kinkaku.
This one's first,
though.
What's going on?!
She didn't say
anything!
Why did she
get trapped?!
Curse them!
Shichiseiken!
His arm regenerated
already?!
And now record
it, Benihisago!
I think I know
what my forbidden
word is.
Though it'll
be dull.
(Darui)
This is all
getting so dull!
My forbidden word...
The word I've said
most often in my life,
is probably dull.
(Darui)
As long as I
don't say it
(Darui)
I won't get
sucked into that
gourd.
(Darui)
But Samui got
trapped and she
didn't say anything.
(Darui)
So that means.
You can get trapped
if your silent for
too long, too!
Am I right?
Sharp of you to
notice. I think you're
the first person ever
to figure that out.
(cont'd)
You're a smart
one, then.
But just a little
while ago you told
us all that silence
is golden!
But sometimes speech
is golden. Successful
deceit is the truest
proof of eloquence.
And in this case
silence is prohibited.
It's the most
forbidden taboo!
Ha ha ha!
Didn't I just
tell you? Words
are merely tools
that people use to
trick each other,
nothing more.
In the Shinobi world,
deceit and betrayal
are acceptable battle
tactics.
Words are ninja
tools, too.
And is it any
wonder that you two
are considered symbols
of disgrace among
the HIdden Cloud?
What did you just
say to me, you
puny little wimp?!
I won't stand here
and indulge your
insults. You're
nothing but a mere
pawn of the Raikage's!
(Ginkaku cont'd)
You're just an imitation
ninja tool! So shut up!
What in the hell is
wrong with the ninja
of today?
Boss, I'm so sorry.
You chose me to be
you trusted bodyguard
but then you lost
your left arm.
No, Darui.
Don't blame yourself.
(Darui)
But...
I can manage fine
without a left arm.
Cause after all, I've
got two perfectly
good right arms
here already.
Two of them?
Yeah. This one.
(Raikage cont'd)
And you, Darui!
(Chuckle)
Hey, how about you
include Cee and give
yourself a third one,
too?
(Chuckle)
Well sure, sounds good.
The more the merrier
isn't that right?
I'm no fake. I'm
the bosses right hand
man! You will indulge
me!
Ha!
(Kinkaku)
Hey, Ginkaku
(Ginkaku)
What is it, Kinkaku?!
(Kinkaku)
Get Benihisago ready.
Hm?
Oh, I get it.
But why?!
I didn't even say
the word "dull."
I'm no fake. I'm
the boss's right
hand man! You will
indulge me!
Wait, I get it
now! I said you
will indulge me.
That word, indulge!
Indulge!
Dull, no!
Ah! Damn it!
Darui, I want you
to be an Allied Forces
company captain.
You will be my
right hand man.
I'm so sorry, boss.
Being your right
hand man made me
so proud.
(Darui cont'd)
I'm sorry, Samui,
Atsui.
(Darui cont'd)
I'm sorry.
(Darui)
I wish I could
say I'm sorry
to everyone.
We should probably
join the fight,
Ginkaku?
All right, Kinkaku.
(Splash)
What?!
How the hell?!
Mm-Ah!
Ahh!
(Grunt)
Damn it! I
touched the Kokinjo!
Why wasn't he
trapped?!
I...
I'm sorry about
the desk and the
wall there.
(Darui)
I'm sorry to cause
you shame, Lords
Kinkaku and Ginkaku.
It's also hard for
me to dishonor the
two rays of light
among the clouds.
Samui, Atsui,
I'm really sorry.
I guess that means
I'm a pretty humble
guy! That's not a
bad thing at all.
(Kinkaku)
I know his word
was "dull..."
I'm so sorry, boss.
I'm sorry, Samui,
Atsui.
I wish I could
say I'm sorry...
(Darui)
...to everyone.
Do you really mean
to tell me that his
most uttered and
second most uttered
words switched their
orders while he was
getting pulled into
the gourd?! Huh?
Curse them,
Shichiseiken!
All right!
Now record them,
Benihisago!
I think I'm doing
this right so far...
What?! How
dare you!
(Darui)
They really do
knock the chakra
out of you...
It feels like I'm
gonna drop before
I can finish this...
Yeah, you're right.
It's true that words
may be tools that
people use to trick
each other.
(Darui cont'd)
But when it really
counts, the spoken
word...
Because after all,
I've got two perfectly
good right arms already.
This one...
...and you, Darui!
Sometimes, the
spoken word...
...can actually
be a really precious
thing. That's able
to relay the truth!
I need your help,
Kinkaku!
And that's the
exact reason that
I'm going to seal
you, right now!
Kinkaku!!
Ahh!
Samui, Atsui,
this was all thanks
to you. I swear I'll
get you out later.
One down, one
to go!
Why you, you
whelp!
How dare you!
What the hell?!
(Screams)
Hey, hey, hey,
No way. That's...
How dare you do
such a thing to
Ginkaku?!
You're going
to pay!
Now he looks,
just like the
Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki!
(Growls)
(Darui)
HQ has a plan!
We'll Strike at Kinkaku
with the Ino-Shika-
(Darui cont'd)
Cho Formation.
Until they get here,
we have to hold
(cont'd)
this location!
(Shikaku)
He may have the
Nine Tail's power,
but we have the
(cont'd)
power of the
Ino-Shika-Cho bond.
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
Golden Bonds.
(Shikaku)
Please hold on
somehow until they
get there!