"The Bridge to Peace"
Uh!
You will not escape!
[grunting]
You can't transport away
to safety this time.
You see, I've been paying
close attention to you
all these years...
When you transport
yourself elsewhere... you
must first materialize.
And it takes longer to
pull yourself in than
another person or
object.
If I hadn't switched from
flying to slipping past
that explosion, things
would have gotten very
bad very quickly...
I also know you can only
slip through objects for
no more than five
minutes.
What...?!
They're all Paper
Bombs!
I have amassed six
hundred billion Paper
Bombs. I'll make sure
that I kill you!
And they'll continue to
explode for ten minutes!
[grunting]
I encouraged and pushed
Yahiko to form the
Akatsuki.
And...
I was the one who gave
Nagato the Rinnegan.
Yahiko and Nagato were
acting of their own free
will.
They were not your pawns!
You and Konan must
survive, no matter
what...
Whatever it looked like
to you, they both fought
and died for their own
beliefs!
They will always share
that!
I won't let you
interfere!
[panting]
My Sacred Paper Emissary
Jutsu has come undone. I
didn't anticipate needing
this much chakra.
But... at least...
Madara...
... Is dead?
How?! How are you... not
dead?!
I ran the simulations
over and over. I was sure
this would work! You
should be dead!
The Izanagi, an Uchiha
forbidden jutsu where the
user sacrifices sight in
that eye to tie illusion
and reality together.
Only those who posses the
powers of both the Uchiha
and the Senju can perform
it.
The powers of both the
Uchiha and the Senju
combined...?
But that is the Six
Paths' power... And I
know that's not a power
that you possess...
[chuckling]
Since you are a dear and
former comrade,... I
suppose you deserve to
know that little bit of
my history...
The Izanagi is the
practical application of
what you know as the Sage
of Six Paths' Creation
of all Things.
Originally, the Uchiha
and the Senju were one.
Their originator, the
Sage of the Six Paths,
possessed the blood and
powers of both and
created many things.
Shadow Style, founded
upon mental energies that
govern imagination...
can be used to create
form out of nothing...
And Light Style, founded
upon physical energies
that govern life... can
be used to instill life
into that form.
The Tailed Beasts are one
example. The Sage used
the Shadow and Light
Styles to create nine
Tailed Beasts from Ten
Tails' chakra.
A jutsu that can make
fantasy into reality.
That is the Izanagi.
Just who are you...? And
what exactly are you...?!
The world believes that
Madara Uchiha lost to
Hashirama Senju.
But what is the real
truth? Victors are those
that look and plan ahead.
The true contest is just
beginning... I only fought
the previous battle to obtain
his power.
I am Madara Uchiha. I
possess the power of
Hashirama Senju.
I am the Second Sage
of the Six Paths. I
am unique.
A few have managed an
imperfect Izanagi, but
they were unable to
control Hashirama's power.
[groaning]
You'll be seeing Nagato
soon. You can discuss how
you both fell for
Naruto's foolish dreams.
There's no such thing as
peace!
There is no such thing as
hope!
Nagato only believed in
Naruto to find solace in
his pathetic existence.
[gasping]
This... can't be.
But Nagato... is someone who
will be the bridge that
leads to peace.
My role's to make that
happen. I'm a pillar that
will support that bridge.
It's Yahiko who'll be the
bridge to peace. That is,
his will itself is will be.
Seems this is it for
me... Naruto... I believe
you of all people...
can...
The never-ending Hidden
Rain downpour is letting
up? What's going on?!
Yahiko! Nagato! Their
wills shall not be
extinguished!
I too believe in Naruto!
And it's his turn now!
Naruto will be the bridge
to peace!
And I vow right now that
I shall be the pillar
that supports him!
Thank you, Nagato...
... for giving me hope
even from beyond the
grave.
I am expendable; I am
only a mere flower. But
I'll take you with me.
[grunting]
Huh!
Uh!
You called me darkness.
Well then, I shall make
you wilt. And cause this
sparkling rainbow bridge
of yours to fade into the
darkness as well.
[choking]
When my genjutsu' is
finished, you will be,
too. After I've made you
tell me where the Rinnegan is.
[choking]
So this is the place.
You were the third Sage
of the Six Paths.
You exerted so much power
that your red hair, proof of
your Uzumaki Clan lineage,
turned white.
You betrayed me, and
still you laugh at me?
That took too long.
I'd better go.
Konan's is the one on the
right. Yahiko's in the
middle. And Nagato's the
one on the left.
But what are they?
You'll flip for these
flip tiles!
Flip tiles, huh?
That's right. The front
side, which you see here,
is red, and the back is
white.
You just flip them over
like this!
Uhhh...
[coughing]
Anyway... listen...
When you guys're here I
want each one of you to
have the red side of your
tile showing.
Then, when you leave to
go out, flip it over so
the white side is facing
out, like this.
This picture is a secret
code that says you'll be
returning shortly. Oh, yeah.
Sensei... What's with
the ridiculous grin?
You know we're only
letting you get away with
all of this frog stuff 'cause
you're the Toad Sage...
[gritting teeth]
But--
... what do these three
tiles have to do with
anything?
This region is still
unstable, so it's unsafe.
We could be targeted at
any time.
When we're in our
hideout, our
headquarters, the enemy
can locate us easily. If
we were scattered, we
could counter with a
surprise attack, for
example.
So if the red side of a
person's tile is showing
but they're not here,
then it could mean that
they've been kidnapped or
something.
Or if the white side is
showing but that person
is in the room, it could
mean that they're really
an enemy, transformed.
With this system, we can
notice stuff like that,
right?
Yes, that's exactly
right. Nicely deduced,
Konan; you're pretty
sharp! Unlike Yahiko here.
I knew! I knew it, too!
Oh...?
Uh, I mean I mostly knew
it...
[giggling]
Anyway, only we three
know this code. It'll help
us know where everyone is
at any given time.
We can't ever really
relax, even when we're at
home, right here in our
own hideout. Also...
I've constructed a secret
room under here with an
underground escape passage
that leads outside.
Wow, that is so shinobi!
If anything happens, use
it to get away.
Oh, and by the way...
The tile back there
behind you is mine.
All right, now it's time
for today's lesson! I
call this "Water in a
Frog's Face" training!
You'll hone your
endurance by becoming a
frog and learning not to
react to anything thrown
in your face!
All right! Yes!
Come on, you
guys, let's go!
Yahiko, do you really get
why we're doing all this?
Sensei turned them around
for us this time, but you
need to do it.
I'm going to get real
strong, I swear! And
then...
I'm going to change the
entire world!
Uh!
[giggling]
[smiling]
Hm!
[chuckling]
Before you start changing
things, you should first
learn to change your tile
like I just showed you!
Wait... is that the look
I gave them before? How
embarrassing!
Uh!
Clever... She used the
Wind Style to speed up
her Paper Shuriken.
However...
[grunting]
Not again!
It's not good enough yet.
You have to move quicker
and coordinate your
attacks better!
All right! Let's eat!
Thanks for the food!
Hey! No fair, Sensei!
Oh, is that so?
That's mine!
[laughing]
It's not funny!
Jiraiya Sensei... Thank
you...
[panting]
Are you the Akatsuki?
Who's that?
The head of the Hidden
Rain, Hanzo of the
Salamander.
Who's your leader?
I am Yahiko! And I lead
the Akatsuki!
I shall remember you.
Yahiko...?
So what did that mean?!
Hanzo acknowledged us.
We're staring to be taken
seriously.
Our organization has
gotten too big. We need a
new hideout.
Today's our last day
here.
Yeah...
This is where all of us
grew up. And became
strong.
Everything started right
here for us.
We're leaving to chase
our dreams and make them
come true. And then...
Uh!
Where'd they go?
I can't believe that
secret room came in handy
at the end.
Okay, now that was
unexpected. But it was
appropriate, I guess.
Now, let's go! Nagato!
Konan!
We're leaving to chase
our dreams and make
them come true. And
then...
Once that happens...
Even if we're split
apart...
Let's meet back here
one day.
And we'll all
celebrate together!
In that case, we should
invite Jiraiya Sensei,
too!
Yeah!
Heh. Good point.
Well, it sure took a
while, but you got
yourself a nice new eye.
It was always mine.
Oh. By the way, this just
arrived as well.
And what is it?
It's some intel from
Kisame.
We know where the
Nine Tails is.
Looks like everything's
back on track.
From Kisame, huh...?
Time to go collect
the Nine Tails.
We must assume the enemy
knows our location.
We're going to have to
move Naruto out of here
immediately, but we
can't let him know
about the war.
Yes, we'll have to fool
him somehow...
All right! This is just
the kind of mission I've
been waiting for!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Super
Secret S-Rank Mission.
Good thing he's not so
smart
"ROCK LEE'S SILLY
CHRONICLES: PART 2"
[yelling]
Hop! Step! Jump!
Are you watching me,
Sakura?!
Uh!
How far?!
[blowing whistle]
Foul!
[groaning]