Now's my chance!
Damn it, that guy is
fast! No doubt about it!
Huh!
But...
I'll try again!
They're so fast, I can't
track them!
Huh?
Do you really think you
can defeat me with your
Lariat?!
[coughing]
Oh, no! Octopops!
If you have time to
worry, worry about
yourself!
Bee?! Why are you doing
this?!
Don't you get it yet,
Bro? Ya hear me? Fool, ya
fool!
Octopops! Thanks, I owe
you one!
Now I can get past the
Raikage.
[growling]
[grunting]
Huh?!
Hokage! Get in here
and help me!
Lady Tsunade?
I won't give up!
Naruto, you don't have to
protect me! Stop,
already!
Dreams don't come true
when you're dead!
Heh, don't worry
about me!
Get out of the way,
Naruto! don't do it!
Until the day that I
become Hokage... Whatever
happens...
There's no way I'm gonna
die!
Huh!
[gasping]
Uh!
Granny!
Hokage! You'd better have
a real good excuse for
this course of action!
"Two Suns"
Hokage! You'd better have
a real good excuse for
taking this course of
action!
Look, even if you were to
kill Naruto. And you buy
us some time until Nine
Tails comes back to life,
I doubt the next
Jinchuriki will be able
to control Nine Tail's
power to this degree!
Since we don't have any
idea which way this war
will go, let's use all
the weapons we've
got... including the
Jinchuriki!
That's why I'll let
Naruto pass!
Nice excuse! I mean, nice
explanation! Now you're
talking!
Now, that's the Granny Hokage
that I remember. The one who
won't let anyone stop her!
Hokage. Who's the one
that's just making
arbitrary decisions now?!
You're all fools.
Where is there any
evidence that Naruto will
succeed?
I already told you your
Lariat won't work against
me!
Listen, Bro... you may be
Raikage, but since the
beginning, you've
underestimated my power,
fool, ya fool!
No one ever expected the
Third Raikage to die.
Hey, where's my Bro? Over
there? Over there?
All of a sudden, he just
started punching his way
out through the wall.
There's gonna be a bunch
of holes in walls now...
Follow them, and you should
be able to find him.
Thanks, will do. I'll
look for Bro beyond the
walls I go through.
It'll be okay, just hang
in there, Bro. From today
on, you're the Raikage,
yo.
I know that!
We're right in the middle
of a war!
I will protect this
village and nation to the
very end! As my old man
wanted!
Bee...
You will go to Unraikyo,
the Storm Cloud Ravine,
and work on your Tailed
Beast Bomb.
You will not be engaging
the enemy.
What?
Yo, but my Lariat, that's
where it's at-
I don't need your
Lariat anymore!
Even if the enemy
invades, you'll stay in
the village and use your
long-range Tailed Beast
Bomb to get them.
All right?! You are never
to leave the village
again! Got it?!
Bee, both you and Naruto
are precious Jinchuriki!
The two of you are very
special to your villages
and your nations.
And that's the reason why
I can't let either of you
pass!
No matter how powerful
you two are,... don't
forget that the Akatsuki,
our enemy, has already
taken down and sealed
away all the other
Jinchuriki!
Just trust me, we ain't
gonna lose, Naruto and
me.
And about that I'll
happily give you my
personal guarantee.
So be it, then! Let's put
it to the test!
Your Lariat against mine!
We'll see who's stronger!
Bee, we still have a long
way to go before the
Double Lariat is where it
needs to be.
I'm still toning down my
strength to match yours.
You're going to have to
get stronger!
I'm gonna surpass you
someday, you'll see! And
on that day, I will be
carefree!
That sounds ideal to me.
And I'll do it, too,
you'll see! Easy as
one-two-three! 'Cause
taking you down is my
fantasy!
No way!
[grunting]
The thing is, being
Jinchuriki isn't our only
power source...
We possess something
that's even stronger
fundamentally.
I'll tell you all the
details. You know your
words to me, and me
alone, back before I
received the Eight
Tails
They'll keep me strong,
no matter what happens,
even when all else fails.
Hmm...
It can be anything.
You'll know it when you
find it. Because it will
keep you strong.
So make sure that Bee
finds it.
All right...
You know, Bee, you really
are very special to me!
You and I are the
ultimate tag team, after
all!
You're talking about...
those words I said to you
in front of the Waterfall
of Truth?
You're finally getting
it, huh? So you're not a
fool, ya fool?
Preaching truth at you
from above is my fantasy.
The fantasy is now a
reality, oh-yay!
White Zetsu uses a
Transformation Jutsu that
can even mimic chakra.
Is there a way to see
through such a jutsu?
[groaning]
Nothing helpful in these
papers either...
Don't you think that we
should relay this intel
to Lord Raikage and Lady
Hokage?
Not yet. The two of them
decided to leave me in
charge here, so I'll handle
this situation.
Besides, we don't want to
bother them. They need to
concentrate on stopping
Naruto and Lord Bee.
But that's the thing...
You see, Lady Tsunade has
already-
I'm looking at new data
right now!
It's imperative that I
come up with a solution
right away! So please,
let me focus.
It's true that you are
very special to me, Bee.
And I do believe we're
the ultimate tag team. I
said that to you, you're
correct.
But just those simple
words are really going to
be enough to keep you
strong all through the
battle that you'd face?
I don't live and fight
just for the village and
nation. I live and fight
for you, too, Bro!
You're still way too
overprotective. You gotta
let me go.
Don't lose faith in me.
You gotta trust in my
power, you know?
The world is dark and
full of pain... when
you're a Jinchuriki.
But I learned you can't
give up, you gotta fight
free. You gotta find a
light that can let
yourself see.
Tailed Beasts are not the
only source of our power.
What we were before the
Tailed Beasts helps in
our weakest hour.
Our true selves shine like
the sun, they're second
to none.
Our true strength means
we will never have to
run.
Only I could control the
Eight Tails, only I could
win that fight.
Naruto's got the same
light inside as me, all
right?
But instead of only one,
that boy's rocking two
suns' light!
Huh?
Yeah, you got that right.
It really is like the
sun, and I'm rocking two
of them!
Naruto Uzumaki.
What are these two suns
that you and Bee have
spoken of?
I'm talking about my mom
and my dad!
Your mother and father?
You mean the Fourth
Hokage and Kushina
Uzumaki?
You're talking about
people who died right
after you were born! You
were merely an infant!
Something must have
happened during his
training to control the
Nine Tails' chakra.
Back when Naruto battled
Pain, he started
transforming into Nine
Tails. Minato had put his
essence into the seal's
jutsu formula. He
appeared and saved
Naruto.
I knew he wouldn't go
down without a fight!
When I was trying to
control Nine Tails'
power...
My Dad made sure that I
finally got to meet my
mom.
Dad said he'd woven Mom's
chakra into the seal. She
was able to hang out with
me while I undid the
Nine Tails' seal.
He did it all for me!
The Fourth Hokage had
studied the unique
Sealing Jutsu developed
by the Uzumaki Clan...
And Kushina's chakra and
life force were powerful,
without question. It is
possible.
As I thought!
When mom helped me get
this power, she told me
absolutely everything.
One time, long ago, dad
fought this guy in a
mask.
And during that battle...
he learned two things.
The first thing he
discovered... was that
this masked guy was gonna
try to destroy the future.
And the other thing he
learned... was that the
only one who could stop
the masked man was me.
But only if I had the
Nine Tails' power under
control.
Masked man... meaning
Madara?
So Madara did cause that
Nine Tails' incident was
Madara's doing after all?
Then this is why Minato
sealed Nine Tails inside
Naruto but left a key to
unlock it.
I knew he had to have a
reason. Minato never did
anything that was
unnecessary.
He must have concluded
that this masked man,
Madara, posed an enormous
threat to us... all of us.
And that only someone
with Nine Tails' power
under his control could
defeat this enemy.
So he chose Naruto.
Minato told you? And he
entrusted everything to
you, is that it?
He knew he wasn't the one
fated to be the savior?
I don't know if Dad ever
considered himself to be
a savior or not.
But then... I remember
that my master had always
told me...
My Dad was a Child of
Prophecy.
Do you remember what I
said to you earlier? That
so-called Savior is now
dead.
What else could you call
that outcome except a
failure?
Yeah, you're right. My
dad died. Mom, too.
He and my mom died
protecting the Hidden
Leaf from the enemy and
the Nine-Tailed Fox! They
died protecting me!
It only lasted a moment.
But they gave me
something.
Both of them gave me the
knowledge that what I'm
capable of is whatever I
believe I can do!
They entrusted me to be
the savior of the world!
Raikage!
If you take down Naruto
to delay our enemy's
plans, Madara will
definitely take the Nine
Tails next time.
And the world will come
to an end!
Only Naruto can control
the Nine Tails' power.
Just as Minato thought he
would!
We need to let Naruto go.
That way, he can protect
the shinobi.
I'm going to bet on
Naruto! So what about
you?
Yo, I gotta second her,
fool, ya fool!
Like you always said...
I'm a big fool, too!
You see, my good friend
Naruto here is just as
foolish as me. You agree?
Right now, you need some
big fools for us to
succeed.
Fools who don't care at
all, how strong or tall
the wall. Yeah!
[grunting]
Bro's at top speed, no
one's faster! I think
he's gonna kill Naruto!
What a disaster!
Just like always,
you're so stubborn.
But you're gonna have
to go through me, first!
I can't let Granny get
involved! This is my
fight!
Naruto, this
ends now!
Way too many people have
put their faith in me for
me to let them down!
No! I cannot fail!
Anyway, I've got my
own responsibilities.
I cannot fail now.
He dodged it?! No way,
fool, ya fool! He really
is!
Just like the Yellow
Flash of the Leaf!
Like you just said,
Raikage...
If I fail,... then I'm
not a savior.
I cannot fail now.
I'm my father's son!
He taught me to be the
savior, so that's what
I'll be!
My attack was simply a
test. I wanted to gauge
your abilities and
conviction.
You're only the second
to have ever outrun my
fastest punch.
So it appears... that we
have a savior after all.
Now go forth!
Yes, sir!
This really is the only
way.
According to this data,
Naruto can sense
hostility when in Nine
Tails Chakra Mode.
He'll be able to see
through White Zetsu's
transformation jutsu.
In addition, we can have
Naruto create Shadow
Clones To counter White
Zetsu on every
battlefield at once.
But if we delay any
longer, then I'm afraid
there will be no chance
of turning back.
But there's one big
problem...
This is a war in large
part to protect Naruto,
a Jinchuriki.
So if we throw him into
battle like that... we'd
be getting our priorities
backward.
I really don't think that
Lord Raikage would ever
allow us to use such a
strategy.
Yes... That's true.
Well...
That's the thing. That
doesn't seem to be the
case anymore.
The long night is finally
coming to an end.
They should be able to
use their eyes now.
Six new Pains. All
Jinchuriki.
I've just added a
little something.
Attacking the Blunt Blade
Helmet Splitter,
Kabutowari, has no
effect!
Trying to block me is
meaningless, too! This
next attack will end you!
Not yet! I hope you
don't think this will
be over so soon.
There's no way to block
the Blunt Blade Helmet
Splitter!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Helmet
Splitter: Jinin Akebino!"
Who said anything about
blocking?!