-I'm going to show the
world what true pain is,
and stop all the wars with the
terror that pain will inspire.
I shall lead the world down the
road to stability and peace.
-But if you do achieve
peace like that,
then the whole thing is
nothing but a big lie.
-Human beings are not the
most intelligent of creatures.
This is the only way that
peace can be achieved.
Of course, after
several decades,
that pain too will
eventually fade with time.
It will no longer
act as a deterrent.
Humanity will
return to war again.
This time, they themselves will
use the tailed beast weapon
against one another, and
reconfirm what true pain is,
and then for a time, peace
will briefly be restored again.
In the course of this
endless cycle of hatred
begetting more hatred,
this unbearable pain
will give rise to
momentary peace.
This is my dream and my goal.
-Nagato, please
don't push yourself.
You've already spent
so much chakra.
-Peace is now within our grasp.
[theme music]
-Hey, I guarantee everybody that
I'm going to be Hokage one day.
Just watch.
I'll show you all.
FEMALE SPEAKER 1: It's that boy.
The Nine Tails.
He's awful.
FEMALE SPEAKER 2: Hey, we're
not supposed to talk about that.
-Ko, what's the Nine Tails?
-Oh, it's nothing that you need
to worry about, Lady Hinata,
but you must stay
away from that boy.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-You argue that my mission
of peace is merely a lie.
But in this cursed
world, a peace
where people truly
understand each other
is nothing but fiction.
-But I truly
believe that the day
will come when all people
will understand one another
and live in harmony.
-But Pervy Sage believed
that one day people
would understand each
other and live in harmony.
You're the one who's wrong.
-Empty words.
You don't even have an answer
to how you'd achieve peace.
Your only option
now is to give me
the power of the Nine
tails for my own use.
And then after
that, as I told you,
your death would lead to peace.
-I want to grow up
to be a great ninja.
I'll be strong like my father.
And I'll be kind like my mother.
-Lord Hiashi is very
strict, but only
because he holds such
high hopes for you.
One day, you'll enter this
academy too, Lady Hinata.
-Will I make it?
-Yes, of course, you
will, so do your best.
-It's that boy.
-Lady Hinata, you mustn't
associate with that child.
-But why not?
-It's time for your training.
Let's go.
-Oh, Naruto.
-What's wrong, Neji?
That's Lord Jiraiya's
summoning frog.
-What?
-So most likely, we'll
find the real Pain
at one of the highest spots
near the Leaf village.
SHIKAKU: Right, let's
search every single site
that's at high altitude.
We need to be in two men
teams at the very least.
Even if you find the real
Pain, don't strike right away.
MALE SPEAKER: Please
include sensory tech ninjas
in the search parties too.
It'll go quicker.
SHIKAKU: right then.
Shikamaru, wait here with
Shiho for us to report in.
-I hate this, but there's no
choice since I can't move.
-Lady Katsuyu, if you
please, relay this
to all able-bodied
survivors in the village.
We need all the help
that we can get.
-Yes, sir.
Understood.
-I want to become a great
ninja, strong like my father
and kind like my mother as well.
To become a great ninja,
strong like father.
KO: Lady Hinata!
-Hey you.
-I'm sorry.
-Hold on She's a
Hyuga girl, isn't she?
-Yeah, she's got those eyes.
-She must be Neji's cousin then.
-And she's probably
stuck up like him too.
-Yeah, I bet she
thinks she's better
than us because of
her family and talent.
-No.
I'm not like that
at all, I swear.
-Come back here.
-Trying to run off without
telling us that you're sorry,
huh?
That's not cool.
-Yeah, that's right.
-Go on, apologize.
-And be nice about it too.
-Do it, now.
-I'm sorry.
-Not good enough.
Say it like you mean it.
-Apologize.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[groan]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Pain's
chakra is getting inside of me.
I've avoided any vital
spots and kept them shallow.
But you will no longer be
able to move on your own.
-Snap out of it, lad.
No matter what he
says to you, you
must not listen to any of it.
You are the child of prophesy.
The savior for this whole world.
Jiraiya boy and Pa risked
their lives for you
because they believed in you.
No, you're not allowed
to lose, Naruto boy.
If you give up now,
I won't forgive you.
You hear me?
Ahhh!
-Loud-mouthed frog.
-Bastard!
-It's time we were on our way.
-Lady Hinata.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): How cruel.
Restricting Naruto's
movement with those rods.
-I won't let you
hurt Naruto anymore.
-Reinforcements
-Why did you come out here?
Just run.
You can't win.
-No.
I'm just being selfish now.
-What's that mean?
Hinata, don't put yourself
in dangerous like this.
Just go.
I'm here because
I-- I want to be.
This time, I'm going
to save you Naruto.
I used to be such a crybaby.
Always given up before I
even got a chance to start.
I almost took the wrong paths
so many times, I lost count.
But you helped me
find my way and take
the correct path, Naruto.
I always chased after
you, wanting to catch up,
wanting to walk together
with you forever.
You've changed who I am, Naruto.
Your smiling face
saved me, Naruto.
That's why I'm not
afraid to die here
if it means I can protect
you, because I love you.
I always will.
-Hinata!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I can't
get close to Naruto like this,
but I have to do something.
I can't let it end like this.
If there's even the slightest
chance of reaching him,
I have to take it.
Gentle step twin lion fists.
-Nagato.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Now's my chance.
One more time.
-Hinata!
Knock it off.
-Huh?
-And what the heck do you want?
-Hey, wait, he's that kid.
That kid who's always
getting into trouble.
That kid everyone hates.
-Oh, that
-That kid, huh?
-Hey, I'm not that kid.
My name is Naruto Uzumaki.
I'm going to be Hokage one day.
Remember that.
-Hokage?
KID 1: Are you crazy?
KID 2: What a bunch of baloney.
KID 3: You're dense, kid.
[laughing]
-Some idiot kid like you
could never be Hokage.
-You want to fight?
You better not or
you'll regret it.
-What's that sign?
-Ha.
Clone--
-No way.
-Jutsu.
-How lame.
-What a loser.
-I caught you off
guard, didn't I?
You just watch.
I will become Hokage.
I'll show all of you.
I'll prove you all wrong.
-Get him.
Don't mess with us, kid.
We'll make you pay for that.
-Lady Hinata!
-Come on, let's get out of here.
-Lady Hinata, are you all right?
It's that boy.
Come along, Lady Hinata.
-No, wait, he came to help me.
-You mustn't get
involved with him.
Now, let's go.
-But, wait.
NARUTO: Hinata!
Hinata!
Hey!
Damn it!
Hinata!
Just stop.
Please, just stay away.
I don't quit and I don't run.
-People can't change no
matter how hard they try.
-That does it!
Who gave you the right to tell
her what she can or can't be?
Go on, Hinata.
I always thought you
were gloomy, timid,
terrified, and basically,
completely weird.
But you know what?
I actually like people like you.
-Why?
Why would someone as weak
as you try to resist?
Why would you fight me?
when you know you'll only die?
-Because I'll never
go back on my word.
Because-- because
that's my ninja way.
-It was just like
this when my parents
were killed right before my eyes
by Shinobi of the Hidden Leaf.
Because of the
existence of love,
sacrifice is born as well as
hate, and one comprehends,
one knows pain.
Yes, know pain.
-What's that?
-Do you hate me now?
[theme music]
SHIKAMARU: What
was that explosion?
KATSUYU: You must all evacuate
as far away as you can.
This is Naruto's
Nine Tails power.
SHIKAMARU: What?
MALE SPEAKER: I thought Yamato
and Kakashi put a sealing jutsu
on him.
KATSUYU: It was Hinata.
She was cut down
right in front of him.
MALE SPEAKER: That triggered it.
Where is Yamato
when we need him?
SHIKAMARU: Next time
on Naruto Shippuden,
"Planetary Devastation."
MALE SPEAKER: This is bad.
This is really, really bad.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, do you remember?
Because I'll never forget it.
That day.
The day that changed me.
Thank you, Naruto.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll never give up.
You'll always be my role model.
-Naru--
[stomach growling]
-Man, I'm hungry.
Guess I'll go to Ichiraku.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I'm sorry.
Sorry that I wasn't able
to thank you back then.