Dead men shouldn't go
around screwing things up!
[attacking yell]
[grunting]
Huh?!
Uchiha Reflection!
[gasp]
I'll get the Eight and
Nine Tails. Obito, you
take down those two down.
[gasp]
You're not getting away!
Obito, what happened to you?!
Why'd you join him?!
Summoning Jutsu!
[roaring]
You're late, Obito!
You finally got here!
So, you're Obito, huh?
We've been waiting!
Made it...
Sure, but you're super late!
Well, we're all done with
our self-introductions.
Other than yours, that is.
[chuckle]
I'm the future Hokage!
Obito Uchiha!
I'm gonna get my
trademark goggles as
well as my Sharingan
carved into my Great
Stone Face for all to see!
That way I'll be
able to glare down at
all the other villages!
[sigh]
I'll scare the hell out
of all of them with my
Sharingan stare!
And no one will
dare attack our village!
Put in that request after
you become Hokage and
activate your Sharingan!
Besides, they can't carve
the Sharingan if you're
wearing goggles!
They can carve 'em in
front of my goggles!
But then it'll look
like your eyeballs
are popping out!
[giggling]
[sad sigh]
Anyway...
I'm glad someone on
the team shares my dream
of being Hokage!
I'm Minato. I'll
be your superior.
It's nice to meet you!
Yeah it is!
Minato Sensei...
[roar]
All of this...
This world...
Doesn't matter
to me anymore!
[growl]
I won't let that happen,
idiot! After all, I am the
Fourth Hokage's son!
There's no way I'm
gonna fall for your talk!
I see. I was going easy on
you because you're the
actual Jinchuriki,
not a clone.
But I warn you, I can't
hold back with this
Hashirama's Wooden
Dragon. He used it to hold
down my Nine Tails.
Madara really is
crazy powerful!
And that's exactly
what makes him such
a worthy opponent.
[wet cough]
Your tough guy act
is crazy solid...
I'm not gonna hold back
against a zombie, either!
Since you're dead anyway!
[roar]
[roaring]
Obito! Why ally yourself
with someone like Madara?
I've got nothing at
all to say to you.
All that's left...
...is this, the
final battle!
Earth Style
Mud Wall!
[gasp]
[grunting]
But... why?!
How about you keep
your mouth shut?
You're all talk!
You're scum!
I believe that the
White Fang of the Hidden
Leaf was a true hero.
You're right, in the Ninja
World, those who break the
rules and laws are
regarded as scum.
[gasp]
But...
Those who would
abandon even one of their
friends are worse
than scum.
The reason is because...
You...
...let Rin die.
I am scum, for sure.
Obito, you've always...
Kamui...
...been my hero.
So why?
Come on!
Damn it!
[roaring]
[gasp]
That wooden thing is...
It's absorbing Nine
Tails' chakra!
Come on!
We share our eyes...
So you made it out, huh?
Obito, how'd you
end up like this?!
Does it have to do with Rin?
I will protect my comrade!
Let's go save Rin right now!
Hey!
[groaning]
I thought I said scum should
keep their mouths shut!
Now die!
I... I couldn't keep
my promise to you.
You're right...
I am trash. But you're a
hero of the Leaf. You don't
have to become trash, too.
[chuckling]
This is reality. Those
who bequeath and the
bequeathed, both.
All shinobi who
survive in this cruel
world become trash.
We are both
good examples...
...Kakashi.
Kakashi Sensei...
Can't move...
They're a distraction
for you too, right?
This world is
just about to end.
In order to enjoy the little
time we've got left, we
really should clear out this
battlefield a bit first.
There is no one that can
escape the cycle that births
the trash of this world.
That's exactly why I intend
to remake the world!
You guys annoy me so much,
I can't even think straight.
So instead, let me teach you
a little something about me.
I'm not trash!
I don't plan on
becoming trash, either!
I will...
...stop you!
I'll never let my comrades
die! No matter what happens!
[chuckle]
I will not allow
my comrades to die.
I'm sorry, Naruto. I'm the
one who taught you Obito's
words, and yet I was
about to waver again.
Hirudora!
Lightning Blade!
Guess it wasn't
just a bluff...
[chuckling]
Obito, your once-strong
will is still alive today...
...right next to me! The
only thing the current me
can do is protect
the current Naruto!
You'll protect the
"current" Naruto?
Yeah, me too. The
same goes for me.
They're both at their
limits! These Leaf shinobi,
they all act so tough!
The wood's constriction
is weakening!
[roaring]
Octopops!
[groaning]
Careful, Naruto! The enemy's
Wood Paralysis is identical
to the First Hokage's!
It can bind Tailed
Beast Power!
Just like Captain
Yamato's technique.
A Lightning Blade that
relies on the Sharingan...
You've really honed and
mastered that left eye,
even awakening
the Mangekyo.
However...
Can you return from the
other plane once more in
your current state?
Now return to the
trash heap, Kakashi!
No! Kakashi Sensei...
...is just like me!
Looks like we're gonna
have to start worrying
about Ten Tails. Let
them handle Obito.
Then we'll make our move! We
need to go after that thing!
[chuckle] I can see
it so clearly now...
All of the pain that's
etched into your face.
You should save that
line for the one
right next to you.
I gotta do something about
Kakashi Sensei, that's for
sure. He's completely
drained from
overusing the Sharingan.
If he's pulled in
again, he's toast!
Naruto, switch
places with me.
Huh?!
Let me handle this.
But...
Don't argue, just switch!
Hey, Kakashi you brat,
give me your hand.
You're--!
Look, just stick
your hand out!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Kurama, what the hell
did you just do?!
Now you don't have any
distractions. I'm leaving
the rest to you, Naruto.
What?!
All right, then!
[gasp]
Now that we know how
your ability works,
I can counter it.
Here's another!
[groaning]
Oh yeah, that's some pain
etched onto your face.
[groaning]
What's going on?!
[grunting]
Kakashi did that, over
there. See, the difference
between you and me
is, I can give or
take chakra
voluntarily, at will.
I'll show you the trick
to doing it later.
When did you
pass it to him?!
When I grabbed Kakashi's
hand to throw him.
So, then!
Yup. Whenever he
wants to, he can use
Kamui to come out.
Kakashi Sensei!
Thank the Nine Tails for me.
Sure!
Let's blast him to bits
before he revives!
Put in all you've
got! All right!
Yeah! Octopops and Eight-o,
it's all ready to go now!
Okay! Fire!
This is it! This ends now!
The Statue's chakra...
It's gone!
Yes!
Ha, ha! We did it,
fool, ya fool!
All right!
It's over?
Yeah...
This world is over.
Very well, then...
Shall we get started?
[growl]
[angry roar]
Here comes a big one. You
really think we can do this?
First, we keep our distance
and see what move he makes.
We'll counter it and
hit him with a big
blow as close
as we can get.
Nine Tails, you're
acting like a Captain.
Got a problem with that?
Nope. In fact I
feel kinda happy!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Allied
Shinobi Forces Jutsu."
Save that line for
after we've won!