-I worked it into the seal spell
that I'd appear on your psyche
if it ever happened that the
seal unraveled to the point
where you had sprouted
the eighth tail.
Truth be told, I'd hoped that
it would never get this far,
since I didn't ever want to
see you again, Nine-Tails.
[roaring]
-But then--
[gasp]
-I was looking forward
to seeing the young man
that my son had now become.
I guess it evens out.
-Mmm.
For the Hokage, come here.
I'll rip you to shreds!
-Well, if that's
the case, then I
think that I'll just
remain over here.
Wouldn't you agree, Naruto?
-Wait.
You called me Naruto.
You know who I am?
But why?
Why in the world does the
fourth Hokage know my name?
-Simple.
I know because I named you.
Because the truth
is, you are my son.
-Did you say "son"?
Seriously?
-That's right.
-Like I said before,
you are my son.
[laughter]
[growl]
-Four Hokage!
-He's a loudmouth,
don't you think?
So let's go somewhere
quieter, OK?
[laughter]
-Lord Third Hokage didn't tell
you much of anything, huh?
Guess he wanted to suppress
as much information
about the Nine-Tails
as he could.
If people had found
out you were my son,
you would have been in danger.
-Dad.
-Huh?
-Augh!
-Why would you ever want
to seal the Nine-Tails
inside of your own son?
Do you have any idea what I went
through because you did that?
All of the grown-ups
just looked at me
with contempt, or with fear,
and I couldn't make any friends.
I just wanted people to accept
me, or at least not hate me,
so I trained really hard to
become as strong as I could.
Then I met Iruka-sensei,
Kakashi-sensei, and Pervy Sage.
And I was happy, because
they helped make me stronger.
But just when things
were looking up,
a group called the
Akatsuki came after me.
So then I had to train even
harder than I did before.
I got stronger, but
couldn't stop the Akatsuki
from killing my friends.
And I just-- I mean
I-- I-- I don't
know what I'm saying anymore!
Damn it, am I supposed
to be happy or mad?
I don't even know.
[sobbing]
-Naruto.
How old are you now?
-16.
-I see.
16 already.
It must have been
hard for you, Naruto.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
Though I suppose it's
little consolation
if I apologize now,
after having put you
through all of that difficulty.
-No.
It's fine.
After all, I'm the son
of the Fourth Hokage.
I'll deal.
-Since you asked, I sealed half
of the Nine-Tails chakra inside
of you because I believed that
you could master this power.
I did it because you're my son.
[gasp]
-There is a reason I went
to the trouble to do this.
A big one.
16 years before now,
when the Nine-Tails
attacked the village,
I learned something.
-What?
-Back then, a
mastermind orchestrated
the whole Nine-Tails attack.
-Mastermind?
-Quite a formidable Shinobi.
Someone you'd need
extraordinary strength
to stand against
and hope to defeat.
I believe he'll attack
our village again.
-But the entire Leaf Village
has already been destroyed.
-Yeah.
I saw.
From inside your mind.
-What?
You watched that?
-I know about
Jiraiya-sensei, Too.
-So, was Pain the one who
attacked the village before,
using the Nine-Tails?
-No.
It wasn't him that time.
-Then who was it?
-He was an Akatsuki.
The one who wears that mask.
[gasp]
-When we fought, he saw right
through every single one
of my moves.
He was extraordinary.
In fact, I think that
he's the one using Pain.
-No way.
You're wrong!
Pain has a grudge against us.
He said that the Hidden Leaf
ruined his village a long time
ago.
-That's exactly right.
And that hatred is being used.
-He's really being used?
Someone as strong as he is?
And what about this
mastermind mass ninja?
What's he up to?
Why is the Hidden
Leaf always a target?
-As long as the
Shinobi culture exists,
there may never be
true peace and order.
Pain queried you about peace.
But finding the
solution is difficult.
-So, Naruto, how would you
confront this hatred in order
to create peace?
-In order to try to protect
something that's precious,
wars are waged.
As long as there is love in this
world, there will also be hate.
And some will take
advantage of that hatred.
As long as we have
this ninja system,
this monster known
as hate will live.
It will give birth
to more Pains.
Pain may have actually
killed Jiraiya-sensei,
but if you look deeper,
then one could even
say that this disordered Shinobi
world created Pain and killed
Jiraiya.
To be a ninja means that
you must confront hatred.
And every one of us must
battle against that hatred.
Jiraiya-sensei bequeathed
to you the quest
for the solution that
would end this hatred.
-But how can I when I can't
find a way to forgive Pain?
There's just no way.
I can't.
-I know.
-Fourth Hokage.
Please tell me!
What should I do?
-You must find that
answer for yourself,
because even I don't know it.
-But if you and Pervy Sage don't
have a clue about the answer,
how am I ever supposed
to figure it out?
Everyone expects too much of me.
I mean, look at me!
I'm not smart.
I'm not a great ninja.
I'm-- I'm just me.
And how's a guy
like me supposed--
-I'm certain that you'll be
able to find the answer, Naruto.
Because I believe
in you completely.
-You do?
Do you really think I can?
-Well, a parent's duty is
to unconditionally believe
in their children.
Now, then.
I'm afraid that it's
time for me to go.
My chakra is starting to fade.
-Huh?
No.
Don't go.
-I'll rebuild the seal now.
But this will be the last time.
[gasp]
-And the Hidden
Leaf can be rebuilt.
Naruto, you can do it.
-(VOICEOVER) Thanks, Dad.
[theme music - in japanese]
[roaring]
-He's actually digging himself
out of planetary devastation.
What incredible power.
I'm going to have to
increase its size,
then-- the Nine-Tails
disappeared.
Oh!
His doubt has been erased.
What's happened?
Has he already mastered it?
Does he now control
the Nine-Tails?
[coughing]
-Nagato, no!
-(VOICEOVER) The transformation
into the Nine-Tails disturbed
my chakra.
It made me lose my last
Shadow Clone at Mount Myoboku.
That means I can only
use the Sage Jutsu
chakra I have left inside me.
-(VOICEOVER) He's
already in Sage Mode.
He's tough.
I had to confirm the extent
of the Nine-Tails power,
but I never imagined planetary
devastation wouldn't stop him.
--[gasp] I thought
I was going to die.
-Wait, what's that?
The village is over that way.
What is--
-You did that, Naruto.
When you were in
Nine-Tails state.
-(VOICEOVER) Did I kill Hinata,
and all the people of the Leaf
village?
-She's alive.
I can sense Hinata's chakra.
-I was quite worried,
but no casualties
resulted from your
assault even though you
were in full Nine-Tails state.
We were lucky.
-Oh, thank goodness.
You don't know what
a relief that is.
-Naruto--
-No!
Lady Hinata.
-Her injuries
don't appear fatal,
but she needs
treatment right now.
-I'll look for a medical
ninja right away.
-The Hidden Leaf village is
under attack by the Akatsuki,
but I can't move anymore.
Hurry up.
They need your help.
-Can't believe
things are this bad.
-Look.
There's a wounded
toad here, too.
-The time has come
for us to end this.
Do you finally comprehend pain?
Unless you come to
know the same pain,
you cannot truly
comprehend someone else.
And even if you
comprehend them, you still
may not ever agree with them.
That is the truth.
That is the reason it's useless
for you to chase after Sasuke.
-Enough of this.
Just take me to where
the real Pain is.
I want to talk to
him face-to-face now.
-Enough of this.
Just take me to where
the real Pain is.
I want to talk to
him face-to-face now.
-So, you figured that
part out, did you?
First Jiraiya-sensei
and now you as well.
You Leaf Ninja are
really quite impressive.
But our discussion's over.
Further conversation will
change absolutely nothing.
-I just want to discuss
something with him.
-You're in Sage Mode now.
I believe that you are
limited to generating only two
of those bothersome
chakra shuriken at a time.
Isn't that so?
And that causes your
Sage Mode to run out.
-I guess I have no choice
but to fight you, huh?
-If both of your
shuriken should miss,
the only possible outcome
is that you shall lose.
You'll have no more chances.
I will take you almost
to the point of death
and haul you off.
-Well, that's too bad.
I'll find the real
Pain myself, then.
-But how are you
going to do that?
-I've got an idea.
[groan]
-Hmm?
He-- he reverse tracked
me using Sage Mode.
-Ha!
I found him!
-You bastard.
[grunt]
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Now, smoke bombs!
Right!
(VOICEOVER) Here comes
the first shuriken.
-Almighty Push!
-(VOICEOVER) He'd already
launched the second one using
Shadow Shuriken Jutsu!
-The window is five seconds.
I can do this!
-(VOICEOVER) Four seconds to go.
He'd already prepared and
hidden those Shadow Clones.
Only three more seconds until
I can launch my next jutsu.
But, two shots, both missed.
It's over.
-What is this?
-We still have two seconds.
Go!
-(VOICEOVER) The rubble!
It's all Shadow Clones!
One more second!
Zero!
-Ah!
-He's using Shadow
Clones as backup?
[grunts]
-You, with no answers
and no solutions.
Just give up!
[grunting]
-But I truly
believe that the day
will come when all people
understand one another,
and live in peace.
If I can't find a
solution to this problem,
then perhaps I'll entrust you
to find it instead, Naruto.
-I'm certain that you'll
be able to find the answer.
Because I believe
in you completely.
-It's because I truly
believe that you
are the only Shinobi who can
surpass the Fourth Hokage.
-He withstood that?
Can't be.
-(VOICEOVER) He can't
throw that jutsu.
I've got five seconds.
This distance will keep me safe.
-Look, Pain, just give up on
trying to make me give up.
[shouts]
[theme music]
-The fact that
you're here-- does
that mean that you won out
against the Sixth Pain?
-It doesn't really matter
who won or who lost.
-Tell us what happened.
-It's not really important.
I'm on my way to see
the real Pain right now.
And please don't
try to follow me.
I want to go alone.
-Alone?
-Next time, on Naruto Shippuden.
The Two Students.
There's something I want
to confirm with him.
-Yamato's Room has been
renamed Guy's Room.
Hello, everyone.
This is your idol.
Me.
Might Guy.
Our guest today is the pride of
the Leaf Village. [inaudible].
-Hello, sir--
-Oh, come on.
Don't be so bashful.
Not on my show.
-Oh, uh--
-She's extremely
introverted and shy.
Her hobby is pressed
flower art and she
loves cinnamon rolls
and sweet bean jam.
Ah, forget the script.
I'll just ask you
whatever comes to mind.
That's what a hip, lively
interview is all about.
-Huh?
-Oh, by the way, you've
really matured lately.
Are you in love?
Is that it?
[mumbling]
-All right, then.
Just look into the
camera and tell us
all that's in your heart!
-Oh, but I couldn't--
-If you're too shy,
then I'll help you.
-But I just don't think--
-OK, love confession time.
Let's do this.
In three, two, one, go!
-Ahhhh!
No, I can't!
-Ahh!
I'm OK.
[giggle]
[theme music]