I will never go over
to your side, Naruto!
I have no
regrets with my path.
Remember I said I
saw everything.
[gasp]
That's right!
So...
...don't...
...keep imagining
yourself as Hokage!
The person Rin wanted to
watch over isn't the current
you, it's Obito Uchiha.
We're late again
thanks to you, Obito!
Let's go, Obito.
Sorry!
We'll be right there!
Rin, you...
That's right.
You ought to fill in that
hole in your heart yourself.
Others won't be of any help.
Now...
Come here.
C'mon...
I won't ever ignore you.
Come...
Obito...
Hold on, Rin!
That's right.
Rin wouldn't even
give the time of day
to the current you.
The one Rin that wanted to
watch over is Obito Uchiha.
[gasp]
So give it up already.
I am...
...Obito Uchiha!
Now come over,
you bastard!
Don't you dare
underestimate...
Everyone's power!
They're all out!
[celebratory yell]
Yeah!
I lost?!
It'll finally be time for
the dreams of the moon to
completely bury this
gaping hole of hell!
There's nothing in my heart!
I don't even feel
pain any longer.
There's no need to
feel guilty, Kakashi.
This hole was opened up
by this world of hell.
Do you think such things can
fill the hole in your heart?
Don't erase the
memories of the real Rin!
Rin sacrificed
herself in order to
protect the village!
You can try all you want to
fill it with delusions...
But that hole in your
heart won't go away!
The hole in one's heart gets
filled by others around you.
Let's go!
[giggle]
Rin...
Well, it looks like you
kept your promise, Naruto
Uzumaki!
So that's the reason I
want to help you, too.
I have to say, I'm impressed
that really rescued us!
Hey, Son!
Sure thing!
[chuckle]
We were lucky.
He done it.
Yes!
Excellent!
You're right.
I'm glad!
Hmm? Isn't he that kid?
Hey!
Wait!
Just...
Hold up, Sasuke!
Where is he?!
What happened to him?!
Over there!
He's still alive!
Right, I lost.
Kakashi!
Sasuke, I promise
we'll talk more later.
I apologize for
appearing so suddenly.
But I was once his
classmate and friend,
so please, let me take
responsibility for him.
Kakashi Sensei!
No, he's now-!
Dad, what-?!
He's weakened!
Now's the time to
finish him off!
Let's go and get him!
Hold!
Obito...
When we played chakra
tug-of-war, just
now, I got to see the
inside of your heart.
It looked like my son
nagged and lectured
you quite a bit.
Something that he seems
to have inherited
from his mother.
But, Dad...
And besides, that
really ought to be your job.
For I believe the one who
truly understands and would
know what to say to Obito...
...is you, his
friend, Kakashi.
Isn't that right, Naruto?
Naruto...
You two and the
Allied Shinobi Forces
should help Lord First.
Go and seal Madara away.
Oh yeah, that's right!
I forgot about him!
Let's go, Sasuke!
I think you guys were
younger than Naruto is now.
You remember?
All the missions that
the four of us went on?
Rin, as a Medic Ninja,
did her utmost to
protect the both of you.
She never would have wanted
things to end up like this.
But what caused all of this
that's my responsibility.
Yes.
Can I explain
the mission now?
We don't have
that much time.
We're getting close
to the border now.
See, it's this line here.
It shows where the Land
of Earth is currently
invading the Village
Hidden in the Grass.
The enemy are shinobi
from the Hidden Stone.
And, according to intel,
they've deployed a thousand
shinobi to the front lines.
Here.
They've advanced
farther than the last time.
Well, the Grass Village
is situated right
next to the Land of Fire.
We should have
stepped in earlier.
If the Hidden Stone's able
to invade like this, Then it
must mean that they have
an efficient system
for reinforcement.
That's why our mission is
this: the Kannabi Bridge. To
crush your enemy at the
front lines requires an
immense amount of
shinobi, right?
Therefore, shinobi like us
whose focus is sabotage are
forced to work in a
small efficient unit.
The bridge...
So our mission
is infiltration.
Team Kakashi, Your mission
is to sneak behind the enemy
and reach that bridge.
Once the three of you are
there, you will destroy it
in order to disrupt the
enemy's support operation.
After that, you will
promptly withdraw.
Understood!
And you, sir?
I'll confront the enemy
directly on the battlefield.
That will create a diversion
so that you can do your job.
Now, remember:
Kakashi's your captain
on this mission.
All four of us will travel
to the border together.
But once we get there, we'll
split up for our missions.
Right!
This is where we go
our separate ways.
Do your best, all of you.
The enemy that we
encountered yesterday
was merely a lone scout.
But now we should
expect to fight teams.
Be careful!
Let's get going
then Captain!
It's no coincidence that
I, who should be dead, am
standing before
you two like this.
Perhaps Rin made it happen.
Her way of scolding me for
my failures as your teacher.
I'm so sorry that I
couldn't protect Rin.
Rin was my sole light and
hope in this dark world.
After I lost Rin...
The whole world as
I saw it changed.
It became a black hell.
This world holds no hope.
I took Madara's identity and
walked the world, but all
that did was further
confirm my belief.
Even possessing this
Sharingan didn't
reveal anything to me.
'Cause there was
nothing to see.
I don't know
anything for sure either...
[gasp]
Then you can't
say my path is-!
Without a doubt, your
path is just one of many.
And it may not
actually be wrong either.
I've thought that
this world is hell, too.
I thought that I'd lost you.
And then lost Rin
right after that.
And later, I even lost
Minato Sensei, as well.
But...
Oh, that's right!
I totally forgot...
I was the only one who
didn't give you a gift for
becoming a jonin and
being named captain.
I thought about it,
and I didn't know
what would be good.
But I do now.
Don't worry, I remember
what you said before.
I'm not going to give
you something useless.
I'm giving you my Sharingan.
[gasp]
Whatever the village
or anyone else may say.
I think that
you're a great Jonin.
It's true.
That's how I really feel.
Please accept this...
Even though I don't know
anything for sure, I tried
my best to see the
world with this eye.
I felt that as long as I had
your Sharingan and words, I
could see the future.
And what you saw
was Naruto, huh?
How can you be sure
that his path won't fail?!
Actually...
He may very well fail, too.
Of course.
So what's the
difference between us?!
Why go so far for him?
Because I can attest that he
won't fail as much as you.
How?!
Because if he starts
to trip and stumble on
his path, I'll help him!
Why?!
Why would you help him?!
Because he'd never give up
on his dreams or on reality.
That's the kind
of guy he is.
Found him!
[gasp]
And the way he forges
ahead draws others to him.
He makes you want
to reach out when
he's about to stumble.
The larger and greater
the support behind you, the
closer you can
get to your goal.
That's the difference.
Massive Rasen Shuriken!
Bigger!
We need a real big one!
Right!
Is such a thing possible
in this pitch-black hell?
Is it?
I'm sure you could've seen
it, too, if you'd tried.
After all, you and I
have the same eyes.
If comrades you trust gather
around you, hope can take
physical form and
become visible.
That's what I
believe...
Obito.
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
Seems you've become rather
close friends with that Fox
Demon's brat, Gaara.
If you're not going to
help, let's talk later.
I'm going in.
Sand Shinobi human,
are you a friend
of Naruto's, as well?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "My First
Friend."
We all want to
help out as well!