[music playing]
-Well, that was fast.
-I heard it was a
matter of great urgency.
-Kakashi's out, and I want
you to take over his team.
-It would be an honor to work
in Kakashi's stead, my lady.
-Now, this isn't an
ANBU Black Ops mission.
You're going on a
regular assignment,
so you can take off the mask.
I'll give you a code name.
During the mission, you
will be known as Yamato.
-Yes, I understand.
-One more thing,
Team Kakashi will
be getting a new
face in its ranks,
from The Foundation, the
Black Ops training division.
-Really, The Foundation?
-However--
-Yes, my lady?
-Keep a very close eye on him.
Study his every move.
[music playing]
-Naruto, do you
know him already?
-Yeah, this jerk
attacked me for no reason
when I was with Choji,
Ino, and Shikamaru today.
[music playing]
-That's enough, Naruto.
-Huh?
Oh yeah, who are you, anyway?
-Oh wait, are you--
-I'll be filling
in as team captain
while Kakashi's recovering
in the hospital.
Please, call me Yamato.
SAKURA: Captain Yamato--
-You three are going
to be comrades now,
so you'd better learn to
get along with each other.
[gasp]
-You're joking.
Comrades with him?
-I'm sorry about earlier.
But, you see, I knew we
were going to be teammates,
and I wanted to see
how strong you were.
-Oh well, that
was pretty stupid.
You didn't have to go that far.
-I was just curious to
see how strong you'd be.
Now I know you're not
packing anything major.
[gasp]
-What did you just say?
-We have to work
together with this guy.
You can't start off
fighting from the get-go.
[screams]
-And the sames goes for you.
That wasn't very nice.
[laugh]
-Is that so?
SAKURA: You're not winning any
friends with talk like that.
-Well, don't write me off yet.
I like everyone, even you, ugly.
-Uh-- what did you just say?
-Whoa, easy, Sakura.
Follow your own advice.
[laugh]
-Don't you look silly.
KAKASHI: Master Jiraiya--
-Well, no more than
usual, I suppose.
Heard you're going to be
holed up in here for a week.
-Well, pretty much.
[groan]
-Hey, slow down.
Don't force yourself, now.
[groan]
-It doesn't look like you'll
be going anywhere for a while.
Well, here's a get-well
gift, both volumes
of "Make Out Paradise,"
the deluxe editions.
I'm sure you've read them,
but it'll help pass the time.
[chuckle]
If you know what I mean.
-Thanks, but you didn't come
back to the Village just
to see me, did you?
-Let's wait for Tsunade
and her man to get here.
I'll fill you in on everything.
-Her man?
Who do you mean?
-I believe that he'll be going
by Yamato on this mission.
You'll know him
when you see him.
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
-So, uh, now that
the four of us are
going to be deployed
immediately,
maybe we should-- ah man.
Look, I don't have time
to throw you all in a cage
so you can get acquainted
with each other.
Let's go.
Introduce yourselves.
-Huh, Naruto Uzumaki.
-Sakura Haruno.
-And you can call me Sai.
-All right, well, that
takes care of that.
Let me give you a breakdown
of Team Kakashi's new mission.
The four of us will
head to Tenchi Bridge,
capture the Akatsuki spy who
has infiltrated Orochimaru's
organization, and
bring him back.
This is our best shot
at gaining intelligence
on Orochimaru and Uchiha.
[gasp]
-Intelligence we
can eventually use
for orchestrating
Orochimaru's assassination
and, if we're lucky,
Sasuke Uchiha's retrieval.
So, keep that in mind.
-OK.
-Right.
-As soon as your gear is packed
and you're all ready to go,
rendezvous at the main
gate in exactly one hour.
-Man, that jerk, Sai, I
already can't stand him.
How come he's replacing Sasuke?
Team Kakashi would be fine
with just the three of us.
-He is rude, and he's
got a foul mouth,
but there's something
familiar about him.
His face or his voice, they
kind of remind me of Sasuke.
-Ha, that guy is
nothing like Sasuke.
Sasuke's way cooler than he is.
I mean he's uh--
he's-- he's-- better.
-Yeah, you're right.
I still think there's
a resemblance,
but Sasuke is a little cooler.
NARUTO: A little?
Oh, come on.
Sasuke's a bazillion times
b-- better than him, man.
[music playing]
[gasp]
-Very nice, but remember,
never let your guard down.
-What do you need, sir?
Oh--
-Listen, the secret
mission you are on
is directed by Lord Danzo.
Just a cat.
As I was saying,
your secret mission
is directed by Lord Danzo.
The future of the Leaf
depends on your success.
Mistakes will not be tolerated.
-Yes sir, I understand.
-Good.
Hm, you're still carrying
that around, are you?
-This is--
[music playing]
-Those of The Foundation
have no names, no emotion.
-There is no past and no future.
There is only the mission.
-We are the roots that support
the great trunk of the Leaf
Village, invisible
from inside the earth.
Never forget that.
-Yes, sir.
[wind blowing]
[birds chirping]
[gasp]
-Hm?
-Sorry to keep you
waiting, my lady.
-What took you so long?
[chuckle]
-I got a little
held up, I'm afraid.
-Well, don't worry about it.
Kakashi is waiting.
[laugh]
-Hm?
-Well, sounds like
they're finally here.
TSUNADE: Kakashi, may we enter?
-Come on in.
-Ha, long time, no see, Kakashi.
-You?
So, this is the Yamato you
were talking about, go figure.
-That's right.
While I'll be filling in
as interim captain for Team
Kakashi, Yamato is going
to be my code name, sir.
-You don't say.
-Which leads me to why
I brought him here.
If he's to be heading
up your team, Kakashi,
I want him to know exactly
what he'll be dealing with.
-What we're about to tell
you is the main reason
you were selected as
Kakashi's replacement.
-Is this about Naruto, sir?
-Exactly.
[music playing]
KAKASHI: You already know that
Naruto has the Nine-Tailed Fox
Spirit sealed inside
of him, right?
YAMATO: I do.
-There are times when the
Nine-Tails chakra will
start to leak out
of Naruto's body
and take on the
Fox Spirit's form.
We've been referring to it
as the Nine-Tails Cloak.
-The Nine-Tails Cloak?
My god, how often has this
been happening to him?
-As recently as
our last mission.
[music playing]
When he's overcome
by his emotions,
the Fox Spirit's chakra
begins to surface,
engulfing his entire body and
revealing the Nine-Tails Cloak.
Just before the
second tail formed,
I was able to suppress
the chakra with a seal
that Master Jiraiya gave me.
If I hadn't intervened, who
knows what might have happened.
-I see, so it's
just as I feared.
-Judging by the shape the chakra
was taking, the number of tails
will probably grow.
And eventually,
there will be nine.
-That about sums it up.
-Master Jiraiya, how
many tails have you seen?
-Hm, in all my years of living,
I've come close to death
only twice.
The first time, I broke
six ribs, both arms,
and ruptured a handful
of internal organs.
That was when I was caught doing
"research" at a hot spring,
and Tsunade beat me like a drum.
The second time--
[music playing]
The second was back when
Naruto and I were off
training together and
the fourth tail appeared.
-I'm off.
[crowd noise]
SAKURA: My lady--
-Huh?
-What is it, Sakura?
You still have some
time before you
have to meet up with
the others, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
I was hoping to have a few
words with you before we depart.
-I see.
Well, your timing is perfect.
There's actually something
I wanted to ask you about.
-What is it?
-It's about Sai.
-Ah, I see.
So, it's that bad already?
-Yeah.
TSUNADE: Why am I not surprised?
Well, you'll just have to
keep Naruto on a shorter leash
than usual.
-Yes, of course ma'am.
I'll do what I can.
-Hm?
[knock]
[gasp]
-Come in.
[music playing]
-Who's that?
-Well Danzo, what do you want?
-I am just curious,
were you were
able to assign a
distinguished Black Ops
operative to lead young
Sai's unit, Princess Tsunade?
-An exemplary shinobi with
experience from as far back
as the Third Hokage's rule.
-Very well.
I just hope he's not
too deeply rooted
in the pacifism of that
pushover, Sarutobi.
The gutless teachings
of the Third,
who hated all manner
of disagreement--
just as the Third
Hokage was rooted
in the teachings of
your grandfather.
-Huh.
-Well, in any
case, I'm relieved.
Now I can enjoy my
meals in relative peace.
If you'll excuse me.
[music playing]
[sigh]
-Who was he?
TSUNADE: Someone who, long ago,
competed with the late Sarutobi
Sensei for the seat of Hokage.
They were polar opposites.
He's the founder of a hard-line
marshal faction, founded
on rigid principles.
He's also Sai's superior.
As a student of the
moderate Third Hokage,
and granddaughter of the
First, he actively despises me.
-Um, shouldn't you--
[scream]
-That's right, it's
almost time, isn't it?
Don't want to be late.
-No, ma'am.
I'll take my leave now.
-Huh?
-Hm.
[clock ticking]
-If we succeed in
this mission, we'll
be one step closer to Sasuke.
[clock ticking]
All right, now
let's hit the road!
[music playing]
-OK people, this is it.
Team Kakashi, we're moving out.
[music playing]
[theme music]
YAMATO: How long are you
guys going to be at odds for?
This isn't good for the mission.
You know that, don't you?
Well look, I'll
give you a choice.
You can either let me
cram your sorry butts
into a cage for 24 hours,
or you can spend the night
relaxing in some hot springs.
It's your call.
And trust me, I prefer the
kinder, gentler approach,
but I'm not adverse to more
draconian methods, if need be.
NARRATOR: Next time,
"The Fake Smile."
[music playing]
JIRAIYA: Introduction to the
masterpieces of the Leaf.
Welcome, everyone.
When we think of
fall, we think of art,
stuffing our faces,
and above all,
curling up with
really good book.
That's why, today, I'll be
introducing some of the hottest
best-sellers around.
We'll start off
with this gem, which
I'm sure you all know,
"Make Out Paradise,"
a landmark in
romantic literature
that has grabbed the hearts
of men across the land.
[chuckle]
Next is "Make Out
Violence," a classic.
It's a highly realistic, yet
dynamic, piece of lyricism,
born out of meticulous research.
And then, of course,
it's the much ballyhooed
"Make Out Tactics!"
There's a feeding frenzy
over the movie deal.
Oh yeah.
-Come on, Pervy Sage.
The only books you're
showcasing here are you own!
-What are you, stupid?
Yeah, I'm pushing my books.
You don't make money
shilling for the competition.
-Wha-- you selfish old--
[laugh]
-Just go out and buy them.
You know you want to, right?