[music]
-Heh.
-[gasp]
-Huh!
[music]
-Aaugh!
-What in the world?
-Not much longer now.
[gasp]
You're pretty good aren't you?
Ha.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): Huh.
That Jinchuuriki sure
comes in handy, doesn't it?
Tell me, how did you
guess I was an intruder?
-There are no birds like
that one in this desert.
-Is that so?
[Music - NOBODYKNOWS, "HERO'S
COME BACK"]
[non-english speech]
-You're pretty good, aren't you?
Huh.
Huh, that Jinchuuriki sure
comes in handy, doesn't it?
Tell me, how did you
guess I was an intruder?
-There are no birds like
that one in this desert.
-Is that so?
-Hey!
What the heck's
going on out there?
Isn't anyone going
to tell me what's
going on-- What-- What
happened out here?
A Kazekage.
-Well how did this
intruder, whoever he is,
get into the village?
I thought Captain
Yura was supposed
to have tightened security.
-Yes, but that's
the strange part.
We haven't been able to
locate Captain Yura anywhere.
-What did you say?
-[groan] That blasted Deida.
He had to make a
circus out of it.
Yura, you should get
back to the village.
It could complicate things if
they were to find you here.
-Yes, Lord Sasori.
-Get on with it, Deidara.
You know I don't like
to be kept waiting.
-Gaara, you in there?
Where on earth could he be?
-Kankuro, my Lord.
The Kazekage is fighting in
the sky above the village.
-What?
He's fighting in-- Gaara.
-Well so much for
a covert operation.
At least this way I don't
have to go looking for you.
Tactically he does
have the advantage.
This could get messy.
Heh.
-So he's over there.
-What?
Naruto's shadow clone
and transformation.
Huh?
If that even touches
me I'm done for.
All right then.
Shinobi battle skill
rule number three.
Ninjutsu.
-The speed of his hand signs.
-Nobody's that fast.
-Fire Style, Fireball Jutsu!
-OK now where is he?
KAKASHI: Earth Style,
Headhunter Jutsu.
Another shadow clone.
Water Style, Water Dragon Jutsu!
-Woah.
[screaming]
-Fire Style, Earth
Style, and Water Style.
One right after the other.
Nobody's got that many
tricks up their sleeve.
-Well they don't call him
Copy Ninja for nothing.
He's giving us an expert lesson
in just how good he really is.
-Yeah.
-(voiceover) Looks like
this could take a while.
-Well, they still have plenty
of time before sunrise.
-True.
-In fact, just watch.
I've a feeling it'll be over
sooner than you'd think.
-Gaara.
-Yes, it's almost time.
[music playing]
The real fun is about to begin.
Now!
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Unusual explosive devices.
Accurately guided
to their targets.
-Think I'm getting
the hang of this.
[heavy breathing]
-I shouldn't be surprised,
but that Sharingan
is something else, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-And his hand signs are faster
than the human eye can follow.
There's no way we'll ever
be able to get past them.
-Fire Style, Fireball Jutsu!
Water Style, Water Dragon Jutsu!
-We don't have a chance of
getting near those bells
unless we can slow
down his hands somehow.
-Like you said,
it's no surprise.
I mean you would
expect Kakashi-Sensei
to be a strong opponent.
He's smarter than Shikamaru.
His sense of smell's
sharper than Kiba's.
His Sharingan's
stronger than Sasuke's.
His Taijutsu's better
than Bushy Brows'.
On top of that, he's
had more experience
than all of us combined.
-OK, but even Kakashi-Sensei
has to have some weakness.
He has to, right?
-Hm.
A weakness.
Hm.
Hey.
Wait a sec.
I got it!
-I never thought they give
my Sharingan such a workout.
But I should be able to
hold them off til sunrise.
Still got plenty of
shuriken and kunai.
And "Make-Out Tactics."
No, I'd better not.
It's not like the old days when
I could fight them off and read
a book at the same time.
But I'm dying to
know what happens.
It's obvious the main character
has some sort of dark secret
that's about to be revealed.
Man, this is killing me.
I don't know if I can wait!
-Well, if you really think he
has a weakness, let's hear it.
-Oh come on Sakura, you know
Kakashi-Sensei as well as I do.
You should be able
to figure it out.
-Well let's just
say I can't, OK?
Now come on, quit stalling.
What is it?
-OK, OK, you really
want to know?
-Yes, spill it.
Of course!
I get it.
It's so simple, it's
simply brilliant.
-Yeah.
Like I said, all you gotta
do is think about it,
and it's obvious!
-If you're right,
that'll be the one moment
when we won't have to
worry about his hand
signs or his Sharingan.
-And that's when
we take him down.
-Naruto, you really are the
number one most unpredictable
knucklehead ninja!
-I was so impressed
with how much
those two it improved, I
let myself get carried away.
From now on, I'm
going to wait and let
them make the first move.
-No sense standing around
here, time's a wasting.
It's up to us to
make the first move.
-Well OK.
Let's do it.
-Now then.
This time with feeling!
Ha!
-Gaara!
-[sniffs] They're here.
A frontal attack, huh?
Getting a little
overconfident, aren't you?
-Now, Naruto!
-Listen to this Kakashi-Sensei!
I know the final plot twist
of "Make-Out Tactics!"
-What?
No.
No!
-Turns out the hero actually
is none other than--
-No, shut up.
I don't want to hear.
Ah!
Oh no, because of the Sharingan
I can still read his lips.
Wha--?
-Ha!
-Hm!
-(disappointed) Oh.
-A ninja must see
through deception.
-Isn't that right, Sensei?
-I deserved that.
[laughter]
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
It's like he's
encased himself inside a cocoon.
It's amazing he survived the
blast, if he survived it.
Hm.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Sand Prison!
[MUSIC - NAGAREBOSHI, "SHOOTING
STAR"] [non-english speech]
NARRATOR: Beating
Kakashi by threatening
to give away the way the
book's ending, ingenious!
NARUTO (VOICE
OVER): I thought so.
SAKURA (VOICE OVER): But isn't
the Make Out series intended
for mature readers only?
NARRATOR: That's right, what
were you doing reading it?
You're not mature.
NARUTO (VOICE OVER): Oh!
I-I barely even glanced at it.
It was really boring.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He
only read ten pages.
NARRATOR: Aha!
Guilty.
All right, Naruto.
Just for that you'll
spend the next three
days cleaning the
Academy bathroom.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Say what?
Next time, the
Kazekage stands tall.
[music]
-Greetings class.
Today our topic will be Gaara.
Known as Gaara of the
Desert for his ability
to control
chakra-infused sand, he's
the youngest of three
sand village siblings.
Shortly after he was born,
the Sand Spirit Shukaku
was sealed within him.
His own father tried
to destroy him out
of fear of the spirit's
terrible power.
After that, Gaara trusted no
one and fought only for himself.
Naruto, who had been an
orphaned outcast himself,
could have followed
a similar path.
But instead, he showed
Gaara that true power
comes from loving
your friends enough
to fight for them, not yourself.
The Sand and Leaf
Villages are now allies,
helping each other
in times of crisis.
And Gaara has been named
Kazekage, Leader of the Sand
Village.
OK, pop quiz.
What do the characters
emblazoned on Gaara's forehead
signify?
Answer?
Love.
Now then, if you
don't mind, there's
a book I'm just dying to finish.