The Hokage's faith in
you is awfully strong.
Have the two of you had
this bond for very long?
Yeah. A long time
ago I made Granny
a promise.
I told her that I
wouldn't die until
I became Hokage.
That's an interesting
promise to keep. The
significance is deep.
And that's just why
Granny decided to
bet on me!
She even gave me a
symbol of my promise.
Just as Minato thought
he would! We need to let
Naruto go. That way, he
can protect the shinobi!
I'm going to bet on
Naruto! So what about
you?
Tsunade...
Hm?
When did you first
decide to place all
your bets on Naruto?
Was it when he defeated
Pain and became the hero
of your village?
Not then. It was
long before that.
It was when...
Playing at being
Hokage?
Count me out, it's
a fool's game.
Ugh! I'm not gonna let
her sit there and make
fun of the old man!
No way!
I don't care if
she is a lady!
I'll knock that
cynical sneer off
her face!
Darn it!
Hnh?
Ahhh!
One question before
you pass out.
Tell me, what makes
you so touchy about
Hokage?
It's because, unlike
you, that's my goal.
Just watch someday
I'll be Hokage!
To be Hokage,
that is my dream!
(surprised gasp)
Well then, care to
make a bet on it?
A bet?
I'll give you one
week. If you can
master that jutsu by
then, I'll admit I'm
wrong and that you're
worthy of becoming
Hokage. I'll even
throw in my necklace.
Well, Naruto won
that bet.
And so, you decided
to gamble on him,
is that it?
Huh?
Yes. that's right.
But the first time we
met, you were making
an entirely different
type of wager.
Do you remember?
Huh? Ah-ha!
Yeah, well back
in those days
the only thing I
could bet on was
money...
Lady Tsunade!
Please, wait
a second!
Hurry up, Shizune!
The next den, I mean,
next inn, won't wait
for us!
The inn isn't
going anywhere!
Huh?
Were they shinobi?
Lady Tsunade,
was that...
Oh, forget it!
Let's go!
(worried sigh)
Wait, is that-?
You guys! You guys!
What is it?!
Zaji, if this is
something stupid
again, you're gonna
get it!
I promise you,
it's not stupid!
Look over there!
Huh?
Whoa, look at
those...
She's the legendary...
The legendary
what?
The legendary...
The legendary what?!
You fool! You called us
out here because you
knew, didn't you?!
(chuckling)
You got me! I just
wanted to liven things
up a little bit and
make you look good!
Hah! You idiot!
I ought to slam
you for that!
Yeah, but still,
you're smiling!
Well, yeah, of
course I am!
(laughing)
Why shouldn't I smile?
She's the legendary...
Sucker!
And she's loaded!
Hah! Let's get going!
Change all of this
into tokens!
You got it! And
thank you for your
patronage, ma'am!
What was that?
Uh, don't mind us! Please,
why don't you just relax
and have a good time
while you're here!
Yeah, just enjoy yourself!
You're here to have fun,
aren't you?!
(worried sigh)
She's being taken
advantage of already!
There's no corpse,
so the enemy escaped.
Damn it all! It's
Nigai! They got him!
Yes, it's unfortunate
about Nigai...
(painful grunt)
We've gotta hurry and
show this to Amai.
We've arranged to
meet up with him
at a nearby inn.
I know you're in
pain, but do your
best to bear it!
Sorry I've become a
burden. I'm so sorry,
sir!
Here we go!
All right, place
your bets!
Even!
Odd!
Snake eyes!
Even!
Odd!
Thank you so much
for stopping by!
What on earth do
you think you're
doing now?!
I mean, you cannot go
into any more debt to
try to make your money
back!
Just go and borrow
some more for me,
all right?
But from where?!
Look, here they come.
Huh?
Is there a woman named
Tsunade staying here?
You know, the one
with the huge jugs!
Ehh! We'll find
her ourselves!
What's the big
idea here!
We're bill collectors!
Come on, let's
search the
whole joint!
Right!
Ahhh!
Huh? Who are you?
Can I help you?
Well, I don't think
we need to bring
names into this, but
you can call us scary
vultures from the
Land of Gold!
Listen, little girl...
Have you seen a
lady who looks
like this? I drew
it myself.
She's got an
enormous chest.
Oh, sure! That's the
pretty lady who's staying
in another room just down
the hallway!
What?! Where?!
I'll go get
her for you!
Wait! Hold on a
minute, little
girl!
Huh?
I've got a question
for you, what's that
shiny thing you have
there in your hand?
What? This?
Oh! The pretty lady in
the picture you showed
me gave it to me earlier.
She told me something
bad happened and she
went crazy up on the
mountain.
She said that after that,
lots of sparkly stuff just
like this started coming
out of the rocks.
What?! Lots, you say?!
Uh-huh!
Lots and lots and lots!
She said there was so
much she couldn't carry
it all. So she gave some
to me, too!
One second!
Okay!
The rock that brat
was holding, was a
piece of gold!
No way! Gold?!
It seems that Tsunade
struck a mother load
up there on the mountain!
You think so?
And that means...
We'll lose out big time
if she pays off her debt!
And that means...
We have to keep on
loaning her money so
we can rack up more
and more interest!
There's no way we'll
lose money on this! We
gotta keep letting her
borrow more and more!
Oh my, if it isn't
the bill collectors.
I'm sorry you had
to come this far to
track me down.
No problem! It
really wasn't any
trouble at all.
Well, it looks like my
war chest is full for
tomorrow! All right,
let's go out drinking!
That was blatant fraud!
I didn't lie. When
I busted open those
rocks on that mountain,
I did find gold inside.
What?! That part
was true?!
Well, it was
only one shard.
Agh! But you said
the mountain was
bountiful!
Yeah, its name is
Ms. Bountiful!
Lady Tsunade!
How could you!
Lady Tsunade?
That you, Amai?
Lord Raikage...
Thanks to you distracting
the enemy, my side of the
mission went off without
a single hitch.
We've obtained the
Ninja Art Scroll for
the Secret Jutsu unique
to the Cedar village.
However, we can't
return to our
village just yet.
(surprised gasp)
Karai!
Yeah. Hey, Amai.
You idiot! What
have you done
to yourself?!
What about Nigai?!
(angry growl)
Nigai...
Do not underestimate us!
Lightning Rat Tremor!
(painful grunt)
No, Nigai!
Ahh! Just get away!
Please listen!
Don't come any
closer!
(angry growl)
Nigai!
(painful scream)
It's this bug-
shaped lump!
Inside of it is a
mass of chakra with
properties similar
to a Paper Bomb.
It siphons off the
chakra of its victim,
and when it exceeds a
certain volume, then
it just explodes. You
mentioned that Nigai
used a jutsu right
before the end, right?
Using a jutsu involves
releasing a large amount
of chakra, which is then
absorbed by this lump,
causing it to grow
even further.
You're saying it
exploded inside
him?! Can Karai
still be saved?
I'm sorry, sir, but
my Medical Ninjutsu...
...just isn't
powerful enough.
I see.
But there is someone
who can help!
What?!
In fact, she's right
here in this town!
Who is it?!
Lady Tsunade of the
Hidden Leaf. She's
here!
No one else can match
Lady Tsunade's skills
as a Medical Ninja.
I'm sure that she's-
How sappy! Look, I
know that your name
may mean "sweet"...
But still, you
don't have to be
so syrupy, Amai!
But Lady Tsunade
can help! I-
You shouldn't call a
shinobi from another
village "Lady"!
And besides, we Hidden
Cloud are not allies
with the Hidden Leaf.
There's no way she
would come to our
aid. Just forget it!
She will!
Huh?
I'll make her!
I'll bring Tsunade here,
even if I have to drag
her! And then-
No, don't! Lord
Raikage, please,
you mustn't rely
on a shinobi from
a rival village,
not for my sake!
I will make her
heal you!
And will you completely
abandon your pride as
the Raikage, too?
I'll keep my pride!
And I'll save you,
as well!
Wow, Lord Raikage...
Now you sound even
more syrupy than
Amai does.
What pride is there
in letting my men die?
How could I call myself
Raikage?!
Karai! You're not allowed
to die! You must stay by
my side until we can safely
return to our village!
Yes, sir, Lord Raikage.
Let's go, Amai!
You're taking me
to Tsunade!
(drunken sighs)
Shizune! We're
all out of sake!
Hey! Wake up! Did you
hear me? We're all out
of sake! Now get up
and get me some more!
Ugh, damn it! What
a wimp, passing out
so soon! I'm just
getting started here!
More sake!
Sister...
Once more...
Is this...
...what I think
it is?
Yep! It belonged to
our grandfather, the
necklace of the First
Hokage.
(happy gasp)
I love you!
And I give my word, I'll
follow our grandfather's
footsteps and be just
like him!
To be Hokage!
That's my dream!
Just one more time...
Just one more
glimpse...
...of their
smiling faces.
I love this village
and the people in it
with all my heart. I
want to protect them.
It's been my dream
ever since my sister
died.
It's all that's
kept me going.
So, him too.
We're the same.
That's why I have
to become Hokage...
...the person that
protects everyone.
To be Hokage.
That's my dream
Take this, I want
you to have it.
Playing at being
Hokage? Count me
out, it's a fool's
game.
I just wish they
were still alive...
I loved them. The chance
to see them again, to
hold them in my arms!
Even just one more time.
Lady Tsunade, one of the
Legendary Sannin of the
Village Hidden in the
Leaves! I've come here
to make a request!
I beseech you!
Please hear me out!
Who are you?
What do you want?
Ma'am, my name is
Amai, and I'm a
shinobi from the
Hidden Cloud Village!
Please, Lady Tsunade!
Come with me and use
your world-renowned
Medical Ninjutsu skills
to save my injured
comrade!
Wait, aren't you a
Cloud Medical Ninja?
Yes, ma'am!
Well, if your comrade
is hurt, why don't you
just go heal him?
THe situation's beyond
my abilities.
Hmmm...
I don't want to.
But, please!
The Hidden Cloud dares
to approach someone
from the Hidden Leaf
to ask a favor?
You tried to steal
the Hyuga's Byakugan
from us!
But the villages
already settled
that disagreement!
A typical answer from
the one who started it.
Please, let bygones
be bygones!
Enough, Amai!
I never actually expected
her to listen to this
proposal willingly!
Lady Tsunade, I present
the leader of the Hidden
Cloud...
...Lord Raikage.
Well, now! What a
surprise! So the big
shot himself waltzes in
here, acting all tough.
If you refuse to come
and help us, then I
will force you to come.
That's interesting.
Do you have any idea
just who you're
threatening?!
You're going to
regret this!
I'll be waiting
for you outside.
Why, that heartless!
Tsunade! You broke
your word to me! You
will pay dearly for
this! Come on, wake up!
Get up and fight me!
Huh? And who are you?
He's Lord Raikage of
the Hidden Cloud.
(shocked gasp)
(angry growl)
Ah-ha! Well, isn't
this a surprise!
You said that
yesterday!
Now, now, don't be
angry! Hey, you know
what? Why don't we
make a little bet?
Make a bet?
You said you'd force
me to come, right?
Tell you what. We'll
arm wrestle, and if you
can defeat me, then I'll
gladly go with you.
Oh, boy. This is not
good. What happened
while I was asleep,
anyway?!
Ready...
Go!
(strained grunt)
(angry growl)
What?! She's
overpowering me?
This... woman!
(frustrated growl)
No! I cannot lose!
If I do, Karai will-
No matter what, I
am not going to
lose this bet!
(shocked gasp)
Lady Tsunade lost a
contest of strength?
Not quite...
That trickster, he
purposely weakened his
hold for an instant to
create an space between
my hand and his. And
then he seized that
moment to push down
swiftly against my hand.
So he didn't actually
defeat me with strength.
He won with speed!
Don't you dare say
I was a coward.
Relax, I won't. We
didn't say this was
a contest of strength.
You just had to beat
me in arm wrestling,
and you did.
Wait, if we won, that
means you're going to
treat Karai, right?
He's this way!
Hnnh! Let's go,
Shizune!
Uh...Right!
Incredible!
Karai! We've brought
Lady Tsunade! She's
the best Medical Ninja
in the world!
You're gonna be
just fine!
You mentioned something
about stealing a Hidden
Jutsu from the Land
of Cedar.
Who would've imagined
that the Cedar Village
would have someone so
skilled.
It wasn't a shinobi
from the Cedar Village.
(surprised gasp)
What's that?!
It was someone that
they hired from the
Nokizaru Troops.
(shocked gasp)
The Nokizaru Troops?
You're talking about the
shinobi who specialize
in hunting other shinobi?!
I can't let this man's
treatment be compromised.
So tell me everything
you know!
A simple surgery should
be able to remove the
Explosive Bugs.
All right, Karai's
in your hands!
Shizune, take
care of it!
What?! You won't be
wielding the scalpel?!
Look, don't worry!
She's a highly skilled
Medical Ninja!
But I thought
you were-
Silence! Shizune
will be doing this!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "One work
Betting On."
You'll be sorry if
anything happens
to Karai!