♪
He barely missed a vital spot.
But I think that she's going to
be all right.
[grunt] Naruto...
[grunts]
Damn it! Argh!
[explosion]
[screaming]
How dare you...
This is just so... it's
unforgivable! All right,
that's it! I'm gonna-!
Hey, demon fox! Lend me some
more of your power!
I'm gonna take this wall of rock
and shatter it to pieces!
This seal is in a whole
different league.
It'll be difficult to break
even with my power.
And besides, you still can't
control my chakra properly yet.
You're drowning in your anger.
Shut up, stupid fox!
Stay strong, everyone!
Don't give up!
However, it's probably
impossible to completely stop
the compression. Ultimately.
For now, I'm going to
put my trust in them.
Them?
What? Something
inside of me is...
Kushina, what's wrong?
It's the Nine Tails!
Usually, I'm able to
keep it stabilized...
but it's irritated and
unsettled right now.
Is it because you're
expending so much chakra
for the Four Crimson Rays?
That's not it, I can
also feel that...
there's something
happening to the other
Nine Tails, ya know?!
Naruto?
Ino, contact the others on the
outside!  I need to find out
what's going on out there!
Got it! Right away,
Lord Fourth!
Shikamaru! Can you hear me?
Is that you, Ino?! How
are things on your side?
Not good... but we're managing.
Anyway, let me know what's
going on out there!
Okay.  Naruto, uh, Yahiko...
The enemy used a jutsu
to seal him up in a
moon-like rock,
Just like what
happened to the village.
What?!  Naruto was...? Naruto's
been sealed?!
Yes. Naruto underwent Nine
Tails Transformation and went
on a rampage.
So the enemy pulled rocks from
the ground, hardened them around
him, and sealed him away.
Sealed even in
Nine Tails State?
Kushina!
He still doesn't have enough
strength...  or enough chakra...
No way!  You can't do what
you're thinking of doing!
If you try that,
Kushina, you'll--!
Naruto is my son.
I'm his mother.
In order to save him, and to
save you and all the people of
the village... In order to do
that...
But then... I'll...
All right. I know that once you
make up your mind, you don't
listen to anyone.
I'm sorry, Minato. But
it has to be this way.
Right now, I'm the only
one who can save Naruto.
Come on, already!  Just give me
your power, all right?!
Looking at you, I can't
tell which one of us is
the one in a cage...
I don't get it!  How can you
stay so calm right now?
If this keeps up, we'll all die!
You know what? Just
forget it! Never mind!
I just want to defeat
that guy, that's all!
Huh!?
What?! Mom?!
How come you're--?
Listen, why are you
so angry right now?
Why am I angry?!
Why else?! That guy who blew up
that other village back then got
you, Dad, and everyone else!
Oh yeah, and, Hinata, too.
I can't. There's no way
that I can forgive that guy!
Yeah, but if you stay
angry, you can't use
your power properly,
no matter how powerful
you might be.
So just calm yourself
down and check in on
how everyone is doing.
You should be able
to sense them now.
[gasp]
(Kushina)
The people of the village... all
of them... are inside fighting.
Hinata!
Thank goodness!
She's still alive!
Uh-huh! One less thing
to be angry about, right?
I kinda don't know what to do
when you're nice, ya know, Mom!
When you're angry, you
can't handle Nine Tails' power!
Mom! Nine Tails! He's right-!
Huh? What the heck
is going on?!
Listen, long ago when Nine
Tails attacked the village.
Minato sealed half of the
Nine Tails inside me,
and the other half
inside you, even though
you'd just been born.
He believed that in time,
this power would come to
be helpful to you.
Yeah, but everyone
hated me so much.
and it was all because of this
stupid monster fox inside of me!
Sorry... Both Minato and I had
faith that in time, you'd
eventually be able to control
this power... despite its
tremendous strength.
So what do I have to do?  How am
I supposed to control this power
properly?!
(Kushina)
Like I said, don't get mad.
And pay close attention
to what people tell you.
And also think about what the
"right way" to use this power
should be.
To wield a strong power,  you
gotta have a strong will, too!
Have a strong will?
That's why...  I'm going to
use my strong will with the Nine
Tails Chakra right now...
What do you mean?
I'm going to pass on my Nine
Tails Chakra to you, and then,
when the two chakras, both Yin
and Yang, become one, I'm sure
that we'll be able to get out of
here.
What are you talking about, mom?
You can't! I mean, you're
a Jinchuriki too!
So you know what that means!  If
the Nine Tails leaves your body,
then you're gonna die!
I won't!  Because I'm gonna make
my power and my will, live!
I have no clue what you're even
saying right now!
That's exactly why
I told you to think.
Y'know, Lord Jiraiya used to
say that you might be the Child
of Prophecy who will save the
future of all shinobi.
"Child of Prophecy?"
Your will is what's going
to save the Leaf Village.
But, mom...
You are our son. You are so
precious to Minato and me...
I'm sorry. It's
the only way.
(Nine Tails)
Half will do. Half is
enough, right?
That side seems pretty cozy, so
I wouldn't mind going over
there...
We may have to do
this again, too...
Right, Nine Tails. Thank you.
Thanks, mom...
It's in your hands. Good luck!
Kushina!  Are you all right?!
Naruto! Go now!
[roar]
How did...?!
Almighty Push!
[gasp]
The real you's not
here, isn't that right?
My business is with the real
Pain. So just take me to
where he is!
I want to go and talk to you
face-to-face right now.
You're nearby, right?  Not here,
but somewhere close!
Aren't you!?
Found him!
(Nagato)
Konan, stay out of this.
But Nagato...
(Nagato)
It's all right.
Are you him, then? Are
you the real Pain?
So it seems the strong has come
to punish the weak, is that it?
You're the one behind all this,
the one who was manipulating all
those other Pains?
Yes. And the final Pain that
you defeated was Yahiko.
Yahiko?
Yes, he is no longer
of this world.
He died three years ago in
that village when you Leaf
Shinobi killed him.
He's...?
...I see. But still, we weren't
the ones who blew up that
village!
Back then, the Hidden Leaf
feared that a scandal involving
them would be uncovered,
so they destroyed that
village in order to
hide the truth.
You see, that's how the
Great Nations save face.
Guess it's the obvious
way to avoid being
ridiculed by other villages.
You're wrong!  Until now, we
thought that it was you guys who
were behind what happened to
that village.
Right now, it doesn't matter
even a little bit who may
have thought what.
It still doesn't alter the fact
that my comrade Yahiko was
killed in that incident.
Your comrade?
Believe me... I know just how
hard it is to lose a comrade...
Hm?
Right now my friend is in danger
of being turned into
Orochimaru's vessel.
We've been rivals since we were
kids, and we trained together.
He's a very important
comrade to me.
Yahiko was a very important
comrade to both of us, too.
Sasuke... is going
through a rough time,
and he set out for
Orochimaru's on his own.
I just have this feeling that
he'd understand if we could only
have it out in one more fight.
As his friend, I want him to
have another chance...
What do you mean? What are
you talking about?!
Yeah, that's right... We're
friends, so we should be able
to reach an understanding.
That's why I'll never
give up on my friends!
I'll never give up!  We keep
being tossed around by the Great
Nations...
But we'll rescue people like us
who are suffering, and we'll
make them our friends...
Of course! Yes, that's it!
Huh?
We just have to become
friends with everyone!
And then we'll be able to come
to an understanding with them
instead of always having to
fight!
We won't have to have wars!
That's the reason why we just
have to keep on making Team
Jiraiya grow bigger and bigger!
[gasp]
Nagato...
Because if I were to give up
then there's no way that I'll
ever become the Hokage!
But I will become the Hokage and
become friends with shinobi from
all over!
No, not just with shinobi, but
with the kids too! Anyway...
If we're all friends, then
fights like this one
don't have to happen!
Is this... some kind
of coincidence?
We just have to become
friends with everyone!
And then we'll be able to come
to an understanding with them
instead of always having to
fight!
And that means you guys won't
have to fight anymore either!
[small gasp]
Anyway, look, I'm not asking you
to be my friend... At least not
yet.
Just let me join Team Jiraiya.
After all, I was Pervy Sage's
student, too, remember?
[gasp]
I'm not asking you to join us...
You can stay with the Leaf.
I want our goals to be
united along with yours.
Just what are...?! What are you?
Nagato...
I'm just asking you to let me
join Team Pervy Sage.
But before that I have
to save Sasuke...
... and also save my
comrades in the Leaf.
I promise to take on Pervy
Sage's will.
It's Team Jiraiya!
[laugh]
It's very mysterious. The two of
you... really are alike.
You're right. They are.
[grunting] Release!
What are you
doing, Nagato?
I  released the jutsu.
You know, you really
are quite a mystery.
The things you say, It almost
feels like someone set it all
up.
In fact, perhaps the truth...
might be that Sensei--!
Well, in any event, whether or
not you're suitable to become
a member of Team Jiraiya...
...depends on if you can save
that friend of yours...
Yahiko was a man who held his
friends in very high regard.
If you're as much like him
as you seem... then we can
definitely be friends.
Yeah... I'm gonna prove it
to you. I will save him!
Your command of the Leaf
Police Force was nothing
short of exemplary.
Thanks to you, there
were no casualties.
I'm very grateful.
Oh, no... It was an emergency,
and I just did what was expected
of a Leaf Shinobi, nothing more.
That aside, your son has
developed into a fine young man.
Whereas, I have failed as a
parent, I'm sorry to say...
We're still continuing to
search for the two of them.
But regretfully, we haven't
gotten any encouraging leads
yet.
All this for my sons... For your
support and that of the Village,
I'm truly humbled.
The consequences I'm suffering
are my own fault, because I only
paid attention to Itachi.
I'm sure Sasuke felt
suffering of his own,
constantly being compared
to his older brother.
Kugaku...
I keep picturing them
together, getting along.
I wish that I could
see them even just
once more before I die.
Yes...
This Chakra Nature!
This is a Change in Chakra
Form I've never seen...
...Who is it?
[gasping]
[difficulty breathing]
The poison...
[grunt]
I know you... you're
from back then.
Itachi's your older
brother, right?
We are the Akatsuki.
We've had our eyes on you
since you went to Orochimaru.
That's why we saved you.
So, a word of gratitude
would be nice.
Did you kill your brother?
Why, you--!
You kept shouting deliriously.
It was easy to figure out.
Get lost.
Why did your brother
have to die?
The ones who should
have died, didn't.
Naruto...!
(Hiruko)
Will you forgive them?
Forgive me... Sasuke.
[gasp]
This irony... This
contradiction. Why don't you
make it right?
The Akatsuki will
lend you a hand.
Tell me. What is it
that you want to do?
My only goal is to destroy
those controlling the Uchiha...
To destroy the Hidden Leaf!
(Tsunade)
Orochimaru is dead.  And it
seems Sasuke Uchiha did it.
(Naruto)
What about Sasuke?  Is he safe?
(Tsunade)
Yes, he is...
But we've received intel that
he's targeting each and every
Shinobi Village
alongside jonin-level Rogue
Ninja known as the Akatsuki.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Shinobi Unite"
(Naruto)
What the hell is he doing?!