What the-- What happened?
Just one second. I'll
replace the candle right now.
Thank you.
Lady Tsunade, are you
staying out here?
Yes, just for a little
while longer...
Okay, but don't overdo it.
That isn't going to be any good
for your health, after all!
Yeah, I know that...
Lord Jiraiya put his heart
and soul into that book...
I don't blame her for getting
so absorbed in it.
♪
[growling]
A fourth tail, huh...?
Well, I guess it was still too
soon for Naruto to be able to
control the Nine Tails Chakra.
[growling]
Hmmm... I guess I have no choice
but to lock the Eight Signed
Seal once more...
Naruto... just quiet down... And
let me take care of things...
[snarl]
Art of the Raging Lion's Mane!
[roaring]
[roar]
[crash]
[groan]
Man... He really packs a punch!
I think that I just broke a few
ribs.
Summoning: Bring Down
the House Jutsu!
[angry snarl]
[grunt]
Okay, Earth Style:
The Dark Swamp!
[angry roar]
Come on now... Take control
of yourself, Naruto!
[roar]
[gasp]
[roaring]
Naruto....
(Fukasaku)
He's dreamt of you, Jiraiya-boy.
And as you are no doubt aware,
his dream was not just a dream.
It was a prophecy of the future,
which he will now tell you.
...So listen carefully.
Yes, sir.
In my dream, you, who are
singularly pervy, will
nonetheless become a great
ninja.
And once you do, you will
eventually acquire apprentices
of your very own.
Pervy?  I can't believe he
remembers that of all things...
One such student will come to
possess great power.
Depending on how you guide him,
the future of the Shinobi World
will undergo a great change.
Wait, I'm the one who's
going to guide him?!
Furthermore, this apprentice of
yours will have an enormous
influence on the future of the
entire Shinobi World.
What, seriously?! My
apprentice will?!
Yes... The future of the Shinobi
World will be wrought with many
calamities.
One of your apprentices will be
the one who will prevent those
calamities.
However....
If they're guided in the right
direction, the world will change
for the better...
...but if guided wrongly,
they'll bring about great ruin.
And the duty that's fated to
fall on your shoulders is to be
the one who will guide the Child
of Prophecy in the
right direction.
"Child of Prophecy?"
[angry roars]
Impossible! To think the one
who might bring about great
ruin is-!
Do you all plan on ignoring
the rules of the village?
Yeah. We can't return home to
the village when our friends are
still being held captive.
We all agree on that.
[sigh] Why did I think that you
would be like Itachi?
It's too soon. You're
not ready yet.
Sasuke...
Itachi was able to master it
when he was about your age.
And currently, he's with the
ANBU that're directly under
Lord Hokage.
The job of the Leaf Police Force
is to uphold the laws of the
village...
...and I was hoping
to fill the void left
by Itachi's transfer...
...Focus.
I won't lose to Big Brother!  To
honor the rules, I'll destroy
these puppets!
A smokescreen...
No, Sasuke!
He used the smoke to create a
blind spot for the puppet user!
He's being reckless!
Fire Style!  Fireball Jutsu!
[gasp]
Cha!
I guess it won't be that easy...
Argh!
[grunt]
Cha!
Even if our intentions may be
different, we cannot just ignore
the needs of our friends!
Just great. All right,
follow Lee, everyone!
Human Boulder! Roll,
roll, roll, roll, roll...!
All right, take this!  Cha!
Fang Over Fang!
Hiya!
Sasuke...!
You know, I really hope that you
didn't go charging in all by
yourself like that just because
you knew that we wouldn't
leave a friend behind!
[snicker]
The Leaf shinobi chose
to attack the puppets...
Do they intend on bringing them
down and then returning to the
Leaf Village?
Have they chosen the rules
instead of choosing their
friends?
[gasp]
Even the young cannot break free
of the curse of following the
rules.
A caged bird is a caged
bird, after all.
They don't know how to fly
freely through the heavens.
Tell me, has your Byakugan
somehow become clouded?
What!?
They're not fighting because
they want to honor the rules!
They're fighting
for their friend!
[gasp]
They're not bound
by the rules
of the village.
By their own free will,
they're fighting to save
their friend right now!
[angry growls0
(Hiruko)
I guess this is far enough...
They've already decided.
It's fairly obvious... there's
no future for shinobi...
There is only... hell.
I'll show you an artistic
and eternal hell!
Damn it! He had puppets
in reserve as back-up!
[struggling gasps]
You told me that there
are three steps to this
training, right, Dad?
But up until now, you've only
actually taught me two of them!
Yep, you've got it!
Now, then...
But, dad, this is just
an ordinary balloon.
The first step is rotation.
And the second step is force.
Yeah, that's as far
as I've gotten.
Well, on to the
third step, then!
The one in my left palm
looks like an ordinary
plain balloon, right?
Uh... Well, yeah!
So, then, if you reproduce
the contents of the balloon
with your right hand...
(Naruto)
Amazing! The massive chakra
spinning wildly and getting
faster
but the balloon still remains
a perfect sphere...!
in other words the chakra in the
second step, infused with power,
is fixed inside the balloon.
What? It's fixed?
Adding force to the chakra,
compresses it and fixes it.
What!? It's hard enough just
making it turn and adding power
with both hands!
Are you telling me that you can
increase it even more?!
I guess you could use all
the help you can get!
But if you can learn
it, you get this...
[gasp]
Whoa! That is awesome!
This Rasengan is a super
high-level ninjutsu.
Only two shinobi are able to do
this: Jiraiya Sensei and myself.
Do you think that I'll
be able to do it, too?!
Yes, of course! I'm sure
that you'll get it!
(Thinking)
Wait... "All the help I can
get."
What is going on here?!
There is no end to this!
(Naruto)
Sakura...! Just hold on!
I'm coming to save you!
[angry roar]
Naruto!?
[grunts]
Huh! Pervy Sage,
what happened?
Oh! So you're back now, huh?
But, how did you get hurt!?
Don't worry, it's nothing. But
I can't move much, so I've
gotta head back for now.
But you'd better get back to
the others you got that?
See ya. Reverse
Summoning Jutsu!
Huh... Argh!
[groan]
[gasp]
Not good. At this rate,
they're all going to be...
Hold on...
What? Why?
The way things are going, the
Leaf shinobi are in real danger.
Just wait. I sense massive
chakra closing in...
Why did this fight have to
turn into such a drag?
Aw, man, I am such an idiot!
(Naruto)
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Huh!?
Rotation! Then, Power!
And with some help, I can
compress it and fix it!
Just what is he doing?
Look at all that chakra!
No way, that jutsu...
Thats Rasengan!
Impossible!  The reason is
because that jutsu is-
Naruto is awesome!
Naruto!?
All right, here goes!
Rasengan!
[revving up yell]
Cha!
No way!
Next one!  Let's go!
[clones yelling]
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[explosion]
Naruto...!?
Damn you to hell!  How dare you
ruin my masterpieces like this!
Are you the Puppet
User behind this?
Heh.
Ah!
Huh...? Damnit!
Uh... Sorry, guys,
but he got away...
That was amazing!
Taking down all of those puppets
by yourself.  Just incredible.
I believe that I just might
have been underestimating
you all this time!
That's for sure!  You were
hiding amazing power!
That power must
be acknowledged.
The reason is because everyone
had a tough time with the enemy
but you came and took
them down by yourself.
Yeah! I'd expect
nothing less!
Well, I was
totally surprised!
They say that skilled
hawks hide their talons
until they need them!
I really hate to admit it, but
this is one time that I have
to acknowledge him.
[bark bark]
Tsk...
By the way, Naruto, we're going
to go and save our friends.
It'll mean disobeying the rules
of the Leaf Village, but it's
what all of us wanna do.
All right, that's great!  And I
feel the same way as you guys
do, of course!
Well, Sasuke?
With this much fighting
strength, you can't tell us that
rescuing our friends is
impossible anymore.
Sasuke! come along
with us, ya know!
Fine, whatever.
Okay then!
it's decided!
Alright, you all heard it!
We're working together now!
We'll rescue Asuma and no, we'll
rescue our friends!
(All)
Right!
Has your so-called test
finally produced a result now?
I believe it's been proven
conclusively that they consider
the bonds of friendship more
important than the
rules of the village.
So there's no need
to continue anymore...
You wi release all of the
Hidden Leaf Shinobi that you've
abducted, won't you...?
Right, Father?
(Naruto)
Who are you guys?
(Konan)
First of all, we're
not your enemy.
(Yahiko)
We want to show you a
sign of mutual trust.
We're sorry for getting you
involved in our employer's test.
(Nagato)
That test's over now. So
shortly, all your friends
will be released.
(Naruto)
What, seriously?
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Caged Bird"
(Naruto)
You're sayin' you guys know
Pervy Sage, too?