Many shinobi from small
villages survived by taking
advantage of the
turbulent situation.
They have no wish to be
controlled by the nations of
Fire, Wind, and Earth.
So I have no doubt
they'll continue
to cause disruptions.
However, this peace
was won through the
sacrifice of many, so
we must maintain it.
And for that, I'm going
to count on all of you.
Yes, sir!
[sigh]
Chidori!
[gasp]
Five shinobi! All
approaching rapidly!
Their headband?
They're from the Stone.
We have a peace treaty
with the Stone, don't we?
So maybe they're here
on urgent business?
[gasp]
Why are you
breaking the treaty?!
Hey! We're shinobi
from the Leaf Village!
Stop! Maybe there's a
misunderstanding?!
Reinforcements!
Retreat!
Thanks for that. Looks
like the Hidden Stone
has betrayed us!
This isn't a Hidden
Stone shuriken.
You mean they were
fakes?! But why would--?!
To cause a rift between
the Stone and the Leaf.
Hey!
Don't chase them too far!
Chidori!
Hey, there! How
have you been?
You're ignoring me?!
It's only been a short time
since Kakashi transferred
into the ANBU, but
some of his actions
have been quite
astonishing.
[sigh]
One...
[scream]
[gasp]
Four!
[grunt]
The Sharingan!
You're the infamous
cold-blooded Kakashi!
Kakashi! Wait!
Agh! Somebody!
Help me!
Five!
All five killed
with a single blow to
their vital points.
If you'd kept at
least one alive, we
could've gotten intel.
[gasp]
Lord Hokage, regarding your
concerns: we've seen no
evidence of psychological
trauma in Kakashi
from taking Rin's life.
Is something on your mind?
I'm okay...
Congratulations!
Huh?
Your due date works out to
be. Let's see, October tenth!
[chuckle] Oh, that's great!
What?! A baby?!
That's right! I'm gonna
be a mother, ya know!
And I'm gonna be a father...
I'm gonna be a
mother, ya know!
And I'm really
gonna be a father!
I'm gonna be a
mother, ya know!
[happy giggle]
Wow, imagine that,
I'm gonna be a father!
[enthusiastic laughter]
I can't believe
I'm gonna mother!
Kakashi, I want you to leave
your current position and
take on another,
special one.
Is there a problem?
Oh, no, it's
nothing like that.
Instead, this will be more
like a top-secret errand.
You see, Kushina
is pregnant!
[gasp] Oh!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
However...
When a female Jinchuriki
becomes pregnant,
the energy that keeps
the seal in place is
temporarily transferred
to the fetus.
As a result, the seal of
the Tailed Beast weakens.
In any event, it will be
roughly nine months
till she gives birth.
Till then, I want you to
guard Kushina against
any incidents.
Yes, sir!
Thank you, Kakashi,
for protecting Kushina.
Of course. But...
This is just standard
procedure. The ANBU
directly under Lord Third
take over guard duties
during the actual birth.
Then I'll be returning to
my regular ANBU duties?
There's really no need
for you to be so hasty.
Why don't you take little
a break for a while?
[sigh]
I'm so sorry I haven't
been able to come by.
It isn't as if I've
forgotten about you.
It's just, this is
technically top secret info.
But Minato Sensei's
child is about to be born.
This generation
won't know war.
If only we'd been
born a little later.
I ought to tell
Obito, too.
So I'll be going now.
Later, Rin.
[chatter]
Thanks for coming!
Sure! I'll be back!
I know, come on!
Let's go home!
Look, why don't we just do
Rock-Paper-Scissors again?
Oh come on! There
must be something more
exciting that we can do!
And you call
yourself my rival!
We have to get an
early start tomorrow.
So let's just take
a pass on tonight.
A mission is no excuse!
I have all of this pent-up
energy inside me, so there's
no better time than
right now for some
really rigorous training!
Honest-to-goodness
discipline and hard work
will lead us to success
in future missions!
Hey! Kakashi! Are you
even listening to me one
tiny little bit?!
You sure have gotten awfully
cold since joining the ANBU!
I've heard the gossip.
Everyone's saying
that you're really
cold-blooded now.
I know we can't discuss the
ANBU, but we can't cast
aside our friendship!
Youth is short, you know!
Forget that for now. Do you
sense something strange?
As if there were suddenly
a dark chill in the air?
The only thing that's
chilly is your attitude!
You must be much
more hot-blooded!
I feel something
ominous.
[baby crying]
There, there. It's okay...
What a strange feeling.
Of all the times for Mom
and Dad to be out...
Don't cry, Sasuke. No matter
what happens, your big
brother will protect
you, I promise you that.
It can't be...
Summoning Jutsu!
[screams]
[groaning]
Is that?!
[growling]
No! No way!
[roar]
The Nine Tails!
[screams]
Go, Nine Tails!
[growling]
[roar]
[angry roar]
[screaming]
Lord Third! It's
the Nine Tails!
The Nine Tails is
inside the village!
Damn you, Nine Tails!
It's time to release all
of my pent-up energy!
We don't know
what we're facing!
Come on! I'll be
your opponent!
Wait!
Huh?
We all need to gather
immediately in the guardroom!
Why?
The Third Hokage
ordered it!
What? Lord
Hiruzen did?!
Well, you heard
him. Let's go, Guy!
Listen up. You younger
shinobi stay away
from the Nine Tails.
What do you mean?
This is domestic
trouble, not a war
against other villages.
There's no need for all
of you to put your lives
on the line for this.
You've got to be kidding!
Stop, Kurenai;
just calm down!
You are also a shinobi.
You aren't going to live
forever, you know.
But, my daughter, you're a
woman, too. Bequeath the
Will of Fire upon my
future grandchildren!
Please make that your
oath to me, your father.
For I do believe in you.
It's no time for a
family argument!
I hate not being able to do
anything! Especially now!
Minato Sensei...
The barrier's
disappeared!
Lord Fourth!
Lady Kushina!
Take her to the
hospital right away!
Summon the
Medical Ninja!
Please, Lord Third...
Kushina!
I beg you. Please
take care of our baby.
Yes, of course, you don't
need to worry about that!
His name is Naruto.
Minato and I...
Together, we both picked
that name out of the pages.
Of Jiraiya Sensei's novel.
Naruto, you say?
Very well. I'll take
responsibility!
But now, for the sake of
your child, you must rest!
[gasp]
Kushina...
I'll keep my promise.
Minato...
And Kushina, both of you
gave your lives to protect
the Hidden Leaf Village,
and to safeguard
its future as well.
Minato Sensei.
We managed to quell
the Nine Tails, but the
sacrifice was
much too great.
However, it's no
time to lament.
The Hokage's seat is now
empty, and we must decide
with all haste on the
person who will fill it.
Perhaps someone from the
generation after Minato
could take over.
We have nurtured fine
jonin, without a doubt!
But unfortunately, none
of them yet possess
the experience to rule
over a whole village.
Is there anyone
who has that?
Uh...
It can't be helped.
This is a critical time.
So I shall take
over as Hokage.
You would really
consider doing that?
Well, then, if you're
still truly willing to--
You quit once.
Do you really believe
that you're up to the task?
Can you actually
handle it?
Truth be told, even though
you did go after the Nine
Tails, you still failed
to save the Fourth
Hokage from his fate.
Such a remark is
completely uncalled for!
And where were you
during the battle against
the Nine Tails, Danzo?
[growl]
[laughter]
Please, indulge
this old man.
Allow me to fill in as
Hokage, just for the time
being until we can
groom the next one.
[growl]
You're Kakashi Hatake,
isn't that right?
Lord Danzo...
Listen, come and work under
me. What do you say to that?
But I was working
for Minato Sensei.
I'm afraid that Lord
Fourth, the one who
recruited you into the
ANBU, is no longer with us.
If you stay where you are,
you'll end up working
directly under the
Third Hokage, who will
reassume his old position.
His foolhardy ideals
of peace are what
caused the war
to drag on.
And also drove Obito
and Rin to their deaths.
But, sir!
Furthermore...
On the night of the Nine
Tails rampage, you weren't
able to join in the fight.
That was because of
orders that the Lord Third
Hokage himself gave.
To be frank, isn't that
one of the reasons why
Lord Fourth lost his
life that night?
[gasp]
I don't want to believe
that Lord Third planned all
this in order to
return to power...
But the future of the Leaf
cannot be entrusted to
someone like him!
A select few of you
ANBU will be chosen to
guard the Feudal Lord's
procession on the way
back to his prefecture.
Yes, sir!
And this will be our plan.
Wood Style?!
Wood Style! Giant
Forest Jutsu!
Enough!
I requested that
he join us here.
Yes, sir.
I appreciate
you coming.
This is it.
It appears that the
time has arrived.
Excellent work,
Kakashi.
Hashirama Senju, who
founded the Leaf Village
and was the First
Hokage, was freely able
to use Wood
Style Ninjutsu.
He was the only one who
could. But now, there's
another who can
use Wood Style.
What does this mean?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Hashirama's
Cells."
How is he able to
us e Wood Style?