[gasp]
W-What is that?!
Katsuyu!
Yes, ma'am!
I shall explain everything!
Are you all
right now, Sakura?
Yeah...
The Five Kage will be
here shortly- Shikamaru!
Shikamaru!
Hey!
Hey, he looks really bad!
Katsuyu!
Let's begin Distance
Healing right away!
That's not possible.
But why?!
Even my mini fragments that
are attached to everyone
have been drained.
They have lost their
chakra and died as well.
But that's--
In short, everyone's
in the same
state as my fragments.
I'm sorry, Dad.
It looks like I'm gonna
be right on your heels.
Shikamaru!
Sorry, Mom.
Sakura!
If we're gonna die anyway,
let's go down fighting to
the very best of
our abilities.
However, at this rate.
[groan]
We'll all die before
we even get to fight!
Shinobi are all done for.
There's no need
to keep going.
If you don't
resist, I won't kill you.
And if you keep standing
against us, you'll continue
to lose your
friends one by one.
This shall become a
world where no one who
acknowledges you will exist.
Regret will fill you unless
you stop and do nothing.
If we just do nothing
then we'll all be saved?
That's right.
No more fearing
death or enduring pain.
You'll be entering a dream.
Don't give up!
If you're put under
genjutsu, you're
as good as dead.
This enormous tree is very
closely connected to Obito
like an extra limb
for extracting chakra.
We mustn't be careless.
Such words of weakness.
How unlike you,
Sarutobi Sensei.
Orochimaru...
You're quite late!
And the Five Kage?
I saw to their healing.
If they don't chicken
out, they should be coming.
You're still as
sarcastic as ever, I see.
Sorry I'm late, Jugo!
Sasuke!
You've come...
Oh, man that tree
really is giant, seeing
it up close like this.
I wonder how long
it's gonna take to cut
that huge thing down.
Ugh, who cares
about that, Suigetsu?!
What's important is to go
jump Sasuke and hug him and
lick him all over, damn it!
Is to heal the Allied
Forces shinobi, right?
Yeah!
Yeah, I know!
Shut your trap!
I know already, damn it!
He seems to be
in a foul mood.
What's going on?
When that bud blooms,
the Infinite Tsukuyomi
will be complete.
That's what Madara said.
And yet, after depleting the
chakra of this many shinobi
the bud shows no
signs of blooming.
So when's it
going to bloom, then?
Eight Tails' and Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki are still alive.
Do you get it?
So the chakra of Eight Tails
and Nine Tails are both
essential for it to bloom
and to complete the jutsu.
However, if it contains even
a small amount of each of
their chakra, then
it is still fine.
In other words...
It is not as if it
is unable to bloom.
All that's affected is how
long it will take to bloom.
There's about
fifteen minutes to go.
In that time, I shall stop
Obito and switch places
with him by using
your Sage Power.
This is bad.
I must relay all that my
original body has heard to
the rest of the
Allied Forces.
Are there any from
the Yamanaka Clan here?
Sir!
Do you know the Mind
Transmission Jutsu?!
Uh, yes, sir!
I do, sir!
Good, then link
me to everyone!
I'd like to explain about
that giant tree and the
Infinite Tsukuyomi!
This sensation!
Grandfather!
Ah!
Is that you, Tsuna?
This voice is unmistakably
Lord Hashirama's!
That means the Five Kage
are now close enough to be
within range of my jutsu!
Wait!
This is no time
for reminiscing!
I have things I must
relay to you five and
to everyone else!
Listen carefully!
I'll retrieve a
little more chakra.
It'll take a while
for it to bloom.
So we're all...
just nourishment
for that tree?
That's it?!
That's what shinobi are?!
Then how are we
supposed to fight it?!
Plus we only have
about fifteen minutes?!
We can't even get near it!
And yet, doing nothing
will yield the same result.
We must either cut down that
tree or defeat the caster
within the remaining time.
But...
I told you not
to give up hope!
Easy for you to say!
You're a Reanimation
from the past brought
back to life!
We're still alive!
It's all over!
If it's going to end
like this, we shouldn't
have started it at all.
[scared chatter]
Yes, that's right.
Just stay like that.
I'll take you to a world
where there're no regrets.
Naruto...
You throwing in the towel?
'Cause I'm not.
Let's go, Jugo.
Right.
These are...
Feelings from Naruto's heart
coming through my jutsu.
I can feel them!
Back then I kept
thinking that I should've
called out to him.
I thought about it
over and over.
His thoughts are flowing in.
That's why...
This is...
This is from that day...
I...
I don't wanna
regret anything,
I never want to
think, "I should've!"
Naruto...
Plus...
I can't just
make everything...
That we've all done up until
this point meaningless!
Sasuke!
I'm coming with you!
[chuckle]
Naruto Uzumaki...
Again and again.
Sorry to have to
borrow more chakra.
No worries.
We're counting
on you, Naruto!
Hey Sasuke, you do
remember that only Sage
Jutsu works on
him, don't you?!
I'm aware of
that I'm not you.
Karin!
Look right there.
Isn't that Sasuke's
Curse Mark patterning?
But wait, I thought that he
lost the Curse Mark power?
Sage Jutsu Power's the
source of Jugo's Curse Mark.
And with regard to Sasuke...
When I experimentally
injected Jugo's chakra into
him, he immediately
unleashed the Curse Mark.
So it's not surprising
Sasuke's Susano'o would
respond to Jugo's
chakra similarly.
I suppose you could call
it a Sage Jutsu Susano'o.
Sasuke Uchiha, huh?
An Uchiha who shows
the same potential as
Madara once did.
Maybe I'll go join them.
You'll trip 'em up
and get stabbed again!
And Sasuke, your
power is unlike that
of the two behind me.
Or rather, unlike that of
any I've experimented on.
It still hasn't come
close to its limits.
I know, my gut tells me
based on intel gathered over
my entire life that you'll
one day be a shinobi who
surpasses Madara!
And Naruto Uzumaki, you
remind me so much of my
Elder Brother. You're a
foolish, naïve brat who
spouts idealisms at
the top of your voice.
And yet, everyone likes you
and wants to depend on you.
-Let's Go!
-Right!
It'll be too
late for regrets.
Not that either one
of you has a future.
Those two really went
to face off against him?
Yeah!
What should we all do?
Let's ask the Five
Kage when they get here.
Is that really good enough?
I look forward to the
battles we shall fight until
I achieve my true dream.
And what is
your true dream?!
I thought everything
we aimed for is right
here in this village!
You simply cannot see it.
What's even further ahead.
Dreams of the far future.
Well, then tell me
about them, Madara, please!
Wait, these are
Lord First's memories?
Dreams of the future.
The simple fact that we
could convene this Five Kage
Summit with the
first Kage of each of
the Five Great Nations.
Truly fills me
with gratitude!
Elder Brother!
The Hokage of the Land
of Fire's Hidden Leaf,
shouldn't bow so
easily to the other Kage!
But I'm just so happy!
Lord Hokage,
raise your head.
This type of behavior
is just not becoming
of a village leader.
In any event, I did indeed
come here to endorse at
least the gist of
Lord Hokage's pact.
However, I'm not just going
to sign anything for free.
I agree.
And besides, if you
behave too humbly,
you'll make us suspicious.
Distributing the Tailed
Beasts that Lord Hokage has
collected to the other
villages is the condition
of signing the treaty.
This is just a transaction,
not something one
should get emotional about.
Exactly.
We'll assign the Tailed
Beasts based on power
balance, but
you're required to pay.
They're not free?
Shut it!
This was the
very first summit!
Yes.
And it was what led to
the end of minor conflicts.
In our village, a certain
temple's acolytes have
been keeping a
Tailed Beast sealed away.
And because we already
possess one, we do not have
any need for another one.
Instead, we would like an
alternative compensation for
our collaboration
in this pact.
Would that be acceptable?
What do you want?
Our nation is
completely covered in sand.
Thus, we'd like the
adjoining Hidden Leaf to
share arable land with us
instead of a Tailed Beast.
And the other nations to
hand over thirty percent of
your Tailed Beast
purchase price as well.
Don't mess around with us!
What?!
This a joke,
Lord Kazekage?!
I won't sign on to this
pact unless all of you
accept the terms
I've laid out!
Mine is a sand-bound
nation with zero fertility!
It's only natural to use my
village's Tailed Beast to
full advantage in
dealings with the four
other Great Nations!
We four other nations could
also join our forces and
crush the Land of Wind.
It is true that our
nations have never
gotten along in the past.
But we each did what we
had to do to protect our
brethren and our clans.
Perhaps at times we
had no other choice.
And now, today, even
if our Five Nation
Treaty comes to be.
I honestly can't say how
long it will last or even
if we can hold onto it.
But I've got this dream that
at some time in the future,
there will come a day when
shinobi will collaborate,
and help each othe, with
one heart, regardless
of their affiliation.
That is my dream
of the future.
I ask you to take the
first step toward
that dream today!
So, please,
please, please, please!
I beg of you!
All of my- no, our
beloved children!
Now is the time to take all
the pain, the frustration
and suffering we shinobi
have endured and weave it
into our true dream!
Your past is filtering
into me through the others.
Naruto Uzumaki, you are
the one who is uniting
everyone right now.
Your tempestuous history
made you who you are.
And your way of
life has brought hope
into everyone's hearts!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Pursuing Hope."
Let's go!
Let's cut down
that giant tree!