[Kiba]
Like before, whoever gets to the
finish line first wins all this!
[eager barking]
Don't worry, Akamaru.
I'll split it with
you once I win.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to win it this time.
No way, this candy's
gonna be all mine!
Choji, you really
going to do this?
You know Kiba's going to win.
He always does.
Just trust me. There is
no way that I'm gonna lose
when food is on the line!
[Kiba]
Shikamaru!
What?
If you're out on this one,
keep time for us, would you?
Egh. This is
such a drag.
[Naruto]
Wait! Don't start yet!
Huh?
I want in on this!
I accept your
challenge, too!
Huah!
What?! Why bother?
You don't have a chance!
Go on,
get lost!
Yeah, beating you
is just too easy!
But with his share,
we'll have even more candy!
Ah!
Hee! Hee! Hee!
Heh heh heh heh!
Choji's right.
Anyone can join as long
as they put up some candy.
Sounds good to me!
I've got mine here!
[chuckle]
I won't be able
to eat all this!
Don't act like
you've already won!
Yeah you'll always
be a loser!
Well, I'll go to the finish
line and give you guys the
signal to start, okay?
[Naruto]
This one's mine!
I'll be first for sure!
[determined growl]
All right,
any second now.
Enough talking,
let's go!
Rawr!
Yahoo!
Aroo!
Yes!
How fast?
Whoa! It's a
new record!
[panting]
Aw... My candy!
[heavy breathing]
[Kiba]
Heh heh heh heh!
[Inagi]
Damn it!
Kiba won again!
Well, at least
we beat that
idiot Naruto!
Aaaaggh!
Yap! Yap!
Aw, my candy's
all gone!
Again! Now!
C'mon, one more race! Let's go!
Yeah, right.
Beat my time,
and then I'll
race you again.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
[dreaming]
Heh heh! I'll be first no
matter how many times we race.
Huh?
[whine]
Oh... just a dream.
[sigh]
Kiba's Determination
Rrrrrr.
[yawn]
Sleepyheads don't
get any breakfast!
A war's about to
start, you know!
Yeah?
I'm on it.
I'll crush all of
them by myself!
A fool! That's what you are!
Don't take war
so lightly.
Your classmate Naruto's the
village hero but look at you!
What are you doing
with yourself?!
Fine! I'll go train then!
[door slams]
Why'd she have to
bring up Naruto?
It's way too early for that!
[Worker]
It's all thanks to
our hero, Naruto!
You got that right!
We're all alive because of him!
So let's put this village
back together for him!
[in unison]
Yeah!
What a miserable
morning.
[whine]
What, you don't
think so, Akamaru?
[whine]
Come on, don't tell me that
you're on "Mr. Hero's" side!
[barks]
Damn! It's the same
everywhere I go!
I mean, sure, he saved
the village, but.
[cheering]
Psh.
[whine]
When we were kids, he was
the worst in our class!
[Shino]
Are you talking about Naruto?
Ah!
Oh! Shino!
Naruto is the village
hero right now.
But back then he was
the class loser!
And who lost to the "loser"
during the Chunin Exam? You did.
Hey!
Too late!
[fart]
Huh?
Hauugghh!!
If he just hadn't farted in
my face then I would've won!
There are no
"ifs" in battle.
That's because you
can't turn back time.
Tch! Great, there
he goes again with
his annoying logic.
[bark]
Also.
Naruto has surpassed
us considerably now.
I'm gonna catch up to
him without a doubt!
You just watch me!
That's understandable.
However--
There's no way I'd let
Naruto leave me behind!
I refuse to be left
in the dust! I won't!
[bark!]
See ya!
[Kiba]
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
Augh!
[whine]
Damn it! It didn't work.
[barks]
Yeah yeah, I know, you
don't have to tell me.
I have to find some
way to power up.
[Kakashi]
Oh! Training, huh?
Huh?
Good! I'm proud of you.
Mmm.
Hm. What's wrong, Kiba?
You don't seem like
your usual self.
It's just, I've
gotta find a way to
become stronger.
Stronger than Naruto.
Than Naruto?
We started out together.
We were both just kids.
I can't let him get any
further ahead of me!
Kiba...
Wait, I know! Kakashi Sensei!
Please, you have to train me!
Huh?!
Kurenai Sensei's pregnant
and Guy Sensei's out of
the village for a while!
You're the only one
I can rely on now,
Kakashi Sensei!
[barks]
Hmmm.
Come on, please!
You know Naruto's
strength better than
anyone, isn't that right?
When you say it like that,
I guess I have no choice.
Excellent!
All right, I'll help you!
Ninja Art: Summoning!
Earth Style,
Fanged Pursuit Jutsu!
What?!
Aaahh!
[barking]
I really would love to stay and
help you out, Kiba, but I'm
simply far too busy right now.
[snarling]
I'll leave it to these ninja
hounds to spar with you!
That's not cool,
Kakashi Sensei!
[barks]
This isn't real training!
Ah!
HUAAAGH!
[Pakkun]
You want to be stronger than
Naruto? And this is the sorry
state you're starting from?
Hey, watch it!
I was just careless!
Bring it on! I'm gonna
make you eat your words!
[Akamaru]
[barks]
I'm only doing this because
Kakashi asked me to.
But we don't have any
time to waste either.
Don't mess around.
Oh, don't you worry.
Kakashi Sensei may have
run off, but I'll get him
back here in no time!
Howl all you want,
but only after you
steal this scroll off my back.
Sounds like fun.
Too bad it won't
last long!
[bark]
Ninja Art: Beast Mimicry!
Man Beast Clone!
All-Fours Jutsu!
You just rush in without even
coordinating your attack, huh?
Crane Wing Formation!
D'egh! Agh!
Since you want to be stronger,
we needed to see what you
had to start with.
And this is it, huh?
Damn you all!
I'll beat you mutts,
no matter what it takes!
Stop yapping!
And show us, already!
[barks]
Right! Then we'll do
this at full strength!
[growl]
Ninja Art: Beast Mimicry!
Man Beast Clone!
Man Beast Secret
Taijutsu Technique!
Fang Over Fang!
[Pakkun]
Scatter!
You can't escape!
Circular Formation!
Ninja Hound Art!
Dust Dance!
You can stop us from seeing you,
but you can't hide from our
sense of smell!
[barks]
There!
[woozy]
Aunn...
[Pakkun]
He falls for such
transparent tricks!
Damn it!
At this rate, this
fool's never going to be
able to surpass Naruto.
There's just no hope
for him whatsoever.
He loses his cool before
the fight even starts,
he doesn't bother trying
to assess his enemy's
strength at all,
and then he just charges
in without thinking,
only to self-destruct!
Eh?
Hey! Where are
you going?
Forget this! I quit! I can't
fight seriously against dogs!
You're running away?!
Tch! I asked Kakashi Sensei to
train me, not all you guys!
Instead--
You told us yourself that
you would end this quickly.
He got that part right.
It sure ended fast.
'Cause he lost!
[all laugh]
Rrrggh!
Quiet! This is just pointless!
[whine]
No! Getting hurt in training
like this just isn't worth it!
So you are running away.
Go on, if you don't
want our help!
Don't worry! I will!
Come on, Akamaru, let's
go train by ourselves.
[whine]
Rgh, I'm not
running away!
That training was just
useless, that's all!
[barks]
Dahh!
Hey, Akamaru!
What are you doing?!
[barks]
Akamaru, stop!
Where are you taking
me, Akamaru?!
Come on, stop!
Just stop, allright?!
Wauugh!
Agh!
Man, that hurts.
Hey, Isn't this...
[barks]
What? Naruto? He kept trying,
but he could never beat me.
[growl]
Wait, Akamaru!
What are you
doing now?!
I know this already!
My name was always the one
on the top of the list!
[gasp]
But... why's his name up there?!
Oh... Kiba!
Hinata, what are
you doing here?
Since our Academy days,
I come here to train
sometimes.
Naruto used to run
here all the time.
Naruto did?
Yes.
Way back then, he was sure,
that he could break your record
if he just tried hard enough.
[Naruto]
Haaaaaa!
Damn it! Too slow!
Why can't I do this?!
Haaaaa!
Uh, Naruto?
Haaaaaa!
Too slow! Damn it!
Okay, again!
Daah! So close!
Haaaa!
Damn!
Damn it!
[panting]
Auuughhh!
[Naruto]
Haaaaa!
[panting]
Huh??
I did it!
New record! Yeah!
[Hinata]
Every single day, Naruto ran
until he beat the record.
Isn't that just like him?
Akamaru, did you
know about that?
[bark]
Damn it! That idiot
is so stubborn!
Huh?
I mean, why doesn't that
loser ever just give up?
Damn it, that kid.
He's such a fool!
He's so stubborn!
That fool!
That stupid fool!
[chuckle]
[bark]
[Kiba]
Sorry to make you wait.
Huh?
[Pakkun]
I thought you quit
and ran away.
No, the only thing that I'm
going to quit is giving up.
Akamaru!
[howl]
Hm?
Hm. Starting off by
marking the field...
I'm not going to
charge into rocks and
self-destruct anymore.
This is a whole
new battle.
Well.
It seems you've had a change
of heart, so let's put it
to the test, shall we?
I'm supposed to take that
scroll that you have on
your back, right?
This time around, I'll make
you take back your words, too!
[growl]
Akamaru! Let's go!
[howl]
Human Mimicry Ninja Art:
Man Beast Clone!
Rrrr!
[snarling]
Fang Over Fang!
[Pakkun]
Incoming!
Hound Barricade Formation!
Scatter!
Akamaru! Dodge!
Akamaru!
[Pakkun]
Assemble, now!
[Kiba]
Are you okay,
Akamaru?!
[whine]
Rrgh!
At least you were able to
avert a head-on collision.
So tell me.
You want to
quit again?
I told you.
I've only quit giving up!
So you quit?
Yeah, I quit.
Ooooo-kay.
Uh- No! That's
not what I meant!
All I'm quitting
is giving up.
I'm not going to quit
training with you guys!
So you're not quitting?
No, of course not!
I...
I want to be... like him.
Like who?
Rrrgh!
Ah!
Heh heh.
Y'know what
I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna become a fool!
That works out well,
since you already
look like one.
No! That's--
You're a
fool, right?
No! Well, yes.
It's a different
kind of fool!
A fool is
still a fool.
Auggh! No, you
don't get it!
What are you trying
to tell us?!
Ahhh!
Agh! Just
forget it! Ahh!
Heh! Heh heh heh!
All right, that's it.
You're all gonna get it now.
What do you mean?!
Listen, don't go blaming us for
the fact that you're a fool!
Shut up!
Inuzuka Style! Man-Beast
Transformation Combo!
[snarling growl]
Go!
Let's go!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
Oh boy that sure is
one intense attack!
He's finally starting to think!
This attack will prevent
friendly fire.
[Pakkun]
But I don't think it'll
handle tight turns very well!
Dust Dance guys!
Ugh! Not that
again...
[growl]
It's all right, Akamaru!
I still know the terrain
because of Dynamic Marking!
Ninja Hound Art!
Hound Hair Clones!
[Kiba]
We're going in!
[Akamaru]
[bark]
Egh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
You can't tell where
the real one is now!
Damn it!
[chuckle]
[barks]
Hold on! He said
"you can't tell where", not
"you can't tell which"!
What that means is...
The real one's somewhere else!
[barks]
Calm down, Akamaru!
It's all right!
Just stay calm!
It's useless.
You should just quit.
Shut up! I said
I'm not going to
quit anymore!
[bark]
Ah!
Oh, yeah, Right.
I gotta stay calm, too. Sorry.
If we can just keep it together,
Akamaru and I can sniff out
even the faintest of scents.
We won't stop
till we find him!
[bark]
Right there!
Well, You got me Kiba.
good job.
And I take back what
I said about you.
Well, well.
He got you,
did he, Pakkun?
Yeah...
Heh heh heh heh!
Kiba!
You did well!
Eh?
Heh heh!
Thank you,
Kakashi Sensei!
[bark]
No need to
thank me!
I didn't do anything.
I mean, I wasn't even here!
We're never gonna quit! Never!
And if we don't, then one day,
Oh!
Hm?
What is it, Guruko?
Earlier, Kiba said,
I'm gonna
become a fool!
Rrrh...
I wonder if he meant
that he wanted to be
more like Naruto.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
No, he'd never
say that!
After all, even
Kiba has his pride.
[Yamato]
We'll enter the Land of
Lightning's territory
after replenishing
our supplies on this
isolated island.
[Aoba]
Our goal's in sight.
[Yamato]
We can't be complacent.
The enemy will seek
any chance to attack.
[Guy]
But since we're this close,
we can call for backup from the
Allied Shinobi Forces, right?
[Yamato]
Those Allied Forces
could be disguised enemies!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Kakashi, My Eternal Rival!