-Well, then, shall we get to it?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Here he comes.
-Die!
-He's fast!
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Did
Hiruko's tail just fall apart?
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Slick move, old lady.
But how are you going
to block this one?
-No!
-Here goes!
SASORI (VOICEOVER): With the
old lady controlling the action,
I'm not getting anywhere.
-Well, in that case--
-What?
Quick, hold your breath, Sakura!
-Poison?
-Sakura!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
Might as well get started.
NARUTO: Where do you
think you're going?
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
I really am lucky,
getting to take down two
different Jinchuriki.
-Naruto!
-Dammit.
We're not done yet.
Kakashi-sensei!
-Well, he is the copy ninja.
A single piece of detonating
clay isn't going to cut it,
I guess.
Hm.
I don't have a lot
of clay left, either.
All I was trying to do was
lure out the Jinchuriki.
Now I've gotta deal with this.
Hm.
-All right, that does it!
-Narut, wait!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): We've
strayed too far from Sakura.
Any further, and we'll be out
of transmission range, too.
I won't be able to
contact Guy's team.
I have to hurry!
[theme music]
-I'm not done yet.
Hi-yah!
No good.
There's no end in sight to this.
[heavy breathing]
-Rotation!
Dammit.
What are we supposed to do?
-How the hell do
you beat yourself?
I'm running out of ideas here.
-Leaf Hurricane!
No good.
I'm exhausted.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
There's no way
the girl will survive my poison.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I'm OK.
I managed not to inhale.
-Sakura!
-I don't think so.
-What?
What have you--
-Ropes with kunai on the end.
You should deflect them.
Dodging only gets
you tangled up.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Can't hold my breath.
-Sakura!
[laughter]
-So you're determined not to
led the child go, are you?
-It's useless, granny.
If one breathes even
a hint of this poison,
then you're a goner.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sakura--
-It's all over.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto-- Sorry, Naruto.
It means you may have to
wait for me a little bit.
But next time, I promise
I won't be dead weight.
I promised Naruto I
wouldn't be a burden.
I promised that things
would be different.
I swore to myself
that this time,
I would protect them both.
I can't let it end here.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
That poisonous gas
will disperse in a minute.
Hang in there, Sakura.
-I have more than one
store of poison, you know?
-What?
Sakura!
Hold on!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I'm
not going to-- die here!
-What?
-Sakura!
Sakura, hold on, child.
Just stay with me.
-Well, well.
Not bad, I've got to admit.
-Oh, this is bad.
She's not breathing.
[coughing]
-Are you all right, dear?
Talk to me.
-I'm OK.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): This
girl-- she used the blast wave
from a paper bomb to
dissipate the gas.
Endangering herself
to escape a trap.
How reckless.
-You listen to me.
I will get you, do you hear me?
You can blow my limbs
off, you can poison me
till I can't move anymore, but
I'm still going to get you!
No matter what you pull, no
matter what you throw at me,
I'm going to make sure you tell
me everything about Orochimaru!
Is that clear?
-All I want is the Jinchuriki.
The copy ninja's a
headache I don't need.
I have to find a way
to separate them.
Hm.
-Kakashi-sensei!
Still the best.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He
sure is trying his damndest
to split the two of us up.
So that's his game.
He wants to face
Naruto one on one.
-So much for strategy.
I guess my only option is taking
the two of them down together.
I don't have much
detonating clay left.
A shame, really.
If I knew I was going to
end up in this predicament,
I probably would have
brought along a little extra.
Heh.
Oh, well.
I still have my trump card.
[clattering]
-Really, now, haven't
you any manners?
A man should be attentive
when a lady speaks to him.
-So, you brought them.
-You remember these, don't you?
-Yeah.
I suppose I do.
-That's right.
These are the very first
puppets that you ever crafted.
The Father and the Mother.
-The Father and Mother?
You mean-- Sasori's?
-What could you possibly
hope to accomplish with them?
Those puppets were
made by my hand.
I know all their tricks.
This is just silly.
-You're quite certain
of that, are you?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Wire?
-Sakura.
Clear out of the way.
-Right.
Incredible.
-This is starting to get messy.
Guess I better
play my next hand.
-So my suspicions were true.
That's the Third's jutsu.
-Brings back memories, huh?
This jutsu is the
reason the Third
is held as the most powerful
ninja the Sand has ever known.
I'm going to grind
you into dust.
-What is that?
-The most terrifying
weapon in the history
of the Sand Village.
The Iron Sand.
[theme music]
CHIYO: Once upon a time,
in a village of yore,
there was an adorable young
boy with hair as red as flame.
NARUTO: Who set off with some
dumplings to slay an ogre!
SAKURA: No, he's carrying
an axe in this one.
NARUTO: Oh.
Right.
CHIYO: Uh, no, no.
The child lived happily
with his parents.
NARUTO: Did he rescue a turtle?
SAKURA: Not even close!
CHIYO: Oh, I quit.
I don't even know what story
I was telling, anymore.
NARUTO AND SAKURA:
But what happens next?
NARUTO: Next time,
Father and Mother.
[theme music]
-Hi, all.
Today we'll be discussing
various lineages
of master and student.
First came our founder,
the first Hokage.
Then his younger
brother, the Second.
The Will of Fire
was then passed on
to the Third Hokage,
who also oversaw
the training of the legendary
Sannin, Master Jiraiya, Lady
Tsunade, and Orochimaru.
Tsunade was mentor to Shizune,
Orochimaru to Anko Mitarashi,
and Jiraiya to the Fourth
Hokage, all of whom
had pupils of their own.
The Fourth, for example, was
teacher to me, Kaktashi Hatake.
And right down here are
my own adorable students,
Naruto, Sasuke, and Sakura.
Although Sakura's a
student of Tsunade's now,
Naruto picked quite a
bit up from Jiraiya,
and we haven't heard a word
from Sasuke since he left.
It's kind of lonely, actually.
What about you?
You're not looking
for a sensei, are you?
I'll cut you a good deal.