We're doing it my way
next time. Help me.
[gasp]
(Zetsu)
Mother. These guys
are such a bother.
Why not split them up already...
and take each of them on
separately?
[gasp]
[grunt]
Sasuke!
(Zetsu)
Now you can't seal Mother away.
First, I'll absorb
all of your chakra!
No...!
♪
(Obito)
It's hard to believe.
So you're saying both your and
Sasuke's powers are necessary in
order to seal away this Kaguya?
That's right!  But like I said
earlier, I can't sense Sasuke
now!
The ice, is moving.
[explosion]
I'm over there!
Huh?
[blast]
[grunt] She's merged
with Nature!
[grunt]
(Sakura)
Naruto!
She's finally showing herself.
You said that you suddenly
stopped sensing Sasuke?
Yeah.
I suspect that he was taken
to another dimension.
If I resonate my Kamui the next
time she connects and opens a
portal to another Time-Space,
I'm positive I can enter it.
If Sasuke is there, I can bring
him back to this dimension.
But, I'll need an enormous
amount of chakra,
...since it's not my Time-Space.
If my chakra runs out, I'm done
for.
Then I'll go with you...
I mean, the real me isn't
gonna down that quickly.
I'm strong.
Your Clone Chakra
won't be enough.
Would it still be inadequate
with my 100 Healings Chakra?
That would give me the minimum.
You two, come with me.
Okay.
I'm not going to waste time on
speeches.  I'm almost out of
time.
But I just ask that you let me
walk in front of you and...
...die for you.
(Thinking)
Then it's true. He...
really can't be saved.
So... he'll willingly
die for us...
We don't know if Sasuke
is in that Time-Space.
But we'll start by
entering her lair.
I promise to find Sasuke, and
get him to the real you.
Obito. I want to thank you for
helping me out. I really mean
it.
And for helping Sasuke.
No, there's no need to
thank me. Watch our foe.
[sigh]
So, no more masks, huh?
I am... Kakashi's friend, your
father's subordinate, an Uchiha
just like Sasuke, and.
A Hokage's the one who walks
ahead of everyone, and who
endures their own pain.
And the way he forges ahead...
draws others to him.
You want to reach out
when he stumbles.
I am your senior, who shared
the same dream as you.
Naruto and Sakura, is it?
Keep a hand on me so we can
teleport to a different
Time-Space at any moment.
(Sakura)
Roger.
She's caught onto us...
like I thought...
We have to assume that even if
we jump into her dimension with
Kamui, she'll perceive us.
(Thinking)
We're not worth her
attention, eh?
(Thinking)
That's right, come
down here!
You really want my
chakra, don't you?!
It's not worth launching a
stupid big jutsu if she's just
gonna absorb it.
I think what'll work best on her
is a feint and taijutsu!
Can't use a pervy joke move to
distract her anymore.
So I gotta go back to the basics
and corner her!
If she tries to escape through
that weird window again, I'll
enter it with her.
That's where I'll
search for Sasuke!
I can still sense Sasuke's
chakra clearly!
This world is my Time-Space!
You are powerless here.
All right! Are you
ready, Naruto?
Yeah!
I'm going to boost your chakra
to the boiling point! Vapor
Style: Unrivaled Strength!
[attack yell]
All right!
[gasp] Amazing.
I infused chakra
for you, Naruto!
Got it. Thanks, Kurama!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Listen up!  Right now, this
world, is my Time-Space!
[grunt]
Na...ru...to!
(Clones)
...Uzumaki Ultimate Barrage!
There she goes!
I'll send the real me!
He forced his way in?
Impossible!
They disappeared?
Seems a number of them managed
to enter, but... the other two
must've run out of strength and
vanished.
Looks like your clones didn't
have enough chakra.
So you're the original, huh?
And?  So what if I am?
Mother, he's come into
this Root Time-Space.
It's not good that he's here in
this place that connects
directly to the other five
Time-Spaces...
He might be able to get to where
Sasuke is, using the resonance
of the dual opposite powers.
Like with that weird jutsu
earlier, this shinobi Naruto has
always been unpredictable.
We ought to just kill
him right now!
No, we cannot do that.
I must absorb the chakra from
those two children.
You use a huge amount of chakra
whenever you change the
Time-Space of the world,
Mother...
You need to preserve the chakra
you've got for an emergency.
It's better if you don't
keep engaging him.
If you get sealed away,
everything will be for naught.
For sure, you'll lose out
on a lot of chakra,
but you don't
need his!
It's better than having our
long-cherished plans turn to
dust.
You're right...
[gasp]
(Zetsu)
We can kill him with this!
Murderous Bone Ash!
[grunt]
(Zetsu)
Die...!
[gasp]
Now all of his clones in the Ice
World should be gone as well!
Thanks to Naruto... we could
hide in my Time-Space.  But he's
gone, even as a clone.
You're the only one I can
rely on, Sakura.
I know!
I mean, there's a
reason why I put myself
at the front, you know!
At this point I'll do
even more than Naruto!
[grunt]
He's the fool that fell
in love with me...
I'm the one... who's caused
Naruto the most pain.
I'm always messing up.  Just one
failure after another.
I don't want to make any more
mistakes. I don't want to fail!
I'm not retreating anymore!
Just let me handle this, Sakura.
I'm one of the greatest ninja
ever!  My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
Remember it!
And my future dream is,
to be the greatest Hokage!
(Sakura)
Those silly dreams you once
had no longer seem so silly.
I won't...I won't let you die!
You're not going to
die...No matter what!
Looks like we succeeded in
getting in, Obito.
(thinking)
Now that you've teleported over
there, please don't get crushed
on the other side!
(Zetsu)
We killed the original!  So why
haven't they disappeared?!
I'll send the real me!
Damn it!
(Kakashi)
You okay, Naruto?!
Huh?
(Naruto)
Are you kidding?! How could
any of this be okay?!
Never mind.  Just be ready for
when Kaguya comes back.
(Naruto)
Huh?
The Kamui worked.
They're onto us!
I'll draw their attention.  In
the meantime, you two go and
hide!
I already marked this spot, so I
can hide in my Time-Space.
And you, too, Sakura.
Huh?
(Zetsu)
Looks like your clones didn't
have enough chakra.
So you're the original, huh?
And?  So what if I am?
(Zetsu)
So they were just
Clones back there...
You fooled us...
Yeah... Guess you found me out.
I'm the original, all right!
(Thinking)
I've gotta fight smart and keep
them busy so they don't go back
over there.
This Time-Space should be
connected to the others.
We'll open them one by one
and look for Sasuke.
Right!
[charging up yell]
(Sakura Thinking)
I'll give him all
the chakra I've got!
What an incredibly vast
Time-Space...
To be able to connect them in an
instant... What the hell is
Kaguya?!
[gasp]
(Sakura)
Isn't that where we were before?
I don't... sense Sasuke in
there!
[groan]
You all right?
Next... one...
Okay!
I thought that it
was around here...
[gasp]
What... is that?
He's not here either.
[groan]
[heavy breathing]
Uh, maybe you
should rest a bit.
What about chakra?
Oh, I still have
some reserves.
Just keep enough to get back.
Because in the event we can't
find Sasuke.
We'll find him!
The next one!
(Clones)
[shouting]
[gasp]
(Zetsu)
Be careful about making a
gateway, Mother... He'll get
closer to Sasuke.
Plus, I've figured
something out.
The original Naruto has
Truthseeker Orbs around him!
[gasp]
A sea of acid?
[grunt]
Are you okay?
I'm fine!  This is nothing.
(Obito)
You're a Medical
Ninja, aren't you?
I can wait until you
heal yourself.
That place wasn't the right one.
After we rest, we'll-
Don't worry about it!
Huh?
Our chakra has a limit, right?
[heavy breathing]
Why don't you tend to
your wound? Just a little.
I don't want to waste this
chance that Naruto has given us!
[sigh]
Hm. You want to help him if he
stumbles. That it?
Huh?
It's nothing.
Okay, next!
Yeah!
Found him!
Sasuke!
Sasuke!  Over here!  Hurry!
[grunt] Damn it!
[panting]
Sasuke! Come on!
Make it! Cha!
[grunt]
Sasuke!
[panting]
No way...
How'd you do that?
That's just one of my abilities.
I can shift myself
between spaces,
although only over a
finite distance.
But I made it here,
thanks to that.
♪
(Kakashi)
Am I powerless to do anything
but sit here and watch?
Sakura and Obito are
battling as well...
I really couldn't do much for
you as your teacher.
Nor for you, Obito and Rin,
as your friend...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Two of Them...Always."
(Kakashi)
I just put on airs that I was
an elite and yet kept making
mistakes.
♪