What a competition!
We should do it again
sometime!
See you guys!
[People Talking]
Choji. You forgot the
plan, didn't you?
[Gasp]
Yeah, you almost ended up
winning that eating contest.
[Nervous Giggle]
This isn't some kind
of joke, you know!
He's in there, right?
Yep!
As long as everyone
followed the plan.
You're really not one to
be pointing fingers.
You're clearly a long way from
home! Thank you for choosing our
inn. Please, make yourselves
comfortable.
We're all set.
Right.
May I come out now?
Yeah. We're safe.
Where are we?
An inn in the
castle town.
Is this one of those places for
travelers?
I know it's small compared to
the castle, but it's only for
one night, so please try to put
up with it.
Just one night? We're
leaving tomorrow?
It can be dangerous to travel at
night, so we'll wait until
daybreak to leave.
Oh, I see...
Before then, can I look
around a little bit?
What?! Well...
[People Talking]
I've just never been out in town
like this before!
But you lived in that
castle right there!
Yes, that's true. But I wasn't
even free to roam around inside
there, let alone go out into
the town.
Keep in mind that I was being
held as a hostage.
[Dog Barking]
So...?
Would it be all right if I go
sightseeing before we leave
town?
Like a tourist?
I don't think that's
a good idea.
I lived here for so long but I
know nothing about this place!
This may be the only chance I'll
get, so I'd like to see it.
Please, can I?
[Birds Chirping]
[Snoring] Hmm.
Wait, where am I?
Hmm? Oh no!
Lord Shu! It's almost time
to go to breakfast.
Uh, yeah! Hold on! I mean, right
there!
[Sigh]
Awake at last, huh? We'll head
out right after you're finished
with breakfast.
[Gasps]
Relax, there's nothing
to worry about.
You're not familiar with this
town, but the opposite's true,
too.
Even if you looked familiar to
the locals, they'd never think
that a lord would stay here.
Well, if my comrade in the
castle did his job right.
[Eating Loudly]
Wow, Lord Shu, you really have
quite the appetite this morning,
don't you?
Huh?
[Giggle] Well, maybe yesterday's
competition rubbed off on me.
What is this?
A dried sardine.
And that?
Bean curd.
[Sigh] I've never eaten anything
like this before.
Please, do try to finish eating
quickly, Lord Shu.
We don't have a lot of time. I'd
like to be on the road by around
midday.
First I want to go to Ama-Ama
An!
Sounds good! It feels like I'm
right back in the competition!
Don't get so excited.
Since when did this become
some kind of foodie tour?!
All right! Well, we'd
better get going!
Ugh, look at this place! What a
puny little nation! This
mission's turning out to be a
real letdown.
Listen, Sasori, how about I just
take care of this whole thing
quickly with my art? You're okay
with that, aren't you?
Fine.
[Sigh]
Boy I sure hope that we drummed
it into Naruto's head enough
that he can't make any mistakes
on this mission.
Aw, man. What a drag.
Things aren't going
according to plan?
Hey, don't look so happy
when you say that!
Oh, here it is! Found it!
Hmm.
[Eating Loudly]
Lady!
Give me one large platter of
bean cakes!
Hmm?
[Choji Yelling]
I don't understand this. What
are we even doing here, anyway?
Sorry. You want a bean
jam cake while we wait?
Here you go, Lord Shu! I
brought you a bean jam cake!
This next part is a piece of
advice that stresses the
importance of time spent
developing your literary skills.
When sleep is about to overtake
you while reading, use an augur
to pierce your thigh, and blood
shall flow from your leg.
Ow! Come on!
And thus, hmm.
Okay, sorry about that. Let me
give this passage a read.
"When sleep is about to overtake
you while reading, use an augur
to pierce your thigh, and blood
shall flow from your leg."
Ya know.
This is the next one!
Great! I wanted to eat their
ramen one more time!
Yes! Gido-Gido is quite
addictive!
I still don't understand why you
guys are tagging along with us.
C'mon, Shikamaru! It's good
camouflage to have locals like
them hang around with us!
See? I can come up
with plans like you!
You just like saying
the word "plan!"
It's time to eat!
I wonder if they have a light
menu...
[Sigh]
Hmm?
[Slurping]
It's delicious!
Yeah, I know!
Once we're finished here...
...let's go to Kemu-Kemu-en
for barbecue!
First, let's appreciate the
flavor profile of this ramen!
The broth is piquant and
unctuous, but its whimsical
silkiness keeps it light and
playful.
That's why it satiates your
appetite...
Uh...I gotta use
the restroom.
Chef! Refill please!
Hey, Lord Shu.
[Gasp]
If you're planning to try and
sneak back into the castle by
yourself, I'd forget it.
I don't know what you want to do
there, but it's a bad idea.
I know! I bet he wants to sneak
back to see the princess!
What? Do you mean
that Princess Chiyo?
[Gasps]
Hey, Pops, we want seconds!
[Both Grunting]
Look, Choji, forget this
camouflage plan of yours and
just get rid of those two, would
you?
Yeah.
I wonder what swordsmanship
training with a samurai is gonna
be like.
Now, Lord Shu...
When you're ready.
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Why you!
Hmm?
[Gasps]
I forgot my cover and dodged!
[Grunting]
Tatewaki...
[Gasps]
Just who are you, really?
What are you talking about,
Tatewaki? It's me, Shu!
You're not Lord Shu!
Where is he?!
I am Shu, ya know!
[Grunting] Let's all calm down,
okay!?
[Grunts]
You're just an impostor!
Even if you look like him, you
can't fool us! Now tell me the
truth! Where is Lord Shu?!
Oh, boy. All of a sudden
pretending to be him doesn't
seem like such a good idea.
Huh?
And if you refuse to tell us,
then we will show you no mercy!
Princess! Don't kill him! We
have to question him!
Yes I know, but perhaps an
injury will convince him to
talk.
Sorry, but I'm not sticking
around for that.
See ya!
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
Guardsmen! To arms! There's an
intruder!
[Guardsman Yelling]
Huh!
[Grunts] I can't believe they
cornered me already! Then
again...
That's just what I want!
Can't catch me!
See ya, suckers!
[Grunts]
Hmm?
Clone Jutsu! It's just a decoy!
The real impostor is still here
somewhere! Find him!
Yes sir!
Those Clones are heading for the
main gate.
Which means I should go this
way.
The intruder's been spotted by
the main gate!
Let's go!
Right!
[Giggling] This plan is perfect!
Huh!
[Screams]
What're you doing here?! You're
supposed to be at the main gate
with the intruder!
When I fell earlier I hurt my
bottom, so I thought I'd go...
Silence, intruder! Tell me where
Lord Shu is!
No one won!
Yeah I know...
Roast pork miso ramen!
You don't have to be shy,
Lord Shu. Just come on out,
okay?
Uh, Lord Shu?
You think he's all right in
there? He hasn't made a peep for
a really long time now.
Hmm, why that little brat!
[Heavy Breathing]
Look, Lord Shu is doing just
fine, I'm sure of it. Honestly,
he's safer than being kept here
as a hostage!
I don't believe you!
We're not trying to do
anything bad to him! I just took
his place to buy him and my
teammates some time to get away!
You helped Lord Shu escape?
Huh?
Tatewaki!
Hey, what are you doing here,
Old Man?
Your clones were just a little
too convincing.
They practically announced that
your real intention was to go in
the opposite direction.
Hmm?
But that is beside the point.
Even if Lord Shu is gone from
the castle, he couldn't have
gone too far in such a short
amount of time.
Sorry, wrong! By now, they've
probably reached his country
already!
That's a lie.
If he had managed to make it to
his homeland, then what reason
would you have to stay here
impersonating him?
[Nervous Grunt]
Lord Shu's nation is
his birthplace.
And that means they
know about this.
So Lord Shu is on his
way home right now.
Hmm?
Mhmm.
It's true then.
Well, I believe this is
good news.
Huh?
An alliance that relies on
hostages is fragile.
Besides, it'll leave scars on
Lord Shu's heart.
But Old Man, I thought this
nation hired you to work for
them!
A samurai's loyalty is to
peace, first and foremost.
A formally negotiated peace
between his nation and this one
would be ideal.
Then are you saying that
you're just gonna let him go?
Right now, you're the problem.
For the sake of peace, it must
never come to light that you
were hired to free him.
Yeah, I know. Don't worry, I'm
not saying anything.
Mind that you don't. Because if
he is caught, then I shall kill
you myself!
[Gasp]
Hear me, and remember it well!
Sure! You can count
on me, Old Man!
Lord Shu...
[Explosion]
Huh?
What is happening?
Sir, you must evacuate!
Get to safety!
[People Screaming]
Hey, Lord Shu!
Lord Shu, you okay?!
That was just a prologue.
Now for the main event!
Deidara, your part in
this ends here.
What's that?!
I'll handle the rest.
Hey, come on, that's not fair!
You said you'd let me take care
of this!
Our objective is not to destroy
this nation, but to take it
over.
All we must do is get rid of the
Feudal Lord and those close to
him.
By now, they're running around
in circles because your
explosives have filled them with
terror.
Oh! Yes, I'm sure that's true!
Drop some on the castle, too.
Then you can just sit back,
relax, and enjoy the show.
Well that sounds good to me! I
sure did get it easy on this
mission!
I wish you success.
Huh?
You had nothing to do with
those explosions?
No! No way.
Then you should take advantage
of all the confusion and get out
of this nation now.
What about you, Old Man?
I will accompany the princess
and ensure that she remains
safe.
All right then.
And as for Lord Shu...
Please take good care of him.
I'm gonna go find Naruto. Choji,
Ino, you get Lord Shu out of
here!
Got it.
I hope Naruto's okay.
Princess Chiyo...
Lord Shu!
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Gasps] What are all of those?!
Puppets? Who sent them?
[Sigh] Ahh!
Damn!
Rasengan!
No way. What's going on here.
[Heavy Breathing]
What do you think you're
doing, coming here?!
Princess Chiyo! You just
have to go and find her!
Save the princess, please!
Yeah, all right, I will. But
don't go off on your own, got
it?!
Hmm.
[Sigh] You two!
[Both] Sorry, Shikamaru.
The Feudal Lord's up in the
castle with all his advisors...
Okay. It's all
right now.
Old Man, what are you
planning on doing?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Will you take the princess from
the castle and get her to
safety?
Huh? But, but what about you?
I'm going back to the castle to
rescue the Feudal Lord.
Tatewaki...
I swear to you that I will do
everything I can to protect your
father.
You must go to Lord Shu and wait
there for me.
I will come for you,
I promise you that.
Listen, are you gonna be
okay all by yourself?
You're the one I'm worried
about. Are you really going to
be able to protect the princess?
Come on! I'm just concerned
about you, that's all!
You know, I've just realized
I don't actually know what
your name is.
Who are you?
Naruto! My name's Naruto
Uzumaki!
Naruto...
I won't forget.
Well then, Naruto. I'm
counting on you.
You got it!
Old Man...don't die.
Stay out of my way!
Hello? Anyone? Is anyone here?!
My lord! It is I, Tatewaki!
So it's you. The one who's
destroyed so many of my puppets.
That's right. Just
who are you?
Let's just say,
the Akatsuki.
Why'd you attack
this castle?
That's not something you need to
know. In any event, I'm done
here.
I cannot let you leave like
this, not after everything
you've done!
You'll have to answer for your
actions!
Even if you could defeat me,
your master is already gone.
That may be, but my duty to
him shall never end!
[Yelling]
Don't underestimate me!
You know, I just finished
up a job.
Then be quite and let me finish
this!
That's what you call
dodging, is it?
Those tubes are just for show,
what really matters are the
needles inside.
Ah, yes! I see that the poison
on the needles has started to
take effect.
Soon you won't be able to move
at all. Even now, it's already
too late. You're done for.
Well, then...it's time to make
my final stand!
[Screaming]
Princess Chiyo!
Lord Shu!
Naruto!
Huh? How come Princess Chiyo is
with you?
Old Man Tatewaki asked
me to take care of her.
Tatewaki?
Yeah! You should have seen him!
He's this super-strong samurai!
Your interference is unwelcome.
It seems that the
mission went well.
That nation fell to
a larger one?
That means there are going to be
more groups out there who will
want to use the Akatsuki.
What about Naruto
and the others?
I shadowed them until they'd
passed beyond the territorial
borders.
After we parted, I brought them
both to Lord Shu's nation. His
people welcomed the princess as
one of their own.
And now their moving around with
the other Feudal Lords so that
they can all stay safe from all
the fighting.
I see.
That's just what I
wanted to hear.
Huh?
Now, move in! Capture
him at once!
Wait! Hold on!
I wish I could've been there. I
wish that I could have seen the
both of them grow up.
You were there for them back
when they needed you. And they
wouldn't like to see you like
this, anyway.
Yes, you're right.
Thank you, now I have no
regrets.
Huh?
He took things into
his own hands, huh?
That's right. In the end, he
was who he wanted to be.
He was a true samurai,
through and through.
I'm gonna stay true to my
convictions, too. That's a
promise, Old Man. And I never go
back on my word!
Next time, to coincide with the
release of the Blu-Ray and DVD
of the movie "Road to Ninja,"
it's the story...
...of what happened the night
before that movie takes place!
It was originally presented as
an omake...
If you haven't read it or seen
the movie yet, I say "what are
you waiting for?!" It'll make
the experience ten times better!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Prologue of Road to Ninja."
Don't miss this next episode!