The war we're facing...
is an unknown.
Shikamaru, I'm really
going to need you in
charge, out there on the
front lines.
Right.
I'm counting on that
sharp intellect of yours.
Hmmm...
Shikamaru...? It's your
move...
Uh!
Your mind is somewhere
else. Are you scared?
No, I'm not scared. But
one bad decision, and my
comrades could die...
So what do I do? What can
I do?
I just have doubts.
Hmmm...
It appears that you're
stuck in Repetition,
too...
Hmm?
[gasping]
Repetition. When each
player has the same
pieces on the shogi board
as he does in his hand.
Which means that four
consecutive occurances
of this will result in
a draw.
Don't lose sight of
your goal. Go see Naruto.
There's a supply mission.
Hm?
I think it will be a nice
diversion for you.
You should go. I'll
recommend you for it.
Mm.
"The Closed Route"
This place is so quiet!
[sighing]
Yeah.
The large coral reef
that's around Mokuzu
Island acts as a natural
breakwater.
So this is an ideal
harbor, with very gentle
waves and little undertow.
Yeah! The sea looks like
a mirror!
Hmmm... but
having said that...
I don't think that we
should linger here too
long.
Hm?
Hard-a-port!
Aw! Really?!
Come on! But tasting
local delicacies is half
the fun of traveling!
The sun's gonna set any
second now!
Why are we setting sail
without even docking?
He may be the village
hero now, but he's still
the same Naruto.
How can you be so
carefree these days?
Did you say something?
Forget about it. It
doesn't matter...
Why were you guys waiting
for us at Mokuzu Island,
anyway?
'Cause we're bringing you
supplies.
Bringing supplies?
All right, I give up!
Where are they, then?!
Right here!
Ahhhh!
Uh... A little help...?
Ohhh! Boy, you're like a
walking storehouse!
[grunting]
You all right?
Don't just stand there
watching! Help me!
Huh?
[sighing]
I didn't find the answer
by seeing Naruto, Dad.
The fog has gotten thick.
Be careful.
Don't worry, I will.
Besides, we have a
compass.
That's a little
strange.
What? What's wrong?
Huh?
Do I really have the
strength to command
everyone and hold their
lives in my hands?
What should I do?
What's the matter,
Shikamaru?
Huh?
I just... it's nothing.
By the way, where's Guy
Sensei? I haven't seen
him onboard anywhere.
Well, he's been seasick
ever since we set out.
He's lying down in his
quarters right now.
[grunting]
Good morning, everyone!
He's sick?! Guy Sensei,
you seem just fine!
Ah! Shikamaru, you're
here, huh?
You feel all right, even
with the ship moving?
Yeah! I don't feel
seasick at all today.
What a great way to wake
up!
Ahhhhhh!
[coughing]
[grunting]
This fog is so dense!
Can't see a thing...
It's taken you this long
to notice that?! Seasickness
has made you dense!
[grunting]
Ahhhhh!
Watch out!
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Ahhhhhh!
[grunting]
Boy, that was close...
Thanks...
[gasping]
Huh?!
Hey, there are rocks all
around the ship!
There aren't supposed to
be any reef systems
around here...
Hold the rudder steady.
I can't avoid those
rocks!
You can leave this one to me!
The Leaf's Burning Youth!
[grunting]
I've just begun!
[growling]
He's goin'
crazy!
That's Guy Sensei for
you.
(cm landing effort)
Bushier Brow Sensei,
look behind you!
Huh?!
[screaming]
Rrrrgh. A rock
that big is nothing!
[yelling]
Damn it. There must be
something we can do.
Yamato!
Right!
Wood Style!
[struggling]
Are you okay, Captain
Yamato?!
Yeah.
Oh, no! Look!
Huh?
No way... A giant
whirlpool!
Not good...
If we get pulled into
that, this ship has no
chance!
It's no good. The
rudder's not working.
[struggling]
What are we gonna do now?
Naruto, use Massive
Rasengan!
Huh? What will Massive
Rasengan do?!
Never mind! Just throw
one in!
Uh... Yeah okay...
Captain Yamato! Just make
sure you pull me back!
Yeah! You got it!
[yelling]
Now!
[grunting]
[groaning]
They're a tough
bunch.
[exhaling]
You think we're
safe now?
[panting and gasping]
Huh? What?! No way!
Are you kidding?
Damn it! Then I'll just
pulverize them all!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Huh?
[screaming]
Naruto!
Right. On it!
[yelling]
What is this? What's
going on? This is too
weird to be a natural
phenomenon...
Our mission is to get
Naruto to the Land of
Lightning safely.
If this is a ploy to
abduct him, we have to
identify the enemy before
it's too late.
[panting]
[gasping]
Again?!
[grunting and yelling]
[yelling]
[grunting]
That's the third time. Is
the enemy trying to make
us use up our chakra?
But even now, I sense no
enemy presence. Wait...
could this be a genjutsu?
No, it's the real thing,
all right. It could be
the Transportation
Technique.
No...
A shinobi capable of a
massive spatial barrier
like this wouldn't need
to bother forcing us to
use up our chakra.
My chakra's all gone.
Huh?
What?! Again?!
That's number four...
This is just like the
Repetition move...
Guy Sensei!
It's hopeless! We're all
out of steam!
I thought so...
[grunting]
This is a drag.
But I'm the only one
left.
With my jutsu,
controlling a ship this
size sure won't be easy,
but then again...
[grunting]
I have no choice!
Shikamaru... I don't
expect anything like that
from you.
But why?!
[exhaling]
You just leave the heavy
lifting to me!
And while I'm doing that,
your job is to use that
big brain of yours to
find a way to get us out
of this mess!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Damn it, why was I so
impatient? Naruto is
absolutely right.
Okay, go through it in
order. What happened
after we left the port?
As soon as we set sail,
we were surrounded by
thick fog.
We were on the ocean, but
Guy Sensei didn't get
seasick.
And the compass didn't
work anymore.
Then, we sailed into an
uncharted reef system...
and that whirlpool
appeared.
Whirlpools are caused by
complex terrain on the
ocean floor and shifts
in the sea level.
Huh?!
Damn it! Today is a
spring tide! And there's
that narrow entrance to
the bay...
A large amount of water
flowing in with the
spring tide will easily
form a whirlpool.
Guy Sensei didn't get
seasick because-
This place is so quiet!
The calm waves of that
huge bay kept the ship
steady. There's no doubt
about it.
Rock straight ahead! Grab
onto something!
What's that...?
Hmmm.
Uh--
Wait, when did that mark
appear there?
So the ship rubbed up
against that over and
over...
And that means...
That this entire time,
we've only been going
around in circles inside
the bay!
Rasengan!
I'm all out of chakra
now, too.
Another whirlpool!
What?! Seriously?!
That's enough, Naruto.
I just got an idea.
That's great. So what is
it? What do we have to
do?
We're simply going to
sail straight into that
whirlpool and get
swallowed up by it.
We're what?!
Wait, just what are
you up to, Shikamaru?
Tenten, I'm gonna need
your power for a bit.
Huh?
About time! That's what
happens when you get
caught in the Devil's
Water Trap of Mokuzu Island!
At last, those shinobi
are all dead!
Their ship was swallowed
by the whirlpool and sent
to the sea floor!
All right! Operation
complete!
[cheering]
This is a big one! Let's
go get that shinobi
treasure!
[cheering]
Huh?!
What gives? There's
no debris anywhere!
Oh! Maybe the treasure
was so heavy that
everything just sank!
[laughing]
So every one of you on
Mokuzu Island is a thief,
is that right?
[gasping]
What is-?! Who're you?!
If you want our treasure
so badly, then you'll
have to come and take it
from us.
[growling]
Hmm.
Don't be afraid! They're
completely exhausted from
handling all our traps!
Don't underestimate us!
Tenten!
Right!
[gasping]
[screaming]
That was a pretty clever
trap for amateurs.
[gagging]
Damn it! I'm seasick
again!
Shikamaru!
It's a good thing we can
rely on that sharp
intellect of yours!
Uh?
Hm!
Y'know, I'm glad I met
you.
Huh? What?
It's nothing. Just forget
I said anything.
Hm?!
Hey! Come on, tell me
what you just said!
Tell me, already,
will ya?
Knock it off! Man, you
can be such a pest
sometimes!
What?! I'm a pest?! What
do you mean by that?!
[sighing]
Don't just sigh at me!
Tell me!
[sighing]
[retching]
So Barbe-Q reopened?
I made us a reservation!
Ooh! Beef tongue with
salt!
The new menu has a
special Ladies Combo!
It's such a good deal!
And I just can't resist
a good deal!
Frankly, my favorite here
is the offal!
Did you decide on drinks?
Excuse me! We're ready
to order!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Girls Get
Together.
I'm going to eat
my fill tonight!