♪
"When the man in the strange
cloak raised up his pointed
blade and drove it into his"
"...side, impaling
himself upon it..."
"Naruto felt an excruciating
pain in the same area of
his own body."
[painful grunts]
Don't think you'll be able to
escape my curse! After all, the
whole shinobi world is cursed!
Just give up....
[grunt]
[evil chuckle]
What the-- it was a clone?
Na... ru... to... !
Uzumaki Barrage!
That's my Naruto
Heh, a cheap imitation
of my Lions Barrage.
What did you say!?
Stop arguing, guys!
Oh, yeah that's right.
Where's Kakashi Sensei?
I don't know. We were merely
hired to help out as a part
of the experiment.
Experiment?
That's right. The one to prove
that there isn't any hope to
be found anywhere.
Not in a cursed shinobi world.
Although... It's a serious pain.
So I figured that I'd just give
you the answer really quickly,
but then...
Huh?
Listen, it seems like
this guy is more than
you can handle, Naruto.
Why, you jerk!
Well, long time no see!
Trained by the Great Toad Spirit
of Mount Myoboku, also known as
the Toad Sage...
...we are the trio
from the Hidden Rain!
And the name that the three of
us go by is Team Jiraiya!
Remember that, and let our
presence be known far and wide!
T- Team...
...Jiraiya?
Wait, Jiraiya?
You mean one of
the Legendary Sannin?
The real cool one? The
one who's super suave?
With that irresistible glance
that makes any woman who sees it
fall madly in love with him in a
mere second?
The one admired by every guy in
the Leaf, who ranks at the top
of the list of masters people
most want to train with!?
(Tsunade)
What the hell is this?!
That Jiraiya!  He's more full of
himself than anyone I know!
Team Jiraiya...
Well, technically our name's the
"Akatsuki," but I don't really
think that it's too catchy or
cool at all...
What I'm saying is just remember
the three of us as Team Jiraiya!
So are you Jiraiya's
students or something?
So only guys from the Hidden
Leaf can train under Jiraiya
Sensei, then?!
Is that what you're saying?
What? No! I didn't
mean it that way!
That attitude rubs me the wrong
way, implying we're not real
shinobi...
...since we're not from the
Leaf, the Five Great Nations, or
the Five Hidden Villages!
Like I said,
I didn't say that!
The Hidden Rain's not a big
fancy village...
...but guys like us are
just as good as you!
Remember that and let our
presence be known!
Heh!
[gasp]
Huh!?
All of this time... the Hidden
Leaf, the Stone, the Sand, the
Cloud...
All of them have waged war
whenever they felt like it...
And we got stuck in the middle
with nowhere to go!
And all the while, none of you
could care less about our
suffering!
Wind Style! Gale Palm!
Oh man!
But we'll rise up and
set aside bitterness!
We won't let it hold us back.
We'll continue to move forward.
Liberty is the goal of Team
Jiraiya. We'll turn the tables!
And this goal of yours is the
reason why you captured Asuma
and all the others?!
That was a passionate speech you
made just now, and I understand
where you're coming from.
But still... I don't understand
why you'd capture Asuma and my
other comrades from the Hidden
Leaf!
The Leaf, The Leaf, The
Leaf! Does the world
revolve around the Leaf?!
Gimme a break already!
Seriously, I'm the one
that needs a break!
[loud crash]
[gasp] Sasuke!
Huh?
[evil chuckle]
Why you!  You would really dare
to kick an apostle of god?!
Curse you, heretic!
[gasp]
What the hell
is going on here?
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
That was a close one!
You okay, Sakura?
Oh, Sasuke! Thank
you so much!
Argh!
If this situation's anything to
go by, we can assume that it's
the same for the other teams, as
well.
Yeah, you're
right. What now?
The sooner that we're able to
join up with them, the better.
Any objections to that?
No, guess not.
What is going on?
This is weird. It's like
they're blocking us from
where we want to go!
Maybe these guys are trying to
lead us astray or something.
[gasp]
They're not
coming after us...
Why did you have to barge in and
interfere like that, Kakuzu?
I mean, I could've offered those
kids up as a sacrifice to Lord
Jashin while I was at it, you
know!
We're not under contract
for that, and you were
about to mess things up.
Our job's just to capture
team-captain-level guys.
We won't earn any money
for just killing brats.
Well, yeah, but the world
doesn't just revolve
around money y'know!
What's the point of living if
you can't even enjoy your life?!
That's a luxury we can't afford.
We have to prioritize
every action we take.
Really?  Come on, that's a
little harsh, wouldn't you say?
Here.
What!?
You take care of that one. I'll
go gather up the rest of the
captains that we've hidden.
Seriously? Hey, wait! Ugh.
[barking]
Huh. Yeah, Akamaru... This area
reeks with the scent of
Shikamaru and the others.
And there's the scent of...
three other people...
It seems like there was a fight
here only a few moments ago.
They moved around while
they were fighting. I
know that, because
they left behind telltale signs
of their movements within the
battle.
Shikamaru and his team are
okay... Or at least I don't
smell any blood.
[barking]
Let's hurry after them.
A village...?
But, doesn't it seem like
something's not right...?
(Ino)
A settlement this large... but
there's no sign of any people
here...
Yeah, it's weird... But my
suspicion is that those guys
wanted to lure us here.
So what now?
Should we wait
for Team Kurenai?
Yeah... Those guys we faced
before probably laid a trap and
are just biding their time.
The more of us there are to
fight them, the better.
We don't really have any clue
about the enemy's strength yet.
It's better if we join up
with the others first.
So how come you're the
one giving the orders?
Look, our captain is
missing right now.
Isn't it standard for the
next best-qualified person
to make the decisions?
I agree.
If it's between Sasuke, who
graduated at the top of his
class...
...and you, who came in last and
only graduated because of pity,
well...
Yeah, if your father
weren't the Hokage...
What?! Hey, you wanna fight?
Heh, Well, I guess that
would be kinda interesting.
At least then I'd be able
to prove who's better.
I'd like nothing more!
Come on, you guys, stop it!
Never say that again!
Not in front of me!
Haven't you sensed it?
[leaves rustling]
[gasps]
Oh, hey there guys!
Glad you're okay!
I don't see Guy Sensei.
Yes. It was all extremely
sudden, but Guy Sensei
has gone missing.
And Kakashi Sensei has
disappeared as well.
There were signs that showed
he'd been dragged underground
by something...
Wait, Some black rope-like
creature wrapped around Guy
Sensei and dragged him away!
Yeah! That thing
attacked us too!
You encountered the enemy?
Yeah... they claim
to have been hired.
Hey, shouldn't we hurry
up and rescue them before-
Just slow down...
Yeah, but, Sasuke...!
spotted chakra underground...
...shortly before Guy
Sensei went missing.
[gasps]
We believe we've pretty
much pinpointed the
source of the chakra.
That's great!
The remaining teams
should be nearby, too.
We need to regroup with every
team before anything else.
And set up a base camp.
Who knows what's happening to
Kakashi Sensei and the others
while we're wasting time like
this...
You're right: first, we need to
regroup with the other teams.
I want to confirm some
things with them.
Chiefly what the status is for
Asuma and Kurenai.
(Neji)
Guy Sensei lost consciousness
and then went missing.
(Sasuke)
The exact same thing happened
with Kakashi Sensei.
Come to think of it... Kakashi
Sensei was watching a Shinobi
Ageha butterfly before it
happened.
It's possible the powdery scales
of the Shinobi Ageha and the
chakra flowing underground
interacted with each other.
Maybe there's a jutsu that
doesn't work on us but has an
effect on the jonin.
Could be, but the scales
of the Shinobi Ageha
aren't toxic or poisonous.
I don't know how the jutsu might
work, but like I said...
there's something that I want to
verify with the
others... about this.
What!? But, that's--
Lord Fourth's kunai?
I have no clue what's
going on here!
Isn't that exactly the
same kunai that you found
earlier, Sakura?
It's not.  This is the one Guy
Sensei dropped when he was
captured.
Two separate jonin just happened
to drop the kunai that were
entrusted to them by Lord
Fourth...
at's something that I find very
hard to believe.
So if we assume the enemy
dropped them there
intentionally...
Must be someone with
considerable knowledge
of many jutsu...
Or somebody who knows the secret
behind Lord Fourth's kunai.
Then I have a feeling that we'd
better hurry up and join with
the other teams quickly.
The tracking team of Kiba, Shino
and Hinata should be able to
pinpoint their locations pretty
easily.
Yes, I agree.
Then can we rescue the captains?
No. Once we know their
situation, we'll send word
back to the village.
Right. We don't have
authorization for a rescue.
Sticking to the rules again?!
We don't have time to wait for
reinforcements to get here from
the Leaf!
I don't care what anyone says.
I'm gonna go rescue them!
I just caught a whiff of some
delicious-smelling food.
Hey, how about we head down into
that village and do a little
search and reconnaissance, huh?
Seriously?  Are you kidding me?
That's just looking for trouble!
Stop thinking with your
stomach!
Yeah, you're right.
Shh! Take a look...
Let's follow them. Come on!
Komichi, let's hurry
up and get Kenta.
There's gonna be a fight here
soon, isn't there?  If there's a
fire, then Kenta's gonna die!
Why'd you leave Kenta behind
in the first place?
Well, because--
Thank goodness!
Nothing's burned down!
Oh, Kenta, We're sorry!
I'll never leave you
again, I promise!
They're just like
we used to be...
Caught up in other nations'
wars... Running... frightened...
We wanted to make sure that none
of the villagers got hurt
because of our strategy...
We told them all to evacuate...
Damn it... Now we're no
different than the Leaf or Sand
all those years ago!
C'mon, Komichi!  Hurry up!  We
have to go before the fighting
starts!
Okay, I'm coming,
big brother!
[gasps]
Hey, do you kids live
in this village?
Please, guys help us... Do
you know where everyone else
in the village has gone?
[stammering]
It's okay!  You don't have to be
scared of us!  We're not scary
people.  I promise you!
[sighs]
[Gasp] Run, Nagato! Run
and don't look back!
...hurry! [dying gasp]
Damn it!
All right...  How 'bout this...?
Has either of you kids seen
another group of two guys
and a girl?
You know, a group
that's just like us?
[frightened cries]
[sigh]
Yahiko...!
Nagato...!
[attack cry]
[screaming]
Nagato...!
Komichi, stay close!
[frightened cries]
The kids are gonna--
Not good...!
Oh no... did...
did I do this?!
[screaming]
[grunts]
What was that?
It's coming from
inside the village.
An enemy.
Could there be a team
fighting over there?
Something serious is going on...
What's happening inside that
village?!
That's the direction
of the village that's
marked on the map.
That's where Shikamaru's
and the others' scents are!
Then we should head over
there immediately. The reason
is because that cloud
of dust is a sure sign that
something big is happening over
there.
What're you doing?
Hurry up!
Wait!  You should listen until
someone's done speaking!
The reason is because...
Hey! Wait!
[gasp]
[grunt]
Not good...
Come on! We've gotta
save those kids!
Hold it!
Huh?
We can't. Don't go down there.
(Ino)
Why?
(Choji)
Shikamaru...
♪
(Tsunade)
"The collapse opened up a hole
in the earth, and it swallowed
the two siblings."
"Yahiko, Konan and Nagato, who'd
come to call themselves Team
Jiraiya, immediately went after
them."
"But Shikamaru... didn't make a
single move..."
We have to do what we
came here to do.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Order of Priority"
(Shikamaru)
We can't be
indecisive right now.