(GARRA) Mommy...
Am I...?
[whimpering]
[heavy breathing]
[grunts]
(KANKURO) Hey, that's so cool!
Hm?
Whoa...!
Hm...?
What about... food shapes? Can
you do that?
[sigh]
Uh... [chuckle]
Wha-?
Whoa...!
Whoa, grilled squid!
[chuckle] Ohhh...
Ramen!
[chuckle]
(KANKURO) Uhhh... Cherries!
Lobster!
Uhhh... Sea urchin rice bowl!
(TEMARI) [chuckle]
Oh, man! You are totally
amazing!
Ummm...
How 'bout...
...a really big poop?
[sigh/groan]
(KANKURO) Can you do that?
(RASA) Temari...
[gasp]
Kankuro...
[grunt]
(KANKURO) Yes, sir!
[sigh] Gaara...
(RASA) Temari!
Hm?! Yes!
[sigh]
[groan]
That kid's so creepy...
Just what is he?
Yeah. He's scary...
So incredibly freaky...
He's that cursed kid.
(GAARA) Hey, hey Yashamaru...
Why is it...
...that we have to get hungry?
Well, just maybe...
...it's so we get the chance to
eat great food!
I see...
I think you're right! [chuckle]
The food that you make me always
tastes so god, Yashamaru!
[slurping]
[chewing]
[coughing]
[grunting]
Hm? [chuckle]
Hey, Yashamaru...
Why is it that the sky is blue?
(YASHAMARU) Well... it could be
that way... so we can gaze up at
the serene blue sky... to allow
us to feel calm and refreshed.
I see...
Yeah, you're right!
Because...
...when I look up at the sky,
the pain inside my heart feels a
little bit better.
[chuckle]
Hey, Yashamaru...
I don't seem to get sleepy even
when it's nighttime. Why is
that?
(YASHAMARU) Now, that's a
problem.
Normally when you close your
eyes, you should get tired.
(GAARA) Oh, really?
Hey...
Why...?
Hm?
Why don't I have a mother?
Oh, uh...
Instead of a mother, you get to
have me, Lord Gaara.
And that is because I'm going to
remain by your side...
...always.
[chuckle]
[gasp and chuckle]
[grunt]
[heavy breathing] Huh?
Hm?
[grunt]
(GAARA) Oh...! Is it lunchtime?
Mhm!
[chuckle]
(IRUKA) Alright... In order to
survive in the shinobi world,
taijutsu is absolutely
essential.
Now, let's see... when talking
about survival, in a way it's
like fish swimming their way
upstream.
It's not an exaggeration to call
it a natural instinct...
but...
[sigh] What a drag.
(IRUKA) So, as we approach the
idea on survival, what we always
have to keep in mind is...
[snoring]
[groggy moans] Huh?
What the-?! What's going on?!
Huh? Uh! [nervous chuckle]
[pained groan]
Hey!
No sleeping in class!
(SHIKAMARU) [snicker]
Hm?
(CHOJI) Ah ha! It was Shikamaru!
[growl] Shi-ka-ma-ru!
[chuckle]
[gasp]
(CHOJI) [grunt]
Whoa!
(CHOJI) [grunts]
[dodging and pained grunt]
Come on, you guys! Quiet down,
would ya?
I'm trying to sleep here!
(IRUKA) Alright, Naruto, that's
enough! We're in class! You're
supposed to be learning! You
hear me?!
Huh...? [chuckle]
It's not the time to sleep!
Naruto! Shikamaru! Choji! You
three, go stand in the hallway!
(NARUTO, SHIKAMARU, CHOJI)
What?!
(IRUKA) No "what's!"
(NARUTO, SHIKAMARU, CHOJI) Yes,
sir...
Aw, man... Iruka Sensei is
always getting mad at me.
(CHOJI) Um, hey... I've got
snacks. You guys want some?
Whoa! Oh... Shhh!
[chuckle]
[chuckle] Hm!
Totally! I'll have some!
Okay you three, have you given
some thought to the way you've
behaved?
[snoring]
(IRUKA) Good grief, you guys!
Really?!
[grunt]
[deep breath] Hmph!
[snoring]
[inhale and yell]
[startled yells]
[laughing]
(NARUTO) Iruka Sensei! You
really scared us, ya know!
(SHIKAMARU) I'm gonna get you
for that...
(CHOJI) Huh?! W-What happened?
Ha! I knew I'd find you here!
Hey, Shikamaru... Can you lend
me some money?
Wait, let me guess why... For
some snacks again?
(CHOJI) Yeah!
I mean, what else is there to
buy besides snacks? And even if
there was, why would you want
it?!
(SHIKAMARU) Aw man, what a
drag...
Hm?
(SHIKAMARU) You know...
...you're one in a million...
[chuckle]
[giggles and chattering]
(BULLY A) What's with your eyes?
(BULLY B) They're so creepy!
(BULLY C) Yeah! Don't even look
at us, ya weirdo!
(NARUTO) C'mon, cut it out!
Leave her alone. What'd she do
to you anyway?!
(BULLY A) What, you wanna be a
bug hero or something?
You shouldn't pick on people
weaker than you, ya know!
What? Just shut up, kid!
[gasp]
(BULLY A) [chuckle] Whatever.
this is boring. Let's go, guys!
[gasp]
(BULLY B) Yeah, this is boring.
(BULLY C) Let's go. [laughing]
Man, what a drag. I can't
believe him, doing stuff like
that.
Instead of butting into
other people's business, he
should be polishing his skills.
Stupid Naruto.
[chewing]
Don't call him that.
(SHIKAMARU) Huh? What?
Naruto isn't stupid.
I mean...
...even you said that in shogi
all the pieces are necessary,
and you said that... about me...
Huh?!
What are you talking about,
Choji?
You're just mad at me 'cause I
didn't loan you any money
before, that's all.
You're wrong.
Naruto is...
Naruto's like you, Shikamaru!
Don't call him stupid! Now take
it back!
(SHIKAMARU) Man...
What a drag! Listen, at least
try and make sense when you
talk.
[grunt] Don't...
Don't you order me around!
[growl]
(NARUTO) Hm? Hey. Hey! What are
you guys doing?!
[grunting]
(NARUTO) Come on, stop it! You
guys are friends, aren't you?
Why are you fighting?! Hey!
Stop!
'Cause- [straining]
...this fatso started
complaining!
[grunts and struggles]
Shikamaru, open your eyes!
[struggling] And I'm not a
fatso!
[grunts]
[straining] I'm pleasantly
plump!
(NARUTO) Alright...
...let me buy into this fight!
(CHOJI AND SHIKAMARU) Huh...?!
[chuckle]
What's that mean?
Oh! Then I'm gonna buy snacks
with all the money you'll pay
me!
What?
What's that about?
[laughing]
[chattering]
Yeah, that's exactly what I
did! And then I went to the
usual spot. You guys know the
place, right?
Huh... so that's what happened.
Mmm... Naruto, you want some
chips?
(NARUTO) Oh! Yeah, thanks!
[chuckle]
(NARUTO) [chewing]
Huh?
Hey! Look!
Hmmm?
(SHIKAMARU) What, seriously?
What a drag!
(NARUTO) Man, forget that!
(CHOJI) Nope, no way.
(NARUTO AND CHOJI) No girls for
me! [gasps] Uh-oh!
Ahhh!
(NARUTO) Look out, she's coming!
(NARUTO, SHIKAMARU, AND CHOJI)
Ahhh!
[heavy breathing]
(SHIKAMARU) Aw, man!
That Ino... She's
terrifying when she's mad!
What a drag. [heavy breathing]
I swear she's gonna end up an
old maid. [heavy breathing]
(NARUTO) [gasp] Hey! Look! Over
there!
(SHIKAMARU) Huh?
Seems I've spied with my little
eye a Pervy Iruka Sensei!
What do you say, Naruto?
You wanna do "that?"
You serious?
You bet!
[chuckle] Mhm!
Oh c'mon, now...
[chuckle] What? I don't know
what to say, ladies...! Hm?
Oh...
So it's you, Naruto. What're you
guys doing out so late?
Young kids should be in bed by
now.
(NARUTO) Sexy Jutsu!
[nervous laugh]
Ahhh!
(GIRLS) Ahh!
See ya later, Naruto. Your Sexy
Jutsu was awesome!
Bye-bye, Naruto!
Hey, Shikamaru. It's curry night
at my house tonight.
(SHIKAMARU) That sounds great!
I'm getting tired of my mom's
cooking... [laughing]
K, see ya!
(SHIKAMARU) Yeah!
(CHOJI) See ya tomorrow!
(JIRAIYA) Hey, you know what?
Why don't the three of us talk
about our dreams tonight?
(OROCHIMARU) Dreams?
(JIRAIYA) Yeah! I mean, if you
even have any dreams at all,
that is...
(RIN) Kakashi's amazing, isn't
he?!
(OBITO) You think? I'll bet you
that secretly, he's probably a
closet pervert.
(KAKASHI) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Jiraiya and
Kakashi."