♪
Hello..!?
Hey, come on!
Now listen, I don't think this
is the time to be fighting, do
you?
Here. Let's call a truce
till we get out of here.
What do you say?
Yeah, okay fine. But I
don't need charity
from a Great Nation!
"Charity?" What
do you mean?
Unsealing Jutsu.
If you had water, you
could've just said so.
The Great Nations...
Don't understand pain.
(Tenten)
Pain? What are you
talking about?
Exactly.
You don't understand pain.
Or the pain you inflict
upon smaller nations.
Sorry, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
But you do understand that
we're gonna need to help
each other...
That is, of course,
if we wanna make it out
of here in one piece!
Help each other...?
I wonder what this
place is...
(Ajisai)
An ancient ruin of the
Land of Wind...
...probably some
underground structure.
(Tenten)
You think so, too?
I think that it's gonna
be too difficult to make
it up that direction...
You're right.
Shall we try
that way?
We don't really
have a choice.
(Tenten)
So, these teammates
of yours...
(Ajisai)
What about them?
My teammates don't have a lot of
search and rescue experience,
so I don't think that
I can depend on them
to find me down here.
I plan to get myself
out of here as well.
(Rock Lee)
Huh...
Did you find something?
Not yet. I thought this
was an entrance, but
it is just a dead end.
I heard that it rains all
year long in the Hidden
Rain Village. Is that true?
Yes, that is true.
Wow. I don't think I
could even imagine that...
Yes, I doubt
you could.
You've had an attitude
towards me this whole time.
But, you know...
You guys are also at least
partly to blame for us not
knowing much about the Hidden
Rain.
Seriously?
(Tenten)
Yeah...
...I've heard that secrecy is a
doctrine of the Hidden Rain.
So it's no wonder that we don't
know anything about you!
We only have contact with you
guys through things like the
Chunin Exams.
But because this is a test,
instead of talking to each
other, we fight.
(Ajisai)
That's true...
Plus, you guys can come to
Hidden Leaf or Hidden Sand,
but if we tried to go to the
Hidden Rain, we wouldn't be
allowed to enter.
A small nation like the
Hidden Rain has to be
extremely careful.
Other small nations don't do
that.  The Hidden Rain's a
special case.
You're right, The Hidden
Rain Village is special.
(Konan)
Small nations become embroiled
in the wars of the Great
Nations,
ending up as those nations'
battlefields, left to suffer the
consequences.
But Lord Pain wants to bring an
end to such a world.
He wants the ignorant Great
Nations to feel and understand
our pain...
...and to bring
about true peace.
[crowd cheering]
(Konan)
The Hidden Rain village will
be... reborn!
[crowd cheering]
The Hidden Rain
will soon be reborn.
So does that mean that you're
gonna be more friendly, then?
(Ajisai)
That's--
Wait... You hear
that noise? What
is it?
Is it your
teammates?
I doubt it.
Guess not.
[gasp]
What is that!?
An ant...
How did an ant
get that big!?
[snarling]
[grunt]...
What in the--!?
Hiya!
Whoa. They call this the Demon
Desert for good reason!  It's
unreal what lives here!
(Ajisai)
I wonder if there are more...
I hope not.  But they're ants,
so this place is probably
swarming with them.
Let's catch one.
What!? Why would you want to
catch one of those things?!
To tame it as a
Summoning Animal.
A summoning...?!
Besides, their nest could be
connected to other openings
that lead out of here.
[groan]
Apparently you know
how to Summon?
Yes.
Is there a trick to it?
Sorry, but I really
wouldn't know.
[sigh] I guess it's
just sheer talent...
Huh...?
Maybe through here.
I sense some chakra,
but it's faint...
It seems like she's moving,
but I can't tell for sure.
(Komugi)
Ha!  Found you!
This must be the
hundredth time we've met!
But this time, you're gonna
hand your scroll over to us!
[grunts]
One of them's missing.
(Inaho)
Did they split up
or something?
(Gennai)
That means it's three against
two, and we have the advantage!
Are we supposed to
be scared of you?
What do you think you'll be able
to do with those old things?!
[grunt]
You gonna run away again!?
You're not getting
away this time!
[gasps]
Why are you
guys here!?
Let me make this clear: Those
guys are our prey, you got it?
You're wrong.  We aren't going
to let you attack these two.
That is right.  We are in the
midst of helping each other out.
Helping!? The
Hidden Rain!?
You mean to tell us that you're
Hidden Leaf just like us, and
yet you're still gonna get in
our way?
We're all competitors.
If it comes down to it, we can
go after your scroll, as well.
Are you serious!?
You'd actually fight against us?
Watch your step. Don't forget
mister, there's only two of you!
What is the plan, Neji?
I'd rather not fight,
but if we must...
You're gonna come at us
three against two?
(Suiren)
No.
You guys are--!
We'll help you.
(All)
Huh!?!
What is going
on with you guys!?
You've gotta be kidding
us, right!?
You'd fight with the Rain
against fellow Leaf Shinobi?
According to the rules, being
from the same village has no
bearing at all.
If your team possesses the
Earth scroll, then you're
fair game, and that's that.
Fair game!>
That's not fair!
[grunt] If that's
the case then...
-Retreat!
-We'll remember this!
(Inaho)
We're gonna be Chunin,
no matter what!
Why did you help us?
If we want to save our
teammates, it just makes
sense to cooperate.
Have you two come to
the same conclusion?
Yeah.
Then let us all
work together to save
Tenten and your friend!
Whoa... it's the nest.
There's no way we would
capture one of them...
Look there...
That tunnel up there must
lead to the outside.
And you're suggesting we go
through this to get to it?!
It does look
difficult, doesn't it?
We should go back to the
first corridor we found.
You're right.
[gasps]
Uh oh!
[snarling]
Hurry!
Is that an entrance?
Yes, I think
you're right.
Okay then! Just
hang in there, Tenten!
Hey! Lee!
I am coming!
Argh! Those ants
are so huge!
(Neji)
Lee!
[ant growls]
They must think that we're
prey to be hunted!
I will distract them.  Neji, you
guys go in and find the other 2!
Got it!
[gasps]
Eight Trigrams:
Air Palm!
Hurry!
-Right!
Leaf Hurricane!
I will not let you get past me!
Oh, wait. I guess...
They cannot understand
what I am saying.
[panting]
[gasp] They're
chasing us!
[grunt]
No way...!
It's caved in.
Can we get through?
Byakugan!
They're right in there.
Yes, that's Ajisai's chakra.
Just step aside!
No, stop! An explosion
could cause a cave in.
[grunt]
Eight-Trigrams Air Palm!
I lowered its power to contain
it, but I guess that didn't work
Not much different
than a Paper Bomb.
What do we do?
Look!
[snarling]
[grunt]
What was that tremor just now?
It's from outside.
Someone is trying to clear
all of this rubble away.
Your friends, maybe?
Could be. Or yours.
You think that they'll
be able to do it?
Might be difficult...
[ant snarls]
They're coming!
Hold on!
Summoning Jutsu!
[low growl]
Go take care of them!
What are you gonna do?
Move this rubble to
another dimension with my
Transportation Jutsu.
But you don't even
know how much there is!
It's the only thing we can do!
[groan]
I'll either remove all
this rubble, or I'll
run out of chakra.
Enclosing Jutsu!
[panting]
Please, you have
to help.
But, I've never done
anything like this...
It's just like when you stow
away weapons and tools.
Yeah, you say that, but...
[waves crashing]
With the Summoning Jutsu, the
quantity or size of what is
summoned is directly
proportional to the caster's
own chakra. So...
For example, you just summoned
this amount of water.
By increasing your chakra,
you could summon enough
water to fill a bathtub
or a lake, or even an ocean.
An Ocean...
Ha!
[screams]
[wave crashing]
Bring it on!
[screaming]
It's impossible!
[happily chowing down]
(Guy Sensei)
Do you remember the
last Chunin Exams?
(Neji)
Yes.
(Rock Lee)
Yes!
Yeah.
As you all know, the last time
around, the Chunin Exams were
cancelled due to unforeseen
circumstances.
On top of not being promoted to
chunin, I was useless during the
Hidden Leaf's most critical
moment.
Lee! It couldn't be helped.
You were seriously wounded and
unable to join the action.
I feel guilty 'cause I was
perfectly healthy but helpless.
Don't let any of that bother you
now. After a two-year hiatus,
the Chunin Exams are going
to be held again.
What!? Really?!
And so, although I'm pretty
sure of the answer, I must
at least ask you...
Will you three take the
Chunin Exams as a team?
No question.
Yes, of course!
Mmhm.
That's the power of youth!
We have grown much
stronger since then!
What's the matter,
Tenten? Having doubts?
Sensei, have I gotten stronger
since the last Chunin Exams?
Well, Tenten, you should have.
But it seems like I have
nothing to show for it...
[gasp]
Hmm..
There's no doubt that you've
persevered and trained hard
since then. Admittedly, it's
not as readily apparent as
Neji's jutsu or Lee's technique
But do not forget, Tenten...
Huh?
Hard work and determination will
never betray you.
[grunt]
[panting]
[ant snarl]
[roaring]
[gasps]
Unsealing Jutsu!
[panting]
[gasp]
Oh no! You
all right?
Move... the rubble!
But, it's impossible.
I just can't move the
rubble like you do. Gah--!!
Hurry! The Ants will dig
through any second!
I know I  just have to
suck it up and do it!
If hard work never betrays you&
Then my chakra has increased!
Hm.
[attack cry]
[panting]
[gasp]
Huh? Daaaaghhhhh!!
[shouting]
No way... I almost
drowned in the desert!
[gasp]
[giggling]
You did it!
Yeah!
To think, seawater
in the desert!
Tenten, you showed the
fruits of your labor!
I sure did, didn't i!?
(Lee)
As expected!
(Tenten)
[laughter]
Well then, there was a truce
between us. So what happens now?
If you agree,... could we
continue the truce?
Fine by us.
After what we all went through,
I do not feel like fighting.
We're going to head straight
for the finish line.
And we...
We will make a detour to the
right and search for a scroll.
(Tenten)
Thank yoU!
I got the knack of it,
all thanks to the
example that you set.
Oh yeah? Well, I'm
glad for you.
Let's both try really hard to do
our best. And we'll meet up in
the Third Exam.
Yeah.
Hope to see you again, guys!
They're strange, the
other villages...
There are... all
kinds of shinobi...
I wonder if the Hidden Rain
Village is really going to
change...
We'll change it. By having faith
in Lord Pain and Lady Angel.
Let's go. We have to
look for a Jinchuriki.
(Ino)
We should've just headed
straight for the goal rather
than going with your strategy!
(Sakura)
What are you talking about?!
You agreed to it!
(Sakura)
Ino, you just drank too much
water, you bloated blister!
(Ino)
Oh yeah? Well you'd have to
drink 100 times more than me,
Miss Flat-As-A-Board!
(Choji)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Place Where I Belong."
(Sakura)
If drinking water is all that
it takes, I'd be happy!