(Kiba) A mission to find a
wedding present, huh?
(Shino) The Hokage's giving us a
wonderful opportunity to find a
great gift.
One that epitomizes the
friendship that we all share.
(Choji) That's right, we've
never had a wedding celebration
like this before!
Naruto and Hinata are the first
ones among our group of friends
to get married, after all.
We gotta do our best to find
something that they'll both
like.
Akamaru!
I feel just the same way!
I am fired up! I will make
sure they love my gift!
So do you already know what
you're getting them, Lee?
I have no clue.
[grunts]
However! If I put myself in
Naruto's shoes and think about
how he feels...
I know that it will come to me
naturally. I will not lose to
anyone!
Hah!
Wake up, Akamaru!
Whoa! [groans]
Well, traditionally, getting
wedding gifts isn't a
win-or-lose competition.
But, still, let's give it our
all!
This is for Hinata. So let's
all try our hardest!
(Shino) There's no need to get
so worked up.
The reason is if you relax,
you'll think of something.
Everyone seems really fired up
about this.
I can't think of anything!
You, Choji?
I have a pretty good idea of
what I'm gonna get. [grunts]
Damn it. This is such a drag.
[grunts]
(Kakashi) We're going to assess
and rank each gift.
That way we can determine who'll
attend the wedding ceremony...
and who'll be placed on duty for
that day's missions.
(Kakashi) In other words, we're
going to sift and screen through
the gifts.
I'd better not tell anyone
that.
[screams]
Hello!
Oh! It's you, Lee!
The ramen Naruto gets most
often, please!
Naruto's favorite ramen, huh?
Let me see, here.
Oh, that's an easy one! It's our
large miso and char siu!
Oh, yeah, right!
But why the sudden curiosity?
If I am going to understand
Naruto's feelings...
I figured that I should first
try the things that he likes to
eat!
Well, I don't really get all
this, but go ahead and take a
seat.
Okay!
Idiot. Idiot.
[sighs]
How was it?
[tearing up] Whoa!
So delicious! Light, yet rich,
with volume and punch, you want
to slurp it down all at once!
[sighs]
Do you get Naruto's feelings a
little better now?
[sobs] I have come to understand
why he would always want to
order this ramen!
But other than that, no, I do
not.
That's too bad.
If you could tell how a guy
feels just by eating ramen, life
would be a lot easier.
Oh, hey, wait! Iruka, you were
Naruto's teacher. So you must
know all about him, right?
Iruka Sensei?! I am sorry! I
was deep in thought and did
not notice you there!
Oh, don't worry. Your name
is Lee, isn't that right? You're
a student of Guy's, aren't you?
Yes! And you were Naruto's
teacher in the Academy!
Which means that you must know
how Naruto thinks!
Please, you have to tell me
everything you can about
him!
The thing is, I was his teacher
a long time ago.
He's earned praise for so many
things that don't really have
anything to do with me.
And I only see him once in a
while anymore.
Oh, I see.
Why are you even trying to
understand Naruto's feelings
in the first place?
For his wedding gift.
So that I would be able to find
something that he is certain to
like.
And I thought that the best
way to start would be to
understand his feelings.
Oh, so that's it. I get it
now.
[sighs]
Anyway, to convey my intense
respect for my friend Naruto...
I am going to throw my whole
being into finding the
best wedding gift for him!
(Lee) Please excuse me, Iruka
Sensei!
[yells]
Wow, he is exactly the same as
Guy.
Sorry about all that ruckus
just now.
Oh no, I'm fine! In fact, I'm
happy! I'm glad Naruto has a
friend like him.
Found ya, Iruka Sensei! You
still haven't recorded your
congratulatory message yet!
Oh, that's right. You think
you can wait just a little
longer?
Aw, man, not again.
Naruto's wedding gift.
Naruto's wedding gift. Ah ha!
Naruto's [gasps] Wait! Uh!
Yes, of course! Dumbbells
would be just perfect!
Naruto! Hinata!
Congratulations on your
marriage!
(Lee) Please use these dumbbells
and find everlasting happiness.
No! Not! Enough!
There can be no denying that
dumbbells are most definitely
useful and welcome tools.
And! Their heaviness is surely
symbolic of the solidity...
and the depth of friendship I
share with Naruto!
But...
(Lee) It is possible that Naruto
will get so hooked on muscle
building...
that he will totally ignore
Hinata!
[sighs]
Even if Naruto and I do have a
very special bond...
giving him dumbbells might not
be the best choice.
I will have to think of
something else!
Hmm.
[grunts] I cannot think of
anything! At times like this
I...!
[sigh]
What gift would make Naruto
and Hinata happy?
I guess that it should be
something that reminds them of
me.
(Tenten) If a kunai like this
was specially ordered and
prettied up a bit.
Marriage, huh? Must be nice!
[gasps] Wait a sec!
She's in love with her dream man
and getting married to live
happily ever after...
while I don't even have a
boyfriend and train every day
from morning till night.
This'd be...
(Shikamaru) Another kunai?
(Kiba) Well, it is Tenten!
(Sakura) Hah! When you think of
her, you think kunai.
Maybe I should think of
something else.
Like something that doesn't kill
people...
within a limited budget that
still captures a girl's heart.
(Lee) Tenten!
Huh? Wait, that voice.
[grunts]
Idiot! Idiot!
You gotta calm down when you
wanna ask someone something!
I am sorry. I just could not
do it by myself.
I had no choice but to ask you
for help, so I came looking for
you, but...
[sighs] You, too huh?
Yeah.
It's just a more traditional
gift won't really be able to
convey our true feelings.
But a present that does a better
job of representing who we
are...
may not be something that makes
them happy.
Wedding gifts are more
complicated than I thought.
[sighs]
What would Neji do if
he were here now?
Enough! No! We cannot get down
on ourselves!
Down on ourselves?
Yes!
Oh, I get it! Instead of just
sitting around trying to think
of something...
if we look at actual items, it
might help give us ideas!
There are so many things here.
I'm sure we'll be able to find
something...
that expresses who we are while
also making Naruto and Hinata
happy!
You are right! For example. How
about a sword like this?
Uhh. It does look nicely
upscale.
But it doesn't really have any
connection to a wedding.
Wrong!
They can use it for their
first effort together as man
and wife!
To cut the cake, seriously?!
It is no good?
Not really.
I mean, don't you think a
cake-cutter would rank pretty
low on the usefulness meter?
Well, then, how about these?
Tonfa? It's "you," since
you're a taijutsu specialist,
but Naruto and Hinata aren't.
And also, those don't actually
have any connection to a
wedding, either.
Wrong!
I believe they would be very
useful for everyday married
life.
Since they will have more
laundry to do!
What?! For hanging laundry?!
All the same, I do not think
Naruto would be pleased if he
got this as a gift.
Maybe you should try to think
of something a bit less out of
the ordinary.
[sighs] You are so lucky,
Tenten.
All you have to do is give
them the things that you
always use.
Huh? You think getting kunai
would make them happy?
But those aren't really
necessary for married life at
all.
Wrong, they are very useful!
For newlyweds who cannot
decide what they should have
for dinner.
They are perfect!
Come on! Is that any way to
use a kunai?!
Idiot! Idiot!
I cannot believe we did not
find a single thing.
We still have time. We'll just
try again.
[yawns] I cannot think of a
single thing to get them.
(Neji) Lee. Hey, Lee!
Hmm?
Neji!
When you get stuck on something,
you even continue to struggle
with it in your dreams.
That's so like you, Lee.
Neji! Is that really you,
Neji?
You were groaning pretty loud,
there, you know.
I just cannot find a gift for
Naruto and Hinata's wedding!
Not even after spending the
whole day looking!
All that I have done is use up
my ideas and energy!
But why are you here, Neji?
Because I have something to
tell you.
Neji, I- I just...
I know. There's no need to
speak of it.
Listen, Lee, and remember this
carefully!
Physical strength over
endurance! Physical strength
over endurance!
Physical strength over
endurance?
And don't forget: Hyuga.
What? Hey wait, Neji!
[distraught]
I thought you came because I was
having a dilemma about a wedding
gift...
and you wanted to give me
advice! Hm? [gasps]
Neji!
Naruto and Hinata, my
congratulations.
Naruto, who'd've guessed a bad
kid would become such a great
man?
And Hinata, please make sure
to take good care of Naruto.
[sighs] All right, I think
that's it!
Okay!
That was perfect! I can just
see Big Brother Naruto's eyes
welling up with tears!
Okay, I'm off to edit this! I
can't wait to see how it turns
out!
Oh, Lee! Hey!
Hello, Iruka Sensei.
[gasps] What the hell happened
to you?
I cannot decide on a gift for
Naruto's wedding.
And on top of that, an old
friend appeared in a dream and
gave me advice...
that does not make any sense at
all, and I could not sleep
thinking about it!
Two thousand seven hundred
sixty-five sheep.
sixty-six sheep.
Two thousand seven hundred
sixty-seven Nejis. Hold on,
Nejis?
Neji, you jerk!
Oh, wow, that sounds terrible.
Maybe I will never be able to
convey the depth of my
friendship to Naruto!
Now, there, there. Don't take
all of this so seriously.
(Iruka) I'm sure it's a big
struggle for all of you.
But I'm actually happy.
Happy? Why?
Well, because it's really
gratifying to discover that a
student I once taught...
has friends who'll go to such
lengths for him.
I realize that it might sound
like I'm just trying to make
you feel better.
Oh, no, not at all.
(Iruka) Actually...
I've never really had a chance
to talk like this with Naruto's
friends before now.
But thanks to his upcoming
wedding, I got to talk to you
and the others.
And as a result of that...
you've all allowed me to see
another side of Naruto that I
never really knew about.
I'm grateful for that.
Now that I think about it, I
haven't seen him much since he
graduated.
So you guys probably know a
whole lot more about Naruto than
I do!
What?! Is that really true?!
Huh? Why's that so shocking to
you?
I was just hoping you would
be able to help me come up with
ideas for Naruto's wedding gift.
I'm very sorry that I can't be
of more help to you.
But considering all of the
effort that you're putting into
finding a gift for him...
I'm certain that Naruto will be
happy with whatever you choose
to give him.
You really think so?
In fact, if he dares to
complain, as his teacher, I'll
knock some sense into him again!
[gasps]
Did I sound conceited saying
that?
Knock sense into him as his
teacher? Yes, that is it!
What now?
I had forgotten something
important! Yes!
I must thank you, Iruka
Sensei! Now!
What the?!
[chuckles] So you've come, huh,
Lee?
[grunt] Guy Sensei!
I figured you'd show up right
around now.
Judging by your expression, it
seems that you're still on the
horns of a dilemma, aren't you?
What?! How can you tell?!
Just one glance at you and I can
see that you've been training
all night...
because something is weighing
heavily on your mind.
Guy Sensei!
And let me guess.
Your worries have something to
do with the wedding gift that
you've been trying to pick out.
[gasps]
Guy Sensei! Can you read what
is in my heart and mind?!
How long have the two of us
been together in the
springtime of our youth, Lee?
Guy Sensei, I cannot even
decide what I should give
Naruto for his wedding gift!
I am still only half a shinobi!
Please, knock some sense into
me! Please!
Well said! It's bugging me,
too! Let's search for a gift
together!
Guy Sensei! [grunts]
Lee!
Guy Sensei!
Huh?! [gasps]
[shudders]
(Guy) Let's set some ground
rules.
First, a wedding gift can't be
something common.
However, it mustn't be too
unconventional, either.
Yes. We figured out that much
by ourselves.
It's just from that point on
that we got stuck.
And the wedding gift should also
be one that leaves a lasting
impression...
and conveys true friendship,
effort, and triumph in choosing
it.
So what would be a gift that
exemplifies me and the hot
springtime of youth?!
[distraught] What is it?!
Hmm. Well, if such a thing
does exist then it would...!
(Guy) Definitely include wearing
a fashionable bodysuit!
Huh?! But why a bodysuit?
Yes, of course! The hot
springtime of youth means
sweat and tears!
Can sweat and tears be given
as gifts?!
Eww gross!
(Guy) Wait, Lee!
In the first place, can man live
on willpower alone?!
Can he overcome the dangers of
divorce only with patience?!
Wait, Sensei, you're going
off-topic!
I have been thinking the same
thing! Should curry be
medium-hot? Or super-spicy?!
No one's on-topic anymore!
I'll circle the village on my
hands five thousand times!
I will do five thousand two
hundred, then!
Five thousand three hundred
times!
Five thousand four
hundred!
Enough!
[gasps]
It's true. We've gone way
off-track, here.
So, let's just go back to the
beginning and go over the basics
again.
The basics?
Yes! Of course!
First of all, what is a
wedding ceremony?
That is a very philosophical
question to ask.
Uh, is that really where we're
gonna start?
Then let me ask you this: what
is absolutely necessary for a
wedding ceremony?
[gasps] Well, would it be
love?
You're a poet.
But be that as it may, I believe
that the more correct answer is
the bride and groom.
Oh! You are right!
Yes, exactly! A wedding ceremony
without the couple is not a
wedding ceremony at all.
It's just a regular old
ceremony.
And who knows? One could even
say that it's more like a party
than an actual ceremony!
How blind I have been!
Guy Sensei!
You have the stunning ability to
see what the truth of something
is beneath the surface!
You are amazing!
You don't need to go
overboard.
You have always been and always
will be my role model!
My everlasting hero, my guiding
light!
Okay so now that that is all
settled, we can think about what
kind of gift would be the...
best to please the happy couple
on their wedding day, right?!
Absolutely!
I'm getting a bad feeling
about this.
All right, then, I'll be the
groom, and Lee, you can
portray the bride.
Okay, Guy Sensei!
I knew it!
[grunting]
Why do I have to play the
baby?!
Not this again!
Hi.
Honey, I'm home.
[gasps]
Do you have any idea what time
it is?!
It is time for the new spring
fashions!
[grunting]
Huh? [grunts] How dare you!
Seventh Gate of Shock! Open!
[screams]
[heavy breathing]
Well, Lee, have you gotten any
ideas yet?
I believe that I have almost
figured it out, but after all
that, it is still far off.
Never mind. You're never going
to arrive at an answer if you
think too deeply about it.
I doubt Neji would speak to
you after that role-playing.
No. But he would, if it's for
Hinata's sake.
(Guy) The husband's young female
coworker appears out of
nowhere...
to threaten his peaceful family
life. Neji would definitely take
on that role!
No way! [grunts] Seriously,
how can you misunderstand Neji
so much?!
Even if it's only as a ghost,
I'm sure that Neji would
appear!
You think that Neji
would appear?! Oh!
Physical strength over
endurance! Physical strength
over endurance!
I get it!
At last! [chuckles] So that
was your message, Neji!
It actually was not intended
for me at all, it was meant
for Hinata instead.
What's that, Lee?
Physical strength is essential
to protect a family!
It is the highest form of
strength!
Yes, that's right! Cooking,
washing, cleaning, raising the
kids, shopping.
The newlywed life is a nonstop
test of strength!
Oh Yes! And newlyweds must
prepare for that!
If that's really the case,
then there's only one possible
answer to what you're seeking!
The truest gift from us is.
Some dumbbells!
Are you kidding?!
Guy Sensei.
Oh, Lee!
[sobs] Guy Sensei!
[sobs] Lee!
[grunts]
All right, Lee, you shall give
the left dumbbell to them!
Yes!
And I'll give the right!
Let us go, Guy Sensei!
Yes! Our wedding gift will
lose to no one! [yells]
[groans]
[gasps] Okay, I'm gonna go
with a custom-made kunai.
[humming]
What?! You fool!
(Teuchi) You want a delivery?
So, you've decided on a
wedding gift, have you?
Yes! And all the thanks.
Go to Guy Sensei and you as
well, Iruka Sensei. It truly
pays to have great mentors!
Well, if you believe that I
was able to help you, then
that makes me very happy.
What are you saying?
Naruto is blessed to have a
mentor like you! I am sure he
feels the same!
Oh, uh, thank you.
Okay, I am going to go take a
look at some dumbbells, so if
you will excuse me, please.
[grunting]
Naruto's mentor, huh?
Maybe I should find out more
about how Naruto's grown after
leaving my care.
And what kind of bonds he's made
with his friends.
After all, if I'm truly
Naruto's mentor...
(Konohamaru) Oh! Iruka Sensei!
We meet again!
Oh, Konohamaru! You have great
timing!
About the message I recorded
earlier, would it be okay if I
do it over?
Yeah, sure! But why?
I want to find out more about
Naruto and send him a proper
message this time.
A message worthy of his
mentor.
(Ayame) I'm back!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What can I get for you?
Uh, Let me see.
[chuckles]
I'll have the miso char siu.
Make it a large.
[chuckles] Coming up!
(Teuchi) One large miso char
siu!
(Ayame) Right! A large miso char
siu ramen!
Miso?!
(Shikamaru) [groans] I can't
think of a wedding gift!
Choji, you wanna help me think
of something?
(Choji) Hey, do you get to eat
sweets every day of your sweet
married life?
Like sweet bean curry, chocolate
hamburger steak, honey fried
rice...
tempura cake, vanilla flavored
food pills? It all sounds so
good!
(Shikamaru) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:
"Hidden Leaf Story, The Perfect
Day for a Wedding, Part 3: Steam
and Food Pills."
Guess I'll just have to ask
Ino.