(KOTETSU) All right, shift's
over.
(IZUMO) Time to close
the gate.
Hm? We weren't
notified about any
departures at this
hour...
Hey, the gate's
about to close!
Ah!
[groaning] Wait!
[groaning and collapse]
"Jiraiya Ninja Scrolls:
The Tale of
Naruto the Hero-
Leaving the Village"
(KAKASHI) Sasuke.
[gasp]
So where are you
going? At this hour?
And why would you need
to resort to all this?
I really am
grateful to you...
...but this isn't
enough for me.
I'm not satisfied
with the mediocre
level where I'm
stuck.
Huh?
So I'm going
to go and
get power...
...at the side
of that other
Sannin.
Don't tell me
you're--?!
Huh?
[grunt] Damn it!
It's too late.
Sasuke!
[groaning]
[gasp]
[heavy breathing]
The Uchiha's genjutsu
is powerful.
You'll be out
of it for
a while.
You all right,
Kakashi?
Yes. Forget me.
(KAKASHI) Sasuke's...
I received word
earlier from Izumo
and Kotetsu.
Where could Sasuke be
going that he'd resort to
hurting you, as well?
Most likely...
...to see Orochimaru.
To gain more
power.
What?! Would he
really?
Orochimaru...
Hm?
(TSUNADE) How foolish...
In just a little
while now, Orochimaru
will be searching for his
next vessel.
That's what Jiraiya
said.
Sasuke's in danger!
[gasp]
No way!
We have to
stop Sasuke from
making contact with
Orochimaru.
Also... if there are rumors
that he left the village, I want
to prevent them from spreading
further.
So what I'm
going to do
is issue an
urgent lockdown order.
Yes. That's
a good
idea.
To keep the
Uchiha's position from
worsening, we'll handle
this internally...
...and what's more,
we have to bring
Sasuke back quickly
and without incident.
NINJA ACADEMY
[panting]
(NARUTO) So what's going on?
We're supposed to be
on lockdown but you called
for us to assemble...
I'll explain once
everyone is here.
[chuckle] Hey, what's up
with the attitude,
Shikamaru?
Um...by the way...why are
we meeting in the classroom?
Oh... Well, I...
I couldn't think
of anywhere else
to meet.
Hm...
The desks and
chairs look so
small. Were they
always like this?
[scoff]
We just got bigger over
the years. [chuckle]
[chuckle] I guess you're
right.
[chattering]
Sakura is completely infatuated
with that Sasuke kid. What's the
big deal with this guy?! I just
don't get it!
Stop, Naruto!
Quit glaring at
Sasuke, would
you?!
Get lost.
[angry grunt]
Get him, Sasuke! --
You show him
who's the boss
here!
Just get him!
What? No way!
Huh?!
Sorry!
[gasp]
[kissing]
Huh?
It's a headband...
A current Academy student
wouldn't have one of those yet.
Please accept my
apologies for being
late!
Lee... We're only late
because you insisted on
walking here on your hands!
Are we the
last ones to
arrive?
You are. But
now, all of
us are here.
What do you
mean, "all?"
What about Sasuke?
I'm glad you asked. It's because
of Sasuke that things have
become a bit of a drag. Right,
Sakura?
Uh... yeah...
Earlier, in the
hospital...
...I heard Kakashi
Sensei and Lord
Hokage and...
Seems Sasuke... has
left the village.
Huh? He what?
Sasuke did what?!
Why would he leave?
He went to go search for
Orochimaru.
I don't know the reason why, but
it seems he left the
village to get more power.
Hold on. This Orochimaru, isn't
he one of the Legendary Sannin
of the Leaf?
Yes. And furthermore, the rumor
is that he killed several
villagers for his unethical
experiments...
...and ran away when he was
discovered.
Why did Sasuke choose
someone like that?
From what I hear, that guy is
still dangerous. What kind of
power is Sasuke seeking, anyway?
Oh, Naruto...
(NARUTO) This headband...
(NARUTO) Sasuke was here.
The headband, which symbolizes
the Hidden Leaf.
He left it here in the Academy
classroom, which holds so many
memories for all of us.
So in other words, does that
mean Sasuke has abandoned us,
and the Leaf?
No way I don't buy it!
Okay sure, so he's been a little
bit irritable lately...
And I'll admit that he's also
been short with me, and he said
some sarcastic things that
really made me mad!
But come on!
He's still a, a Hidden Leaf!
Sasuke's still our friend!
Naruto...
Orochimaru is gonna steal
Sasuke's body and use it as his
new vessel.
Huh?
But Sasuke doesn't know that, of
course.
What the hell's Sasuke thinking?
Why would he wanna do this?
I'm gonna go and bring Sasuke
back! Before he finds
Orochimaru, I'll bring him home!
Just wait a minute. We also have
to think about the position that
the Uchiha are in right now.
We can't make a big deal out of
all this. And yet, we also can't
allow Naruto to go and handle
this on his own.
So I'll go with him!
Naruto!
Yeah I know, Sakura, but don't
you worry!
I'll bring Sasuke back, even if
I have to beat the hell out of
him!
(chuckling)
You're looking at me and
Akamaru's secret tunnel.
Sometimes we like to go outside
the village for fancy moonlight
picnics and stuff like that.
What do you mean, picnics?
You're just taking him out for a
walk!
Kiba, you know you're gonna
get caught one day.
I wouldn't mess up like that!
And besides, thanks to our
secret tunnel, you can get
outside the village now, so you
should be grateful.
Shikamaru, we'd better
hurry up and go.
Yeah.
(SAKURA) Naruto!
Yes Sakura?
Naruto...This is a desperate
request.
Please bring Sasuke back to me,
no matter what!
Don't worry one bit! I'm
definitely gonna bring Sasuke
back home!
I promise that on my life!
Good luck, Naruto, Shikamaru.
Yeah, you bet.
Naruto...Please
be careful.
Huh?
When Sasuke left, he just boldly
walked through the front gate,
leaving tracks everywhere.
That's going to make it way
easier to follow him.
Sasuke...Why? Why
would you do this?
I am...
(sighs) Why did I think that you
would be like Itachi?
It's too soon. You're
not ready yet.
Itachi was able to master it
when he was about your age.
Damn it!
(grunts)
Chidori Stream!
(heavy breathing)
Three whole years...
(NINE TAILS) Roar!
This feeling... what the
hell is it?
I can't let those three years
end, in the blink of an eye!
That Naruto Uzumaki, he seems to
have gained a lot of strength in
the past three years.
That loser!
I'm going to obtain power, no
matter what it takes!
(KUSHINA) Minato!
Kushina!
Minato, listen! Even though you
issued the lockdown order,
Naruto has snuck out and run off
somewhere!
And he hasn't come back yet!
Well, uh, you're not actually
supposed to leave the house
either...
It's not only Naruto, ya know.
Shikamaru's gone missing as
well.
What?
Sakura and Ino were both still
at their houses, but something
didn't seem quite right...
It's like they were trying
to hide something.
Hide something?
Hmm, like what if...
...they saw Naruto being a
delinquent, going out every
night and being reckless...
...but because they're so nice
they didn't tell us anything
since they don't want us to
worry about him, you know?
Are you listening, Minato?
Uh, oh, yeah!
Don't worry about Naruto.
I bet he's probably out getting
in some extra training, that's
all.
Hmm.
Hmm?
This way!
Kay!
If Sasuke of the Uchiha Clan
leaves the village, there will
be a few who will not stand
idly by...
...Mainly the children that were
raised in this cowardly system
that's been passed on from the
Third Hokage to the Fourth.
(DANZO) Keep an eye on them, and
if they make a move, follow
them.
(Danzo) I want to make sure the
gift to Orochimaru reaches him
safely.
And if they do interfere, get
rid of them, whatever it takes.
It's possible those fools won't
be the only ones involved.
That's why I've gathered all of
you, the best the Foundation has
to offer.
Make sure that you live up to
that name.
Huh?
Not good!
Damn it!
Huh?
What the?
Bushy Brows?
Neji! Tenten!
What are you doing here?
We saw some shadowy figures
pursuing you when you left.
So all of us hurried over here
in order to provide you with
backup.
I must say, being of help like
this is much more invigorating
than staying in the village!
Hah!
Hey, don't get too worked up,
Lee. Nothing good ever happens
when you get all excited like
that.
No, get as worked up as you
want! You're a big help.
Look out!
Huh?
You guys are...!
Wait, those masks! ANBU.
Oh, man. Don't tell me Dad
already found out.
Byakugan!
It's only those four that
have followed us here.
And there are five of us! Which
means this will be easy!
(grunting)
Sorry, but, there's no way that
we're going back! Not even if my
Dad tells us to!
Hmph!
I can't believe you're doing
this! You can't just get into a
fight with some guys from the
ANBU!
(grunts)
Listen, we definitely have to
bring Sasuke back before he
meets up with Orochimaru, ya
know.
So please, don't get in our way!
Ah!
(grunts)
(gasps)
(grunting)
Retreat, everyone!
(grunts)
These guys...aren't ordinary
ANBU.
(grunting)
Naruto! Are you okay? Hmph!
They're coming at us with intent
to kill!
This is way too harsh,
considering that all we did was
disobey the lockdown order.
And on top of that, there's no
way they would try to kill
Naruto, the Hokage's son.
I see what's going on. These
ANBU aren't the Hokage's!
They're from the militant
faction led by someone else!
Not the pacifist faction led by
Lords Third and Fourth.
(SHIKAMARU) It was supposed to
have been dismantled!
I heard all about it a while
ago...
That there's a separate ANBU
unit still in existence, and it
serves as a training division.
I think it was called the
Foundation.
What?
So they're with the Foundation,
huh?
(grunts) Damn it! At this rate,
we're never gonna catch up to
Sasuke!
(SHIKAMARU) These guys aren't
with the Hokage! They're from an
underground organization called
the Foundation!
(NARUTO) I don't care if they're
underground or aboveground!
(NARUTO) If they want to kill
me, do it fair and square, with
their faces showing! Now just
try and get me!
(ANKO) Such a hot-blooded child!
(NARUTO) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Pursuers."
(NARUTO) We're all from the
Leaf, but these guys are...!
What's going on?