-You think I'm gonna run?
Your, uh-- shadow jutsu.
It lasts about five
minutes, as I recall.
And it's just the two of us now.
You make this one
easy for me, boy!
Ha!
-If you're counting
the original,
my body holds up to five hearts.
Thanks to you, though, I'm
not in need of a replacement.
That's why I'll be taking yours.
-Oh, how I've been
waiting for this.
-They were two separate bodies.
But they merged.
-The fire style and wind
style masks are now one.
-I will take your
heart, Kakashi,
to replace the one
you took from me.
-Over there.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He's
trying to force me into the open
where he can shoot m down.
-You call that hiding?
-Sensei!
[theme song]
-You did well this
time, Kakashi.
But do you have the courage
to show yourself and stand
before us like a man?
-Not again.
Water style, water wall!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Looks like
fire enhanced with the wind
change in chakra nature can't be
put out with water style alone.
Which means I'll just have
to fight him in close range.
-No!
-Kakashi-Sensei!
-You took your eyes off me.
An unfortunate distraction.
And now your heart is mine.
-Now die!
How about that?
Pain can be so
addicting, can't it?
-I'm counting on you, Shikamaru.
-How worthless.
Jashin must be disappointed
it's already over.
Well, then.
I'm sure Kakuzu must be
wrapping things up now, too.
-What-- what did you do?
-It seems he pulled
it off just in time.
-But-- but how?
-Time to go.
Hm?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Not deep enough.
-Damn you.
Why are you still alive?
You shouldn't be standing.
How?
-It's simple.
I fooled you.
You thought you killed me,
but you were dead wrong.
And all that blood
dripping off your weapon?
It isn't even mine.
That's right.
It's your partner's blood.
-It's not possible.
-That's where you're wrong.
That ritual of your partner's?
Sorry to tell you this.
He used your blood for it.
-So that's the plan.
Use this when you get a
chance, Kakashi-Sensei.
Please hold onto it until then.
-You see, Shikamaru knew Hidan's
powers utilized other people's
blood, so he prepared
blood capsules in advance
just in case.
-What are you saying?
-It could have been anybody.
If there was an
opportunity, one of us
had to get a sample from Kakuzu.
See, this capsule
came in quite handy.
-It can't be.
When could you possibly
have had the chance?
-When I struck you through
with my lightning blade.
At that exact moment I
extracted your blood.
-I'll get ahold of him.
You guys can stay out of it.
And the diversion--
that'll be me.
I've got this.
That's when I nabbed it.
My job was to trap you.
-Where are we going, kid, huh?
Splitting up me and Kakuzu
isn't gonna save you.
Damn you!
-Wasn't wise for
the kid to go alone.
He's underestimated Hidan.
He did show a lot
of promise, though.
He'd have commanded quite
a bounty down the line.
But today that boy dies.
-Yah!
-Anyway, that's how our
little strategy played out.
-You little rat.
-No way.
That lousy kid planned
that far ahead?
-That's about the size of it.
You should have
been more careful.
This time you misunderstood
your opponent.
Asuma gave his life leaving
behind that information.
No way he was going
to let it go to waste.
You people take lives
without hesitation.
There's no way you
could ever understand
the depth of what
Shikamaru feels.
-Kakashi-Sensei!
-Are you OK, sensei?
-Yeah.
Somehow I am.
INO (VOICEOVER): I can't believe
they invaded his body that much
in such a short time.
If Shikamaru had
taken any longer--
-Slowly.
Make sure not to
damage the vessels.
Here, let me treat you
with medical ninjutsu.
-It'll have to wait.
They're coming.
-Expansion jutsu!
Super slam!
-Nice work!
Way to go, Choji!
-Huh?
-Choji!
-Dammit.
-What?
He reanimated?
-He somehow absorbed the
lightning-style monster's
heart.
-What is he becoming?
-His primary body is
becoming a monster, too.
-Not one of my hearts, but two.
This hasn't happened
to me in a while.
[laughter]
-You know, I'm not
all that bright,
but even I can see through you.
You've used it so
many times now.
After seeing you do
it so much any idiot
could figure out the ins
and outs of your jutsu.
-What did you say?
-I can tell your jutsu isn't
as strong as it was before.
It hasn't even
been five minutes,
and I can already move again.
Thing is, I realized that both
the power and the duration
of your little jutsu gradually
weakens each and every time
you use it.
Admit it, kid.
The longer you use the jutsu,
the more feeble it gets.
Until you have nothing left.
I'd even venture to
guess you're approaching
the limit of your chakra.
Ain't that right?
-This time there's no escape.
-Get ready.
-Right.
-He's fast.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): I can't move.
-Kakashi, I had
intended to replace
the hearts I lost with yours.
But I've changed my mind.
After all, I can find more
hearts any time I please.
Now die!
-Wind style, Rasengan!
-Water style, ripping torrent!
-Hurricane fortress jutsu!
-Sorry we're late.
But better late than never.
-Huh?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Perfect timing.
[music playing]
-You know what those words mean?
If you curse someone
and take them out,
you'll also be defeated
in retribution.
You'll end up digging
your own grave.
My sensei's gone because of you.
Can't just let you
run around free.
This hole's the last
thing you'll ever see.
Next time-- When
You Curse Someone,
You Dig Your Own Grave.