[grunting]
The rudder isn't working!
[gagging]
Awesome! Oh, man,
this is some storm,
isn't it?!
What's going to happen to
us if we can't escape
this current?!
It should be fine. If we
continue like this, we'll
get back on course!
[laughing]
All right, then it's
straight on for the Land
of Lightning from here!
What was that?!
What is this?! What's
going on?
Here comes another one!
They're cannonballs made
out of paper bombs?!
That's some serious
firepower!
Where the hell are
they coming from?!
Uh-- is that...
... a battleship?
No. That's not a
ship. That's an
island!
"Battleship Island"
We're being pulled in
towards that island!
Can you change course?!
No, I can't! The
rudder's still not
working!
Come on, you gotta be
kidding me!
[grunting]
Ah!
Naruto!
Wood Style!
[gasping]
The ship.
[loud banging]
Scoop it all up! The
cargo, scrap metal,
everything!
Even the people!
[laughing]
Boss Gataro!
There's no sign of
their ship, sir!
It was blown apart, I'm
sure! No one returns to
the island without a net
full of loot!
Any crew that comes back
without enough plunder...
will face a most painful
punishment!
[cowering]
Why you--
You're not gonna get away
with messing with our
ship!
Oooh.
Seems there's treasure to
be found here after
all...
Huh?!
[laughing]
[grunting]
A feisty one like you is
sure to fetch a good
price.
But this here's just
a piece of junk!
Give me back that
headband!
Open fire, men! Corner
and capture the brat!
Prepare to fire!
Port twelve degrees,
angle twenty-six degrees,
range 500.
Fire!
Huh!?
[panting]
[laughing]
Yes, run! Run!
[gasping]
Huh! Uh!
Uh?
What in the
world is this?
Huh!
What in-?!
Why, you incompetent
fools! Their ship hasn't
been destroyed yet!
Quickly! Fire! Fire!
[growling]
Don't let them get away!
Switch the depth charges!
Just kill 'em! Blast 'em
to smithereens!
Huh?
How can this entire
ship be underwater?!
I had to work fast, but I
used Wood Style to
enclose the ship and
create a ballast tank to
keep us beneath the
surface.
It's a makeshift
submarine.
Thank goodness we have a
Sensory-Type with us.
[gagging]
It looks like we're
finally out of range
of the depth charges.
Can we just stay
underwater and travel all
the way out of this area?
Well...
Remember, it's still a
sailing ship.
While it remains
underwater, it can't
propel itself.
The only reason we're
moving is that the current
is still pulling us.
[chuckling]
The water gets shallower
just up ahead.
When that ship comes up,
I'll blow it to pieces!
We're going to have to
stay down here for a
while.
What?! You mean we
can't even surface
again?!
Uh...
[groaning]
[worrying]
Ahhhh!
It's leaking!
Plug it, quick!
[grunting]
[struggling]
Stop already!
Wait, can we move towards
twelve o'clock? There's
a pocket of air right
ahead of us!
But we have to move down!
Everyone to
the front, now!
[gasping]
Uh!
That was a
little too close.
Where are we?
Well... it
looks like...
An underwater cavern...
There seem to be tunnels
further in...
We must be beneath the
island!
[gasping]
Stairs... This cavern
was excavated for human
use at one time...
And that means there
could be a path that
leads up to the surface.
Let's split up and go
search for it.
Mm.
Naruto! Come back here!
Sorry, but I'm gonna go
get my headband back!
Wait!
You can't do it.
Going back to the
surface would mean
certain death.
[grunting]
But that headband's
really important!
You'll get it back, I
promise you will. But
for now, we must stay
hidden,
and wait for the
right opportunity...
Besides... I
think--
Huh?
I used Wood Style too
much.
I just need... to rest...
Captain Yamato...
Huh?
Oh, man, that's hot!
Look, it's a hot spring,
Captain Yamato!
Really?
We can replenish our
chakra if we just soak in
here for a little while.
Ahhhh, you're
right!
This is nice...!
What the what?!
What is this...?
Hmm...
It appears that these
people were the island's
inhabitants.
Are they... pirates?
No... It seems they lived
here before the pirates
even arrived.
But what happened to all
of them?
It says here that several
decades ago, those pirates
attacked the island.
The native
islanders were
slaughtered.
What? Really...?
Hmm?
[grunting]
No, please!
Some of them got away by
escaping into an
underground tunnel and
hiding themselves inside
the mountain.
[growling]
[chuckling]
Yes, run! Run!
Keep me entertained until
their boat resurfaces!
Just grin and bear it!
All right! The next boat
with the least loot, it's
your turn now!
The pirates control the
land above. If these
people had been
discovered,
it would've meant
certain death.
So they all just lived
down here quietly for
decades. How very sad.
What are you doing?
I, Naruto Uzumaki, will
get justice for their
pain and suffering!
Captain Yamato! We don't
have a choice, here. We
have to go confront that
pirate.
Mm.
So this is how they got
in...
It won't work. The wire
is frayed. It's not
functioning.
We need some way up.
We're in a volcanic
crater. It's a long
way to the top.
Aw, man.
Hmm? What's this?
The rock's warm.
It seems that beneath
here... there's an
underground hot
spring system.
That's right! Captain
Yamato was soaking in it
a while ago!
It's pretty massive!
[grunting]
Uh...
[struggling]
What's the matter,
Naruto?
Not now! The hot
springs... and floating...
And... wood style
submarine...
Huh?!
I've got it!
Uh... You've got what...?
Just hear me out. And
don't laugh, okay?
Right... now, this
is my plan.
[laughing]
No good, huh?
You know...
let's try it out.
[struggling]
[pulling]
[groaning and grunting]
[sighing]
[groaning]
Naruto...?
Don't worry! I'm doing
just fine!
All right!
It's time to set sail!
Bushier Brow Sensei! Go
ahead! You're up!
Got it!
All right!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Well? How was that?
[gulping]
It seems that it's
impossible...
Huh?
Uh!
Hot!
[cheering]
Way to go!
Now, pirates... We're
coming for you!
[screaming]
[laughing]
Boss Gataro! Maybe the
guys on that ship just
died at the bottom of the
sea!
There's no sense
in waiting--
[grunting]
Ahhhh!
Nobody tells me
what to do.
That kid isn't gonna die
that easily. I swore I'd
kill him, and that's just
what I'll do!
Just like when I took
over this island.
What?!
What just happened?!
[yelling]
That little brat!
[grunting]
Do not fire it!
It'll blow!
Curse that boy!
Hm?
[giggling]
How'd you like that?
[growling]
Get him!
If you let him escape,
then you're all dead,
every last one of you!
[laughing]
[giggling]
Surround him! Catch him
like a rat in a trap!
Mm.
Right!
I won't lose!
This is retribution!!
...for the suffering of
all the islanders.
Are you kidding?! This
island belongs to me!
If you make trouble, I'll
kill you the same way
that I killed the others!
Wait...
Where are your
friends?
You're the one...
...who's gonna get
pulverized this time
around!
Enough!
A clone...!
Hey! Over here!
Huh?
What's that?
Damn it!
Hey! Pirates!
You're done!
Wood Style!
Let's go!
[gasping]
Fly!
Ahhhhh!
All right!
Rest in peace... You've
been avenged...
Aoba, is this the island
where Bushier Brow Sensei
is?
Well, the bird flew off
this way. So I think its
safe to say its nest is
here.
I still can't believe
that bird was big enough
to carry him off!
We have to find him fast!
Wait, look! There's
someone there!
I'll go talk to them.
You two keep looking.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Forgotten
Island.
Wait! Just who are you?