Damn it!
He's the most
insensitive
person ever!
All right, calm down. Should
you really be fighting with your
dad when the Fourth Great Ninja
War's about to start?
Hmm.
Maybe not.
But...
I'm coming
in, Ino.
[embarrassed yell]
[shocked yelp]
You're so
stupid, Dad!
[scoff]
So? What did
you want, dad?
It's just... You, uh...
You seem so preoccupied
lately.
So, uh...
Is there anything
that you wanted to
talk about with me?
[scoff]
There's nothing
going on, okay!
I'm not entirely
clueless, you
know.
I mean, you're
a young woman
now...
What does
that mean?!
So who is it?
Huh?
Uhh... Have you
decided to go out
with Shikamaru
or Choji?
[annoyed groan]
Why would I want to go out with
either one of you guys, anyway?!
But the worst thing is that he
had the nerve to enter a woman's
room without even bothering to
knock! Can you believe that?!
Look, I get that you're upset,
but why are you taking it out
on the two of us?
Both of you just relax. Ino,
Inoichi's just worried about
you.
Come to think of it...
you did cry a lot over Sasuke
when you found out about him.
So I suppose your
father's not too
far off the mark.
[embarrassed gasp]
That's just 'cause
it was so sudden.
It doesn't matter now
anyway. Worrying about
Sasuke won't do any good.
I've finally decided
to leave it to Sakura
and the rest of her team.
Hmm... I guess Ino's over it.
Good. With war getting closer,
we can't have our teamwork
suffer because she's unfocused.
She's gonna be okay.
Hey Choji,
are you
going to--
It's all
your fault!
Huh?
No, it's not!
You started it!
Hey!
You're the one who
complained first!
[groans]
All right, enough!
Stop it! What is the
problem here, anyway?
Listen, just mind
your own business,
you fat- [muffled]
What?! My body!
It's moving on
it's own!
[chuckle]
Shadow Possession
Jutsu complete.
You really shouldn't be
fighting when the village
is in such a sticky situation.
I guess.
But he would-
No "buts" about it!
You're never going
to be popular with
the girls...
...if you always argue
over little things. Heh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now go run along and
play nicely, okay?
Okay!
As usual, your
teamwork was
perfect.
Wait...
aren't you?
So, uh who
is this guy?
It's Kosuke,
right?
He's been a genin
for over fifty years.
He's also known
as the Eternal
Ginin.
Uh, We've actually
met him before.
Seriously,
we have?
Oh, yeah!
That was when we
were still genin.
[chuckles]
And I was much
obliged to you
back then!
"The Legendary
Ino-Shika-Cho Trio"
[grunt]
[leaping grunt]
If this intel will spare my
comrades in the Leaf Village
from danger, I'll gladly give
up my life.
I must do everything
I can to deliver this
scroll!
Ah ha!
[grunt]
No one's ever escaped
the clutches of the
three brothers!
And you won't
be the first!
Big Brother,
we gotta get
him!
[chuckle]
Wily geezer...
But look, Iwaji,
Iwazo... that's
just a Substitution.
[grunt]
He has sharp eyes.
Don't underestimate us!
He's fast, too.
Oh, no you don't!
Earth Style: Earth Hold!
[grunt]
You won't get
away from us!
He's really
strong, as well.
Give up and stop
wasting our time,
old man!
Trying to steal
Intel from the
three of us, huh?
We're just going to have
to return the favor, then.
..And make you tell
us all about your
village.
My enemy doesn't seem to have
any vulnerabilities. Guess my
life will end on this moonlit
night.
[rolling attack yell]
[grunt]
Reinforcements?
[rolling attack yell]
What?
My- M- My
body just...
Shadow Possession
Jutsu, complete!
Ino!
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
[grunt]
This isn't the
time to joke
around!
[groan]
You brutes have some
nerve attacking our
comrade from the Leaf!
You brutes?
Ha ha!
All right!
Now it's
payback time!
Wha- Brother,
you're turning
on us?!
You're one
to talk!
Here I come!
[fighting]
[chuckle]
Yep! It
must be...
It's over.
[heavy breathing]
You can release
your jutsu, Ino.
What in the hell
is going on here?
(Choji)
It's the Hidden
Leaf's Secret...
...coordinated
ninjutsu formation...
Ino-Shika-Cho!
[attack yell]
[scared grunt]
Well, mission
accomplished,
guys!
And your formation
was really spot on
today!
All your training's
paying off.
Hmm?
Huh?
Are you all right?
Whatever the reason,
going on a solo mission
is reckless.
Amazing, I never thought
I'd be rescued twice by
the Ino-Shika-Cho formation.
Huh?
Of course! You're Kosuke,
the guy we rescued back
when we were still genin.
Yes, and I'm very happy
that you three remembered
me after all this time.
It's all coming back to me
now. Something you said back
then caught my attention.
Uh...
You said that you had
been saved twice by the
Ino-Shika-Cho formation.
Did we rescue
him twice?
Umm.
My life has indeed been saved
on two separate occasions by
the Ino-Shika-Cho formation.
Huh?
Yes... The day before the
destruction of the Hidden
Leaf...
It was late at night,
but the village was abuzz
with excitement over the
next day's festivities.
My, Kosuke!
That smells
delicious!
Am I intruding?
If you don't mind a hotpot stew
made by an old man, please join
me, Lord Third Hokage.
[chuckles]
With pleasure!
So I see that the final
stages of the Chunin Exam
are going to begin tomorrow.
Yes. That's right.
Mmm..
[exhale]
Delicious!
[chuckle]
Little things like this
are the only things I've
ever been good at.
Oh... Don't sell yourself
short. Sitting down to a
meal is the best part of
a mission.
You know, there have been many
shinobi who have specifically
requested you for their teams.
No matter how risky
the mission, if you
order me, I'll go
on it.
You shouldn't take
your life so lightly,
Kosuke.
Thank you
for the food.
It really was delicious;
some of the best I've had.
By the way,
Kosuke...
Would you be willing
to accept a mission
right now?
Huh?
The Chunin Exam is an
opportunity to check the balance
of power among the villages..
..so some mutual distrust
is always to be expected.
However, this time,
I feel a deep unease...
But hopefully, it's
nothing more than an
old man's imagination.
[crowd chatter]
What?  A message from
the Third Hokage?
Quiet, Choza!
Not so loud,
you fool!
Oh, right.
Sorry.
[moan]
So what did
Lord Hokage say?
It's too early in the season
for the leaves to dance. He
said that you would understand.
Message received
and understood.
A special code between the
Sarutobi Clan and the three
houses, huh?
[gasp]
Impossible!
[cheering]
[fleeing]
[crowd panic]
Leaf Ninja Art!
[frozen straining]
Yanagi!
What enemy could possibly
infiltrate the Hidden Leaf
Village?
Expansion Jutsu!
[attack yell]
Ahh, my body!
Never seen this
before, huh?
The Secret Shadow
Paralysis Jutsu.
And try this one out, too.
The Leaf's Secret...
Shadow Strangle Jutsu.
[yell]
Mind Destruction Jutsu.
[moan]
Stop! What Are
you doing?
I can't control
my body!
[pained groan]
[moan]
This sure brings
back old memories!
I know, it's a reunion
of the Ino-Shika-Cho Trio.
I'm a shinobi of the Leaf, not
as skilled as they are; but I'll
gladly give up my life.
For the sake
of the village!
What?
I won't allow you
to ravage the Leaf!
Even if it means sacrificing
this old body, I'll take as many
of you fools with me as I can!
It's Kosuke.
He charged right
into the middle
of the enemy, huh?
We can't just
let him go!
Then let's do it!
You mean, the
Ino-Shika-Cho
Formation?
I sure hope
you haven't
forgotten how!
If I ever forget,
I don't deserve
this earring from
the oath we all took!
[chuckles]
Got that right!
Let's go!
Right behind you!
[groan]
[attack yell]
[screaming]
You always make
such good shadows
for me.
[struggling]
[screaming]
Ten, twenty,
thirty...
Thirty-three!
Shadow Stitching Jutsu!
[grunt]
[struggling]
[groans]
Black Spider Lily!
You can take
the final blow.
Mind Destruction
Dance Jutsu!
[stunned groan]
Nicely done.
I'm really glad
that all of us are
on the same team!
Hmm..
Oh, hold on;
that's right.
Woah.
Are you all
right, Kosuke?
Huh?
[landing grunt]
All right, then...
Now on to
the next battle!
Shikaku, Inoichi!
Well that was as expected
from the Leaf's most powerful
Secret Ninjutsu Formation,
Ino-Shika-Cho!
Hm.
Ino Shika Cho.
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
Shadow Paralysis Jutsu!
Expansion Jutsu!
Your battle style has such
depth: you overwhelm your
opponents while filling
your comrades with courage!
That formation transforms
your comrades' fears to
bravery.
The power of your
experience, judgment,
and most of all conviction.
It's nothing short
of magnificent!
Thanks, but you've
got it all wrong,
Kosuke.
We're simply stuck
with each other,
whether we like it
or not.
That's right,
but don't tell
anyone, okay?
We don't want to make
ourselves look bad in
front of our kids, since we
all live in the same village.
You know?
[chuckle]
Oh..
Well, in any event, our kids
will surpass us in no time at
all, I'm sure of that much.
The seedlings
of the Leaf are
growing fast and
strong.
[laughing]
Seems that somehow
I've survived once
again.
Anyway...
It will be a pleasure
watching the seedlings
of the Leaf grow into
stately trees.
Our dads fought
a battle like
that?!
They really are
pretty amazing,
don't you think?
Yeah. They are. But here I
was, just thinking that our
own formation had gotten so
much better...
Compared to our dads,
we still have a really
long way to go, don't we?
[sigh]
If you don't
mind my saying...
...A shinobi is not
made in only one day.
I'm looking forward to seeing
your Ino-Shika-Cho formation...
...when it has
fully matured.
Until then, I'll have to learn
to be more careful, so you don't
have to keep coming to my rescue
all the time!
[chuckles]
Well, our dads had
their way of doing
things and we three
have our own way.
No sense getting
worked up over
this.
Yeah! You're right.
Hm.
Huh?
I think of myself as all grown
up but I guess in my Dad's
eyes, I'm still just a child.
There's no doubt that despite
our skill, we haven't gotten
up to our dads' level...
And to think, we're facing an
enemy that's even stronger than
they are...
Which means,
this upcoming war.
I wonder what kind of enemy
we're going to have to face.
[chuckle]
Huh?
Ever since we were genin,
practically all we thought
about was running away.
It's true. We were always
scared and just kept trying
to find the easy way out.
Mhm.
I guess to put a positive
spin on it, you could say
that we knew ourselves well.
[grunt]
But face it!
We're still
too weak!
What?!
That's why we use
our heads to think
of solutions...
...like how to
stay alive...
...and strategy,
like how to beat an
enemy that's stronger
than we are.
Oh!
I'm counting on you,
Ino and Choji.
We may never fully measure
up to our dads. But we're not
going to war alone, either.
We just have use
our strengths as
best as we can.
All we can do is
our best as who
we are right now.
Up to now, we've stuck
together and done all
right for ourselves.
So even with
this next war...
We'll be okay,
don't you guys
think?
Huh? Oh. Yeah...
We'll be fine, you guys!
Show a little spirit!
Come on!
(Ino)
We can do this!
Right!
Damn it, what a miserable
morning!  First, that weird
dream, and now, all anyone
can talk about is Naruto!
It can't be helped.
Naruto's the village
hero right now.
When we were kids, he was
such a loser. If he hadn't
farted during the Chunin
Exam, I would've won!
There are no "ifs"
in battle. That's
because-
You're so annoying!
I'll catch up to him!
Just watch!
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
Kiba's Determination.
I won't be
left behind!