So at long last, you're
finally heading out.
There have been many
changes to our plans.
You say that as if I'm
the one to blame for
everything.
But it was thanks to you
that we had to change our
strategy.
Thanks to me, your
military might and range
of attacks increased. You
would do well to remember
that in the future.
Don't do anything outside
of what we've agreed upon
while I'm away.
We are comrades. So you
really do need to learn
to have a little more
trust in me.
You're looking out for
your own interests. Don't
pretend otherwise.
Aren't you even going to
bother telling me where
exactly you're headed off
to?
The Hidden Rain Village.
The Hidden Rain Village?
But they aren't even
directly involved in the
Great Ninja War.
So, why go there?
It doesn't concern you.
Hey, wait up, Yahiko!
Yeah, wait for us!
I'm gonna get there
first!
[screaming]
Mmm.
[gasping]
[trembling]
It's a toad! A giant
toad!
How did something like
this ever get inside of
our hideout?
What do we do now?
You're so noisy! What
is all of this ruckus
about?
Jiraiya Sensei?! Is that
you?!
What do you think? Does
it look good on me?
Well, now that you
mention it... I guess it
kinda does!
[laughing]
What are you laughing at?
This isn't funny!
"The Angelic Herald of
Death"
Are you trying to find
something?
Yes...
Just tell me where you've
hidden Nagato's corpse.
You're not going to find
him here.
Seems like you're not
going to tell me where
you've hidden the Rinnegan.
I mean, hidden Nagato.
I was sure that you would
show up here looking for
it, sooner or later. I've
been waiting for you.
Now that you're here, I
will stop you.
I won't go easy on you
just because we were comrades.
The Akatsuki does not abide
traitors. Understood?
One question... Why would
such loyal members as you
and Nagato betray me?
You both approved of my
Project Tsuki no Me,
after all.
If you lost to Naruto
Uzumaki, it would be one
thing. That couldn't be
helped.
But Nagato sacrificed
himself... using the
Rinne Rebirth Jutsu for
Naruto.
That jutsu... was to be
used for my sake.
[cheering]
I never imagined that
someone as powerful as
Pain would be defeated.
We've got to tell Tobi
about this. Let's go.
But even Zetsu wasn't
able to see what made
Nagato change his mind so
drastically.
I've told you my story
just as you asked.
Now let's hear your
response.
I truly believe that
eventually the day will
come when all people will
understand one another.
Even if I understand you
now...
That doesn't change how
I feel.
There's no way that I can
forgive you.
I still hate you.
Then you want to settle
things with me...?
I do.
But Pervy Sage
believed in me and wanted
me to continue his quest.
And for those reasons...
I choose to believe in
him, and to follow what
he taught me.
So that's it; that's my
answer.
No! Never! How can I
believe in Jiraiya's
words after all of this?!
There never will be such
a thing as true peace!
Not as long as we're
forced to live in this
accursed world!
Peace is impossible!
Impossible!
Well, then...
I'm gonna to break that
curse one day. If there's
truly such a thing as
peace in this world,...
then somehow, I'll find
it.
And I'll never
give up!
[gasping]
You...
But that's...
Nagato? What's the
matter?
Those words... it can't
be...
That's right; you know
them.
All of those words are
taken right out of this
book.
The very first novel that
Pervy Sage ever wrote.
He was seriously trying
to change the world with
his message.
And in the back of it...
he wrote about a student
who helped provide him
with inspiration.
It was you, Nagato.
But...
...the name of the hero
in this novel...
His name is---
His name's Naruto!
Listen... My name is a
precious heirloom that
has been handed down to
me by my master!
There's no way that I'm
just gonna give up and
dishonor my master's
gift!
I will become Hokage!
And I will bring peace to
the Hidden Rain. I will!
I'm asking you to
believe in me!
Why should I?
How can you stand there
and tell me that you will
never change your mind?
Do you really think you
will never stray from
that ideal, no matter how
much pain befalls you?
You think you will always
believe in yourself?
Can you guarantee it? How
can you possibly have
that much faith that life
won't change you?
There's still pain
buried deep down inside
of me.
And there's no telling
what kind of pain I may
face down the road...
But--
If I stop believing just
because things get
difficult... if the hero
in this book were to
change who he is...
Then... it would become a
whole different story. It
sure wouldn't be the story
our Master left behind.
And it wouldn't be about
Naruto!
The thing is... I can't
write books like our
Master did.
And so... any sequel has
to come from the life I
live.
That's why no matter how
much pain my own path
brings, I'll keep
walking.
Because that's who
Naruto is!
Naruto Uzumaki... You
truly believe he's worthy
of all this?
He is the light. That's
why we all can carry
flowers of hope.
You bare your fangs at
me, yet you wear that
cloak.
You still care for the
Akatsuki.
Yahiko was the one who
founded the Akatsuki, not
you.
The red clouds on these
cloaks symbolize the
unending wars that rained
blood down upon the
Hidden Rain!
You merely jumped onto
our bandwagon for your
own purposes. These
cloaks are our legacy,...
not yours.
And the Rinnegan is
something awakened by
Nagato, a shinobi of the
Hidden Rain Village.
Again, it doesn't belong
to you.
His eyes belong to this
nation. They are this
village's treasure!
You're mistaken on two
points. Since you're
about to die, I shall
enlighten you.
I encouraged and pushed
Yahiko to form the
Akatsuki.
And...
I was the one who gave
Nagato the Rinnegan.
[gasping]
Perhaps it would be more
correct for me to ask for
it back.
But never mind... In my
opinion, you're just an
ignorant little girl who
knows nothing.
Except now... you know
the location of Nagato's
Rinnegan.
Once I capture you, I'll
have my answer. Do not
underestimate the visual
prowess of the Uchiha!
She's trying to overpower
me with numbers, hoping
to catch me when I
materialize.
Very well. I know she's
got some plan up her
sleeve. Bring it on!
There she is!
[struggling]
She mixed in Paper Bombs!
I'll take you with me to
the afterlife.
More members have been
killed in the Seventh
Ward.
It's becoming a guerilla
war zone.
We need to take measures
now.
I'll go and scout it out
in the afternoon.
No, Nagato, Rest awhile.
You shouldn't push
yourself so hard.
But, I-
No buts. Just rest. I
will go.
Yahiko, please be
careful.
I don't need to have a
send-off. Just go and
tend to Nagato's wounds
instead.
From now on, you should
save all your worrying
for him.
He's the keystone of the
Akatsuki!
He's the man who will
change this nation and
this world!
But the same can
be said of you!
Every one of us is here
because we respect and
admire you... Nagato
included!
But Nagato... is someone who
will be the bridge that
leads to peace.
My role is to make that
happen. I am a pillar
that will support that
bridge.
Yahiko...
As usual,... this land
continues to weep.
It endures pain.
I used to hate this land
that's crying all the
time.
But now, I want to save
it... It's what I want
with all my heart.
Hmm.
It's like the crybaby I
was. I can't ignore it.
Yahiko!
Please, be careful...
It's Yahiko who'll be the
bridge to peace. That is,
his will itself will be.
Nagato...
We believe in Yahiko with
all our heart!
Let's go, everyone!
Right!
I will be a pillar
that supports two
bridges. Yahiko and
Nagato!
I didn't take you
seriously enough. You are
a former member of the
Akatsuki, after all.
[panting]
It seems that you planned
to blow the both of us up
when I pulled you in. But
you failed.
I was faster. I pulled
the explosion away.
Though I did get hit.
You were also saved. You
ought to thank me.
So was that the last of
your secret schemes?
Madara... I have a
question...
What is it?
Do you want me to tell
you why Nagato and I
decided to betray you?
And why instead we put
our faith in Naruto?
Not really. Besides,
that's your problem.
Naruto is just a naive
child chasing an immature
dream.
I can see where Nagato
might be swayed by the
thought of true peace and
hope... But you, Konan?
I realized something
after meeting Naruto...
Him as well? You're
taking him, too?
Yes. This Tendo Pain
was created ú from the
body of our dear friend
Yahiko.
He's something that's
very precious to us both.
Yahiko? I guess I
understand, then...
What are you going to do
now? I'd hate to think
that you're going back
to the Akatsuki.
No, I'm leaving the
Akatsuki... Yahiko and
Nagato... meant
everything to me.
Yahiko's dream...
And then Nagato's
dream...
Both of their dreams have
been entrusted to you...
You now embody those
dreams.
Nagato chose to put his
faith in you. So now I
will do the same.
And we of the Hidden Rain
Village, will all continue
to pursue our dreams
together with you.
[inhaling]
The name Naruto,... the
guts to never give up,...
and now... more pain.
They're the things I've
inherited from my master
and from my sibling
student!
This time, I wish that
you will be the blossom
of hope that will never
wilt away.
You are darkness.
And in a world without
light, all that flowers
do is wilt!
They both fought and died
for their own beliefs.
Nagato will be the bridge
to peace.
Yahiko's will
itself...is the bridge to
peace..
Their will shall not be
extinguished!
If there's truly such a
thing as peace in this
world, I'll find it.
Naruto Uzumaki will be
the one to carry on their
will!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Bridge to
Peace.
I shall be the pillar
that supports Naruto!
"ROCK LEE'S SILLY
CHRONICLES: PART 1"
[chuckling]
Lead, lead, lead--
That guy... he thinks
he's so hot.
I am totally going to
steal a base!
Lead...
Naruto, did you
call me?
I said "lead," not Lee!
[chuckling]
You're out.
[screaming]
[chuckling]
Huh. It seems that once
again I have done something
terribly wrong.