Due to the increased number
of assignments, I'm adding
an additional
team to the ANBU.
Itachi, I'm appointing
you as a captain.
Yes, sir.
I'm not saying that
I'm opposed, but you
still seem very young.
What's your age?
Thirteen, ma'am.
There have been quite a
number of shinobi who were
younger but nonetheless
became jonin.
Two years in the ANBU
and already a captain...
He has to be the
youngest captain that
the ANBU has ever had.
Well, in any event, I shall
assign my personal ANBU
agents to this new team.
Does this mean you're
going to be transferred
to Lord Danzo's ANBU?
It remains uncertain.
Well, try not to get
entangled in the higher-ups'
political wrangling.
Captain Kakashi...
Thank you for the
past two years.
Come on, now. You're
only changing sections.
You're still a
Hidden Leaf shinobi.
It's not like you're going
somewhere far away.
He's only thirteen...
And they're already
appointing him
to be a captain?
Well, he is an
extraordinary shinobi.
Sure, he has the
Sharingan, but making
captain at thirteen is
simply unheard of.
What's up, Yugao?
Beginning today, I'm being
assigned to Team Ro.
So you're the new
replacement, huh?
I will do my best,
Captain Kakashi.
All right, attention!
I expect exemplary
work from all of you.
Yes, sir!
I've gotten reports
that the Leaf Police
Force is strengthening
their armaments.
So tell me, what do
you make of this news?
Among the Uchiha,
dissatisfaction towards the
Village is running high.
Seems we can't
ignore it anymore.
No...
You are aware of the
barrier system that the
Leaf has in place?
Yes, sir. It senses
when the Village
has been infiltrated.
It seems that someone's been
getting through the barrier.
And they've also been
doing so undetected.
Even among the citizens of
the Hidden Leaf Village,
only a select few
know the secret code
to pass through
the barrier.
Either there's a traitor in
our midst, or a jutsu user
who can break the barrier
without alerting us.
If the intruder's a traitor,
we can smoke them out
with a new jutsu formula.
But I believe it's someone
capable of passing through
the barrier with a jutsu.
I can't bring myself
to believe that...
The new mission I'm
assigning you is to look
into this matter...
That is a map of the
barrier placements.
Some areas have more
pings than others.
Where is this?
Near the Uchiha District.
If it were possible,
we'd install a barrier
system there, but
it's a self-governing
district so we can't.
Make sure your
investigation isn't traced
back to the ANBU.
Hm...
Listen!
There's no way I'm gonna
lose to a guy like you!
Keep talking nonsense.
Hey, shut up!
No, you shut up, you loser.
[sigh]
Curious finding
you here.
What brings you
to the Academy?
My new appointment.
I'm a jonin leader,
in charge of some genin.
So you're gonna look
after a few genin, huh?
Yeah, but I have to say, I'm
a bit worried about the kind
of students I'll be getting.
Don't act so
stuck up, Sasuke.
You are seriously annoying.
I told you to shut up!
[laughter] I bet students
like those are gonna
be hard to handle!
Hey, come with
me, would you?
All right! You
wanna spar?
Let's just take a walk.
Hey, wait a minute. This
is the Uchiha District.
This part of town
has character.
Been a while since
I was here...
I used to come
here quite a bit...
...long ago.
Hey, look! Now that's
a rice cracker shop
with real character!
[kissy noises]
Hey.
What're you doing?
Come on. It's way past
our rendezvous time.
So is this
house special?
It's nothing.
These rice crackers
are seriously tasty!
They're worth making the
trip all the way down here!
There are other specialties
you can only find here, too.
Oh! You've
gotta show me!
What is this place?
Nakano Shrine, home of
the Uchiha's patron deity.
I don't believe in
stuff like that...
Look, just be
a good sport!
Go take a fortune
for yourself.
Captain Kakashi!
Itachi!
What are you doing here?
Just thinking about
something from the past.
And you?
Well, I'm from here,
Captain, you remember.
I'm often here.
How's being captain?
It's the same.
I still have missions just
like the ones I had before.
I see...
Hey, Kakashi, check it out!
The fortune I drew is
"Excellent Luck!"
I'm sorry, there's not
enough intel to figure out
who the infiltrator
is or what he wants.
Hmm...
We would need to place
agents at each section of
the barrier system
and we would have to
coordinate their efforts with
those of the barrier team.
Without anti-infiltration
tactics, it'll be almost
impossible to track
down the culprit.
Unfortunately, we can't
spare the manpower for an
operation such as that.
Well then the only thing we
can really do is ask the
Police Force to step
up their patrols.
What's bothering you?
It's just...
I went down to the
Uchiha District recently.
It was the first
time in a while and
the atmosphere
had changed.
It was tense.
Were they antisocial?
Yes, they were. It felt to
me like they didn't want to
have any outsiders
there whatsoever.
Yes, I see. Well, I'll
discuss the Leaf Police
Force with the
executive committee.
You completed your
mission, Kakashi.
How convenient.
On the pretext of village
security, we'll have a brand
new patrol unit created.
We'll switch security duties
away from the Uchiha's
Police Force and
reduce their strength.
No, that will only provoke
the Uchiha Clan further.
We should make the Police
Force oversee the patrols
and increase their
workload to show
our good faith.
Why, when we should be
stopping their coup d'état,
would you want to increase
the Uchiha's power now?
I won't let the
Uchiha stage a coup!
Of course we won't!
That goes without
saying, doesn't it?!
Calm down, both of you!
We're still uncertain if
there will be a coup at all!
We should just bide
our time and see how
everything pans out.
Isn't that why we have
Itachi in the first place?
Isn't Itachi coming today?
He's off on a mission.
The Uchiha Clan intends
to revolt against
the Hidden Leaf.
[gasps]
You're sure of that?!
You've obtained
concrete proof?
I have...
Hey.
There is something
that I would like you
to help me with.
We won't let the
Uchiha stage a coup.
That's one thing, at least,
that the two of us can
undoubtedly agree upon.
[sigh]
Wait, we haven't
reached a conclusion!
If the Uchiha are getting
ready to act, then we're
going to have to make
our preparations, as well.
Preparations
only, Danzo.
[grunt]
We move tonight.
Fine. I shall assist
you as promised.
Very well, then.
I'm counting on you.
I'll help you annihilate the
Uchiha because I have
another goal.
And for that...
I want you to keep
your "eyes closed."
So I'm not to use my
Sharingan against
whatever you're
planning?
Yes, and I guarantee that
I won't kill your little
brother. I have no use
for a child without
the Sharingan.
You think that that is
supposed to reassure me?
Although, at this point,
I have no other choice
but to trust you.
If you need refuge,
join my organization.
Your organization?
The Akatsuki.
It's an Emergency
Alert, Level One!
Get ready to
move out! Hurry!
Who are you?!
We're moving out!
Those on my team to the Leaf
Police Force Headquarters!
My team, to the
Uchiha District!
This is horrible!
What happened?!
Rescue anyone who
still remains alive.
Lord Third!
There's a survivor!
Get him to the
Medical Unit!
No one else made it.
Take away all
of the corpses.
I mean every single one.
Search the buildings, too!
Who do you think could
have done something
as monstrous as this?
Itachi Uchiha.
Itachi?!
Itachi Uchiha harbored
a secret about his
clan: he despised it.
That is why he killed Shisui
and took his eyes for his
own, and also why
he caused infighting
among his brethren.
And in the end...
He committed this atrocity.
But why would he?
That's enough chatter.
Now get to work!
It would appear that
this settles everything.
What does it settle?
Are you really not able
to see the huge problem
that we're still left with?
I consider it minor.
Hear me, Danzo, I can't
allow you to act on your
own authority anymore.
You are now relieved of your
duties as second in command.
Listen, Hiruzen,
I did this for-
What, "for the
good of the Leaf?"
The Uchiha Clan was
a part of the Leaf!
Your ANBU and Foundation
will be dissolved. And
later, I'll deal
with you personally.
Till then, you're
under house arrest.
Lord Danzo, the body
count doesn't match up.
What's that?!
It's like they just
disappeared.
I witnessed everything.
And I will
continue to watch.
If you so much as touch
Sasuke, I'll pass on
classified Village intel
to every enemy nation.
Itachi...
If this is the scope
of Itachi's hatred,
it ran deep...
Only one of
them survived...
Start removing them.
Yes, sir.
What a mission,
even for the ANBU.
Hm?
What's up with him?
Uh... [grunt]
[laughter]
Hey!
The entire clan
was wiped out...
Not quite all of it...
The rumor I heard is
one child survived.
What's the difference?
The Uchiha Clan is
essentially extinct now.
All except one.
I never imagined that
Itachi Uchiha would be
put in the Bingo Book.
S-class right
from the start.
Well, he did slaughter
his entire clan.
Hey, what's the
matter, Captain?
It just goes to show
in the end, I really
knew nothing about him.
I understood nothing...
What'll happen to
the Uchiha District?
Will it be torn down?
Torn down?
Well, a terrible incident
took place there.
No one'll want to go
near it after everything
that's happened.
Obito, what have
I been doing...
...since that day?
I know you have something
that you want to say to me.
We are quite alone here.
I appreciate your
discretion.
First, you have
my thanks.
Your actions averted
civil war within the Leaf.
We've maintained
peace despite all odds.
Yes...
But even so, I sincerely
regret that there was no
other way to achieve it.
I apologize, Lord Third.
I'm the one who should
apologize. You will be
branded as a Rogue
Ninja who killed his
whole clan and be
listed in the Bingo Book
as a fugitive,
wanted dead or alive.
Of course.
What will you do now?
I've found aid from a
group named "Akatsuki."
I intend to stay close to
them in order to make sure a
promise is not broken.
You're going to
join the Akatsuki?
Lord Third, will you make a
promise to me that you will
continue to protect Sasuke?
Your younger brother will
study at the Academy and
will grow up to become
a Hidden Leaf shinobi.
I'll ensure that he
wants for nothing.
But I doubt that I can erase
the hatred that he is bound
to harbor for you
once he learns what
you have done.
I know. I am prepared
to bear his hatred.
Now, then go, I'll
leave the jutsu
formula for the barrier
unchanged, so if
you ever worry
about Sasuke.
You can sneak back
in to check on him.
Lord Third, I...
It is very unfortunate that
the Uchiha Clan did not
understand your compassion.
That wasn't it. I'm afraid I
was simply too weak...
That is what precipitated
this tragedy.
I'm thinking of undertaking
a complete overhaul of
Danzo's Foundation.
And also turning my
attention to my ANBU.
In addition to that,
we're going to need a
new Leaf Police Force.
Instead of sticking to one
clan, let's have an open
recruitment for
the Police Force.
We must think of the Leaf's
future, and find the right
person for the right job.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Tell me this, Kakashi.
How many years have you
been in the ANBU so far?
I joined during the
Fourth Hokage's tenure,
so about ten years.
Originally, Minato's
purpose in having you join
the ANBU was to help
you deal with the
darkness inside
your heart.
He also wanted to
keep you close to him.
I kind of figured that.
Then when Minato
died, I resumed the
position of Hokage.
And I took Minato's ANBU
under my command.
However...
I do not believe that
keeping you by my
side is going to be
of any help to you.
In fact, it will only
darken your heart.
Please remove your mask.
Ten years, you say?
Yes, perhaps I have
asked too much of you.
You are hereby relieved of
your ANBU duties and will
assume a new position.
Yes, sir.
You'll become
a jonin leader!
[gasp]
What?!
There's no way I'll allow
people who can't work
together as a team
to become shinobi!
All of you fail! You're
going back to the Academy!
That icy glare of his. In
the depths of that gaze
lies darkness itself.
The darkness has not yet
been driven from his heart.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Jonin Leader."
It seems he
needs more time.