ITACHI: My foolish
little brother.
SASUKE: Wow, Itachi.
You nailed every
target, even the one
in the blind spot
behind the rock.
All right.
Now it's my turn.
-No, Sasuke.
It's time to go.
-What happened to the
new shuriken jutsu
you promised to teach me, huh?
ITACHI: It'll have to wait.
I have an important
mission tomorrow.
I must prepare.
SASUKE: You're such
a big, fat liar.
-Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
-Ow!
OK, just watch this.
-Hey, be careful!
SASUKE: Ah Ow!
[music playing]
-How come the one who
twisted his ankle is
the one who's laughing?
Or maybe you were
just looking for a way
to get out of walking home.
-That's not it.
I just can't stop
thinking about how
I'm going to start at
the academy tomorrow.
Now I'll finally get
the chance to catch up
to you, big brother.
[music playing]
-Itachi, have you
made up your mind yet?
If you haven't, then we will be
forced to take action instead.
-No, please wait.
I need more time.
-It will be too late
once the players
start to make their move.
The situation's extremely dire.
ITACHI: I realize that.
I shall settle this
with my own hands.
FUGAKU: What?
Do you know what
day tomorrow is?
I don't really think you
understand your position.
-I'm setting out on
a mission tomorrow.
-What are you talking about?
-I can't tell you that.
The mission is covert.
-Itachi, you also serve as
the Uchiha clan's pipeline
to the village nerve center.
You know that, don't you?
-Yes.
-Well, make sure
you don't forget it.
You will be at that
meeting tomorrow.
SASUKE: Father only
cares about you, Itachi.
-You probably hate me, huh?
It's all right.
People often think
ill of shinobi.
It's only logical.
SASUKE: That's not how I feel.
-Being the best isn't all
it's cracked up to be.
When you have power, you
become arrogant and isolated
from the world, no matter
how coveted and sought
after you are in the beginning.
But with us it's different
because you and I
are flesh and blood.
I'm always going to be
there for you, even if it's
only as an obstacle
for you to overcome.
Even if you do hate me.
That's what big
brothers are for.
YASHIRO: Is Itachi in there?
Come here.
We need to talk.
-What's wrong?
What are you all doing here?
YASHIRO: There
were two people who
didn't show at
yesterday's assembly.
-Want to tell me why
you weren't there?
You're in the ANBU
black ops now.
I know full well you
can be called away
at the drop of a hat.
And that's the case
your father was
trying to make when we
asked why you weren't there.
-But we're not him, so you
won't get any special treatment
from us.
-I understand.
Guess I should have
been more careful.
Will that be all, gentlemen?
-Yeah, sure thing.
But you know what?
Before we go, there's
just one other thing.
Know anything about
Shisui Uchiha?
He killed himself
in Nakano River.
-It's funny.
If I remember correctly,
you kind of looked up to him
like an older
brother, didn't you?
-How terrible.
Forgive me.
I haven't seen him
at all recently.
What a tragedy.
-Yeah.
Well at this point,
the police force
sees no other
choice but to launch
an all-out investigation.
-What?
-This is a note
Shisui left behind.
We've already had
it fully analyzed.
There's no question
this is his handwriting.
ITACHI: But if it
wasn't homicide,
why the investigation?
-It would be no great
feat for someone
who possesses Sharingan
to copy his handwriting.
YASHIRO: The most
talented of all our clan,
feared as Shisui the Teleporter.
He was a man who would do
anything, take any mission,
if it was for the
good of the clan.
-Hard to imagine a man like
that throwing everything away,
don't you think?
-You shouldn't
judge by appearances
or by your own
preconceptions, either.
-We'll leave that
with you for now.
Take it to ANBU black ops
and put in a request for them
to start sniffing
around on this, too.
ITACHI: Understood.
-Let's just hope we get
a lead on this soon.
ITACHI: Why don't you
just come out and say it?
You believe I had a
hand in this, don't you?
-Yeah, that's
right, little punk.
[fighting sounds]
-Like I said before,
appearances and preconceptions
aren't going to
tell you anything.
For instance, you've
made the mistake
of assuming I'm a patient man.
The clan, the clan-- you
overestimate your own abilities
with no idea of the
depth of my own.
And look at you now,
grovelling in the dirt.
-Shisui had been keeping
an eye on you recently.
The strangeness of your behavior
happening during your time
at ANBU couldn't get overlooked.
What are you playing at,
you filthy little wretch.
-Obsessed with the organization,
obsessed with the clan,
obsessed with our lineage.
A worthless compulsion
that enslaves us.
All it does is limit
our capabilities.
And that, in turn, leads us to
fear what you don't understand.
FUGAKU: Stop it, Itachi!
That is enough.
What on earth is
the matter with you?
Itachi, you've been
strange lately.
ITACHI: Nothing
strange about me.
I have my own duties
to fulfill, that's all.
-So why didn't you
come last night, then?
-To reach the next level.
-What are you talking about?
-I have had enough of this.
There's no hope left
for this pathetic clan.
The people of this
clan are all the same.
You focus on the
trivial and lose sight
of what's most important.
Change is impossible in
this fog of ignorance.
How can we evolve
when regulation
is the only thing
we've ever known?
-Such arrogance!
-That's enough.
If I hear one more
word of this nonsense,
I'll have you
thrown behind bars!
Well?
What's it gonna be?
-I can't take this anymore.
Please, sir, just
give me the order.
SASUKE: Big brother!
You have to stop!
-I'm not the one
who killed Shisui,
but I apologize for the
words I have spoken.
I'm truly sorry.
-Well, I guess he has
been pretty tired lately.
Up to his ears in missions
from the ANBU black ops.
-But Captain.
FUGAKU: ANBU are under the
direct control of the Hokage.
Even if you wanted to
arrest one of them,
you would need to
get a warrant first.
As for Itachi, I take full
responsibility for him.
You've my word.
-Very well, sir.
-Inside, Itach.
MIKOTO: Itachi?
I'll just leave your food here.
I know you're busy
with work, but I really
wish you'd join us for
a meal once in a while.
-Thank you, Mother.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I shouldn't have
stayed to practice
with my shuriken.
Now I'm totally late.
What was that?
I could have sworn
there was someone there.
What is this?
Oh, no.
Father and Mother!
-Big brother!
Father and Mother are
both-- I don't understand!
Just who could do
something like this?
-My foolish little brother.
Mangekyo Sharingan.
-He's a worthy son.
-All our father ever
talks about is you.
-No!
Stop it!
Itachi, why are you
showing me all this!
Why?
Why did you do this?
Itachi, why?
-To test the limits
of my ability.
SASUKE: To test your ability.
That's why you did this?
You're telling me that that was
the reason that you butchered
every single member of our clan.
-It is of great importance.
-No.
This isn't like
you, big brother.
It's not.
-I have acted like
the older brother
you desired for one
reason-- because I wanted
to discover how
powerful you were.
I needed to find
a worthy opponent
to test the limits
of my own abilities.
You have that unique potential.
Now I've made you hate me.
Now you have the
desire to defeat me,
which is exactly why I'm
going to allow you to live.
Don't you see?
It's all for my own benefit.
Just like me, you may be
one of the few people who
are able to use
Mangekyo Sharingan.
However, there is
one big catch to it.
Take the life of
your best friend.
You must kill him.
Kill him just like I did.
-You're saying that
was you, Itachi?
You killed Shisui?
-I did.
That's how I
obtained these eyes.
In the main hall
of Nakano Shrine,
underneath the seventh
tatami mat from the far right
is the clan's secret
gathering place.
There you will find
a secret document,
an explanation of the
Uchiha clan's jutsu.
It tells of the visual
jutsu's true purpose.
If you discover
how to activate it,
you will be the third person
to obtain the Mangekyo
Sharingan, including myself.
To ensure that happens, that's
enough reason to let you live.
Oh, don't worry, Sasuke.
You're not worth killing.
If you wish to kill me one
day, in hate and revenge,
surviving in such an unsightened
manner as this, by all means,
flee.
Cling to your wretched life.
And then, one day, when
you possess the same eyes,
come back and face me.
[music playing]
How much can you see it with
those Sharingan of yours?
SASUKE: How much can
I see with these?
What I'm seeing right now,
Itachi, is you dead at my feet.
-You see me dead, do you?
Well, then, go on,
make it happen.
-Chidori.
Chidori spring.
-You have gotten strong.
-Listen close, Itachi.
I have one final
thing to ask of you.
[music playing]
-The exact same words as
before, and the crows, as well.
Starting with your favorite
genjutsu farce, huh?
-So what do you want to know?
It won't be the last thing, but
I'll hear what you have to say.
-Let me try this again.
-Genjutsu.
SASUKE: I have one
last thing to ask.
You hear me, you bastard?
Answer my question.
The pain in your chest
won't stop until you do.
-You deliberately
avoided a vital spot.
-Remember what you said?
-If you discover
how to activate it,
you will be the third person
to obtain the Mangekyo
Sharingan, including myself.
To ensure that happens, that's
enough reason to let you live.
-The third one, the other
one with that Sharingan,
who in the Uchiha
clan obtained it?
-But why?
Why do you even concern
yourself with such a thing?
-I'm going to go
kill him after you.
That is why.
-Kill him?
-Back when you slaughtered
our entire clan,
you mentioned the
existence of another.
The other Uchiha
that you didn't kill,
he must have been a
co-conspirator because even
you couldn't have taken down
the Leaf Police Force alone.
-So you figured it out.
SASUKE: Who is it?
-Madara Uchiha.
-With that vision of
yours and a chakra
more ominous than my own,
you're the spitting image
of Madara Uchiha
from the elder days.
-Never heard of him.
Am I supposed to care?
-Madara Uchiha.
ITACHI: One of the
founders of the Hidden Leaf
Village, the man who first
awakened the Mangekyo
Sharingan.
[music playing]
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
Madara Uchiha--
the only man who
was able to uncover
the other secret of
the Mangekyo Sharingan.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
If it's Madara,
one of the founders
of the Hidden Leaf,
he should be dead by now.
Who could believe
a story like that?
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
Madara is still alive.
Whether you choose to believe
that is entirely up to you.
SASUKE: Next time--
"The Light and Dark
of the Mangekyo Sharingan."
ITACHI (VOICEOVER): Let
me tell you a little bit
about the past.