"The Two Mangekyo"
Zetsu...Why are you still
clinging to Obito?
Forgive me...But doing so
allowed me to steal the Nine
Tails' other half from these
guys.
Good. Now bring it, and my left
eye, to me.
[gasp] I sense Sage Power...And
it's even stronger than what
Obito possessed...
So the Fourth Hokage's Nine
Tails is inside that black
thing?
Madara?! How'd he get Six Path's
power?!
[gasps]
[gasp]
Since Lord Madara is here, now,
you can't do anything to
me...Even if I do separate
myself from Obito.
Damn it!
Now, Kakashi!
[grunting]
[heavy breathing]
Why you-! You're still-?!
Not yet...
I need to ask you something,
Madara.
Huh?
Hold on. We need the Nine Tails
inside that thing.
We can't afford to miss.
We have to wait for the right
moment.
Tell me now...What am I to you?
[chuckles]
You have to be kidding, right?
What kind of a stupid question
is that? You have always been
only one thing to me.
You are Madara.
[heavy breathing] Now go on.
[heavy breathing] Until the
time when I will be revived...
You shall be...
Madara Uchiha.
You see, Madara is defined as he
who rejects this world.
All who hold that thought in
their heart,...and strive toward
achieving the Infinite
Tsukuyomi,...are Madara.
That was...
That was once my path, too.
I left you in charge, everything
in your hands.
And let you walk in my shoes,
while I slept the eternal sleep
waiting to return.
It's the exact path I guided you
toward.
You were supposed to live out
your life as Madara to achieve a
mutually agreed upon goal...
...as the savior who rescued
this world.
This world laid out by the Sage
of the Six Paths...
...has failed.
Listen...
The chakra Six Paths dispersed
was meant to be a linking
power,...
...something that would connect
the mental energies between
people,
so all could understand
each other's hearts
without words,...
...and would lead to peace and
stability.
The one who preached this as
Ninshu, the Shinobi Creed, and
sought to guide the people
forth,
was the Sage of the Six Paths.
And yet...
Before long, time after time,
people used chakra, not to
connect with others,...
but, only to link the mental
and physical energies within
themselves.
Through a method of infusing
one's own chakra and increasing
it manifold...
...they changed chakra into
ninjutsu that could be used as
weapons in battle.
Whic, ironically, meant
reverting things back to the way
Six Paths' mother, Kaguya,
originally used chakra.
Exactly what in the hell is he
talking about, anyway?!
Gaara...
Yes, I know.
The Sage's actions ended up
merely furthering the human
paradox.
And even of some bonds were
established...All they really
learned...was that true
understanding wasn't possible.
Either way,...chakra only gave
rise to conflict...and false
hope.
We know the reality all too
well...Even as we seek peace, we
seek war at the same time.
And this reality...compels
infinite suffering via the power
known as chakra.
Power only leads to a desire for
conflict. And the lack of power
leads to losing everything.
But I shall create a new world
that will overcome that!
The Infinite Tsukuyomi will
produce a dream world without
any abominable chakra!
And I, as the person who
possesses the most powerful
chakra, will lead it!
You are me! Madara himself! Not
Obito!
Obito Uchiha,...with his Uchiha
Chakra,...challenged Kakashi
Hatake,
sought the title of
Hokage, and yearned for
Rin Nohara!
But because his power was a
deception,...he ended up losing
everything!
This entire world is hell! Have
you forgotten that?!
[gasp]
Just come over here.
Yes! You, come over here,
Madara!
Starting today, you will be the
savior.
You are still the
savior, even now!
Sand Wave!
Kamui!
Sage Jutsu!
[gasp]
Rasengan!
[grunt]
[thwap,  groan]
[gasps]
[groans]
No...! No way, even their
combined attack was...
And now...
[groan]
[gasps]
Why you damned...!
What are you doing?!
No...
What I'm doing's no different
than a okage's actions.
More, in fact.
For I can truly bring about
peace.
There's no need to voluntarily
walk a rugged path...
And step over comrades' corpses.
It's the exact path I guided you
toward.
What I want to know isn't the
shortcut or the easy path...
I left you in charge, everything
in your hands. And let you walk
in my shoes.
A Hokage walks ahead of everyone
else, enduring their own pain,
no matter what.
Those who truly lead others...
...would never step over their
comrades' corpses...Even if
their own ends up being stepped
upon.
Well then, in order for you to
confirm that's true, you're
going to have to become a
corpse.
I  won't let you step on me
anymore.
I know now that letting someone
use your name and handle things
for you...
isn't the same as
truly entrusting them with
the task.
I am not you!
[gasps]
[heavy breathing]
Go for it, Obito!
Become Hokage and show me just
how you're gonna save the whole
world.
And that's another promise for
you to keep!
The current me is...
...the one who wanted to be
Hokage, Obito Uchiha!
[heavy breathing]
Obito...
Obito...You've finally found
yourself!
[grunt]
[gasp]
I passed through...
That's your original right eye's
power...
Are you really trying to extract
the Tailed Beasts and thereby
weaken me?
How could you possibly think
that you could win against me?!
[grunting]
You're so weak...
You were only able to grab a
small piece of One Tail and
Eight Tails!
[grunting]
Quick, Kakashi! Take Naruto to
our Time-Space!
Obito plans to hand him the Nine
Tails there!
Kamui!
[gasp]
I know that your body
materializes when you
teleport...
If I try to teleport carelessly,
he'll come after me.
My transfer speed's too slow.
Since, at one time, he'd been in
Sage Mode, he was able to steal
some Sage Power from me along
with the Tailed Beast chakra.
[gasp]
[deep breath]
Madara...could have killed me
at any point back there! I was
so terrified that I completely
forgot to breathe!
Compared to everyone else,...
he's on a whole other level!
I've transported Naruto. So all
that's left is for you to send
yourself there, and Naruto can
be saved, right, Obito?
[chuckle] Oh, damn it.
You're still talking down to me.
And acting so superior...
Just like old times.
Hey, Obito!
Rin's here to pick you up for
the fair!
Oh! Sorry, Rin!
I can't wait to see what my
great-grandchildren will look
like, Obito.
Grandma! I'm only five years
old!
Come on, hurry up! It's about to
begin!
Whoa!
It's the kunai they're giving as
a prize!
Wow, it's so cool!
[clapping]
Okay, great! Thanks for showing
us what you can do! I wonder
what kind of ninjutsu we'll see
next?
Ha!
If that's the competition,
this'll be easy!
Up next, Obito Uchiha!
That's me!
[cheering and clapping]
You can do it, Obito!
So what is it you're going to
show us today, Obito?
I'll be doing Fire Style:
Fireball Jutsu!
Wow, impressive! Well, let's get
right to it, then!
Here goes!
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
[clapping]
Six points! Seven points! Seven
points! Those are some solid
numbers!
It looks like Obito Uchiha is in
the lead, right now!
[clapping]
[laughing]
That was great, Obito!
[chuckle]
I wasn't really in top form
today,...but I think it'll still
be good enough to get me the
win!
Now, here's our final
competitor!
Kakashi Hatake!
What are you going to
demonstrate for us today,
Kakashi?
How about the Earth Style: Mud
Wave?
Whoa...! That jutsu requires a
lot of chakra.
Will you be all right?
[scoff] Yeah, Mud Wave, at our
age? Gimme a break!
Earth Style! Mud Wave!
[gasping and crying]
It's unanimous! A perfect ten!
And the winner is Kakashi
Hatake!
[clapping and cheering]
[growling]
Sorry, Obito. That's too bad.
Kakashi...Hatake!
[panting]
Youre late, Obito!
We've all been waiting!
Sorry! On the way here, this old
guy needed help and I-
Kakashi!
Kakashi's gonna come abd play
with us today!
Why don't we play kick-the-can?
Yeah, sure! Let's play!
[panting]
Kakashi's the only one left.
Nobody can run as fast as
Obito...
Hey! Come help us out, Kakashi!
No prob', I'll catch him in no
time!
Whoa!
Huh?!
What-?!
Saving my friends, no matter
what...That's my Ninja Way.
[grunt]
Wow...!
[huffing and puffing]
Want me to be "it" for a while?
As if!
[slurping]
You were "it" the whole time,
Obito!
But he still couldn't catch
Kakashi even one time!
Yeah, Kakashi's amazing!
Oh! My mother's here!
Obito, I have to leave, now.
Me, too!
See ya later!
Well, I win again.
[growl]
But I'll commend you for one
thing...
You're the only person, up 'til
now, who never chickened out.
Harrumph...You're just a show
off!
Hey! I just said something nice
to you!
It's my dad!
See ya!
Yeah...See ya...!
[gulp]
Hey, Grandma...? Am I more like
my mom? Or my dad?
Well, let me see...You're like
both of them!
Huh?
You are alive because of your
parents. So you must honor them
both and make sure you work to
help others.
Right!
Oh man, oh man, oh man! (exhale)
This is the one day I can't be
late!
[panting]
This is so exciting...Hey, can
we go check out that place
later?...Hey, I can't wait,
either...
[inhale and sigh]
You're even late to the entrance
ceremony?!
[growl]
Someone like you has no business
being in the Academy at all.
You'll fail out.
It's okay.
Huh...?
Since you weren't there, I
picked this up for you.
[gasp] For me?
Yeah! Just submit this packet
and you'll be able to enroll!
Wow, thank you! You're a
lifesaver!
You know, if you keep pampering
him, then he'll never get over
his tardiness.
Hey, shut up! You wanna fight?!
Say that again!
What?! Why I-
It's your own fault!
[chuckle]
What did you say?!
Stupid Kakashi!
That Kakashi Hatake! I'm gonna
take him down and become the
Hokage no matter what happens!
[chuckle] That's the spirit!
[chuckling]
Whoa!...Yeah!
[growling]
Ha!
Wow, I can't believe
this!...Kakashi-
Wow, Kakashi's really in a
league of his own, isn't he?!
[growl]
What a dummy! He challenged
Kakashi and got his butt kicked
again!
As if the class loser could beat
the class star!
[gasp]
Hey, Rin!
Someday I'll awaken my
Sharingan,...and then I won't
lose to him anymore...
Kakashi hasn't been coming to
class at all lately.
Yeah, I know...I heard something
bad happened to his father.
Oh...
I think he's going through a
difficult time right now...
After that,...you skipped a
grade and quickly left the
Academy.
Back the,...if I'd noticed the
emptiness that engulfed your
heart...Perhaps our destiny here
and now might've been different.
I don't know if I ever fully
realized...how deeply the death
of your father, Sakumo,...had
changed you...
Hey, Rin, you seen much of
Kakashi lately?
Why do you ask?
I heard some guys talking about
him yesterday. And it wasn't
very nice.
And the last time I
saw him, he seemed to
have changed a lot, too.
Do you think...?
Do you know something, Rin?
Uh, no...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Formation of Team Minato"
Well, okay, Obito! See you
tomorrow!