I truly detest... you both.
Hagoromo...
Hamura...
My two children...
You are now mine.
(Zetsu)
My role has come to an end.
You shall return with me to the
almighty god that is mother.
Why you...
The two of you on your
own aren't all of
shinobi history, you know!
And besides that, moms should be
happy their kids are leaving the
nest!
That's what being
a mom is all about!
(Zetsu)
So your teen rebellion
continues.
Mother is the very
progenitor of chakra.
You brats can't hope to
accomplish anything.
We need to create an
opening so we can launch
the Sealing Jutsu, got it?
I know. And the only thing
that'll work... is that jutsu!
♪
"That" jutsu?
Yeah...
Sasuke, just hear me out.
(Zetsu)
I don't know what you're
scheming, but Mother can absorb
any and all jutsu.
Your actions are meaningless.
(Kakashi)
Well...?
It looks like they're just
staring each other down.
I see...
...The power to forcefully drag
us all into this dimension
that's not genjutsu...
It's a totally different scale.
(Kakashi)
She's like... a god.
So what's your plan? How are you
going to fight her, Naruto?
I know that this could
be our last hurrah...
But we gotta give
it our best shot.
Just like we've been
doing all along, right?
[small grunt]
Are you serious?!
We won't know unless we try it.
Look, I'm telling ya, I've been
secretly practicing this jutsu
even more than the Rasengan, ya
know?!
Hey, it's worth giving
it a shot, isn't it?
Well, if there's even a chance
that it'll create an opening...
...then I'm game.
I'll get my left eye ready.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Amaterasu!
They're attacking!
Take this!
(Naruto)
Sexy Jutsu!
(All)
Reverse Harem Jutsu!
(Thinking)
These sexy-type jutsu tend to
work better the stronger the
opponent.
(Thinking)
That idiot!  Using a jutsu like
that in this situation?!
That might work on me, but
there's no way that jutsu will
work on such a god-like person!
(Thinking)
It worked!?
You may be the progenitor of
chakra or whatever, but I'll bet
you've never seen a jutsu like
this!
The history of shinobi,
is this , ya fool!
(Thinking)
The number one most
unpredictable...
Don't tell me that Naruto's
Pervy Ninjutsu is going to
save the world!
I believe Naruto is the
Child of Prophecy...
...the one who is destined
to save the world.
I guess that... he's kind of a
throwback from the viewpoint of
the Leaf's Shinobi Way...
...but he's actually quite
endearing, being more like me
than Minato...
(Thinking)
Are you watching, Jiraiya
Sensei?!
Naruto, now!
All right!
[attack cries]
(Thinking)
It's cold! What's going on?!
[ice cracking]
[gasp] It's all changed!
This place... did
we shift dimensions?
Naruto, whose jutsu's effects
are we seeing now?
Huh? Well, uh... I
think that it's...
It feels the same as
when we were taken to
that lava world before.
I'm sure this is our
enemy's ability.
To rewrite the world in an
instant and make it reality.
This really is
just like genjutsu.
And we're in an ice
world this time?!
Why bring us here?
(Naruto Thinking)
She vanished!
(Sasuke Thinking)
This ability. Can she move
across dimensions?
[gasp]
[gasps]
[ice cracking]
Why that-!
Amaterasu!
Flame Control!
Nice.  Thanks.
And, Sasuke... sorry that my
Sexy Jutsu didn't work.
Humph. Yeah, well...
it's not like I really
expected it to work.
We're doing it
my way this time.
Help me.
[gasp]
(Zetsu)
Mother. These guys are
such a bother.
Why not split them up already...
and take each of them on
separately?
[gasps]
Huh? Argh!
[grunt]
[gasp[ Where am I?
(Naruto)
Sasuke...!
[grunts]
[exhausted gasp]
No...!
(Zetsu)
Now you can't seal Mother away.
First, I'll absorb
all of your chakra!
[gasp]
Nice reflexes.
Not good!
I gotta find Sasuke!
(Zetsu)
The child's quite fast.
So I guess I don't know
where she'll strike from.
[;large crash]
[gasp]
What the--!?
[thunderous crash]
[gasp]
[grunt]
Could it be... that we were
the only ones who were
brought to this world?
No, My real body is around
here somewhere, too.
But, I can't sense Sasuke here.
[weak grunting]
Where are we?
Obito!
Kakashi!
I thought that I had died...
You're okay.
I healed you.
Naruto...
Although...
Yeah, right.
I know that.
[gasp] What happened to Madara?
Did you get him?
No, it ended up
way different.
I can explain it really easily.
Plus, I can tell you all about
the Sage of Six Paths and
Kaguya.  And about the seal,
too!
I don't know what happened,
but... you didn't stop the
enemy yet, right?
So take me to where
the fight is.
You can tell me on the way.
I can't sense Sasuke right now.
And my real body's
feeling all tingly.
So it might be really
dangerous over there!
I don't know if we're only gonna
be in the way or if we can be
useful to you.
But I don't want us to fail
'cause we weren't there when we
were needed.
And besides, if we don't take
down this Kaguya, then our
world's gonna be done for
anyway.
So the few of us who are still
left have to do whatever we can.
We've already prepared
ourselves,... haven't we?
(Kakashi)
We're all ready to die.
[panting breaths]
Nothing seems to work...
(Obito)
It's hard to believe.
So you're saying both your and
Sasuke's powers are necessary in
order to seal away this Kaguya?
That's right!  But like I said
earlier, I can't sense Sasuke
now!
The ice is moving.
[explosion]
I'm over there!
[gasp]
[grunt]
[grunt] She's merged with
nature!
[scream]
(Sakura)
Naruto...!
She's finally showing herself!
What's happening now?
[gasp]
(Thinking)
That's a type of Time-Space.
[grunts]
Argh, damn it!  It's no good!
(Thinking)
Okay, I've made it look
like I'm trapped...
(Naruto Thinking)
I'll just wait until she gets
closer-then attack!
You said that you suddenly
stopped sensing Sasuke?
Yeah.
I suspect that he was taken
to another dimension.
She emerged from a different
Time-Space.
It's similar to my
Visual Prowess.
Can you get in?
If I resonate my Kamui the next
time she connects and opens a
portal to another Time-Space,
I'm positive I can enter it.
If Sasuke is there, I can bring
him back to this dimension.
All right! Then for now I'll go
and support the real me.
But...
[gasp]
I'll need an enormous amount of
chakra,  since it's not my
Time-Space.
If my chakra runs out, I'm done.
Then I'll go with you...  I
mean, the real me isn't gonna
down that quickly.
I'm strong.
Your Clone Chakra
won't be enough.
Would it still be inadequate
with my 100 Healings Chakra?
That would give me the minimum.
You two, come with me.
Okay.
We don't know if Sasuke is in
that Time-Space.  But we'll
start by entering her lair.
I promise to find Sasuke, and
get him to the real you.
Obito.  I want to thank you for
helping me out.
I really mean it.
And for helping Sasuke.
No, there's no need to
thank me. Just watch our foe.
So, no more masks, huh?
I am... Kakashi's friend, your
father's subordinate, an Uchiha
just like Sasuke, and
A Hokage is the one who walks
ahead of everybody else,
enduring their own pain.
There's no shortcut to becoming
Hokage! And no ways out for
anyone who does!
And the way he forges ahead...
draws others to him.
You want to reach out
when he stumbles.
(Obito)
I... I am your senior, who
shared the same dream as you.
I'm not going to waste time on
speeches.  I'm almost out of
time.
But I just ask that you let me
walk in front of you and...
...die for you.
(Minato)
Sorry I'm late.  Have you
learned anything yet?
There's no one here.
...Just... the lower half
of Madara's body.
If we've found part of Madara's
body just lying about, then is
it safe for us to assume that
he's dead now?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Well, either way, it looks like
he managed to complete it, his
Infinite Tsukuyomi.
Though it doesn't seem to
affect us dead folk...
Lord Fourth, how'd things
go at your end?
I tried to free some people by
chopping off a branch of that
tree that had wrapped around
them, keeping them
trapped in the jutsu.
But they didn't awaken.
And instead...
...another branch just whipped
down and wrapped them right back
up again.
So it was the same for you...
In order to confirm Madara's
status and learn what
happened...
we should use his lower half to
revive him with the Reanimation
Jutsu.
Then we'll make him talk.
But we need a living
sacrificial victim for that!
How can you still be so naïve?!
There's just got to
be another way...
[gasp]
You know, you truly are a very
kindhearted soul...
...previous reincarnate
of Ashura.
And who are you?
I'm Hagoromo, founder of
Ninshu, the Ninja Creed...
...also called the
Sage of Six Paths.
♪
(Hashirama)
The Sage of the Six Paths?!
(Hagoromo)
In order to save Naruto and
Sasuke, who at this moment are
battling against my mother
Kaguya, you must know everything
that has occurred before now.
Before I talk about Ashura and
Indra, I must first explain the
origin of Ninshu, the Ninja
Creed.
(Hashirama)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Ninshu: The Ninja Creed."
(Hagoromo)
It was a few thousand years
ago...
♪