[music playing]
[water running]
-Oh, could he be--
[snoring]
-Hm, Sakura, no!
You've got it all wrong.
I wasn't peeking,
I-- I swear to you!
-Naruto!
-Uh, uh, uh--
-Didn't I tell you, Naruto--
-Ow, ow, ow-- Sakura,
I can explain.
[screams]
Oh, it's morning.
[yawn]
I don't feel like I got any
sleep last night at all.
Hm?
What, he's up already?
[sigh]
Huh?
[gasp]
Sai's stuff is gone!
That snake, where did he go?
-Naruto, good morning.
-Ca- Captain Yamato, that
jerk Sai isn't in our room.
-Sai is outside.
-Eh?
-I'm glad I caught you.
I have something I
need you to do for me.
-Huh?
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
SAKURA: Oh-- so,
you're an artist, huh?
-Is there something you wanted?
-For someone so
rough on the outside,
you're pretty sensitive.
[laugh]
What do you know?
-There's that fake smile.
I really hope you're not
thinking of punching me again.
Are you?
-I haven't decided.
Oh, I'm only playing with you.
I was just curious
about your artwork,
thought I'd take a peek.
-I see.
-I would have thought
that a place like this
would have you
drawing a landscape,
but this is an abstract.
What are you going to call it?
You have a title?
Or are you still working on it?
-Don't know.
-What do you mean?
You have to have a name for it.
Come on, now.
I'm sure you have
something in mind.
You can tell me.
I won't laugh.
-It wouldn't even occur to me.
-Huh?
-I've drawn tens of
thousands of pictures,
but I've never
titled any of them.
Why should this one
be any different?
-Hm?
But that's what you do
with pictures, isn't it?
Like, if it's a portrait, you
name it after the subject.
Or with other
pictures, you title
it to convey the thoughts,
feelings, and emotions
you felt while
creating the piece.
[music playing]
-The truth is, I couldn't
really title any of my drawings,
even if I wanted to.
-Huh?
-Nothing comes to mind.
I've never really felt
anything, anything at all.
[music playing]
-Well, that figures.
I wouldn't expect
such a heartless
bastard to have feelings.
Captain Yamato sent me
over to round you guys up.
We're moving out.
-OK.
-Ha, whatever.
That drawing's nothing special.
-Yes, you're right.
Just like what's between
your legs, right?
-Huh?
Ah, that's it, I've had it.
I hate you.
And if you've got a
problem with me, pal,
then drop that stupid
fake smile of yours
and tell me straight to my face.
Anytime you want to
fight, I'm ready.
Oh, you want to go?
-Problem?
I have no problem with you.
-Huh?
-I don't feel anything
toward you, good or bad.
[music playing]
You can go ahead, without me.
I'll catch up as
soon as I've packed.
-Here, let me help.
This isn't a
printed copy, is it?
Did you draw this, too?
-Yes.
-Wow, your own picture book.
That's so cool.
-Hm.
-Oh, hey, would you mind
if I took a look at it
while we're on the road?
-I do, actually.
It's just-- I haven't
finished it yet.
Anyway, I'm sorry, I don't
show it to other people.
-Oh.
-It belongs to my older brother.
-I thought he said
he drew it himself.
-What's he talking about?
[music playing]
FEMALE VOICE: Thanks so much.
You come back, now.
-Well gang, how we doing?
Everyone getting along?
[chuckle]
-I'm so sick of this guy.
-Maybe you'd like me to resort
to more draconian methods.
[growl]
[whimper]
-Don't worry, Captain.
We're really starting to build
up that old report, you know.
[laugh]
-Well, you're certainly in a
better mood now, aren't you?
-You're not serious, are you?
He's obviously faking it.
SAI: Really?
-The best way out of a tough
situation is a smile, isn't it?
You said so yourself.
Don't you remember?
-Oh yes, that's right.
[giggle]
[laugh]
-Hm, ha.
[wind blowing]
-I've never really
felt anything.
I don't feel anything
toward you, good or bad.
YAMATO: Well, I guess
it's about time.
-Hm?
Is there something the
matter, Captain Yamato?
-This way.
-Huh?
-What?
YAMATO: Hurry up.
-OK, we're coming.
[music playing]
-What are we even doing in here?
-Hm--
[scream]
Captain Yamato,
what's the plan here?
The path we were on was fine.
Where are we going?
Captain?
-Lady Tsunade told
you, I'm sure.
-Hey, what are you
guys talking about?
YAMATO: The information Sakura
got could actually be a trap.
[gasp]
-There's a possibility that the
Akatsuki are just playing us.
Tenchi Bridge could be
nothing but an ambush.
Naruto, they could
be after you here.
[gasp]
[music playing]
-No way.
-I don't think it's
really all that likely,
but still, you can
never be too careful.
We'll keep hidden
as much as possible
until we reach Tenchi Bridge.
NARUTO: Right, you got it.
[crickets]
-Well, this spot should do.
-But--
-What do you--
-All right, let's pack
it in here tonight.
-Say what?
If you really want
to set up camp,
then we should backtrack
to that cave we passed,
instead of lying in
the open out here.
-OK everyone, step back.
Wood Style, Four-Pillar
House jutsu!
[gasp]
[moan]
-We'll camp out here tonight.
-Boy, I don't know.
Can you really
call this camping?
-Whoa.
[laugh]
[music playing]
-Whoa--
-Cool.
-Man, look at this
place, will you.
-It's so spacious.
-Oh boy, I can't
wait to see what
our rooms are going to be like.
Huh?
Welcome, Team Kakashi.
[chuckle]
What the--
SAKURA: I didn't think it
would be so bare, though.
-Well hey, it's better
than sleeping outside.
-That's true.
[sigh]
-Time to kick back.
Now, if we only had a bath.
-Hm?
Is there something you want?
[grumble]
-Ha.
Not from you, pal.
[music playing]
[sigh]
[banging]
-All right, gather
around, everyone.
Sakura, there are few
things I need to know.
-What about?
-Everything regarding the
Akatsuki member Sasori.
-Sasori--
[music playing]
-I wanted to bring
it up sooner, but I
promised we wouldn't talk about
stuff like that yesterday.
I need you to tell
me everything now.
You're the only one who's
ever seen him and lived
to tell the tale.
-Yes, sir.
-I received his file from
the Hidden Sand Village,
but it would help if you
could fill in the blanks,
like his personality or speech
pattern, even mannerisms
or quirks.
-Why do you need
to know all that?
-The spy hidden in
Orochimaru's ranks
expects to rendezvous
with Sasori.
They might catch me
right away, but I'm
going to try to approach
them in disguise.
-But if Sasori is a
no-show at the bridge,
the spy might not
reveal himself.
-Absolutely, that's a
distinct possibility.
NARUTO: Than this will
all have been for nothing.
-Working as a spy always
entails a certain amount
of risk and danger.
I think our target will
definitely have their guard up.
-All right.
So then, you'll be the one
to transform into Sasori.
-That's the plan, yeah.
He would always hide himself
within this Hiruko puppet,
so it really should be me.
Remember, I'm master of
the wood style ninjutsu.
-You're right.
-Oh, and one more
thing-- since there's
a slight chance this is a
trap, I'll approach on my own,
at first.
-Go to the Tenchi
Bridge in the village
hidden in the grass 10
days from now, at noon.
-Why, what's there?
-One of Orochimaru's henchmen
is working for me as a spy.
And that's where I'm supposed
to rendezvous with him.
However, I don't think a--
-The way he was talking at the
end-- I really don't believe he
was lying to me.
And besides, the
Akatsuki had a spy
named Yura in the
Sand Village, as well.
[gasp]
[music playing]
-I just want to play
it safe, is all.
You three will hang back
and wait for my signal.
-Either way you look at
it, one thing is certain.
This spy is likely to be
strong and quite accomplished.
[music playing]
-Maybe, but so are we.
[wind blowing]
[crickets]
-Now then, let's get to it.
Shall we?
The devil's in the details, so
here's the mission from A to Z.
Our one and only goal
is a live capture.
The target must not be killed
or injured, no matter what.
If they are, we lose our
only source of intelligence.
This will be more difficult than
simply taking out the enemy.
The mission is a delicate one.
That's why I'm taking
the lead, but you guys
are to be ready as back-up.
The strategy is simple.
I move in and
restrain the target.
If that should fail, and I
enter into a combat situation,
we move to plan B. That's your
cue to enter into combat mode.
You'll enter on
my signal, alone.
Should that second
scenario come to pass,
we'll be using the buddy system.
-Huh?
Buddy system, how do you mean?
-Every warrior's action will
be covered by their partner.
The watchword,
people, is teamwork.
Make sense?
-Oh yeah, I remember now.
[laugh]
Yeah--
-What is wrong with you?
-So, here's how
we'll be pairing up.
Sakura, you and I
will be on one team.
And, of course, Naruto and
Sai will make up the other.
[music playing]
-You expect me to work with him?
[theme music]
-You jerk, do you know
what a comrade is?
-I could explain it
for you, if you like.
NARUTO: That's not what I meant.
-You know, you really
shouldn't blame others
for your own lack of competence.
NARUTO: Say what?
SAI: It's not easy
to fight while you're
covering for someone
who has lost his cool.
All I did was size up the
situation, make a decision,
and act.
-I'll never acknowledge you.
-Hm, I wonder what
Sasuke would have done.
NARRATOR: Next
time, "Simulation."
[music playing]
[bells]
-Hi there, everyone.
Today, I'll be giving you an
overview of the Five Great
Nations.
The Five Nations
are the countries
in which the powerful
hidden villages preside.
For example, the
Hidden Leaf Village
is found in the Land of Fire.
And here, in the Land of Wind,
is the Hidden Sand Village.
The Hidden Stone
Village is found
in the Land of Earth, the Hidden
Cloud in the Land of Lightning,
and the Hidden Mist Village
is in the Land of Water.
Five in total-- these make up
what we call the Five Great
Nations, whose powerful leaders
earn the title of Hokage.
Collectively,
these men and women
are known as the Five Hokage.
Let's test your knowledge.
Which headbands belong
to each village?
You all know this, right?
[beeping]
Let's have a look.
So, did everyone
out there get it?
For those of you
didn't, you have
got a lot of studying to do.