All right! We've
cornered him!
This is what I come back
to after regaining
consciousness...
[gasp]
What's that?!
You are indeed strong,
Pakura Sensei.
Maki?
Pakura Sensei?!
Come on! Let me out!
I've had it! I'm done! I'm
completely fed up! I'm gonna
explode any second now!
Hmph!
You okay with that?!
Please, we've got you
sealed with Lightning
Style, exactly so
you can't explode.
So just shut your trap!
Face it, you're nothing
but a dud!
There's are no such thing as
a dud when it comes to art!
No way, he's gonna explode?!
What's happening?!
What's this?
Dan!
I know... It looks like
someone has succeeded.
Hm?
Naruto! The Jinchuriki are
gonna quit it! Looks like
Itachi did it!
[chuckle]
Thanks, Itachi!
We better get out! Time
for us to quit it!
Zip it! Come on!
We have to go!
Tell Ohnoki...
He must secure the future of
the Allied Shinobi Forces!
Only then can he
come and tell me
all about it...
What the hell
is going on?!
I see... It looks like
the bookworm has been
taken out...
It was a dud... don't
scare us like that!
Bang!
Nothing I do is a dud!
True art...
...is indestructible!
Scaring us like that...
[gasp]
Granny Chiyo!
It seems at last I am
free of this cursed spell.
Pakura Sensei!
Maki, make sure you
don't die in vain!
Sensei...
You all have a future
to look forward to...
Looks like I can
finally die now...
Granny Chiyo!
Kankuro!
I entrust you with the
Puppet Master techniques.
I gladly accept....
Granny Chiyo.
Now there's no need to
play possum anymore!
As I expected, it seems
that I'm able to move my
body freely now.
Can you undo the
barrier, Choza?
It's safe now.
It looks that way...
Hey! We don't need
the barrier now!
Yes sir!
Choza, please forgive me.
Those signs. Ghost
Transformation Jutsu...
I understand. Please, go on
ahead and hurry to Lady
Tsunade's side!
This jutsu that has killed
so many shinobi...
I never imagined that it
would come in so handy in
a situation like this!
Ghost Transformation Jutsu!
It's just as I thought!
Souls ascending after
release from the Reanimation
Jutsu are able to be
controlled with this
jutsu as well.
However, it doesn't seem
like you have a lot of time.
So you'd better hurry!
Yeah...
Farewell, Choza! Thank
you for everything!
Wow. How cool! He flew
away just like a ghost!
What is the Ghost
Transformation?
It allows one to become a
living ghost who can then
possess and kill an enemy.
Normally, that is.
Tsunade...
Reform is absolutely
necessary for the
future of our village.
It is the only way to
minimize the loss of life.
I know. You're right.
Please, help me
with it, Tsunade!
Yes, whatever you need.
What I really need is you.
Dan...
Let's make all our
dreams come true!
Yes.
Our dreams as shinobi.
What is this?
What's going on?
Chakra from all the
Reanimated Shinobi is
fading rapidly!
Reports are flooding in.
From every battlefield!
The reanimated are all
turning back into souls.
Even the sealed ones.
And the ones still fighting!
The only way to explain
all of this is that the
Reanimation Jutsu has
somehow been released.
There's no mistake. The
Reanimation Jutsu has been
dispelled.
Quick! Relay this
information to every
company!
HQ reporting! The
Reanimation Jutsu's undone!
I repeat... The Jutsu
is undone!
Amazing! They're all
just disappearing!
Good, but... Which
company managed to
pull such a thing off?
You don't ever have
to forgive me.
And whatever you do from
here on out, know this...
No matter what, I will
love you always.
I...
Yugito...
Yagura...
Han...
Utakata...
Fuu...
Old bearded guy!
Just leave this to us!
They're all gone...
Then this means that the
other battles are...
Curse Kabuto. He
has failed.
Hey, what do you think
you're looking at, huh?
Did you forget already?
You're fighting me!
As well as the
Noble Blue Beast!
It looks like the
Reanimation Jutsu
has been released.
And...
What of it?
What is that? That light
coming from him?
The Susano'o is gone and the
debris from the Reanimation
is swirling in a whirlwind
around him...
Without a doubt, this means...
Yes, it would appear that
the Reanimation Jutsu has
been released.
What?! It has?!
But how? We haven't even
located Kabuto yet...
It's too soon!
Even if Kabuto was
found... To be able
to stop this jutsu...
Who could have done it?
It doesn't matter! Whoever
did it is a hero who saved
the Shinobi World!
It seems the heavens
haven't forsaken us yet!
It appears that you
have able shinobi on
your side, too.
It can't be helped...
He planned for this?!
Stay on guard!
He's planning a final strike
before he disappears!
So watch out!
Fire Style: Dragon
Flame Caterwaul!
Water Style...
No, it won't be in time!
[groaning]
Lady Hokage!
I'm all right!
[gasp] The 100 Healings
Jutsu has worn off!
But...
...we've won...
Damn it!
What just happened?!
I thought that she had
completely lost
consciousness!
I couldn't move
anymore, so how?
It's been a long
time,Tsunade.
It's me.
Dan... But how
are you here?!
The Reanimation Jutsu
has been undone.
I used my Ghost
Transformation Jutsu
to fly here.
Although... that sure
was a close one!
But Dan...
You haven't changed,
Tsunade.
I... I've always
tried to honor your-
There's no time.
We can't wallow in
sentimentalities. 'Cause
I have to go soon.
But, please, Dan...
Who ever said it was a
shinobi's duty to watch his
comrades die one by one?
I love this village and
the people in it with
all my heart.
I want to protect them.
The person that
protects everyone.
To be Hokage,
that's my dream.
Dan! For a long time
after your death,
I kept running from all my
memories of you.
But I've changed so much
since then, and now...
All of your regrets. The
dreams you left behind.
I can make up
for everything!
I've even become
the Hokage!
But still...
Thank you, Tsunade. But
please, don't worry.
You're fulfilling my
dreams just fine.
But it really seems that
I've caused you a lot of
pain, haven't I?
Sorry...
I'll be waiting for you on
the other side. But don't
come too quickly, okay?
For you, are my dream.
I was able to protect
you in the end...
So it appears
something good...
...did come from
being reanimated.
Hokage, you all right?!
Your vitality has
returned... Did you
receive chakra?
I got to see an old friend
for a little while...
Well, you'll be with
them again soon enough.
But what?! What is going on?
Madara's chakra, which had
started to separate from
his body, is now
clinging fast to it.
He's still reanimated?
But how? Why won't
he disappear?!
I thought the Reanimation
Jutsu was undone!
The Reanimation Jutsu
is a jutsu that summons
back the dead.
There is only one risk to it.
What risk?
As long as they know the
correct signs to weave, a
reanimated Shinobi...
can actually rescind
the Reanimation Jutsu's
Summoning Contract
from their end.
They can rescind
the contract?!
And when that happens, you
end up with the biggest
problem of all.
An immortal body and
infinite chakra, on the move
without any way to
control or restrain it.
You don't mean...
Tell the jutsu caster to
never use a Forbidden
Jutsu like this carelessly!
Reanimation Jutsu, release!
What is a clan?
What is a village?
What is a shinobi?
What am I?
Ha! Found ya!
[chuckle]
It's you two...
That's right. But what're
you doing here, anyway?
Putting a stop to the
Reanimation Jutsu.
Huh?!
You've always been like
this, you know that? You
never really feel the need
to explain things in
better detail, do you?
Look, it's been a while
since we've seen you,
so just tell us what
you've really been doing!
Heh?
What?
It's Kabuto...
Kabuto was the one who cast
the Reanimation Jutsu.
But how?! How is
this possible?!
Your ridiculously juvenile
jutsu cannot hold me back.
Don't you get it by now
after fighting me for all
this time?
Now, then. You have seen
the Perfect Susano'o...
And everyone who lays eyes
on it dies, or so they say.
I'm almost embarrassed to
have to do this again. I
already used it once, but...
My interest has waned
thanks to the interference.
So perhaps I ought to go and
retrieve Nine Tails instead.
What?
Please, let all of us deal
with this Madara! I swear
we'll finish him off!
Rest assured and
leave this to us!
No!
Lord Tsuchikage! I'm sorry,
but this is beyond us! We
cannot stop him.
We still have to fight him!
We must stop him right here!
How pitiful you are.
Lightning Cable!
Guy!
Right!
Take this! Pinky Attack!
[attacking yell]
[chuckle] What's wrong?
You don't look too happy!
What do you mean?
Well, you're hiding your
face, so all I can really do
is take a guess at it.
If you're actually calm
under there, take off that
stupid mask and prove
it to me! Ya fool!
[chuckle]
Nice going, Naruto!
[sigh] I told him not to
aggravate the man.
I have no choice...
I have to use this.
What is that?!
Uh, looks like a giant
gourd and a jar...
I would have preferred
bringing it back in a
completed state, but...
It is only a fragment, but
it is not lacking in power.
It's taking too long. And
now's the time!
We found something
incredible in one of the
hideouts. Take a look at it!
This is it! The all-knowing.
I need to get out of here to
meet up with someone. I'm
leaving.
Huh? Meet who?
Orochimaru.
What are you talking about?
You killed Orochimaru!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Orochimaru's
Return."
Are you surprised that
someone as tenacious as
him might not be dead?