- So,
the girl has bodyguards now.
I never imagined
that the Hidden Leaf
would reach her so quickly.
- Even so,
there's only four of them.
I say we get rid of them
and take the forbidden jutsu
from the girl.
-Don't be so impatient.
- What's the plan going to
be, then?
- That forbidden jujitsu is
worth far more than money
to every one of us.
We cannot afford to fail.
During the last Great Ninja
War, that jutsu
revealed its unbelievable power.
If we can just find a way
to get our hands on it,
we could go from a
little band of thieves
to powerful lords
of our own domains.
- But the people
from the Hidden Leaf,
could they have the
forbidden jutsu?
-It's unlikely.
The previous Hokage
and En no Gyoja
forged a secret treaty to
protect it at all costs,
so the Leaf wouldn't keep it.
They're merely fulfilling
their obligation
to keep the jutsu safe.
- Still, if they were entrusted
to uphold that treaty,
then they must be very skilled.
Do we really want
to mess with them?
-Yeah.
And they'll probably
call reinforcements, too.
- Nango, Benten,
are you planning on losing
the fight before it even begins?
- I always thought it
was just your face,
but your head's got
something wrong with it, too.
-What did you say?
- Just think about
all the possibilities.
Use your head.
-Enough with the fighting.
We are a team.
Don't you forget that.
None of us are expendable.
It's been our unity and
our combination jutsu that
have kept us alive through
these difficult times.
-All right.
- There's no need to
rush into anything.
I already know
their destination.
They're headed to the hideaway
of the Tsuchigumo clan,
and the best part is,
once they drop the girl there,
they'll simply
leave on their own.
-OK.
But won't there be trouble
if they enter the village?
- Akaboshi, you still don't
understand human nature.
To us, that forbidden jutsu
is treasure beyond compare.
But to everyone else,
it's nothing but a nuisance.
[theme music]
[crash]
- What the heck did
you do that for?
-That's what I wanna ask you.
Just why are you
guys following me?
-What do you mean?
We're here because
we're your bodyguards.
- How many times do
I need to say it?
I don't need any bodyguards.
I'm able to protect
myself just fine.
So, all of you Hidden
Leaf ninja can leave now.
NARUTO: Look, we can't just
say, oh, OK, bye, and leave.
HOTARU: Why not?
Really.
Please.
I don't want you
bothering me anymore.
NARUTO: It's not bothering.
It's called guarding.
YAMATO: Oh, well.
I guess we'd better just
do as she says and leave.
-What?
How come?
-We have no choice.
- Just wait here a
second, would ya?
-Are you sure?
the enemy could
still be close by.
-Don't worry.
-Hm?
Hey!
OK, then.
I guess we're gonna
get going now.
-Fine.
[scream]
-Get it off me!
Get it off me!
-There.
It's gone.
-That... that was horrible.
What was it?
-A mountain leech.
There are actually a whole
lot of them around here,
so they just come raining
down on you all the time.
-Raining down?
NARUTO: Yep.
Well, see ya.
Be careful out
here all by your...
What the heck you do that for?
-Please, Naruto.
Stay with me?
I could never touch
anything as gross as that.
I can't.
It's simply impossible.
If it's going to rain
leeches, can you
please stay and block
them, Naruto?
- But you said you
didn't need a bodyguard.
- Just until we get
out of this forest.
-I don't know.
It's a tough call.
-Please, Naruto!
Please!
-I guess I could.
If you want.
- You know,
now that I think about it,
I guess Utakata
would probably still
be my bodyguard if all you
Hidden Leaf guys hadn't
shown up and taken over for him.
-Utakata?
You mean the guy that does
that weird bubble jutsu?
- He's the man that
I consider my master.
I hope I can become
as strong as he is.
Well, someday.
-Hm.
Your master, huh?
I'm not sure there's such a
thing as a good master, really.
I mean, look at my master.
The guy's a perv
and a scatterbrain.
And boy,
does he get carried away.
Then again, when it comes to
being a ninja, he's way strong.
And he's also dependable.
And above all, kind.
Well, I guess you just can't
judge a book by its cover.
And if I could, I wouldn't
mind becoming a ninja like him
someday.
That's for sure.
- Seems to me that you like
your master a lot not, Naruto.
- Who'd like an old
pervert like him?
- Somehow, I must become
as strong as Utakata.
Because if I can,
I can master the jutsu
that grandfather left to me.
And then, perhaps I could even
restore the Tsuchigumo clan
to greatness.
- For someone so
young, you sure are
carrying a lot of
responsibility.
Hey, so where do you
think that master of yours
ran off to, anyway?
-Don't know.
And for some reason,
every time I call him master,
he gets very upset with me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sai, what
is it with all these leeches?
- You can stop with
the leeches now.
- So, I guess the leeches
aren't big enough, then.
That's not it.
OK.
-Enough is enough!
[screaming]
-What are you doing, stupid Sai?
Get a clue!
My gestures couldn't
have been any clearer!
-Oh, boy.
- At last, I'm back to
my vagabond lifestyle,
traveling the world.
She'll be OK.
That guy can protect her.
But that chakra... naw.
It couldn't be.
-You need immediate attention.
We'll take you to our fort.
- Looks like no one's
coming after me.
And my wounds have healed.
So I guess it's time to leave.
- Please, you must accept
me as your student.
-That fight.
After seeing you fight, I have
great respect for you, master.
-Master?
-That's right.
Master Utakata.
-Don't ever call me that again.
-Huh?
But...
-Don't ever call me master!
-I...
- I have no intention
of taking on a student.
-Utakata... you forget.
You owe me for my hospitality.
Do you think it's OK to
just lounge around here
and get free room and board?
Well, fine!
What would you like for
your free meal today, sir?
-That was a cheap shot.
I guess you're not afraid
to hit where it hurts.
- Well,
I had to get your attention.
Tonbee told me to
say that if you
refused to take me as a student.
-So he was in on this too, huh?
Hotaru,
the thing is you haven't had
any kind of training at all.
-I have.
I've received numerous
ninjutsu lessons from Tonbee.
- Then why don't you
go study with him?
-Because it's not enough.
That's why I'm asking you.
-OK.
Let's see you walk on
that water over there.
-Walk on water?
Fine.
I will.
[scream]
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): Good grief.
At this rate, I'll be long gone
before she learns anything.
-Utakata!
Utakata!
Look!
I did it!
See?
- You... you've been
practicing all night long?
-Yes.
Now will you make
me your student?
-No.
Uh,
that was just the first step.
The next is the jutsu.
Water Style, Raging Waves.
-Amazing.
- If you can't handle that
jutsu, you can't be my student.
-It's a deal.
Water Style, Raging Waves.
Water Style, Raging Waves!
Nothing.
But why?
- I'm afraid that
jutsu can only be
done if the wielder
possesses water chakra.
Don't take it personally.
It's raining?
-Utakata, I got it.
-What are you doing?
-Please, watch this.
Water Style, Raging Waves!
I did it.
So you'll make me your
student now, right?
-Well... I... I can't.
Not yet.
-Wait!
Utakata!
- I figured you'd come to
see me sooner or later.
-You're damn right.
What were you thinking,
putting that kid up to that?
She's out of her
depth, and you know it.
- That's why I want
to ask you a favor.
Would you consider staying
here and acting as a guardian
to keep Lady Hotaru safe?
-Amazing.
You ask that is if
it's no trouble at all.
- Lady Hotaru is a
child of destiny.
Judging by the way you
handled those men back there,
I can tell you're a man
of extraordinary skills.
Above all, you're not greedy.
As you can see,
I'm too old now to defend her.
But if she becomes
your student, I
know her life will be
safe in your hands.
So please,
won't you do me this favor?
-I'm sorry, but I just can't.
As I'm sure you've
noticed, there
are men who are pursuing me.
No matter where I
go, death seems
to follow close at my heels.
How could you even think
of leaving her with me?
-You may be right.
- Besides, the bond
between master and student
is nothing to put your faith in.
Master!
What are you trying to do to me?
Master?
No!
[scream] I guess I dozed
off there for a bit.
Hm?
-What do you think?
Could we really become
lords of our own domains?
-Of course we could.
Isn't that right, Akaboshi?
-That's right.
So even if we just
sold that jutsu,
we'd still have enough money
to live the rest of our lives
in leisure.
-What?
What's wrong?
-Be on guard.
There's somebody nearby.
-There!
What was that?
-What is going on here?
[laughter]
-Who the hell are you?
- Doesn't look to me like
he's one of the Hidden Leaf's
reinforcements.
- Maybe this guy's
after the jutsu.
-Hm.
Sinceyou know about
the forbidden jutsu,
that means you must
be the band of thieves
who infiltrated the fort.
Makes me wonder, is that
jutsu really so impressive?
'Cause if so,
maybe I do want it for myself.
- I suppose you think we're
just going to let you take it?
-So what do we do about him?
-Idiot.
Kill him.
After him!
What is this slime?
-I can't see!
-Spread out!
We'll surround him.
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER):
This chakra flow...
their movements have
suddenly become much faster.
Barrier jutsu?
-Let's go.
-Shin!
-Fu!
-Jin!
-Rai!
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER):
That's just great.
-It's over.
Just how long do you
intend to follow me?
-What are you talking about?
You told us to stay till
we got through the forest.
-Yes, I did say that, but.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The thing is,
the only thing between
the fort and the hideaway
is this forest.
-You're still here?
- Well, it looks like we'll
complete our assignment
without incident.
-Huh?
Whoa.
The village is right there.
So weird.
There's no one here.
Hey!
Hello?
Anyone here?
-Look sharp.
-Got it.
-Hey!
Lady Hotaru's back!
Doesn't anyone want to
come out and see her?
Huh?
Hm.
Wait, I know what we can do.
-Wait.
Naruto!
Oh, boy.
[ringing]
-Emergency!
A big fire!
Emergency!
[ringing]
-Ah-ha!
So you were here!
-What is she doing here?
-I don't know about this.
[whispering]
- Sorry if I scared everyone,
but since all you guys
were hiding away, I had to
do something pretty drastic
to get you to come out and
welcome Lady Hotaru back
to the village.
Sorry about that.
[whispering]
-What?
What's the problem?
-Ah.
Hotaru.
HOTARU: Uncle.
- Thank you for
bringing her here.
I'm the one responsible for
the welfare of this village.
Lord En no Gyoja
instructed me on what
to do if Hotaru
were to come here.
Your job is done.
You can leave the rest to us.
-Very well.
Then we'll be on our way.
-Stay a moment, if you would.
We haven't had a chance
to thank you properly.
YAMATO: We appreciate
your thoughtfulness,
but we left the teammate at Mt.
Katsuragi, and would
like to get back to her.
-Very well.
Although that is unfortunate.
-Come on.
Let's not keep Sakura waiting.
-Oh.
OK.
-Naruto?
-I...
-You'll be fine.
-Thank you.
-What's the matter, Naruto?
- Sorry, Captain
Yamato, but I think
you better go on
ahead without me.
'Cause I've gotta go
back to that village.
-Go back?
- Something about
that place bugs me.
I can't stop thinking
about the way
those villagers looked at her.
-Naruto!
Wait!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can't
leave her there alone.
[theme music]
NARUTO: What do you
mean Hotaru is gone?
Where did she go?
YAMATO: Naruto.
Don't.
NARUTO: But something might have
happened to one of their own.
Why aren't they looking for her?
YAMATO: There's no
point in arguing.
In any case, finding her
is our top priority now.
Sai.
SAI: Understood.
I'll scout the area right away.
NARUTO: Next time
on Naruto Shippuden,
The Successor's Wish.
Just hold on.
We'll find you.