[music playing]
-Hm.
You seem fine.
Good.
You're cleared to leave
the hospital today.
-By any chance, this
isn't because you
want me to hurry up and get
my baggage out of here, is it?
[snoring]
-Well, yes.
There's that too.
-That fool Naruto
has been camped out
in this hospital
for days, just so he
can resume training
the minute you recover.
-Actually, I was kind of
hoping I could take it easy
and recuperate at
home for a few days
before getting back into
it, but since I've run out
of reading material
anyway, I suppose
I might as well start
his training again.
-Hm.
That's the spirit.
NARUTO: Rasen!
I won.
So now, so now, you
owe me Ramen for life.
-Hey, you idiot, wake up!
-Hey, there, ugly.
Huh.
-What'd you say, Naruto?
[theme music]
-OK.
Time to get to work.
[giggling]
-What's so funny?
-Oh nothing.
It's just been so
long since I've
trained with you,
Kakashi Sensei.
I don't know
exactly why, but I'm
feeling really good about it.
-Is that right?
[laughing]
-Laugh it up while
you can, Naruto.
-Huh?
-Time will not
stand still for us.
As I told you at the hospital,
the goal of this training
is to create an ultimate
ninjutsu for you,
one that is uniquely
your own, a jutsu that
goes beyond the Rasengan.
In order to do that, you'll
need to master two techniques,
how to change your
chakra's nature
and how to change its form.
-How to change my chakra's
nature and change its form.
-Huh.
OK.
I thought maybe you could
handle two things at once,
but I guess I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
One thing at a time.
We'll start with changing
the chakra's form.
-Right.
Got it.
KAKASHI: Do your
Rasengan for me.
-Sure.
No problem.
Are you ready?
Let's do it.
Rasengan!
-OK.
OK.
Stop.
-Huh?
-There you see.
You've already mastered
the change in chakra form.
-Huh?
-Your Rasengan has seen to that.
-My-- it has?
-Compressing your
chakra into a sphere
and then making it spin like
crazy at blinding speed, that's
a change in form if
ever there was one.
In fact, your Rasengan carries
the technique to an extreme.
-So then, I've already
passed the first part.
-Mhm.
That's about the size of it.
-Woohoo!
-Now then, the next step is
the change in chakra nature.
OK.
Let's take the
Chidori for example.
This is a jutsu that
requires accomplishing
both a change in the chakra's
form and a change in its nature
simultaneously.
Watch carefully.
First, I concentrate the
chakra in my right hand.
Then I change the
nature of it, so it's
like an electrical current.
-So that's the change in nature?
-Exactly.
And now, I change
its form so that it
will discharge at whatever
range and level I determine.
-Whoa.
-That's the secret.
In order to move
beyond the Rasengan
to an even more
powerful jutsu, you'll
have to learn how to execute
a change in chakra form
and a change in chakra
nature like with the Chidori.
-Piece of cake.
I'm already halfway there.
All I got to do is add this
change of nature thingy
to my Rasengan, and
bingo, ultimate ninjutsu!
-Listen, Naruto.
I'm afraid it's not
quite that easy.
It's not something
you just add on.
And anyway, you don't
know how to do it yet.
I bet you don't even know
the nature of your own chakra
as it is right now.
-Huh?
It's got a nature.
--[sigh] Well, I kind of figured
it might be difficult making
you understand all this.
OK.
Listen very closely.
There are five basic
types or natures
of chakra-- fire, wind,
water, lightning, and earth.
The five great nations
took their names
from these five chakra natures.
They are the foundation of all
ninjutsu and the foundation
for everything we
learn as shinobi.
-Whoa!
I had no idea.
-Most everyone's
chakra falls under one
of these five natures.
For example, members
of the Uchiha clan
have fiery natures, which is why
they excel at Fire Style Jutsu.
Wind nature leads to Wind
Style Jutsu, and lightning
to Lighting Style,
like the Chidori, which
is, of course, a
Lightning Style Jutsu.
-Wait.
So that means that
someone like Sasuke
has two natures going for
him, both fire and lightning.
-That's right.
Whereas right now,
you don't have any.
We don't even know which nature
you're predisposed to yet.
-What?
So we're going to find out,
using these slips of paper.
-How are we going to do that?
-If you have a lightning
nature like me,
the paper will wrinkle.
If you have wind
nature, it tears.
A fire nature will make it burn.
A water nature, the
paper becomes wet.
An earth nature, and
it crumbles away.
These are litmus papers
that react to chakra.
They come from a
special kind of tree
that grows by absorbing chakra.
Just let your chakra
flow into this paper,
and we'll find out what
nature you possess, Naruto.
-OK.
[deep breath]
[ripping]
-Well, now you know.
Your chakra nature is wind.
-Wind, huh.
-It's a chakra nature
that's perfect for battle.
It can rip and sever almost
anything in its path.
-Oh yeah.
I knew it.
I'm unstoppable.
-Hold your horses.
We've only just
figured out what it is.
Now comes the hard
part, learning
how to properly use and
control your nature.
-Let's do it.
-The problem is normally it
would take an incredible amount
of time to really master
this technique, time
that we don't have.
But the good news is I
think I've hit upon a way
to shorten our training
time considerably.
-Awesome.
-The one way to do that is to--
-Huh?
NARUTO: Captain Yamato.
What are you doing here?
-Kakashi thought my special
expertise might be of use.
He asked me to help
you with your training.
Sorry.
I hope I'm not interrupting
anything, Kakashi.
-No.
Not at all.
I was just about to--
-Hey, Captain Yamato, which
one of the five natures
does your Wood Style
Jutsu fall under, huh?
-Huh.
Well, you see--
-He may be a little unfocused,
but at least he's enthusiastic.
Go on.
Go ahead tell him.
-Right.
Well, Earth Style.
Rampart of Flowing Soil.
-What the--
-Water Style.
Waterfall Basin Jutsu.
-Waterfall.
Cool.
-You see, Naruto, I possess both
earth and water chakra natures.
-Huh.
You've got more
than one of them?
-Eventually, when you get
to be a jonin-class ninja,
you generally have two or more.
There are other natures I
can use besides lightning,
you know.
-So that means
Captain Yamato really
has three of them,
including his Wood Style?
-No.
No, that's not
quite how it works.
-It isn't?
-Earth and water natures are
the only ones that I can use.
You see, technically,
Naruto, there
is no such thing
as a wood nature.
-Then how did you do that?
-By combining the other two.
By activating the earth and
water natures simultaneous,
he's able to create
something new, a wood nature.
-Earth with my right
hand, water with my left.
-Amazing.
-When one possess
two chakra natures,
it's not that difficult to use
each of them independently.
To be able to activate and use
both of them simultaneously.
Well, that's a different story.
-This ability to activate two
chakra natures at the same time
in order to create a new nature
is known as Kekkei Genkai.
I think you may have heard that
term somewhere before, right?
You remember our battle
with the one called Haku?
-Yeah.
-Good.
Well, Haku had a Ice
Style Kekkei Genkai.
He was able to manipulate water
and wind changes in chakra
simultaneously to create ice.
He could perform
such a special jutsu
because he was of a clan that
possessed that Kekkei Genkai.
-Haku too, huh?
-That's why I couldn't copy
his jutsu with my Sharigan.
-Really.
Then, what about Shikamaru's
Shadow Possession Jutsu
and Choji's Expansion Jutsu.
And what about Medical
Ninjustsu and Genjutsu.
How do they work?
-To explain all that to
you would take more time
than we got, it would probably
only end up confusing you.
-Hey, uh, Kakashi, I'd save
the discussion regarding
the yin and yang of chakra
nature until next time.
-Huh?
Yin?
Yang?
What are those?
-Good point.
Forget it.
You wouldn't
understand now anyway.
[laugh]
[groan]
-So where were we
before we got off track?
-Huh.
Oh yeah.
You said you knew a way
we could cheat and skip
the training time.
-Reduce the time, not skip it.
-Yeah whatever.
OK.
So how do we do it?
-How we do it is--
how we do it is--
-How?
How?
-Through Multi-Shadow Clones.
-Huh?
-Yes.
Multi-Shadow clones.
That's the secret.
-The secret to what?
-To significantly reducing
the amount of training time
you'll need.
-[groaning] Sorry.
I'm not getting this at all.
-Right.
I'll explain it to you, but
you've got to pay attention.
OK.
-Yes, sir.
But please keep it simple, sir.
-I'll try.
As you know, the
Shadow Clone Jutsu
creates actual physical
copies of yourself,
not just illusions as with
a Standard Clone Jutsu.
NARUTO: Yeah.
Yeah.
I know.
Of course, I know that.
-It allows you to duplicate
your real self many times over.
I know this, because I can
make Shadow Clones too.
Though not nearly
as many as you can.
But this ninjutsu also imparts
a unique effect on its user.
As experienced as
you are, you must
have picked up on it by now.
-Uh.
-When the jutsu is
released and you're
restored to your single
original self again,
everything that each one of
your Shadow Clones experienced
is now inside of you, stored in
your memory banks as it were.
-Didn't I ask you
keep it simple?
-I guess you hadn't
picked up on that, huh?
-I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You lost me a long time ago.
-All right.
Let's both just go ahead
and make some Shadow Clones.
OK.
One should be
enough for starters.
-Right.
-(BOTH) Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-Good.
Now, we'll split up
into a team of originals
and a team of clones.
OK.
So the Shadow Clone team will go
hide in those woods over there.
Shadow Clone Naruto,
come with me.
-Right.
Let's go.
There.
Now, there's no way that the
team of originals out there
can see what the team of
clones is doing in here.
So now we play a game of
rock, paper, scissors.
-We do?
How come?
-Never mind, just do it.
-Wait.
Just rock, paper, scissors.
That's no fun.
-It's not supposed to be fun.
-How about this?
Loser buys the other guy
an Ichiraku Ramen lunch.
-OK.
OK.
Fine.
Well, all right.
Now, it gets interesting.
-(BOTH) One, two--
-So what is it our Shadow Clones
are doing in there anyway?
-You'll know soon enough.
-I won.
-Ha.
Ha.
Looks like lunch is on
you, Kakashi Sensei.
-OK.
OK.
Now, let's just release this
jutsu and get out of here.
-You got it.
-Do you know what
our clones just did?
-I sure do.
They played rock,
paper, scissors.
And your clone lost.
You owe me some Ichiraku Ramen.
-What he was thinking,
making deals like that?
Anyway, you get it now, right?
Whatever our clones experience,
we experience, all of it.
It's part of us now.
-Whoa.
Yeah.
I guess I kind of just randomly
made Shadow Clones before,
so I never really noticed.
-Now, you see why this
jutsu was originally
used for gathering
intelligence for things
like serving in
dangerous terrain,
or infiltrating an
enemy stronghold.
-OK.
Great.
That's all really
interesting, but I
don't see what it's
got to do with reducing
the amount of time
I'll need for training.
-Hang on.
Don't worry.
I was just getting to that.
-All right.
-Where Master Jaraiya
found the patience
to teach the Rasengan to
this kid is beyond me.
I mean give me a break.
-Come on.
Come on.
-OK.
So basically, if you
and a Shadow Clone
perform the same training
exercise at the same time,
you'll rack up twice
the experience.
To put it another way, by
training the two of you, you
and your Shadow
Clone simultaneously,
we can cut your
training time in half.
Training three of you would
take only a third of the time.
-Three of me would take
only one third of the--
-And a thousand would take
one thousandth of the time.
-I see.
-Just think of it.
Training that would normally
take two days to finish
can be done in one
with two of you.
Skills that would take 20
years to master by yourself
can be learned in a week
with a thousand clones.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
I get it now.
That's genius.
-Huh.
I was starting to think
we'd never get there.
So that's the plan.
While we're treating
you to achieve change
in chakra nature, we'll use your
Shadow Clones the whole time.
-Sir.
Now, I understand how you got
to be so strong, Kakashi Sensei.
So this is the sneaky way you've
been training all along, huh?
-Nope.
This'll be the first time.
I've never tried
this method before.
-Huh?
But what's been stopping you?
You can make Shadow
Clones too, right?
-Sure.
I can, but the problem is I
can't maintain them long enough
to put them through an
entire training regimen.
My chakra simply isn't
as powerful as yours.
And the jutsu that requires
me to divide and disperse
my chakra into many equal
proportions isn't good for me,
not having a lot of
chakra to begin with.
-Wait a minute.
Do I really have that much
more chakra than you have,
Kakashi Sensei.
-About four times as much.
-Yeah?
That much?
Whoa.
I really am awesome, aren't I?
-If you weren't suppressing
the Nine-Tails' chakra,
you'd have about
100 times as much.
-Yeah.
The Nine-Tailed Fox.
-That's why this
form of training
will only work for you, Naruto.
But because it will
require you to use
a large amount of
chakra, there's
a danger that the Nine-Tails
could be awakened.
So that's why I'm
standing by, to make
sure we keep the
Nine-Tails under control.
The person who injured
Sakura was you, Naruto.
-Thanks, Captain Yamato.
-OK then.
The first thing we
have to do is practice
making your chakra's
change of nature stronger.
-Right.
-Hold this leaf
between your palms,
and using only your chakra,
tear the leaf in two.
-You got it.
No sweat.
-Hang on a second.
As I said before, you'll
be doing this training
with Shadow Clones.
-No problem.
How many Shadow Clones
you want me to make?
-Hm.
Well, let's see.
If there's one of you
per leaf, that many.
-Huh?
-Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
[grunting and struggling]
-He's already starting to
tear some of the leaves.
May not take as
long as I thought.
[theme music]
SHIZUNE: We've received
disturbing news
that a village near the
border with the Land of Fire
has come under attack.
TSUNADE: The Akatsuki?
SHIZUNE: No.
It seems to have come from the
Village Hidden in the Rain.
TSUNADE: What?
What could their motive be?
SHIZUNE: Perhaps, they're trying
to take advantage of the fact
that the Akatsuki
are after Naruto.
TSUNADE: Whatever it is, we
have to get to the bottom of it.
Summon Asuma.
SHIZUNE: But my lady.
TSUNADE: What?
SHIZUNE: With Naruto here in
the village sending out any more
jonin could put his
safety in danger.
NARUTO: Next Time, "Writhe."