Nine Tails'
chakra mode.
It's great for lighting
up the night, but it
could cause Naruto lots
of strife, even cost
him his life. It's
like a double-
edged knife.
Naruto may have
learned to use the
Nine Tails' Chakra
Mode, but he hasn't
made the Nine Tails'
his friend yet.
The Nine Tails'
continues to sap
Naruto's chakra.
And if it reaches
zero, he'll die.
Oh, yeah. His tension
is high, but stopping
his passion would be
a real shame. That
would make me cry.
I guess it's okay
to use the Nine
Tails' chakra like
a flashlight...
But stick close to
Naruto! Don't let him
out of your sight!
Yeah!
Naruto...
You waste my chakra
on something so
trivial?!
I've been inside you,
watching you, for a
very long time now.
Naruto...
After all you've been
through, you're still
so naive...
I can stop this. I
know that I can.
You have to let me.
I'll take it all
on myself. All the
hatred and all the
pain.
Because that's
my role.
You know, it looks
like you've put on
some weight. Let me
guess, you're using
my chakra again,
aren't you? And
what's got you
talking to me all
of a sudden, anyway?
Usually you never
say anything to me at
all unless I make you!
What, are you lonely
or something and you
want somebody to keep
you company for a
little while?
'Cause I'm kinda
busy now! Let's
do this later!
Do you seriously
believe that you
can end this war
all by yourself?
It's simply
not possible.
I'm sure you've
sensed by now just
how massive the
enemy force is.
This is Madara we're
talking about, after
all. There's no telling
what he'll do...
Of course, if you
want to borrow more
of my power...
Hmph! I'm not gonna
fall for that trick
anymore!
(chuckling)
I see you've gotten
a bit smarter since
last time...
I am when it's
that obvious!
We'll talk after
the war. Later.
If your comrades
are killed, hatred
will arise from
their deaths.
Are you planning to
defeat all of the
enemy before that
happens?
Then again, if you take
down the enemy, they'll
bear you hatred.
You really think you
can take that on all
by yourself?
If you do, then you're
completely deluded.
Stop treating me
like I'm stupid.
You don't understand
a thing! You're so
naive!
Do you honestly believe
that you can take on and
erase everyone's hatred?
The war has
already started.
I bet there are a lot
of casualties by now.
And the resulting
hatred to match
as well.
You've seen it firsthand.
Your former teammate
Sasuke has been gripped
by hatred for a long time.
Have you ever really
been able to do anything
for him at all?
Ever since that day.
That's right. You've
known it ever since
that day.
I wonder who I'm going
to be fighting...Hm?
Which one of these guys
is it gonna be?
The one with the dog
for a hat? Or the kid
with the hood and the
shades?
Or...
So, um, Sensei?
What is it?
Uh, the thing is. I
really don't want to
have to fight against
my friends, you know?
Well...Look, Choji,
this isn't like a
fight.
This is traditional
Shinobi hand-to-hand
combat! Even our Hokage
and those before him
participated in such
drills and became
stronger through
sparring.
Yeah, uhh, look, Sensei
just go ahead and
put down that I went
out of bounds, okay?
And then you can move
on to the next pair.
Hey. Wait!
You might be calling
this training or
whatever, but if
there's gonna be a
winner, then it's
actually a match.
And since that's the
case, wouldn't it
save you some trouble
to decides who wins
from the start?
(sigh)
Boy, he really has no
motivation. He is
never gonna make
chunin like that!
That's not
necessarily true.
Huh?
It's because, people
can change over the
course of a lifetime.
A lot can happ-
You are so hung up
on minor details!
Come on, Shikamaru!
You are the laziest
kid that I've ever met!
And Choji, you're
just a coward!
Hey, Ino, do you
know those two
boys or something?
Yeah, our parents
are friends.
Forget it...
Shikamaru, Choji,
give the Unison Sign.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
Hm...
Mm...
I'm really sorry,
Shikamaru.
Nah, it's okay. I
know that you stink
at stuff like this.
And it's a drag
for me, too.
Mm-hm! Good, Unison
Sign complete! Next
up is, Naruto Uzumaki.
You better
believe it!
Wait, is he
the one...?
My parents said that
I wasn't supposed
to talk to him...
Out of everyone here
I wanna be paired with
him the least!
And Sasuke Uchiha!
Step forward, you
two!
Sasuke! Get him!
Go, Sasuke!
I wish I could do
the Unison Sign
with Sasuke!
You've got this,
Sasuke!
You're totally
gonna win I'm
sure of it!
Mmm! What's with
him acting all cool!
Dammit! Why does he
get all the attention!
I'm gonna take Mr.
Popular down and
become the new hero!
Let's go! I'm
gonna win this
for sure!
Um, best of
luck, Naru-
Take him down,
Sasuke!
All right, it's
Naruto Uzumaki
versus Sasuke
Uchiha-
Come on! Let's
just do this
idiot!
Hey, stop that,
Naruto! You need
to make the proper
Spar Sign before you
two begin! It's
simple etiquette.
I don't care about
any of that stuff I
just want to hurry
up and defeat this
jerk already! It's
time for a new Mr.
Popular around here,
you know?!
Whatever, loser.
But I'll make it
quick, if that's
what you want.
Enough, both of
you! Good grief!
Shinobi Hand-to-
Hand combat is a
traditional drill
passed down from
generation to
generation.
You might think
it's stuffy to
be so formal,
but here at the Academy
we have respect for
tradition. This stuff
matters!
First you always face
and make this one-
handed sign toward your
opponent before starting.
It represents half of
the two hands used to
activate a jutsu and
indicates your
intention to fight.
Now, we call this
the Spar Sign.
When you finish sparring
and the bout is concluded,
you each extend forth
the Unison Sign and lock
your fingers around
each other's. This
indicates that you
recognize each other
as comrades. That's
the etiquette of
shinobi hand-to-hand
combat.
Are you listening,
Naruto? I've explained
it twice now!
Yeah, yeah...
Come on! One yes
is fine, you fool!
I get it,
okay?!
Naru-
Pound that kid into
the ground, Sasuke!
Begin!
Whoa! He's
so cool!
Oh, Sasuke,
you rock!
Whoa... So fast!
Sasuke...
That look in
his eyes...
It's the same look
that everyone
gives me.
No...
No, it's stronger
than that.
Wait...
...it's not
for me.
Sasuke wins. Now,
make the Unison
Sign. So we can
move on.
Hey, come back!
Huh?
You weren't even
looking at me! That
didn't count! You're
a turd! No, you're
crap! Hard and runny!
You're stupid! Stupid!
Uh, that's not really
an insult. This guy's
so dense, he can't
even swear properly.
I wish he'd make up
his mind. You can't
have be constipated
and have the runs, th-
Again, hung up
on minor details!
Hmph!
Got something to say
to me, you hard and
runny crap-turd?!
Ow!
I told you, Hand-
to-Hand Combat is a
sacred tradition! Now
make the Unison Sign!
And you, too!
Do it, Sasuke!
Come on, you two...
You wanna go another
round, you loser?!
Hey! Enough! Quit
it, both of you!
Naruto's just
the worst!
Yeah, what's
up with him?
It appears you
do remember...
So, what happened to
Sasuke after that?
Where is he now?
Where you able to
erase his hatred? No,
in fact, quite the
opposite, right?
Just snap out of it
already, will ya?!
What the heck do you
know about it. It's not
like you ever had a family
in the first place!
You were on your own
right from the beginning!
You don't know anything
about it!
Naruto...
No matter what you
may say to me now,
I'm not changing.
I'm still going to
kill each and every
person in the Hidden
Leaf, including you!
But, is that really
the only way, Sasuke?
Yes.
Your only choices are
to kill me and become
the hero who saved
the entire village...
...or get killed by
me and be known as
a loser!
His hatred has grown
ever stronger! You
weren't even able to
protect someone you
consider to be your
closest friend!
No matter who you're
dealing with, no one
can erase or fight
that much hatred.
And you certainly
can't take it all
on yourself.
Okay...
You finished?
What did you say?!
I get it. Are you
just trying to scare
me into doing nothing?
That's exactly what
you want, Nine Tails.
Isn't it?
Hey...
You're the one who
doesn't get it.
Who are you to be so
confident, when you
couldn't even save
Sasuke?
(painful growl)
Once you question
your beliefs, then
it's all over. I
don't know how yet,
but I will find a
way to save Sasuke
and stop this war!
(worried growl)
A Ritual Altar? He's
planning to seal me
up again! Not inside
that baby?!
All right look, you
stupid fox! You're
in my body, and you
owe me rent! So for
payment, I'll take
your chakra! You
got that?
All right...
You're done!
Sage Art!
Massive Rasengan
Barrage!
Once more!
What kind of
power is this?!
No way! This is
really the Nine
Tails...
Naruto...
How dare you!
You have infuriated
me! Naruto!
You still have
this much power?!
Wow. You really
are amazing.
(angry growl)
Isn't this the
Six Paths?!
You'd better watch
out, Naruto...
Hah!
So the little brat
thinks it's all
grown up, does it?
Hey! You know
what, Nine Tails?
Hnh! I believe I'm
gonna come after all
of that hate that's
inside of you,
too, someday!
You've made me
miserable my
whole life.
But I know just how
bad it feels to be at
the mercy of your hatred
and to feel ruined by it.
Arrgh! Are you
stupid?! I am the
Nine Tails! I can't
and won't be changed
by some mere brat!
I am hatred!
That's fine by me.
'Cause I'm not a
little brat anymore.
And it's more
challenging
this way.
Later!
Nine Tails...
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I am naive.
It's funny. You've
always been with me,
inside me. Like how
mom and dad stayed
with me. You know
everything about how
I feel, and everything
that I went through
growing up. Of course
I'm pretty sure you
didn't like doing it,
but still, you continued
to watch over me this
whole time.
That's why...
I want you to stay
there a little longer
and watch over me.
Sasuke, you too.
You might never have
cared about me at all
from the very start.
I've always been
watching you...
...Always.
That's right! I'm
gonna help Sasuke
and stop this war!
Yo!
Naruto, you're shining
bright, but you're
looking awfully grave
in this full-moonlight.
So try to lighten
up, all right?
Yeah!
Hm? What's this? Did
you have a fight with
the Nine Tails again,
my good friend?
Tailed Beast Mode's
a tug of war, 'tween
Nine Tails chakra and
yours. When your chakra
runs out, it's
curtains, no doubt!
So don't be too
reckless, yo!
I know that I'm
taking a chance.
But I have no
choice.
I don't go back on
my word, ever. Because
that's my nindo, my
ninja way.
Hm?
Now hurry up!
Let's go!
Hey, wait for
me, yo!
There you go. I've
taken care of your
external wounds.
Please get some rest.
You doing all right?
It appears that they're
targeting out Medic
Ninja.
Yes, Neji.
It's easy to get
discouraged. We don't
even know who it is
that we're supposed
to be fighting
right now.
Next Time On Naruto
Shippuden: Medic Ninja
In Danger.
I know. We have
to be careful.