-Huh?
A worthy adversary.
I'd expect no less
from a clone of me.
-I did it.
-Yes.
-Are you all there?
Did you beat them?
LEE (ON RADIO): Yes, Guy-sensei.
NEJI (ON RADIO): Yeah.
TENTEN (ON RADIO): Of course.
-Good.
Then let's go give Team
Kakashi the backup they need.
-On our way.
-Lady Chiyo!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Lady Chiyo.
It's no surprise.
With Sasori's poison
working on her,
it's amazing she hasn't
already passed out.
-We have to get
back and neutralize
that poison, and quickly.
Our job here is finished.
We beat him.
-But more than that,
there's something I must do.
My job isn't done.
Yet.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It's only
the sheer force of her will
that keeps her conscious.
What is this thing she
has to do that she'd
push herself so hard?
-I'm sorry.
-Here we go.
-Still on my tail, I see.
-Time to give it a try.
Naruto.
-Hm?
-You'd better fall
back a little.
-Right, Sensei.
Got it.
Mangekyo sharingan.
[theme music]
-Mangekyo Sharingan.
-Whoa.
-What is this?
What's going on?
A visual jutsu.
No!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What
kinda jutsu is this?
Incredible.
-I've got you now.
Damn.
-My arm is being sucked into
oblivion by this damn jutsu.
-I missed.
I'm still not very good
at controlling the size
or position of
the barrier space.
But I'll get it right this time.
-Damn it.
I let him get away.
-Well, good.
I shook him off.
-Rasengan!
-Good job.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Gaara.
Gaara!
Kakashi-sensei.
You all right?
-Yeah.
I think so.
-Don't worry, Gaara.
We'll get you out.
Hey, Gaara!
-They came this way
from the looks of it.
-You're right.
They were probably following the
one who had taken Gaara away.
-You monsters.
Gaara!
What are you doing, Gaara?
Come on.
Knock it off already!
-Enough, Naruto.
You know full well that--
-Your friend right,
and you know it, too.
He's been dead for a while now.
CHIYO: We must hurry.
-Right.
But please.
You have to tell me if
the pain gets too great.
-I will.
-Lee.
-Pick up the pace there, Tenten,
or I will leave you behind.
-What are you talking about?
I was only dragging my
heels waiting for you
guys to catch up.
-Oh, sorry.
But Naruto and the rest expect
us to keep our rendezvous
with them, so we
really must move.
Let us go.
-Hold on.
Shouldn't we wait for
Guy-sensei and Neji?
-Oh, I would not
worry about them.
-Why so slow, you two?
Hurry it up.
-Argh.
Now look what you
have done Tenten.
You let them get ahead of us.
-Huh?
Well, we'll just see
who gets ahead of who.
cashier are you there?
Come in, Kakashi.
Guess the radio is out of range.
Neji, can you see what's going
on with Kakashi and the others?
-Yes, I see them.
They're still engaged
with the enemy.
It appears they've
recovered the Kazekage.
However
-However?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Gaara.
-Talk to me.
Hey.
Come on.
Gaara.
Gaara!
DEIDARA: I told you, didn't I?
Gaara's dead.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
It worked perfectly.
Using the Kazekage as bait to
lure out the Leaf Jinchuriki.
But what I didn't plan on was
that one coming along too.
First it was my left arm.
-Sand coffin.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): Crushed
by the sand Jinchuriki.
Now my right arm too.
I can't use any jutsu.
It's over.
I never thought it meet anyone
with visual jutsu as powerful
as Itachi's.
This Jinchuriki is nothing.
The problem is how
to deal with Kakashi.
Hm.
-You will pay for this.
-Yeah, yeah.
Maybe someday I'll give
you a rematch, kid.
Ha.
-You've let down your guard.
-Damn it.
-Yes!
-Dropped your guard, didn't you?
You should be more careful.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Naruto.
It's clay.
A substitution.
Is that--
[theme music]
JIRAIYA: Get your hankies ready,
because our next episode's
inspiring conclusion
is guaranteed
to move you to tears.
Watch as I rush in
from afar to save
my knuckleheaded
but lovable student
with the power of devotion.
KAKASHI: Hey, I'm
involved in this too.
It's the devotion of two
masters that saves him.
JIRAIYA: Fine.
We'll call the
episode Devotion Saved
the Knuckle-Headed Student!
KAKASHI: Sounds
good, Master Jiraiya.
What do you say, Naruto?
You on board with that?
NARUTO: No way.
That title sucks!
[theme music]
-The Leaf Ask Us Anything
Investigation Team.
-Any question you have,
we're here to answer it.
-And today's question
is, what's Kakashi-sensei
got under his mask, anyway?
-This is a very
popular question.
-Yeah, we tried everything we
could think of go to find out.
We bought him some ramen once
so we could watch him eat it,
but no luck.
SAKURA: We tried following
him, but that didn't work.
NARUTO: The guy keeps his mask
on even when he takes a bath.
SAKURA: Pretty
weird for a sensei.
For anybody.
NARUTO: Then we tried
disguising ourselves
and using brute force.
SAKURA: Yeah.
That worked out really well.
NARUTO: Oh, yeah.
SAKURA: Finally, he answered
the question himself
when he took off his
mask and showed us.
NARUTO: And do you know
what was underneath?
Nothing but another stupid mask.
That's all.
-Yeah, he totally faked us out.
-Still, we'll never give
up trying to find out.
-We'll get a look at his
face one of these days.
-So you be sure and stay tuned.
Got it?