JIRAIYA: You want to
end up like this, too?
Talk, or you'll end up living
on dragonflies and beetles
for the rest of
your miserable life.
-Fine, turn me
into a frog, then!
I'm not going to say
anything else to you!
I made be low-ranking,
but I still have my pride.
I'm a ninja.
I have nothing to say
to an outsider who
has no idea what goes
on in our nation.
-Heh, still a ninja
no matter how lowly.
Well, interrogation was
never my forte, anyway.
OK, talk time is over.
But you're still
going to stay put.
I'll just go ahead and ask this
god of yours in person, then.
-What's the big idea?
I mean, what are you
thinking summoning me here
right now, Jiraiya?
Is this about Naruto's key?
-No, it's not about
training this time.
I have my reasons,
but I'm thinking
of removing you
from me for a bit.
-Thinking of removing me?
What in the world is going on?
-I'm just about
to go into battle
with a very tough opponent.
-Uh-huh.
This guy must
really be something
if you have to release
me to go fight him.
-Don't worry.
It's just a precaution.
Anyway, I want to press the
storage release seal now, so--
-Very well, then.
JIRAIYA: There
-So how long do you
think it'll take?
When will you be coming back?
-I really doubt that
it'll take all that long.
But if something
should happen to me,
you just go and store
yourself inside of Naruto.
-What?
Have you lost your mind?
You're well aware
that the key that
corresponds to Naruto's
eight sign seal
is transcribed on my belly.
Each and every year, the Fourth
Hokage's seal grows weaker.
We keep the key in order
to re-tighten the seal
if we should ever find the need.
To place a key right next to
the lock it opens is unheard of.
-Yes.
And yet, don't forget that it
was entrusted to us by Minato.
It was always meant to be
returned to Naruto one day.
-But it's too soon.
Once already you sweet talked
me into loosening the tetragram
seal, and you know
just as well as I
do what happened that time.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
-No.
But I believe that
Minato entrusting me
with his jutsu formula indicates
that his will was for Naruto
to complete that jutsu
for himself one day.
-That jutsu?
Are you serious?
-Yes.
-You really think that
Naruto requires such a jutsu?
He would never be able to
control the Nine-Tails's
chakra.
And besides, when that
lock was loosened,
Naruto's own chakra
was pushed aside
by the Nine-Tails's
chakra, which
leaked out in large amounts
and took over Naruto.
If the seal is
undone any further
and the Nine-Tails
completely overtakes Naruto,
that would really go against
the Fourth Hokage's will.
-But Minato only used this seal
on the Nine-Tails's Yin chakra.
He split the Nine-Tails's
power into Yin and Yang
and sealed the Yang
power inside of Naruto.
He left the Nine-Tails's
chakra to Naruto on purpose.
-Perhaps.
But still--
-Why did Minato do that?
Why did he go so far as to seal
that chakra inside his son?
-Who can tell?
Perhaps it was necessitated
by the sealing.
Or it could be that
as a father, he simply
wanted to pass on
that power to his son.
-I was Minato's teacher,
so I knew him very well.
And he never did anything at
all without a very good reason.
Minato must have known
something important.
And as a result, he entrusted
the Nine-Tails's power
to Naruto because of
the knowledge he had.
-I think you're reading
too much into it.
-Do you really
believe that's true?
The last time the
Nine-Tailed Fox spirit
attacked the Hidden
Leaf Village,
it was said to have
been a natural disaster.
But lately, I've begun
to suspect something else
happened, that its appearance
was not a natural phenomenon.
I think there's more to it.
I believe it may very well
have been manually summoned.
-Fool.
The Nine-Tails has always
been a natural disaster
that appears when humanity
becomes steeped in evil.
Besides, there's no one
that's powerful enough.
No one can summon the
likes of the Nine-Tails.
-Yes.
Well, that's just the thing.
There was one.
-What?
-And who's that?
-One of the Uchiha clan
founders, Madara Uchiha.
-Ribbit, ribbit!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
You fool.
Madara lived back in the
early days of the Hidden Leaf.
No way he was still
alive 15, 16 years ago.
-Yes, that's true.
And I also know,
as everybody does,
that the First Hokage defeated
Madara Uchiha in the Battle
at the Final Valley.
-Exactly.
Your theory is pointless.
-Perhaps.
But I just have this
feeling that I can't shake.
And it fills me with unease.
-Return to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
When you get there, go
straight to see Ibiki.
He already knows
you'll be coming.
I'm counting on you, now.
Well, then, I certainly
hope this plan works.
Here we go.
[music playing]
PAIN: Well?
-It's Jiraiya.
PAIN: I see.
Jiraiya sensei, huh?
How nostalgic.
-What'll you do, Pain?
-Jiraiya isn't on our side of
things, isn't that correct?
-Probably.
-Then I must kill him.
It's far too late for regrets.
I came forth in this body
to kill the intruder,
and I'll do just that.
Now take me to him.
-All right, then.
Pain, I'll go ahead now
and handle him by myself
until you arrive.
-Try to kill him if you can.
-Fire Style Flame Bomb!
[coughing]
-Toad Subjugation.
Art of the Manipulated
Shadow, huh?
JIRAIYA: I dangled
a lure in hopes
of drawing out this Pain fellow.
But I never imagined
that I'd catch you.
You've honed your
jutsu magnificently.
But even more, you've
become quite a catch, Konan.
It was my understanding
that all of you had died.
But I never would have
guessed that you'd
turned into sheets of paper.
-It's really you.
You're the messenger,
Lady Angel.
-First a god, now an angel.
Which means that
you're the messenger
for this so-called god.
Is that right, Konan?
-This man is an intruder.
You should kill him now!
-Leave now and stay away.
-Yes, ma'am!
-So who is this Pain?
-It's really none of
your business, sensei.
-And doing that helps
you feel like an angel?
Does putting on an act like
that really have any benefits?
-I've received my
orders from god.
I will kill you.
-Cloud oil bomb!
You're soaked in oil so
you can't peel apart.
You had such a love
of origami, and you
were the kindest and gentlest
of the three of you children
that I trained.
What happened to the others?
Nagato and Yahiko?
I heard you all died, but
I guess that was a rumor.
Oh, I see.
So tell me, which
of the other two
ended up becoming
this Pain, then?
-Just what do you want
appearing before us
after all these years?
-That wasn't my
intention if you all
hadn't been part
of the Akatsuki.
I heard that all
of you had died.
I never imagined that it would
come to something like this.
-Way back then, you should have
done what Orochimaru suggested.
Isn't that what
you're thinking now?
-These kids-- shall I kill them?
We've seen so many war orphans.
It's always so pitiful.
They'd be better off if
we simply put them out
of their misery right now.
-Back then, you saved the three
of us from that fate instead.
But it's too late now.
We've wholeheartedly
embraced his ideology,
and we have now made our move.
-I have no regrets about
letting the three of you live,
no matter how this may end.
I'm just very sad.
The reason I taught you ninjutsu
was to enable all of you
to survive those harsh times.
You were all
undoubtedly my students.
And I know the world
is a cruel place,
but to attack me without even
so much as a greeting-- well,
that's just too sad.
For a few years after
our time together, I
heard your names
mentioned here and there.
You made a reputation
for yourselves,
fighting for hire
in a few conflicts.
But then--
-You know nothing about what
happened to us afterward,
sensei.
-No, I don't.
That's quite apparent.
But why all this stuff
with the Akatsuki?
What the Akatsuki is
doing now is simply wrong.
-This is what I've
thought through on my own.
And that is that,
Jiraiya sensei.
-Well, your appearance
has changed quite a bit.
But those eyes,
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): That
shape, that ripple pattern.
I can't believe it.
That eye.
The Rinnegan.
-So I guess you're the
one who became Pain.
Nagato.
It appears you've strayed
from the path of goodness.
What happened to you?
-You don't need to know.
After all, you are an outsider.
-You really have
changed, Nagato.
-Summoning jutsu.
-Hmm?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Foam.
Leave it to my students
to know my weakness.
He intends to nullify
and wash away the oil.
-Kona, stay back.
-Art of the Raving Lion's Mane!
Nagato, it's time for me
to ask you a few questions.
What happened to Yahiko?
-Ah, yes.
There was such a fellow
once, wasn't there?
But he died a long time ago.
-Nagato, what happened?
-All I want to do is protect
those two, no matter what kind
of pain I may be
forced to endure.
-I understand.
What happened to you?
The old you would never--
-Nothing happened.
Nothing except for the war.
Too many people
died in this land.
All that pain forced
me to grow up.
-What does that mean?
-That even innocent,
foolish children
will grow up in the face of
pain until their thoughts
and beliefs are
the same as adults.
-But abandoning one's love for
his friends and fellow man?
Is that really what it
means to become an adult?
-Oh, sensei.
You are still merely a man.
However, I, mired
in endless pain,
have matured and become
much more than a man.
-What are you saying?
-Yes.
I've grown from a man to a god.
And since I'm a god, all
my words and thoughts
have become absolute.
Poor sensei, you're
still only human.
It's not your fault if you don't
understand what I'm saying.
-Have you really
become that twisted?
-Things that I couldn't see
when I was human are clear to me
now that I'm a god.
And being a god, I realize that
there are things I can do which
moral men cannot even dream of.
Or to put it more simply,
I have evolved beyond that.
-Just what exactly are
you planning to do?
-At last, I'm
going to put an end
to this senseless,
war-riddled world.
This will be my sacred deed.
-If that's your goal,
then why are you
gathering up all
the tailed beasts?
-Well, you are about
to die, anyway,
so I don't need to keep this
secret from you any longer.
I will use the
sealed tailed beasts
to develop new, forbidden
jutsu, jutsu of such magnitude
that just one could
destroy an entire nation.
They will be the most powerful,
the ultimate forbidden
jutsu weapons.
-But how could creating
such jutsu possibly
bring about an end to war?
Weapons such as
those will simply
increase conflicts
between nations.
PAIN: The world is already
rife with conflict, so what's
the quickest way to
get nations to stop
fighting each other,
Jiraiya sensei?
JIRAIYA: That's
what I'm asking you.
So answer me!
-To each one of the
warring nations,
I will hand out a
forbidden jutsu weapon.
For once they have them, once
they possess such a power,
then they're bound to use it.
-Wait.
What are you saying?
-Just think.
Tens of millions of
people will die instantly,
and all mankind will
quake in terror.
All of humanity, all the nations
will learn what pain truly is.
Fear would breed a
strong aversion to war.
Conflicts would cease.
It can be said that
this world is still
in the process of
maturing, that it's still
on the path to stability.
Pain will make
the world grow up,
just like it forced
us to grow up.
In order for the world
to develop to the point
where it can think
and walk on its own,
it needs the help
of a god's hand.
This world is still
but a child, you see.
-You want to teach the
world pain in order
to make it grow up?
Is that it?
Do you really believe
that this is your mission?
-I do.
I believe in this fully
because I am a pacifist god.
-Well, I see you've developed
a sense of humor, Nagato.
-Oh, I'm not joking.
Far from it.
My vision is too important.
I'm over here, sensei.
-So that's your
summoning then, is it?
-To me, you're like a
single-celled organism
that hasn't evolved at all.
[laughter]
-Summoning jutsu!
Just imagine a kid
treating me like a kid.
Well, I have news for you, kid.
I'm not really human
anymore, either.
These tears of blood
overflowing with rage--
I went from Sannin to Sage-- the
Hermit Sage of Mount Myoboku!
I am master Jirai--
-You haven't matured
at all, sensei.
You're just as clumsy as ever.
-Come on!
Watch it, Mister Gamaken!
Don't jostle me during
such a crucial juncture!
[music playing]
-I'm sorry.
I'm quite ungraceful.
[music playing]
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
I really have
to hand it to my former student.
He knows my moves all too well.
I don't know what
happened in the past,
but now he's powerful enough
to head up the Akatsuki.
Plus, he wields the
legendary Rinnegan.
Against this foe, there
shall be no playing by ear.
I'll have to go full
strength with my Sage Mode
from the get-go.
Next time-- Honored Sage Mode!
Look forward to seeing me
in all of my awesome action
then because I know you are!