Look, I had...
I had my Father. I had my
Mother. And I had Pervy
Sage.
Kids love looking up to
their heroes!
That's why I can run forward
without hesitation!
And I will become the
greatest Hokage of them all!
That's my dream! I
won't give up on it!
[defiant roar]
I guess that crack in your
mask will have to come
first.
You will not touch the
statue!
[angry roaring]
[roaring]
Naruto! You know his
abilities, right?
Your window is the
instant he tries to pull
you in, that's when he'll
become solid. If you
attack him normally, you'll
just pass right through him.
That means go for a
counterattack.
Diversionary tactics! Create
an opening through close
combat!
Avoid using big moves!
Thanks, but I already know
that! That's why I created a
clone!
Master Bee! Please,
raise me up high!
I got this!
I'd better avoid
direct attacks...
Up you go, yo!
Super Mini Tailed Beast
Bomb!
Mangekyo Sharingan!
Twin Fangs!
This one?
I guess not. Then
it must be...
[chuckle] Nice timing!
I'll deal...
...with you first!
Nice moves, Bushier
Brow Sensei!
Okay! I think I've put
enough chakra into this now!
Sorry, but...
I'm going...
...after the Gedo Statue!
Hm?
Kamui!
If I gouge out its head, it
shouldn't be able to
survive, Statue or not!
So naïve.
[heavy breathing]
What just happened?!
Don't tell me...
He vanished?
Naruto!
Damn it! These boulders
are in the way!
Master Bee!
Got it!
Huh?
Go fly!
He cut the rock with his
Lightning Blade! Nice,
Kakashi!
I'm not going to be in time!
Naruto! Just keep going!
I'll take care of the kunai!
Kamui!
Damn it!
He's really strong! I can't
get my attacks to land!
You all right?!
Yeah...
But... if even that attack
isn't good enough...
What can we do?!
[gasps]
Man, what is happening
all of a sudden?
Hey, Kakashi, you see that?
Yeah.
Huh?
There's a crack in his mask...
What?!
Seriously, where?!
You're right! It's
true! On the left side!
It looks like your earlier
attack hit right before it
passed through him!
Nice work, Naruto! Let's
keep going, then!
Yeah, all right! Now I feel
like we might be able to get
somewhere against him!
No... to be honest, it
didn't look to me like
Naruto's attack landed.
You're doing it again! You
always say things like that!
So... was it something else?
What's going on?
From the looks of that
crack, it doesn't seem to
be from Naruto's punch.
That mask was scored,
carved, by something a lot
sharper...
Wait a minute!
You're wide open! Gotcha!
Do not mock me!
Uchiha Flame Formation!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Whoa!
Are you all right?! Are ya,
Octopops and Eight-O?!
Agh! Do I look it?!
Now that he's erected a
barrier, we have no choice
but to tackle the masked guy
first.
That's been my plan right
from the beginning!
Damn it!
I thought so...
No... It can't be...
Except...
I'd never heard... that the
Kamui could be stopped!
But... if that chip
in his mask...
...was caused by the
kunai I used my Kamui on...
That means his ninjutsu is...
It's no use just thinking
about it...
It's not an implausible
theory, but it's not
impossible, either...
Guy, Naruto, Master Bee...
Huh?
There's something I want to
test. Please, lend me a
hand.
Let's do it!
Right!
Yo!
[attacking yell]
Impressive destructive
power.
How's that?!
No chance to pull
me in, huh?!
You underestimate the
Sharingan. I can read your
movements.
I'll keep these.
He becomes solid when
he absorbs things!
Now!
Rasengan!
Don't you see that
it's futile?!
It went like you said,
Kakashi Sensei! I don't
really get why, but I
finally landed an attack!
I see... It wasn't that Naruto
undid his Rasengan...
...but that you used the
Kamui to send the Rasengan
away... right, Kakashi?
As I suspected. I thought
you had two different jutsu,
one to slip through things
and one to
pull things in or take
them out. But, no...
It's all just one
single jutsu!
Are you sure it's just one?
Yep.
Well, there's no one better
at jutsu analysis and
breakdown.
His jutsu... Can you explain
it to us quickly?
Knowing exactly what it is
and how it works might
change how we approach the
battle.
The gist of his jutsu is
very simple.
You see, the jutsu he
uses to pull things in and
the one where he slips
through objects are
both the Transportation
Technique.
Wait, what do you mean? Just
how were you able to
determine that?
Well...
Let me explain in order.
First, that crack in his
mask...
That mark is from my
Lightning Blade kunai knife.
There's no doubt about it.
And I can tell from the look
of the wound on his right
shoulder that it was caused
by Naruto's Rasengan
just now.
What those two things
have in common...
...is that they both involve
areas of his body that were
overlapping and in contact
with
Naruto's body while he was
slipping through him.
Also... there is one other
thing that the two have in
common. And that is...
...the both of them were
caused by a kunai knife and
by a Rasengan that I had
teleported using my Kamui.
In short, I can deduce from
all this that his
Transportation Technique...
...and the time-space of my
Kamui are linked!
Wait just a second! What are
you saying? How come his
Visual Jutsu and yours are
both linked?!
Does that mean that all
Transportation Techniques
are linked between all
users?
No... That's not the case. I
suspect that it's just him
and me.
Never mind that! Why did
your kunai hit but I wasn't
able to land my punch?
That's right, fool! Even
with shared time-spaces it
should still be impossible
to hit a guy that
can slip through everything
like it was nothing at all,
ya fool!
Except that our theory that
he slips through things was
wrong.
I still don't get it. What
do you mean?
Although it looks like your
attack slipped right through
him...
...in fact, only the part of
his body that would have
been in contact with yours
was transported into
time-space.
In other words, the left
side of his mask that your
punch "slipped through" was
simply
transported into time-space
and no longer existed on
this plane.
At least materially.
And then...
Almost simultaneously, I
hurled that kunai into
time-space using Kamui,
remember?
Just as his momentum carried
him forward... when he
extended his arm toward you
in order to grab you...
...My kunai finished entering
time-space and it scored
his mask.
The same... with my
Rasengan?
Yeah...
So that's what
happened, huh?
But how come both your
Visual Prowess are linked?
Kakashi, is he?
Just where did you
obtain that eye?
Where?
[chuckling] During the last
Great War, if I dare say.
The Battle of Kannabi
Bridge...
The same battle where you
earned the nickname "The
Sharingan Hero."
Wait, are you?
I thought I told you not to
flap your mouth so readily!
You have sunk so low as to
become
nothing but talk! Your words
are worthless and
meaningless!
It is too late for regrets.
Reality just keeps cruelly
moving forward.
You have seen reality, so
you ought to know. Not one
wish ever gets granted in
this miserable world.
That is why I shall guide it
toward the dream of Infinite
Tsukuyomi.
I shall create a world where
it won't be necessary for a
hero to pathetically make
excuses in front of a grave.
[heavy breathing]
Hey, are you all right,
Kakashi?!
Bastard! Are you still
yakking on about that?!
I told you! I won't quit! My
dream is to be Hokage!
I've been entrusted with way
too much by way too many!
You tell him!
[harrumphing chuckle]
Entrusted...
But, Naruto... What if you
were to lose the things
Jiraiya and the Fourth
Hokage entrusted you with?
I wonder what they
would think.
I've always wanted to do
something about all of this
hatred...
I'm just not quite sure how
to go about it as of yet.
If I can't find the solution
to this problem, then
perhaps I'll entrust you to
find it instead, Naruto.
I'm very glad I
made you my student.
You must find that answer
for yourself. Because even I
don't know it...
I'm certain that you'll be
able to find the answer,
Naruto.
Because I believe
in you completely.
If you fail at the things
you were entrusted with...
I wonder what you'll think
of yourself, as well?
If you postpone dealing with
problems and cover them up
with the word "hope..."
...all that awaits you is
empty reality. Both the
entrusted and those that did
the entrusting all in vain.
[growling]
I sealed half of the
Nine-Tails' chakra inside
of you, because I believed
that you could
master this power.
I did it because
you're my son.
Naruto! Switch with me!
There's something I
want to say to him.
Sorry, but your words don't
apply to this guy.
That's Nine Tails!
The Fourth entrusted him
with me and Naruto's...
... befriended me now and
mastered my power, too!
The Fourth Hokage sealed me
inside Naruto as a force to
help take you down.
Go, Naruto!
You will not fail!
Yeah!
That man, he couldn't be!
There's absolutely no way!
Kakashi, I've got a pretty
good idea of what you're
thinking right now.
But you need to just leave
it be. There's no time to
wallow in sentimentality.
Your former subordinate
Naruto has already jumped
into action!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Who Are You?"
How foolish, attacking
all by yourself.