-This is starting to get messy.
Guess I better
play my next hand.
-So my suspicions were true.
That's the Third's jutsu.
-Brings back memories, huh?
This jutsu is the
reason the Third
is held as the most powerful
ninja the Sand has ever known.
I'm going to grind
you into dust.
-W-w-what is that?
-The most terrifying
weapon in the history
of the Sand Village,
the Iron Sand.
-Iron Sand?
-Mhm.
This is one of the original
jutsu of the Third Kazekage
himself.
Adapted from one used by the
former host of the Shukaku.
It can mold particles of Iron
Sand into any shape or weapon,
forming the perfect weapon
for every situation.
The Third had a special
physical constitution
that allowed him to
convert his infused chakra
into magnetic forces.
This puppet has
the same ability.
It's manipulating the sand by
making it's chakra magnetic.
-How can that be?
Even if it's made from the
body of the Third Kazekage,
this thing's still
just a puppet,
it's not like it's alive.
how can a puppet hold chakra?
-It can't.
That puppet is a human puppet,
built from a real body.
It is fundamentally different
from the mother and father
puppets of mine.
It was made from a real person.
Sasori is the only one who
can produce human puppets.
The puppet retains
whatever chakra the body
possessed in life.
The added benefit
being, the puppet
is able to use the same jutsu
it could when it was alive.
It's the great advantage
that human puppets
have over ordinary ones.
-There's more to it than that.
This puppet is my favorite
out of my whole collection.
-Sakura, get out of here
while you still can.
Leave it to me,
I'll handle this.
This is more than
we bargained for.
There is nothing else you
can do, not against that.
-But I--
-You're to slow.
Iron Sand, Scatter Showers!
-[gasp]
-No
-[gasp] Hmph.
You've made some changes, I see.
And a chakra shield at that.
A definite upgrade since
I last played with them.
[heavy breathing]
-Huh?
-CHIYO (VOICEOVER): As I feared,
crippled by the Iron Sand.
--[chuckle] You have to do
more than just block it.
You have to dodge
this jutsu to survive.
Is that it?
Saving the girl is
all you could manage?
The Iron Sand has crept into
every crevice of the puppet.
As long as I have the
Third's magnetic power,
That puppet is worthless.
Let's see, yes, I think it's
time I attack both of you
at once.
Just to make sure
you're really dead,
I'll use my most lethal form.
You won't get away this time.
One puppet, two people,
can't protect both.
What do you say to
that, you witch?
[chuckle] Which of you will die?
[theme music]
-[grunt] [gasps]
SASORI: Just enough, but
still rigging your own body.
We puppet masters are all alike.
Our minds work the
same, don't they?
[chuckle]
-Your face is exactly the same.
You haven't aged.
-Of course, now I understand.
-[gasp]
-Once the Iron Sand gets in,
it's the end of the line.
The puppet's useless.
So granny, what now?
[flashback music]
[camera click]
-No, it can't be!
Curse you!
Curse you White
Fang of the Leaf!
[laughter]
[grunt]
[crying]
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Now, now.
Come on, up you get.
[laughter]
CHIYO: Sasori?
-Huh?
Huh?
-Granny Chiyo, can we stop
for a snack on the way back?
-You want a snack?
I don't see why not.
[door]
-Huh?
[gasp]
[laughter]
-Granny Chiyo.
-You like it, Sasori?
This puppet master jutsu
is as old as our family.
What do you think, you want to
begin learning how to do it?
-Really?
You can teach me how?
-Well now, come with
me and you'll see.
This warehouse is
where they all end up.
Every prototype and
unfinished puppet
ever made in the
Hidden Sand Village.
Sasori, everything in here is
yours to use as you please.
I want you to try and
build your own puppet.
-My-- my own puppet?
-[gasp]
-What?
That's--
-[gasp]
[crash]
-Hmph.
Take away all of their puppets,
and even the greatest masters
are nothing.
-How could I let
it come to this?
How could I be so blind?
And now what will I do?
-[grunt]
-Sakura, you must get
out of here now, hurry.
Sakura, why are you
just standing there?
I told you before, there's
nothing you can do.
Not against this.
You must leave it to me, now go.
Run!
SAKURA: (VOICEOVER): Run?
Run away and leave Lady
Chiyo to face him alone?
No.
There must be
something-- there has
to be something
that even I can do.
Yes, there is something.
One thing.
SAKURA: Lady Chiyo, you
can use me to fight him.
SAKURA: (VOICEOVER):
Yes, that's it.
That's what I can do.
I can be her puppet.
But a puppet with a difference.
-My body's made of
flesh and blood,
he can't stop me
with that Iron San.
CHIYO: I have only one arm now.
I won't be able to support
you like last time.
-I'll be alright.
It's true, I might
not be rigged up
with a bunch of fancy weapons
like some of these puppets,
but the unbending
spirit of my teacher
has been drilled into me.
-Huh?
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade, eh?
Hm.
CHIYO: You're right,
the Third Kazekage's
magnetic forces render puppets
made of iron and steel useless.
-Exactly.
Like my teacher, I can
fight with my bare hands.
-Not this again, you fool.
-[gasp]
-[scream]
-How dare you?
-That's just the beginning.
[theme music]
NARRATOR (VOICEOVER):
Naruto Shippuden
gets more exciting
with each episode.
LEE (VOICEOVER): In
the next installment,
my beloved Sakura finds
herself in deep trouble.
As Sasori, the evil
puppet master--
[chime]
REPORTER (VOICEOVER): We
interrupt this program
to bring you a
breaking news bulletin.
A massive earthquake has been
reported in the Land of Rivers,
causing the collapse
of at least one cave.
Strong aftershocks
are still being felt,
so caution is advised to
all people in the area.
More later.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Hey, she
cut us of in the middle
of our preview of
the next episode.
NARRATOR (VOICEOVER):
What nerve.
Take it from the top, Lee.
[theme music]
-Today's topic is
medical ninjutsu.
So if your all
ready, let's begin.
Medical ninjutsu consists of
many different techniques,
each requiring specialized
knowledge and precise chakra
control.
They are jutsu designed for
treating poisoned wounds,
but there are also
jutsu designed
for inflicting damage in
combat, such as the chakra
scalpel, which attacks the
opponent's nervous system.
The ultimate medical ninjutsu
is Lady Tsunade's Mitotic
Regeneration jutsu.
Using this, almost
any injury can
be healed by the rapid
regeneration of cells,
but it requires a
great deal of chakra,
and actually shortens
the user's life.
-Now, here's a question.
Which of these is Lady
Tsunade's assistant Shizune?
[beeps]
-The correct answer
is, C. I know
I've got to keep training hard
if I want to be a first class
medical ninja, like
Shizune and my teacher.
Hiya!
Oops, sorry about that.