Why do you get up?!
There should be no
reason to keep fighting
for a world like this.
No matter.
It's coming to an
end in a few minutes.
So why do you
keep on fighting?!
Because it's my Ninja Way.
No matter what, I
never go back on my word!
That is and always
will be my Ninja Way.
I thought I told
you to go to sleep.
Let's end it with
our next move, Naruto.
Yeah!
We'll sleep tomorrow and
we'll dream our own dreams!
The Susano'o is...
Wait, that's!
I believe this is
what Madara did
once before, didn't he?
Is that Naruto and Sasuke?!
Nothing you try now
will change anything.
Look above you.
What do you see
through the hole at the top?
I can see what Obito
sees and hear his voice.
It's resonating.
The moon.
The time to enter the
dream world draws near.
It'll finally be time for
the dreams of the moon to
completely bury this
gaping hole of hell!
Look at me!
There's nothing in my heart!
I don't feel
pain any longer.
Reality is cruel.
This hole is just going
to keep getting bigger.
How will you seal
this hole by living in
a world like this?!
This sword is the Sage
of Six Paths' Divine
Blade, the Nunoboko.
You can no longer defeat me.
Your strong emotions
dwell within it, this
sword of the soul.
The Sage created the
world using this blade.
Hey guys, did you feel that?
Yeah...
Hold on!
Tenten, is this-?
Yeah.
Let's go, Lee!
-I think he's calling us.
-Mm-hmm.
I will vanquish all of you.
No matter how much you
resist, it's useless.
The power of the
Sage will stop you.
Sasuke, let's focus
everything on a single blow.
I think we'll only have a
small window to strike.
Let's not miss it.
[affirmative grunt]
And I'll use this sword to
obliterate this whole world!
[defiant roar]
[gasp]
Obito...
When people see someone
trying twice as hard as
others, even if it's someone
they used to make fun of
they instinctively start
wanting to lend a hand.
That's because people
eventually learn that they
only have each other to fill
the holes in their hearts.
[gasp]
I'm giving a Rasengan
to each of you!
Use them to blast through
and wreck his shield!
This, huh?
Can I really do this?
You can!
And he who possesses a
heart filled with comrades...
[gasp]
...is truly powerful!
Why am I
seeing such images?
[roaring]
Like we thought, their
chakra reacted to the chakra
they gave you earlier so we
could pull out his Tailed
Beast chakra in one shot!
That's right!
But this stunt wouldn't have
worked if the other Tailed
Beasts hadn't liked you
and shared their chakra.
I told you how
you could stop me.
But I didn't actually tell
you how you could save me.
You should have just
told me that right
from the beginning!
Man, why can't you
Tailed Beasts be more
straightforward?!
[annoyed sigh]
All right, what do I do?!
Before I tell you,
there's something I want
to pass on to you.
What?
Hold out your hand.
You're gonna
give me something?
It's something good.
It'll come in handy
one of these days.
Now hurry up!
[chuckles]
We assembled here because
of Four Tails' summons.
And we hung around
after promising to tell
and give you something.
Wow, he really did all that?
[chuckle]
Well, I'm glad that you're
all gathered together and
that you're all
getting along, too!
Yes, but that only happened
after Four Tails and Roshi
left here, Naruto.
It's all thanks to you.
Naruto, step forward.
Extend your hand.
We'll fulfill our
promise to Four Tails,
or rather Son Goku.
My name is Matatabi.
Yugito Ni'i...
My name is Isobu.
We've met before, huh?
And I am Yagura, the
former Fourth Mizukage.
I am Kokuo.
I'm Han.
Me, I be called Saiken.
We meet again.
I'm Utakata.
I'm Lucky Seven Chomei.
The name's Fuu!
Naruto, you really
are something special!
Go now!
[determined growling]
You know what to do
next, right, Naruto?
Tug-of-war!
Just pull the Tailed Beasts'
chakra right out of him!
Got it!
Damn!
We can't grab One or
Eight Tails since we
don't have their chakra.
Originally One Tail
was linked to me.
I'll get him.
Gaara!
Come here, Shukaku!
We finally found a
weakness, this is key!
You can leave
Eight-o's chakra to me!
Nice, Octopops!
Let's do this, Bee!
Don't lose!
[chuckle]
Extract them!
Then the only power
he'll have left is
Ten Tails' husk!
And the Tree's
bud won't bloom!
They've all stopped.
Which means he
doesn't have control
over the Divine Tree!
So in other words...
Everyone!
Remember when I told
you that even a small
power can be helpful?
Well, now is the time!
Our power will change
the course of this world!
Listen closely!
Your chakra's
connected to his!
His feelings will
flow into you, but
don't get distracted!
Don't underestimate me!
My power's equal to
the Sage of Six Paths'!
Just keep pulling, Naruto.
Naruto!
You're the one who
asked us to lend a hand!
So we're helping out
till the very end!
You guys!
[chuckle]
And that isn't all...
All right, everyone,
now grab onto my chakra!
[gasp]
It's this, right?
All right!
On my mark, everyone
pull together hard, okay?!
Now pull!
Are...
Are you saying
I've got regrets?!
You once told me
that you're nobody.
That you don't
want to be anybody.
No, stop it!
Don't step into
my thoughts!
But the truth is
that you wanted to be
Hokage, just like me.
It could've even ended up
being the case that I was
chasing after your shadow
since becoming Hokage has
always been my dream.
I threw away the
past and my naïve self!
Don't say--
Then tell me why I'm
able to see this!
You can hide behind a
mask, but it's pointless.
You were Kakashi
Sensei's friend, my dad's
subordinate, an Uchiha like
Sasuke, my senior, and a
Leaf shinobi who shared
the same dream as me.
What is all this?!
Just tell me!
What is it that
you want with me?!
I want to remind you
that you're Obito Uchiha.
I told you that I'd tear
that mask right off your
face, remember?!
Obito Uchiha?
What meaning is
there in that name or
in that existence now?
I've merged with Ten Tails,
and I've transcended and
attained enlightenment.
I am no longer human.
I shall lead mankind
into its next stage.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Obito Uchiha."
I am the Second
Sage of Six Paths!