NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Just like Sasuke, huh?
Well, there's sort of
a resemblance, I guess.
-Well, what is it?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sorta
sounds like him too.
-If you keep on staring at
me like that, I will hit you.
-Where did that come from?
Where do you get off
saying things like that?
Listen, you!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I take it back.
This guy's nothing like Sasuke.
-I really have nothing
personal against you.
-Yeah?
Then why'd you say it?
-You don't understand.
I was only trying out a certain
personality type, that's all.
-A personality type?
-Hm?
If you were trying to do in,
then that means you meant it!
We don't need someone
like you on this team.
You really rub me the wrong way.
-That's enough.
That's no way to talk,
especially not in front of me,
your team captain, Naruto.
Mutual respect and trust are
essential elements of teamwork.
Wasn't it Kakashi
that taught you that?
You are part of the team
led by the great Kakashi.
Lose the attitude.
-He's not a part
of Team Kakashi.
Not now, not ever!
The fourth member of our
team is and always will
be Sasuke Uchiha.
This guy, he's just
a fill in for Sasuke.
That's all he is.
He will never be a real
member of our team!
-Well.
I'm glad.
I'm glad that
that's how you feel.
Sasuke is a traitor.
He betrayed the Leaf
and joined Orchimaru.
Yes, you're right.
I'm not him at all.
I'm not a traitorous cockroach.
I can't fill in for
someone like that.
-I've had it with you, Sai.
-Remember what's
important, Naruto.
It's teamwork.
Calm down.
Sai.
Naruto was out of line,
but it's just because he
doesn't know you
well enough yet.
I'm sorry.
I hope you can find it in
your heart to forgive him.
-But, Sakura.
-Glad we have one level
headed person on the team.
-Oh, don't worry.
He doesn't bather
me in the least.
-Good.
That's a relief.
[theme music]
SHIZUNE: I wonder if they're
getting along all right?
The new Team Kakashi, I mean.
-I'm sure they're doing fine.
After all, they're not a
bunch of rookies anymore.
They're full
fledged shinobi now.
-Yes, but Naruto and
the new one, Sai,
didn't seem to hit it off.
I just hope that doesn't lead
to any friction between them
down the road.
-And whose fault do you
think it will be if it does?
Whose bright idea
was it to stick
Naruto with someone
he can't stand?
That.
-I-- I never imagined that one
of Lord Danzo's men would end
up joining the team.
TSUNADE: I don't wanna
hear any excuses!
Just get on it!
-Oink.
-I wanna know what Danzo's
up to and who this Sai is.
Understand, Shizune?
-Yes, m'lady.
-As for Naruto and Sai,
I'm counting on Sakura
to handle it.
She should be able
to keep them in line.
-Yes.
About Sakura.
-What about her?
-Uh, nothing.
Nothing, m'lady.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): The problem
is, as Lady Tsunade's student,
Sakura is becoming more and
more like her teacher every day.
I wonder if she's really the
best person to smooth out
any friction between
Naruto and Sai.
It might be like throwing
fuel on the fire.
-I don't care one bit
if you forgive me.
-You fooled me quite well.
That smile of your
looked so sincere.
-Sai.
You don't know a
thing about Sasuke.
I won't stand for you
talking as if you do.
Just keep badmouthing him and
next time, I won't hold back.
-Hm.
Fine then.
I'll keep my mouth
shut in front of you.
Well.
It would appear
I've just learned
another use for a fake smile.
I'll remember that.
-How can you just
sit there grinning
after she knocked
you into next week?
-The best way to defuse
a troublesome situation
is by smiling.
Even if it's only a fake smile.
It will fool more
people than you think.
At least, that's what
it said in the book.
However, it appears
I haven't quite
mastered the technique yet.
-OK, you jerk.
-Four Pillar Prison Jutsu.
I'm warning you.
I will toss you
all into this cage
if you insist on
fighting with each other.
Look, we don't have
much time if we're
going to make it to
the Tenchi Bridge.
With that being said, we
have just enough time, I
think, to sort this
out once and for all.
-But-- But isn't that--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Wood Style Ninjutsu.
A secret ninjutsu known
only to the First Hokage.
So how does Captain
Yamato know it?
Who is he?
-As the peacemaker here, I'm
offering you two choices.
Spend the rest of the day
crammed inside a wooden box,
reacquainting yourselves
with the meaning of teamwork,
or enjoy a night at
a comfortable inn
with a relaxing hot spring.
Which do you choose?
You don't really know
me very well either.
I prefer the kinder and gentler
approach, but believe me.
I'll use more draconian
methods when it's necessary.
-Ah.
Naked like this with no
secrets from each other.
There's nothing like it for
bringing people together,
is there?
There's nothing
like it, is there?
-Right.
There's nothing like it!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That freaky look again.
Forget kinder and gentler.
He's definitely going
with the draconian method!
-What do you know?
Looks like you do have
some balls after all.
NARUTO: Mind your own business!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto?
NARUTO: Damn it!
You're always balls
this, balls that!
You're so annoying!
[giggling]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Oh.
You and your big mouth.
Sometimes I wish I could just--
-Argh!
Great, now look at
what you've done.
They're all laughing
at me thanks to you.
-Well, at least you brought
little joy to Sakura's day.
Try to look at it like that.
-That's right, Sakura.
-Hm.
All righty then.
Well, I think I've soaked
enough for one day.
But before I go, let me
share an interesting story
with you, Naruto.
-Huh?
-Once, when Master
Jiraiya was young,
there was one incident that
nearly cost him his life.
He fractured six
ribs, both arms,
and suffered several
ruptured internal organs.
Supposedly, Lady
Tsunade did it to him.
Her strength is astonishing.
It all happened because he
did precisely what you're
contemplating right now.
I wonder how Sakura would react.
Looks like a great
change is in the wind.
[knocking]
Yes, come in.
-Excuse me, sir.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you ready?
Should we begin
preparing the meal?
-Yes, thank you.
-We'll start serving
as soon as it's ready.
-That felt good.
-Hey, Naruto.
Well, I'm getting out now too.
I really wouldn't stay in
there too long, if I were you.
You don't want to pass out.
A-haw!
Caw!
-You're kidding.
I've never seen such a spread.
-It's amazing.
Hey, uh, Captain Yamato?
-What is it, Naruto?
-What's the deal here?
Is all of this really for us?
-Yeah.
Go ahead and dig in.
-Yes!
Thanks a lot!
-Thank you so much!
NARUTO: I don't
know where to start.
Delicious.
-Mm.
Oh, that's tasty!
-If we get treated to a feast
like this on every mission,
then I say you can lead our
squad forever, Captain Yamato!
-I second that!
Let's hope Kakashi-sensei
doesn't get out of the hospital
too soon.
-Ah-- Ah-- Ah choo!
When do I get to eat something?
-You'll have to stick
to an IV for now.
Weak as you are, you don't even
have full use of your arms yet.
-I see.
-Once your arms and
legs are working again,
we'll get you on a
liquid diet, but it's
going to be a while before
you can eat anything solid.
-Food.
Real food.
NARUTO: Oh man.
I am stuffed.
Ah.
Oh yeah.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Yes indeed.
Thank you.
-Now then.
Normally I'd say this was
the perfect time for us
to discuss our mission now
that we're all fed and rested.
But since the reason we're here
is to improve our team morale,
we'll save the heavy
stuff for later.
-Now you're talking,
Captain Yamato.
Good idea!
-All right, then.
We'll discuss the mission
specifics tomorrow.
-So, we'll be staying at the
hot springs another day then?
-Whoa.
Let's not get carried away.
I'm not made out
of money, you know.
-What?
Wait a second.
Are you saying you paid for all
of this out of your own pocket?
-Mhmm.
-All right.
That's so cool!
OK, it's settled.
Captain Yamato is now
the official leader
of Team Kakashi.
SAKURA: I second the motion!
NARUTO: Woo hoo!
-Slept like a log.
Looks like another
beautiful day.
Huh?
Sai?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What
is he doing over there?
[theme music]
SAKURA: Sai.
So you're an artist, huh?
SAI: What do you want?
SAKURA: Nothing.
I'm just surprised to see
you have a sensitive side
when you come off
as such a jerk.
SAI: So that's all you wanted?
To insult me again?
Punching me wasn't enough?
SAKURA: Hey, I just wanted
to see what you're drawing.
I was trying to be nice.
SAI: I see.
SAKURA: It's strange, though.
sitting out here, I thought you
must be drawing a landscape,
but it's some kind of
abstract, isn't it?
NARUTO: Next time, Untitled.
[theme music]
-The Leaf Ask Us Anything
Investigation Team.
-OK, our question for today
is, how is captain Yamato
able to use the
Wood Style ninjutsu.
Hang on.
This question was sent
in by you, Sakura.
-Well, aren't you curious?
-I don't know, what's so special
about that ninjutsu anyway?
-You knucklehead!
Listen.
The Wood Style ninjutsu
is not only special.
It's uniquely rare.
It has the power
to transform chakra
into a sort of life itself.
-NARUTO: Uh, OK.
Run that by me again.
SAKURA: Ugh.
Why waste my breath?
The main point is, the Wood
Style ninjutsu can only
be used by the First Hokage.
NARUTO: Ah.
I see.
Then, how come Captain
Yamato's using it?
Tell me that.
-That's the whole
point of my question.
Oh no.
Now we've run out of time!
Look what you've done,
Naruto, you idiot!
We're out of time!
-Hey, calm down, Sakura.
Calm down!
Don't worry.
We'll keep investigating 'til we
find the answer, so stay tuned!