Damn it!
As usual, your
Lightning Blade is as
brilliant as ever, sir.
Brilliant? There's no
such thing as brilliant or
inferior in assassination.
Killing is
killing, that's all.
By the way, what ever
happened with the
replacement?
Our team is still
short a member.
There isn't really a rush.
We're not in the
middle of a war now.
Someone'll show
up soon enough.
Hey, Kakashi!
What's going on?
You look so tired.
Just finish a mission?
Don't be an idiot, Guy! You
know that the ANBU aren't
allowed to discuss
their missions!
That's how it goes.
Well, anyway, we're going
out for sweet dumplings.
You want to join us?
Sorry, I don't
really like sweets...
He's become so
antisocial lately.
Huh.
Maybe 'cause of the
secrecy in the ANBU.
No! No way this'll stand!
Kakashi is my
lifelong rival.
He has a heart that's
completely filled with
burning passion.
I guess it's up to me!
What's up to you?
Please let me
join the ANBU!
It's the best thing
to help Kakashi!
Guy, please, calm down.
I completely understand
your concern for
your friend Kakashi.
But the saying "the right
person for the right job"
applies here, I think.
Your skills won't be well
used in the ANBU.
It's not about what's
good for me, Lord Third!
If I were Kakashi's
partner, I could--
Silence! You simply aren't
suited for the ANBU!
Huh?! [screaming]
I can't believe he said
that I'm not suited...
Huh?!
Lord Danzo!
This is perfect!
What is it?
Please, you just
have to accept me as
one of your ANBU!
I'm afraid that you lack it.
Heh?! Lack what?
You lack darkness.
Darkness?
Very soon, a new member
will be joining your team.
Is it the one we
talked about?
Yes, he's an extremely
capable shinobi.
Perhaps. But very young.
That's why Danzo's
recommended that he
gain more experience.
Here's your equipment.
Yes, thank you.
I'm starting my new
ANBU assignment today.
Itachi Uchiha.
I'm glad to be here.
So, you're the one.
You can take the locker
that's in the back.
Yes, sir.
That him?
They say he's
only eleven.
That makes him the
youngest ANBU ever!
You'll be on Team Ro.
Meet at the Third Training
Ground in five minutes.
Right.
What are you doing?!
Explain yourselves!
We wanted to make
sure he had the skills
to be one of us.
Since he's so young.
You have a problem with
your superiors' decision?
No, sir. It's not like that...
Haven't you already been
able to tell that he's not
an ordinary shinobi?
I'm Kakashi, captain of Team
Ro. You're new, but I want
you to learn the ANBU rules
and formations quickly.
Yes, sir.
He's good.
He is talented, but making
an exception for someone so
young is rather
unusual for the ANBU.
Well, Lord Danzo
recommended him...
Really? Huh. He doesn't
seem to fit the mold, though.
How so?
Lord Danzo has his own
set of criteria for ANBU
and Foundation agents.
And?
I just can't see it...
I started my duties today.
Is that so?
That's my boy.
Itachi, I'm proud
you've joined the ANBU.
But there's one thing
you must never forget...
...that even more than being
a Leaf ANBU, you're first
and foremost an Uchiha.
Yes, sir.
The Uchiha Clan's
been entrusted with
the security of Village.
So our clan has
to live outside the
village boundaries.
It's essential that
our clan have one of its
own inside the ANBU.
I am counting
on you, Itachi.
Fugaku Uchiha stood out
as one of the shrewdest
security captains
in generations.
It comes as no surprise
that he is your father.
I mean no judgment.
The Leaf ordered the Uchiha
Clan outside the village.
But the Leaf also granted
them the ability to govern
themselves. So we cannot
intervene in their matters.
Therefore, we need our own
set of eyes and ears there.
I'm counting on you, Itachi.
Have you settled
into the job?
Not quite.
That's unlike you.
I haven't gone out
on a mission yet.
Protecting Lord
Hokage is a mission.
Isn't the ANBU an
assassination and
special tactics unit?
Well, we're not
at war now...
Kakashi...
Sir?
As Hokage, when I
assign a mission,
it's an official one.
However, I cannot ignore
Danzo's view that there is
an underside to
this mission.
So, a separate,
unofficial team will be
dispatched, too.
One that the
Hokage didn't order?
You will work under Danzo.
On the surface, it's a
diplomatic mission.
We'll be exchanging intel
with the Hannya Black
Ops of the Land of
Woods at the border.
But...
I believe that this meeting
is, in reality, an enemy
trap. Lord Third
agrees with me on that.
The ANBU will secretly
guard the team that's
on the official mission.
When the enemy turns on that
team and attacks, kill them.
Leave no survivors.
Total annihilation, sir?
We must show them that
the Hidden Leaf does not
tolerate betrayal!
I'd like to be in a two-man
squad with Itachi.
As you wish.
I shall take my leave.
Kakashi, I recognize your
worth as an ANBU.
I'm even tempted to pull
you into the Foundation.
Surely you jest, sir...
No.
You possess all
the right qualities.
Especially the one
called darkness.
[gasp]
It's a covert exchange
with the Land of Woods'
Hannya Black Ops.
The Hidden Leaf will
hand them this scroll.
And in turn, you'll
accept a scroll from them.
Should we verify
the contents?
This is a test of mutual
trust between our two lands.
So if they hand you a fake
scroll, then it will prove
that the Land of Woods
has no interest in
an alliance with
the Hidden Leaf.
That means if nothing
happens, we just bring
back the scroll, correct?
Yes. Presently there are no
hostilities between us and
the Land of Woods,
but we cannot be
certain it will remain
so. Be very careful.
On it! [chuckle]
[grunt]
Hey, Itachi. First
ANBU mission, huh?
Yes.
I heard it's just Captain
Kakashi and you.
Watch your back.
Why's that?
If it's for a mission, the
Captain won't hesitate to
kill a comrade.
He's a shinobi of
the highest degree.
Okay, everyone!
Time to fire up your
youthful passion!
Now! Let's go!
Captain! Wait!
Sometimes I wonder if I'm
getting too old for this.
[sigh]
So they weren't
actually told the true
nature of this mission?
That's right. Only the top
ranks of the Leaf know it.
And the two of
us, of course.
You are a godsend on
long-distance missions
like this one,
Mr. Kosuke.
Please help
yourselves to seconds.
Yes, that's right! Make
sure that you eat up and
replenish your energy
and chakra, everyone!
But Captain, is it
wise to have a fire
out in the open like this?
Aren't we announcing
our presence?
Yeah! What if the enemy
sees and attacks us?
Well, if they want to
attack us, then so be it.
My hunch tells me
this mission's really a
provocation to
clear up whether
they're friend or foe.
Impressive.
He's only been told the
superficial facts of the
mission, but he's figured
out its true purpose.
It's a good time for
us to refuel as well.
Right.
In a way, this symbolizes
the ANBU perfectly.
How is that?
They sit in the sun
and enjoy a hot-pot
meal together.
While we sit in the
shadows and eat food pills.
I don't mind at all. I
realize this is merely a
part of the job we do.
I see...
Huh?
Are you with the Land of
Woods' Hannya Black Ops?
Indeed we are. Now
hand over the scroll!
Fine. Together.
You first.
Very well, then...
There's no mistake.
And where is your scroll?
Here.
[gasp] [grunt]
We're supposed to
exchange scrolls, not fire!
The Hidden Leaf has
reneged on our agreement
and attacked us.
We shall seek retribution.
That's just a bold-faced
lie! You broke our
agreement! It was you!
[harrumphing chuckle]
[confident laughter]
Captain, they!
They planned to betray
us from the start!
We'll take over.
You all get away!
You guys?!
Earth Style!
Rock Collapse!
Quick, run!
Earth Style!
Mud Wall!
[chuckle]
You two, get
out of here!
Right!
Rumor has it you'd
kill a comrade for the
sake of a mission.
I'd never let my
friends get killed.
That's why I was entrusted
with this Sharingan.
You go, too.
Like I'd ever turn
my back on a mission!
Get on with it!
Earth Style!
Rock Collapse!
Eight Inner Gates:
Fifth Gate of Closing!
Open!
All that with
just taijutsu?!
Admire him later!
[attacking yell]
Retreat! Retreat!
Your mission is
complete now.
Return to the village.
[scream]
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is our mission.
Even if that's true,
stop this, Kakashi!
Hey! Only an idiot calls
someone by their real name
on an ANBU mission!
How can you?
[screams]
Rest assured, Captain. The
enemy has been neutralized.
[gasp]
I'll report back
to Lord Danzo now.
Your part of the
mission is complete.
Captain...
The Sharingan you
possess wasn't
originally yours, was it?
No...
Do you ever feel doubt about
using a power that wasn't
your own to begin with?
You aren't an
Uchiha, Captain.
And yet you possess
the Sharingan.
You wield the power
the Uchiha do.
So tell me: whose
side are you on?
I've never thought
about it quite that way.
This Sharingan was entrusted
to me by a friend...
And he...
...made me vow never to
forget what's important.
A friend?
Yeah...
To never let a
comrade get killed.
Yes, I see. That
was nicely done.
Lord Third...
I get why you told me
that the ANBU isn't
suited for me.
I understand...
But that's not all! Because
I don't believe that
Kakashi is suited for
the ANBU, either!
Is that so?
So how did the
new guy do?
He did well.
He'll probably be a better
ANBU than me, in fact.
But...
You're an exceptional
ANBU, sir!
There is a darkness beneath
every ANBU mission.
Why are you saying
this all of a sudden?
All of a sudden?
You're right...
Deception and killing
are part of the missions.
And always were.
[gasp]
Big Brother!
Let's walk home
together, Sasuke!
Okay! Done with
your mission, huh?
Guess what,
Big Brother!
Today, my sensei at the
Academy complimented me!
Hey, Kakashi...
I'm sorry about what
happened on the mission.
No, I'm sorry.
As some of you may know...
My son Itachi has
joined the ANBU.
Close proximity to the
Hokage and top officials
will mean access
to more information.
And that will be of benefit
to the entire Uchiha Clan.
Itachi, do you have
anything to report now?
Yes...
I'm still new, so there
isn't too much for me to
report yet.
But in the Leaf's higher
ranks, I don't believe
there's much solidarity.
It's my belief that the
Uchiha Clan's choices
will forge the future of
the entire Hidden Leaf.
Exactly. By all rights, the
Uchiha Clan must be central
to determining the
future of the Leaf.
[cheering]
That's the--!
You're part of the ANBU now.
So this is one mission
that you can't avoid.
So tell me, what is it?
Six years ago, after the
Nine Tails incident, the
village higher-ups
suspected that the Uchiha
Clan was behind
the entire thing.
Since then, the Uchiha
district has been under
twenty-four-hour
surveillance.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Coup d'État."
A mission's a mission.