"Their Backs"
Not yet... I
don't have enough
chakra...
[wincing]
Huh?
[straining and grunting]
[grunt]
Wake up, Choji!
Choji!
So tell me... what will you try
and fail at next...
...with my dear
puppet here...?
Stop saying that!
He's not your
puppet!
He's my friend! [angry yell]
[grunt] What do you think you're
doing?!
Get out of Choji's mind, you
hear me?!
I'm not going anywhere. You're
the one who's leaving!
[straining]
No. I'm not gonna lose!
There's no way that I'll let the
Yamanaka Clan's Mind Transfer
Jutsu be defeated!
[gasping and screaming]
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
[gasp]
[angry grunts]
Ino?!
[gasp]
(SANA) Elder sister!
Lady Saya!
My jutsu... It
was...
Somehow my
jutsu was
undone!
No, that can't be true!
I didn't lose, I didn't!
There's no way that I would ever
lose!
[stunned gasps]
Huh?
[frightened gasps]
[screaming]
[dazed groaning]
[paniful groans]
Ino! You did
it!
[heavy breathing]
[reassuring sigh]
[groaning and heavy breathing]
Ino! Sakura!
Huh?
(SAKURA) She was a puppet?!
(INO) Impossible!
Lady Sana! Over here!
Mamushi, you're alive?
Damn right!
and Elder Sister?
Lady Saya!
Elder Sister,
you're okay!
Yes, I'm just fine...
But I'm afraid
that my beautiful
doll's been
completely broken!
I can't believe
your jutsu was
defeated...
Huh?!
Ahhh!
No, I didn't
lose! I didn't!
You hear me?!
I did not lose!
[heavy breathing]
I don't care
about the Chunin
Exams anymore.
I want revenge!
I will have my
revenge!
Yes, Lady Saya!
But... how...?
I'm going to turn all three of
them into puppets and make them
clean toilets for ten years!
Ahhh!
What a deliciously depraved
idea! As I'd expect from you,
Sister!
[chuckling]
I'm going to get those three
from the Hidden Leaf Villiage no
matter what else happens!
Especially that blonde
Sensory-type kunoichi!
Sana, you know what to do?
Yes. Of course, Sister.
[heavy breathing]
Choji and Ino are almost out of
chakra from all these battles.
It's just been one after another
with no break!
Their strength and willpower...
are at their limits!
Back then... I always relied
on Sasuke and Naruto to protect
me.
Now, I should be able to protect
my teammates.
Like Naruto and Sasuke did for
me...
(JIRAIYA) Alright, today we're
going to step up our training
even more. We're taking it to a
whole new level!
Think of it
like kind of
an experiment.
Even I don't
know what's
going to
happen.
Alright, are
you ready?
Uh... yeah!
Alright! Let's get
started!
Mhm! Come on out Gerotora!
I have a bad feeling about this!
Anytime you summon me, it means
that you...
That's right. I'm gonna
ask you to loosen
the Nine-Tails' seal
just a little bit.
Huh?!
(GEROTORA) Well... let me just
start off by saying that I'm
opposed to this.
The Nine Tails simply cannot
be controlled by mere humans!
That's why I've taken
the time to make
sure that we're making
the right choice.
With all the training that we've
done up until now,
I know that Naruto can maintain
his own psyche through up to a
two-tail transformation.
But we need to know how much
further he can go.
Tell me the
truth, kid: can
you handle it?
If I do what he wants and loosen
the seal, that means the Nine
Tales' influence over you will
grow stronger.
Can you say for sure he won't
take you over and end up going
on a rampage?
Uh, well, I...
(JIRAIYA) [laughing]
Oh, relax! If worse comes to
worse, then I, Jiraiya, one of
the Legendary Sannin, will stop
him even if it kills me.
Thanks, Pervy Sage!
And besides, I still
have complete faith in
Naruto's ability to master
this jutsu.
Just as the Fourth Hokage, the
one who sealed the Nine Tails in
Naruto, was able to master it.
Yeah!
Alright, here goes!
Right!
Here we go!
[grunt]
(GEROTORA) Two tails instantly!
And there's the third tail!
Now, Naruto! Suppress
your chakra now!
[straining]
[heavier straining]
You can do it. Suppress it
yourself!
You don't have to tell me, you
know! [grunting]
What- What is this.. awful
feeling...?
So bitter and hateful... I feel
like... my insides are turning
black!
(NINE TAILS) I'll cooperate with
you.
Huh?
Wait... You're the-!
Don't hold
back. You
want power,
don't you?
Knock it off!
Huh?
You know... this is pretty
pathetic, don't you think?
Trying your hardest to bring
back someone who chose to
run away from the Village.
He's probably forgotten all
about you and has already
found a better partner.
Just shut up and get lost!
[struggling for air]
[choking]
(NINE TAILS) Fool! If anyone's
getting lost, it's you!
[growling]
I said this
was a bad
idea!
Well, I guess I've got no
choice...
[growling]
Gerotora, just stay
back, okay?
I'll go and
stop Naruto...
[leaping grunt]
[battle cry]
[growling]
[triumphant roar]
[dazed groans]
What is...?
[groggy moans]
Where am I...?
(JIRAIYA) Welcome back!
[groaning] Pervy Sage!
[groan of pain]
Hey, what happened...?
Isn't it obvious? You
went on a rampage,
I stopped you, and
here's the result.
Eh, but it's
only a few
broken ribs and
what not...
[stab of pain]
[disbelieving sigh]
I did that to you...?
It isn't your fault, Naruto. I
just made the worng call with
your training.
It seems I underestimated a few
things.
Pervy Sage...
I, uh...
Don't apologize.
Sometimes, training
goes wrong. It's
normal.
Yeah, but...!
I... He provoked
me and I gave
in!
Oh, I see...
So was Gerotora right, then?
You're gonna give up 'cause it's
too hard?
I was able to hold
on to my consciousness up
until the third tail
appeared.
But then I felt this immense
power...
Now I know this jutsu's
absolutely necessary!
It may be impossible now. But
I'll never surrender!
I won't betray the faith you and
the Fourth Hokage put in me,
Pervy Sage!
[approving groan]
Well, I always knew it
wasn't going to be simple or
easy to deal with this...
So... we'll just have to
figure out some other way to
make it work.
[painful groan]
I know that Naruto is probably
somewhere training hard right
this minute...!
And I...
I can't waste anymore time
feeling sorry for myself!
Sand Storm Jutsu!
I'll leave the
rest to you,
Elder Sister.
We're counting
on you!
Time for revenge! Cursed Sand
Puppet Jutsu!
Where did this sandstorm
come from?! And why did it only
appear around us?!
It's not natural! We
have to assume that
it's some kind of
attack!
I bet that it's those guys!
Haven't they learned their
lesson yet?
They're trying to
block our vision,
and then they'll
attack!
And they have a
ground advantage
over us!
Don't worry!
I'll grab whatever
images I can and then
send them on to you
guys.
[pained groan]
[gasp] Ino!
Are you okay? You've
been in full Sensory
Perception mode for
a long time!
It's okay. I
can still handle
this...
From here on, my Cursed Sand
Puppet Jutsu... will continue to
bring forth more.
That blonde Sensory-type
is near exhaustion.
Having to ward off my jutsu for
such a long amount of time means
she's been forced to use up
a lot of her chakra.
Now she must
deal with all
these Cursed Puppets...
Using Sensory abilities on so
many is certain to be quite a
burden!
[heavy breathing]
[determined grunt]
(SAYA) [chuckling]
Mamushi...
Roger!
Now, Sana, you
take over.
Gladly, Elder Sister.
Sand Cloak Jutsu!
[grunting]
(SAKURA) Ino!
Don't push yourself
too hard!
Yeah, but...
If the three of us
can just guard our own
line of sight, we'll manage
somehow!
Well, okay...
I'll use the
Mind Transmission Jutsu
to connect what
we see.
That way it's
less of a
burden on me.
[punching]
Huh?
[attack grunt]
Ha! It's working, Ino! These
guys are pretty weak.
You're right about that! It's
gonna work!
[attacking yell]
That's it! Keep coming at me!
I'll take you all down!
[chuckle]
Huh?
[hissing]
[grunting and pained yell]
Choji!
[hissing]
(INO) Sakura!
[worried gasp]
[pained groan]
Ino!
[grunt and attck yell]
Huh?
[attack yell]
[gasps and grunts]
Doesn't matter! That venom
spreads fast. Soon you wont' be
able to move!
[maniacal laugh]
Choji! Ino!
It's nothing. We can still win
this!
That's right! I'll pulverize all
of them before the poison has a
chance to spread through my
body!
(SAKURA) I'm still the one being
protected...
This isn't right!
I know I've changed!
[determined grunt]
I gotta build up my chakra fast!
Just like that time...
(MED NINJA A) He needs emrgancy
surgery now or he'll die!
(SAKURA) We've gotta get Lady
Tsunade fast!
[groaning in pain]
Quick, take him! Get to the ICU!
Right!
[worried breath]
As a result, I can not let you
perform any surgery...
Or go onto the battlefield.
But... if we wait for Lady
Tsunade, the patient will die...
I have to do it.
What was that?
It's the Mind
Transmission Jutsu. Sakura's
feelings are flooding
into us!
[groans of pain]
[gasp]
It's down to me. Only me!
Now, more than ever, I need to
control my chakra!
I can't. I don't have enough
chakra...
[frustrated grunt]
Sasuke... Naruto...
[gasp]
Even now I'm
still depending on
those two!
[groaning in pain]
No more saying "I can't!"
Because unless I do it, this man
will die!
I need more chakra...
More...
I have to do it... With my own
strength... With my own
willpower!
It's just a little, but I feel
my chakra replenishing! I can do
this!
I will save this man!
(TSUNADE) You're going to take
the Chunin Exams?!
Are you serious?
Yes, so please...
I already told you I can't
authorize it.
The reserve that contains my
normal chakra and the one for
The 100 Healings Jutsu...
I was able to maintain control
of them both and successfully
performed surgery.
Huh?
I want to test my limits.
I want to push myself as far as
I can by taking part in the
Exams.
I know that I'm still
inexperienced...
But... despite that... Choji and
Ino still asked me to join
them...
...to take the
Chunin Exams with
them.
And I want to make sure that I
honor the trust that they've
put in me!
Please let me!
Bring this with you.
[gasp]
Thank you very much!
But whatever happens at
the Chunin Eams will
be your responsibility alone.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am!
(CHOJI) I didn't know...
You were under that much
pressure, but you still joined
up just to help us out...
We had no idea...
And we put more
pressure on you by
asking you to...
No, you're wrong!
I didn't agree
to do this
for you guys!
It was for me!
It was for myself...
I've always watched Naruto and
Sasuke's backs from behind.
This time I wanted to
challenge myself...
Ino... Choji...
Thank you for believing in me!
Thank you for asking me to join
you!
I'm really, really...
...grateful!
Elder Sister, the
big one and the
blonde can't move
anymore.
Soon, big forehead will-
[gasp]
Big forehead's chakra
suddenly spiked!
[gasp]
Finally I have enough chakra!
I will protect Choji and Ino, no
matter what!
I'll end this...
...in one blow!
[gasp]
This is over right now! Cha!
[quivering groan]
[screaming]
I didn't lose. I didn't! There's
no way that I would ever lose!
Elder Sister!
We lost! We definitely lost!
(SAYA) Mamushi! You'll clean
toilets for a hundred years!
Ahhh!
(INO) [groggy moans]
Hey! How are you feeling?
I extracted the venom. The
numbness will wear off soon.
Oh. Thanks.
No...
Don't thank me! I owe you two an
apology...
Huh?
You saw with The Mind
Transmission huh?
I put you both in danger because
of my own personal reasons...
Yeah, you sure did.
[shocked groan]
Nah, just kidding!
I'm glad that
we asked you
to join our
team!
Ino...
That's right! I'm happy about
it, as well!
I feel like the three
of us can defeat just
about anyone we might come
across!
[chuckling]
Really you guys...?!
Uh... I guess I should say
thank you too!
[gasp]
[chuckling]
(SAKURA) What? Hey, what's so
funny, you two?!
Come on! Let's
get going to
the central tower.
We're almost at
the finish line
of the Second
Exam!
Choji... Ino...
Seriously, thank
you.
(KANKURO) A massive sandstorm's
appeared all of a sudden? Is
someone trying to interfere with
our long-range sensors?
Who would do that?! And why?!
(TEMARI) Forget that for now and
focus on the safety of the
exam participants.
(KANKURO) We'll lead all the
entrants into the shelters.
I leave the Kazekage to all of
you. I get the feeling he might
go and take matters into his own
hands...
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
"The Hidden Plot Set
Into Motion"
(TEMARI) Make sure he doesn't
set foot outside.