♪
"The Loser Ninja"
This can't be! Is that...?!
What is happening now?!
[loud crash]
Get a hold of yourself, Tsunade!
What is happening here?
[small splash]
(Jiraya)
I've completed my latest work!
Jiraiya!  You never even
contacted me-!
Huh?
[restaurant chatter]
[small slurp]
What are you doing?
I'm in the middle of
writing my latest work.
Another "Makeout"-whatever
book?!  So ridiculous!
Hey! That hurts my feelings...
This new novel is different
from the others. It's very
innovative.
I'm still not finished, but
this'll be a masterpiece about
the "future of shinobi."
And you can be the first
one to read it when
it's finished, Tsunade!
That's all right.  No thanks!
(Tsunade)
"Jiraiya Ninja Scrolls"
"Long ago, there was a Fox
Spirit that possessed nine
tails..."
"If it lashed its great tails
even once, it could smash
mountains and send tidal waves
crashing to the shores."
"A band of ninja arose to defend
their village from its
attack..."
"and a lone shinobi sacrificed
his life to seal away this
beast."
[groan] [yawn]
Good morning!
Good morning!  You got home late
last night, huh?
Sure did... I was busy for a
long time with Lord Third.
So how'd your discussion go?
You had just mentioned an
important meeting a while ago.
So? How was it?
Uhhh..
I think... there's no need for
you to dirty your hands anymore.
Though it was unlikely, the
alliance between the Uchiha and
Senju has remained strong.
...and it has protected the
peace of the Hidden Leaf
Village.
From here on out, it will
continue forward until the end
of time.
Oh, it was fine.
Where's Naruto?
Well, he told me that an
important mission was going to
be assigned today
and that he couldn't be late no
matter what happens, but...
Naruto...! Naruto!
[groggy groan]
Huh...?
What!? I'm late!
Hey, good morning!
Heh heh! I'm outta here!
Hey, wait! Where are
your manners, huh?!
I gotta hurry or I won't make
it on time to the meeting
with Kakashi Sensei!
Heh, Same as always!
You spoil that kid! Can't you
scold him a little bit, too,
Minato?!
Uh, yeah... okay.
All right!  We're gonna get an
S-ranked mission today!
Hey, look... isn't that kid up
there the Nine-Tailed-
Shhh! Remember, he's still
the Hokage's son. Just let
sleeping dogs lie...
(Lady)
Well, still! I don't like
it! Not one little bit!
Alright!
Gahhh!
What the hell!? What are
you doing, scaring me?!
Hey!
Oh! I didn't know it was
you, Young Lord Naruto!
Mister... how much
is this mask?
No, no!  Don't even ask me!
I can't take money from you,
Young Lord!  Lord Hokage would
scold me if I did that!
Please, just take it.
It's okay! I don't have any
money today, anyway!
Oh, I see.
Thanks, though!  I'll just have
to come back sometime to buy it.
(Thinking)
Ugh, Lord Hokage this, Lord
Hokage that...
Hey, throw some salt!
I know that it's supposed to be
some kind of big secret in the
village...
But everybody here knows what
exactly that kid is...
... If he weren't the
Hokage's son, he'd've been
chased out of the village by
now.
Hey, Shiro!  Good morning!
Oh, Naruto! Good morning.
Hey!  Good morning to you, too,
Big Brother Itachi! Sasuke here?
Thanks for picking him up.
My brother can be pretty
difficult, so I appreciate it.
You can just leave him
to me! I'll make sure
that I train him right.
Thanks. You're a good friend.
You bet!
(Sasuke)
Hmph. Who's training who now?
I'm not so lame that I need
some loser to train me!
Just leave me alone.
Oh, Sasuke, just get over it!
We're friends, aren't we?
Since when are we friends?!  And
don't come to get me every day!
Just having to see your face on
missions is more than enough!
Yeah, right!  Admit it, you're
actually glad I came!
(Iroha)
[labored breathing]
[gasp]
Huh? What's wrong?
Who is he?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
...Hang in there!
Ageha...
Kakashi Sensei, Aren't you gonna
tell us what our new mission's
gonna be?
Before that, I wanna show you
something... this.
Engraved on this memorial are
the names of some of the Leaf's
legendary heroes.
Legendary heroes?
Well, I'm definitely gonna make
sure my name'll be engraved on
here!
All the shinobi listed here were
killed in action during missions
for our village.
Eh?
But there are others who put
their lives at risk, fought for
the village, and even saved
their comrades...
Yet they weren't given a heroes'
burial or even buried in an
ordinary grave.
So what's the story about this
person, Sensei?  Why weren't
they put with the others?
He was a captain on a difficult
top-secret mission.
While in enemy territory,
he faced a difficult choice:
continue the mission or save
the lives of his men.
And which one did he choose?
It must've been his
comrades' lives, right?
To save their lives... he
cancelled the mission.
I knew it!
However, the village suffered
huge losses as a result.
He was held responsible and
blamed for his actions...
In the end, even the
shinobi whose lives he
saved denounced him.
He was deeply hurt, and it
took its toll mentally and
physically.
Until he took his
own life.
But, that's--!
Why?!  I mean, yeah, he broke
the ninja code, but he did it to
save the lives of his own men!
One of the very first things
that we learn at the Academy is
that under shinobi rules, the
mission takes priority.
Yeah, but...
In the shinobi world,
those who break the rules
are scum. That's true...
But, that's not--
However! Those who'd sacrifice
even one of their comrades...
are worse than scum.
Hm?
Anyway!  Until you get the
signal to assemble for the
mission, you guys should go do
some training!
Dismissed!
-Right!
-Uh, right!
Hm? Something wrong?
Tell me, Sensei. Why was I put
on the same team as Naruto?
You have a problem with it?
No, I don't.  Not exactly.
But if he's on a team where
there's too large a difference
in skill levels
then I'm sure he's gonna
suffer because of that.
You were the Academy's most
promising student.
Are you blaming Naruto for
S-ranked missions not coming
your way?
Because it seems like it...
No. I didn't mean
it that way...
Because it could be
just the opposite.
I have a good feeling that
today's the day we get an
S-ranked mission!
Yes! I'm going
all out!
Honestly... How is it that you
can be so positive about life
all the time?
Well, remember, Sakura, I'm
gonna be the Hokage someday!
So for the sake of the village,
I can't be a downer!
Talk about dreaming...
(Sasuke)
No...
Naruto might become the Hokage.
Huh?
Sasuke!
So you're finally
ready to acknowledge my awesome
skills after all, huh?!
(Sasuke)
Idiot!
You're the son of the
Fourth Hokage.
So thanks to some favoritism,
even a loser could follow in
the Hokage's footsteps.
What?! You have no right to say
that kind of thing to me till
you can beat me with your
ninjutsu!
I don't need any ninjutsu to
defeat you, loser!
[grunts]
Lions Barrage!
Stop fighting! We're all on
the same team, remember?!
[groan] That was nothing!
Sasuke, let's race!
Whoever makes it to the
top of that rock wins!
Alright, ready....
Hey, wait!
Go!!
He doesn't know when to give up.
Hm?
[firework crack]
Lord Hokage just gave us
the sign to assemble.
Yeah, but... Naruto is...
What about Naruto...?
Damn it!  Like I'm going to
quit!  I'll never give up, no
matter what anyone says!
No sign of Sasuke at all!  He's
never gonna catch me!
I knew that I could beat him!
Huh? [screaming]
Damn it!
[screaming]
All right, now we shall see if
the strength that has been given
to you is a blessing or a curse.
[gasp]
If you don't wish to die, then
do something about it right now.
I'll never give up! Never!
There's no way that I'll ever
give up!
Huh?
(Nine Tails)
[growl]
That voice is... It's in pain...
So bitter and sad...
[growl]
[louder growl]
[low growl]
[gasp] It's huge...
You're the--!
I wasn't expecting to hear that!
I didn't think you would come.
Didn't your parents warn you?
You're... the Nine-Tailed Fox!
Why are you here, foolish boy?
What do you want?
Alright now, just listen up, you
stupid fox! You're in my body,
and you owe me some rent!
What's that?
So for payment, I'll take your
chakra. You got that?
[chuckle] You,
ordering me around?!
[low growl]
Well, I suppose I can't
kill you, can I?
I mean, if you die, I die.  Your
courage is impressive!
[gasp]
[gasp] [shouting]
Okay, first I'm gonna show you
how this jutsu's done.
Now watch carefully.
Summoning Jutsu!
This is it... Summoning Jutsu!
[relieved sigh] Man,
that was close!
So, Naruto ran off for that
rock?  Is that what you're
saying?
That's right. He wanted to
challenge Sasuke to a race.
course, I didn't want
anything to do with it.
(Kakashi)
It seems... he might have
tried to jump over this.
He what?! Did he
fall down there?!
Heh, what a fool.
(Naruto)
Hey! What are you doing?
C'mon, we'd better hurry or my
Dad's gonna get mad at us!
[gasps]
(Thinking)
Jiraiya Sensei...
Over there!
(Nine Tails)
[low growling]
I must erect a barrier now!
But I don't have much chakra...
I can still do it... Minato
[coughing]
Kushina!
[crying]
Woke you up, huh?
Sorry, Naruto.
Kushina...
I'll take the Nine Tails with me
to my death. Because that way we
can reduce the interval...
Kushina... There's no need for
you to die with the Nine Tails
now!
(Minato)
In your condition, you sealing
the Nine Tails' chakra is
physically impossible.
...But you should be able to
manage half.
(Kushina)
And the other half...?
(Minato)
I'll seal it inside Naruto
with the Eight Signed Seal!
[gasp]
Listen, I know what
you're going to say...
However, in time, the Nine
Tails' chakra will open up
Naruto's future as a Jinchuriki.
I think that if Naruto is ever
in serious danger, the power
will be invaluable to him.
But right now, I'm afraid
that it seems to be just
the opposite.
Well, yeah! It's just that he's
not able to control the Nine
Tail's enormous power yet...
But I'm confident that in time
he'll be able to learn how to
harness it.
That's if... Naruto truly
is the Child of Prophecy.
(Thinking)
But... what if he's not able to
fully control the Nine Tails...
...Was it too soon to let
you go on this mission?
No... sooner or later you're
going to have to overcome this
trial...
Wow, we're all here.   It's like
our entire class was called up
for this mission.
(Shikamaru)
Yeah...
I guess it's turned out
just as we feared, huh?
What?
I say we have a little as
possible to do with that guy and
just focus on completing the
mission.
All right, listen up: each team
will take a separate route to
the target site.
Once you arrive there,... you
will begin a search for the
missing shinobi.
If you find them, send
word right away!
Under no circumstances rush in
and try to rescue them! Got it?
Yeah, and you really don't need
to keep on reminding us...
I'm gonna rescue every
last one of those guys!
Seems like someone over
there doesn't get it.
As we thought.  This is gonna
turn out to be a real drag.
Scatter!
All right, you guys!
Let's do this!
(Tsunade)
"Right around that time, the
young shinobi who just been made
genin...
"...began making their way to a
village where their jonin had
disappeared."
"And amongst them was the Child
of Prophecy,... Naruto."
(Minato)
Time is tight. So I'll
explain the mission now.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:... "The Search
Mission"
(Minato)
Naruto, most likely
you're the one who...