♪
[electric shock]
[crash]
Well, it seems, that I've
managed to master Sage Power.
You just might be able
to take Kaguya on now.
Huh?
...A Messenger Toad?
[toad gibberish]
What was that?
What is it
Kaguya has returned, and they
can't contact Hamura anymore.
Then that means,
It's safe to assume that she has
seen through all of our plans.
Then the moment of
confrontation has come...
[moo]
Forgive me, everyone.
I know... but doing this is
really the only way that we
can save this land.
This is far enough.
Any closer is risky.
You should go and
hide somewhere.
Ah, If you and Kaguya
were to end up fighting.
...I honestly can't even begin
to imagine the sheer scope of
the battle that would result.
Anyway... this is
for you, brother.
What is this tag?
(Gamamaru)
[proud chuckle) You feel
its enormous power?
...It's a treasure
that's been passed down
in the Land of Toads.
It's forbidden to take it
outside our lands, but our lives
are also on the line right now.
That tag has been
infused with Sage Power.
Our ancestors sacrificed
their lives to create it.
Use it when you don't have
the time to replenish your
Sage Power on your own.
It can only be used once, but
it'll revive you even if you're
close to death.
I'm in your debt.
I'll pray for your
safety, brother.
I'm here, mother.
Tell me, Hagoromo, Both of you
broke the law, didn't you?
You went to that forbidden peak.
Hiding it is useless.  I can
read
all of your thoughts and your
feelings.
Well, then you must be aware of
why we're so angry with you now,
Mother.
(Kaguya)
It seems that you were in
love with that young girl.
No, not just her, But with
everyone!  The whole land!
I loved every last
one of those people.
But besides that, I also found
out what you did in the past.
Tell me... why would you ever
do such a terrible thing?!
Neither of you two know the
truth of how dreadful they can
be.
That is why I need an army.
They're soldiers?
I must know...  Just what
exactly are you, Mother?
Where did you come from?
The place that I came here
from... is far away, up in the
sky...
It's a place where you
two can never go.
But someday, they will
come to take me back.
They have no comprehension of
love.  They only understand
power.
But even so, you must've
believed in love at some
point in the past!
Hamura and I are the
proof that love!
(Kaguya)
But my love... also
led to betrayal!
My strength.
Lady Kaguya is with-
[grunts]
Aino!
And now it seems that I'm also
to be betrayed by the two that I
risked my life for, and shared
my power with.
Mother, please! Remember
the power of love!
End the Ritual of
the Divine Tree!
I will not.
Please, mother!
I protected the two of you, and
nurtured you all this time...
But it seems it was all for
naught. We are never going to
see eye to eye, Hagoromo.
And since that's the case... I'm
now taking back, the power that
I shared with you.
Hamura!
Mother, what have you
done to Hamura?!
Hagoromo, if the love you speak
of is real, then you won't be
able to kill Hamura.
[grunt]
Hamura! Snap out of it!
I'm not your enemy!
Ah, So she's taken
Hamura as a hostage!
(Gamamaru)
If Hagoromo stays on the defense
the whole time, even he will.
What's he planning to do?!
Forgive me, Hamura!
Elder... Brother...
[wretch]
[gasp] I'm... sorry...
Mother's the one who's been
controlling your actions.
I messed up, didn't I?
Don't talk now. Let
me heal your wound.
[chuckle] Well... I'll
be damned...!
To think he'd use the Secret
Treasure of the Toads like that
[gasp] My wound is completely
healed! What did you do,
Elder Brother?
If we make it out of this
alive, just thank Gamamaru.
[crash]
Hagoromo Hamura.
(Hagoromo)
Mother... I am indebted to you.
You enabled me to awaken the
Mangekyo Sharingan and Rinnegan.
[distant rumbling]
What's this?
Elder Brother!  Look up there!
[rumbling]
What is that...?
I can sense an enormous power.
[roaring]
(Zetsu)
And that is how Hagoromo
and Hamura's battle, the real
battle, began against my mother
Kaguya.
Mother still possessed the power
of the Divine Tree.  And to
protect her, it transformed into
the Ten Tails.
Ten Tails isn't just the Divine
Tree, it is mother herself.
It wasn't the Divine Tree's
incarnation trying to reclaim
its Chakra Fruit...
...but mother's will trying to
take back the chakra she'd
shared with her sons.
[thunderous stomps]
[explosions]
The intense fighting between my
mother and the brothers
continued for months.
It took a massive toll on
the land around them.
And at long last, the
decisive moment arrived.
Hagoromo and Hamura's powers...
overcame Mother's.
[gasp]
Do it, Elder Brother!
(Hagoromo)
Catastrophic Planetary
Devastation!
[Ten Tails Shriek]
[crashing]
(Zetsu)
Mother gathered up every ounce
of energy she had left, and just
before the seal took hold
...she gave birth to me.
[gasp] You mean you
came out of her?!
(Zetsu)
Even Hagoromo didn't
know this truth.
Nor that I was working on her
behalf to restore her.
[waking gasps]
(Hagoromo)
I split the Ten Tails
into nine souls.
When you look at them like this,
they're actually kinda cute.
What will you do with them?
I'm going to take care of all
these Tailed Beasts.
And I'll raise them to
trust and to help humans.
Elder Brother, I think I'm going
to stay close to Mother.
Hamura...?
When she controlled me, Mother's
consciousness was present inside
me.
I could feel her emotions.
Mother's been afraid all the
time.
In order to protect us, she only
did what she thought she had to
do.
It made me realize like she was
just a woman, alone all by
herself.
I guess I still
love her, after all.
Hamura You know... you
are a very kind soul.
Elder Brother, I will be in the
sky always watching over the
world you create.
Come visit once in a while.
We won't be that far apart.
Yes, I will. You take care.
(Zetsu)
That's how the battle between my
mother and the brothers ended.
I remained, but I was powerless.
That's why I went deep into the
darkness where I could carefully
and cautiously plan my mother's
revival.
Ignorant of this, Hagoromo was
raising Indra and Ashura ...
and created that Ninshu/Ninja
Creed nonsense.
Time passed, and so did
Hagoromo.
but not before scattering the
Tailed Beasts around the world.
To revive Mother, I needed the
Divine Tree and the Infinite
Tsukuyomi cast by the Rinnegan.
But the Rinnegan required
Hagoromo's chakra, which he
passed on to Indra and Ashura.
The Tailed Beasts, needed to
form Ten Tails, were scattered
across the world.
To bring Mother back, it all
had to be collected.
You can't imagine how
long it took to do that.
First, to regain Hagoromo's
chakra, I tempted Indra, who'd
lost the fight over ninja creed
succession.
And later, I selected Indra's
descendants, the Uchiha, to be
the cast of my tale...
...by meddling with and altering
that rubbish Hagoromo penned,
just a little bit.
You mean?!
That's right. Hagoromo's Stone
Tablet. I took it upon myself
to rewrite some of it,
like how Infinite
Tsukuyomi was the path
to save the Uchiha.
I must say, you Uchiha played
your parts brilliantly.
(Sasuke)
Why you-!
(Zetsu)
Indra and the Uchiha...
Ashura and the Senju...
I was able to set up a pattern
of fighting and power-seeking.
Time after time, I'd approach
the reincarnates of Indra and
Ashura in each clan to attempt
Rinnegan manifestation.
But it always ended in failure.
Just with that alone, a
thousand years passed.
But when the reincarnates became
Madara Uchiha and Hashirama
Senju,
I came to believe that
Madara could achieve it.
That was the first step
towards Mother's return.
However...
Madara Uchiha lost to
Hashirama Senju.
I thought that I'd have to go
back to the drawing board.
But Fate did not turn
her back on me.
Madara's corpse was like a
treasure trove to other shinobi.
Tobirama, who'd been studying
the mysteries of the Sharingan,
didn't destroy Madara's body...
He hid it deep within the Leaf's
mountains instead.
But Madara was no fool.
He guessed that if he lost to
Hashirama in battle, Tobirama
would keep his body.
So he placed a jutsu on himself.
You can invoke a time-delay
spell in one's eye using the
Mangekyo Sharingan.
Just like how Itachi implanted
the Amaterasu in yours, Sasuke.
[gasps]
(Zetsu)
Madara had installed the Izanagi
in his right eye.
At the cost of that right eye,
Madara rewrote reality and
returned to life-
then passed off a Shadow
Clone as his corpse.
He vomited up the piece of flesh
he bit off Hashirama,
transplanted it onto his
wound...
...and finally awakened the
Rinnegan and summoned the Gedo
Statue.
He then cultured Hashirama's
flesh using the Statue to try to
prolong his life.
The White Zetsu seemed to be an
incidental by-product of that...
...but actually were people from
the past Infinite Tsukuyomi,
whom I extracted from the Statue
and made look that way.
"It is these opposites operating
together that give rise to all
things."
As inscribed on the Stone
Tablet, Madara solidified his
attachment to Hashirama.
I started implementing a plan: I
made it look like I was born out
of Madara,
manipulated Obito, and began
collecting Tailed Beasts.
I formed the Akatsuki and
steered them towards war.
To increase battle strength, I
deliberately let Kabuto discover
Madara's corpse.
I guided him to use it as a
bargaining chip and cooperate
with Obito.
As long planned, the Infinite
Tsukuyomi was launched during
this war...
...and by amassing a large
amount of the human chakra
that'd been scattered, Mother
was restored.
I truly detest both of you...
Hagoromo... Hamura,  my two
children...
You  are now mine.
♪
(Zetsu)
My role has come to an end.
You shall return with me to the
almighty god that is mother.
(Naruto)
The two of you on your own
aren't the entirety of shinobi
history!
(Naruto)
And besides that, moms should be
happy about their kids leaving
the nest!
(Zetsu)
So your teen rebellion
continues...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The No. 1 Most Unpredictable
Ninja."
(Zetsu)
You brats can't hope to
accomplish anything.