-I can't get a break.
Who'd have thought my
self-destructing clone would
prove useless as well?
I think it's about
time I revealed
my ultimate work of art.
Art is an explosion, ha!
-It worked.
Just in time.
-Then again, it did create
enough of a diversion for me
to get away.
-My arm is being
sucked into oblivion
by this wretched jutsu!
-Hmm.
But all is not lost,
only up to the elbow.
I just have to find the
rest of it, and the ring.
Hmm.
[footsteps]
-So this is Sasori's true form.
-Look, here it is!
Here it is, Mister Zetsu!
I've found it!
-Maybe now I can become a
member of the Akatsuki, huh?
After all, there's an
open spot now, right?
-Fool.
Do you really think
it's that easy?
-Oh, come on.
Why not let him join?
Toby's a good boy.
[gasping]
-Let's go.
-Wait, wait a minute!
Mister Zetsu, please!
It's right here somewhere.
I'm sure I can-- gah!
Huh?
Mister Zetsu, hey!
Mister Zetsu, hey, wait!
Wait, please!
[music playing]
[footsteps]
-How much longer?
-They'll soon be in sight.
-It's Gaara.
[cheering]
-Huh?
That's--
[cheering intensifies]
[crowd chanting "yes"]
-That's what I call
a warm welcome.
-Oh, yeah.
-Look at how many
people there are.
-Just what you'd expect
for the Kazekage.
-No doubt.
[crowd cheering]
-I am happy you're safe
thanks to these people.
Naruto Uzumaki, I thank you.
-Huh?
I'm not the one who--
I mean, I hardly
did anything at all, really.
-Lord Kazekage, you people are
waiting to welcome you home.
Come.
Lead the way.
-All right then.
Shall we go?
-No, wait.
Not yet.
-Yes, you're right.
-Let us honor the
memory of Lady Chiyo.
A moment of silence.
-Well, sis.
We made it back home.
-What?
You're leaving already?
You can stay a little
longer, come on.
-Kankuro's right, at
least a day or two.
You need time to rest.
-Believe me, I wish we could.
-Me too.
But we must report back to
m'lady the Hokage right away.
-I see.
-Besides, if the Akatsuki
have managed to penetrate this
far into the sand, I'm worried
about the Leaf Village's
safety.
-I understand you want to
get back as soon as possible.
-Yes, exactly.
-Even so, in your condition?
-Don't worry.
I have comrades I can
rely on to get me there.
-He's right about that.
-By the way, we
already dispatched
the preliminary
report with Takemaru.
But there was no mention in it
of fates of the two Akatsuki
members.
Won't you want to
inform your village?
-I'll report that news
to the Hokage myself.
You see, there's something
else troubling me.
-Hmm?
-Lady Chiyo of the sand
was the only casualty.
The Kazekage has been returned
to his village safely.
Team Gai and Team Kakashi
have completed their missions,
and they're scheduled
to return to the Leaf
Village in three days.
-Very well.
-M'lady, if I may?
-What is it?
-Despite the fact that this
mission was successful,
I was wondering if
Master Jiraiya wasn't
right to question the wisdom of
sending Naruto, a jinchuriki,
to face an enemy that we know
is on the hunt for the Tail
Beasts?
Even with a former ANBU
Black Ops member like Kakashi
along to protect him, wasn't it
taking an enormous risk sending
Naruto on such a mission?
-It's because Naruto is
what he is that I sent him.
The only one who can truly
understand a jinchuriki
is another jinchuriki.
Besides, Naruto's got
that mysterious power, one
that makes everyone he
meets want to bet on him.
-Is that?
-Lady Chiyo's resting place.
-She didn't want a
headstone on her grave.
But despite her
wishes, I thought
it was better to have one.
I felt sure that
people would want
s place to come to remember her.
-Everyone, say your farewells.
-Let's go.
-Right.
-Sakura, Naruto!
We really should be going!
-Right.
Come on, Sakura.
It's time to go.
-Thank you, Lady Chiyo.
-Well so long.
-Uh, yeah.
-I guess this is where
people are supposed
to shake hands and
get all choked up.
But I've never really been
very good at that stuff either,
so let's just leave it.
[both men sigh]
SAKURA: Can't you
two go any faster?
-Sorry about this, guy.
That new sharingan really
takes a lot out of me.
Takes me a while to
get back up to speed.
SAKURA: Hurry up, will you?
[rock lee grunts]
-Uh.
Guy?
[shouting]
-What happened?
-That's just wrong.
-Grown men playing piggy back.
It's almost creepy.
-Oh, brother.
There
-What the?
I get it, a training exercise!
-Ha ha ha ha.
So you want to see faster?
I'll show you faster.
Gangway!
What's wrong, slow pokes?
Can't keep up with me?
Let's go!
-It looks even weirder
when they're in motion.
-Neji, forget it.
-Well, what do you know?
Looks like Deiter
has a goner, too.
Blew himself to bits
from the looks of it,
don't you think, Mister Zetsu?
There are probably body parts
scattered all over here.
-Get your hands
off that, you fool.
-Hey, he's alive.
-Where's the jinchuriki?
-Don't look at me.
I did my job.
-Dear, dear.
You must have had a
close shave, huh Deidara?
But you're in one piece.
Oops, sorry.
-Toby, even the
Buddha loses patience
when insulted a third time.
One more word, and
there'll be no doubt
about the cause of yours death.
-You're just going to
bomb me to death, right?
-That was the third one.
-Death by suffocation.
-I have made certain
that you will
be assigned to team Kakashi.
I've made arrangements.
Not only are you a close
to Naruto Uzumaki in age,
you are stronger than anyone of
your generation in the village.
Most important of
all, you possess
those incomparable
talents with a paintbrush.
From today until the
completion of your mission,
your name will be Sai.
-Sai.
Yes, I understand.
-And wipe that fake smile off
your face when you're with me.
-Forgive me.
If read that, in order
to win people over,
one must be able to smile.
I've been practicing, but,
creating facial expressions?
It's still quite
difficult for me.
[music playing]
-According to what
Sasori told me,
he had a spy in
Orochimaru's camp.
And he was to
rendezvous with him
at the Tenchi bridge
in the village hidden
in the grass in ten days.
-He could lead us to Orochimaru.
-Lady Tsunade, this
mission isn't over yet.
Let us finish it.
-And what makes you so
sure this information
he gave you isn't
bait for a trap?
-What if it is?
If it's a trap, then we fight.
We'll have to fight them
sooner or later anyway.
-Next time, "The New Target."
[music playing]
-To celebrate the
safe completion
of this multi-episode story arc,
I thought you deserved a party.
So everyone have fun!
-Thanks for all your
hard work, guys.
-Hey, thank you.
If you don't mind, what
are you thoughts now
that this story arc is over?
-What are my thoughts?
Well, um, I was hardly in it
after I get beaten by Sasori,
-How come I was kept
totally out of the action?
I didn't have a
single fight scene!
-Yeah, come to think
of it, you guys
were given all the
really juicy stuff.
-Well, it's not my fault.
That's not my department.
-Gaara.
How about putting in a
word or two on our behalf?
-Looks like I'm in
your debt again.
-It's nothing, don't mention it.
-Hey Naruto, next story arc?
We get double the
screen time you do.
-You better believe it.
-Huh?
I don't think you
guys are even in it.
-Huh?
-I heard you guys
are on a break.
You know, a hiatus
from the show.
[both together] Are you nuts?
Without us, this
show is nothing!