♪
(Sasori)
Over there?
(Itachi)
Yeah...
The "Akatsuki"?!
Don't know and don't care! Now
get lost! You're keeping me from
my "art appreciation"  time.
And I have to take this
brat on as my partner?
Sure, he's full of
energy, but he seems like
the early death type.
It's our Leader's orders.
His talent will be very useful.
You know about my
talent?! But how?!
Who are you? Talk!
(Kisame)
We know you're aiding
anti-government factions
with terrorist bombings.
And we are also aware that
you're a rogue ninja...
...So just what exactly
is your purpose?
(Deidara)
Purpose?! I don't
need a purpose!
I take commissions to make
explosions... using my art!
Disgusting.
Is he finished?
Who knows... Who cares...
I'll handle this...
[metal scratching metal]
To be clear... I'm still not
going to stop in the pursuit of
my art!
As you please...
But... You're part of
the Akatsuki. You will
fulfill your missions.
Yeah, all right.  I understand.
But you...! Don't ever try
to catch me in a genjutsu
again! Hmph!
You're one of us now.  I doubt
that I'll have to use it on you.
Well, good! But just remember,
I wouldn't mind giving you a
taste of my art!
Leave it at that.
(Tendo Pain)
Sasori...
Hm?
Partner with Deidara and
go kill Orochimaru.
About time...
Hold on! Who is
this Orochimaru?
I'll tell you on the way.
We believe that Orochimaru has
escaped into the Land of Wind.
But beyond that, we don't
really know anything.
That's all I need to know...
...Let's go.
Hmph.
Boy, you Akatsuki guys
sure like to bark orders!
(Sasori)
Just hurry up...
Yeah, I'm coming!
(Tendo Pain)
Itachi and Kisame, the
Hidden Grass Village.
What about my partner?
Wait a bit longer...
(Sasori)
I've ordered Kabuto
to keep me updated.
He has several methods
at his disposal.
If they're headed to the Land
of Wind, this is the spot...
[gasp]
The Great Sand Dune
of the East...
I see. That's one place
the villagers won't go.
Is that where
you're from, my man?
Never mind that.
Anyway, that location
works out perfectly.
[howling wind]
That's his hideout.
You can leave it to my art!
I'll just blow the
entire thing up!
We don't even know if
he's there or not!
[quick gasp]
[hiss]
Sand Snakes!
(Sasori)
It's useless...
...He already knows we're here.
Seriously?
Let's go.
I was under the impression that
Itachi would be the one to come,
but apparently the Akatsuki has
sent you two instead?
We'll kill you without
hesitation, traitor.
You think you can?
You're the Hidden
Stone boy, right?
From the Demolitions Unit?
I'm not a kid! So don't
treat me like one!
Keep watch from above and
make sure he doesn't escape.
What gives, my man? You
want to capture him
yourself or something?
Yeah, since you have no
grudges against him, right?
[annoyed grunt]
Well if you want back-up, just
call on me, all right?
Hmph!
I have the
geographical advantage.
So that's your art, huh?
You're aware of the Third
Kazekage's power, aren't you?
Yes.
My hobby is to collect things
that I find interesting,  so I
took a little something...
What the hell...!?
Huh...? What is that?
It's you Sasori How
dare you do this to me!
What is this, you damn snake?
The Third Kazekage,
whom you killed.
I used a Forbidden Jutsu to
resurrect him.
The outcome here will be
different than last time...
Enough of your complaints...
Now, then
...Your Human Puppet against
my Forbidden Jutsu.
Let's see which is best!
Damn you...
Iron Sand: Scattered Showers!
[shouting]
That puppet stops working when
Sand hits it, doesn't it?
Don't you dare lecture
me about puppets!
[fast whirring sound]
[grunt]
Unlike the real thing, I've
built lots of hidden tricks
into this puppet.
Now it's your turn...
Not yet...
What...?!
This is a form of immortality.
It can't die since
it's already dead.
We'll just see about that!
[gasp]
Hiya!
[explosions]
Well, then? How'd
you like my art?
Why won't it die?!
After you both die, I'm going to
resurrect you in the same way.
Although, to be honest,
what I really wanted was to
get hold of Itachi's body.
My man! Does that guy
have a weakness?!
Resurrection isn't one
of the Third's abilities
[grunt]
You're going to become
my pawns forever!
(Third Kazekage)
Stop kidding around.
[gasp]
Don't forget... that I
am the Third Kazekage!
...I am not your pawn!
Oh, my I wonder if my jutsu
wasn't complete...
Take this!
Did that get him?
Hey, no running!
Hiya!
Ha! My art!
is an explosion!
Hey, c'mon now...
(Sasori)
We searched the whole mountain
of rubble but didn't find his
corpse...
...So we can't say for
sure that we killed him.
(Deidara)
If he's still alive, I swear
I'll kill him myself.
...And what's with that
ridiculous jutsu, anyway?!
(Tendo Pain)
Do you know about it?
It's probably the Second
Hokage's Reanimation Jutsu.
It brings the dead back to life
and allows one to control them
like puppets.
You can't kill them
even if you try.
(Itachi)
You have to use a Sealing Jutsu
or suppress their movement
through force.
(Deidara)
Or just kill Orochimaru, right?
(Itachi)
Even that won't stop a
Reanimation...
(Deidara)
What do you mean?
(Tendo Pain)
Be wary of Orochimaru
from now on.
If he's alive, he's bound
to make another move.
(Deidara)
It would be really out of the
ordinary if he survived that
explosion, hmph!
(Sasori)
No one who joins us is
"ordinary."
(Konan)
It sounds like we have another
immortal on our hands now.
(Tendo Pain)
The Land of Steam has requested
that we eliminate a homicidal
maniac that's appeared.
(Kakuzu)
Don't they have their own
Hidden Steam shinobi?
(Konan)
Apparently, they can't kill him.
(Itachi)
So this maniac is immortal, too?
(Deidara)
Was he also
"reani-whatevered"
by Orochimaru?
(Tendo Pain)
I'm dispatching a different
team this time.
[birds chirping]
[gasp]
(Hidan)
You, there
[chuckle] Would you like
to join the Way of Jashin?
[bird noises]
This wasn't for money
or revenge.
This was done out of a
deep desire to kill.
There are many other ways to
quench a thirst for blood...
I believe he had some
other purpose in mind.
You really have a way of
irritating me, you know that?
And you...  did you come to make
sure I don't kill Itachi?
There are no other Sensory
types besides me. Plus
I'm certain that none of the
others are cut out to be
decoys...
Decoys?
[grunt]
(Hidan)
Hey!  You there!
Would you like to join
the Way of Jashin?
Way of Jashin?
Yeah, that's right! The
Way of Jashin...
And what exactly is that?
It's an ideology where you can
kill people and you won't be
punished at all.
In fact, it pleases Lord Jashin
even more if you do just that!
Oh
It's a wonderful
teaching, isn't it?
What do you say, wanna join up?
Ah. So you clearly must be that
homicidal maniac that we heard
about...
What?  A maniac? No, at all!
Look, I'm simply offering up
prayers to Lord Jashin.
And now it seems like I'm gonna
have to offer you up, as well!
Your thoughts?
He doesn't seem to
be a Reanimation.
Fine. I'll test him to
see how immortal he is.
Who are you guys?  And why are
you all dressed the same way?
What, are you in a band?
Let's see...  The gloomy one
over there plays bass guitar
The girl does vocals
and keyboards...
No, wait, the emo guy's got
be handling the vocals...
We're nothing like that.
I still think Lord Jashin would
like you guys as an offering...
[laugh] What's wrong?  Is
running all you can do?!
You're not getting away... ha!
[chuckle]
[spits blood]
What? Done so soon?
Ouch...
Huh?
Seriously, that...
really hurt!
[gasp]
I'll punish you in
the name of Jashin!
[grunt]
Thanks, but I'm
done with this now!
Looks like the rumors of
your immortality are true.
[chuckle] It's time to
start the ritual.
[lick]
Oh...
[gasp]
All the preparations
have been completed.
Die!
[gasps]
[groan]
One stab through the heart
Damn you...
It feels so good
All glory be to Lord Jashin!
[grunting]
You bastard You
got some nerve
Hey!  Why didn't you die?!
I'll beat you to death!
But you can't!
Did you see that?
Yes.  He licked Kakuzu's blood
and mentioned a ritual, probably
a jutsu...
Any damage he sustains affects
those whose blood he licked.
But that doesn't explain
his immortality...
(Konan)
Can you separate them?
Weren't you going
to eliminate him?
Well...
[crows screeching]
Hey! What's this?!
What's the big idea, Itachi?!
It seems that
we're recruiting him.
A guy like him?
Are you kidding me?  No way!
Whatever this "Akatsuki" is, I
already have a mission!
...To spread the Way of Jashin!
Then you'd be wise to
join the Akatsuki... for
the sake of your mission.
Why's that?
Assassination and war,
you name it...
...the Akatsuki are
killers for hire.
[metal scratching]
I still plan to continue
spreading the word about the Way
of Jashin, you know...
(Tendo Pain)
As you please.
Begin your missions. Our
two-man teams are in place.
(Kakuzu)
I didn't think I'd
be partnered with you.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Don't irritate me,
or I'll kill you.
Like I said, just try it!
I don't want your
heart, you know.
(Deidara)
Art is...
[explosion]
an explosion!
Huh? Yep, that's art.
I still don't get
what your art's about.
In time, you'll come to
understand the aesthetics of
something fleeting.  Hmph!
It's our leader
Huh?
(Tendo Pain)
A shinobi village by the name of
the Hidden Sound was recently
founded.
It's possible that Orochimaru
is involved with it.
What?  That guy again?!
(Tendo Pain)
You two covertly check them out.
Yeah, 'cause we're the best ones
at sneaking around behind the
scenes.
Don't you worry,
I'll find him!
He'll go boom!
You don't know what
"covertly" means, do you?
[waves crashing]
[thuds]
(Tendo Pain)
There's been an incident in
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Orochimaru's behind it.
Orochimaru used shinobi from the
Hidden Sound and Hidden Sand to
wage war against the Leaf,
but he failed to destroy it.
Serves him right!
(Tendo Pain)
The Third Hokage died, and
the village was damaged.
Orochimaru escaped, but
no one knows where.
I'll send someone to
investigate, but-
I'll handle it.
(Tendo Pain)
Then I'll leave this to you, as
well as the status of the Leaf's
Jinchuriki.
(Kisame)
Seems they averted total
destruction...
...but still sustained
massive damage.
The Village was at the height
of prosperity. Tragic.
That's not like you.
So even you have feelings for
your birthplace, is that it?
No...
Not at all...
(Thinking)
Sasuke... I hope
that you're safe.
♪
(Itachi)
It's been a long time Sasuke.
(Sasuke)
Itachi Uchiha I hope
you're ready to die.
(Kisame)
Well The Sharingan...
...And he looks an
awful lot like you...
...Itachi, who is this kid?
(Itachi)
He's my younger brother.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Truth."
(Itachi)
So you've awakened your
Sharingan...
♪