[yawning]
Boy, it sure gets boring
when everything goes
right on a trip.
Captain Yamato! You have
anything for me to do?
You, Aoba?
[sighing]
I wonder how everyone's
doing back at the Hidden
Leaf... Maybe one of
them'll come by again.
[grunting]
[heavy breathing]
Good morning. You're up
early.
Good morning,
Tenten!
With this war on the way,
we have to make sure to
hone our skills.
You're right...
Huh!
They say that this war is
going center on Naruto,
but it's kind of hard to
imagine why that is...
I wonder how he's doing
on his mission.
Probably eating some
local ramen special! He
didn't seem too worried.
Uh!
Lady Hinata! We'd best
be going soon!
For what?
We have a big clan
meeting today. So, bye...
We, the Hyuga Clan, will
play an important role
here in Hidden Leaf
Village.
Expect to be given
Sensory-type duties
once the impending Fourth
Great Ninja War begins.
Assignments will vary,
but in a crisis, we'll
need one person to unify
and lead the whole clan.
I can't. I've been
assigned to the rear guard.
And Hanabi's still too young
for real combat.
Neji, I want you to
command our clan on the
front lines.
(shocked, scandalized,
tittering about how
irregular this choice is
reax)
Neji? From the Side
Branch?
But what of Lady Hinata
from the Main Branch?
The entire clan is well
aware of Neji's abilities.
Go, Neji. Do well.
"The Girls Get Together"
Please! Reconsider!
Lord Hiashi, you're aware
how hard Lady Hinata has
trained these past few
years.
She proved her bravery
when she stood up to Pain
all by herself.
A favor to ask? What is
it, Hinata?
Neji...
Please, could you use your
help to train in the
Gentle Fist.
Lady Hinata, you're the
Main Branch's-
Hanabi is the Main
Branch's heir.
Did you know, Neji? Naruto
left to train with Master
Jiraiya.
While he's gone...
I want to train as much
as I can, too!
I don't know if my
instruction will be too
strict or not, but
okay.
Oh, thank you!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Gentle Step Twin Lion
Fists!
[grunting]
Quite excellent, Lady
Hinata.
[panting]
Heh!
There's no doubt she has
the potential to develop
further.
Then--
This isn't just about
being a Hyuga. She does
not have the disposition
to lead shinobi.
What do you mean by that?
Lady Hinata is simply
far too kind.
Since I can't serve as
captain anymore for
obvious reasons... Team
Eight has been disbanded.
You're all scattered on
separate missions.
I really feel quite bad
about that. You forgive me?
Of course.
Thank you.
It's so much easier to
talk woman-to-woman. It
wouldn't be as smooth
with Kiba and Shino.
It is, really?
Yes, of course!
Huh? Oh, it's Hinata.
Hello, Shikamaru!
Sensei.
You seem so busy.
I was just on a mission,
but I don't have it as
rough as Lady Tsunade or
my dad.
So you were out of the
village, then?
Tenten and I went to
deliver supplies to Naruto
and the others out on the
ship.
Really? To Naruto?
That's right; and he's
doing just fine, don't
worry.
Oh, that's why this
morning, Tenten was--
I guess Sakura, Ino and
Choji ran into him by
chance on a mission, too.
Oh, that's right; I
almost forgot: Lady
Tsunade was looking for
you.
Is it for a mission?
Who knows?
I'll stop by again,
Kurenai Sensei.
She's always been like
that when it comes to
Naruto.
So? Did you decide on a
name yet?
Huh?
For the baby.
I've been giving that
a lot of thought.
Lady Tsunade!
Oooinnnk.
What were they thinking?
How could it end up like
this?
Where's Lady Tsunade?
Oh, hi. She stepped out.
Let me see, where is
she supposed to be right
now...
Um... Ah! She's scheduled
to be with the Cipher
Corps. But I doubt that
things are on schedule.
I'll go there. Thanks.
Okay. Fine.
Frankly, Lady Tsunade
left already.
Oh, I see; too bad...
The Cipher Corps has been
very busy working on a
secret code that's going
to be used by the Allied
Shinobi Force.
We got chewed out because
we're running behind
schedule.  [giggling]
She said she's going to
check on the food supply
situation next.
Thanks, I'll go see.
Good luck.
No, Lady Tsunade's
already come and gone.
Hey! What's up, Hinata? You
here to help us out or
what?
Oh, uh, no, I'm sorry,
I'm not.
I wish they'd send more
help. We can barely keep
with all these food
deliveries!
We need 'em! We don't
know how long the war
will last!
Yeah. Whatever.
Ya know, Lady Tsunade did
mention that she was going
to check on Ninja Tools.
Well, she was here, but
she left.
Um, Tenten...
Did you see Naruto while
out on your mission?
Yeah, when I delivered
supplies to his ship.
Are there any other
missions like that, do
you know?
Don't look at me; I
wouldn't know that!
Ask Lady Tsunade. She
said she was going to the
Medical Corps.
Thanks, I'll try there.
[chuckling]
No, Lady Tsunade couldn't
make it.
Huh?!
I was just told to submit
a report to her.
But everyone's been
helping out.
I have at least some
knowledge about
medicines.
And they put me in charge
of the food pills, isn't
that great?
Oh, there you are!
Hmm?
Hey!
Tenten...
What can I do for you?
What do you say we get
together tonight and do
it up a little?
We can all go to Barbe-Q!
Barbe-Q?! You can
count me in!
Sounds great.
Sorry, boys, but you
men aren't invited.
Huh?
Aw. But why not?
Because I think it's time
that all of us had a
girls-only get-together.
Right?
It is...?!
We're gonna have a girls'
night out!
For combat units one
through five...
...we will assign
personnel according to
their skills.
The Commando Unit and
Support units are going
to handle surprise
attacks.
Those units will be  reinforced
with shinobi from the
Hidden Leaf and the other
villages.
You must slow down! We
can't keep up! You must
be more respect for the
elderly.
It's your age that I'm
counting on!
Oh...?
You've managed to live
through two of the Great
Ninja Wars so far.
I want you to pass on the
wisdom of your
experience.
Sometimes I feel that
perhaps I shouldn't have
lived so long.
You two are lucky.
I've quit drinking and
gambling and still can't
handle all this planning!
And I've come to believe
that it's because I no
longer have any peers to
lean on.
There's no doubt that
times were hard for your
generation...
Your class in particular
lost so many.
These days, I even wish
for Orochimaru to be
here.
If he were here,... I
seriously doubt he'd side
with the Hidden Leaf.
Forgive me. I was just
venting.
That's fine... that's what
I'm here for.
Excuse me!
Pardon my intrusion!
What is it?
The Feudal Lord would
like to speak with you
now, if it's not
inconvenient.
Which it looks
like it is.
This is why I can't
get any work done.
Pardon me, Lady
Tsunade...
Oh. Yes, Hinata?
Do you have a mission for
me?
No.
But I did receive
Hiashi's report that Neji
will be leading the Hyuga
on the front lines.
That's right.
Hinata. You must not take
this as a rejection of
your skills.
Uh--
Just keep doing what you
must do for now.
It will suffice.
Lady Tsunade, we must
hurry.
I know.
But... my Father--
--doesn't believe that
I'm strong enough.
So Barbe-Q reopened?
I made us a reservation!
Ooh! Beef tongue with
salt!
The new menu has a
special Ladies Combo!
It's such a good deal!
And I just can't resist
a good deal!
Frankly, my favorite here
is the offal!
Mm--
Did you ladies
decide on drinks?
Great! Excuse me! We're
ready to order!
Thanks for coming!
I figured if the girls
were having a get-together,
the boys should have one of
their own, too.
So let's eat and drink
until our bellies are full!
So, what did the Feudal Lord
want to discuss?
That was no "discussion!"
He only cared about what
might happen to him! What
if this? What if that?
Over and over!
I'm done for today!
What?!
Shizune! I'm going
drinking!
But you swore off
alcohol!
I'm drinking tonight!
Okay! Oh, no.
Here's to us!
Cheers!
So, why are we
all getting together?
Well, everybody's just
been so busy with getting
ready for the war...
We need some stress
relief, right?
Yeah, all of us need to
unwind!
There aren't any
ordinary missions anymore.
Everything's focused on
getting ready for the war.
Frankly, I appreciate
being invited tonight,
but how does everybody
here know each other?
That's funny. Why do we
always end up hanging out
with each other, anyway?
Maybe it's because we all
took the Chunin Exams
together or something...
[gasping]
Oh, right; I bet that's
it.
We're basically
classmates. And we sure
did go on a lot of
missions together!
Boy, the Chunin Exam...
You were such a nuisance
back then!
You're sure one to talk!
Hmmph.
[laughing]
To be honest, I still
don't get this Allied
Shinobi Force thing.
It's like putting all
kinds of meat on one
plate...
Nothing wrong with a
little variety!
But we're not talking
about food here, Choji!
The Hidden Leaf Village
just doesn't really have
any close ties
with other villages aside
from the Hidden Sand Village.
I've heard there have
been issues with the
Hidden Cloud.
I'm sure it's not just
us. With the villages'
histories,
there's bound to be
issues between and
inside all of them.
I agree, every village
has one kind of grudge or
another against all the
other villages.
And yet the Five Kage all
agreed to this alliance.
That means the Akatsuki
is quite formidable.
Well, when war breaks
out, we'll all just have
to fight our hardest...
Without really knowing
who's fighting on either
side of us.
You've never been afraid
of strangers, Kiba.
Hey, shut up! It's just a
big pain to remember
their scents.
When all of us are
together like this, it
brings back memories of
that mission...
But then, the Chunin Exam
was cancelled, When it
was only half way done.
You mean when the Leaf
Village was attacked?
So much has happened, but
we haven't lost anyone,
and we still get together
like this.
It must mean
our generation is
exceptional!
Yeah, you're right. The
only one who's really
gone is Sasuke!
Oh, boy. Guess I
shouldn't have said
that...
Hey, Sakura, come on
back; it's okay!
Are you talking about
that time we went to
get Sasuke back?
But we failed.
The reason is because you
didn't take me along.
You're seriously still
upset about that?!
Well, it certainly was a
tough battle, and yet
all of us made it through
okay somehow.
Yes. And it turned out
to be a good experience.
Uhhhh...
Now both of them are
depressed.
Huh?
That isn't true! I'm not
depressed!
[gasping]
I'm glad...
Huh?
...that I took the Chunin
Exam.
You lost to Neji, but you
gave it your all! That's
what matters.
Mm-hm. It's because
he cheered me on back
then.
Because Naruto supported
me, I was able to do my
best.
Naruto. He was
unpredictable even way
back then,
but who ever
would've imagined that
he'd become the village
hero one day?
Yeah!
And this time it's now
our turn to protect
Naruto.
Uh!
Our turn... to protect
Naruto.
That kid can still be a
real grade-A idiot,
though.
I know!
Oh, I think these are
good to go!
Yeah, let's eat!
So! Finally found your
appetite!
Yes, I need to become
stronger.
The marinated pork jowls
you ordered are ready now!
Yummy! Gimme!
You'll turn into a pig!
What are you talking
about? They're full of
collagen! It's good for
you!
It kind of feels like
someone's missing without
Naruto...
That is true. Naruto would
make our group feel more
complete.
Man, I wonder what he's
doing out there...
I'll bet that he's not
having barbecued meat!
No, not while he's at
sea.
Fish again, huh? Why's it
always gotta be fish...?
[sighing]
Some barbecued meat would
be nice once in a while,
you know!
C'mon! I've got to have
meat when I'm drinking!
Meat! Meat! Get me some
meat!
... slow down!
Let go of me! And go find
me some food already!
[laughing]
Oh! What's all this? A
girls' night out?
Lady Tsunade!
Uhh--
Uh, yeah! This is a
girls-only get-together!
Girls' get-together?
Move over, move over!
But Lady Tsunade,
you're not really a
girl anymo-
Is it my chest? They're
too big now, aren't they?
First, bring me a drink!
Oh, you're way past your
first drink, milady.
So, what are you up to?
Are all of you talking
about the boys that you
like?
We were talking about the
Chunin Exam.
We were just reminiscing.
With things the way they
are now... we thought
having some fun together
would be a nice break.
I see.
Please, eat!
Sure.
Hinata. What I said
before...
I'm fine...
I know what I must do
now.
Thanks to all of you!
You know, you
girls... are so lucky.
Mm.
All right!
Who wants to do a little
gambling?!
Time for the Princess
Game!
Lady Tsunade--
Who's gonna be the
Princess?!
Did Tenten really invite
Lady Tsunade to the
girls' gathering?
I know, talk about
daring...
Lady Fifth must be
feeling pretty stressed
out.
Boy, did I eat! It's been
a while since I've had
that much barbecue!
Okay, time for the
after-party!
What'll we do?
I'm going home. Gotta get
up early.
Me too.
Frankly, I have to go
back to work.
Oh yeah, I wanted to
finish up some stuff
tonight, too.
Sorry, Lady Tsunade, but
we're all gonna head home.
[exchanging goodbyes]
What a dedicated bunch,
aren't they?
Agreed!
All right! Let's drink
till dawn!
What?! No!
That's what I'd like to
do, but let's get back to
work!
Oh, right!
Neji...
I want to become much
stronger than I am right
now.
I think you're strong
enough.
But... this next war is
to protect Naruto...
So...
I must become much, much
stronger.
I have to be strong!
Don't you see?
It's because of Naruto
that I've come as far as
I have.
Lady Hinata,... I'm the
same...
It's all thanks to him
that I'm free.
Ah! Welcome back.
It's good to be home.
I'll be all right!
Huh--
Thank you, Ko.
You're from the Main
Branch. You should be
leading the clan on the
front lines.
No. You're suited for the
job, and there should be
no Main or Side Branch
now.
Unless all of us stand
united, this war cannot
be won.
Huh!
You're livelier than
usual Bushier Brow
Sensei!
Of course! Nothing's
better than the feel of
solid ground under your
feet.
Well, it's only till
the next harbor.
Oh, by the way, I
overheard something back
there at the harbor, there
may be imposters here.
Imposters...? What
imposters?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Naruto's
Imposter.
What?! Who are you?