[footsteps]
[heavy breathing]
ITACHI: In the main
hall of Nagato's Shrine,
underneath the seventh
tatami mat from the far right
is the clan's secret
gathering place.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I see now.
So that's what it all means.
FUGAKU: Now then, that's my boy.
-When were alone, the only one
he talks about is you, Sasuke.
-I just wish I knew
what kinds of things
he said to her about me.
ITACHI: If you wish to kill me
one day in hate and revenge.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Brother, no matter
what darkness may await me,
if it means killing you,
I will meet it head on.
And whatever happens,
I will get that power.
-I fed my hatred
and gained power,
and now I'm here to
settle this, Itachi.
You will die right here.
You'll fall by my hand.
[theme music]
-Now, Itachi, you asked for
it, so here is it at last.
I'll make your death a reality.
-Jutsu that can't be evaded,
just like the Amaterasu?
What is it?
What kind of jutsu could it be?
[thunder]
BLACK ZETSU: That's it.
That's what Sasuke's fire
style earlier was for.
WHITE ZETSU: What do you mean?
BLACK ZETSU:
Sasuke's real target
was never Itachi to begin with.
That's not what the fire
style attack was for.
WHITE ZETSU: I
still don't get it.
What does that mean?
BLACK ZETSU: He shot his
fire style jutsu into the sky
to cause the ambient
temperature of the atmosphere
to rise rapidly and create
an ascending air current.
WHITE ZETSU: A what?
Ascending air current?
BLACK ZETSU: To form
a cumulo nimbus.
In other words, to
create a thunder cloud.
WHITE ZETSU: I don't understand.
What does that have to--
BLACK ZETSU: He doesn't
have to use his own chakra.
Instead, he intends
to take advantage
of the enormous energy
in the atmosphere
to create a lightning
style jutsu.
WHITE ZETSU: Which one?
BLACK ZETSU:
Whichever it is, it'll
be on a totally different scale
from what anyone can create
using change and
nature chakra alone.
I see.
Sasuke deliberately
lured Itachi outside,
so he could use the heat
generated by the Amaterasu.
-This jutsu guides the
lightning down from the heavens.
All I have to do is merely
direct it's power right at you.
BLACK ZETSU: Just as I thought.
That's why this jutsu
can't be evaded.
-Why not?
BLACK ZETSU: Ligtning flashes
in 1/1000 of a second.
It's faster than sound.
-This jutsu is called Kirin.
-What's that?
BLACK ZETSU: Sasuke has
tamed the lightning.
-Come.
You'll be gone with
the thunder clap.
BLACK ZETSU: Such power.
WHITE ZETSU: So did Itachi die?
-It's done.
It's finally over.
ITACHI: Is this the death
you had imagined for me then?
-Damn you!
-That's--
-If I hadn't had this,
I'd have been dead.
-What's that?
-You really have gotten
stronger, Sasuke.
Now, it's my turn.
I'm going to reveal to you my
final trump card, the Susanoo.
I'm going to reveal to my
-The Susanoo.
-Yes, the one other jutsu.
Once the Tsukuyomi and the
Amaterasu were awakened,
it also took root in
these eyes of mine.
Sasuke, is that it
for your jutsu then?
If you have anything
else up your sleeve,
now's your last
chance to play it.
The real battle's
just beginning.
-The sky is clearing.
BLACK ZETSU: Seems
that last jutsu
was limited to only one shot.
-What's that?
-What's the matter?
You use up all your chakra
and run out of options?
-What?
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
I can give it to you.
I can lend you the
power that you need.
-Damn it!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
You need me.
Don't you, dear Sasuke?
I thought that you wanted
to take revenge on Itachi?
Now, release me.
Release my power and you can
fulfill your dream at last.
-That feels like Orochimaru's
eight headed serpent jutsu.
-What is that?
BLACK ZETSU: This is
all because Sasuke
tried to squeeze out more
power despite not having
any more chakra left.
Orochimaru's chakra, which
Sasuke absorbed and suppressed
has shoved its way
to the surface.
-And now, it finally emerges.
-Wait, is that-- Well,
father was always
regurgitating something
out of his mouth like that.
BLACK ZETSU: Slithering
around like the snake he is.
-This is it.
This is what I've
been waiting for.
Thanks to you, the
repressive chakra is gone.
And now, at last,
I have the chance
to take over this
child's body for good.
And so-- [laughing]
Did you truly
believe that a puny
attack like that
could take down the likes of me?
Ah.
-Well, Sasuke, what
will you do next then?
-This sword, it can't be.
The Totsuka blade.
Itachi, it was hidden
in you all along.
-What's with that sword?
BLACK ZETSU: The
Totsuka Blade, also
know as the Sakegari Blade.
It's a sword of Sealing.
It is said to trap
and seal away those
who it pierces in a
genjutsu world of drunken
stupor for all eternity.
The blade itself is
imbued with sealing jutsu
and is a variant of
the Kusanagi Blade.
Orochimaru has long
searched for that sword.
WHITE ZETSU: It's
power is immense.
-This is it, Sasuke.
-So what's with Itachi's jutsu?
BLACK ZETSU: That
jutsu he calls Susanoo,
it seems to be awfully risky.
WHITE ZETSU: But Sasuke can no
longer maintain his Sharingan,
and he's also been stripped
of Orochimaru's chakra.
Don't you think Itachi's
already won this?
-And now, your eyes are mine.
I'll take my time
retrieving them.
-Ah!
-Whoa, what the hell?
BLACK ZETSU: Something's
wrong with him.
[coughing]
-Damn it.
-That Susanoo jutsu
of his, it's simply
repelling every single
one of Sasuke's attacks.
BLACK ZETSU: There's
no mistaking it.
It's another spirit weapon.
It's called the Yata
Mirror, and it's
said to deflect all things.
With that and the Totsuka
Blade for attacking,
Itachi's invincible.
-They're my eyes.
They're mine.
-Ahhh!
[groaning]
[heavy breathing]
WHITE ZETSU: Itachi collapsed.
No way.
Is Itachi really dead?
BLACK ZETSU: It's
Sasuke's victory.
-There's something
I still don't get.
BLACK ZETSU: Like what?
WHITE ZETSU: I know that
Itachi is stronger than this.
He was moving quite strangely.
Even you said that something
seemed off about him.
BLACK ZETSU: That's true.
He couldn't evade
or counterattacks
that he should have
been able to handle,
and he was coughing up blood.
Perhaps he sustained
some serious damage,
even before the battle.
WHITE ZETSU: Could
it have been caused
by using the Sharingan too much?
BLACK ZETSU: Not sure.
I don't think we can
draw any conclusions.
WHITE ZETSU: He was close to
getting Sasuke's eyes too.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Damn it.
What is this guy?
All he's doing is
try to stall us.
Why can't I hit him
with my rasengan?
No, that's not it.
I did him it.
I know it, but-- damn it,
we can't waste anymore time.
I have to get past this guy.
I have to get to Sasuke.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"The Mystery of Tobi."
Be sure to tune in.
You won't want to miss it.