-Without a doubt, he's matured.
But he's still
not strong enough.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
It hurts, but I
know it's just a genjutsu.
I gotta fight through it.
SASUKE: Naruto.
Naruto.
-Is that-- Is that Sasuke?
-It's been far too long, Naruto.
I should've finished you off
the last time we saw each other.
-You're finished.
-Why?
Why, Naruto?
When Sasuke left, why didn't
you bring him back to me?
I was wrong to believe in you.
-You couldn't even protect
your closest friends.
I expected more from you,
but you're a failure.
GAARA: As always.
No matter what,
you come out ahead.
Only you achieve happiness.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Just a genjutsu.
I know that's all
it is, but still.
-Naruto.
Why did I believe in you?
-You're such a disappointment.
Naruto.
-Such an easy life.
So lucky.
-Now, at long last,
I'll finish you!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
Damn it!
Damn it.
This isn't happening,
but I can't--
NARUTO: Let me
get this straight.
I mean, I get the basics of
what you're talking about,
the part where you temporarily
stop your chakra flow
and direct the extra power at
the enemy to disrupt his flow.
That make sense.
But what if you do that
and it still doesn't work?
What can I do when that happens?
If I just can't
break the genjutsu?
-Hm.
In that case, I guess
you just give up.
-Huh?
-Sometimes, you have to accept
that you're plum out of luck
and throw in the towel.
You never know what'll
happen with genjutsu.
-You gotta be kidding me!
Then I guess there wasn't any
point to the whole me falling
into the river and
getting drenched lesson.
-Of course, if you've got your
comrades along to back you up,
there's still a chance
you could pull through it.
What I mean is, if you somehow
got an ally to actually touch
you, they could funnel some of
their chakra into your body.
The sudden surge of energy might
disrupt the dangerous chakra
flowing inside of you.
And then, you could
break the genjutsu.
-You liar.
You broke your promise to me.
-Such a disappointment.
-You always get everything.
-I will end you.
-Naruto.
-Sakura.
-Kakashi-sensei
-Naruto.
-Gaara.
-Sasuke.
S-Somebody give me chakra.
Kakashi-sensei,
Sa-- Sakura Please.
I need your chakra.
-Naruto!
Are you all right?
-Wh-- What happened to me?
-You were caught in a genjutsu,
but you're gonna be fine.
We all funneled our chakra
into you and broke the hold.
-I don't get it.
Where did his shadow clones go?
-What do you mean,
his shadow clones?
Why, he's used no such thing
the entire time we've been here.
-Yeah, all of a sudden,
you kind of freaked out
and started shooting off your
Rasengan at absolutely nothing.
Don't you remember any of that?
-Rasengan!
You're saying I was
already in the genjutsu?
-I'm afraid he's using more
than just a visual jutsu.
-I think it's about
time for the main event.
Better get it together, Naruto.
-Hey, snap out of it, will you?
-Come on, Naruto.
I'll show you how it's done.
[theme music]
-Fire Style.
Phoenix Flower Jutsu.
-Whoa, what a dodge.
-He's not done yet!
-Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu.
-Lightning Blade!
-Rasengan!
-What happened?
Did he do it?
-Naruto!
-Well now.
He's learned an interesting
jutsu, hasn't he?
However--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Man.
I didn't think he'd
survive it that easy.
I could've sworn we were
gonna get the drop on him
with Kakashi-sensei's
Lightning Blade as a diversion.
His Sharingan is a real problem.
He can instantly foresee
what I'm gonna do.
Not again!
No way this is gonna work
unless I combo attack
with Kakashi-sensei.
On top of that, I
need a powerful jutsu
that'll take him
out in one shot.
Looks like I gotta
try out my new trick.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Where's Naruto?
Did he make it?
Wait.
Is he using another genjutsu?
The Hidden Mist Jutsu?
-Don't worry, my dear.
This jutsu is Kakashi's.
-Wait.
Are you saying--
-But the mist is
getting thicker,
so we both need to focus now.
You must keep your
attention firmly fixed
on Kakashi's presence.
-Right.
I will.
-The Hidden Mist Jutsu.
Quite an effective
technique to prevent one
from casting a genjutsu.
Unless, of course, one
posesses the Sharingan.
Kakashi.
Can we please stop this
childish game of hide and seek?
-Sure.
Why not?
-Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
get where you're going.
Awesome move, Kakashi-sensei.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): That
fireball was different.
Something's not right.
[music playing]
-Don't tell me Kakashi-sensei
is caught in Itachi's genjutsu.
-Nicely done.
You certainly have
mastery if your jutsu.
Your Earth Style move hid
you from view for a moment,
so I didn't notice the change.
It all makes sense.
Of course my genjutsu
has no effect on you,
because you're a shadow clone.
-He's fast.
-Do you think that he--
-I do.
-The game is over.
-Asa Kujaku!
-Well, that pretty
much wraps that one up.
-Attack him and my shadow clone.
Now, Naruto!
-I'm on it!
-Huh?
Improve my Rasengan?
-That's what I'm saying.
-Come on.
I'm practically an
expert with the Rasengan.
What I really want to
learn are some new jutsu.
What do you say?
-Don't get ahead of yourself.
Do you honestly
think the Rasengan
you use now is good enough?
Think back to when you
fought with Orochimaru's four
eyed friend.
Remember what happened then?
-I don't know what
jutsu you learned,
but you'll need to be
more subtle than that
if you want to hit me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): It's no use.
I'm not gonna be able
to hit a moving target.
JIRAIYA: And then what happened?
What did you do next?
-OK.
Let's see you
dodge me this time.
Rasengan!
JIRAIYA: Are you just
gonna let your hand get
cut like that every time
you face a tough enemy?
Is that your plan?
-This is exactly what
I'm talking about.
That's why I need a new jutsu!
-Naruto.
I can't believe I'm
hearing this from you.
Don't you remember, or are you
telling me you forgot already?
The Rasengan is a precious gift.
A jutsu passed down
from the Fourth Hokage.
-Oh, I, uh-- No,
I didn't forget!
-I'll let it slide.
The Fourth Hokage is responsible
for creating the Rasengan Now
the challenge for you will be
to figure out how to perfect it
and make it unique.
It'll be hard, but I bet
you can improve the Rasengan
and make it your
own original jutsu.
-Huh?
-You're saying I could
develop my own original jutsu?
-That's exactly right.
If you can harness the power of
that massive chakra of yours,
it would make your strike super
focused and more destructive.
A power that can't be done
without your particular chakra.
Your Rasengan would be
a one of a kind jutsu.
-Yeah.
My very own, original Rasengan
-In order to increase the
power of the Rasengan,
you'll first need to master how
to infuse more of your chakra.
I won't lie to you.
The training will be tough.
But if you can
withstand it, you'll
emerge with by far the strongest
weapon in your arsenal.
We'll call it--
-Giant Rasengan!
-Incredible.
-My word.
What power.
-What the-- What's
up with that smirk?
-It's strange.
I got the feeling I'd fought
him somewhere before, but--
-So, you do not remember
ever meeting this man?
-That's weird, 'cause
from what he was saying,
it seemed like he
knew everything
about you, Guy-sensei.
-Something's going on here.
-His-- His face.
-Wha-- What on Earth?
-When we were fighting, I
could feel something was off.
-I don't get it.
What the heck just happened?
-It has to be some kinda jutsu.
-But that man.
LEE: Who is that?
Sensei, what does this mean?
-I don't know.
But there's one thing
that I am sure of.
There is no way
I've ever met him.
-Lady Chiyo, do you
know who this person is?
-I do.
His name is Yura, and he's a
Jonin from our own village.
[theme music]
MAN: Seeking the
truth always involves
putting your life in jeopardy,
and this particular mystery
sent us into the desert, where
we overcame the blazing sun,
deadly sandstorms, and
poisonous scorpions.
But it was all worth it to
cut through the darkness
and get the story.
The secret of an enigmatic
statue will now be revealed.
Answers at last, the intrigue
of the shinobi, uncharted lands,
and the mystery of
the giant statue!
-That's just a statute
of the previous Kazekage.
NARUTO: Next time.
The Secret of Jinchuriki.
[theme music]
NARUTO: And now, Notable
People in the Leaf Village.
In this feature, you get to meet
famous people from our village.
Today, we'll be introducing--
-Sorry I'm late!
I'm the one and only
Jiraiya, the sexy beast
who strikes fear in
the hearts of men!
-What's the deal, Pervy Sage?
You're totally upstaging me!
-Don't be just a
stick in the mud, kid.
Just get on with my
introduction, will you?
NARUTO: Fine.
Um.
He's one of the Leaf's
three legendary Sannin.
JIRAIYA: That's right.
NARUTO: A powerhouse who
trained with the Third Hokage
and taught the Fourth Hokage.
JIRAIYA: Go on.
NARUTO: And the author of
a bunch of boring books
Kakashi-sensei's always reading.
-Hmph.
Like a kid could understand
how great my books are.
NARUTO: Not to mention,
drinks, ladies, money.
These three things are
forbidden to shinobi,
but this Pervy
Sage doesn't care!
JIRAIYA: Hey, that's no
way to talk to your master.
I taught you the
Rasengan, after all.
NARUTO: Ha!
If you want my respect,
then how about paying me
back all the money you owe me?
What the-- He's gone!
Aw man.
Where'd he go?