So how the hell am I
supposed to beat that guy?
Well, that I don't know,
I'm afraid.
Uh, hey, hold on, Octopops
trained here too, didn't he?
I can just go and ask him!
No. he's never going to tell
me. Not with his attitude.
Perhaps...
I wonder if Octopops
had a dark side too?
Hey, Motoi?
Can you help me out?
Can you tell me more
about Octopops?
Like, how he grew up,
and what his
personality is like.
Maybe I can get a few
hints from all that stuff.
Then I can figure out what's
different between us and why he
can control his Tailed Best!
If you're also a Jinchuriki,
you know what it's like to
live with that burden.
Tell me, isn't that true?
Yeah, I do know
all about it.
And he should be able
to understand what it's
been like for me, too!
To be honest, I don't
normally like to prattle
on about other people.
But Naruto, you're
also a Jinchuriki just
like Master Bee is.
And controlling the Nine Tails
will lead to world peace.
I'll do it.
Ah! Thank you!
Now, I told you earlier,
As a fellow Jinchuriki,
you know what it's like
to live with that burden.
As you can well imagine.
Incredible power breeds
dread and ill feelings.
Master Bee was long feared and
resented by the other villagers.
But he never got depressed or
complained, not even once.
He was always cheerful,
continuously working
the people around him.
Instead of feeling shame
at being a Jinchuriki,
he turned it into a positive.
It seemed to me that he decided
to take pride in himself and
even added self-expression.
Yo!
And the main reason that
he was able to take pride
in being a Jinchuriki,
Was probably,
thanks to his older brother,
the Raikage.
For ages now,
to prevent betrayal,
Jinchuriki have almost always
been selected from blood
relations of the Five Kage,
like siblings or spouses.
A Jinchuriki is both an ultimate
power to protect the Kage,
And a symbol of the
Kage's ultimate strength.
I believe Master Bee strove
diligently to become a worthy
Jinchuriki for Lord Raikage.
It is said that he mastered
this Waterfall of Truth
challenge in no time at all.
I have deep respect,
for the kind of
person Master Bee is.
In my eyes,
he is a true hero.
To be such a
well-loved Jinchuriki,
Master Bee must be
quite a great man.
And you must be, too.
Ah...
Wait, that's it!
I've got it!
You can go ask Ocotopops
for training hints on my
behalf, Motoi!
Would you please
do that for me?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Aaagh!
Come on!
Why not?!
I am not worthy of
such an errand.
Huh?
Because... I once tried
to kill Master Bee!
[gasp]
"Killer Bee and Motoi"
But why?! You said
that you respected
Octopops! Just now!
I'm sure there's
some explanation.
So, what was it, tell us?!
It's time I confessed.
Since you're a Jinchuriki
too, I think it's okay to
tell you about that incident.
Incident?
What do you mean?
It all took place
30 years ago.
[roar]
Back then, the Jinchuriki
that contained the Eight Tails,
wasn't strong enough
to completely control
the Tailed Beast.
The Eight Tails would get
loose, rampage, and wreak
havoc on the Hidden Cloud.
Each time, the previous
Raikage-Lord Third-would
stop the Eight Tails
with his elite force.
Listen! I need you
to hold the Eight
Tails still!
And while you're doing that,
I'll imprison him in the
Sealing Urn.
Understood.
Okay! Get to it.
(om throwing effort)
[roar]
[snort]
Huaaagh!
[roar]
Aaah!
Damn it! The
Sealing Jutsu chain!
We can't give up!
Or the Hidden Cloud Village
will be destroyed!
There. Got him.
[big roar]
Now move in!
Pin him down!
Back off, accursed humans!
Yaaahh!
[roar]
Huaah!
[roaring]
[panting]
Every time, they somehow
managed to subdue the
Eight Tails and shove him
back into the Sealing Urn.
There were always
casualties.
However, despite the risk, it
was crucial to possess the Eight
Tails to preserve the balance of
power between the nations.
So the Jinchuriki
experiments continued.
(cm mild sitting effort)
And among the many
countless casualties...
[distraught]
...was my father.
You lost your father
to Master Bee.
So that's why--
That's not it.
Master Bee and I were
close friends once.
We were both only five years
old when my father fell.
Ha ha ha!
Yea-eah!
You did it, Bee!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
Ah?!
The Jinchuriki responsible
for my father's death,
died when the Eight Tails
was extracted and sealed.
That was the
previous Jinchuriki.
It was after that tragedy that
Master Bee was chosen to be the
Eight Tails' Jinchuriki.
Why, then?
Why try to
kill Master Bee?
I assumed that it
wasn't possible to
control the Eight Tails.
I believed that there
would always continue
to be more victims.
My hatred toward the
Eight Tails continued to grow.
I was only a child...
But all I could think
about was getting revenge.
Got a song in my heart
that's gotta come out,
it's gonna make y'all
scream and shout,
ain't no doubt the rhymes I
spout are what I'm all about.
Yeah!
Ain't nothing gonna keep me down
or make me frown, yo!
Master Bee...
was always laughing.
I started hating him more
and more because it seemed
like he didn't care at all.
My hatred of Eight Tails shifted
to Master Bee, his Jinchuriki.
I thought...
if I killed Master Bee,
the Eight Tails would also die.
Hm?
[gasp]
Ha ha!
So, I attacked Master Bee
from behind.
But when I failed, I became
terrified and ran away.
I had masked my face,
but it was possible that
Master Bee recognized me.
As a result,
I just stopped
talking to him.
But after all that,
how did you come to
respect Master Bee, then?
My hatred didn't
disappear overnight.
For a long time, I continued
to follow Master Bee and
keep an eye on him.
But, I wasn't the only one.
Master Bee was shunned
and despised by the
villagers all the time.
Yo!
[beatboxes]
Yeah!
Huh??
Get lost!
You disgust me!
Even though he was forced
to become a Jinchuriki
because of politics,
and existed to
protect the village,
he continued to be
ostracized by the villagers.
[chuckle]
Oh, yeah? You think you're bad?
That's far from the worst
I've ever had.
Yo, yo, check it, yo!
I ain't gonna get mad,
I'll just keep being glad.
C'mon, c'mon, yo!
Yo! Hey, yo!
Almost anyone else would have
gone insane. And I realized,
Master Bee's suffering was
even greater than mine.
Why tell us this?
Well, truth be told,
I'd rather have
Master Bee hear it.
But the reason that I'm
telling Naruto this,
is that he's a
fellow Jinchuriki.
Hm.
And yes, I am well aware
that I ought to tell Master Bee
the truth someday.
Or this isn't a true confession.
[Dark Naruto]
Heh heh!
How convenient for him.
[gasp]
Heh heh!
Mm.
Naruto, where are you going?
I just want to be
alone for a while.
It's that boy!
I told you to stay
away from him!
Go away!!
[cheering]
You're a hero, Naruto!
Ha ha ha!
Thank you, Naruto!
To all of the people in
my village, I was a relic
of the past that they
wished would disappear.
[Temari]
Gaara's the Kazekage, remember?
Ugh! Show a little respect,
you nitwits!
[Matsuri]
Lord Gaara is the hottest
thing ever! He's a quiet, cool,
strong and elite warrior!
A lot of people
trust Octopops now.
He earned that from them.
And Gaara's become Kazekage.
His village trusts him to
take care of them.
They accept and
respect him.
And me, I have Iruka Sensei,
and my comrades...
Why didn't you give them
your autograph at Ichiraku?
Can't blame you, you know.
I mean, after all, they came
kissing up to you like that.
They were completely
disgusting, weren't they?
Who the hell are you?
Don't you remember?
Everyone in the village used
to treat us like outcasts,
and then they try to pull that?
I am the real you. The one that
exists in your heart, I am you.
The real me.
I never gave it
much thought.
But I guess somewhere
deep inside my heart,
It's true. I'm still not
confident that I have everyone's
trust back home in the village.
Where'd Naruto
run off to?
Wait, you don't
think that...
This is a secret location.
An enemy couldn't possibly--
[Motoi]
Yaaagh!
Huh? That sounded
just like old man Motoi!
Augh! Rrgh!
Huh? No! Motoi!
Naruto! Use Formation C!
Why?! Why's he doing this?
Naruto! Come on! Focus!
Stop, Octopops!
Just stop it!
Listen to me, okay?
Motoi really does trust you!
And he cares about you!
That's the squid!
It isn't an
octopus at all!
What? A squid? Are you sure?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
You don't have to count!
An octopus's head is round!
A squid's pointy!
Oh. Right.
I thought 'cause Motoi confessed
what he tried to do, Octopops
got mad and then attacked him.
We got worried about
you, and when we went
to go look for you,
this guy attacked us!
Okay, I got it.
This is the squid
from before!
Ahg! Gaah!
Naruto! Fight first,
talk later, okay?
Yeah, gotcha.
Wood Style!
Silent Strangle Jutsu!
Hang on, old man Motoi!
We're coming to get you!
[Killer Bee]
I'll tell you how I feel!
I'm gonna save you for real!
That's my deal,
that's my spiel,
gonna make this squid squeal!
Eight Tails and me
retake the stage!
Knocking the beat-up squid
right off the page!
The rest,
I wont engage.
Haaa!
HAAAaaaa!
Nice one, Octopops!
Bee, why did you save me?
Hm?
You knew, didn't
you, Master Bee?
You knew all along.
That I tried... to kill you.
And yet you...
Hm. Y'know, I don't
remember that happening.
[gasp]
All that I do remember is...
Motoi and me, Motoi and me.
Motoi and me spending time
together, training hard
like birds of a feather.
We made mistakes,
but it was no disaster.
And we were always
bursting into laughter.
The two of us smiling,
best of friends forever.
The times Motoi
and me spent together.
Awesome!
Yeah! Yeah!
Ha ha ha!
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah,
Yeea-eeaah!
Yeaaaaaaah!
[chuckles]
[Killer Bee]
From this moment,
I'm gonna be your instructor.
So prepare yourself
or suffer death or torture.
[Naruto]
It's finally time
to start training!
[Killer Bee]
This is a sacred place where
those selected as Jinchuriki
have long come to undergo
purification ceremonies.
You'll be fighting the Nine
Tails here, fool, ya fool!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Next Challenge!
Naruto vs. Nine Tails.
Hey, Nine Tails.
Evil glare as usual, huh?