[crying]
[theme music]
[bells ringing]
-Asuma.
-Uncle Asuma.
-Where is he?
-His mom said that
that he had already
left when I went by his house.
-Come on, it's my turn!
-Over here!
-Give it!
-Hey, you two!
How many times do
I have to tell you
kids not to play
around on the roof?
-We're sorry!
[laughter]
-Well, hi there, Shikamaru.
-Uh, hey.
-Haven't seen you in a while.
You been busy?
-Kinda, yeah.
-Well, stop in soon.
Oh, and tell Asuma-sensei
and Choji I say hello.
Which reminds me,
we have to work out
Asuma's tab when he comes in.
-Asuma was-- well--
-Yeah?
-Killed in the line of duty.
-So, the shinobi who
was lost yesterday-- no.
-Shikamaru?
Dinner's almost already.
-I'm, um, not
really that hungry.
-Shikamaru.
Come spend some time
with your old man.
Your game is a
little off tonight.
You're not going
to win like that.
-Whatever, Dad.
-That Akatsuki.
They're strong, aren't they?
-Yeah.
-So, what's your plan?
If someone like Asuma
couldn't handle them,
what shot do you
think you'd have?
Sarutobi was a hell of a guy.
-I know.
-Not so hot at Shogi, though.
You know what you're doing?
-Look, you play your
way, and I'll play mine.
-No, son.
I'm not talking about Shogi.
Well, you wouldn't do
anything stupid, I suppose.
I'm lucky in that respect.
Who wants to go to
their own son's funeral?
You've done well for yourself.
I'm very proud to
be your father.
You're as sharp as they
come, with great talent.
Someone the Leaf can
depend on in the future.
But now, Asuma is dead.
-Just what are you
getting at, here?
-Only the truth.
-Will you shut your mouth?
All this talking
is making me sick.
Say what you want.
I'm still nothing
but a useless coward.
-You're wrong.
-What do you want from me?
-Let it out, boy.
All of the anger, the
sadness, and the fear.
Everything that's
brewing inside of you.
You've got to let it go.
It all starts from there, son.
[sobbing]
-Remember, I'll be here for you.
-Huh?
-Hm.
BOY: Whoa!
BOY: Oh, man.
I almost tripped.
BOY: You almost got me!
[laughter]
-Over here!
-Wait, where are you going?
[laughter]
-I'm gonna get you!
-You can't catch me!
Look how fast I can run!
I'm going so fast!
-Hey.
-Shikamaru.
-Good morning.
-Oh, it must have
been so hard on you.
Seeing Asuma.
Oh, there aren't any words.
You poor, poor boys.
-Shikamaru.
-Darling?
-You must be looking for Choji.
he's in the hills out back.
-Hm?
[grumbling sounds]
SHIKAMARU: I don't k You
think it's deep enough?
-Shikamaru!
[stomach grumbling]
[laughter]
-Just saw your mom.
Brought you a little something.
-So when do we do it?
-Huh?
You're gonna do it?
Right?
How can I help?
Wait a second.
Are you telling me that
you don't want me to--
-Well, actually, there
is one thing you can do.
-Ah?
Mm-hm?
-Huh?
-Shikamaru!
We're gonna do it, right?
-Thank you.
-Huh?
-Forgive me.
I know I'm late.
I was a little lost,
but I'm good now.
We're about to try something
pretty crazy, so please,
keep an eye on us, OK?
-Asuma-sensei.
-Ready to head out?
-Let's go, Shikamaru.
-All right.
TSUNADE: Hold it!
-Huh?
-Milady.
-You going somewhere?
-Your mission directive
still stands, right?
I've just assembled a new team.
We're going ahead
with the mission.
-Not without my
approval, you're not.
Shikamaru, you will be assigned
to a troop of my choosing,
and only when we have a solid
plan of attack in place.
-Listen, just send some
reinforcements after us.
The three of us have already
worked out our own strategy.
-I've heard enough!
Asuma is dead.
There's only three of you.
-That's not true.
Asua's still with us.
-You're after vengeance,
then, are you?
This isn't like you at all.
Are you so eager to die?
-We're not stupid.
We have no intention of
running straight to our deaths.
Believe me.
It's just--
-Well?
Just what?
-We don't want to
run away, and just
go on living without
fulfilling our duty.
We aren't going to
live without meaning.
That's why we're going.
-Grow up, you three.
The shadow of death
hangs over us all.
Some deaths may be harder
to accept than others,
but unless you can get past
that, there can be no future!
-Carrying this
lighter around, it's
almost like Asuma's
still close by.
Like he's watching over us.
I really feel that.
Until I've close the
book on this thing,
his lighter will stay with me.
-Face reality.
There's only three of you, OK?
A full squad has--
-A full squad has four.
-Huh?
-Kakashi-sensei?
-I'll take over as Team 10's
leader, and go with them.
Fair enough?
-Kakashi, what are you--
-It's no use.
They're just going
to go, anyway.
I figure you might
as well send me along
to keep an eye on them.
Make sure they
don't go overboard.
-All right.
As you wish, then.
-Yahoo!
-But Kakashi-sensei,
what about Naruto?
-Huh?
-Your arm.
It's--
-Oh.
It's nothing.
He doesn't need
me at the moment.
Plus, he's got another squad
leader with him now, so--
-Man, that guy.
-All right.
Team Asuma, let's go.
-OK.
SHIKAMARU: Thanks, Kakashi.
We owe you one.
[theme music]
KAKASHI: OK.
Time to go after so Akatsuki.
Shimamaru, let's hear
this plan of yours.
-All write.
I'd like to tweak
it a bit, though,
now that you're
along for the ride.
-No problem.
Go on.
-I'll explain all of it
piece by piece for you,
with all the
possible variations.
Everyone listen carefully, and
be sure you've got it down.
-You've got it.
NARUTO: Next time,
Target Locked On.