Mh! This is bad!
Something wrong?
How long until we
reach the island?
There hasn't been any
wind, so not for a while.
But we're still okay.
Yeah, we'll be on time to meet
the Tsuchikage's messenger.
Huh?!
That'll be
too late!
What?
Chojuro, what is it?
I'll go on ahead!
Please follow as
soon as you can!
Hurblh.
I give up!
Even on solid ground,
everything feels wobbly!
Wow, you've been
seasick this entire
trip, haven't you?
All the way from
start to finish.
Finish?
Whaddaya mean?
After we restock our
supplies, we're going
to head straight on to
the Land of Lightning.
Oh, I see.
A lot of things happened,
but it seems that we'll
accomplish our mission.
Wait, where's
Naruto gone?
[slurp]
[gulp]
Ahhh!
Miso and pork broth is the best,
but seafood broth's great too!
[Yamato]
Damn it!
He always seems to dash off
before you can stop him.
Well, we'll be staying
here for the night,
and it's a small island.
So I don't
think there's
any harm in it.
Oggh,
So dizzy...
Hang in there.
Ngh...
[Akatsuchi]
Hmmmm.
So from here on out,
we'll be in the
Land of Water.
I can't believe how
tiny this island is.
You know...
We should stop walking,
or the people we're here
to meet won't find us.
So? That's
their problem!
We got here early, didn't we?
Let's go take a look around
Guy, are you feeling
better at all?
while we still can!
It's taking a while
for you to perk up.
I'm sorry, but
I can't do that.
Lord Tsuchikage has
appointed me as his
official messenger.
You just invited
yourself along.
Oh, don't be so
disagreeable,
Akatsuchi.
The Land of Water
hasn't had diplomatic
ties with anyone,
so we've never had a
real chance to gather
Intel about it.
Our nations are allied now,
but we're still shinobi.
Who knows when the situation
is going to change?
You the messengers
from the Tsuchikage?
Huh?
Maybe. Who're you?
I'm the one...
Who'll kill you!
- Aah! Run! Run!
- Get outta here!
Hm!
Watch out!
Hey, you know we're part
of the Allied Shinobi
Force, right?!
So back off!
Shut up and die,
Stone ninja!
Just who are you people?!
Huh?
Ah! That's...!
Auuggh!
Akatsuchi!
[struggling]
Hey!
Why are the Stone and
Mist fighting here?
Yeah, that's what
I want to know!
These guys just attacked
us right out of nowhere!
What is up
with that!
Move it,
Leaf ninja!
Nngh!
You know I
can't do that.
But I'll stop you!
Out of the way!
Haugh!
What did you--
Even if you're from the Leaf,
if you interfere--
[Chojuro]
Please! Stop!
Huh?
[Kurotsuchi]
Backup?
Don't interfere, Chojuro.
No. This ends now.
It violates Lady
Mizukage's will.
Per her orders,
I'm going to have to
stop you right now!
I mean, if I can.
What?
They disappeared!
So, um...
Is everybody all right?
What?!
Dggh!
Does it look like
we're all right!?
You're...
scaring me...
Talk! Why'd you
Mist guys attack us
like that?! Huh?!
[Naruto]
Hey!
Eh?
This is no time
to be arguing!
Rrrgh...
This is not good,
not good at all!
We've gotta
get him help!
You! Leaf underling!
Help us out, here!
Huh?
I'm not an underling!
"Naruto's Vow"
[Kurotsuchi]
What?!
What do you mean,
there isn't a doctor
on this island?!
I'm very sorry...
But this is an isolated place.
However...
there's a Medical
Ninja on my team, and
he's headed this way.
He'll be here
shortly.
Hey.
I brought the towels
like you asked.
I didn't ask for a report!
Just wipe him down!
You're not a very smart
underling, are you?
Why do you keep
calling me an
underling?!
Who else but a lowly
messenger genin would be
in a place like this?
Hurry up and
get to work.
Huh?
Dagh!
[feverish groans]
Why's this
my job?
Damn
it!
Why'd it have to
turn out like this?
And who were they?!
I recently received a
message from Lady Mizukage.
Several shinobi have
suddenly dropped out of
sight in the village.
They all oppose the alliance
between our nations.
Their leader is a
jonin named Ganryu.
[Kurotsuchi]
Is he the one who
injured Akatsuchi?
That's right.
He's the sole survivor of
an incident known as the
Tragedy of Yosuga Pass.
Okay, and what
happened there?
I'm certain you're already
aware of this, but there's
a deep hostility between
the Mist and Stone.
The Yosuga Pass incident
is said to have started it.
Ten-odd years ago the Hidden
Cloud went around collecting
jutsu from each Nation.
They seized a highly
confidential document
from us.
That same day, a team from the
Mist led by Ganryu was to meet
with allies from the Stone in
order to recover the document.
Stay alert. The Cloud
is just up ahead.
Not to worry.
We'll have help from the
Stone from here on out.
That may be so,
but still...
If this mission
is a success,
we'll show everyone that
there is true solidarity
between the Stone and Mist.
And that way, we'll get a
little bit closer to peace.
Yes, Suiren.
That's my wish.
And I hope with all my heart
that it will come true someday.
Why?!
Why do this?!
The Stone and Mist are
supposed to be allies!
Hand it over.
Our mission is to bring
that document back.
And we will have it.
This is...
...unforgivable!
Heh heh heh heh heh.
Kill him.
[stabbing]
[horrified gasp]
Suiren no...
I wish I could've...
...seen peace.
Oh Suiren...
And Junsai...
[sobs]
[Ganryu]
Noooooo!!
"That way we'll get a little
bit closer to peace."
Hmf.
Ganryu.
[Chojuro]
He's never gotten over his
hatred of the Hidden Stone.
It could be that hate is
the reason why he just
can't bring himself to
accept this alliance.
Don't tell me that's
why he attacked us.
I believe that he intends
to get his revenge by
assassinating you.
the messengers from the
Hidden Stone Village.
...thereby destroying the
alliance that he opposes.
[glass shatters]
There's no way I'm
gonna stand by and let
him get away with that!
Ah! Where
are you going?
To get him before he can get me.
Please, don't do that!
The Mist will handle this--
[punched]
Huaagh!
Ooogh!
Hey!
[Kurotsuchi]
You guys take care
of Akatsuchi.
[feverish struggling]
[Tendo Pain]
The shinobi world of ours
is ruled by hatred...
and hatred alone.
If I can't find the solution
to this problem, perhaps
I'll entrust you to find it
instead, eh, Naruto?
What do you want,
underling?
I understand that
you're angry because
your friend was hurt.
But, still, please
don't go after Ganryu.
So I should just wait
till he comes for me?
That's not what I mean!
If you go, one of you
will die.
Yeah and it ain't
gonna be me!
That just isn't the answer.
So I can't allow the
two of you to fight.
[in unison]
I can't let you do it!
Just what in the hell
are you talking about?
You think you
can stop me?
Go ahead
and try!
Damn, there's
no end to this!
We won't let you
go after him.
Why you!
Dagh! Even more?!
However many it takes,
we will stop you!
For just an underling,
you sure do have a nasty
jutsu for stalling people.
I'm gonna go and settle
this, all right? Go back and
take care of your friend.
I don't want to.
And you shouldn't
underestimate me.
Huh?
[gasp]
Ah! I've gotta
hurry up!
One of the messengers has
gotten away from Chojuro
and is headed this way!
[chuckle]
That's just perfect!
We can ambush them!
Right, Ganryu?
Listen. You guys just
stay out of this.
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- What?
Return to the village.
I'll handle it.
What?!
I can't believe that
you're saying this!
He's right! It was the
Hidden Stone Village
that killed my father!
I want to be
part of this!
-Yeah!
-C'mon!
-It's our fight too!
I want you to think about all
those you've left behind.
Your anger and
your hatred.
I will take every ounce of those
feelings with me into battle!
But...
Yahhh!
Why are you
interfering?
Why? Because I'm
Naruto Uzumaki of the Leaf.
You're the Nine
Tails Jinchuriki?
I heard your story, and I
know how you must feel.
But I'm here to stop you
from making things worse.
[Naruto]
My Master was killed by Pain.
So I understand the bitterness
you carry inside.
But no matter what reasons
you have, you can't do this.
I heard that you killed
Pain and got revenge
for what he did.
You're wrong.
He merely used up all
of his power and died.
Are you telling me you
didn't want revenge?
Yes, of course I did.
When I saw him,
standing there before me,
I was consumed with hate.
I wanted to kill him so
bad my whole body shook.
But then, I realized
that wasn't gonna
solve anything.
Why not?
Because it would just
start a cycle of hatred.
And once it begins,
the cycle would keep
going on both sides.
The only thing revenge
begets is death.
Yes, I see. But I've
been fully aware of that
for some time now.
Then why do it?
There's no other
path to take,
in order to make
their wish come true.
What wish? What are
you talking about?
An act of revenge would threaten
the stability of the alliance.
That will force the Five Kage
to think more seriously.
...About the difficulty and
risk involved in maintaining
such an alliance.
And they'll also be forced
to think about peace.
Peace?
A village always looks out
for its own best interests.
Though some villages may
form alliances, they
easily break them if doing
so suits their needs.
For the sake of their villages,
shinobi have committed
numerous acts of betrayal.
They've fought and killed each
other time and time again.
Just how many shinobi do you
think there are within the
Five Great Nations
who harbor hatred towards
shinobi from other lands?
I may have started it on this
occasion. But this kind of
thing happens all the time.
And not everyone can suppress
their desire for revenge
like you're able to.
An alliance formed only by
the higher ranks will
simply end up repeating
the problems of the past.
No. That's not true.
Huh?
Because I'm going to make sure
that I change the future.
[gasp]
How can you be so sure?
My master and my
comrades entrusted me,
to find the answer
to deal with hatred.
The answer to stop
this cycle of revenge.
The answer to foster
understanding between shinobi!
They've put all of their
faith in me, So I'm going
to find the answer!
I need your faith, too.
Even it takes a while.
I will bring us all a
little closer to peace.
And then, that way, we'll get
a little bit closer to peace.
[stunned trembling]
Suiren...
Ha! I found you, Ganryu!
[gasp]
Why did you?!
Are you crazy?!
What were you
thinking, jumping
in front of him?!
Don't worry about me. 'Cause
this is barely even a scratch.
Don't put on a tough act!
I just full-force on you!
Doesn't matter.
Even if I am hurt, I just
can't afford to die here.
I still have
too much to do.
This could start an
international incident!
And it's all my fault!
You gotta be kidding me!
Don't you dare die!
Relax wouldja! I was
only resting because
someone went and hit
me with a sword!
Naruto Uzumaki.
I understand. And I'll
put my trust in you, too.
Huh?
[Chojuro]
Stop right there!
Huh?
I'm taking you into custody.
And if you should try to
resist me...
[clang]
Eh?
I have no intention at
all of resisting you.
And please, tend
to his wounds.
Hey, Mist guy!
How's Akatsuchi?!
I left a Medical Ninja
to treat him.
But his injuries aren't
life-threatening.
Thank goodness.
And Ganryu.
I brought this.
The messenger you injured
entrusted this to me.
[gasp] But this is...
He was returning the effects of
those who died at Yosuga Pass.
Along with a formal apology
for that incident.
That was the true purpose
behind the messengers that
were dispatched to the
Mist by Lord Tsuchikage.
The Hidden Stone...
...has actually apologized?!
That stubborn old
man said sorry?
This was done in order to
strengthen the new alliance
between the Mist and Stone.
I see.
So what now?
What happens to him?
[Chojuro]
He will either be
executed or released.
He committed a serious offense.
But he's prepared to
face the consequences.
[Akatsuchi]
I don't believe that
it will come to that.
Hm?
I only got hurt because
I took a wrong turn,
stumbled, and fell.
Right, Kurotsuchi?
You're not doing this
to make up for what
happened to you in
the past, are you?
Hm. I'm just going to have
the Mist owe us one.
That's all that's going on.
You know, Maybe the old
geezer wasn't the only one
who had a change of heart
because of the Kazekage.
Kazekage...?
Hey, Mist guy!
Don't forget
you owe us one!
Oh! Right!
Thank you very much!
And you, Leaf underling!
Huh?
Wait, is your
wound still?
I'm sorry. I have comrades
waiting. I'll see ya!
He could've at least
introduced himself!
[Yamato]
What did you get yourself
into this time?!
Heh heh heh heh heh!
You know, it's kinda
embarrassing.
I took a wrong turn
and just fell!
You what? You fell?!
Where was this?
Is that really all
you have to say
about this, Aoba?!
Look, forget it!
We're leaving tomorrow, right?
Let's just get everything ready
and then go to bed early!
Actually, we've had a
little change of plans.
The ship from the Land of
Lightning is going to come
and pick us up directly.
Really?!
It should be here any moment.
Oh! Here it
comes now!
You mean that's...
[Naruto]
This is it! The octopus is
here to guide me!
All right! Y'know?
[Killer Bee]
"Y'know..."
I don't want to be rash, but
will we clash or be a smash?
If I dare say, it'll be a
no-go, whee! I'm a brat-hating
outlaw! yeeeeeuhhh!
[Naruto]
Just who is this shades-wearing
meathead with the weird rhymes?
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Land Ahoy! Is This the Island
of Paradise?
This old man's the
Eight-Tails Jinchuriki?