Man...
I can't believe this!
It's my first day off in
forever. How did I end up
getting sent on an errand?
Huh?
What was that,
lightning?
No way! That's Sakura!
[screaming]
Are you okay?
Sakura! Talk to
me! Sakura!
Hang on! I'll get
you down from there!
"Road to Sakura"
Well,... from what I can
see, it's nothing
serious.
Bones are fine, internal
organs okay...
Considering the height
that you fell from,
you're tough,... even for
a student of mine.
However...
Hey. Do you know who I
am?
Uh, well--
She's okay physically,
but psychologically...
What's wrong with her,
Lady Tsunade?
It appears to me that she
has some kind of
amnesia...
Yeah, I thought that
might be it.
But this condition is
only going to be
temporary, isn't it?
It's really hard to say.
I've treated all sorts of
patients, but I've never
seen symptoms exactly
like these before.
Are you saying that she
might stay like this
forever, then?
Oh, don't worry. She's
only sixteen years old.
I mean, she still has her
entire life ahead of her!
(clears throat)
Listen, I'll do some
research on amnesia.
For now, we'll just need
to keep an eye on her.
Sakura, what exactly are
you doing?
So uh, have these things
always been this big?!
I mean, they seem almost
unnatural. Did they get
bigger recently or
something like that?
I was blessed with these
by Heaven, I'll have you
know!
[grunting]
[crying]
No, Lady Tsunade, please!
Not her head! You mustn't
hit her in the head!
Sometimes a shock fixes
this kind of thing.
Sakura isn't herself
right now. Try to go easy
on her, all right?
Now, Sakura... Do you
feel okay?
You're flat as a board.
[gasping and growling]
I'm completely normal! I
have nothing to be
ashamed--
Hey! Not the head!
Shizune, please! Take it
easy, all right?!
You really shouldn't be
acting so reckless and
fearless, you know.
Because of you, I got
caught in the crossfire.
But you seriously don't
remember anything at all
now?
Well, I suppose that this
place looks vaguely
familiar to me...
I mean, I guess I sort of
know that this is the
village where I used to
live.
But beyond that,
everything just starts
getting all foggy for
me.
Uh--
Look, why don't I take
you home? You can relax
there and rest up for a
while.
Wouldn't you know it?
Nobody's home! Good
grief!
But I can't very well
just leave you here, not
when you're in this
condition.
You're not pulling my
leg, are you? This is
really my home?
Sure is! You've lived
right here your entire
life, ever since you were
born. It's where you grew up!
Since I was born?
Really...?
All right... we'll have
to ask you-know-who for
help.
It looks like he's not
home, either! Sure, when
a friend really needs him,
he's nowhere to be found!
Ino, where are we now?
It's the home where one
of your teammates lives!
You've been on the same
squad together forever,
so I thought that coming
here might help you
remember something.
What's this person like,
anyway?
Well, let's see...
He's blonde and kinda
dopey-looking, he wears
orange clothes all the
time, he's completely
scatterbrained, and he
also loves ramen a lot.
Wait, ramen?
What? Did you remember?
This guy's name... Is it
Char Siu?
Wakame? No wait... Corn?
Hold on, lemme think...
Ah! Nitamago!
No, not quite, but you're
really close. It's
Naruto. Does that help?
No, sorry. For a second
there I thought I
remembered something.
That's okay. It won't
come back all at once.
But there's someone else
that you've known for a
long time. His name is
Sasuke.
It's Sasuke...?
He's actually out of the
Leaf Village right now,
but...
He's a totally cool guy
with black hair, and he's
really handsome, and on
top of that, he's-
He's a playboy?
Hm?
Oh, boy, I really have no
idea why I said that!
just had this image pop
right into my mind all of
a sudden!
If she doesn't even
remember Sasuke, this is
more serious than I
thought!
Sakura, I am going to
find some way to make you
better, I promise you I will.
Now, come on!
What? Really? This is the
first time I've ever seen
someone with amnesia!
Did she forget me, too?
Are you kidding me?
You're probably the first
one that she forgot!
This is horrible! The
bittersweet days of our
youth together, all gone
from your memories! I do
not know if I can stand
it!
How cruel!
Were we... dating or
something?
It's probably best if you
just ignore him. That's
simply the way he is, you
know?
What's the prognosis,
anyway? I mean, is she
going to get better?
Lady Tsunade just said
that she'd have to do
more research.
But worst case, Sakura
might stay this way.
Oh, no! That can't be!
It isn't right!
All right, then! This is
when we, as her friends,
are gonna have to step up
and help her out!
Now... is there anything
at all that you can
remember, even if
it's small?
It just might give us
a starting place to
help you.
It's really weird. It's
like I remember all of
you guys, but everything
about you's
just a little bit
different than I recall.
What does that mean?
I don't have a clue,
except that she seems
totally confused.
Poor Sakura. All of this
is so sad...
Okay, here's what
we'll do.
What if all of us
changed ourselves to
match up with Sakura's
memories?
Um... I know we all
agreed to this, but...
Meow!
I'm the Hidden Leaf
Village's top canine
handler!
I can't stand being
demoted to a cat
handler, even for
a friend!
[whimpering]
[screaming]
I never thought I'd face
such psychological
torture.
Hang in there, Shino.
We're all in the same
boat here.
But remember, we're doing
this to help Sakura.
Oh, Lady Hinata, you poor
unfortunate girl.
But tell me...
Why have you and I been
separated from everyone
else?
And why are we tied up
like this to boot?!
I do not know.
Apparently the both
of us, but especially
you, Neji,
give Sakura the chills
if we are too close to her.
What have I ever done?!
This is absolutely
outrageous!
Huh?!
I'm sorry about all
of this, but Sakura
asked us to do it.
How awful...
Now let me see here....
What were these two like?
Hey, Ino. Do you really
think that this ridiculous
stunt is going to help her
regain her memory?
Yeah, everyone looks
pretty weird and
uncomfortable.
Maybe, but if this helps
her get her memory back,
I say it's worth it.
Just be a good sport
and go along with it.
Hm!
Choji, wear this!
But this is- What's going
on here?!
All right, Shikamaru.
I'm really sorry to ask
this, but would you act
kind of like an idiot?
Huh?! Why would you
want me to do that?!
And smile, if you can!
Come on, Shikamaru!
[gasping]
Weeee! Woo hooo! Wee!
Yahooo... yippee.
I don't get it.
Sometimes I feel like my
memory is just about to
clear up, but then it all
goes away.
At least you're trying
hard. That's all you can
really do.
But this entire thing
just feels so gross, you
know.
Like, why did I suddenly
show up, falling out of
the sky like that?
And I... I can vaguely
remember everyone in the
village, but all the
details are a little off.
I still don't remember
this house at all!
It's as though I came
here for the very first
time today.
[grunting]
What is it?
Ah! If it
isn't Ino!
Auntie, Uncle! I'm glad
you're home. Where have
you two been?
They were having a big
sale across the bridge,
so of course we ended up
buying way too much.
And now we're bringing
home all of the spoils!
They were heavy, and it
was a long trip, but we
can't let the spoils
spoil, can we?
Get it? Hilarious!
[laughing]
Listen, something really
bad happened.
What is it? What
happened? Was there
a battle?
I'd rather take a bubble
bath than be caught in a
bloodbath!
I think we've all had
enough jokes for one day.
Look, you're practically
scaring Ino away.
Well, whatever else is
going on, your parents
are still as intense as
ever.
But now that they're
back, you can rest easy.
I'm sure they'll take
good care of you.
What's going on?
Sakura...?
What in the---
why are you crying?!
I don't know... The
moment I saw them...
I'm sorry...!
Hey! Where're you going?!
Don't just run off!
Huh. So what do you
suppose is going on with
those two?
You don't think... that
my jokes really were too
much for her, do you...?!
I get it, so that's
what it is!
Right.
Huh?
Hey, Sakura, wait up,
would you?!
Sakura, c'mon! Stop!
[panting]
Listen, I don't know what
happened back there that
made you cry, but why'd
you run away like that?
Did you hear me?
I don't know what
happened, but I have this
uncomfortable, painful
feeling in my chest.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what came over me.
It's okay, but we can't
leave things like this.
Let's go back.
Until things calm down,
I'll stay with you if
you'd like.
Ino...
[gasping]
No...
My pendant is missing!
Huh? Your pendant?
Come to think of it, you
were wearing some jewelry
I'd never seen you with
before.
Oh, no...! I've never
taken it off before, and
now it's gone!
It's something that I
just can't lose!
Sakura?
Oh!
We finally found the two
of you!
Auntie! Uncle!
This is just too much! I
can't believe you ran all
the way here at top speed.
[sighing]
Sakura, are you by any
chance looking for
something?
Well, losing things is an
age-old problem... Just
like old age!
[laughing]
Huh?
It's not like you to pass
up shutting your Dad's
bad jokes down!
Apparently, she lost
something that's very
important to her.
Oh. I see.
But listen, Sakura, this
thing that you lost...
Is this it?
[gasping]
You must have dropped it
in front of the house
earlier.
I was really surprised to
see it, since it's exactly
like the one I have.
[gasping]
Reporting in! Our third
line of defense...
... it's--
Yes, I see.
Sakura!
[chuckling]
Thank you again.
Don't mention it. It's
the least I can do after
your parents--
Here.
Buying the exact same
necklace... like father
like daughter.
But from here on out, I'd
be careful not to
drop it, okay?
So that's what's
happened.
Now, we chased after you.
Isn't there anything that
you'd like to say to us
after going through all
that trouble?
Yeah, but, Uncle and
Auntie, the thing is...
Sakura isn't...
What's this for?!
Thank you both!
Well, it's not
something to get
all teary about!
I didn't know that nuts
grew on cherry trees.
It's 'cause...
I'm just so happy!
I love you both so much.
Be sure to come home by
suppertime!
Okay, I have no
idea what just
happened,
but I'm assuming that it
means you've remembered
everything?
Yes, everything.
Then tell me... What
happened? Why'd you fall
from way up there?
Well, earlier today...
... I was dispatched as a
messenger by Lady Hokage.
Okay, it should be just
ahead.
Huh?
[screaming]
I don't know what it was,
but some powerful force
reeled me in.
And when I came
to, I was here.
I'm don't think that I'm
the Sakura that you know.
I'm not actually from
this world.
Hold on, what are you
talking about, this world?
Oh, boy. I guess your
memory must still be
affected.
Ino!
Don't worry, Sakura. I'll
stay with you for the
long haul. I'll even
study up on amnesia!
[gasping]
Sakura! You're glowing!
Ino.
Thank you for being my
friend here, as well.
Huh? I don't get it!
What's going on?!
Hey, Sakura!
Uh-- she just...
faded away!
What just happened? Was
it a Summoning?
But I don't see any jutsu
formulas anywhere.
I don't think that I'm
the Sakura that you
know...
No way! It's
impossible.
That couldn't really be
what happened... Because
if it's true, then...
Where did MY Sakura go?!
Ninja Network News!
Welcome and good evening,
I'm Mabui of the Hidden
Cloud.
I'm Shikaku Nara of the
Hidden Leaf.
Now that the Fourth Great
Ninja War has broken out
in earnest, various
campaigns are unfolding
in the theater of
operations.
The battlefields are
split into three main
groups.
Darui's First Company
and Kitsuchi's Second
Company are deployed on
the Coastal Front.
Gaara's Fourth Company
is facing the previous
Kage on the Desert Front.
Kakashi's Third Company
and the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist are
engaged on the front lines.
Mifune's Fifth Company
is en route to provide
support for the Commando
Unit.
Late breaking news: on
the Coastal Front, the
formidable enemies
Kinkaku and Ginkaku have
been successfully sealed.
Now, for a live report
from the scene, we go to
Samui from the First
Company!
Oh, it seems there was a
mistake. That's Darui.
It appears that we
don't have any audio,
either. What as happened
to Samui?
Well, why don't we
go back to the desert
front, then?
The enemies are the
Second Mizukage, The
Second Tsuchikage,
the Fourth Kazekage
and the Third Raikage.
To be honest, it's hard
to see a connection
between them.
Yes, all of them do come
from different time
periods, after all.
Let's see if we can go
to the scene. Here's
Temari from the Fourth
Company.
[inaudible crowd yelling]
Uh, Temari...?
Temari?
The Desert Front appears
to be engulfed in a
sandstorm.
I wonder how things are
on the front lines...
The Third Company has
sealed one of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the
Mist, Zabuza Momochi,
along with his
subordinate.
Let's go to Tajiki,
who's there. Tajiki?
It doesn't look like
we'll be able to get a
hold of him right now...
So onto the main issue in
this Fourth Great Ninja
War. The Jinchuriki of
the Eight and Nine Tails,
Lord Killer Bee and
Naruto.
In order to hide from
Madara Uchiha... they've
been isolated on Turtle
Island.
Seizing this opportunity,
Naruto is currently undergoing
training to learn the Tailed
Beast Bomb.
[yelling]
Don't send it my way,
I'll just send it back
to you, hey!
So you say, but it's not
your day!
Learn balance while we
play. And count it, okay?
Ah! One to two, the
square root of three?
Fool ya fool! For a fool
you're quite the right
triangle.
I'm trying my best, you
know! Can't you see?
Ahhhhh!
Huh... what kind of
training is that...?
Let's go talk to Naruto
and see what we can find
out directly from him!
Naru--!
Stop right there! Naruto
doesn't even know that
the war has broken out
yet!
You're right.
Sorry about that.
I think we should just
leave it at that for
tonight.
Then we'll see you
again next time!
All right! We're out!
Thanks, everyone!
Did I do ok?
Why stay with the
shinobi? You are
staunchly samurai.
You serve shinobi, how can
you still call yourselves
samurai?
We do not serve the
shinobi. The one master
that we follow has never
changed since the olden
days, and that master...
is called peace!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Mifune vs.
Hanzo.
We pledge ourselves to
peace, and then act
upon that conviction!