[theme music]
-It's no wonder
it was completely
useless to look
for a scroll that
contained the forbidden jutsu.
He had used his very
own granddaughters
as the jutsu's hiding place.
That En no Gyoja.
What a cruel thing to do.
If the forbidden jutsu is simply
removed from its human vessel,
then its power will
become lost forever.
Also, unless the
person who's its vessel
is very skilled, and strong
enough to control it,
the forbidden jutsu
can never be activated.
Even if someone looking for
the forbidden jutsu found it,
they couldn't lay
a finger on it.
En no Gyoja's foresight
and selflessness
has kept it protected
all this time.
However, if it stays like
this, the treasure's wasted.
Right now, for my purposes, you
have become nothing more than
a container to accumulate
natural chakra energy.
But you've yet to learn to wield
the activation jutsu necessary
to set off all that
collected energy.
And that's where I
come into this story.
The only survivor of
the Tsuchigumo clan
who has mastered that jutsu.
What a lucky turn of events.
The jutsu that could
restore our class
and help regain
our former glory is
on the verge of seeing
the light of day.
We'll use it to strike fear
into the hearts of anyone who
ever denounced our clan.
What's the matter, Hotaru?
Doesn't that make you happy?
Aw, come on.
Smile for me.
No?
Then here.
There.
See?
Now you're happy, too.
And you should.
You should be joyous!
[laughter]
-Tsuchigumo Style
forbidden Jutsu Release.
Big Bang It's here.
Now, the secret weapon
that will restore our clan.
The jutsu awakens after
its decades long slumber.
Now gather, chakra.
Come, fill this vessel
until it overflows.
Come and manifest your
terrible and beautiful power!
-Utakata.
What are you doing?
-That chakra.
It's flowing.
-What chakra?
I don't see it.
What are you talking about?
-It is there.
Chakra from the
atmosphere and terrain.
-What's that for?
-They'll ride the
chakra current and flow
right towards where
it's being drawn in.
And towards Hotaru.
-That's where she is?
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Right!
But why's the chakra gathering?
Hey.
Are you sure that
Hotaru's gonna be there?
-If you have time to talk, then
you aren't moving fast enough.
Hotaru.
There.
-Let's go!
Hotaru!
-We're too late.
-Akaboshi's men are useless.
Couldn't they have
at least held you off
until I was finished here?
Oh, well.
I suppose that I don't
mind having an audience.
-You bastard.
Just what are you
going to Hotaru?
HOTARU (VOICEOVER):
So, Utakata--
-It's her dream.
All I'm trying to do
is breathe life into it
and make it into a reality.
The revival of the
Tsuchigumo clan.
And the key to that dream is
activating the forbidden jutsu
with my abilities.
-And what abilities are those?
What do you mean?
-Hotaru doesn't have the skill
to activate the forbidden
jutsu herself.
She's only able to
accumulate chakra
from the world around her.
So when she's
absorbed enough, I'm
going to activate it for
her, from the outside.
All of this is in order
to restore the tarnished
honor of the Tsuchigumo clan.
-You don't know what honor is.
You're taking advantage
of Hotaru's feelings
for her grandfather, for
Tonbee, for her people.
You're dishonoring
everything Hotaru holds dear!
-Who wants something as cheap
and pointless as feelings?
I'm going to steal
the entire world.
-You what?
-While I have this, be it the
five Kages or the Daimyo lords,
no one can ignore my
demands or me anymore.
New village?
No thanks.
Soon I will attain
land and holdings
that are even superior to
the five great nations.
-Have you lost your mind?
-Oh, I'm quite serious.
Now that I've come
this far, I can
match the might of
any of those nations.
With this forbidden jutsu,
taking over the world
is no longer just a daydream.
-I knew it.
I just knew it!
You don't really give a damn!
All the people of the Tsuchigumo
clan mean nothing to you!
-Well, that goes without saying.
-And what about
Hotaru's feelings, huh?
-Couldn't care less about them.
She put her faith in you,
carrying that massive seal
in her own body.
She protected it with
all of her might,
for the sake of her entire clan.
And she entrusted you with it.
-What?
[laughter] Look, it's true that
I killed my own father in order
to satisfy my own ambitions.
I'm not denying that.
But you're in no
position to talk.
I know about you.
All about you.
You're listed in the bingo book.
Isn't that right?
A rogue ninja from
the Hidden Mist.
You turned your back on your
village and on its laws.
I don't need to be lectured
by someone like you.
You don't care about
your village, either.
Hmph!
You and I, we're quite
alike, I can tell.
MIght not want to admit
it, but we're the same.
I hid no such thing.
What I said before
was true, although I
didn't tell you one thing.
That the reason my father
died protecting the jutsu
is that I killed him.
-A monstrous crime.
He killed his own master, and
then fled from the village.
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): No.
I won't believe that.
Sir Utakata is
nothing like that man.
And yet-- and yet I--
[screaming]
-What?
This-- This power.
Wait, no!
No!
Stop!
[roar]
-Hit close to home, didn't I?
[laughter] Well, whatever.
But since Hotaru is so
attached to her people,
I'll do her a favor.
The new nation I form will
be named after the Tsuchigumo
clan.
See?
I'm not such a bad guy.
Using the name of the land of my
birth will return it to glory.
I'd say I'm a pretty great guy.
-Knock it off!
-Maybe you're right.
Maybe it's true that I don't
really give a damn at all.
At least not about my village.
-But Utakata--
-Tell me.
What'll happen to her?
-I'll keep her around,
as the ultimate weapon
to launch the forbidden jutsu.
And through her
I can control it.
The perfect vessel
to build my nation.
-Vessel?
Did you just say vessel?
-That's right.
She's my vessel.
-Enough!
-Aw.
So close.
But now you can't oppose me
anymore, just Hotaru can't.
Good.
More chakra.
Let your body overflow with it.
And what about you?
What shall I make you do, now
that you're under my control?
Perhaps I should
make you two comrades
turn on each other in battle.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can't move.
-Or maybe I'll keep you
around as bodyguards.
You two can be the
protectors of my vessel.
-No.
Never.
-You didn't think you could
get near my vessel that
easily, did you?
-All right, that's it.
I've heard enough!
Stop calling her that.
Hotaru's no one's vessel.
Got it?
-You annoy me.
Be quiet.
Don't you understand?
You have no grounds to object.
This was Hotaru's decision.
She came to me of
her own choosing.
She agreed to become the vessel.
It isn't up to you two anymore.
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): To Utakata.
I'm going to work
together with Shiranami
to restore the Tsuchigumo
clan to greatness.
Thank you for
everything you've done.
Goodbye.
Your student, Hotaru.
-Hotaru doesn't
really want to be
rescued by you, or by anybody.
So you get to stay
right there and watch
as the Tsuchigumo clan's village
disappears in an instant.
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): Sir
Utakata, I'm so sorry.
All of this is because
I was so foolish.
-Well.
So you still have the
will to resist, do you?
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): Sir Utakata.
-This can't happen.
-Just a little more.
Just a little more,
and Hotaru will
be all filled up with chakra.
You will be my witnesses
to the glorious reawakening
of the forbidden jutsu.
-No chance.
We can't fight those
four like this.
-Yeah, you're right.
So first we have to
stop the villagers.
-But how?
-We have no choice.
We'll have to get a
little rough with them.
We need to contain
them in one place.
[shouting]
-I'm so sorry.
A little rough, huh?
Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll!
-Wood Style.
Four Pillar House Jutsu!
We'll just keep them
there until later.
-Gee, way to ruin our fun.
-We can't keep letting
them have their way,
so we have to shut
them down right now.
-Funny.
I was about to say that to you.
-We'll see about that.
-It's just not as much
fun without an audience
to watch us.
[laughter]
-This is not good.
There's no end to any of this.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Dammit.
-You're doing great, Hotaru.
But our two guests must be
getting impatient by now.
Now, surrender to me completely.
Unreleas the chakra that
you've accumulated all at once.
Take this place that
has rejected you,
and reduce all of it to ashes!
-Ninja Art.
-Huh?
-Bubble Bomb!
-You snake.
When did you set up that attack?
You know, if you'd
just behaved, then
you could have lived
a little bit longer.
[shouting]
-My Word Bind Jutsu.
Why did it fail?
These guys-- their chakra
levels are extraordinary.
-Startign to get it now?
We'd never let you
control us that easily!
-No!
You can't!
-Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Word Bind Jutsu!
Rock!
-You bastard!
-Hotaru.
Are you all right, Hotaru?
-What's wrong?
So what should we do about this?
[laughter]
-Hey!
Back off!
Or do you still want to fight?
-Just hold on.
Have you forgotten that
thanks to my Word Bind Jutsu,
I still have her
under my control?
Now out of my way!
-You won't win.
-She isn't fully charged
with natural chakra yet.
But it'll have to do.
Now let's show
them, and everyone,
just how strong the
forbidden jutsu is.
All right.
Let us begin.
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): No.
-We're going to show the
entire world our power.
No, mine.
My power!
HOTARU (VOICEOVER): No.
No!
-Everyone will die!
Fury Jutsu!
-No!
[theme music]
HOTARU: I never
wanted to hurt anyone.
I only wanted to protect
the jutsu entrusted
to me by my grandfather,
and fulfill his dream.
And yet I hurt Naruto, and Sir
Utakata with my very own hands.
I didn't want this.
I betrayed Sir Utakata.
Someone like me should
disappear, along
with the forbidden jutsu.
NARUTO: Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, Master and Student.
HOTARU: Goodbye, Sir Utakata.