Just a little farther!
(Tenten) With this, I can-!
[scream]
With those two Ninja Tools, we
can seal the enemy in an
instant!
But before we can, I need to ask
someone from the Cloud how to
use them!
Wha-?!
Heh!...Now! Become one!
(Tenten) I...can't...move...
(Tenten) No...! I have to...
I have to save everyone before
it's too late!
Wait, huh-?!
Huh?
I don't know how, but this is my
room, right...?
The Hidden Leaf Village...
Wait, but how...?
Does this mean that I was
transported here from the
battlefield?!
[chattering]
[panting]
If I was brought back here, what
happened to everybody else? I've
gotta find somebody that I can
ask!
Yeah, I'm doing great! How 'bout
you?
Can we go to get some ice cream?
Please?!
(Tenten) Hold on...What is this
feeling...?
[laughter]
PORK BUNS
Here you go! Enjoy them!
I may not be on the battlefield
anymore, but, still,...it's way
too peaceful here...
(Rock Lee) Tenten!
Huh?
(Guy) Ah! There you are!
Oh, thank goodness!
Guy Sensei, you and Lee got
transported here, too?
(Tenten) Huh?!
Like a new comet, I am Rock Lee,
the fashion trendsetter of the
Hidden Leaf!
[chattering]
Coolly making my entrance!
Nope, no good!
I'm sorry, but that was no good!
But, why? What was wrong with
it, Sensei?
A true fashion trendsetter
doesn't say such things, he
elicits them from others!
Remember, adults must always
conduct themselves in a cool
manner, Lee.
I will be more careful! Thanks,
Sensei!
That is the power of style!
Hold it right there!
What's with you?! At a time like
this?! What is happening?!
Time like this...?
(Tenten) Yeah! We're in the
middle of a war!
This is not the time to be
joking around, my friends!
But, Tenten...What are you even
talking about?!
If you're referring to the Third
Great Ninja War, it ended a long
time ago.
Just snap out of it. You're not
helping things by playing the
fool.
Well, from my standpoint, you
are the one who needs to snap
out of it.
What?!
(Neji) He's right, Tenten.
It seems to me that you need to
wake up!
[gasp] No way!
But that voice is...!
You keep insisting on wearing
those ugly sports bras!
It's time for you to wake up and
go put on some "better"
underwear!
Huh?! Ugly sports bra? What...?
(Tenten) [shriek]
Why would he-? What is going
on?!
That was completely uncool! You
do not have any sense of style
at all, Neji!
Ugh! This is all just a part of
discipline and training!
(Tenten) You've got to be
kidding! Neji's acting like a
pervert!
(Tenten) Wait,...Neji is
supposed to be dead! So why are
Guy Sensei and Lee acting like
nothing happened?
(Menma) Hey, what's with all the
noise over here?
Oh, perfect! You guys are just
in time!
Huh?!
Uh...
It is the usual issue...I hope
you will give Neji a good
scolding. Please, Menma!
Huh?
(Tenten) Menma?!
Yeah? Is something wrong?
Well,...uh...
This is great! Barbecued meat is
the best!
That's hardly the truth. Even if
it is dinnertime, I'd prefer
something much lighter.
Oh, you would? This feels pretty
light to me.
I don't think that's what
he was talking about...
(Kiba) [laughter] You're always
such a fool!
Do you want more to eat? Hey,
Tenten?
Huh? Oh. Yeah...
(Tenten) I came along to confirm
my suspicions, but...
I have to say, Neji, that your
dirty mind is still a really
serious problem.
Oh, I was merely trying to
discipline her!
Quit makin' excuses!
You're a freakin' disgrace to
our clan!
Do that again and I'll rip your
eyes out! You'd better remember
that, you idiot!
Uh,...that's not a nice joke,
Lady Hinata.
Oh, that's so scary...I just
couldn't imagine doing something
like that.
Hey! Don't use this as a chance
to get close to Menma or I will
kill you!
Listen, Menma doesn't want your
kind of attention, all right?!
Just go away! Shoo! Shoo!
No, you go away!
Shoo! Shoo!
You're both huge pains; just get
lost.
What?! Menma!
(Sakura) Aw, don't be so
cold to me, Menma!
Hey, don't get so worked up. I
mean, you still have me!
Huh? I don't need a cheap flirt
like you!
Wow, talk about an overreaction.
But, then again, that's what I
like about you, my kitten.
Oh, did someone say kitten?
They're so cute! Hey, I love all
cats!
(Shino) No one's talking about
But what really concerns me,
right now, is the source of this
repulsive feeling I've been
having...
There it is!
(Hinata) Hey, what the hell are
you doing?! We're trying to eat
here!
Don't worry! This spray
is harmless to humans. But I
will show no mercy toward bugs,
not even teeny ones!
That's not the problem here!
[sigh] Thanks for the food.
What? Are you leaving already?
We're all splitting the bill, so
you should eat up!
[sigh] Thanks, but I'm
feeling full. This is for my
share of the food.
Hm.
[chattering]
(Drunk A) Lord Kizashi Haruno is
the best!
Hear, hear! Raise a toast to
Lord Fourth! [laughter]
Hm?
(Tenten) Whose Great Stone Face
is that...?!
I don't know what's going on
here, but this isn't the Leaf
Village that I know...
[grunt]
And it isn't a dream either...
Wait, maybe...I could be trapped
inside a genjutsu, right now!
Well, then I'll just have to
break out of it!
Release!
[laughter]
Release! Release! Release! I
said, release!
[laughter]
What the heck is going on? It
isn't working at all!
Does this mean that I'm not able
to release the genjutsu or is
something else going on?!
That's right,...I still have to
save everyone...
Whatever might be going on, I
can't just stay locked up here.
(Tenten) I'm not gonna let you
get away with this!
(Tenten) I'm going to find a way
to get out of here, Madara, and
then I'm going to seal you away!
(Tenten) If I'm going to escape
from this world, I have to learn
every detail I can about
genjutsu.
It seems that I can't release
the genjutsu. But there must be
something else I can do...
Although,...it sure doesn't seem
like these old textbooks are
going to be a whole lot of
help...
(Neji) Hey, Tenten!
(Rock Lee) Are you up?
(Tenten) Oh. Is it time for
morning training?
No, of course it's not! 'Cause
this is a fake world created by
our enemy!
I can't wast any time on fake
people like them!
(Neji) Oh, here she is!
Good morning, Tenten.
How are you today?
I gotta say, they did a good job
making you guys. Even up close,
you look real!
What does that mean? What are
you talking about?!
Listen, I don't have any
intention of getting all
friendly with you.
I'm not going to be training or
going on missions, so make sure
that you remember that, you got
it?
(gasp) No training or going on
missions?!
Uh...Hey, Lee...Do you think
Tenten's still half-asleep or
something?
I suppose it is possible.
She left early yesterday when we
all ate...And it could very well
be that she caught a cold, too,
so she-
Look, I'm wide awake, and I
don't have a cold! Anyway,
please just leave me alone!
Okay, no more distractions! I
gotta study everything I can get
my hands on!
(Rock Lee) What do you think is
going on with Tenten, anyway?
Ditching her training and her
missions...That's completely
forbidden for a Hidden  Leaf
Shinobi!
Nyah, nyah! She must really hate
you!
I really don't think that's the
problem!
Then again, he could be right on
target about that.
I mean, face it: your team has
some serious issues.
That is true. I know that I
wouldn't be able to handle all
of that vulgar talk...
You're saying I'm the problem?!
No, we aren't. As far as I've
been able to make out, her angry
feelings are directed at
something more than that.
Does that mean you are telling
us...that I am also to blame?
LEAF VILLAGE LIBRARY
Guess I'll have to use the
library to research this.
I'm not used to visiting this
place, but...
(Rock Lee) Uh, hey, Tenten!
Why are you two here? I
mean,...didn't you hear what I
told you guys before?!
We did hear you! And that is
exactly why we are here!
Now, let us do this, Neji!
(Rock Lee and Neji) Please!
Forgive us!
Huh?
That was a really nice apology.
Sincerity is reflected in your
attitude!
(Tenten) What's happening?! I
don't understand this at all!
(Tenten) Wait,...could they be
Madara's henchmen?
(Tenten) Which must mean that
they intend to tempt me - or
drag me - into accepting this
world?!
Huh?!
Please give them a break and
forgive them, would you? They're
both really sorry for whatever
they did!
Yeah, I agree. Please forgive
them!
No-!
Uh,...Tenten...?
You can all try to come after
me, but whatever you do, it
won't work!
(Tenten) You, and you, and you!
Don't come near me till hell
freezes over!
(Choji) Oh,...wow!
(Shikamaru) Ooooh! You're gonna
have to wait  a long time!
Seriously? I cannot believe she
said that.
Now, now, Lee. Hang in there.
Don't get all depressed...
But I do wonder what's making
her act this way...
Well, maybe she's not actually
mad, but she's just worried
about something instead?
Worried, huh?
She has no appetite,...she
rejects her friends,...and she
wants to be left alone...
It's completely clear to me!
There can be no mistake! She's
lovesick!
Ha! That's all you ever think
about!
(Sakura) What do you think,
Menma?
What I think is that we aren't
going to get anywhere just
talking amongst ourselves.
You're right about that.
So instead, I say that all of us
should work together to do
something for Tenten!
(Neji) All right!
(Rock Lee) Let us do it!
(Tenten) Nothing here...
(Tenten) Or here. Or here,...or
here,...or here!
I thought that I could find some
answers by coming here,...but
not one of these books is
helpful in the slightest!
It's not like I'm any good at
research to begin with...
To be honest, I prefer to have
someone else do the thinking for
me...
(Tenten) I wonder what's
happening with everyone back in
the real world, right now...
(Tenten) I can't be wasting so
much time like this!
A rose?
That's a face longing for love
for sure, my kitt-
(Sasuke) [yelp]
Hey, just what do you think
you're trying to pull?!
I'm sorry about that, Tenten.
I keep telling you to stay out
of my way! When are you guys
going to listen?!
Wait. You're leaving already?
Yeah, because you're bothering
me!
You don't have to be so rude,
you know! All of us are just
really worried about you, that's
all!
Enough! You can cut the act now,
you fakes!
(Sakura) Ten...ten...?
You can try to get in my way,
but I'm not gonna quit!
I'm going to find a way to get
home to my own world!
She's got it bad.
She's just upset thanks to your
stupid idea!
Oh boy...
I think she's beyond our help
now. She's in full battle mode
and just isn't listening to us
one bit!
So you didn't fare any better
than we dud, huh?
If it is not Neji's dirty mind,
and is not that she is in
love,...
...then what can we possibly
do?!
(Shino) Leave her alone.
(Shino) And by that I mean don't
"bug" her...
He's right! Believe me, I'm sure
that's what Tenten wants!
But is that not...too cold a way
to behave toward a friend?
Actually, I don't think that we
should leve her alone.
Something has been bothering
me...
Menma, you never cease to amaze
me!
You're such a kind, good, and
thoughtful friend!
You're the complete opposite of
that damn Tenten! You know what
I'm gonna do? I'm gonna go beat
some sense into that idiot!
Oh...! Wait just a moment, Lady
Hinata!
She vanished!
That was just a clone she left
behind. The real one is already
gone.
Ugh, that Hinata!
(Rock Lee) I have a bad feeling
about this...
It's okay! I'll track her scent.
Everyone follow me!
An entire day gone, and I still
haven't found any leads at all.
Will I ever get back, or am I
stuck here for good?
Is it even possible for me to
get back home?!
Huh?!
(Hinata) The hell is this?
Wow, what an ugly weapon!
You can't just take that from
me! Now, give it back.
Yeah. No way. If you want it
back, you're gonna hafta
apologize for your behavior
today.
(Hinata) Everyone's all worried
about you, and all you do is
trash us and point fingers!
No more games! Just spit it out,
Tenten, what is going on here?!
(Kiba) There she is!
Hinata! You're being too rough,
like always!
Just shut up! We won't get
anywhere otherwise!
All right, then I'll just take
it back by force!
[gasp]
Hey, what-?!
No! Hinata!
[gasp]
Tenten, stand down.
Huh?
What just happened?!
(Shino) That was...
[chattering]
(Hinata) Hey, wait, damn it!
You don't train something like
that on a friend. What is going
on with you, Tenten?
You deserved it. Quit
pretending! You aren't my
friends!
(Tenten) And I didn't ask you to
worry about me!
(Tenten) I have goals of my own
to pursue. And I don't want any
of you to get in my way.
This isn't the place where I
belong. I don't care about this
village or any of you!
(Rock Lee) You are lying!
Huh?
That cannot be true!
(Rock Lee) You are not really
like this!
Hm.
Believe whatever you want to!
Man, what has gotten into her,
anyway?!
This is more than just
weird...It's like she's a
totally different person, now!
[growl] She's really pissing me
off!
Those kids are fighting! Isn't
it terrible?!
Yeah, but, that's what kids are
like these days...
Very interesting...
(Tenten) All I want is to know
some methods to undo genjutsu!
(Tenten) What do you do when the
usual release jutsu doesn't work
and you can't rely on help from
your friends?
(Kurenai) Wow, that's a very
difficult question...
(Kurenai) Maybe it's possible if
you're more powerful than the
jutsu user, but...
(Tenten) I thought so...
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Where Tenten
Belongs"
(Tenten) I have no idea what
else I can try!