Another one!
We have reports from all
regiments! Our comrades
are falling victim to
multiple surprise attacks!
It's chaos! We don't
know who the enemy is!
What could be going
on?! It's doubtful
that they'd launch a
night raid. Sensory
ninja watch each
camp, and we've
increased patrols.
So why can't we
detect the enemy?!
Is is some kind of
poison? What's the
condition of the
corpses?!
All of them received
external wounds! So,
they're physical
attacks.
Someone from the outside
must be using some sort
of control genjutsu on
them.
(gasp)
Itachi...
Wait, hold on!
There's word from
the Medical Corps!
It seems that the
enemy is...
White Zetsu has been
impersonating various
Allied Forces Shinobi.
He's able to mirror
our chakra imprints!
That explains it...
If one of our shinobi
had his chakra absorbed
during the daytime
battle...
White Zetsu can fully
transform into him!
Well, Shikaku? What
should we do? There's
no way that we can tell
friend from foe, now.
How do we prepare to
fight when dawn comes?
If we don't discover
a way to tell the
difference fast, we
will lose time, plus
all our men will be
endangered! In the
end they could wind
up killing each
other by mistake!
So this was White
Zetsu's ability
all along, huh?
The battle during
the daytime was to
set up these secret
nighttime assaults.
That was the
enemy's true
motive.
(frustrated groan)
There's no sign
of the enemy.
Good. But make
sure to stay
alert.
Yes, sir. I have
lookouts posted
everywhere.
Huh?
Halt! Who goes there?!
I'm an ally.
I'm Kurotsuchi, of
the Stone, Second
Company. And I've
come to speak to
your prisoner.
I'm here to
relieve you.
Great, thanks.
Try to get some rest,
all right? Don't worry
he'll keep watch.
You got it.
It's tasteless to
exhibit one's ultimate
are over and over, but
if I must! Fine! Hmph!
(painful grunt)
Lightning Style?!
And I was being careful
since I'm susceptible
to Lightning Style!
Deidara...
Deidara!
Stop calling my
name! It's obnoxious!
It's me, Zetsu.
Zetsu?!
Seriously?!
You were always a fun
guy. So I'm going to
help get you out of here
in remembrance of that.
Yes! Excellent!
Hurry!
Hurry...
Hold on a
second...
(startled gasp)
He's inside
that? Really?
What's this?
Big brother Deidara,
you alive in there?
Of course not. I'm dead.
Wait, Kurotsuchi? You
here to rescue me for
old times' sake?
Well, I probably was
sent because we used to
be friends, but no, I'm
not here to help you.
I need your help.
Huh?! What do
you mean?
She's questioning
Deidara...
Where is Kabuto
Yakushi?
I don't know! I
wouldn't tell you
if I did!
Ugh, look, bro.
Kabuto brought you
back to life and
is using you for
his own ends! You're
dead, so the least
you can do is forget
the past and cooperate
with us a little.
Come on!
Kabuto gave me
an opportunity
to acquire a Super
Ultimate Art!
Then where is
Sasuke Uchiha?
Sasuke?! Why, was he
reanimated as well?
What? No, Sasuke
isn't dead!
Don't be ridiculous!
I know! I killed him
myself with my
Ultimate Art!
But I saw him after
you died! Sasuke was
alive and well, and
fighting against the
Raikage and a bunch
of other guys.
Wow! Amazing!
He joined the Akatsuki
and is now an enemy
of the Allied Shinobi
Forces.
What?! He's with
the Akatsuki now?!
Right?
Huh? Uh, yeah,
I guess.
What's up with that?
Sasuke's alive? And
joined the Akatsuki?
You've gotta be kidding.
In death, I shall
become art itself!
No one's seen an
explosion like this!
One that shall leave
behind a scar on the
very earth itself!
And then! I'll receive
more admiration for
my art than anyone
has ever seen before!
Tremble! Be afraid!
Recoil in despair!
Cower in awe!
And cry your
heart out!
Because my art...
(powerful grunt)
Is an explosion!
There's no way
he's still alive.
I'm telling you, he is!
But I used my
Ultimate Art!
Listen, nobody
cares about art!
That damn bastard!
What's the deal
with that guy?!
Was he not in awe?!
Trembling in fear?
Didn't he feel
despair?! Didn't
he scream out, what
the hell is this?!
Earth Style's
vulnerable to
lightning. I knew
that if I used it,
then the lightning
blade would defuse
your bombs.
It's their Achilles'
heel, isn't it?
You know what,
Sasuke?! Screw you!
Just watch! Your
Lightning Style won't
hold me down forever!
Commander Mifune!
Message from HQ!
A disguised enemy's
infiltrated our men
and is taking them
down, as well!
Chaos is spreading
within all the
companies!
Is this company in
any danger, sir?
No, not at the
moment, we're not.
Right! I'll send
your reply.
Sir, what about the
Hidden Stone Kunoichi
who showed up earlier?
I don't think she's
an enemy...
Big brother? Hey,
are you listening?
Answer me!
Argh! This is
going nowhere!
Open it up. I
want to face him.
Should we open it?
Hey...
Sir?
Mountain...
Huh?
Uh...Distant skies?
(painful grunt)
It's River.
Damn samurai...
You're so
predictable!
Bastards!
It's Zetsu!
What?!
Careful! They'll
absorb you're
chakra!
That is true art!
It's an explosion!
Nice one, Deidara!
But how?! Why didn't
Lightning Style seal
his Explosion Style?!
(chuckle)
He used that
sword to ground
the lightning.
What was it doing
inside that puppet?!
It was thanks
to me!
Zetsu...
What?
Let's go!
Hey! Wait!
Stop them!
Man...
Deidara's such a pain
even when he's dead!
The prisoner Deidara
has escaped with his
comrade, Zetsu!
Apprehend them, now!
Okisuke!
Sir! I take full
responsibility for
this blunder!
This isn't the time for
blame! Just get them!
Yes, sir!
Why are we running
away? I say we just
kill of them.
I can't! I'm all out
of Detonating Clay.
I need to find more.
Oh! They're coming!
Outta my way!
In front, too!
Damn it!
You're still just
as weak as ever,
aren't you?
That was merely a
tactic to buy us
some time.
So, you escaped
the seal.
Kabuto!
As expected. I'll
bring you back.
Wait! My Ultimate
Art was completely
rejected! I can't
die like this...
...e-even if I am
already dead. Hmph.
You intend to stay
there and fight?
I'm going to perfect
my Super Ultimate Art.
I simply don't
understand how you
artist think. But
intellectuals do
have to protect
artists, I suppose.
(gasp)
That's...
You escape. I will
hold them off.
They're all
yours, Chukichi!
Now, then. Hidden
Frost Jutsu.
What the hell
is this?!
Where's he hiding?
(attack yell)
So many...
He's gone.
Curses!
Commander Mifune!
I sense them! They
went that way!
Let's go!
How much farther are
we going to run?
I need clay! Hm...
So I need to find a
place with clay in
the soil.
Just leave it to
me, I'll find some.
You may fight as you
see fit, Deidara.
Freedom suits you
quite well. Besides,
I'm going to be
busy myself.
Unless we catch Deidara
before he finds some
detonating clay...
...this could get
troublesome.
Omoi contained the
explosion with his
Lightning Style
earlier. But he's
in a different
company now.
Anyone in this
unit us Lightning?
The Fifth Company has
been split in two. The
weapons in this half
are mainly samurai
swords, and our only
ninja are sensory,
sealing, and intel
support personnel.
Captain Mifune, I
can wield Lightning
Style, sir.
Good...
(shocked gasp)
They're getting close,
Deidara! There's lots!
Agh! I've only managed
to get this much
Detonating Clay!
Scatter!
Lightning Style!
What now?!
Did he?!
Down there!
Land mines!
Jump!
Hgh!
You can't stop us!
Take this!
Ahhh!
Nope, that's
not enough!
This is what
true art is!
Big Brother's
gonna explode!
You need to keep on
discharging it. We
need a stronger level
of Lightning Style!
This is the best
that I can do!
Lord Mifune!
(attacking grunt)
Hey, welcome back.
What's happening?!
A reanimated body is
immortal, remember?
In a way, you're like
the walking
Detonating
clay bomb.
I thought so.
So crass!
How depressing.
Why?
Art is a single
moment of brilliance!
A scattering of
blossoms! But this
body can't scatter
anymore...
I'll find a Super
Ultimate art that
will transcend my
Ultimate Art.
Damn you, big
brother. Not cool.
Lord Mifune?!
Where are you?
Lord Mifune!
The holes left by
his land mines became
trenches in which to
hide.
Guess he wasn't very
thorough with his
Detonating Clay,
was he?
We're gonna
need a plan.
Insulation would keep
him from channeling
away the lightning.
Our Lightning Style
wielder's too weak.
I'm sorry. I
tried my best.
Focus on sensing
their whereabouts.
Shall I request
reinforcements?
No, we don't have
time to wait for
them.
We'll do it with
the personnel
we have.
What am I
going to do?
This immortal body is
incompatible with my
aesthetic.
Sasori might have been
able to come up with
something, but he
left too quickly. Hmph.
I'm all alone. But
then, artists are
loners to begin with.
I buried all the
land mines. Well?
Any ideas yet?
True art doesn't
come to one that
easily. Especially
not a Super
Ultimate Art.
Sasuke?!
What?! Why
are you...
It's you two, huh?
Bastard! How
are you alive?!
Tell me where
Naruto is.
I don't know! But
you need to pay
attention to me
right now!
My business is
with Naruto.
Damn it! Not
that crap again!
First Itachi, then
Naruto? You don't
give a damn
about me, do
you?
No.
Bastard!
They're coming!
Good luck.
Stop!
Deidara!
Get them!
You won't escape!
Deidara! Wait!
Doesn't Sasuke
seem different?
(painful grunts)
This time you'll
tremble with fear!
And awe, too!
You'll feel despair!
I'll wipe that smug
expression off your
face!
Huh?
Ha ha ha!
I see you!
Right there!
Right up there!
Ha ha ha ha!
Your weakness isn't
Lightning Style, Bro,
it's you ridiculous
obsession with art!
(shocked gasp)
Kurotsuchi?!
Bastards! What
are you up to?!
(attacking grunt)
They were duds?
Damn!
Nice sword you got
there. But it cannot
stop my art!
(painful grunt)
Samurai, don't use
Lightning Style!
It's not Lightning
Style. It's a storage
cell. Seems to come
in quite handy!
Too bad it
doesn't work!
What?!
What you're standing
on is all bedrock,
big brother.
The sword can't
pierce it. And it
won't discharge the
Lightning Style.
Not again!
There.
One other thing.
Where's the real
Sasuke right now,
Big Bro?
Damn it, Kurotsuchi!
Treating me like a
fool, pretending to
be Sasuke! You didn't
even look like him
by the way! Get
out of here!
Oh, well! I suppose
it's no use trying to
get any information out
of Big Brother now.
He's too busy
pouting.
We'll head back. And
maintain our front
line. Go inform
Headquarters.
Commander, Uh, could
I have that back now?
Huh? Oh!
Here's hoping you
don't come back to
bother us again, Big
Brother Deidara!
See ya!
That just might work.
It'll be the theme
of my Super Ultimate
Art!
I think it really
could use a face
on it, though...
Art will never die!
Even if I already
have!
While the shinobi are
all away fighting in
the Fourth Great Ninja
War, we need to be
prepared to protect
the village! The
enemy could come
for us as well!
We've had incidents
like that before. And
every time we just
beat the stuffing out
of them and chased
them out!
Do not underestimate
the mothers of the
Hidden Leaf Village!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Allied
Mom Force!
Protecting the
village is a huge
responsibility, too!