[loud crash]
"The collapse opened up a hole
in the earth, and it swallowed
the two siblings."
"Yahiko, Konan, and Nagato,who'd
come to call themselves Team
Jiraiya,immediately went after
them."
"But Shikamaru... didn't make a
single move..."
Not good.
Come on! We've gotta
save those kids!
Hold it!
Huh?
We can't. Don't go down there.
(Ino)
Why!?
(Choji)
Shikamaru...!
♪
[gasp]
Careful, the enemy's ahead!
What is that?
What do you see, Hinata?
It looks like a hole where
the ground caved in...
You see Shikamaru
and his team?
I don't... there's
no sign of them.
[sniffing]
That collapse is making it
really hard for me to track
their scent.
[cough] And I don't think that
I'll be able to until after the
dust settles.
[sneeze]
It's hard to believe the
collapse is just a
coincidence...
Hey, kids! Can you hear me?!
...Anyone! Hey!
If you can hear us, respond!
Where are you?
We're coming to
save you!
[rushing water]
Were they... swept downstream?
C'mon, let's go!
My eyes... they
did this...!
Nagato...
Listen: First things first,
we have to find those kids.
Just focus on that right now!
[quiet grunt]
Is this really
okay, Shikamaru?
Are you sure that we shouldn't
go and help rescue them?
Those guys are handling it.
Maybe, but that
isn't the point!
This just doesn't
seem right to me.
There's an order of
priority to follow...
Right now, our team captains
have been taken prisoner, and
our mission is at a standstill.
So our number one priority now
has to be to regroup with the
other teams and try to come up
with a plan of action.
Yeah, I know that, but,
I don't like it...
(Shikamaru)
The shinobi who were here in the
village have gone to rescue
them... We have to do what
we came here to do.
Even if it is a real big drag...
We can't be indecisive now.
We should move to a wider area
where Kiba and Akamaru can track
us more easily.
[sighs]
The shinobi from the Hidden Leaf
aren't coming after us.
I guess now we know what
they're really made of.
Well... this should be good
enough. I'll let him know
exactly what happened.
[gasp] Yahiko... Konan!
What is this tunnel...?
(Yahiko)
Hey! What are you--?
[gasp]
What's the matter, Konan?
These walls... this tunnel...
I wonder... Were
they... created naturally?
[gasps]
What's going on!?
Hm.
Please, Lord Mashima, I beg you!
Oh, please protect my sons, Lord
Mashima!
[gasp]
Please! Oh, please!
Protect them and keep them
safe, Lord Mashima!
Bring them back to me!
I'm sorry to interrupt your
prayers. We're just passing
through the area, but...
May I ask
you something?
What is this?
A shrine to Lord Mashima.
He sleeps deep beneath the
earth.  And he provides
protection for our village.
Oh.  So, uh...  did something
happen recently in the village?
We villagers have always tried
to maintain a modest and
peaceful way of life, so that we
don't awaken Lord Mashima.
But then, just a little while
ago, strangers came to our
village and warned us that it
might become a battlefield.
They told us to evacuate to a
safer place for a while.
So we were forced to
leave our homes.
But... My two boys... returned
to the village...
I tried to go after them,... but
they were much faster than I
was... and we got separated.
That's why I'm praying
to Lord Mashima
in hopes that he'll keep them
safe and bring them home again.
Huh... Lord Mashima, eh?
[rushing water]
It's coming...
It sounds huge!
...What is it?
[roar[
This is bad! There's
no way around it!
Thanks, you saved us, Nagato.
Yes, thank you.
We barely made it.
What the heck was that thing?
I don't know...
We'd better go find
those kids quickly.
(Ashitaba & Komichi)
[Frightened screams]
What is that thing!?
[gasp]
[gasp] That's Kakashi Sensei!
Kakashi Sensei...
(Voice)
Come to me if you want to save
them. Or I'll execute them.
[gasp]
Just stay put!
Guy Sensei!!!
Calm down!
It's a trap! Don't fall for it.
We have to get word to the Leaf
Village as soon as possible.
Yes. We'll have to break up into
two teams. One of them will stay
here.
The other notifies the Leaf.
No good.  There's a chance that
we could be ambushed on the way
back.
We have to try to maintain our
combat advantage.
(Voice)
You'd abandon your friends to
follow the rules?
So it seems that the essence of
the Hidden Leaf... has been
passed down to its younger
generation, too.
That's right.  And what's more,
that's how it should be.
So don't get rattled by this
guy, whoever he is.
He's trying to challenge us to
break up our strength.
But I'm... No, I'm not like you!
What's that!?
I'll never turn my back on them!
Naruto!
No! Come back!
I'll go! Take care of things
here!
Neji!
Big brother... we lost
Kenta somewhere!
It's okay, Komichi.
We'll find him later.
You promise...?
[frightened cries]
...Big brother!!
[screams]
Big brother! I'm scared...!
It'll be okay!
[screams]
[roar]
[frightened cries]
[gasp]
Kenta! Ha!
Hey, Shikamaru... Come
on, let's not do this.
I don't know. It just
doesn't seem right...
Deities supposedly live in those
shrines, so you know what you're
asking for...?
...For divine punishment!
(Shikamaru)
Ha! I knew it. I was
right after all.
Hm?
Okay... C'mon, let's go and meet
this Lord Mashima.
(Choji)
What!?
(Ino)
This is...
Come on! Bring it!  I'll filet
you into three pieces!
Nagato! Now!
[grunt]
Look out!
[roar]
What!? There's another one?!
Leave us alone!
Expansion Jutsu!
HUman Boulder!
[frightened cries]
[struggling grunts]
Argh!
Oh, no!  Komichi, look out!
Huh?
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Now complete!
So you guys....
You actually came.
Heh.
What do you think has happened
to Neji and Naruto?
And what was that thing?!
It's probably some
time-space ninjutsu.
But who's able to use a ninjutsu
that's as high-level as that
one?
Damn it. Thanks to him, we just
have more trouble to deal with.
[gasp]
[grunt]
Where are we?
I don't know.
Are you the one who's
responsible for all of this?
Listen up! Return Kakashi
Sensei and everyone else
from the Leaf!
Or else you're gonna get it,
seriously big time!
Naruto, you need to get away
from him right now.
Look, stay out of this, all
right?!  I'm about to settle
this whole thing right here and
right now!
Just listen,
look at his eye...
[gasp] The Byakugan!
You're no match for someone
who possesses that.
Hmph.
Who exactly are you? How do
you possess the Byakugan?
Hold on... Don't tell me you
have ties to the Hyuga!
Look at the cloud of dust...
Your comrades are the ones...
who are responsible for that.
What happened?
They put the rules of their
village ahead of the lives of
children.
So many years have passed... and
yet the Hidden Leaf hasn't
changed one single bit.
And what would you know
about the Hidden Leaf?
Oh, I know plenty. In fact, I
know more than anyone who's
here at the moment.
[gasp]
(Masked Man)
Now...  follow me, Neji Hyuga.
[gasp]
Come with me...  if you want to
know the ugly truth that the
Hidden Leaf has covered up.
What...? What is this guy
talking about...
♪
(Sasuke)
We'll return to the village and
give them our report.
We can't afford any more losses
or casualties.
(Rock Lee)
What are you talking
about, Sasuke?!
We have already lost Guy
Sensei. And now even Neji
has gone missing!
And Naruto from
your own team, too!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Masked Man."
(Sasuke)
Look, all of this happened just
because he acted on his own.