[music playing]
-[gasp]
-Who are they?
-What?
You really don't know?
That's Lady Chiyo,
and her brother Ebizo.
-I thought-- I thought
they retired years ago.
[life support beeping]
--[gasp] We were
hoping you'd come.
Please, come in.
I'm sure you know our visitors,
Lady Chiyo and Lord Ebizo.
-Welcome.
-[labored breathing]
-Hmm, why that that
looks very much like--
-Yes, it's Kankuro, older
brother of the Kazekage.
-Oh, so I was right, then.
-I assume you've
examined his blood.
-Yes.
Here are the results.
-Fascinating.
I've ever seen this.
-Yes, we believe
it's a new poison.
-Hmm.
Any luck finding an antidote?
-We've tried everything we have.
But so far nothing's had
any noticeable effect.
Of course not.
It explains why he's
let him linger this way,
instead of killing
him right off.
He's confident we won't be
able to counteract his poison.
To make a man suffer like this,
how typical of Sasori that is.
[bell ringing]
It feels good to be
leaving the sand behind.
-Keep moving.
-I don't like keeping
people waiting.
-Yeah, right.
You're one to complain.
Whose fault is it that it
all took so long, anyway?
-We're both to blame for that.
-That's true, I suppose.
Hmm.
[music playing]
-Now.
-[gasp]
-Hmm.
That one didn't work, either.
-Tell us, what other methods
have you already tried?
-As a matter of fact, we've
asked for a specialist
to be sent from
the leaf village.
Perhaps it would be best
to wait for them to arrive.
-Hmph.
You would have us
depend on others?
It's because of your
dependence on this alliance
with a foreign land
that our own people
have become backward and lazy.
-No, we don't depend on them.
I surely wouldn't go that far.
-Kankuro's partly to blame.
By pursuing the enemy
too far, he recklessly
exposed himself to
danger, something
a Shinobi should never do.
-Instead of trusting and
depending on the leaf
to come to our rescue,
we should concentrate
on training our own people
to take care of themselves.
In any case, this alliance
is just a pipe dream.
They are they.
And we are we.
And no alliance
will change that.
Ha.
If they send anyone at all,
it won't be a specialist,
but some useless underling,
just as a simple formality.
-I can't believe
they'd ever do that.
LADY CHIYO: It's the
way of the world.
Everyone only looks
out for themselves.
-All right.
Break time's over.
-Hey.
Kakashi Sensei, where's Naruto?
-Right up there.
-Huh?
-(THINKING) One more day until
we reach the sand village.
We have to hurry.
-OK, let's get moving.
-[labored breathing]
-This is not good.
Poisons are my specialty.
But this one's beyond even me.
-Lady Chiyo?
-He has a day at best.
-Actually, from the
looks of it, he'll
be extremely lucky to survive
until tomorrow if you ask me.
-Sasori's outdone
himself this time.
His skills have
improved considerably.
-Surely we can do something.
-Well, there's one who's more
versed in antidotes than I.
That old queen of slugs,
Tsunade of the leaf.
She was a thorn in my side
in the era of the Great War,
coming up with antidotes
for every kind of poison
I could throw at her.
Who knows.
Now that we're such
great friends with them,
perhaps we could
send word to her
to come help us
with her expertise.
-But Lady Tsunade is
now Hokage of the leaf.
She must look after
her own village.
She can't just drop everything.
Besides, even if she were to
come, what good could she do?
It takes three days to
travel here from the leaf.
-I know that.
I'm not a fool.
I wasn't seriously suggesting
we summon her here.
That would be the
last thing I want.
I can't bear that
old slug queen.
-[sneezing] [breathing deeply]
-Lady Tsunade,
are you all right?
-I'm fine.
-There's a very bad cold
going around the village.
You really should be careful.
-I will.
Team Kakashi left two days ago.
If all goes well, they should
be there tomorrow morning.
[gasp]
That's a bad sign.
Don't tell me.
Group three, number 117037.
I knew it.
I won, and first prize, too.
Definitely a bad omen.
Shizune, Shizune, get in here.
-All right.
We've finally
reached the desert.
TEMARI: The village hidden
in the sand is just up ahead.
It's best if I take the
lead from here on out.
-Lead on.
-At last we're here.
-Let's go.
-You're late.
We must get ready at once.
-The jinchuriki proved more
powerful than we expected.
-Rah!
-Now let everyone gather.
All right.
Shall we begin?
-We'll soon be done
removing the traps
and debris from the road, sir.
-Good work.
-We've managed to
recover the remains
of all of our casualties.
But there's one concern.
-What's that?
-We haven't been able
to find Captain Yura.
-What?
-There's no doubt
to any of us that he
was headed for the road,
right before the incident.
But there's no trace of him, not
a scrap of clothing, nothing.
-Yes, that is strange.
Perhaps you just
haven't found him yet.
Or perhaps he managed
to survive the trap,
and is right now in
pursuit of the enemy.
I could quickly put
together a backup squad,
and send them out after him.
But without knowing
where he is--
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade,
did you call me?
-Yes.
We have to send reinforcements
to the sand village at once.
-Reinforcements?
-There's one team that must be
done with their mission by now.
They'll be on their way back.
-Oh, do you mean-- ah.
Yes, milady'.
I'll see to it.
-We have to be ready for
a worst case scenario.
-It will now take
three days and nights.
Stay aware of your
physical selves.
Zetsu, have your physical
bodies stand guard outside.
Use the one with
the greatest range.
Understood?
-I know.
Only three days?
Isn't it possible that it might
take longer than that, since we
don't have Orochimaru with us?
-All the more reason
to get started at once.
-That's true.
-Indeed.
-Sounds good to me.
Hm.
[chanting]
-Ceiling Jutsu.
Nine phantom dragons!
-Lady Tsunade, you were right.
They're back from their mission.
-Excellent.
-Uh, wait, Lady Tsunade!
-I've got an S-rank
mission for this squad.
-Huh?
-Really?
-Uh--
-An S-rank?
-Mission?
-You're joking.
You hear that?
We're getting an S-rank mission!
I don't believe it!
-Finally, our talents
are being recognized.
I knew it would happen.
-You can't be serious.
[sneezing]
-You feel OK,
[inaudible] Sensei?
-Just spent a
little too much time
soaking in the hot
spring, that's all.
-Too much time spying on
pretty girls, you mean.
-This is our first shot
at an S-rank mission.
So don't you go
blowing it for us
by getting a cold on account
of your pervy habits.
-What the hell's going on.
-Wrong room, milady.
It's over this way.
-Well, I should hope so.
-Aww.
-What about our S-rank mission?
-It was all a mistake.
Thank goodness.
-I'm assigning you
essentially the same mission
as team Kakashi.
Get to the sand village
as fast as possible,
and provide any
support necessary.
Is that clear?
-Crystal.
-Ready, Lady Tsunade.
-Leave it to us.
-We're on it.
-Good.
-Team Guy is always
ready for action.
[sneezing]
-You have a cold?
-No, no, just my
allergies acting up.
That's all.
[chuckling] [sniffling]
-Don't worry.
We'll make it to
the sand in one day.
-I think we can make it
in half a day, Sensei.
-It will take three days,
no matter how you slice it.
-Yeah.
What's the point of making
promises we can't keep, huh?
-We won't know until
we try we, will we?
Forward everyone, with
the speed of youth.
-Lead on, Sensei.
-It's so embarrassing.
-They are who they are, Tenten.
-They're still as
enthusiastic as ever, I see.
-I haven't seen Naruto
for a long time.
-I am curious to see
how much he has changed.
-Same here.
-We got this close
to our target.
And we're just sitting here.
I can't stand this waiting.
-Naruto, for the
last time, relax.
There's nothing we can do.
-I know.
But--
-Just be patient.
Would you look at Temari?
She's the one who's
worried the most.
-The cardinal rule of
traveling in the desert.
If you hit a sandstorm,
you stay put.
You lose all your sense of
direction in a storm like that.
I've heard of many people who
ended up lost in the desert,
and dying of thirst.
Don't worry.
The sandstorms we
get this time of year
usually don't last very long.
-Well, I just hope you're right.
-[roaring in pain]
-Kankuro.
-Quick, a sedative.
-Right.
-As you can see, all we're
able to do is ease his pain,
and try to help them rest.
At this stage, our
only hope is the squad
of leaf Shinobe, who are
due to arrive tomorrow.
That is, if Kankuro
can survive until then.
And if they brought an
experienced poison specialist
along with them.
-Right now, there's a
sandstorm in the desert,
making the route from
the leaf impassable.
There's no telling
how long they might
be delayed if it keeps up.
-If that happens,
then all hope is lost.
-That we've sunk
to this, I never
thought I'd see the day when
we'd have to depend on the leaf
to help us.
-You must be weary, my sister.
Come.
We'll find a seat outside.
You haven't had a wink
of sleep since yesterday.
LADY CHIYO: Relying on
the leaf, it's pathetic.
Mm.
-Hey, sis?
[sigh] Asleep.
-If they left once they
got word and moved quickly,
they could be here any minute.
-Don't count on it.
Even one of our own
people would have
had a hard time
with that sandstorm.
-[gasp] Look, over there.
-We've been expecting you.
-Lady Temari, you
were with them?
-Please, this way.
-What?
You say they've got
Kankuro as well?
-Yes.
When the enemy
took Lord Kazekage,
Kankuro went after
them by himself.
He was poisoned.
And we haven't been able to
find anything to counteract it.
He won't last much longer.
-Damn it.
-Don't give up yet, Temari.
Let me take a look at him.
TEMARI: Kankuro!
-Kankuro!
-(THINKING) Him!
The white fang of the leaf.
Damn you!
-Huh?
-Get ready to defend
yourself or die!
[music playing]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Emergency
medical situation, 2400 hours.
We're coming to you
live from the sand
medical facility, where a
patient in critical condition
has just been
wheeled into the ER.
The patient, a 17-year-old
in serious condition,
appears to be a
victim of poisoning.
The doctor in charge is a
young female, very young,
perhaps too young.
But she seems to be
successfully drawing
the poison from his
body and-- [gasp] oh no.
[beep]
Despite a heroic effort, the
procedure was not a success.
KANKURO: Damn it.
You can't kill me off yet.
NARUTO: Next time, the
medical ninja's student.
[music playing]
SAKURA: Notable people
of the leaf village.
In this part of the show,
we ask a famous person
from the village to share
their experiences with us.
Our guest today
is the only female
among the legendary Sani, the
Fifth Hokage, Lady Tsunade.
Even while defending the village
with your unsurpassed strength
and medical Ninjutsu,
you still remain
the loveliest [inaudible] ever.
How do you do it, milady?
Do you have any beauty
tips for our viewers?
LADY TSUNADE: Rule number
one, get plenty of sleep.
Oh, I see.
Then, drink plenty of
sake, but only the best.
Good sake is great for the skin.
SAKURA: Ah.
LADY TSUNADE: Then, of
course, you should always--
NARUTO: Stop right here, Sakura.
What do you care
about her beauty tips?
I mean, she still
looks like an old lady.
LADY TSUNADE: What?
NARUTO: Come on.
What do you want with a
big curvy body like hers?
It just slows you down.
What's wrong with the nice,
skinny, bony body you've got?
-The skinny, bony
body I've got, huh?
-Old lady, am I?
NARUTO: Uh.
-Goodbye.