PAIN (VOICEOVER): I
thought we dodged that.
-That's it.
I can't waste any more time.
I'll finish this
with my new jutsu.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-I see.
So you've become a sage, and
you've mastered the same jutsu
as Jiraiya-sensei.
-Jiraiya.
You called him sensei?
-That's right.
I also learned
jutsu from Jiraiya.
He was once my master as well.
And that makes us
sibling students.
Sharing the same
sensei, we ought
to be able to
understand each other.
Our master desired peace.
-Just shut the hell up already!
-What a massive
amount of chakra.
Did you teach him that, Pa?
-No.
First time I'm seeing it too.
He never did that
during our training.
I wonder what Naruto
boy's planning to do now.
-What's that jutsu?
-What's happening?
-Naruto's chakra
is forming a-- I
think it looks almost
like a shuriken.
-Wind Style Rasenshuriken?
Naruto, what are--
NARUTO: Everything
you've done here,
all this destruction, what
part of all that is peaceful.
PAIN: You simply cannot see
the forest for the trees.
You're not able to comprehend
the true meaning of peace
or what I'm trying
to accomplish.
Just let yourself be captured.
Surrender, and your
death will lead to peace.
-I already told you.
Shut the hell up!
-He threw it!
-He did what?
When did he learn to hurl
chakra with such high rotation
and density?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All my
secret training is paying off!
-Incredible.
It expanded.
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Well, it appears
that Deidara was
right-- this boy
does not listen.
-What was that?
What's going on over there?
Who could be fighting
against Pain?
-It's Naruto.
-What?
Naruto?
You mean he's back
in the village?
-Yes.
He's mastered Sage Jutsu, and is
down there battling Pain alone.
Are you kidding me?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Damn this leg.
-Please, just stay here.
Naruto asked that no
one else interfere.
-Man, that guy's
so full of himself.
They practically destroyed
the whole village.
There's no way he can
take them on alone.
it's impossible.
-No.
It's no.
If Naruto has
mastered Sage Jutsu,
then he's in a class
of his own now.
That means staying
out of the way
is the best teamwork
that we can offer him.
You need to be patient
here, Shikamaru.
-Damn it.
[theme music]
-Please, be careful.
When you strike, it divides into
greater and greater numbers.
-So, why didn't
you tell me before?
-You see?
I'm ungraceful.
-All right.
So how do we handle this?
-We must ungracefully
endure it for now.
-Sorry, Chief Toad.
-You're really
beginning to slow down.
It seems that your Sage Jutsu
is rapidly starting to wane.
Did you use up your
Sage Jutsu chakra
with that last move of yours?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
Sage Mode's gonna run out.
Before it does, I have to
bring down at least one
of these guys.
-Ma, you know what to do.
We're gonna have to sever
the Rinnegan's visual link.
-Right.
Gotcha, Pa.
-Bunta boy.
-Boss.
-Now, listen to me.
I'm going to hurl you
straight at Naruto boy,
do you understand?
-What?
You're going to hurl me?
But why, Boss?
-I'll tell you, but
listen carefully,
because we haven't
got much time.
-Pa, are you ready?
Sage Art Wind Style Sand Dust!
-Where are they?
-Rasengan Barrage!
PAIN (VOICEOVER): In his mouth?
-You've exhausted
all your Sage Jutsu.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Even in Sage Mode,
I can only manage two
Rasenshuriken each.
-Pa, the boy's no
longer in Sage Mode,
so he's vulnerable right now.
-Yes.
I'm aware of that.
-It's going to be dangerous,
but merging with him
is our only chance.
-Except, we're not
able to do that.
-Finally, here's my chance.
MA: What?
You mean we can't merge with
him because of that Nine-Tails
inside of him?
-Well, it certainly
seems that way.
-But then, what
are we going to do?
-Naruto boy's come up with
his own unique solution
to this problem.
That's what he's about to do.
-You little scamp.
Why you!
Damn it.
-Come on.
-Over here, Naruto boy.
Quick.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
-Bring it!
-Step back, kid, and let
me take care of this guy.
-I'm going to enter Sage Mode.
-What?
-Get back, Chief Toad.
I don't want my
Rasenshuriken to hit you.
Go!
-Don't go acting all tough.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can
replenish my sage chakra just
two more times, which
means that I can only
produce four more Rasenshuriken.
I have to settle this
before I run out!
-Let's go, Naruto boy.
Now, Reverse-Summoning Jutsu!
-I've summoned him.
Now you can release the jutsu.
-What?
-What is going on, Pa?
-It's simple really.
Naruto boy prepared
shadow clones beforehand.
He had them build up
Sage Jutsu chakra,
and then maintain
a holding pattern.
All that's left is to
summon them from Mt.
Myoboku using the scroll.
Once the clone's
summoned, Naruto
undoes the shadow clone
and the Sage Jutsu chakra
is fully restored
to the original.
-Oh.
I see.
What a creative solution.
[gasp]
-It's over.
You're mine!
What?
No way.
Wait.
That's right.
That's his ability.
That one can absorb
any ninjutsu.
But I thought we already
took care of him.
What is that?
-That Pain is the key
player in all of this.
-The one Geezer Sage
spoke of, right?
So he's the one who can
bring the dead back to life?
-Yes.
He's the one with that ability.
That's why when they are
lined up in formation,
that Pain took the
rearmost position.
The most bothersome is
the Pain on the left.
He can repel all
jutsu and attacks,
and pull things
toward him as well.
He hasn't shown his
power yet, which is odd.
Perhaps for some reason he's
unable to use his ability now.
-Well, whatever the case,
the first thing we have to do
is get rid of that
guy in the back.
And use smoke bombs, too.
All right.
-It's useless.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What you absorbed
was a Transformation Jutsu.
-Tricky bastard.
You're the original?
-There's no time to dodge this.
You're done.
-It seems my power
has finally returned.
-You've gotta be kidding me.
He repelled the
kid's Rasenshuriken.
-Just wait.
Sage Jutsu Rasengan Barrage!
-What?
FUKUSAKU (VOICEOVER): Yes.
-That's some nice work, kid.
-Two more left.
-Hold on.
How exactly did he
do that anywhere?
FUKUSAKU: Well, the first
Rasenshuriken was actually
a Transformation Jutsu
performed on Naruto boy himself.
Pain was unaware of that, and
tried to absorb the jutsu.
GAMABUNTA: I get it.
So that's Naruto appeared.
FUKUSAKU: But that Pain can only
absorb ninjutsu, not physical
attacks, so he took a direct
hit when Naruto tackled him.
-Oh.
I see.
So that was the purpose behind
that three stage attack.
PAIN (VOICEOVER): Back then,
he'd already leapt into the air
under the cover of the smoke.
Just in time.
-Almighty Push!
-Are you all right, Naruto boy?
-Yeah.
-Damn it.
What was that
jutsu he just used.
-It appears the central Pain's
attraction and repulsion
power has returned again.
NARUTO: Yeah.
That one.
KATSUYU: Which means
in all likelihood,
our village was destroyed
by that Pain's jutsu.
And the more power that he
uses, the longer the interval
is before he can power back
up to use another jutsu.
-That's why he couldn't use
that repelling jutsu until just
now, huh?
So what do we do?
I can't use ninjutsu
or taijutsu on them.
-Well, according
to Choji's intel,
the minimum interval
between Pain's jutsu
is only about five seconds.
You'll have to target and
strike within that window.
-Only five seconds?
-Then perhaps our best hope
is to trap him with genjutsu.
-But how?
I'm no good.
I can't pull off
genjutsu to save my life.
-We'll do it, Naruto boy.
-Yes.
Of course.
Just like the last time.
-The last time?
MA: That's right.
During the battle between
Jiraiya boy and Pain
it was going to be
our means of escape.
-We've gotcha cornered.
There's nowhere for you to run!
-Again.
Almighty Push.
-Chief Toad!
No way.
[theme music]
PAIN (VOICEOVER): This is the
farthest that Pain has ever
been pushed.
Now, don't worry.
I won't kill you.
You are a precious jinchuriki.
Sage Mode is indeed troublesome,
but now you are helpless.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time
on Naruto Shippuden-- Nine-Tails
Captured.
I'm losing power.
-Sometimes it's hard to believe
that Manda has passed away,
isn't it?
-Huh.
You know, I never
really liked that guy.
I remember though.
People used to call us
the Three Way Deadlock.
Well, maybe I will
miss him a little bit.
-Three Way Deadlock.
That means that frogs fear
snakes, snakes fear slugs,
and slugs fear frogs.
Everything's balanced.
Wait!
But with Manda the
Snake gone-- Oh!
Oh!
-Hey, Pops.
Toss some of that
escargot my way, will you?
-Escargot?
-All right.
I'll try, but I'm ungraceful.
[scream]
KATSUYU: I-- I just remembered.
I have to be somewhere else,
so I'd better get going now!
Help!
GAMABUNTA: Whoa.
What in the world got into her?
-I don't know.
I'm ungraceful.
[theme music]