-So here's how
will be pairing up.
Sakura, you and I
will be on one team.
And of course, Naruto and
Sai will make up the other.
-You expect me to work with him?
-Captain Yamato and
I will be one unit.
OK.
But the other?
It's their unit
I'm worried about.
Naruto and Sai.
[sakura sighs]
-I can't wait.
-There's that fake smile again.
I can't stand it.
Captain Yamato?
-Yes, Naruto?
What is it?
-It's just that-- why'd
you put me with that guy?
-Got a problem?
-Uh, no, No problem.
Excellent.
-I see.
Why am I not surprised?
You'll just have to keep Naruto
on a shorter leash than usual.
-Yes, of course, ma'am.
Excuse me Captain Yamato?
-Yes, Sakura?
-I think maybe Naruto and
I would make a better team.
We've been together
for a long time.
We know each other's
moves inside and out.
-Mm-hmm.
You tell him, Sakura.
-Sakura.
-Yes?
-Listen.
You'ew the only medical
ninja we have on this team.
Because we can't afford to
have anything happen to you,
you stay with me,
-But--
-Do you understand me?
-Yes.
-As Sai mentioned before,
we can expect the enemy
to be highly skilled.
Any mistakes or loss of
focus could prove fatal.
So save any more questions
you have for later.
Let's concentrate on
the mission right now.
-Yes, sir.
-OK, you got it.
-It is imperative
that we discover
where Orochimaru's hideout is.
And the spy who might
be able to tell us
is probably on his way to
Tenchi bridge right now.
[wind howling]
[music playing]
-He's coming.
Come on.
When do we make our move?
[bells ringing]
NARUTO: There he is.
Come on.
Where's the damn signal?
There's the signal!
Hold it, right there!
-No, Naruto!
-Here we go, Sai.
Let's do it.
-I don't usually do this.
But after our talk, I think
it might be a good idea.
So tomorrow morning, we're
going to have a battlefield
simulation.
-Simulation?
-That's right.
So far, all I really
know about you
three is what I've
read in your files.
I want to get a better
idea of your battle
skills, your individual
fighting styles and jutsu.
I want to see them myself.
The more we work together
and learn about each other,
the more it'll help
with our team work.
[naruto sighs]
-Teamwork again?
-You might think I'm being
unnecessarily cautious,
but that's the way I am.
Anyone have a problem with that?
-Dammit.
-Oh, don't tell me
that's all you've got.
-Not good enough.
-Ninja art, super beast scroll.
-How about that?
Was that good enough?
Gah!
Let it go, you idiot!
Sai, get this thing
off me right now!
Sai, where are you going?
Hey, I captured him first.
You don't get points
for capturing me.
Get me out of here!
-Naruto, ugh.
What are you doing?
That's not Captain
Yamato you've got.
[naruto gasps]
-Hey, what's going on?
OK, that does it.
Hey, Sai!
Get back here and untie
this stupid snake!
-You got me fair and square.
Good job, Sai.
[thinking] He's
better than I thought,
it's hard to believe that a
shinobi with his skill level
was assigned to team
Kakashi as a mere alternate,
-One more thing.
Team Kakashi will be getting
a new face in its ranks
from the foundation, the
Black Ops training division.
-Really?
The foundation?
-However--
-Yes, m'lady?
-Keep a very close eye on him.
Study his every move.
-It's beginning to look
like Lady Tsunade's concerns
about him weren't groundless.
-Hey!
Sai, you jerk!
-I see,
--[thinking] To be strong
enough to snap that snake,
I must be careful not
to get hit by her again.
Release
-All right, that
concludes the simulation.
-Listen, you.
-Problem?
-You think?
Do you know what comrade means?
What the-- hey, I
asked you if you even
know what the word comrade is.
-Why yes, of course I know it.
You write it like this.
-That's not what I
meant and you know it.
-Hey, calm down, Naruto.
-You really shouldn't
go around blaming others
for your own shortcomings.
-Say what?
This guy's fast.
-Aww, don't tell me
that's all you've got.
-If you hadn't fallen for
the captain's obvious trick,
he never would have found out
I was hiding somewhere else.
And perhaps I might have
been able to capture him
with even less
trouble than I had.
-Oh yeah?
What do you mean by that?
-Why even bother
masquerading as me
if you're going to reveal
yourself almost immediately
by using one of your own jutsu?
-Because of your
mistake, the captain
was able to see
through our strategy
and use a substitution jutsu
to escape into the forest.
-Well then.
If you knew it was
a substitution,
why didn't you break
your jutsu right away?
-It's impractical to
fight while covering
for someone who's lost his cool.
I simply considered what would
best ensure mission success
and acted accordingly.
-I'll tell you
something right now.
I don't accept you as a comrade,
or as a member of Team Kakashi.
Not now, not ever.
[sai sighs]
-I'm beginning to
get the feeling
that this entire thing
may not work out at all.
I wonder what Sasuke
would have done?
Would he have wanted
to fight an enemy
and cover for you
at the same time?
I mean, after all, you consider
him to be a comrade, right?
-Uh oh.
Naruto is going to blow his
top again if he keeps this up.
-Though how you can call someone
who betrayed his own village
a comrade is beyond me.
-Naruto.
-Oh, no.
-If it means saving a comrade,
I'll do whatever it takes.
Even if that means
teaming with you.
-Naruto.
-Tell me, Why does he feel
so strongly about Sasuke?
-It's because Sasuke's more
than the teammate to Naruto.
He's like a brother.
You have a brother of
your own, don't you Sai?
You must be able to
understand how he feels.
-I don't.
Not at all.
Remember our conversation
about titling my drawings?
The truth is, I couldn't
really title any of my drawings
even if I wanted to.
Nothing comes to mind.
I've never really felt anything.
I you you, I just don't
have any feelings at all.
-But you don't
really mean you can't
feel any emotion about anything?
-Yes, exactly.
I meant what I said.
-You say that, but if
you have a brother,
try and imagine what it
would feel like to lose him.
Surely you should
be able to do that.
-Hmm?
Oh, yes, that.
Well, you see, my
brother is already dead.
-Then all the more reason to--
-I suppose I should have
looked like that, shouldn't I?
-What are you trying to say?
-Well, it's just that, I simply
didn't know what kind of look
a person makes when
his brother dies.
-What kind of look a person--?
What a jerk.
-All right, that's enough
talking now, come on everyone,
gather your things.
It's time to move out.
-Sai, you were lucky.
I had every intention
of pounding you
into the ground a moment ago.
I warned you I wouldn't
hold anything back
if you badmouthed Sasuke again.
The only reason I didn't
is-- well, like Naruto said,
if it means saving Sasuke,
we do whatever it takes.
Even teaming up with
someone like you.
No matter how much I may want
to, I can't afford to hurt you.
Not if you can help
us save Sasuke.
-Sakura, about you and Naruto?
I don't know how to
say this, but you're
being considerate
of his feelings.
I don't really understand
how such feelings come about,
though there was something
about this in the book.
-Let's go, What
are we waiting for?
If we don't get there
by noon tomorrow,
this will all have
been for nothing.
-It's right up ahead, let's
make sure we're all ready,
then we'll head for the bridge.
[wind howling]
[music playing]
-How long are we going to
have to wait for this spy
to get here?
-As long as it takes.
Remember, the enemy is
highly skilled and dangerous.
Caution is the best policy.
-But if we're too cautious,
we might give ourselves away,
thus losing the opportunity
of capturing him
quickly and effectively.
SAKURA: That's true.
SAI: Shh.
I think he's coming.
NARUTO: It's about time.
Hey, wait.
Is that--
SAKURA: No way, it can't be.
He's the Akatsuke spy?
NARUTO: Next time,
"The Tenchi Bridge."
--[sakura and naruto together]
The Leaf Ask Us Anything
Investigation Team!
-This question comes from
Tazuna from the land of waves.
-I just don't get the
whole ninja ranking system.
Can you please explain
it to a layman like me?
-Good one.
-This takes me back
to the good old days.
-All right, Going down the
ranks of ninja from the top,
the jounin are the elite,
the best of the best.
There aren't many
of them, and each
possesses incredible abilities.
Next come the specialist
jounin, each uniquely gifted
in his or her field.
They're assigned
special missions
depending on their abilities.
Ibiki-sensei is an
expert in interrogation,
and Ebisu-sensi is good
at training, I guess.
Below them are the chunin.
Our main job is to act as
team leaders for the genin.
-That's I should be there
if there was any justice.
-Lastly, the genin.
-And finally, you're
getting to me.
-They don't really need
much explaining, Anyway,
we're just about out of time.
-What do you mean we don't
need much explaining?
-Thanks for the
question, Tazuna.
See you next time, everyone.
-Hey, wait!