[groan]
Huh?
Naruto!
[grunt]
[gasps]
Yes!  You have regained
consciousness!
Oh, thank goodness!
Where am I?
Is everyone okay?
We were all about to head
back to the village.
For some reason, the
enemy has retreated.
Yeah. Even though we
were at a disadvantage...
We think their goal was to
deliver Sasuke to Orochimaru.
Although, that's really
little more than a hunch.
Uh...  But where's Sasuke?  What
happened to Sasuke, guys?!
When I finally caught up with
you, the only thing I found
was you, unconscious.
[grunt]
I'm sorry, but... we couldn't
track them due to the rain.
Oh, I see...
[grunt]
Yeah, but... I promised Sakura
that I'd bring Sasuke back...
[grunt]
Hey, just take it easy!
No way! I mean, I can't just sit
around here doing nothing, you
know!
[crows squawking]
Huh...
♪
I've sent Kotetsu
and Izumo home.
But just to be safe,... Kakashi
is going to stay overnight.
Yes, I understand.
Well, that's a relief.
Urgent news!
Someone has just managed to
infiltrate the village!
[gasp]
You are...
It's been a long time,
Lady Tsunade...
Do you know him?
Wait, you're that boy from long
ago that Jiraiya saved, the one
from the Hidden Rain.
Yahiko, right?
It seems you do
remember me, then...
However, I'm now known as Pain.
Yahiko?! The one from
the Hizashi incident
three years ago?!
So why did you sneak
into our village now?
Our pain is twofold.  First...
...from the Five Great
Nations...
...and the Five Great
Villages...
The pain of being trampled...the
pain of all the people that you
killed.
And secondly,  the pain in our
hearts caused by the Leaf's
betrayal.
...Our pain... will become
the whole world's pain!
No...
True Planetary Devastation!
[loud engulfing noise]
[grunt]
[gasp]
What is that thing?!
Shikamaru! Explain
what's going on here!
Well, as you can see... this is
something ^ that seems to defy
explanation-and reality...
Hey, Neji! Is everyone in
the village still safe?
I mean, can you confirm what's
inside that big thing with your
Byakugan?
Of course. I'm on it now.
I can see chakra, and it seems
to be coming from the villagers.
So they're okay
inside there?!
It appears so, but I'm not
entirely positive.
[grunt]
Naruto!
What do you think you're doing?!
In your condition?!
I don't know what kind of jutsu
that is, but I'm gonna undo it
right now!
Huh?
Hey, Sakura...! I'm
glad you're okay!
I was out on a mission,
and I just got back.
But what's going on here?  What
happened to the village?
We don't know! We just
got back here, too.
But we have to find the guy who
did this and rescue everyone!
So, let's do this!
That's crazy!  You shouldn't
even move in your condition!
Everyone in the village is
inside of that thing!
We can't just sit around down
here and twiddle our thumbs!
[gasp]... All right, kneel down!
Huh?!
C'mon!  Just kneel down!
You need to recover first.
Oh, right.
(Thinking)
Okay... I'll use this time to...
What's this?! What's
happening here?
Seems the power supply was
cut, and the emergency
back-up system was activated.
I can't teleport
outside the village?
The wall... is it closing in?!
At this rate-- A simple
Earth Style will do!
Use a rock pillar as a support
to stop it from closing in
further!
The Akimichi Clan will use their
Super Expansion Jutsu to push
the wall back!
[yell]
[grunts]
I'll do whatever it takes
to hold it back!
Leaf Police Force!  Our priority
is to keep the villagers safe!
Now, go!
We will protect the Hidden Leaf
Village! We will stop this wall,
no matter what it takes!
[charging up yell]
Physical attacks don't
have any effect at all!
[explosions]
Everyone has reacted swiftly
and jumped in to help!
Minato! This is a special
Sealing Jutsu!
If this keeps up, everyone'll
be crushed by the mass of
stone around us, ya know!!
Everyone is pushing it back.
But you're right, it's only
a matter of time...
We have to figure out
what we can to do about
the jutsu caster...
(Kushina thought)
Lord Fourth!
[gasp]
Huh?
I have an idea to try. Kushina,
please stay here with these two
for right now, okay?
Flying Raijin Jutsu!
Lord Third, sir!
Yes, Minato?
We think this is a sealing
attack by the enemy.
And unless this jutsu... is
countered with another
jutsu of equal strength...
...everyone inside
here will be crushed.
Just as I suspected...
I was thinking that we could
try using the Four Crimson
Ray Formation.
But I'm going to need your help
to do that, Lord Hiruzen...
Right. Yes, let's try it.
Wait, Lord Fourth, I
know Tsunade has power
equal to a Hokage
But that's only three of us.
The Four Crimson Ray
Formation requires four people.
Kushina also possesses
the Nine Tails' chakra.
And she has far more experience
with Sealing Jutsu than anyone
else here right now...
Rivaling even that of a Hokage.
Yeah, but this Sealing Jutsu is
too strong for the Four Crimson
Ray Formation!
I mean, even a Tailed Beast
would have a really difficult
time trying to suppress it, ya
know.
[explosion]
There's no time left!
If we combine our strength with
everyone who's pushing back
against the wall, at least we
might be able to buy some time!
So we buy time, but then what?
Unless we can stop the jutsu,
this solves nothing!
We'll think of something
definitive in that time!
Please get to the
village's four corners.
[groan] All right.
Shizune,  your job now is to
tend to the wounded!
Understood.
[crumbling and cracking]
Four Crimson Ray Formation!
(Thinking)
All right, everyone,
hang in there...
If we can buy some time,
there's still hope.
[exhale]
Awesome, Sakura!  Thanks to you,
I think I'm fully recovered now!
[gasp]
Why, that...!
Hey, wait, Naruto! Don't
rush in like that!
You just recovered a second ago!
This kid is just hopeless...
Summoning Jutsu!
So, was it you guys? Are you the
ones who wrecked the village?!
[attack yell]
First of all, I'm gonna beat up
every last one of you guys
and then we're gonna talk!
That guy is...!
Naruto! That guy's Yahiko!
He was a part of Team Jiraiya.
Wait, you destroyed
that village back then!
You say you're Pervy
Sage's students?!
We're the Akatsuki.
And I'm Tendo Pain.
What...
We cast off the name Jiraiya the
moment the Hokage of the Hidden
Leaf burned that village
and everything inside
of it to the ground...
...just to hide the
embarrassment that
occurred there.
What are you talking about?  You
were the ones who destroyed that
entire village!
We have proof. And now,
to render judgment...
...for the pain
caused to the weak.
The pain of death... the pain of
my friends... my precious
friends...
The Hokage and the people of the
Hidden Leaf Village... will get
to taste pain!
I'll settle this right now!
[explosion]
[gasps]
[wince] Naruto!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto...!
[Gasp] What are you doing?!
You can't! That Pain guy isn't
an opponent we can deal with.
Naruto, however...
That's amazing.
Summoning Jutsu!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Sage Art: Giant Rasengan!
You're right. It's a
different level...
But still, I cannot just
stand here watching this!
If we get a chance,
we must assist him!
[grunt]
I see... That's Sage Jutsu.
So you've mastered the same
jutsu as Jiraiya Sensei.
You're no student of Pervy
Sage's, not with what you
guys are doing!
Now I'm gonna pulverize you!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Sage Art: Rasen Shuriken!
[panting breaths]
As I suspected... Sage Mode lasts
no more than five minutes...
What's this?!
Universal Pull.
[gasp] Argh!
[gasps]
(Thinking)
He's sucking all the Sage Jutsu
chakra right out of me!
This'll be just perfect...!
[grunt]
[cry of pain]
(Thinking)
What was that?  Is someone
watching?
So tell me, has this tamed you,
my sibling student...?
Naruto! I am coming
to help you!
Almighty Push!
Arghhh!
Lee!
[gasp]
I won't let you hurt Naruto
anymore!
That's right!  Hinata was on a
mission outside the village!
Why did you come
out here?! Just run!
You can't win!
I'm not afraid to die right
here... if it means I can
protect you!
And that's because Naruto is my-
(Tendo Pain)
Almighty Push!
[screams]
(Tendo Pain)
I've experienced it countless
times, right before my eyes,
so close I could feel
their breath...
...people dear to me dying...
Share my pain!
Yes, it was just like this...
My parents killed right in front
of my eyes by Hidden Leaf
shinobi...
[growl]
The power of Nine-Tails...
Rage summons him forth...
Do you hate me now?
[roar]
As you wish...
Almighty Push!
He withstood my Almighty Push!
And the recoil hit me!
(Thinking)
Naruto...
No way! That's six tails!
Universal Pull!
[explosion]
The Nine-Tails' power...
It's magnificent!
[roar]
Planetary Devastation!
(Kushina)
What? Something
inside of me is...
(Minato)
Kushina, what's wrong?
(Kushina)
It's the Nine Tails!  Usually,
I'm able to keep it stabilized
(Kushina)
but it's irritated and
unsettled right now.
(Minato)
Is it because you're expending
so much chakra for the Four
Crimson Rays?
(Kushina)
That's not it! I can
also feel that...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Comrade."
(Kushina)
There's something happening to
the other Nine Tails!