[frogs croaking]
[ribbit]
Has your so-called test finally
produced a result now?
I believe that it's been proven
conclusively that they consider
the bonds of friendship
more important than the
rules of the village.
So there's no need
to continue anymore...
You wi release all of the
Hidden Leaf Shinobi that you've
abducted, won't you...?
Father...?
No way! The Masked
Man is Neji's?!
Huh?
I thought you might want
this right about now...
Oh, wow, how thoughtful!
Here you go...
Ah, ah, ah! Hold it!
[slurp]
Ah! That was wonderful! It
sure does hit the spot!
All right, now to continue...
♪
Very well...
Where are you keeping all of the
captives? I trust that they're
safe...
Of course.  I'll have you
brought to them right away.
You can go and gather everyone.
All right then.
I have to tie up some loose
ends, but I'll join you later.
(Shikamaru)
All right, you all heard it!
We're working together now.
We'll rescue Asuma and-
No, I mean we're going
to rescue our friends !
(All)
Right!
Well, come on!
Let's get going!
Wait, hold up, Naruto!
What's the problem?! You're the
one who said we're going to go
rescue our friends!
Yeah, I did. But we
gotta slow down!
We don't even know
where they are now!
Yeah, not even one clue...
That is, unless there is some
intel that you have that we
do not, Naruto.
Yeah, yeah!
What!? You really think I'd
have that kind of stuff?
(All)
[groan]
Heh. Your fighting skills may've
improved slightly, but your
brain's still as lame as ever.
What was that?!
Hey! Stop fighting, guys!
I guess that's the cue
for the Tracking Team!
[bark]
I don't think that
you'll be needed...
Huh?
[bark bark]
Oh, Neji! I'm
glad you're safe!
Sorry to have worried you.
So, what happened with the
enemy?  Did you take him down?
No.
What?!  You let him get away?!
No, not exactly, but...
Well, then tell us what
happened, already!
Naruto! Give Neji a chance
to speak and he will!
Good grief...
Oh, uh... right.
So? What happened, Neji?
Hm?
Finally!
I've been bored to
death here, you know!
The test is over.  I don't need
you mercenaries anymore, so I'm
dismissing you.
What? You can't do
that! Just look!
...My art has been damaged, and
you expect me to just leave?!
Everything is complete. I was
able to verify the truth. So
you're dismissed.
Huh? Hey, partner, wait!
The job's complete. Once
we get paid, we're done.
Guess it can't be helped...
Huh... Huh!? Hey!
Wait a second!
I'd like you three to
tie up some loose ends.
What are these "loose
ends" you speak of?
Helping the evacuated villagers
return to their homes.
Sure, be glad to.
And there's one other thing that
I'd like to request of you...
Anyway, that's it.
So you're saying everything
that's happened so far was just
a part of some kind of
experiment by this masked man?
Hold on! That means Guy Sensei
and the others are safe?
Yes. That's what he told me,
and he also promised that he'd
free all of the captives and
lead us to them.
Lead us to them?
What does that mean?
[gasp]
Who the hell are you guys!?
First of all, we're
not your enemy.
We want to show you a
sign of mutual trust.
We're sorry for getting you
involved in our employer's test.
That test's over now.
So shortly, all your
friends will be released.
What? Seriously?
We three are shinobi of
the Hidden Rain Village.
We have been traveling the
land, in search of those who
share our vision of the Shinobi
World's future.
We are Team Jiraiya.
Huh! Team Jiraiya!?
You're sayin' you guys
know Pervy Sage, too?!
Yes! He saved our lives, and
he was our ninjutsu master.
(Shikamaru)
I get it now. When you attacked
us, I didn't sense any malice
because it was just a test.
So... what's the verdict, then?
Did we pass the test or what?
I think so. That's why
we've come to tell you
where your friends are.
Konan...
(Naruto)
Shinobi Ageha Butterflies...
These butterflies will guide
you to your friends.
We must depart in order
to return the villagers
to their homes.
So we'll be leaving you now.
Wait, hold on!
Damn it!  I wanted to hear more
about them and Pervy Sage.
Well, guess we should
follow them...
Ready, Neji?
Yes.
(Hinata)
Shinobi Ageha Butterflies...
They're over there!
By that structure...
All right, guys! Let's
go and save everyone!
Hold on! Naruto! There
could be traps set and-
He's not even listening.
Damn.
They're here!
How embarrassing...
Oh, Guy Sensei! I am
glad you are okay.
Thank you, Lee! I'm
just super-overcome
with emotion right now!
To be rescued by my own
student! This is truly
far more than I deserve!
[crying]
Tenten! Can ya
be a little gentler?
But it's only a little scratch!
Asuma...
Sensei... Did you
get hurt at all?
Not a bit. I'm sorry that
we made you all worry.
I'm just so relieved!
Anyway... did you guys
figure out what this
incident was all about?
Do you think you
could explain it?
Oh, uh...
(Masked Man)
Allow me to explain...
Just wait a second!  It's okay.
He's no longer our enemy!
Well, okay, then.
[shocked gasps]
No way... You're--!
...You're... Hizashi Hyuga...
(Hinata)
Impossible...!
Everyone knows that you're
supposed to have died when I was
only three years old!
What!?
Please allow me to
explain that part.
Go on, Neji.
Back when Lady Hinata was three
years old, a major crisis befell
the Hidden Leaf Village.
...Shinobi from the Hidden Cloud
attempted to kidnap you...
...but instead, Lord
Hiashi killed them.
(Hinata)
It was all the Hidden
Cloud's fault...
Naturally, relations
became strained and the
threat of war loomed.
In order to prevent further
fighting, he Leaf secretly
talked with the Cloud
and accepted their terms.
Because... that was their
only choice...
What were the terms that
the Leaf agreed to?
The Hyuga leader who possessed
the Kekkei Genkai, Byakugan.
In other words, they demanded
the Leaf hand over the corpse of
Lady Hinata's father, Hiashi
Hyuga.
And so, Hiashi's younger twin,
my father Hizashi Hyuga, became
his stand-in...
...and because of that,
peace between the villages
was maintained.
As for my father's decision and
the circumstances behind it, you
saw it yourself, Naruto.
[gasp]
The terrible system of the Curse
Mark that's been passed down
within the Hyuga to protect the
Main Family...
We may be alive, but
we're unable to change
the currents of fate.
What you saw was my father,
who by his own free will...
chose to defy his fate.
Kakashi... This has caused
everyone so much stress.
But you're supposed
to be dead, How did-?
Yes. At first, I didn't
understand it all, either.
After a long slumber, I
awoke, and found myself in
a certain hideout.
Hizashi, you've been revived
thanks to my Reanimation Jutsu.
Although... it was also because
your heart still has attachments
to this world.
I have no attachments.
I wanted to die for-
(Orochimaru)
-the sake of the clan.
You may tell me that it was your
wish to give up your life...
But what if you knew that
your death was in vain...?
Perhaps that man was right... I
did feel that way at the time.
And that's why I planned
this course of action.
(Hizashi)
I hoped that my death
was not in vain...
...that my death would
provide the impetus for
the Hidden Leaf Village
to rethink the cruel rules
and belief in destiny
which took away my life...
Well, all that
doesn't matter now...
I'm a man who simply shouldn't
exist in this world any longer.
However, it seems it's
impossible for me to undo
this jutsu myself.
Please, return to the
village and find out how
to release this jutsu.
But before that, I would ...like
to take a moment to speak with
my son Neji, alone.
Neji, do you remember
that fateful day?
Neji, you must survive.
You've been gifted with the
Hyuga's abilities more than any
other member in our clan.
I should have been born a few
moments earlier, and made you
part of the main household.
Even though I did what I did in
order to protect the village,
our family, and you,
I'm sorry to say that defying
the fate of the Hyuga appears to
have brought you nothing but
sadness.
On top of that, I was worried
about your future, tied as it
was to the destiny of the Hyuga.
Yes... It was only
natural, having lost you,
I used that as motivation
to resent and curse my
destiny as a Hyuga.
[gasp]
Argh!
But then, after meeting a
certain genin, my way of
thinking changed drastically.
[labored breathing]
(Neji)
You don't know what it's like to
be branded with a mark that sets
you apart...
A mark that can never
be wiped away!!
I know what that's like.
[gasp]
Well... Big deal.
Man, you think you've
got troubles?
I've got news for you, Neji,
you're not the only special
one around here.
Everyone ... is desperate to
defy their own destiny.
And you're no different.
I'm gonna show you you're wrong
about a lotta things, starting
right now!
It may be the Hyuga way to cave
in to destiny, it's not mine!
If you think it's futile to
fight, then don't! Just stand
there and take it!
I'll change the way
of the Hyuga clan...
...after I become Hokage!
Naruto Uzumaki...
taught me the truth...
That even a caged bird, if
it's smart enough, will use
its beak to open the latch...
...because it wants to
fly free across the sky.
I don't know what will
come; maybe I'll just end
up in the same place.
But when people can make their
own choices... they can strive
earnestly towards their goal in
life.
What's more... ...if you
do that, that's what
makes you truly strong!
Please listen, Father...
I have only one goal now...
To become stronger, and
never be defeated!
That is how I feel.
You have made a wonderful
friend... Neji.
(Neji)
Although right now,
he's a rival...
(Neji)
Father...!
Huh?
It seems that we don't need
to find a way to release
that jutsu after all...
Yeah...
[gasp]
You've become a fine man, Neji.
Father, wait!
Father...
[hawk cry]
(Neji)
Guy Sensei...
You know, Neji, it seems
to me that Hizashi's
greatest regret in life
was that he wasn't able
to be here to guide you
into adulthood...
was that he wasn't able
to be here to guide you
into adulthood...
Yes.
[villagers chatter]
Well, I'm glad that the
villagers are finally back home
and that peace has returned to
this village once again.
Yes. So what are we
going to do now?
Are you still thinking
of joining up with
the Hidden Leaf Genin?
Yeah... We are different, but I
feel we can call them comrades.
Perhaps one day we'll be
able to team up with them.
Huh?
Nagato, what's that?
Isn't that the kid's?
I found it on the road nearby.
With all the chaos of everyone
trying to get home, they
must've dropped it.
[chuckle] And right now, I bet
they're making a big fuss about
their missing friend.
Well, then, I'll go and
return it to them.
Yahiko...
I'll be right back.
Just wait here.
All right! Let's hurry home
so I can report to Dad.
Okay, then, Naruto, let us have
a race back to the village.
I'll warn you,
I won't lose!
Well, neither will I!
I said I'm not gonna lose!
Same here!
Me too!
Me, too, as well!
Why aren't they tired?!
Seriously...
(Kakashi)
Hey! Hold up!
(Guy)
Yeah! My body's still
not, well, it's, uh...
(Kurenai)
Why don't we rest a bit?
[labored breaths]
Oh boy...
Huh?
[massive explosion]
What was... what just happened?
Yahiko...
[gasp]
[frightened breaths]
Nagato...
[crazed gasps]
[screaming]
(Tsunade)
Damn that Jiraiya!
Why'd he write a story with an
ending that leaves such a bad
taste in your mouth?!
I've gotta find out
what happens next...
(Shizune)
I thought you might like a
little something for tea...
Or is this a bad time?
(Tsunade)
No, not at all, thank
you for that!
I was actually just starting to
feel a little bit hungry...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Returning Home"
(Tsunade)
Right! Onward!