Excuse me!
Yes, come in!
Lady Tsunade,
everyone's here.
Huh? Where's my Dad?
Since this morning,
representatives from all
the villages have been in an
emergency summit.
Lord Fourth brought Kakashi
and the other jonin with him
to take part.
No wonder-
But don't you worry, Naruto!
'Cause I'm here, too!
What?! Pervy Sage!
Lady Tsunade, what did you
want to see us about?
It's regarding the news
that's been going around
recently.
It's coming in from every
region...
Um... what news?
That Orochimaru is dead. And
it seems that Sasuke Uchiha
did it.
[gasping]
It's disappointing... I
had always hoped in my heart
of hearts I could bring
Orochimaru back...
I'm sorry, Pervy Sage...
But Sasuke not ending up as
Orochimaru's vessel makes
me glad!
There's one more thing...
the Akatsuki have been
attacking shinobi villages,
kidnapping Kage and Jonin
Class Shinobi.
And word is also going
around... that Sasuke
is working with them.
No way!
Yeah, I couldn't believe
it either. But the intel
that I gathered comes from
quite a few trusted sources.
It seems that it really is
true.
The representatives from the
villages are likely
discussing sanctions
on the Akatsuki
and Sasuke.
Does that mean that Sasuke
is going to become a wanted
criminal, then?
What did my dad have to say
about this?!
Well, naturally, of course,
Lord Fourth wouldn't want
that to happen.
And that's why...
Right here is all the data
that we've gathered so
far.
The Akatsuki members. All
about them. Including...
...their special abilities
and where they've been
spotted.
Use this and find Sasuke
before any of the other
villages...
... and bring
him back!
Doing that is probably the
only way that we're going to
be able to save Sasuke.
Got it?
On this mission, our team is
gonna be working with each
one of yours to track and
locate Sasuke.
Don't take action on your
own. We have to work
together on this.
Yes. Right. The reason
is because our goal
is to find Sasuke
and bring him
back home.
So don't rush off,
especially you, Naruto!
Gimme a break! I know that!
All right, C'mon, let's
go!
Hey, what is all this?!
My art. My Human Puppets.
They number in the tens of
thousands.
You've been making stuff
like this with the personnel
we gathered?!
What are you planning
with all this military
build-up?
We Akatsuki will rule the
world instead of the Five
Great Nations.
First, we'll crush
the Leaf Village.
[gasping]
So your strategy is to win
with quantity?
Your idea of what art
is differs from mine.
Art must be an explosion, or
it isn't art!
Deidara, your aerial attack
will disorient and
disorganize the enemy. Then
I'll send in my Human
Puppet army for an all-out
ground battle.
[chuckling] After my artful
explosion, there won't
even be a blade of grass
left to fight on!
Are you an idiot? Then there
won't be anything left to
rule!
What did you say?!
Tsh! Do you have a
problem with my art or
something?!
That's it, you
idiot!
I'm letting you handle the
destruction of the Leaf like
you wanted.
Aren't you satisfied?
I just want to destroy the
current system that has the
Fourth Hokage at its helm.
I'm not looking to destroy
the Leaf itself.
Are you planning on
deserting the Akatsuki?
I never agreed to be
your henchman in the
first place.
We nursed you back from the
brink. And now you're
gonna betray us?!
A few of them have broken
the barrier and slipped into
Akatsuki territory.
The Five Great Nations
probably sent them.
[barking]
So you caught the scent,
too, huh, Akamaru?
[barking]
We found him! Sasuke is
close by!
Are you sure that it's
Sasuke's scent?
Which direction?
Follow me!
[barking]
What?
It's the Akatsuki!
Sasuke.
Itachi?! I thought
you were dead!
I can't die while your
future and that of the
Uchiha are so uncertain.
Healing from my wounds just
took longer than I expected.
I'm glad you're okay.
Look, Sasuke, what is it
that you're trying to do?
And just where do you
belong?
Itachi, that's--
You should already know what
it is that you must do.
[cawing]
Where's Sasuke? He's with
you guys now, isn't that
right?!
He was with us until a
little while ago.
But he didn't care for
the way we do things...
and he left.
Listen, talking with these
guys isn't gonna accomplish
anything at all!
I say that we just kill
'em off already!
Hey, wait! You were at that
village!
Oh, yeah! I remember you!
Well, guess what, punk!
It's payback time.
Let me have that one, all
right?!
Whatever you want.
Naruto!
Huh-hey, what are you
guys doing here?
I managed to track
you with my Byakugan!
That's Hidan. Just leave
him to us.
But, you guys---!
Relax! Thanks to Lady
Tsunade's data, I have his
jutsu all figured out.
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
C'mon, I'm not falling for
that trick!
You won't escape!
Let's go!
Now that Hidan has taken off
what do we do?
You're his partner. So do
something!
Who are you calling his
partner? Guess I have no
choice...
I think his name is Kakuzu.
According to Lady
Tsunade's intel, that guy
possesses five hearts...
My Gentle Fist can handle
it.
Is there anything that
the rest of us can do?
Seems he specializes in
mid-range attacks. But the
Gentle Fist is a just
short-range attack.
I understand! We will
distract him by creating
a diversion!
When we do... take him down!
Here goes!
You may run, but it is
useless.
Guess it's time for my art
to make an appearance.
What is that giant thing?!
Didn't you read through
the data on him?
Oh... Uh, no.
That's the C2 Dragon.
Deidara is an explosives
expert.
If you're going to
compliment me, I wish
you'd say that I'm an
"explosive artist",
Quit messing around!
Huh?
Watch out, Naruto!
Hold up, there! That's a
land mine, you know!
Step on one, and my art will
go off!
A land mine?!
Aw, come on!
It's Sasuke!
[screaming]
Huh?!
Hold on... There was no
explosion!
His Lightning Style disabled
the land mines!
Sasuke!
After you took down
Orochimaru, why didn't you
just come back home?
I would've been happy to
take you on any time.
We'll talk more about that
after we finish them.
Wait, what? But aren't
those guys your comrades?!
Those who don't share my
goals aren't my comrades.
Then that makes this easy.
You can leave the ones up
top to us! Go, Akamaru!
[barking]
Fang Over Fang!
[chuckling]
Now, Akamaru!
[barking]
What?!
Dynamic Marking!
Ew, that's disgusting!
That jutsu didn't have
even one ounce of art to it!
All right, that's it!
I'm going to show you what
real art is!
Ha! You know what I
say? To hell with art!
Hey, wait, you bastard!
I don't get it. Why'd you
save me?
Because I'll be the one to
take you down.
[chuckling]
We'll talk after we take
care of the Akatsuki.
Yeah! All right.
This doesn't look too
good, wouldn't you say so?
Let's get out of here
quietly before we're dragged
into it.
[grumbling]
Looks like it's down to just
you, now!
Sasuke, I'm very
disappointed in you.
[growling]
Take this! Cha!
Chidori!
Rasengan!
[chuckling] It's been a
long time since I was
outside.
What the-?!
[gasping]
I'll turn you all into
Human Puppets and make you a
part of the Akatsuki.
We'll never join up with
you!
You think so? Oh,
we'll see about that.
Summoning Jutsu!
Reanimation!
What is happening?!
They're Shinobi Puppet
Users Orochimaru and I
prepared
while he was still
alive.
It's the jutsu used to
resurrect Hizashi three
years ago.
And what's more...
Well...?
I hope you like my
masterpieces,
which will let me
rule the Shinobi World.
They're my
human puppets.
There's so many of them.
I know, but we gotta destroy
them all...
Ninja Art: Wind Scythe
Jutsu!
[grunting]
No way! It's Dad! And
everyone!
I rushed over from the
summit as soon as I heard
what was going on.
We're certainly not
going to ignore a
friend, after all.
Thanks, Gaara!
When it comes to puppets,
we're experts.
We'll be happy to take you
on.
Aim for the Chakra Threads!
You do that and they'll
become simple dolls!
Naruto, you deal with
Sasori.
Right!
Okay, now it
really is just you!
[gasping]
He'll be your opponent.
No way! Is that--?!
It'll all be over quickly.
[gasping]
Sakura?
I've trained hard too, and
I've caught up to both of
you guys.
And besides that...
... it's full now.
Huh?
Anyway, just watch!
Here, take this! Cha!
Wow! Awesome!
I'll say.
All right, how about this,
then?
Those are...!
The Kage! They were turned
into Human Puppets, too?!
[grunting]
It wasn't easy turning them
into Human Puppets.
It cost me a lot of military
strength...
And to make up for that
loss, what I did was bring
you into the Akatsuki,
Sasuke.
I should've made you a
Human Puppet right away!
[grunting]
So are you telling us...
that Sasuke is innocent?
That doesn't matter right
now. Just focus on the enemy
that's in front of us.
Now!
All right, they've all
been sealed away.
Summoning Jutsu!
Lady Katsuyu, our focus is
healing everyone!
And in the meantime,
we'll handle the Kage!
Heh!
Wait, Sasuke!
I'll settle this by
myself.
Particle Style: Atomic
Dismantling Jutsu!
[gasping]
Aoda gone in one hit?!
You see? Isn't that
what you'd call a
masterpiece?
Now you will become a
piece of my art.
Hold it right there!
Huh?
Pervy Sage?
Team Jiraiya is now on the
scene!
Nagato? Konan?
It seems you were able to
save your comrade like you
promised you would.
Uh, yeah! But we haven't
really had the time to
patch things up yet.
Well... Then, Naruto,
you are--
That's right. Yahiko
is dead, but you can
take his place.
But you guys, that's--
It looks like Team Jiraiya
is back in action!
The Child of Prophecy who
will save the future of
shinobi...
... let's see what you
got, kid!
Heh! Yeah, okay.
[grunting]
Lava Style: Lava Monster
Jutsu!
My, how disappointing.
[gasping]
You're too reckless,
Sasuke.
Big Brother?!
[gasping]
Why do you insist on
fighting alone? You
have comrades with you.
[gasping]
[chuckling] Anyway,
I'll help you out.
Hm. Do what
you want.
Gamakichi! Go!
This is seriously not good!
Leave it to me!
Particle Style: Boundary
Dismantling Jutsu!
I can absorb any jutsu.
Uh--
Naruto! Now!
[grunting]
Rasengan!
Sasuke! Do it!
No way! All my
art has been...
Damn! Not yet! It's not
over!
This ends now! I
will not lose to you!
Nope, wrong. Sorry, but you
can't win this.
What was that?!
Just take a good look
around.
[gasping]
A person like you who goes
around turning comrades into
puppets...
...can never...
...win against my friends!
Heh-heh. Idiot.
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
Inferno Style: Flame
Control!
[yelling]
[struggling]
It's over.
Sasuke, come back to the
village.
Look, couldn't we just...
I don't know, start over?
And then maybe
be friends?
Sure, I'll return to the
Leaf.
But don't get the wrong
idea.
Huh?!
I'm not gonna join up with
you guys.
I'll change the Shinobi
World and do it my own way.
Huh?!
My feelings won't change, no
matter what happens. As a
true friend, I'm gonna
take you back
to the village!
Remember when I first met
you? Back at the Academy
entrance ceremony?
Yeah, what
about it?
This has been destined to
happen since back then!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Rival."
I don't know what you're
talking about! That was
a long time ago!