[chatting]
Hey, Ino, you
here? Come on out.
What's up? What are
you two guys doing
here?
Do you remember what
Kakashi Sensei said?
Our assignment?
All right, I'm giving
each of you a secret
mission to prepare a
congratulatory gift
for Naruto and
Hinata's wedding.
Yeah! Of course!
And? What about it?
Well, I thought we
could discuss what to
get them.
Sorry!
I've already got
something really
great picked out for
them. Actually, I was
just about to go down
to the store to get it.
Which store? We'll
go with you!
No, you won't! We
can't shop at the
same place. You two
can think of
something on your
own!
Later!
[gasping]
What are we gonna do
now...?
Oh! Miss? I'd like
some ice cream for
dessert.
You, Shikamaru?
No, nothing for me.
You sure can eat,
though, you know that?
Your appetite
hasn't changed a bit
since you were a kid.
Well, I'm starting
to like chicken thigh
and grilling my beef
super rare, so I
think that my tastes
are really beginning
to mature.
Sure, whatever you
say Choji. Anyway,
getting back to the
topic at hand...
Yeah, I'm thinking
maybe yuzu sorbet's
better than ice cream.
No! Not that! I'm
talking about Naruto
and Hinata's present!
Oh, yeah. Of course.
That whole thing...
Here's your ice
cream.
Oh, good, it's here!
From Ino's
attitude, I'm
guessing that she
isn't gonna be
of any help to us.
If this keeps up, we
might be the only
ones who can't find
a present in time.
What do you
mean by "we"?
I've already picked
something out.
[gasping]
R- Really?! What are
you getting them?!
Since you asked, this
is what I'm thinking
of giving them.
[grunting]
Huh?
This is-!
Yup, gift
certificates
for dinner!
And it's not just for
some run-of-the-mill
place!
These are gift
certificates for a
super-fancy
restaurant that VIPs
like the Hokage go
to!
It's a special
occasion!
[grunting]
What's going on?!
This is Choji we're
talking about! And
somehow he chose the
perfect gift!
Having dinner in a
restaurant you
wouldn't normally
be able to go to is
special, and it's
really memorable for
a couple!
Not a lot of gifts
would have as much
impact as this one!
And even if this
is for a special
occasion, he's
willing to give up a
gift certificate to a
fancy restaurant,
just like that?
Oh, miss?
May I have another
bowl of ice cream?
Are you really the
Choji I know?! It's
not just your taste
buds that matured!
Have you completely
become an adult now?
[grunting]
Hm?
Here's your ice
cream.
Not bad, huh? They
came as a three-for-one
special.
[gasping]
Wait, why would they
offer three for dinner?
A romantic dinner is
for two!! Come on,
what's wrong with
you, fancy
restaurant?!
Choji's totally gonna
tag along if it's
three certificates.
Shikamaru? What's
wrong?
Oh, it's nothing...
So are you planning
to go along with them?
Are you kidding me?!
Even I know better
than a tag along with
newlyweds!
Uh, oh, yeah, right!
Of course you'd know
that!
I was just gonna have
the host there seat me
at a different table.
[gasping]
So, you are going?!
Still, this isn't the
time to get on
Choji's case...
I haven't figured
out what to get them.
And I can't waste
time deciding.
Something functional?
No, not festive
enough. A decorative
item? No, that's
useless if it's not
their style.
Flowers and food are
perishable, so they
would seem like a
seasonal gift.
Honestly, giving them
any item is risky.
So that just
leaves cash.
Actually, that's
not a bad idea.
Then they can get
whatever they want.
It's way better
than getting
something they
won't use or a
duplicate gift.
Wait, what if
everyone else gives a
gift and only I give
them money...
It's not much, but
here ya go!
Not good! Everyone
will think I was too
lazy to go out and
buy a gift, so I just
handed them cash
without giving it a
second thought!
You okay, Shikamaru?
Uh, yeah; I just felt
a chill, that's all.
Oh, sorry. Did you
get cold from
watching me eat all
that ice cream?
No, that's not it.
I needed it. All that
barbecue got me hot!
Plus, I'm the kind
of guy who could eat
ice cream even if
I'm traveling deep
in snow country
during a blizzard!
My appetite beats the
cold every time.
Heh, damn it, there's
nothing that could
beat your appeti--
Choji! What did you
just say?!
Um, do you mean My
appetite beats the
cold?
No, it was before
that!
Snow country?
Oh, right! I can eat
ice cream even if
I'm traveling in
snow country.
Heh! Travel!
So... a honeymoon?
Yeah. I'll give
them a honeymoon.
Thanks to you,
I came up with
the perfect gift.
So where are you
off to now, then?
I have to decide on a
destination for them
and then go and
check it out.
And I'm gonna have to
get a woman's point
of view so that I can
get a sense of
whether Hinata might
like it.
If only Ino were here
right now.
Check it out.
Huh?!
Uh?!
[gasping]
Oh, hey, there...
It's been a while.
Ever since that
one day, huh?
Yeah, that's right.
So, um, what are the
two of you up to, today?
Oh, just stuff... We
had a little lunch.
How 'bout you?
Uh..
I'm here to discuss
the Chunin Exams, and
I've been making my
rounds to catch up
with a few people
here.
Oh, yeah? Is that so?
What's the matter
with you, Choji?!
I thought you mean
Ino was there.
You said that you
needed a woman's
point of view, but
that doesn't mean
that Ino has to be
the one to help out.
But this is Temari!
She's a warrior-type
to the core. I
can't talk to her
about some wedding
gift!
Seriously? You're
gonna give them a
honeymoon as a
wedding gift? Ha!
Talk about a
ridiculous and
pathetic idea!
I just know that her
response would be
something like that.
But, I mean, couldn't
you say the same
thing about Ino, too?
Hey, just what are
you two whispering
about over there?
Oh, it's nothing!
I think that
Shikamaru wants to
talk to you about
something.
T-Talk to me?
How about sometime...
we, uh...
...have dinner or
something like that?
Oh, uh so you wanna
talk? About what?
Damn it, Choji!
[grunting]
I can't very well
come out now and say
something like,
it's no use talking
to Temari about
honeymoons.
Well, uh...
I have no choice.
Huh?
All right, you see
the thing is...
I've been giving
some really serious
thought to honeymoons
lately.
[gasping]
So, if it were you,
where would you like
to go?
Ah! Where would I like to
go on a honeymoon?!
W- What's wrong?
N-Nothing. So, a... a
honeymoon, huh?
And, uh, is there a
reason why you're
asking me,
in particular...
Huh? Well, I just
figured that-
Wait a second... I
can't come out and
say it doesn't
really matter who, I
just need any
woman's opinion?
I just thought that
out of everybody, the
best person to ask is you!
What?! I'm the best
one out of everybody?
I think I see... So
that's it, huh...?
Okay, I'll hear
you out.
Oh, wow, that's
great! Well, I was
thinking that going
somewhere like a
secluded hot springs
would be a nice and
relaxing vacation.
Or does that sound
like something an old
man would do?
No, a trip to a hot
spring sounds great!
Really? I'm so glad
to hear that! I mean,
good food and a hot
spring! That sounds
perfect, right?
Good. At least I got
confirmation. So now...
You just have to
choose where to go,
right?
Huh? Oh, yeah, I
guess so. Maybe I can go
check a few of them out.
It's still pretty
early. Why not go
right now?
That's true. All
right, then-
I'm going to go to the
sweets shop now, so
why don't you two go?
[gasping]
[chuckling] I'm
really sorry, but I
just gotta have a
little dessert after
eating!
Oh, come on,
you just ate!
You know there's a
different stomach for
dessert.
You had desert! Now
you want dessert to
dessert?!
[gasping]
You idiot! Because of
Choji's big mouth,
Temari is standing
there all red-faced
and upset!
Oh, um... Choji
didn't mean to get
you upset or
anything. Since we
were talking about
honeymoons, he just
figured there's no
sense in me going
alone.
That's right. A
honeymoon is meant
for two, so you guys
should go together.
Uh?!
Okay, bye, you two.
I'm gonna take off
now!
Hey, uh Choji...?!
[grunting]
What exactly am I
supposed to do now?!
[grunting]
I'll go.
Huh?
How did it end up
like this? And
what's with this
weird tension?!
I never expected
Temari to be helping
me choose a wedding
gift for Naruto and
Hinata...
But why's she so
silent all of a
sudden? I can't get
a read on her at all!
First, I have to get
her out of her bad
mood.
Hey, you know...
since we're out,
you wanna...
...make a couple
stops?
Oh, okay... that
sounds fine...
Uh!
[grunting]
Now that's rare! You,
missing a target?
[gasping]
No way...
[chuckling]
Sorry I couldn't
win any more.
[giggling]
[gasping]
I'm not sure, but I
think she's in a
good mood now!
[humming]
Thank goodness!
It's still here!
When I saw it last
time, I knew it was
the perfect wedding
gift.
It's cute and sweet
and simple. It's
really one of a kind!
I have to dig into my
savings to afford it,
but I just know that
Hinata is going to
love it!
Anyway, my wedding
gift to them is all
set now!
[gasping]
Oh! Hello, Ino! What
a surprise!
How funny! I was
gonna say the same
thing to you!
No way-!
Is she-?!
Oh, by the way, have
you seen Naruto
recently?
Mm-mm. Not at all.
It's hard to imagine,
Naruto getting
married. He used to
be so crazy about
you!
Oh, that was way back
when we were just
kids. I'm really
very happy he and
Hinata are together.
I knew it...
She's also...
(both)... planning on
getting that as her
wedding gift!
I have to get that
picture frame before
she does! But how?
Uh!
Uh... listen, I don't
mean to be rude, but
you weren't planning
on getting this for
Naruto and Hinata's
wedding, were
you, Sakura?
Huh?
That's right! I
have to provoke her
and make her feel too
proud to buy it!
I mean, that's
impossible, right?
You would never get
them something so
tacky, would you?
[grunting]
I'm not gonna fall
for that one! She's
just trying to diss
that picture frame so
I won't buy it!
What are you trying
to pull? You were
totally about to buy
it just a second ago
and you know it.
Uh! No, that's--
How could you even
think about buying
something as tacky as
that? It's so stupid!
What?! Stupid?!
I never said I was
going to buy that
thing! I was only
gonna move it out of
the way because it's
obviously a big
piece of junk!
[clearing throat]
Look, you may have
more brute strength,
but you don't have
any taste at all!
Brute strength?! Are
you kidding me?! I
mean, seriously, that
is a completely lame
comparison!
Excuse me... but
you're starting to
annoy all the other cust--
You see, Ino! You're
annoying everybody,
like always!
What do you mean,
me?!
[arguing]
This is mine!
Hands off! It's mine!
I found it first--
Now, now. Please
calm down! Don't pull
so hard on that,
or else you might-!
[grunting]
Back off and shut up!
[humming]
You've got some
nerve!
[grunting]
Hm!
Nice. Because of you,
we got kicked out of
there!
I should be saying
that to you!
You don't know what
compromise means, you
have no regard for
anyone else, and you
have no chest! All you
have is brute strength.
Huh?!
My chest has nothing
to do with this!
The fact is, you
never win against me,
so you always bring
up something
unrelated! You're
so immature.
I don't know the
meaning of not
winning. And besides,
I win hands down in
being feminine!
Being feminine?! You?
How?
Now, now, guys.
Please, just stop
fighting, okay?
Choji! Great! Your
timing is perfect!
Which one of us do
you think is more
feminine, me or
Sakura?!
Huh?! You can't ask
that out of the blue!
[chuckling] Even
Choji, your own
teammate, won't
pick you over
me! How sad!
Ha! Choji's not
on your team, but
he won't even try
to flatter you.
That's what's really
sad!
Hey, come on, now.
Cut it out.
Wait, hold on a
second... If you
really want to know,
then why don't you
put it to a test?
What? A test?
For example,
personally I think
that someone who can
cook is very
feminine. So maybe
you could see which
of you cooks better?
Okay, let's begin
this challenge!
The person who makes
the tastiest food
pills will be
declared the winner.
You'd better watch
out, Sakura. I know
what you like and
dislike. All that I
have to do is cook up
something that'll
make you gag.
And the judge is
gonna be Choji.
Huh?! You mean you're
not gonna eat this?!
Works for me! I may
have just eaten a
whole mountain of ice
cream, but I always
have room for a few
food pills!
Wait, just hold on...
This isn't right.
Choji's my
teammate. That gives
me an unfair
advantage!
Fine by me. Anyway,
you should be okay
with having an edge...
...unless you were
planning to poison
them to make me sick.
But you wouldn't do
that, would you?
As if I would ever do
that! Come on, let's
just get this
thing started!
Now let the contest
to see who's more
feminine by making
food pills, begin!
Ready...?!
Now fight!
Whoa, what is this?!
Instead of a mortar
and pestle, she's
using her fine chakra
control to get the
ingredients to the
size she needs!
I can't wait to
taste the sensation!
Whoa!
She's searing the
ingredients with fire
power!
Now Sakura's using
some legendary golden
honey!
Ino's adding cacao
powder! Both seem
irresistible!
Th-This is--
[eating]
It's... it's...
[yelling] Yum!
So delicious!
It's rich, yet not
overpowering, an
indescribable
something that
explodes on your
tongue, a delicate
aroma and lingering
taste, a treasure
trove of sweetness!
Choji!
Hm?
So, which one is it?
Which tastes better?
Oh, I ate 'em both so
fast I couldn't tell!
[groaning]
But they were both
really, really good!
[struggling]
Choji!
Choji?! Choji!
[gasping]
I have made so many
great friends in my life.
Noooo!
Choji! Don't die!
Please!
What is going on? Is
his life flashing
before his eyes?!
Ino! You did use
poison, didn't you?!
You know I wouldn't
do that! Just who do
you think I am, anyway?
I've made so many
great friends...
This is really not
good! Choji's
delirium's getting
even worse!
[grunting]
What are you doing?!
I have to identify
what's inside of
these food pills
before I can know how
to treat him.
If there's any
poison in them, my
tongue will go numb.
I told you, I didn't
put poison in these!
Damn it, oh, alright!
[eating]
Delicious!
Mm!
How did you-?! This
is like my favorite
flavor!
Mine too! This tastes
amazing!
Oh man, I think I
just ate too many
sweets!
My blood sugar
probably shot
up too fast.
But I feel
okay now!
Is that what just
happened?! Thank
goodness.
Hey, Ino... Why would
you go out of your way to
make something I love?
To tell you the
truth, I kinda just
thought that if I
made you gag with
surprise, then I'd
win the contest!
Really?! You know
what's funny?
That was my
strategy as well!
Huh?! No way,
you, too?
I guess, then, it's
no wonder I love how
these taste.
[eating and giggling]
In the end it seems
that we both saw right
through each other.
Since we know each
other so well, there's
something I
wanna say to you,
that okay?
What is it?
Don't you think
that we'd find an
even better wedding
present if we both
teamed up and looked
for one together?
[giggling]
What now?
Sakura... I thought
the same thing!
That inn seems nice.
Huh?
I'd better hurry up
and choose a place,
or I'll keep
mulling over this
wedding gift forever.
I just have to
pick something!
Okay. Let's go in!
Wait. What?!
What's wrong?
I thought we were
just gonna look...
Yeah, but we have to
go inside or we won't
be able to make a
good decision.
But I'm not really
mentally prepared.
What? Mentally
prepared? Is she
panicking because
this place too fancy?
It's okay, Temari!
Let's just go inside
and then we
can decide.
It'll be too late
once we go in! I
could get all caught
up in the mood or
something like that.
What is she talking
about? The mood? The
mood of that inn?
What does she mean by
getting caught up in
it? I don't get it!
[gasping] Wait
Temari, hold on!
You don't have a
fever, do you?
All right, I've had
enough! I think I
need to go home!
Wait, it'll be dark
soon!
Seriously, if
you're not feeling
well, then we really
should book a room so
you can get some
rest!
[grunting]
Please wait! I
really--
I need you!
You're sure? That
I'm really the one?
Yeah! You're the
only one!
[gasping]
I mean, I can't just
walk into the women's
bath to check it out.
Huh?
Temari, I need you to
do this for me... Go
into the women's
bath and report back
with every detail!
That's all! It
should be easy,
right?!
Wait a sec. What
exactly is this all
about?
Well, what else? I
wanna give Naruto and
Hinata a honeymoon
for their wedding
present, and I need
to choose a good place!
Oh, so that's
what's going on, huh?
Uh, yeah... Didn't
I explain it earlier?
No. This is the first
I've heard of it!
[gasping]
[grunting]
[slurping]
So you're back to
square one in your
search for a
wedding gift?
Mm-hmm. But I think
it turned out for the
best in the end.
And? How 'bout you,
Shikamaru?
Trying to explain
things is a drag.
[chuckling]
(Killer Bee)
It's Naruto's Wedding!
Hinata's in love, fellas!
And I'm totally jealous!
Fool, ya fool!
A wedding gift, I
gotta prepare,
something extravagant
and rare. If the cost
is too steep, split
it among my peeps!
Now I wanna get
married, too! I will,
for sure! I'll be
the next one up!
I'm so popular!
I'm about to burst,
that's my stance!
I'm on the frontline
of romance.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Hidden
Leaf Story, The
Perfect Day for a
Wedding, Part 4:
The Kazekage's
Wedding Gift."