MADARA: After the attack of the
nine-tailed fox, 16 years ago,
unjust suspicions
grew that the Uchiha
had tried to stage
an insurrection
and seize power to take over
leadership of the village.
As a result, the Uchiha were
put under strict surveillance
by the ANBU black
ops, and were forced
to relocate to the
outskirts of the village.
They became completely isolated.
Distrust bred hatred,
and eventually, their suspicions
became reality.
The Uchiha clan
started plotting a coup
de tat to take over the village.
And so the Hidden Leaf's
leaders planted a spy
within the Uchiha
clan to watch us.
That spy was your older
brother, Itachi Uchiha.
And that's when Itachi's
suffering began.
-An Uchiha coup de tat.
And Itachi...
was he really a spy?
- Despite being an Uchiha,
you were told nothing
because you were so young.
But it's all true.
Your father, Fugaku,
was the mastermind
of that planned coup.
And Itachi was a spy who
entered the ANBU black ops
on your father's orders.
- Itachi, you also serve as
the Uchiha clan's pipeline
to the village nerve center.
You understand that, don't you?
- However,
it was actually the opposite.
Itachi was supplying the
village with intelligence
on the Uchiha.
In other words,
he was a double agent.
You can't even imagine what a
heavy burden that was to bear.
-But why?
Why would Itachi
betray the Uchiha?
- You may never
understand his reasons,
because you've never lived
through the horrors of war.
The Third Great Ninja War,
when Itachi was merely
four years old,
he saw many people die.
He should have never
had to experience war
at such a young age.
War is hell.
That trauma turned
him into a pacifist
who hated warfare,
one who had the peace
and stability of
the village foremost
in his mind and actions.
Instead of being bound by
obligation to his clan,
he was a ninja devoted
to his village,
and the village leaders
exploited that trait.
They assigned him to a top
secret mission... an eye
for an eye.
For they'd need the
sharingan to face the Uchiha.
That's right.
The mission was the eradication
of the entire Uchiha clan.
What must Itachi have
gone through emotionally
when he learned
of his assignment?
Itachi was faced with a
terrible choice... the decision
to raise his hand against
his fellow brethren
was probably an
unbelievable struggle.
But if ninja the caliber of
the Uchiha were to revolt,
both the Hidden Leaf
village and the Land of Fire
would be shaken tremendously.
Other nations would take
advantage of the situation
and invade.
It could easily become the
trigger for the Fourth Great
Ninja War.
The Uchiha clan's self-interest
would embroil innocent people,
who had nothing to do
with the Shinobi world,
and countless people
die once again.
If you were Itachi,
what would you have done?
So he made up his mind.
He himself would
drop the curtain
on his own clan's history.
Of course,
he did not hate the Uchiha.
He simply did what he had to.
The discrimination by the
village and the object
of their antagonism...
he shouldered all the
blame himself.
No one should ever
question Itachi's decision
and the sacrifices he made.
To be truthful, back then, I had
also been quietly plotting war.
I held grudges against the
Senju-led Leaf, as well as
the Uchiha, and Itachi
had picked up on that.
He alone knew of my existence.
He sought me out and
made me a proposal.
In exchange for
letting me carry out
my vendetta against
the Uchiha, I
was to leave the village alone.
He would aid me
against the clan.
The third Hokage tried
to resolve the situation
through other means.
He attempted to open
negotiations with the Uchiha
to reach a compromise,
but time ran out,
and his efforts failed.
The night drew near.
He knew his fate.
To become known as a criminal
who murdered his own clan.
To bear the burden of disgrace
and become a rogue ninja.
All of that was
part of the mission.
Itachi completely
fulfilled his duty,
except for one single mistake.
He could not bring himself
to kill his younger brother.
[theme music]
- Afterwards, Itachi
appealed to the third Hokage,
beseeching him to protect you
from Danzo and the councillors.
He fled the village
after threatening Danzo.
If anything were
to happen to you,
Itachi would leak
all the intelligence
he had on the Hidden
Leaf to unallied nations.
He worried about
you above all else,
and yet he could not
tell you the full truth,
so he told you as
much as he could.
-It's a lie!
This just isn't like
you, big brother!
It's not!
- I have acted like
the older brother
you desired for one reason...
because I wanted
to discover how
powerful you were.
I needed to find
a worthy opponent
to test the limits
of my own abilities.
You have that unique potential.
Now I've made you hate me.
Now you have to
desire to defeat me,
which is exactly why I'm
going to allow you to live.
Don't you see?
It's all for my own benefit.
Foolish little brother.
If you wish to kill me one
day, in hate and revenge,
surviving in such an unsightly
manner as this, by all means,
flee.
Cling to your wretched
life, and then, one day,
when you possess the same
eyes, come back and face me.
- He gave you a reason to
seek revenge against him,
and hoped it would
make you stronger.
They wanted you to believe
that the Uchiha was
a proud clan from the
Hidden Leaf village.
He begged the Hokage to
make sure you would never
learn the truth.
And from the moment
he left the village,
he resigned himself to battling
you to the death in order
to bestow upon you new powers.
That is Itachi's truth.
-No.
You're lying.
It's got to be a lie.
It just has to be.
It's all nonsense.
Itachi tried to
kill me many times!
- If Itachi really
wanted to kill you,
you'd most certainly be dead.
- He even used the mangekyo
sharingan against me!
There's no question he
was trying to kill me!
[screaming]
No question.
- Even your
contingency plans were
factored into his calculations.
He had to pressure you
hard during that battle.
Surely you've figured out why?
You understand it
now, don't you?
-And now it finally emerges.
- He wanted to free
you of the curse mark
and the death of the
one closest to you.
It was a battle to awaken
your mangekyo sharingan.
Itachi carefully set up
everything in that battle,
diverting your
attention from the truth
by pretending to the very end
that he was stealing your eyes.
You're starting
to see the truth.
-You're lying.
I know it.
You sent the Nine-tails
to attack the Hidden Leaf!
Itachi told me that
it was all your doing!
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
16 years ago,
when the Nine-tails
attacked the Hidden Leaf
Village, it was Madara's doing.
But like Madara's bid for
power, the Fourth Hokage
stopped that, too.
In short,
Madara is a bitter,
defeated loser.
He is not worthy or
capable of achieving
Uchiha's true greatness.
I am the one.
I shall surpass Madara and
become the ultimate ninja.
- You laid false charges
against the Uchiha
and you teamed up with
Itachi to toy with our clan!
- Itachi was lying
when he told you that.
Just as I've explained.
He was gripped with fear
that you would somehow
discover the truth.
He wanted to make
absolutely certain there
was no chance of that.
He fed you lies to make
sure you wouldn't trust me.
He even implanted
Amaterasu in your eyes.
- There's no way that
I'd ever believe you!
Itachi was pure evil!
He was a criminal who
slaughtered our clan
and became an Akatsuki!
- He took the burden
of all this on himself
and fled his birth village.
Then he joined the
Akatsuki to spy from inside
on the organization that
threatened his village.
He always had the welfare of
the Hidden Leaf in his mind,
just as he always thought
of yours, as well, Sasuke.
Itachi appeared in the
Hidden Leaf Village
after the death of
the Third Hokage, who
had promised to
be your protector.
He wanted to remind
Danzo and the councillors
that he was still alive and
still very much a threat.
He wanted to make sure...
-Stop it!
More lies!
Everything you say is a lie!
You're still alive, aren't you?
- Each of us lives
dependant and bound
by our individual knowledge
and our awareness.
All that is what
we call reality.
However, both knowledge and
awareness are equivocal.
One's reality might
be another's illusion.
We all live inside
our own fantasies.
Don't you think that's
true, Sasuke?
How much can you
see when you look
with those sharingan
eyes of yours?
- My eyes are not the
same as they once were.
My sharingan can see
through genjutsu.
- You speak with such
confidence, as you always do.
Well, for now, I'm willing
to take your word for it.
- Those eyes of yours did
not perceive a single truth
about Itachi.
You weren't able to pierce
through any of the illusions
he created.
Itachi killed his friends,
his superiors, his lover,
his father, his
mother, but he couldn't
kill his little brother.
He killed every shred
of feeling in his heart
in order to
slaughter his own kin
for the sake of his village.
But he just couldn't
bring himself to kill you.
Do you understand
what that means?
To him, your life was even
more precious than the village.
Until the moment of his death...
no, even after he died,
it was all for you,
to confer on you new powers.
By allowing you to defeat him,
he had avenged the Uchiha clan.
He made you the hero of
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Ravaged by illness, painfully
aware of his impending death,
he forcefully prolonged his
life with medication, all
for the sake of his
beloved little brother.
Because he had to fight you
and die in your presence.
For the peace of the
Hidden Leaf Village,
and most of all for
you, Sasuke Uchiha,
he wanted to die being known
as a criminal, and a traitor.
He accepted disgrace
in the place of honor,
and hatred in the place of love.
And yet, Itachi still died
with a smile on his face.
He bequeathed to
you the Uchiha name,
still fooling you
to the very end.
ITACHI: I'm home!
-Welcome home, Itachi!
Hey come on,
let's go outside play together.
So what do you think we
should go play first?
-Stop that, Sasuke.
Your brother has academy
homework to do first.
You could play after
he's finished doing that.
SASUKE: But Mom!
- It's OK,
I can do my homework later.
Besides, it's easy.
-Oh, goodness.
SASUKE (THINKING): I wonder
where he could be hiding.
-Ha!
I found you, big brother!
-You're pretty sharp, Sasuke.
But too bad!
-Aww!
That's so not fair!
Hey Dad?
-Huh?
- Itachi and I were out
playing hide and seek today,
but then he used a clone jutsu
to trick me and run away.
And that's cheating, isn't it?
- Oh, you've mastered
using the clone jutsu?
- Hey wait, you could
teach me the clone jutsu
after we finish dinner, OK?
-Homework, boys.
-Sorry about that, Sasuke.
But we'll do it some other time.
No Sasuke, it's time to go.
- What happened to
the new shuriken jutsu
you promised to teach me, huh?
ITACHI: It'll have to wait.
I have an important
mission tomorrow.
I must prepare.
SASUKE: You're such
a big fat liar.
-Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
SASUKE: OK, Just watch this.
-Hey!
Be careful!
[grunt]
-Itachi?
That was fun.
Will you train with
me again sometime?
-Sure.
But I'm going to be
assigned missions soon,
and starting tomorrow, you'll
be attending the Ninja Academy.
So, we aren't going to have
as much free time to ourselves
anymore.
- That's OK,
as long as you can still
spend time with
me once in awhile.
-We're flesh and blood.
I'll always be there for you.
Even if it's just as an
obstacle for you to overcome.
-Big brother?
Listen.
Can you please help me with
my shuriken training today?
-I can't, I'm too busy.
Why don't you ask
father to teach you?
- But you're better
than he is when
it comes to shuriken jutsu.
Even a kid can see that.
Hey!
-Sorry, Sasuke.
Some other time, OK?
Even if it's just as an
obstacle for you to overcome.
Sasuke,
I'll always be there for you.
Even if you do hate me.
That's what big
brothers are for.
-Forgive me, Sasuke.
But this is it.
-We are no longer the Hebi.
From this day on,
our team will be the Taka.
And Taka has but one goal.
Our mission
is to destroy the Hidden Leaf.
[theme music]
KILLER B: Oh my eyes,
light too bright.
Is it noon already?
Dammit, man, no fool, you fool.
Training for more and
my belly is starving.
Rap loving guy,
I got me a hunch that I just
decided on sukiyaki for lunch!
Yeah.
-Sure looks like that's the guy.
Next time,
on Naruto Shippuden...
Battle of Unraikyo.
Eight-tails,
I'm here to capture you.