Huh.
Hey, is that?
All right, which one of these
guys is really a fake?
Huh?
[Scream]
Why you!
[Grunting]
Hmph!
What are you doing? Don't just
recklessly jump in front of him
like that!
Huh! Wait where have I seen
that guy before?
[Screams]
No way! He's a samurai, but he's
got ninja skills?!
Get back! Create a buffer
between you and him!
What is going on here?!
And where's the Sealing
Corps, anyway?!
[Groan] They got separated from
the main company because of
those fakes. We're waiting on
reinforcements.
Hey, wait! Who the hell are you!
What? What do you mean,
who am I?
You totally beat me up a while
back! You don't forget something
like that!
Did you forget what
you did to me?!
Are you saying you're Naruto?
Yeah!
You've changed so much I
didn't even recognize you!
Anyway, who is he?
Oh, he's a reanimated samurai.
And he's super strong.
Samurai?
[Grunts]
Huh!
Get back, shinobi!
I bear no grudge against you
whatsoever!
But my body's being controlled.
So at the moment, I have no say
in my own actions.
And furthermore, I'm not
actually a true samurai. I
abandoned the Land of Iron ages
ago...
I'm a displaced samurai, a
ronin. No, not quite. I...
Old man. Don't tell me you're
Old Man Tatewaki?!
Hmm?
Tatewaki...Yes, that's indeed my
name, and who might you be?
You really know this guy,
Naruto?
Naruto? You said, "Naruto"?
That's right! It's me, Naruto!
So you're still alive, are you?
But please tell me, what
happened to those two? Are they
all right? Did they survive?
This mission is a direct request
from the Feudal Lord of the Land
of Fire!
That means this assignment comes
from our nation's highest ruler.
Don't forget that!
This is gonna be such a drag.
Come on, don't
say that.
Are we gonna have time to eat
before we go?
Is food really the only thing
you ever talk about?!
What if it is? What the heck are
you even doing here with us
anyway?
For this mission, Naruto will be
joining Shikamaru's team.
Huh?
He is? All right, I guess. But
what exactly is this mission
that we're supposed to be going
on with him?
Well, to put it bluntly, it's a
kidnapping.
[All] What?!
A young lord is being held
hostage in a castle in this
small nation.
Your mission will be to kidnap
the young lord back from his
abductors without being
discovered.
So we sneak the guy out of
there, and then what? Are we
gonna demand a big ransom?
Get real, would you? This is a
political situation.
His homeland has a treaty with
the nation that kidnapped him.
But his land wants to break the
treaty and ally with the Land of
Fire.
And so, the mission is to
retrieve the young lord and take
him home...
...so his abductors don't have
leverage over his homeland.
All right, Granny, what rank is
this mission gonna be?
Normally, a B-rank mission.
But depending on how fortified
the castle is, it may become
A-rank.
Yeah, all right! Now you're
talking! That makes this whole
thing worthwhile!
Come on! We don't concern
ourselves with that stuff!
Well, I warned them.
They know that there's been
suspicious activity surrounding
that nation lately.
And it has something to do with
the fact that his nation wants
to cancel the treaty, correct?
If this mission goes awry, it'll
become an A or S-rank quickly.
As an ANBU, you are to stay in
the shadows and watch their
backs to make sure that doesn't
happen.
Under what circumstances
should I reveal myself?
I want you to gather intel on
any other suspicious activity,
as well.
I'll leave it up to your
judgement.
Understood.
"The A-Rank Mission: Food
Fight!"
You know, Sasori my man...
The missions we've been
getting lately have been so
excruciatingly trivial.
That's because we've been
accepting every little request
that comes our way.
Pedestrian, mercenary jobs
only for money!
They don't have one single iota
of art to them at all! Hmph!
I agree completely, but
unfortunately we have no choice
but to listen to the
organization.
Lately world conquest seems like
it's a long way off...
Hey!
Hmm?
Well look who's late!
We've received two new missions.
One of them is for profit, and
the other is war.
Simply making money
doesn't interest me.
Me either.
Then we'll take
the job for profit.
Hey! You don't get to decide
all on your own!
Ahh, I'm not interested in money
either you know.
Well someone has to do it! And
Sasori and Deidara both prefer
war. Let's not bicker
unnecessarily about this.
Yeah fine! But you guys
all owe me one!
So, who are we fighting
in this war?
It's one nation, and a
small one at that.
And what's so special
about this nation?
The political standing of a
small nation changes often.
In any event, this request comes
from a large nation that wants
its territory.
How interesting.
So that's the castle we
need to get into?
Yeah, and kidnap
the young lord.
The real problem is keeping
anyone from knowing that we did
it.
Wait, let me guess what the plan
is! We'll use Shikamaru's Shadow
Possession or Ino's Mind
Transfer Jutsu, right?
All wrong. You and Choji are
gonna be the key players in this
mission.
We are?
What?
Yeah. Choji, you'll enter a
contest that the lord will
attend.
Normally, only authorized
personnel can enter the
castle...
...but participants in this
contest will be allowed in.
So it's gonna be
something like...
[Nervous Noises]
[Screams]
Are you serious?! Why's it have
to be me?
You sure about this? Choji'll
lose right away!
Nope. Because the contest that
he's entering is actually a food
fight.
It is? It's really a food fight?
This should make you happy.
Simply put, Choji, it's a
competitive eating contest.
Seriously?! You mean it?!
Wow, Shikamaru! Entering an
eating contest as a mission is
like a dream come true!
So what am I supposed to be
doing on this mission then?
Well, while Choji's creating a
diversion in the contest, you'll
sneak into the castle.
And you'll use Transformation
Jutsu...
...to switch places with the
young lord and buy us time while
we make our escape with the real
one.
You're okay with Naruto
impersonating this guy?
What's that supposed
to mean?!
Exactly what I said!
She's right, though. He's
supposed to be some kind of
royalty.
So if he does something like
ordering ramen for lunch, his
cover will be blown right away!
[Grunts] Come on, you guys! Give
me a break!
You're really gonna have to
watch how you speak, you know!
Enough, already! You don't have
to tell me how to do this!
Well, I guess we'll see.
[Naruto Groans]
All contestants, step forward!
You're up, Choji!
Yeah!
Every year, in hopes of
prosperity and an abundance of
crops for our nation, we hold
this contest. So let's begin!
The winner will be honored by
our Feudal Lord and shall
receive a most generous reward.
So, everyone, do your best and
partake of the foods with
dignity and with grace.
Well, the preliminaries should
be a breeze for Choji.
But I still don't get why
you picked Naruto.
Because one of these events
features ramen.
But in the other ones he's no
better than anyone else!
Yeah, well...
Now, contestants, in this first
event you'll be eating bean jam
cakes!
What?! You mean it's not ramen?!
The famous Ama-ama An in castle
town has made these bean cakes!
On your mark, ready, now eat
your fill!
[Munching]
[Sigh]
You see I told you Naruto
couldn't cut it.
Hmm? Ino, over there!
Hmm?
Are those the ones?
Yeah.
The one on the right is the
young lord we're after.
But forget that now,
look at him!
Huh?
You mean that big guy?
This nation hires former samurai
as guards. And he's their
captain.
If I'm right, he's the biggest
threat to the success of this
mission, by far.
Huh?
And that's time!
[Groaning]
Hey, are you doing
okay, Naruto?
Honestly, I don't
really know.
Any contestants who were unable
to finish must withdraw!
[Groaning]
I made the finals, but barely.
Now we'll continue with the
second round!
What?! A second round?!
And the second round will be...
A ramen-eating contest!
What?! Ramen? After eating all
of that?!
[Gasps]
This is ramen from the famous
castle town shop, Gido Gido Tei.
No way! This portion's huge!
Get ready, and begin now!
[Slurping]
[Gulps] Tasty, but oh man!
Gido Gido's fatty broth
is so rich!
[Slurping]
It's delicious, but the noodles
they use are so thick, and right
now I don't have the room!
Wow, this roast pork is just
amazing! The meat is so tender
and juicy!
I can't do it! Even though it
tastes so incredible!
I can't! I can't take another
bite.
I mean, I, I want too...
But, if I eat any more of this,
I'm gonna be in real trouble!
But still, I want to eat it!
Everyone's doing well, huh.
Father, watching them eat has
made me start to feel hungry,
too.
Well, why not have some of those
bean jam cakes from earlier?
You!
Are you hungry?
I'd really like to try some of
that ramen. It looks incredible!
No, you don't want the ramen.
What? Why not?
By now it's lukewarm and the
noodles are soft.
The taster always checks the
Lord's food for poison, and by
the time he's done, the noodles
have gone limp.
Mhmm. Bean jam cakes are
good. They stay the same.
Oh, is that so? Boy,
that's too bad.
Now, Lord Shu, it's
time for your lesson.
Huh?! But there's a contest
going on today!
Sorry, that doesn't matter.
Come, let's go.
All right...
[Laughing]
These contestants are amazing!
Just thirty seconds left!
[Slurping]
It looks like Choji is sussing
out his rivals.
Five seconds left!
Four...Three...Two...One...Zero!
Stop eating!
The final round will be
held at sunset!
Only those who've finished the
bowls in front of them will be
allowed back in the castle.
Right!
Oh, man...Hey Choji.
Do your best, okay?
Just leave it to me.
Okay, the groundwork is laid.
How about you and I go get some
lunch.
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screams]
[Grunting]
Guard your side!
[Grunts]
You must always keep moving!
Good! Keep your eyes on your
opponent.
Don't retreat! It
shows weakness!
[Grunting]
[Heavy Breathing]
Pick it up.
I can't move anymore.
You're not done.
What's the point of all
this training, anyway?!
I mean, I'm only a hostage. All
that I really have to do is
behave, right.
For now, that's true. But
Fate is unpredictable.
Not mine.
It isn't gonna change...
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Tatewaki!
It seems you can move.
[Light Breathing]
Your training is far too harsh!
That's all for today.
Sorry, Shu. Are
you all right?
I don't think that Tatewaki
likes me very much.
I'm sure that he's just being
dutiful. I mean, he is a
samurai.
Not quite. Former samurai.
Congratulations, all you
finalists!
I commend you on
reaching this stage!
There's no need to be reserved
now! Eat your fill!
[All]
Yes, sir!
Yeah! You can win
this thing, Choji!
He can't.
What? Why not?
He should be second. That's
our strategy for the young
lord's rescue.
Ohh!
I see...
We've reached the finals! And
the first event will be a
speed eating contest!
You have to eat one hundred
pieces of sushi!
The three top contestants will
advance to the next contest.
The renowned Neta Neta
Sushi in the castle town
prepared these!
Eat wisely! Ready, set, and go!
[Thud]
[Munching]
Let's do this, Naruto.
Right!
Ino...
Yep, I'm on it!
Ninja Art...
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Oh wow!
Uh.
Huh?
What's the matter?
I'm going to the washroom.
Oh my! What a fine group
we have this year!
[Munching]
Ohh, so you're the lord
we're after huh?
Make it snappy!
Transformation Jutsu!
Okay, I'm outta here!
Huh.
Lord Shu! I have a missive here
that was sent to you from your
father.
And you are?
A shinobi sent at the request of
your homeland.
[Munching]
Mmm!
What an appetite!
Her too!
Huh?
Choji! You're still eating?!
Hmm?
[Munching]
Clean your plates!
That's it! Stop eating!
We'll take a short break, and
then the top three will go on to
the final event.
Wow! Man, that was good!
Choji you've got me worried! Do
you really know what you're
supposed to be doing?
[Sigh] Sushi is wonderful, too.
It's not soft.
Ah, Lord Shu, some sushi?
Nah, I, I mean, no thank you. My
appetite has left me.
Oh, that's so unfortunate.
Is anything the matter?
[Gasp] It's nothing. I'm just
shocked by how much they can all
put down.
And now, the final event will be
barbecued meat!
Barbecue?!
The renowned castle town shop,
Kemu Kemu-en, supplied this
food!
Eat with care! Now, begin!
Hey, is it working?
Yeah, for now it seems to be.
If it's barbecue this'll
be easy for Choji.
Well actually, I don't
know about that.
Huh?
[Munching]
Aww, this is just amazing!
Well, all right then!
I'll use Two-Handed Style!
Incredible! She's eating
with both hands!
Oh ho! Look at that! She's using
a special technique!
Oh yeah? Well watch this!
Lethal Juggler!
Whoa! He's using two
hands, as well!
No, he's using his left hand to
put the meat on the grill, and
using his right hand to eat the
meat that he's cooking!
Going ambidextrous means he's
wasting no time at all!
But...
I can't even see his chopsticks!
[Chewing Loudly]
So fast!
If he keeps going like this,
Choji's gonna win!
[Grunts] He needs to come in
second for this plan to work.
This is it...
This is the last one!
The last...
[Gasp]
The last bite!
[Gasps] I can't move!
[Groans]
It's over!
Shadow Possession Jutsu,
complete!
[Sighs]
You can stop eating!
We've found a winner for this
year's eating contest, and he is
named Isono!
Yeah!
[Sigh]
That was close!
You all did an excellent job!
Very commendable.
But I lost.
It couldn't be helped.
You did well. You just
slowed down at the end.
Now, to hand out the prizes!
First, the winner, Isono, is
awarded the grand prize of a
brand new house!
Thank you sir!
Choji, who took second place, is
awarded a large wicker basket.
Thank you.
Lastly, Tamao, in third place,
is awarded a small wicker
basket.
Thank you.
With the prizes given out, I
hereby declare this year's
contest over!
That was so much fun!
Don't you think?
Uh, yeah.
[Stomach Growls]
Except now I'm so hungry!
What a puny little nation! How
about I just take care of this
whole thing quickly with my art?
Deidara, your part
in this ends  here.
What's that?!
I'll handle the rest.
That's not fair!
Our objective is not to
destroy this nation, but
to take it over!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Fallen Castle."
You can just sit back, relax,
and enjoy the show.