NARUTO: Give Sasuke back.
Give him back!
Argh!
Don't you talk about
Sasuke like you own him!
Especially in front of
me, you rotten bastard!
[theme music]
-How interesting.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Chakra.
He did all that with
just his chakra.
-Sakura!
SAI (VOICEOVER): That
chakra is powerful.
It's almost like it's
acting on its own.
This is the perfect opportunity.
Time for my real
mission to begin.
YAMATO: Sakura!
Can you hear me?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): She must've
hit her head when she fell.
Of all the times
to get knocked out.
-Wood Style Jutsu!
I can't hold it!
-Ninja Art.
Super Beast Scroll.
-Sai!
Sai!
Get her!
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Of all the--
-Is that all you've got then?
Even with the power
of a Jinchuriki,
that's the best you can do?
You're no Sasuke.
You're not even in
the same league.
-What is this place?
Where am I?
[growling]
Sasuke.
Sasuke!
Wait!
Wait up!
Sasuke!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Damn it!
[heartbeat]
I don't-- I don't have the
power to bring Sasuke back.
[heartbeat]
If only-- If only I'd
been stronger back then.
-Sasuke!
I'm not letting
Orochimaru take you away!
Do you understand me?
I'll break every single
bone in your body
if that's what it
takes to stop you!
You're not going anywhere!
-You're still not gonna be able
to lay even a single scratch
on my forehead.
I know that hasn't
changed at least.
You're not leaving me a
lot of choice here, Naruto.
There's no question
that you're special.
Unfortunately, you're not
quite as special as I am.
Chidori.
-Rasengan!
-Chidori!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I'm too weak.
There's nothing I could ever
say that would reach him.
He'll never acknowledge
me the way I am now.
[heartbeat]
That's why I gotta do whatever
it takes to become stronger.
[heartbeats]
I can't let our friendship
have been for nothing.
[heartbeats]
I won't let you break
that bond, Sasuke.
I won't allow it!
-Well, what do you know?
Something about this
feels different.
-Sakura.
Wake up.
Hey.
Sakura.
Are you all right?
-Yeah.
I'm fine.
-Sure?
-Sorry.
I think I'm OK now.
What happened here?
-It was Naruto.
-It's no wonder
they're after him.
The power of the
Jinchuriki's no joke.
-Where is he?
-He's on the other side already.
He went running off
after Orochimaru.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Naruto
will be the tricky one here.
-What's the smoke?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): I have
a bad feeling about this.
-Wood Clone Jutsu.
I'm counting on you.
Don't worry.
Wood Style.
Domed Wall Jutsu.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-The things this boy can do.
I must admit, he's
piqued my interest.
-Damn it.
[theme music]
YAMATO: The force
of that shockwave.
From just a single
blow of his hand.
It's incredible.
SAKURA: Is that-- Is that
the power of the Nine Tails?
YAMATO: That's right.
SAKURA: Captain Yamato.
There's something you're
not telling me about Naruto,
isn't there?
YAMATO: Sakura.
SAKURA: Please.
What's going to happen to him?
YAMATO: Don't worry.
Naruto is going to be fine.
It was exactly
for this situation
that I was chosen
to lead this team.
SAKURA: Next time,
Orochimaru Versus Jinchuriki.
[theme music]
NARUTO: The Hidden
Leaf Fitness Jam.
Get ready for a taste of some
down home shinobi training.
For step one, we'll move right
into some strength building!
-Uh, if you wanna
be a great shinobi,
then physical strength is key,
and no two training regimens
are alike.
There are thumb stand push ups,
rock climbing, or doing laps
around the village
on your hands.
Ugh.
I'm sweating just
watching all this.
And then there's step two!
Tree climbing.
-Gather all your chakra
at the soles of your feet
and maintain it.
Step three!
SAKURA: Try to keep your
balance while you release
a steady stream of
chakra over some water.
Get it wrong, spa-loosh!
Sometimes I wonder how
we ever survived it all.
But like they always
say, no pain, no gain.
Right?
So listen all you folks at home.
-Yeah!
With hard work, even
you can be Hokage.
-It's dangerous stuff!
So don't even think about
trying this at home, kids.