YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
The third tail.
[theme song]
-Sora.
No!
Soray!
-Naruto, no!
Be careful!
-Naruto, don't!
Naruto!
-That idiot!
-Is he OK?
-That's Sora.
He's in there.
It might not seem like him,
but the real Sora is there.
He's just gotta be!
-From the sound of things,
Sora has finally transformed.
Nobody can stop that boy now.
-Kazuma.
You fool.
-Wood style jutsu!
Such destructive power.
-Sora, that's enough!
-Shadow strangle jutsu!
I knew it wouldn't work.
-Let me try!
-Choji!
-Don't worry.
I can heal him.
-Darn it.
For crying out loud,
snap out of it!
-Kazuma.
Why on Earth did you do this?
You're his father.
So why?
The Nine-Tails-- you
put it inside him
to turn your son into a weapon?
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
-Of course I do.
And I'd do it again
if I had the chance.
It's all for the cause.
-I've heard enough!
-Let me give it a try!
Hiya!
-That jerk.
Fang over fang!
Dammit.
-You're mad.
What cause are
you talking about?
-A very worthy one.
To make sure the Land
of Fire stays as it is.
And I'll do anything for
the sake of that cause
-Then what about your child?
Mizura died for it as well?
-When you were young, growing up
as the son of the Third Hokage,
wasn't your cause
the same as his?
-That's not--
-I am protecting my king,
just as you have sworn to do.
How dare you question that?
-It's true.
I have indeed sworn
to protect my leader.
But that's not the kind of
king you've got in mind.
-There you go.
We're both the same, you and me.
You see, it doesn't
matter who your king is.
When all is said
and done we're just
pawns who only exist to
shield them from harm.
But a pawn is too weak
to protect a king.
Which is why I made
Sora what he is.
A pawn deep enough
in enemy ground
to be promoted to a
more powerful piece.
-You just don't get it.
Children aren't pawns
to protect the king.
-I don't care.
We're all merely pieces.
All we can do is try and
take out the other's king.
It doesn't matter how it's done.
Even if the game was
reversed, I would still win.
-Wood style jutsu!
-Dammit.
-No!
-Why?
He's an outsider.
-No he's no.
He's Team Kakashi.
He's a comrade now!
-You and me are the same.
Sora.
Hey, Sora, remember?
We thrashed around
like this then
and tried to stop each other.
I guess we were
pretty dumb, huh?
That's just the way we are.
-Did he get him?
-Naruto.
-Sora!
Sora.
Come back to us.
I know you're still in there!
Sora!
Sora.
-Don't do this!
-Get away from Sora, now!
Naruto!
-Sora!
Come on.
Snap out of it.
You gotta try.
Listen to me!
Sora.
What is this?
-What's happening?
-What-- what the
heck is going on?
Did it-- did my Nine-Tails
awaken on its own?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Now.
-Hokage style, elder jutsu.
Tenth edict on enlightenment!
What's happening here?
It's never like this.
It's coming from the outside.
-Naruto.
-No.
Not now.
I can't let it come out.
Why?
Why now?
-Fate sure has a funny way
of causing coincidences,
doesn't it?
Fuka pointed it out.
-Furido.
About that kid I fought
against back there
with the pointy hair.
I wonder-- he and
Sora seemed alive.
-She thought Sora an the
boy might be connected.
The chakra is the same
in both Nine-Tails.
So of course Sora's
rage is resonating
with the original
nine-tailed fox.
-What?
-It's perfect.
Isn't this so interesting?
We'll get to see the
true jinchuriki-- no,
the nine-tailed fox spirit--
set loose to once again destroy
the Leaf Village.
[laughter]
-No!
[ominous laughter]
Dammit!
You don't want to do this.
Come on.
Stop it, Sora.
Sora!
No-- it can't--
What is that?
-This does not look good.
-Guys, run!
-Naruto!
-Sakura-- come on.
Sora, for the last time.
Wake up!
-That's my boy, Sora!
Smash the Leaf where it stands!
-No way.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sora--
-Naruto!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Can't let it happen.
I'm not gonna let that
nine-tailed monster take over
so easily.
-What the--
-Nice work.
Keep it up, Sora!
-I-- I didn't call on you.
So get lost, you dumb fox.
You think you can
just show up like this
whenever you feel like it?
Beat it!
-Captain Yamato,
can't you do anyhing?
-No.
My jutsu won't work
on Naruto like this.
We have to just
hope his willpower
is enough to hold it back.
-Oh no.
-No.
Darn it.
-Go ahead.
Leave it to me, boy.
-I'm not letting you out.
I won't back down!
No monster fox is
gonna take over me!
-Naruto.
-What did he--
-This is bad.
-That's right.
I made a vow.
I will not be overtaken by you.
That-- that's a promise.
I won't succumb.
I can't do the things
I warned Sora against!
[laughter]
-Why hesitate?
Just say what you're dying to.
I'm in your power.
Say it.
-Why don't you shut up?
Don't worry, Sora.
I'll bring you back
with my own hands.
You hear?
-Naruto?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sora.
SORA (VOICEOVER): Who's that?
-Come on!
Sora!
Come back!
I know you can hear me, Sora!
Get out of there!
Are you gonna stay
asleep forever?
Well, I won't let you.
Wake up!
Sora!
SORA (VOICEOVER): Who's there?
Who is that person?
What-- it's me.
As a boy.
When I was little I
was always crying.
I was always so alone.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sora--
-Who's that?
Whose voice is that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sora--
-I knew it.
It's just as I expected.
Nothing's changed.
I'm still alone.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sora--
-Fight it, Sora.
Hang in there.
I'm gonna save you.
Come on, Sora.
Hang on!
-Whose voice is that?
[music playing]
-Sakura.
My medical ninjutsu isn't strong
enough to heal Choji's wound.
-I was worried about that.
It's just like when
Sakura was hurt.
-Wounds from the Nine-Tails
chakra take longer to heal.
-What?
-Even after proper
treatment the patient
might experience
long-lasting pain.
-So what then?
Does this mean Naruto's the
only one who can control him?
-Unfortunately that would
seem to be the case.
-No way.
-All we can do is
have faith in Naruto.
-Next time-- My Friend.