(Killer Bee)
Hey, Nine Tails kid,
Thanks for trying to
rescue Motoi back there.
Sure!
[pleased chuckle]
Naruto has got a
mysterious something
that draws people
to him...
Master Bee has
that as well.
I totally agree
with you. Yes.
I think I need to
reconsider you, mate!
You're actually quite a
good guy, real top-rate!
Octopops, ya got the
very best rap! I'm
happy to know ya,
I'm one lucky chap!
Fool! Ya fool!
(Thinking)
It's great that Naruto
and Bee have found
such common ground...
...But no offense,
I hope Naruto doesn't
pick up  his rapping.
Yo! Meet my
beat, son!
Huh?
You don't know a
damn thing about
Master Bee!
Now I suggest you shut
your mouth before you
say something you'll
regret!
(Naruto)
Motoi puts great
trust in Octopops...
You know, I don't
remember that
happening...
(Naruto)
And in turn, Octopops
trusts Motoi, too.
Yo! I'm Naruto!
Ya know? Ya know!?
[chuckle]
[Thinking]
There, I did it!
Man, it's "Ya
know, ya know,"
all the time...
So shut up!
Ya know!?
[small chuckle]
Go back to the Waterfall
of Truth, and you'll
pass with flying colors
this time around!
Heh!
Haven't learned your
lesson yet, huh? Try
all you want, it'll
still be the same...
(Dark Naruto)
You can't defeat me.
Yeah. Trying to
defeat you with force
isn't gonna work, I
get that now...
Because the two of
us have all the
exact same moves.
And you can't chase
me out, either.
I know you better
than anyone else
could ever know you.
Then you must
already know!
I already know
what?
What I decided
earlier.
What are you
talking about
now?
Don't act like
you don't know.
Alright, fine!
This place is supposed
to reveal the truth in
your heart, right?
Just let me
concentrate, then.
And I'm gonna show
it to you right now!
Huh!?
(Naruto)
Number one candidate
for Hokage: Naruto!
What you see here
is my autograph!
You bastard!
Oh! That's right!
Can I get your
autograph!?
And if you don't mind,
could you make it out
to my kid, please? He's
a real big fan!
Autograph?
You're the hero of
the Hidden Leaf!
Naruto! The kid
who makes miracles!
Can I please have
your autograph, too!?
No, it's not that!
I'm just not used to
the celebrity thing!
I've never given an
autograph before!
I didn't have an
autograph to give
them at Ichiraku,
but I have one now.
[annoyed scoff] So
what that you've come
up with some autograph?
What a joke!
Everyone in the Village
is just falling over
themselves to deceive
you!
(Dark Naruto)
They've been lying to
us since we were kids!
Inventing stupid rules!
And making us outcasts!
Don't you remember
that!?
It was always so
hard... and so
painful, too.
I'm the only one
who will ever
understand you!
You can't trust
any of those
villagers!
Maybe...
The villagers are
important... but there's
someone else that I have
to trust more first...
[gasp]
What I need to
do right now is
believe in myself!
I need to trust the
me that all those
villagers believe in.
[sobbing]
Why? Why!? After
all they put us
through...?
[sobbing]
I realized it
while watching
Octopops.
He doesn't let
himself get pulled
down by doubt...
..and he has
pride in himself!
Do you think that
I'm just something
in your way?!
What exactly was
I to you, huh!?
I became strong
because you existed.
It's thanks to you
that I got where I
am today.
And..? What now,
huh!? What am I
supposed to do
from now on!?
That's easy
to answer.
Huh!?
You just need
to become me.
You are me,
after all.
[gasp]
Thank you for
everything you've
done. But it's
all right now.
[gasps]
[pleased chuckle]
It looks like...
It went well,
I take it?
It's too early to
celebrate, ya hear
me? Fools, ya fools!
Whattya say? Should
we try controlling
the Nine Tails power?
From this moment, I'm
gonna be your instructor!
So prepare yourself to
suffer death or torture!
Yeah! Bring
it on!
Follow me, Naruto,
ya know?
Um, may I come
along with you
guys, too?
Okay!
Well, Motoi?
I have to make
periodic reports to
the Hidden Cloud so,
I must leave you.
Thanks for all
your help.
From now on, things
probably won't get
any easier.
There's something
behind the waterfall?
Huh!?
Woaaaah!
You'll be fighting
the Nine Tails here.
Uhhh, I'm gonna
fight the Nine
Tails!?
That's right!
Ya feel me?
Fool, ya fool!
Yeah.
[grunt]
Wow! This is
incredible!
Come on!
These ruins seem
to be quite old...
I bet they have
archeological
importance, too.
They should be
restored.
[Bee]
No. All of these statues
were carved without
heads to begin with.
[Bee]
There's a reason
for it....
Hm?
But listen, how am
I ever supposed to
fight the Nine
Tails here?
I mean, really,
how do I even go
about facing him
in the first place?
I hope you're
not going to do
anything excessive.
You think you can
control a Tailed Beast
without being excessive?
Fool! Ya fool!
This is a sacred place where
those selected as Jinchuriki
have long come to undergo
purification ceremonies.
It's set up here so
that you can talk to
your Tailed Beast in
a special way.
Inside there...?
[Bee]
Only those who have been
chosen may enter this place.
Put your head in this space.
If you're a good
man, respected, no
darkness in your
heart detected--
--the door will
open, you won't
be rejected.
Uh, look. Could
you please explain
all this a little
more normally.
I don't
understand it.
No darkness in your
heart. That means...
I see... That's why
at the waterfall...
However, if there's
any darkness in your
heart, then the
doors will not part.
You consent?
And the statue will
bite off your head
and tear you apart,
...you content?
[Bee]
Those headless statues
you saw on your way here-
[Bee]
...are past
Jinchuriki who's
hearts weren't sincere!
I'm the truth that
you're supposed to
face. I'm the real
you, your true self.
[gulp]
This is too
risky...
Naruto, just use
a shadow clone!
Yo! Check yourself!
This is a sacred
place, fool! Ya fool!
And many generations
of Hidden Cloud
ancestors watch over it.
Tricks like that
won't work.
But still--!
Captain Yamato...
The entire reason that
I came here is to learn
how to control the power
of the Nine Tails!
I have to do this!
I can't run away
from it!
It's important!
[thinking]
I just have to
believe in myself.
[nervous breaths]
[screaming]
Naruto..!
[horrified gasp]
This can't...
How could this
happen!? Naruto...
(Yamato)
Are you...?
Only kidding!
There was just
a switch inside
the statue!
Huh!?!
Heh heh heh!
Sorry! Couldn't
help myself!
What's funny is I did
the same thing, too!
Those statues are just
there to scare you!
I thought you told
us this place was
sacred! What was that!?
Fools! Ya fools!!
So, is this...
You need to go in
there, sit down,
close your eyes,
and focus...
Just like at the
waterfall. Then
you'll meet up with
your Tailed Beast.
You know, a while
ago, back when I
was in training...
...I was taught a
drill that allowed me
to meet the Nine Tails
inside of my  mind.
Yeah, sure. All
Jinchuriki can do
that!
But this situation is
a little different, ok!?
[Bee]
Listen closely,
and I'll give you
an explanation...
Naruto, what kind of
Sealing Jutsu was used
on your Nine Tails?
Answer my question.
Umm...
It's a Tetragram
Seal.
Tetragram Seal, huh?
I gotta say, that's
impressive.
It's even more solid
than my Steel Shell Seal.
[Bee]
You got the key?
[gasp]
Alright! But only
because you say so,
Great Lord Elder!
[gasp] What is this?
A key left by the
Fourth Hokage to lock
and unlock the Sealing
Jutsu on your belly!
Yeah.
So you'll really have
to undo the seal...
But what if Naruto isn't
able to control it?! What
happens if the Nine Tails
fully manifests!?
Then we'll just have
to seal him away in
here!
[Bee]
That's what this
place is for.
We'd trap Nine Tails
here in this outpost
until we were able
to get a new host.
Got a problem?!
No boo-hoo-in'!
But we'll still--
(Naruto)
That won't happen.
Trust me. I'm
going to do this.
Okay. Then I'm
gonna shut the
door, ya know?
And I'll tell
you how to
deal with the
Nine Tails.
[Bee]
Naruto, you really
impress me. Now the
rules are simple, see?
[Bee]
Once you greet the
Nine Tails inside your
mind, undo the seal.
Hey, Nine Tails.
Evil glare as
usual, huh?
Naruto... What
are you up to?
So, what's up?
Where'd the
real you go?
I don't sense
him anymore.
The real me?
I'm right here.
Right in front
of you.
[Bee]
You may have conquered
your hatred, but don't
let your guard be hazy-
[Bee]
The Nine Tails is a
lump of loathing, and
don't forget, he's crazy.
What are you
plotting!?
Can't you see my
mouth is full? I
can't talk now.
Here goes!
[roaring]
[Bee]
When the Nine Tails emerges,
grab his chakra with your
own chakra and pull hard!
Chakra can only be
captured with Chakra.
It's common sense, son.
Take the Nine Tails'
chakra away from him
and you'll be number
one.
Huh?
[angry struggling roar]
[Bee]
Touch the Nine Tails
directly, and stick your
chakra onto it's chakra.
[Bee]
Only then can you
pull on it.
[growl]
[Bee]
In other words,
it's going to be
a tug-of-war, ok!?
[angry roar]
Damn it!
[Bee]
I'd really like to
help you in your fight
but unfortunately-
--while we're stuck
in your head, I got
no might!
The Nine Tails
is really strong.
One Warning: there's a
chance your chakra might
get pulled from you when
you try to take his...
..and you know what
happens when all off your
chakra is taken from you
and drops to zero, right?
Oh I see, you're
hoping to gain control
over my power, are you?
You teamed up with the
Eight Tails? You? The
Jinchuriki of Nine Tails?
How pitiful!
[determined grunt]
[Bee]
The risks are high for sure,
but if you can get it in, the
Nine Tails Chakra will be yours!
[Bee]
Just get as much of the  Nine
Tails' chakra as possible!
That'll be your payoff!
[Bee]
Don't get caught up
in his hate! Use
your strong will!
[Bee]
That's how you can
ward him off!
[angry growl]
[struggling gasp]
don't mock me!
[thinking]
Thanks, Octopops.
I contained the
explosion! But I can
give no more cooperation
to your operation.
[thinking]
Got it. Like I thought,
I'm sitting still, so I
can use Sage Mode.
Sage art!
Massive Rasengan!!!
[attack shout]
(Naruto)
Damn it! The Nine
Tails is no joke!
(Ghost Voices)
-I hate you!
-I just wanna kill you!
-I'll get my revenge!
(Naruto)
What?
(Bee)
Don't give
in, Naruto. Fool!
Ya fool!
(Ghost Voices)
-You'll never have the
respect you desire!
-Get out! Get lost!
(Naruto)
What is this?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Orange
Spark.
(Naruto)
Who... are you?