[screaming]
‐Hey, hey, hey!
Deidara, look at that.
A dumpling shop!
Let's take a breather.
Can we, can we?
We've been walking all day!
I'm totally exhausted!
‐You don't look
all that exhausted.
You're like a four‐year‐old
sometimes, you know that?
‐Aw, what's the rush?
We're trying to catch
one of the tailed beasts,
but we don't even
know where it is.
What's it going to hurt
if we kick back for a bit?
by the way, which one
are we after, again?
‐The Three Tails!
‐First we find him,
then we catch him.
Just leave it to Tobi.
Okey dokey?
Right?
‐Here you go.
Dumplings for two.
‐Wah ha!
These look tasty.
Let's see, let's see.
Down the hatch.
Mm.
That is good!
The sauce is out of this world!
Not too sweet, not too salty.
What a masterpiece.
Oh, that hit the spot, huh?
Wait.
Deidara, get a load of this.
‐Hm?
‐That looks exactly
like your work.
Doesn't it?
Could it be that your
art style is a rip off?
‐Tobi.
‐Wah!
‐You're dead!
[shouting]
[theme music]
[screaming]
‐What?
What's going on?
‐The Three Tails is surfacing.
‐Wait a minute
What is this feeling?
‐Shino?
What's wrong?
‐My insects are sensing
an abnormal chakra.
‐An abnormal chakra?
‐They've never felt
so much all at once.
It's a massive amount.
[bark]
‐Yeah, same goes for
Akamaru, you guys.
He's picking up the
exact same thing.
‐That means we must be
closing in on the place, huh?
‐Let's move.
‐This feeling.
There's bloodlust in the air.
Crackling all around us.
And it's not the Leaf.
It's something else.
What's going on?
KAKASHI: Is that it?
‐What the heck is that?
Some kind of fog?
‐It appears to me like the
bats are flying right into it.
‐No question.
There's an ocean
of chakra in there.
‐From where?
Inside the fog?
‐Yeah.
But what's the source?
‐What do you say we all just
dive in there and find out?
‐One step at a time, all right?
We have to be prepared.
‐Just say the word.
‐Be ready for action, everyone.
I want you all on your toes.
‐Roger that.
[bark]
‐No problem!
[screeching]
‐Looks like there's even
more of them out there now.
They call for reinforcements?
‐If they didn't know we
were coming, they do now!
‐It doesn't matter.
Keep going.
‐They've got us outnumbered.
We need to buy
ourselves some time
until Guren can get back here.
So Kiho, you're up.
Lay down some cover.
‐Whatever you say, boss.
‐Kakashi, what is it?
‐It's a smokescreen.
They were waiting for us.
We can't just rush in there.
But if we hang back
too long, we'll
never find out what's
happening at that lake.
We have to split up.
Naruto, you'll be on your own.
‐What?
I'm not fighting?
‐Our main objective
is that lake.
‐Oh, yeah.
That's right.
‐We'll create a diversion
while you head off
to see what's happening
down there in the fog.
But you're not to engage.
‐Right.
You got it.
‐You really think
it's a good idea
to send him out on his own?
‐I think he's earned our faith.
Don't you?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Besides, no one
is a better survivor than he is.
Good luck, Naruto.
That legendary unpredictability
is just what we need right now.
‐No reaction.
Seems no one's here.
‐Let's go.
‐This is great.
I can't see anything now.
Think they already fled?
‐They're probably buying time.
Keep your guard up.
‐All right, no more
waitin' around.
Time to take a closer look.
Guess I went too deep there.
‐Did ya bring some snacks?
‐We'd just gotten home, and
you had to call us up again.
You really like to crack
the whip, don't you?
‐Look, just help
me out, will ya?
I'll make it worth your while.
‐The chakra around
here is pretty intense.
I wonder what's in this fog?
[screaming]
‐It's coming!
‐So this is the Three Tails?
‐It's so much bigger
than we thought.
‐You sense it?
This feeling of dread?
‐Success.
We did it.
Yukimaru is controlling
the Three Tails!
‐Yukimaru!
‐Dammit.
If he keeps using his power‐‐
‐What happens to the Three
Tails if he loses control?
‐Your job's to prevent that
from happening, remember?
[screaming]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Even Yukimaru's power
isn't enough to control it.
‐Yukimaru.
[roaring]
‐Wait a second.
Do you guys hear that?
‐Guren!
Stop this behemoth!
‐I don't take orders
from you, four eyes!
GUREN (VOICEOVER): He may
be big, but he's fast, too!
‐Guren, hurry!
‐Gozu!
‐Now's your chance!
‐Crystal Style!
Divine Pathway Jutsu!
There we go.
It actually
shattered my crystal?
Giant Crystal
Hexagonal Shuriken!
Well, you're a tricky one.
Blasted turtle!
‐Guren!
What are you doing?
Trying to kill it?
You need to contain the Three
Tails, or we'll all be dead.
GUREN (VOICEOVER):
A jutsu of that
scale is gonna need
some preparation.
I'm too late!
Gozu!
‐Hurry!
Do it!
‐Crystal Style!
Crystal Wall, Eighth Formation!
Take that, you damn turtle!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): She did it.
The Crystal Style‐‐ I never
knew Guren was this strong.
‐I think I used too much chakra.
‐Watch it, Shino.
Don't get so close.
‐Trust me, that's the
last thing I want.
‐So why are you bumping me
with your shoulder, then?
‐Why?
Because our circle is
growing smaller, that's why.
‐Enough with all the chatter.
You should be focusing
on finding the enemy.
‐Yeah, but Kakashi‐sensei, he‐‐
HINATA: Above you!
Watch out!
‐Huh?
‐Our ambush failed.
‐Kakashi‐sensei!
Thanks a lot, you two.
We owe you one.
‐Hinata!
You're feeling better already?
‐Yeah.
‐But still, how did she‐‐ I see.
Your Byakugan.
‐We'd better be careful around
that little girl's jutsu.
Even with a smokescreen,
she can still find us.
Dammit.
NARUTO: What's with this place?
‐There's no signs
of fish anywhere.
And not a single wave in sight.
It's really weird.
‐Huh?
I see something.
GAMATATSU: Hey, it's a turtle.
There's a turtle inside.
Brother, what kinda
turtle is that?
‐Naruto, that's a
tailed beast in there.
‐Tailed beast?
‐Yeah.
It's the Three Tails.
‐Three Tails.
[roaring]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Even a jutsu
like that couldn't stop it?
‐Guren!
Take Yukimaru and
get out of here.
You too, Gozu!
‐Gozu!
Protect Yukimaru!
‐All right.
You got it.
‐Guren!
‐This is our fight.
You hear me?
‐That woman.
What is she fighting
the Three Tails for?
‐Be careful!
[roar]
‐I don't get it.
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me‐‐
‐Wherever somebody is thinking
of you, that place is home.
‐The place he wanted to turn
to all this time was with them?
‐Don't underestimate
me, you damn turtle!
‐Are you OK?
‐Well, this one
will never wither,
as long as I'm
alive in this world.
‐Guren's safe.
‐Gozu.
What are you doing here?
Take Yukimaru and go.
You have to hurry.
‐Of course, Guren.
[roaring]
‐I finally figured out where
I'm supposed to return to.
‐What are you‐‐
[screaming]
‐What happened?
The Three Tails
has stopped moving.
‐It can't be.
‐That kid‐‐ he's
controlling the Three Tails.
‐What the‐‐
‐Kakashi‐sensei.
‐Huh?
‐I think that's‐‐
‐We've got trouble.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): That's
the dimension where
the Three Tails comes from.
If we're swallowed up by it‐‐
‐Hey, are you all right?
‐It's so warm in here.
Here.
GUREN: Wait.
That's‐‐ Yukimaru!
GUREN (VOICEOVER): I'll use
all my power for this jutsu.
‐This time, I'll hold your hand.
[theme music]
TSUNADE: They say
the Three Tails
vanished after the
last great war.
No one's seen it since.
Orochimaru is stirring
up something foul.
SHIZUNE: But we
discovered it in time.
Perhaps it was a
blessing in disguise?
TSUNADE: Maybe.
But we mustn't let it
fall into the wrong hands.
‐We'll capture it, then?
‐That's easier said than done.
I'm going to do some research.
I want you to assemble
the following team.
NARUTO: Next time,
Inside the Mist.