[music playing]
-[sniffing] So they're in there.
If I get any closer,
I might be spotted.
-[moaning]
[door unlocking]
-Hey, sis.
You're going to
take those with you?
Fate has arranged our meeting.
If I'm going to see him,
I'll be needing these.
I have lived a long life.
[theme music]
KAKASHI: Hmm.
You're sure that's
where their hideout is?
-It seems more than
likely, since Gaara's scent
was coming from there as well.
-I see.
I've got one more
favor to ask you.
-Huh?
-[light snoring]
Ah!
Ow, that hurt my--
-Oh, Naurto, you're up.
-Huh?
Hey, Pakkun.
-All right.
Better get moving, Pakkun.
-I'll see you around, Naruto.
-Kakashi Sensei, does
this mean that they
found where the
Akatsuki are hiding ou?
-Yep.
Get ready.
Because we're moving out.
TEMARI: What?
Gaara, you're sure?
SOLDIER: Yes, ma'am.
They found where the
Akatsuki have taken him.
The leaf village ninja are
getting ready to move out.
-So will we.
I want you to put
together a pursuit squad.
And be quick.
SOLDIER: Right.
KANKURO: Temari.
-Kankuro, what do you
think you're doing?
You're not going anywhere.
You need to rest.
I give you my word.
I'll get Gaara back.
[soft cooing]
-Seems we'll be
working in conjunction
with a squad from
the sand village.
As soon as they're
here, we'll head out.
TEMARI: Sorry to
keep you waiting.
SAKURA: Temari.
-If that's everybody.
-OK.
There's no time to waste.
Let's get this show on the road.
LORD BAKI: Wait.
-Huh?
-Temari, you and your
group are to stay here.
Patrol the perimeter.
-Are you kidding me or what?
-Orders from above.
-[gasp]
-If word gets out that
the Kazekage is missing,
our enemies may use
it as an opportunity
to launch an attack
on the village.
-Come on.
-Don't you get it?
That's all the
more reason we have
to get him back as
quickly as we can.
Look at these leaf ninja.
They left their village, and
came all the way here just
to help us rescue Gaara.
And Gaara's not
even their leader.
He's our Kazekage.
The sand Shinobi should
be the ones to save him.
-I'm sorry.
LADY CHIYO: Well, I'm going.
If a sand Shinobi is needed,
then I'm the one to go.
-Granny Chiyo?
-But, but you're so--
-I'm retired, yes.
Which means, of course, that
I'm free to do whatever I want.
-Yes, but, the journey
will be difficult.
-Bah.
Don't treat me like a fussle.
-What in the?
Whoa.
-After all, it's been
a while since I've
doted on my adorable grandchild.
-[moaning]
-All right.
We'll head out on our own, then.
-Thank you.
I'll try to convince the
counsel to change their mind.
-Don't worry.
We'll catch up with you.
-Ha.
By the time you can
catch up with us,
we'll have already
rescued Gaara.
-We'll see you soon.
-Oh man, I hate this.
I'm the one who
should go after Gaara.
If it weren't for
these injuries--
-Hey, slow down a little.
We've been going at full
speed since we started.
Would it kill us to
take a little rest?
-Tenten, you're really
not training hard enough.
-Lee, up ahead.
-Huh?
-Hey, Guy, wait.
-Pakkun!
-Naruto, can I ask
you a question?
How long do you think the
Akatsuke have been after you?
-Huh?
I don't know.
-Two members of
the Akatsuke came
to the leaf looking
for Naruto once.
But it's been three years since
then, and no sign of them.
And now they're back.
-But why do you
think they waited
so long to make another move?
KAKASHI: It could be they
wanted to add before this,
but for some reason they
couldn't-- maybe because Master
Joraia was around, and they
didn't want to face him.
LADY CHIYO: That's not it.
From what I've learned, there
was an entirely different
reason they had
to wait this long.
-What reason?
-If you're going to try and
draw out the tailed beast that
dwells within, a great deal
of preparation is involved.
They just needed some more time.
-What are you talking about?
What tailed beast?
-My, my.
You're a student of that
old slug queen Tsunade,
and you don't even know
that, when the leaf
itself is host to
the nine-tailed fox?
-Huh?
-Oh?
-The nine-tailed fox spirit is
not something we talk about.
It's considered top secret.
-Really?
Well, not surprising, I guess.
Tailed beasts are demon
spirits with one or more tails.
The sand have had a
single-tailed beast
since long ago.
That's the shukaku
sealed within Gaara.
-So then there's more
of these demon spirits?
LADY CHIYO: Oh yes.
There are a total of nine
of them in the world,
each with distinct
characteristics,
and each with different
number of tails.
The demon beast of the
sand, with its single tail,
a two-tailed spirit,
three-tailed, and so on,
all the way up to that
nine-tailed fox of the leaf.
The beasts are huge
concentrations of chakra.
And during the great
war, every nation
competed for control of
them for military purposes.
They fought
relentlessly over them.
But the tailed beasts' powers
were beyond human imagining.
No one could control them.
I don't know the
intentions of the Akatsuki.
But that kind of power is
far too dangerous for anyone
to get a hold of.
Eventually, with
the coming of peace,
the tailed beasts
were forgotten.
But nevertheless, they still
exist, all nine of them
scattered over the world.
-Kakashi sent eight
of us ninja hounds out
to scour the countryside,
and try to pick up
the Akatsuki
organization's scent.
Well, we soon
discovered they were
headed for the land
of rivers bordering
the leaf and the sand.
-Land of rivers?
-That's right.
And since your squad is on
its way from the leaf village
to the sand, I guess
this is your lucky day.
You're the closest, if
you can call it lucky.
-All right then.
-I'll show you the way.
Follow me, and I'll
explain the rest as we go.
-Right.
You heard him, everyone.
Let's move out.
-What?
Already?
[chanting]
-[moaning]
-Our location has
been discovered.
The enemy approaches.
-Which enemy is that?
-A very skilled
and dangerous one.
His name is Might Guy.
-Might Guy?
Who is he?
-An elite leaf Shinobe,
a master of taijitsu.
Don't underestimate him.
-Ah.
That strange beast again.
-We'll use that
Jutsu against him.
-I'll go.
Let me take care of him.
It will give me a
chance to make up
for failing to find
a jinchuriki host.
-No, leave him to me.
You see, I know him.
I have a personal score
to settle with him.
-Yes, as you have the most
chakra of any of the Akatsuki,
you're probably the most
suitable to employ that Jutsu.
Very well, Kisame.
-Excellent.
-But I'll still require
30% of your chakra here.
-Well, well, finally.
I've been waiting to pay him
back for that kick he gave me.
-Severe leaf hurricane!
-Well, who have we here?
-The leaf village's
fiercest beast of battle.
I'm Might Guy.
-[sniffing]
-What is it, Pakkun?
-Someone's coming.
[panting]
-Yakukan.
Its behind us.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
Wait a minute.
-You know this
person, Guy Sensei?
-Who are you?
-[sigh]
[music playing]
-More intruders.
You didn't cover your
tracks very well, did you?
-Well, as I said,
the jinchuriki host
proved more powerful
than we thought.
-You're a bumbler, and a fool.
Your methods are too crude for
any sort of secret operation.
-Crude?
Hah.
Those clumsy traps of yours
were hardly subtle, my friend.
Hmm
-Why you--
-Stop bickering
amongst yourselves.
Focus on the Jutsu.
Now then, who to send this time.
-Me.
This time, it must be me.
This time, a leaf
shinobe should go.
-Very well.
It's decided, then.
-Everybody stop.
-Who's that?
-(THINKING) Sosun?
-(THINKING) Those
eyes, could it be?
-I know you.
-Unreal.
His chakra level
is off the charts.
I've never seen anyone but
Naruto with that much chakra.
-That much?
-Your memory is as
bad as your haircut.
-Can it be that you're--
-You finally
remembered, have you?
-You've met me somewhere before?
-It's no wonder
you're called a beast.
Your intelligence is
certainly sub-human.
Well, don't worry.
I'll refresh your
memory soon enough.
-Itachi Uchiha!
--[gasp] (THINKING)
That's, that's him.
That's Itachi Uchiha.
[music playing]
-What is it, Guy Sensei?
GUY SENSEI: The moment
we've been waiting for.
LEE: Yes, I see.
The big wave that every surfer
longs to ride, the wave that
comes only once every few years.
-Big Thursday Conquer
that monster wave,
and prove yourself a man.
LEE: I will, Sensei.
There is no wave on earth
bigger than my fighting spirit.
Will you two keep it down?
You're giving me a headache.
NARUTO: Next time, a
meeting with destiny.
[music playing]
LEE: The gallery of memories.
Allow me to present
some treasured images,
and happy memories
of our friends
from the leaf village
in days gone by.
Naruto is a baby, so peaceful,
so cuddly, so different
than he is now.
Oh, the young Third Hokage,
with the three legendary
[inaudible].
Can you believe it?
Lady Tsunade with a pony tail.
Here's the Fourth Hokage,
with Kakashi's squad.
Did you know Kakashi became
Ochunin at the age of six?
No wonder he and Guy
Sensei are rivals.
Even now, Kakashi sleeps with
this very picture by his bed.
And here are some
familiar faces,
memories of student
days at the academy,
and the times we
had, and Sakura.
Sakura, she has
not changed at all.
Even then, she was almost
too beautiful to look at.
And who could this
young fellow be, with
that noble brow
and fearless gaze?
The leaf village's
handsome devil.
Could it be yours truly?