You're no longer
a Jinchuriki,
Gaara?
What do
you mean?
Some time ago,
those who control
you, removed Shukaku
the One Tail from me.
And in doing
so, killed me.
[raspy gasp]
Sealing Jutsu:
Nine Phantom
Dragons!
[low moans]
Is that me?
What am I anyway?
But thanks to the
assistance of Granny Chiyo and
my friends, I was revived
and am still alive today.
You mean
Granny Chiyo
did that for you?
Wait, hold
on. You said
friends?
Are you telling
me that you
actually have
friends?!
Up until this point
in time, everything
I've done in my life
has been wrong.
But at least,
here in my final
hour...
...I can finally
do something
right for a
change.
The sand...
...And the
leaf.
May the future that
awaits them, be different
from the way things
were in our time.
Gaara!
Gaara...
Naruto...
[shocked gasp]
[quiet breath
of disbelief]
What is this...?
They all
came running
to help ya.
You've had
everyone worried!
You didn't think
he'd have any friends?
Did you really
believe that your
son would just be
alone this whole time?
He was a kid!
Everyone has
friends at
that age.
Six, father.
You made six
attempts to
kill me.
And each time,
my fear and
hatred of you
increased.
But I no longer
harbor any
hatred for you
father.
Now I'm even
able to understand
why you did it.
I've become
the Kazekage.
It is a leader's
duty to eliminate
threats against
one's village.
We must protect it.
[gasp]
What did
you say?
You are...
Kazekage?!
And that's
not all of it!
He's also been named
the commander in chief
of the Allied Shinobi
Forces' Main battle Regiment.
Despite his young
age, he not only calls
himself Kage...
...But has the
respect of the
other Kage as well.
Now it all
makes sense...
I thought it was
odd that I sensed chakra
types from various villages,
all mixed together.
Just imagine,
shinobi united
in an allied force!
Well, apparently
what you lack in
eyebrows you more than
make up for in charisma!
Hm...Actually
come to think of
it I'm just
the same!
Then explain that
sorry excuse
for a mustache.
Hmph!
If you're going
to kill us, then I
suggest you guys start
with the mummy, here!
I'll be more
than happy
to cheer you on!
So he's your
son, then, is
he?
He's a fine
shinobi.
He's so small...
He's premature...
Are you really
sure he's going
to be alright?
I'm not certain,
but he's adapting.
This is the third
child. So far
he's the only one
that's compatible.
His upbringing
is going to
require a good
deal of care.
[heavy breathing]
Please let...let
me see my...
baby's face...
Are you
alright, Karura?!
[heavy inhale]
He's so...
just so tiny!
It's lady Karura's
heart rate. It's
dropping sir!
[worried reaction]
Then do something
about it now!
[fearful gasp]
That child's
a failure, too...
The rampage's
have begun like
before.
[frustrated grunt]
We are at a point...
...Where if we can't maintain
our defenses anymore the
Sand will be weakened beyond
all hope of repair.
What we must do
is figure out
how to negotiate
with the other lands.
But
something must be done
about Shukaku
as well!
The new
Jinchuriki remains
unreliable.
So for the moment,
we have to depend on
Lord Kazekage's development
of new jutsu...
...And in our
gold dust trade for
village stability.
And now as
for Gaara...
Yashamaru,
I need to speak
to you later.
Yes, sir.
But Lord
Kazekage,
Lord Gaara...
...Is still just
a child!
In my time
as Kazekage, I've
had to judge the
value of many things.
And I'm going
to have to
test his worth
as well.
[defeated sigh]
We shall
assess Gaara
tomorrow.
After the village
has been evacuated,
go and corner him.
Tell him about
his mother, and
provoke him
emotionally.
If he doesn't
go Berserk after that,
then I will spare
his life.
Tell him...
about my sister,
are you sure?
I am well aware
that he loves and
respects his mother
Karura with all of his heart!
If that's taken
from him, and he
can still suppress
his rage...
Only then will
he suffice as
a Jinchuriki!
Huh?!
What are you?
But why?
Why come
after me?!
Why always me?!
Who are you?
What do
you want?!
[shocked gasp]
You did well
Gaara...You
did very well.
Yashamaru...
[agonized scream]
[quiet sobs]
I don't
understand!
Yashamaru...
Why did you
do it?
It was an order.
[soft gasp]
You see,
I was ordered
to kill you
Gaara.
[shocked gasp]
By Lord Kazekage...
By your own father.
My father...
[sickened reaction]
[heavy panting]
But why would...
My father...
Want me dead?
Before you were born,
the Sand Spirit Shikaku,
was planted inside
of you.
All these years
you've been watched
and studied as part
of an experiment.
It became clear
that you could
never control it...
...This Shukaku that
possesses the
power of the
sand itself.
The day is coming
when your existence
will be too dangerous
for the village.
It had to
be done
before then.
You-You had to
obey my father.
You didn't have
any choice.
You're wrong.
I actually
had a choice.
Yes, Lord
Kazekage made
his wishes known to
me. But...
Still I could have
have refused to
do this if I
had chosen to.
I suppose
it's because...
...Deep in
my heart...
...I hate you,
Gaara.
[quivering]
My sister died
bringing you
into this world.
I can't
forgive you
for that.
[quiet quivering]
You were all
that was left
of her.
And so I kept telling
myself that since I
loved her, I should
love you as well.
I tried...
...But I
never could.
It wasn't her
choice to have
you, to be made
a human sacrifice.
And so she died,
cursing this
village.
The day
she died...
...I felt a wound
in my heart that
I knew would
never heal.
The name you
have, is the one
that your mother
gave to you.
Your name
is Gaara...
...A demon that
loves only itself.
As you must
love no one
else.
Care for no
one's existence
but your own.
In that way,
you will be
sure to survive.
This is the
dying gift,
your mother
left you.
However...
It was not done out
of maternal affection, it
was not because of love that
she gave you your name.
She wanted you to
survive-not as a
kindness, but as
a punishment.
It was part
of her curse.
It was from her
undying rage at this
village. That you should
survive and grow.
Her hate,
lives on in
you.
You were
never loved,
Gaara.
Never.
[angry roar]
It's another
failure.
Gaara is
useless to
us now.
[angry roar]
It's seems this
Reanimation Jutsu...May
actually have something of
merit to it after all.
Come! show me!
Let me determine
once again what
you may be worth,
Gaara.
Can you defeat
me or can't you?!
Yes, Ohnoki...You
must stop me.
Against Particle
Style, the number of
opponents doesn't
matter.
You're the
only one
who can stop me.
I'm aware
of that.
And also...
...You must remember
what I taught you about
what happens to allies
after a victory.
Once the war is over,
the alliance is too. It
becomes a fight for the
spoils of victory.
That is what
truly decides
which village is
the victor.
Hey! Knock it off,
Tsuchikage! You're
just playing dirty
now!
I won't let
that happen!
I have no intention
of doing any such
thing, Lord Mu.
Not at all!
[in unison]
Hm?
I see!
So it seems that you
didn't actually
turn into a stubborn
old geezer.
Pft. I wouldn't
be so sure
yet.
In any case,
we aren't in
control of our
own bodies right now.
We've been set to
automatically counter
whatever jutsu the enemy
tries to use against us.
So hurry! Kill
us and return us
to the netherworld!
We'll even tell
you all our powers
and weaknesses.
But still, it's going to
be up to you to stop us.
And it isn't going to
be an easy task.
Move in!
Everyone!
Let's go!
[cheers and
battle cries]
Now, Sand Hail!
[grunt]
Damnit!
Sand Hail was
just a diversion!
He used it to
force me to
life the gold
dust!
[grunting and
struggling]
Karura...
You still live
on inside this
child.
That really
is father!
You have truly
grown up, Gaara.
[emotional gasp]
What parents
need to do, is
to believe in
their children.
That one simple
thing...
...Is the real
treasure.
[stunned gasp]
Isn't that the
whole truth of
it, Karura?
Now I see
it clearly.
I didn't posses
the ability to
judge the true
value of things.
What do you
mean by that?
No matter what,
the Sand will
always protect
you.
But that is not
Shukaku's power...
...It belongs
to your mother!
It's Karura's!
He's so...
just so tiny!
No matter what
happens...I will
always protect
you, Gaara.
Your mother...
Loved you!
[shocked gasp]
Father did-did
you really just
say my mother
loved me?!
But that day
long ago...when
Yashamaru came
after me!
You were never
loved, Gaara.
Never...
I told Yashamaru
to lie to you then,
he was merely
following orders.
I had to see if you'd
lose control of the
tailed beast inside you
if you were distraught.
For the sake
of the village.
If there was
anyone Yashamaru
truly hated...
...It would've
been me, and
not you.
I'm the one who
forced Yashamaru's
pregnant older
sister Karura...
...To suffer
the sealing of
Shukaku, the
Sand Spirit.
But Yashamaru
was a consummate
shinobi.
He was loyal to me,
and a reliable ANBU
Black Ops for the
Sand.
He followed me
orders for
the sake of
the village.
[shocked gasp]
It was all
a mistake.
Sometimes it seems
that every single
thing I did was
a mistake.
I burdened you
unnecessarily.
I arbitrarily
decided that you held
no true value to our
village-or to anyone.
I took away your future by
making you a Jinchuriki,
robbed you of your mother, and
poisoned you against her.
I took away
everything.
Your ability
to know or
love others.
I even tried
to take
your life.
In the end, as
a parent...there's
just one thing
that I gave you.
The only thing
you got from
me was a
broken heart.
[stunned reaction]
I know I'm not
bleeding...But lately
I've felt a lot
of pain here.
[gasps]
You wound your
body, and blood
is going to flow.
Following fast
on the heals
of pain.
But as time passes,
the pain eventually
fades away.
And with a
little help from
medicine, it can
heal even faster.
But even more
dangerous is a
wound dealt
to the heart.
'Cause there's
nothing that
has more trouble
healing.
A wound
to the heart?
Wounds to the
heart are a little
different from
wounds to the flesh.
Unlike an injury to
the body, there is no
medicine for a
wounded heart.
And sometimes it...
never heals.
But don't worry,
there is one thing
that's capable of
mending a broken heart.
[gasps]
But, that cure...
is a very
complicated remedy.
It can only
be administered
by another person.
[light surprised
gasp]
What is it?
It's love,
Gaara.
It's love.
Yep.
But-But
how am I
supposed to
get it?
Don't you
know, Gaara?
It has
already been
given to you.
Huh?
My mother...
There's no question
that my older
sister always
loved you.
Shukaku, the Sand Spirit
is a living soul
bent toward the
purpose of war.
But when the sand
that you wield
automatically rushes
in to protect you...
That is your
mother's love.
I believe your
mother's will is
carried in every
grain of that sand.
My sister...
even after
death...
Wants more
than anything
to protect you.
[quiet sobs]
Karura...
Mother's are
powerful.
Yours believed in
you and protected
you even after
death.
She's the one
who made you
what you are
today.
She allowed you
to reach your
destined role
as Kazekage.
And to make friends.
She gave you bonds
with your siblings
and community.
All the things
that I took
away from you.
But as your
father, all I
ever did was
torment you.
I don't even
deserve to
be called your
father.
My mother...
is amazing!
[shocked gasp]
Thanks to her...
I have now received
medicine from
you father.
Gaara...
My son!
You surpassed
me long ago.
I leave the
village to you,
Gaara!
Itachi Uchiha?!
Nagato?!
You know these
guys, Naruto?
Yeah! I know
both of them!
Never did I think
I would have to
battle you again,
Naruto.
You now command
the power of
the Nine Tails?
I'm impressed
with your
development.
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
Contact! Naruto vs.
Itachi!
Naruto, there's
something I must
ask you.