What was that?!
Did you say that Omoi
deserted the battlefield?!
Is this true, Kakashi?
I'm afraid it is. Reports
say he ran from his post
after stating that he needed
to leave for a bit.
He did?! But why?
Why would he--?!
Omoi! Come back, my
comrade-in-arms!
[growling]
Damn it, Omoi! What
were you thinking?!
Doesn't he know our
situation?! We're strained
enough as it is! Even losing
a single man
could decrease the military
strength of the unit!
Lord Raikage, sir! You
dumb?! You buy this crap
about him deserting?!
Huh?! Karui?!
He may act a little anxious
at times, but he's
definitely not a coward!
He'd never just run from the
enemy. This whole thing must
be some kind of mistake!
Look, I don't want to
believe that he could
do this either...
But still, deserting under
enemy fire is a serious
offense in the Hidden
Cloud. And so...
I've remembered something
that might be of help.
Yes, Sai?
Before Omoi left
we got a report.
Our unit on Battlefield
Seven was under attack.
They were requesting that
reinforcements be sent...
I saw that when he heard
that, Omoi went pale.
We received their call for
reinforcements four hours
ago.
It appears that they were
surrounded and pinned down
by a large number of White
Zetsu.
There were two thousand!
Two thousand?!
We had no forces nearby to
send to their aid, and so we
told them just to hang
tight.
We haven't heard
from them since...
It's entirely possible that
battlefield is where Omoi
is heading.
Who's deployed on
Battlefield Seven?
The Amphibious Search and
Destroy Unit. Most of them
are from the Hidden Mist
Village.
Twenty-four of them were
deployed to the front.
The Hidden Mist? Why's
Omoi so eager to help?
We received another
troubling message, too.
A supply unit that was
traveling on the road close
to Battlefield Seven...
has yet to reach their
destination and has been
reported as missing.
Perhaps they went to the aid
of the Amphibious Search and
Destroy Unit.
Which supply
unit is missing?
The Hidden Cloud's
Thundercloud Unit!
What did you say?!
Thundercloud Unit?!
I don't understand.
What is that unit?
It's a group of seven, made
up of twelve to thirteen
year-olds.
I realize that sounds too
young, but they're all
extremely talented.
We decided that they were
ready to go to war, so I
assigned them to work with
the supply unit.
Guess I was too hasty...
So Omoi knew all
about them correct?
Omoi, you giant idiot.
Check out the chakra on
Battlefield Seven. I want to
know if that unit is alive!
White Zetsu have
overrun the area.
As for allied chakra, I
sense... seven.
Seven...
The size of the
Thundercloud Unit.
Please, Lord Raikage, don't!
Those kids knew what they
were signing up for!
They were prepared to die
on the battlefield. Don't
belittle their sacrifice
by risking others to
go check on them!
Hey, those kids
are still alive.
Damn it, Omoi, what
are you doing?!
Omoi!
Sorry I ran off, everyone.
Omoi! Get back to your post!
We're at war, here! You
can't just do whatever you
want!
Please, give me an hour.
That's all the time I need
to bring every one of them
back safely.
What?! Will you just drop
all this nonsense?!
How can you stand there and
say something like that?!
You're the one who's always
worried about everything!
Every unit is going to have
some casualties. It's just
wishful thinking to assume
that those
seven are all from the
Thundercloud Unit.
Sorry, but I believe the
survivors are those kids.
Okay, but even if they are,
you're never gonna get there
in time to help them!
[yawning]
Listen, if you're just going
to bore me like this, then
we're done here. Later!
Hey, Omoi! Come back here!
Knowing them, they've
probably already taken down
the enemy and they're having
a party to celebrate.
I mean, by now, they could
even be well into their
second round of partying!
I can't have any alcohol,
but maybe they'll give me
juice for a toast. If they
do, I'll make one
that lasts until morning!
It's no good. He's
not answering me.
Lord Raikage, I'm so
sorry about this! Please
let me go capture that
fool and tie him up.
I gotta do something, here!
You know if there are
survivors from the
Thundercloud Unit out there...
We still can't give them any
special treatment, even if
they are young!
Kakashi, Guy, Lee, Sai...
You can handle things there
without Omoi for about an
hour, can't you?
Huh?!
Even if it's just for an
hour, losing someone as
strong as Omoi will hinder
us.
But we'll manage.
We'll try five- No, ten
times harder, and we'll make
it all work somehow!
Just leave it to us!
I will fight a
hundred times harder!
You do that.
You heard them!
Thank you.
Sorry, Omoi... I guess
it's all up to you now.
But, still Omoi's
all by himself.
Give me the positions of
Naruto's Shadow Clones!
That kid?
A single one of his Shadow
Clones has the strength to
protect an entire village.
Well, uh, that's
overstating it a bit.
There's only one Shadow
Clone that's close to
Battlefield Seven, but at
least he's headed in
that direction.
He's quite a ways
away, though.
Notify Naruto!
I know that I promised
Lord Raikage I'd take
care of this in just one
hour. But what if I
actually manage to finish
it all up in only thirty
minutes?
And what if he's so
impressed that he says,
"Good job, Omoi! You're going
to be the next Raikage!"
But what if instead of
one hour, it takes me
three hours!
Then he might say, "Go back
to the village! We don't
want you around here
anymore!"
Well, either way
I'm getting close.
Over this hill is a desolate
place without even a blade
of grass.
I bet that they rolled out
the red carpet for me and
maybe even hung up a banner
that says, "Welcome Omoi!"
No way! Are you kidding?!
What, is this all some kind
of prank?
The Hidden Mist...
[sinister chuckling]
Just one of you?!
You can't stop us!
Damn you!
Boy, this sure isn't the red
carpet I was expecting!
I'm sorry to let you down
but that sure doesn't mean
that I'm just going to give
up, you know!
Naruto Uzumaki! At your
service to help out!
Wait, you're that...
That Jinchuriki from a while
back... Naruto Uzumaki!
Rasen-Rampage!
So much power!
You're Omoi, right?
I don't quite get what's
going on... But I do believe
what you said.
Huh?
That those kids are still
alive! And that you're gonna
save them.
[chuckle] Thanks, but it's
not just about believing.
Those kids are alive. And
they're waiting for me to
come help them.
You got that right!
[chuckle]
They're coming!
With him here...
Forget about this taking
thirty minutes! We can mow
all these guys down in
twenty!
And then Lord Raikage will
say, "I was right. You are
the next Raikage..."
Come on!
Oh, no!
What did you do?!
Sorry! It was just
an accident!
Oh, good. It was
just a Shadow Clone.
No! Not good!
Naruto was really
helping! I'm a fool!
You know, I bet Naruto
thought I could handle this
whole thing by myself.
And he let himself get hit!
Yeah I got this! These guys
aren't that good. I can
definitely handle them
alone!
Those kids are alive out
there somewhere!
But it's impossible to do
this in thirty minutes. Even
in an hour it might not be
possible.
How about two hours? If I
get it done in two hours,
maybe Lord Raikage will
give me a break
and still name me as
the next Raikage.
What is this?!
[gasp]
They're exhaling poison gas...
Red soil?
Some of those white guys
have turned red... It must
have something to do with
that red soil.
What do I do? I'm stuck
here, and in every direction
is a field of poison.
What is that thing?
There!
They're inside!
I'm sure of it!
They're alive!
They're alive, they're
alive, they're alive!
They're definitely alive!
It's bad! Stay back!
Stay away!
Not good. They'll
locate us soon.
They'll figure out we're
here sooner or later.
And we're running
out of air.
We weren't ready. We're
still too young for battle.
That's why Lord Raikage put
us with the supply unit.
No point saying that now.
Back when Yukai first
suggested that we go to help
out, why didn't you guys
oppose it?
Sorry... I'm just frustrated
that there doesn't seem to
be anything we can do now.
Same here.
I'm angry, too, Yukai.
I feel horrible about this.
It was my decision as leader
that brought us here.
I'm frustrated, as well.
If we're just stuck
waiting to die...
Let's go out with
a bang, together!
Good thing I was able to
get away underwater!
But I'm just like everyone
else: I can't hold my breath
forever!
Damn it! That's it! I've
reached my limit!
Lightning Style!
Thunderbolt!
[screaming]
This is...
They're alive, they're
alive, they're alive!
[yelling]
Even if we all die, at least
we can deal the enemy a blow
before we do...
Big sister gave me this...
You came, Omoi!
[chuckle]
Lightning Style!
Coordinated Thunder Bomb!
[painful screaming]
[heavy breathing]
This red soil is saturated
with moisture, so it
conducts really well.
Which makes the Lightning
Style's power off the charts!
Hey, it's okay to
breathe, right?
[big inhale]
Yeah, but it's not fresh
like an open field.
I used up my chakra...
Big Brother Omoi, just
give us a chance to show
what we can do now.
Sure. I think that you
guys'll manage just fine.
[yawning]
Let's go!
[attacking yell]
Didn't I tell you guys? I
knew that they were still
alive!
Someone who left his
post in the middle of a
war and acted on his own
without orders has
no right to sit on
some high horse!
And tell your subordinates
there to stop showing off!
Sorry, but I think it's
about time they started
showing off.
These guys have come of
age in a major way.
Omoi! You impulsive
greenhorn!
[gasp] Lord Raikage!
I gave you just one hour!
And if you don't return
within that time, then I'll
punish you myself! So be
prepared!
Yes! I understand!
[scared whimpering]
[laughing]
Thank you...
Omoi.
I bet that I'm gonna fall
into a hole somewhere along
the way back to camp...
And I'll get trapped because
it's so deep. And the whole
time that I'm stuck I'm in
there, the clock will
just keep on ticking.
So I won't make it back by
the time I promised Lord
Raikage, and he's going to
get super mad at me...
Oh man, why am I
always so unlucky?
Finally caught up with you!
Well, it's about time! What
have you been doing?
A persistent pee, yo.
Anyway, one of your Shadow
Clones contacted me earlier.
How are all the others
doing, by the way?
They should arrive on the
frontlines of every last
battlefield right about now.
Then all the fakers we're
gonna seek out. All the bad
guys we'll defeat, no doubt.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Reinforcements
Arrive."
But we gotta hurry!