Everyone is growing
tired of fighting.
I know...
Even if we win, the Akatsuki
never really gets rewarded...
The only things that we
have are our ideals.
In time, pent-up
frustrations will
erase even those.
So everyone's going to
forget what they're fighting
for? Is that what
you're telling me?
Nagato...
Will you take over as
leader of the Akatsuki?
Huh?!
It's just...
I'm not cut out
to be a leader.
That day...
I killed someone
for the first time.
It's like I can still
feel that moment...
And I can't stop trembling!
Yahiko...
But you're different.
You have the mark of a hero.
A special symbol known as
the Rinnegan and that will
become everyone's new ideal.
Yahiko!
Are you trying to
exploit my Rinnegan?!
I'm frightened of myself.
These eyes have brought
me so much suffering.
I know...
But remember, you have
someone who can help you
keep that power in check.
Konan will always
be by your side.
Yahiko...
Brother! Big news!
What's going on?
Hanzo sent a messenger!
Are you Yahiko, the
leader of the group that's
known as the Akatsuki?
Yes, I am.
I am Kanzo, a trusted friend
of Hanzo of the Salamander,
the one who sent me here.
We have heard many rumors
about you Akatsuki...
For example, how
you seek peace
without relying on
military might.
That is the founding
principle of the Akatsuki.
Hanzo has asked me to
deliver a confidential
letter to you. Here it is.
Is this?!
Is he serious about this?!
He would very much
like to meet with your
group personally.
Hanzo has given the Akatsuki
his seal of approval.
In time, Hanzo will leave
you to handle the peace
negotiations between
the three nations on
behalf of the Hidden Rain.
We'll handle the
negotiations?! Brother!
That's amazing!
Please relay to Lord
Hanzo that I accept.
[cheering]
This means we can
step out of the shadows
and help people openly!
So many have died...
...for us to
reach this point.
Finally, we'll be able
to face them with pride!
You did it...
Your determination to
free others from pain and
suffering has gotten
through to Hanzo.
Look...
[laughter]
The Akatsuki's faith in our
ideals has been restored.
There was never a
need for a symbol.
We'll all follow your
dream, wherever it leads.
Nagato... [chuckle]
We were right after all!
Tomorrow, Nagato and I
will go to the meeting
with Hanzo alone.
You sure about
this, Brother?
We'd all be happy
to go with you.
No, that's all right.
Besides, Hanzo might wonder
what he's gotten into if too
many of us show up!
[laughter]
Yeah, I know
that, but still...
Where is Konan, anyway?
She went to go and
patrol the Seventh Ward.
She won't be back
until tomorrow.
I see... On such a
special day, too.
Today, the Akatsuki took
a giant step forward!
So all of you! Set
aside your duties tonight
and celebrate!
[cheering]
The brats in the Akatsuki
aren't becoming
suspicious at
all, are they?
No, of course not.
I'm certain that if the
one named Yahiko is
killed, the Akatsuki
will naturally die off.
What about your plans?
No need to worry.
Who could have--?
[gasp] Poison!
[groans]
We should be securing the
hostage right about now.
With this operation, that
lawless gang that threatens
your village will be
gone, and the Hidden Rain
will be all yours.
I can't believe
we've come this far...
Nagato.
You--!
Reality is moving
forward quickly.
The time has come for
you to cut ties with
Yahiko and join me.
Otherwise, you'll all...
We'll all what?
What Yahiko proposes
are just naïve ideals.
He tries to understand
others' pain, but they make
no attempt to know ours.
But in any event, this world
has no desire for either
attempt. That is reality.
You possess the
Rinnegan, so you really
should understand.
No matter what you say...
I believe in
Yahiko's ideals!
I guess without pain you
cannot comprehend reality.
Though you possess the
Rinnegan, you still think
like an ordinary man.
Very well, then... Go
witness reality for yourself.
And experience pain.
There you are, Nagato.
Yahiko...
Was someone here?
No one...
Well, we'd better get going.
Or we'll be late for our
meeting with Hanzo.
Right. Let's go!
[snoring]
Ow!
Hey, what's the big idea?
I was having a nice nap!
Huh? Let's see...
Hey, you guys! Where're
Yahiko and Nagato?!
I think they both left for
that meeting with Hanzo
already. It's
today, remember?
Wake everyone up!
We gotta catch up to them!
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later!
So, talk! What the
hell is going on?
We just received word
from a member of the team
at the Hidden Leaf border.
The Leaf's Anbu Black
Ops are on their way
to meet Hanzo, too.
What? Anbu from the
Hidden Leaf Village?!
But why would they be
going to see Hanzo?!
I don't know any of
the specifics...
But the timing of it
sure seems suspicious.
Besides when you think
about it, this thing
with Hanzo really sounds
too good to be true!
Then that means today's
meeting with Hanzo is...
Whatever's going on,
we need to let Brother
know about all this!
As much as I regret this, I
cannot let you go any further.
Who are you?!
My name is Madara Uchiha.
Damn you! Did Hanzo
send you here?
[grunt]
I don't work for Hanzo.
Still, I cannot let
you interfere with his
plans right now.
I want Nagato to see
what reality truly is.
Look, we don't have time
for any of your nonsense.
Kill him!
[growl]
You take care of
the weaker ones.
You sure do like to
order me around!
[fighting grunts]
I'm Kyusuke the Swift!
Don't you dare
underestimate my speed!
[attacking yell]
What?!
What just happened?! I
slipped right through him!
Kyusuke!
You bastards!
Why are you doing...
...all this?!
To awaken Nagato's
Rinnegan by opening his
eyes to the truth.
What're you talking about?
There is no such thing as
peace in this accursed
world. Nagato must
abandon this dream and
set out to create
a new world.
I'm not gonna let you!
Daibutsu! Now!
Go through me!
But...
Hurry!
All right, I'll see
you in the next world!
[yell]
The Water Prison Jutsu?
You cannot defeat me
with a jutsu like this!
This is no ordinary
Water Prison Jutsu.
This is cement!
For the first time in my
dismal life as a war
orphan. I'd finally
found some hope
in the Akatsuki!
Do you really think that I'd
let some bastard like you
take that away from me?!
He's sacrificing his life to
make this attack. But as
expected, we're literally
in different dimensions.
No way!
Kyusuke...
Your death will
not be in vain!
Ow! When that stuff
hardened, it peeled off my
outermost layer of skin!
Boy, that stings!
Impossible...
Terribly sorry, but this is
the end for all of you.
[groaning]
Are you alright?
Yes.
Come alolng, we
have to hurry.
We must witness
Nagato's destiny!
Yahiko... You're the
leader so you must die!
Resist, and I'll
kill her instead.
You! Redhead! Use
that to kill Yahiko.
If you do, I'll
spare you and the girl.
Don't, Nagato! Forget
about me, just get
away, both of you!
Nagato.
Just kill me.
[gasp]
Nagato!
Don't do it!
Hurry up. Do you want
this woman to die?!
[heavy breathing]
Konan...
Yahi-
You and Konan, must
survive, no matter what...
You are the savior...
of this world.
I know... you
can do it.
Yahiko!
[sobbing]
Kill him!
He repelled them?!
How?!
[grunting]
Did we get him?
Nagato...
Konan, hold onto
Yahiko and stay still.
Impressive, boy! You
escaped even while being
hit by my Fire
Style Jutsu!
You're no ordinary brat,
are you? Those eyes...
Get him!
Summoning Jutsu!
Gedo Statue!
[screaming]
[roaring]
There it is!
So he's summoned it,
the Ten Tails' husk...
What- What is that?!
Nagato! No,
don't use that!
[yell]
Run! If it touches
you, you die!
[attacking yell]
[death screams]
[harrumph]
It appears you were in the
shadows as the real leader.
That you possess
the Rinnegan is
quite a surprise.
Nagato...
[attacking yell]
Teleportation Jutsu!
[gasp]
Nagato, Yahiko, Konan...
The world of dreams...
I shall let you see
it there without fail.
Didn't I tell you?
Yes, I understand now.
The selfish desire to
preserve peace gives rise to
war. Hatred is born from
wanting to protect love.
There is no such thing
as peace to be found
anywhere in this
whole accursed world.
Precisely.
You'll forever remain the
leader of the Akatsuki...
Yahiko.
Hey, Kakashi!
What's all the fuss?
They're about to announce
who the Fourth Hokage is!
Don't be surprised, but it's
going to be Minato Sensei!
Rin, it seems that Minato
Sensei is going to be
Hokage! If he is,
I'm sure he...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "A Mask That
Hides the Heart."
He will prevent anyone
else from becoming
a victim like you!