[clanging]
[thud, groan]
Gaara, don't overdo it!
I am no longer a Jinchuriki...
So that means...
We can now pull all-nighters as
equals.
Gaara...you...
There's really no need
to distinguish between man and
beast.
...remind me of Bunpuku.
[moan]
[clang]
[growl]
[groan]
Hey, kid!
Kazekage! Do me a favor!
[clanging]
Good.
You got that,...Gaara?!
Naruto!
"A True Ending"
[plop]
[heavy breathing]
[clanging, gnarr]
Shukaku!
Sorry, Bee!
I'm counting on you, Kazekage!
No way!
All of them were pulled into it!
Well,...Guess I can't expect
more with my current strength...
That took longer than just a few
seconds! But, I guess that you
were faster than Obito.
Humph...You really do talk too
much.
You're all flops, failed
inventions of mine...Always
finding fault with me.
Well, Black Zetsu's nickname is
Wicked Tongue, and we White
Zetsu call ourselves, Wagging
Tongues, so- [laughter]
I trust that the other battle is
going well, too?
Oh, don't worry, it is! After
all, the base is pretty good
material!
Flying Raijin Slice!
[whack]
You're mine!
This is my chance!
Naruto...
Gaara...!
Gaara...
Naruto...
I'm not going to let you die!
I swear it!
It's your M.O. to strike when
your opponent is sure of
victory...
Making the brats do all the hard
work...
It appears the you haven't
changed at all. You're still a
delegator, aren't you, Tobirama?
The same goes for you.
[chuckle] But I'm the one the
heavens are smiling on right
now.
Just look at you, the one who
was touted as the fastest
shinobi ever.
There's a reason why you two
brothers can't regain your full
power and, you, your former
speed.
Whether it's coincidence or if
it's inevitable, I've got the
edge right now.
And some new eyes are ripening
as well,
[inhale] though it's unclear
which side they'll end up
on...
Wait!
[gasp]
Uchiha lad...
Let me...give you a jutsu.
A jutsu...?
That's right...Madara has stolen
my Sage Jutsu Chakra...
This jutsu will react to the
Sage Jutsu Chakra and bind him.
Then you can use it yourself...
As a Reanimation, you'll recover
fast.
I can pull those out of you, if
you want me to.
These rods appear to be piercing
my Chakra Points, and they're
preventing me from infusing more
chakra now.
Also, I think it's a bad idea
for you yo touch them.
Now,...I'll give you all of my
remaining chakra.
So stop Madara.
Why ask an Uchiha?
You're quire a lot like him...
Madara's...younger
brother,...Izuna Uchiha.
Yeah, so what? What does that
have to do with me stopping
Madara?
Madara is fundamentally kind.
He was a devout man who loved
his siblings very deeply. That's
the reason why he gave you a
chance at redemption.
Although, with an eye like that,
killing you would be such a
waste.
How about...
...putting your blade down and
joining up with me, as a fellow
surviving Uchiha.
Oh, please. Make no
mistake,...in my mind, you're
nothing but a dead man.
[chuckle} Very well, then...But
either way, you don't have a
whole lot of time left.
You might be able to stop
Madara, without using force.
Now,...come stand before me...
[crack]
[thud, grunt]
To be honest...
I have wanted to do this to you
or a very long time now.
Since you're...
...the one who killed Izuna!
But you're just a moving corpse,
so it's hardly fulfilling.
Madara...What do you want so
badly that you'd come back to
life?
Our era, our time, ended long
ago!
All I want to do is build the
nation that Hashirama couldn't
finish.
However, this world belongs to
him, my failed predecessor.
Drastic measures are needed to
save the dying patient.
I'm going to go on ahead!
This Infinite Tsukuyomi...That
was really your idea, then?
Do you think that it's a cure?
That's right. Hashirama's nation
building bore a paradox.
People desire peace...
And yet, on the other hand, they
crave conflict as well.
That duality is mankind for
you...To want only peace and to
discard only conflict...
...would, in fact, cause people
to stop being people.
And those two things stand
together side by side.
I won't forgive anyone who would
dare to threaten the village.
Be they friend, sibling, or even
my own child.
People will sacrifice something
in order to protect something
else.
Except in a true and perfect
dream world.
You do have a point, there.
However,...it's not a dream for
you...
...to meddle with!
[clink, swish]
Now!
[sigh]
[clunk, grunt]
You could say...
...that this world is
Hashirama's paradox world.
Damn it!
What...is this?!
So in order to protect
something...something else gets
sacrificed.
Stop, Madara! Enough!
Don't go any further!
Be they...
...a close friend or a sibling,
or even if they were my very own
child...
[groan]
Honestly, I gave you plenty of
time.
And I even warned you that you
didn't have a whole lot of it
left.
How unfortunate.
Madara!
What kind of man are you?!
[spluttering]
Here it comes!
[slamming, yelling]
[smash]
[bash, thudding]
[growl]
[pow, scream]
My jutsu won't activate!
And my chakra is--!
I can't believe that we've been
stopped by the likes of him...!
Not good...that weird guy's
still blocking our way!
He's using Wood Style! Who is
he?!
I told you...I wouldn't let you
get beyond this point easily.
Plus,...is there seriously no
one out there who can give me an
answer to my question?
I asked you...what does it
feel like to poo?
Well,...I bet it's like the
refreshing feeling you get after
killing someone.
Five chakra natures, all at one
time?!
How do we counter that?
Yes, I see that!
[boom]
Impressive...Using the same
jutsu simultaneously as a
counterattack...
[inhale and exhale]
We're saved.
[chuckle] Yeah! Don't you dare
undersestimate Lord Third!
Then again, everyone's exhausted
most of their chakra.
The reanimated Lord Third is the
only one who's really still
ableto fight...
If Lord Third goes down, we're
toast...Forget Madara...We need
to do something about him.
To be honest, everyone needs to
start fighting as if Lady
Tsunade, Shizune, and I
aren't able to use
Medical Ninjitsu anymore.
We've been using big attacks in
this large-scale battle for too
long. And we haven't had a
chance to regroup!
We'll just have to trust young
Naruto to take care of Madara.
This could be our big chance,
Lor Orochimaru!
Not yet.
This enemy...
No way! No...!
Hey, shut up!
This just- It can't be!
What is it?
Sa-...Sa-
Something happened to Sasuke?!
It seems I should jump in sooner
after all...
[gasp]
Ino, what is it?
[gasp] Naruto...!
Huh?
What's that?!
I think it's Lord Gaara!
There they are.
Naruto!
There's no time to explain right
now.
Hokage, you must come with me!
Try to heal him as much as you
can en route.
I don't have enough chakra left
to perform Medical Ninjutsu.
Take Sakura instead.
I think she should be able to
help some.
What happened over there?!
Naruto!
How did he end up like this?!
Just come!
Don't waste time! I'll explain
later!
Sakura, get up on the sand!
Right!
What's going on now?
Is Naruto nearby?
Yeah! he's over there! Hey,
wait, can't you use your
Byakugan to see?
He took Madara down?
[gasps]
Naruto's heartbeat is...
...getting weaker and weaker!
Naruto!
[thud, heaving sobs]
Brother Neji,...please protect
Naruto!
Naruto Uzumaki...
Hmm?
He'll stubbornly cling to life
for a bit, since he's an
Uzumaki.
But trying to heal him now is
completely useless.
A Jinchuriki dies when the
Tailed Beast is extracted.
Can't get around that. It's an
absolute rule!
[kaboom]
[thud]
The simple fact that you possess
such eyes...
...proves that you've continued
to seek something despite many
great losses.
[groan]
But all of that ends right here.
You shall lose your very self.
You see, this is what they call
a true ending.
[moaning]
I have...
...always lied to you and
asked...
...for your forgiveness while
keeping you at a distance.
Because I wanted to keep you out
of this.
But now, I think...
That perhaps you...could have
changed Father,...Mother,...and
the rest of the Uchiha as well.
No matter what, I will love you
always.
[thud]
[groaning]
[plop]
I'm not dying.
I can't...
...die yet.
[yelling]
[plop]
[clunk]
I can't allow Itachi's life...to
have-[groan]
No matter what darkness or
contradictions lie within the
Village...
I'm still Itachi Uchiha of the
Leaf!
...been in vain!
Until I build...a true
village...And become a true
Kage...
I am not-
I'm not gonna die!
Hang in there! Don't give up!
You are so strong! You'll make
it! I know that you will!
[crying]
My chakra's almost all...!
[whimpering]
Sa-...Sasuke is--!
What's the matter, Karin?
Sasuke is really gonna-!
At this rate...
At this rate, Naruto is going
to...
...Die!
To think Naruto would end up
like this...!
Sakura,...I leave Naruto in your
hands!
He's always been our village's
symbol of hope.
Everyone always seems to keep
Naruto in their thoughts while
they're training!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The New Chunin Exams."
Yes, ever since that time...