(painful screaming)
Spill it! How were
you able to recreate
Neji's chakra?!
Of course. I get it
now! You use the chakra
that you absorb from
someone, and then you
copy that person and
their chakra! Is that
right?
As the war rages on,
the enemy uses a new
tactic: White Zetsu
clones infiltrate the
Allied Forces. A
barrier protects each
camp's perimeter,
making infiltration
difficult. But it
seems there might be
a weakness in the
barrier. Team eight
has come to
investigate it.
You know, guys, I think
we might have just walked
into something really
dangerous, here.
Yeah, but at least
it's clear for now.
This is the spot
where the barrier's
weak. This is where
the Zetsu are entering.
And there's bound to
be a lot of them. So
be careful.
Byakugan!
Kiba!
Fang over fang!
(painful grunt)
(attack grunt)
Hidden Jutsu:
Beetle Sphere!
Kiba!
How many of them
are there?!
Don't let them touch
you. That's because if
they do, they'll absorb
our chakra!
Easier said than done.
How can we take them
down without touching
them?!
I just sent out a
messenger owl. So the
sealing corps should
arrive here in a little
while to seal up
this mine.
And what, we're
just supposed to
wait until then?!
Oh, come on! Things
are just going from
bad to worse!
Hinata! Kiba!
Shino!
They're finally
here!
The Sealing Corps?
We'll start sealing
this place immediately!
So please, exit this way!
Quick! Stop them!
Man, they sure are
persistent! All right!
Fang over fang!
Careful! There's
oil on the ground!
Those are Paper
Bombs used for
mining!
Not good! They're
gonna explode!
Akamaru,
Dynamic
Marking!
(heavy coughing)
Are you doing
okay, Akamaru?!
This is terrible...
Is anyone there?!
Shino!
Hinata!
I'm over here.
Huh?
Oh, Shino! Good,
you're okay!
Yeah.
Where's Hinata?
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess those
Paper Bombs caught us
all a bit by surprise.
(sigh)
We'd better go
look for her,
then.
Kiba, couldn't you
locate her by her
scent?
No, I can't. The
smell of smoke is
too strong.
Hinata! Where
are you?!
At least I'm not
sensing the enemy
anymore. I guess
that explosion took
care of those
white guys. So
something good
came out of it.
With a blast that
strong, the exit
might have been
sealed off.
Huh? Kiba!
Huh?!
Are you okay?
Nah, it's no
good. He's dead.
Who's there?!
Kiba! Shino!
Hinata! You're
all right!
The ground gave way,
and I fell down to a
lower level beneath us.
Is that?!
I know, it's really
unfortunate. Wasn't
there another guy from
the Sailing Corps, though?
Maybe we can get to
him in time.
Yes, there was. Let's
find him and get out
of this place.
Right.
No, we can't
leave yet.
Hm? And why not?!
This shinobi didn't
die because of the
explosion. Rather, he
was fatally wounded
by a kunai.
You're absolutely
certain that he was
killed after the
explosion?!
Yes, I am. At least
one of the enemy
has survived.
They can absorb a
victim's chakra and
transform into them.
In all this confusion,
he'll be able to slip
right back in among
our forces and strike
at us again.
Are you saying
that one of us
is a fake?!
It's not
impossible.
There's no way!
All of us are on
the same team, here!
We'd be able to see
through a fake,
right?
I wonder about that.
Hinata, why aren't you
using your Byakugan?
Well, because, the
Sealing Team's barrier
jutsu was incomplete
when it was activated,
and it disrupted
my Byakugan.
Oh, did it now?
Wait, do you suspect
that Hinata's the
impostor?
Kiba, is it really
true that your nose
isn't working?
You suspect me, too?!
What about you? How
do we know you're
the real Shino?!
Because they didn't
lay a hand on me in
our earlier skirmish.
So what? They could
have gotten your chakra
from any number of your
insects!
That's true. There's
no way that I can
disprove that.
However, I am
the real me.
Yeah, and I'm the
real me, too!
And I'm really me!
This is a pointless
argument. That's
because none of us
can convince the
others that we are
truly ourselves.
Guess you're right!
But if we can't trust
each other, then I
say we should just
all go our separate
ways! I'll find the
other Sealing Corps
guy on my own! Akamaru!
(sad whine)
Kiba!
It seems that none
of us can trust the
others, and that
includes you and me.
(painful grunts)
Oh, thank goodness!
Can you give me a
hand, please?
(frightened gasp)
(painful screaming)
What happened?
It's the second
Sealing Corps
member...
How terrible...
This proves that
there's an impostor
among us.
What are you
doing, Kiba?
Don't play dumb! He
was gripping this
scrap of fabric
in his hand!
From the scent, it
came off your cloak!
Admit it! You're
the impostor Shino!
(gasp)
You're the one who
brought up fakes
in the first place!
I've had my doubts
about you all
along!
That fabric got
ripped off in the
explosion. And
besides, if I were
the fake, why
would I introduce
the ideas of there
being impostors!
You probably figured
that if you brought it
up first, no one would
suspect you!
But, damn it, I'm
not gonna fall for
that trick!
Now!
Hold it! If we let
the fake manipulate
us, we'll end up
killing each other!
That's what the
enemy wants! We're
playing right into
their hands!
There's one thing I
know for sure in this
situation. Only one
of us is a fake.
That's because if both
of them were impostors,
they could attack me
without hesitation.
Whichever of them it is,
they're waiting for me
and the other real one
to destroy each other.
Then what do you
intend to do? Just
stay here until
who knows when?!
I have only one
idea: Rock-Paper-
Scissors.
Huh?
Are you serious?
Rock-Paper-Scissors,
now?
Yes. The loser must
answer the questions
the other two pose.
But why couldn't we
just take turns
answering each
others questions?
No! Rock-Paper-
Scissors!
I don't get why
we'd bother to do
that, but okay...
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
I won...
What are your
favorite things?
Hm?
Well, I guess I like
beef jerky and going
on walks with Akamaru.
All right.
Again.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Rock-Paper-...
Listen, do we really
have to do the Rock-
Paper-Scissors part?
Yes we do. It's
the most important
part of all.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
I'm the one who
lost that time.
What are your
favorite things?
I like a lot of
things, but I guess
I like sweets the
best.
Come on, tell
the truth!
What's wrong! I
did tell the truth!
What you actually
like the best is
Naruto, right?
(gasp)
What?! Is this really
the kind of thing you're
going to ask me?!
Ha ha ha! I'm just
kidding, Hinata!
(kiba laughing)
Again.
I was just joking
around! Lighten up
a little, would you?
Let's just continue.
Okay, okay.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
That means you lost,
Shino, so here's my
question. And this is
something that only the
real Shino would
know the answer to!
The first time that
we went after Sasuke,
you were the only one
who was left behind.
How did you feel
about that?
I cannot answer
that question. Or
rather, I won't.
Come on, that isn't
fair! If you play like
that, then this entire
exercise is pointless!
If you want to know
the truth, then you're
going to have to take
me down.
Do what?!
There's real meaning
to be found in this.
You'll see...
Rock-Paper-
Scissors! Go!
I won again!
One more time.
Why do we have
to say it over
and over?
Because that is the
most critical part.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
It's your
turn, Shino!
No, the game
is over now.
What?! You can't
just go changing
the rules!
I've been thinking.
With Captain Yamato
held captive, it's
possible the enemy
has obtained
personal intel
on us.
Do you really
believe they'd
go so far as
to do that?!
Yes, of course. That's
because a major part
of their whole strategy
involves impersonating us.
And so, it's crucial
that they know the
thoughts and habits
of each person that
they might copy.
Huh! Makes sense when
you put it that way.
Does that mean that
everything we've been
doing here is
meaningless, then?
Don't make me
repeat myself.
Playing Rock-
Paper-Scissors
has a purpose.
I don't trust either
of you, after all.
I'll take both of
you down!
(attacking grunts)
Hey! Whose side
are you on, here!
Damn it! All
right, fine!
Let's go,
Akamaru!
Agh! Fang Over Fang!
Don't you worry,
Kiba! I'll be back
you up! I'm sure
that he's the phony!
(attacking grunt)
Gentle Fist!
I won't let
you get away!
These flames will
keep you from using
your insects!
Here I come! Take
this: Fang Over Fang!
(painful screaming)
Kiba...
Yes! We did it!
Now we can get out
of this cave!
That's true. But
only for me...
Huh?! What?!
Haahhh!
Akamaru!
Ta-dah!
The star of the
show appears!
No way! You were
the fake all along?!
I was getting really
nervous that you'd start
asking touchy questions
during that game.
But like your friend
said, the intel that we
got out of Yamato about
all of you has proved to
be invaluable. Because
of it, you guys have had
a falling out and saved
me a lot of trouble.
Ugh!
And with your mutt
down, even I can
beat you now!
So the Shino I fought
was the real one?!
I'm so stupid!
You're right!
You are stupid.
That's because
you're the real
Kiba.
And now you have
shown your true
colors.
(gasp)
No way! You're
still alive?! But
how can that be?!
Because of you, I
had to sacrifice
many of my precious
insects...
Your insects? Then
the one I defeated
was an Insect Clone?!
Exactly.
How did you ever
figure out that
I was the fake?!
I didn't figure it
out. I didn't know
who was the fake.
But still, I thought
about it after we
first faced each
other. Even if there
was a fake among us.
If it was possible for
the impostor to remain
transformed, would we
truly be able to fight
against each other
in earnest?
(painful grunt)
Gentle Fist!
Ahhh!
Then let's
finish him!
(painful screaming)
If we trust our
comrades, can we
really bring ourselves
to take them down?
Then I started
thinking about
something even
more ridiculous.
If I was going to be
defeated by someone
like that, then maybe
it was for the best.
And then, it
became clear.
I'd make it appear
that the real me had
been taken down. I was
certain that you'd
reveal yourself
after that happened.
That's why we played
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Rock-Paper-Scissors?
So they were
actually hand
signals.
But, why do we have
to say it over and
over?
Why? Because that is
the most critical part.
After he said that,
I started to figure
it out.
Earlier, the message
that you gave me was...
...Follow my
instructions.
And then,
after that...
If you want to know
the truth, then
you're gonna have
to take me down.
I wasn't entirely sure
what you meant to do,
but when you came at me
they way that you did,
I simply reacted
and then...
It worked out.
And all thanks to
you taking down
my Insect Clone.
You revealed
yourself.
And since you knew
my hand signals,
that meant you were
the real Kiba.
So you played a dirty
little trick on me,
huh? Fine, I'll just
take both of you down!
It's useless. And
that's because you are
completely at the mercy
of my jutsu already!
I'll avenge your
two victims!
Hidden Jutsu!
Beetle Tornado!
(painful screaming)
Thanks, Shino. You
did a great job
with that guy.
I must say, though, I
had serious misgivings
about fighting a comrade
with my full strength.
But you had no qualms
about using your Fang
Over Fang against me.
You're the one who
told me to do that!
And besides, you came
at me first, or did
you forget that part?!
I didn't know which of
you two was actually the
impostor, so I had to pick
one of you to attack.
Of course, there's
no way I'd attack
a girl.
Hnh! Quit trying to
act all chivalrous!
Wait, hold on a
minute! We brought
down the impostor...
But where's the
real Hinata?
(gasp)
Are you all
right, Hinata?
I'm fine, Kiba.
Akamaru, hi!
Oh, and Shino, too!
Always the last one...
(relieved sigh)
What happened
anyway?
Eh, nothing
much, really.
However, during this
incident, the most
closely guarded secret
of the Allied Shinobi
Forces was almost
leaked to the enemy.
What closely guarded
secret is that?
That you're in
love with Naruto.
(gasp)
What?! But
how did...?!
It slipped out when
Kiba was teasing you,
and then that Zetsu-
Why are you telling
her that?! Shut up,
idiot! It seems that
in order to impersonate
all of us better,
those White Zetsu
guys got a lot of
personal intel from
Captain Yamato!
Wait, does that mean
they know that secret?
The one that only
Captain Yamato knows?
Including the secret
from that time when I...
Even a secret
like this?
That's it! Then
we've got to destroy
all of them! Each
and every one!
Yeah!
Sasuke?! How are
you alive?!
Tell me where
Naruto is.
I don't know! But
you need to pay
attention to me
right now! Hmph!
My business is
with Naruto.
Damn it, not that
crap again! You
don't give a damn
about me, do you?!
No.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Aesthetics
of an Artist.
I'll wipe that smug
expression right
off your face!