[Foo]
It appears to be a jutsu,
where a plant-like clone
with no chakra latches
onto a life form.
And then feeds on
that host's chakra.
[Torune]
That's why even you
didn't notice it.
[Foo]
Most likely a ninjutsu
by that Akatsuki at
the Summit.
And?
The other one?
The one who's
been following us?
He's still tailing us,
and I think I know
who he is.
the Hidden Mist
Byakugan wielder.
That one eh?
There.
It'd be a stroke of luck
if he falls for this.
[Torune]
Those traps of yours
are quite special.
It'll work.
Whether he survives or dies,
We must make sure to get
his right eye.
Yes, sir!
Kisame Hoshigaki.
Pleased to meet you
after the fact.
Ki-sa-me... Ho-shi-ga-ki.
You've got ink in your mouth.
So The rumors are true.
you really are an octopus boy.
Now get ready, 'cause I'm gonna
make you weep! You sharky creep!
Wheeee!
A Tailed Beast cloak, with
only seven chakra tails!
That means he's not
completely serious yet!
Hey, did you know?
Did I know what?
In the wild, octopi eat sharks!
That blade dodged him!
Bee!
That blade siphoned off
Bee's chakra again,
and it's grown even bigger!
It appears that this time, the
shark shall devour the octopus.
That sword Sharkskin's
got a big appetite, and
it's a speed-eater.
But it can only devour
six tails' worth of
chakra at a time, huh?
If that's the situation with
this version, my next version
should do the trick.
This is the first time
Samehada has ever
grown this big before,
and the delight it's feeling
isn't trivial, either.
What'll you do, Bee?
[Eight-Tails]
I'll help. Enter
Tailed Beast State!
[Mizukage]
Based on the marking
pattern here,
Ao's that way.
Let's hurry
ahead quickly.
Yes, ma'am!
The Tailed Beast vs.
The Tailless Tailed Beast
You need to watch over
my body soon, Torune.
A booby-trap, huh?
It's one of Danzo's.
Uhh??
What?! Why am I
seeing my own body?!
'Cause I got you.
What's going on?
Mind Transfer
Puppet Curse Jutsu.
Damn it! That object curses
whoever attacks it, activating
a Mind Transfer Jutsu!
That's right. Your consciousness
is sealed inside that puppet.
I'm in possession of your body.
And now I will
retrieve what's ours.
Of course, I
should have known.
Forget it. Only we Hidden Mist
ANBU, the Shinobi Tracking Unit,
can undo that Barrier Ninjutsu.
The Mist will do anything to
protect this precious Byakugan.
Don't think you'll
reclaim it easily.
So it automatically
activates when danger
threatens the eye, huh?
That's quite an appropriate
jutsu for one of your kind.
The Undertaker Squad.
And I didn't think
it would be easy.
Taking your eye means that I,
as the jutsu caster, will lose
my eye as well. You know that.
That was Danzo's order?
What does he think his
subordinates are?
[Foo]
If the Mist's military power
is diminished because of it,
losing one of my eyes is
a cheap price to pay.
Although thanks to your barrier,
that's not going to happen.
But there are plenty
of other options.
Enter Tailed Beast State, Bee!
No way, fool, ya fool!
Merge with you and each attack
will have too much power and
destroy the whole area.
[Bee]
Master Kin and Ponta are
here with us, don't forget.
Plus, I finally managed to
sneak off under the radar.
If I let you out, it's
like setting off a Killer
Bee is here beacon!
It's not like you to
make excuses, Bee!
So what are you going to do?
Fight in Version 2 State?
Yeah, man!
Except, most of my chakra got
taken away, during those last
few exchanges with Kisame.
so you're gonna have to lend
me some of yours, okay?
Yegh.
[Eight-Tails]
If it weren't for me, you'd have
already lost a long time ago.
A cheeky personality, but I'm
grateful for your hospitality!
Yeeeah!
Eh?
Going into Tailed Beast State?
No, this is Tailed
Beast's power that's
trapped in humanoid form.
It's Version 2 State!
[Bee]
Lariat!
Samehada's so excited,
it's tripping over itself.
The earlier chakra's
nothing compared to this
volume and quality.
I'm amazed he can
control this much chakra
without losing his mind.
Samehada can't devour
this much chakra!
Yeeahh!
Yes, you did it!
[Bee]
Can't believe I was reduced
to Version 1 State.
He's still alive!
Hurry up and
finish him off!
Heh. Well, you've
certainly done it now.
Huh?
What's going on?!
The thing about me is,
the stronger my opponent is,
the stronger I become as well.
I will not tire.
I will not fall.
That blade of his steals
his enemy's chakra and
transfers it to its master
in the form of stamina!
That's right. And that's
why I have often been called
the Tailless Tailed Beast.
Water Style! Super Exploding
Water Shock Wave!
What are you plotting?
I'm simply going to jump
down now and behead you.
If I can't remove your eye,
I'll just take your whole
head back to the Leaf.
You'd kill yourself?!
No. I'll undo the Mind
Transfer Jutsu just before
the blade hits your neck.
Either way, you'll die. And then
once I'm back in my own body,
I can simply retrace my steps
here to grab your head.
Fine. But you'd
better be careful.
Or else you'll fail.
What does that mean?
If you get nervous and undo your
jutsu even a second early, I'll
be able to dodge that scythe!
If I'm not dead,
You're going to have a serious
fight on your hands when you
return to grab my head.
Hmpf.
[panting]
Thanks, you
saved me.
What's going on?
An enemy's jutsu.
I couldn't move
my body at all.
If not for you,
I'd be dead.
Whew. That was way too
close for comfort!
I'm sorry if I
made you worry.
So you couldn't move?
Must have been a
genjutsu or something.
A type of Mind
Transfer Jutsu.
Your right eye. It looks
like the enemy was after
your Byakugan.
And they almost succeeded
in destroying it.
I'm sorry, but can
you untie me now?
Of course.
I'll also undo that jutsu
protecting your right eye.
Great. Thank you.
That would help a lot.
Hm?
I wonder what that is?
No! Don't!
He hasn't undone the
Mind Transfer Jutsu yet!
She fell for it.
If she undoes the
jutsu, I couldn't
ask for better.
I can destroy the
Byakugan and then undo
the Mind Transfer Jutsu.
This chakra belongs to
that Sensory Type ninja
from the Leaf. This was
his plan all along!
No! Lady Mizukage!
There you go!
Lady Mizukage?
Hand me
Hiramekarei,
Chojuro.
But, why?
This man is not Ao.
I'm not able to undo the jutsu
protecting that right eye.
And the real Ao would
know that very well.
Besides, Ao would
never apologize in
front of Chojuro.
You sniffed me out.
you old witch.
G'aaahh!
Ungh!
But I was not the one,
Who said that, m'lady.
Oh, good. You're back
to normal, are you?
I'll kill him!
That Sensory type
Leaf ninja...
Good thing it was only her
hand and not Hiramekarei,
you were lucky!
Foo.
Well, then?
Forgive me, sir.
But I have failed
my mission.
It could not be helped.
[Kisame]
The longer this battle drags on,
the more chakra will
be shaved from you and
the weaker you'll get.
And the stronger I will become,
as I feed off your chakra.
Bee! You've got to steal
his blade away from him!
That sword is the
key to his strength!
Hee he he he he he!
Huh?
[Kisame]
You can take it.
If you can rip it out
of my body, that is.
What?! He merged
with his blade?!
[Bee]
It's like he's become a fish
human. Or is it a human fish?
Bee! Focus! Be
more concise and
save your breath!
He's a merman!
You ready? Here I come!
[Bee]
At this rate, Master Kin
and Ponta will drown.
First thing's first, I've got
to get them out of the water!
Huah!
[Kisame]
You cannot escape from
this Water Style.
Besides, in this environment,
I have the clear advantage
over you.
[Bee]
I can't see the boundary!
So much water! So crazy!
[Kin]
Bee, behind you!
Mm?
These circumstances
are hunky-dory!
I won't be taken
down, sorry!
[Eight-Tails]
No time for your
ridiculous rhymes!
The water bubble is in motion.
And that half-fish guy is at the
center! Pay attention!
He's faster than
you in the water.
Plus, he can probably
breathe underwater
with his gills!
If you just run around,
he'll catch and kill you.
So what
should I do?
You're the Akatsuki's
target, Bee!
[Eight-Tails]
Leave that Enka geezer and
the raccoon and swim in
the opposite direction!
He'll chase after you!
[Bee]
Oh, yeah! Then
they'll be safe.
[Eight-Tails]
Yes, As he chases after you, the
water bubble will move with him.
So they've got to fall
out of it at some point.
Good! Now come this way!
What?!
My orders are to capture
the Eight Tails alive.
But there's no rule against
killing these two along the way!
Not gonna happen,
you fool!
Wha--?!
Gotcha!
Suckers?!
[Bee]
Now I got you! I'm not giving
you my chakra for free forever!
Fool, ya fool!
[Kisame]
You're truly worthy of
being called the
epitome of Jinchuriki.
Changing just a part of you into
your Tailed Beast is impressive.
All right, they're out.
(om struggling to breathe cough)
You seem to be having
trouble breathing.
Getting to the end of
your air supply?
You had a good idea there,
but as long as our bodies are
touching, I will continue to
drain your chakra away.
I can feel Samehada trembling
with joy. It has discovered its
favorite kind of chakra ever!
No one in the Akatsuki
is as good as I am at
taking prey alive!
This Water Prison
Shark Dance Jutsu,
shaves away your chakra
until you're barely alive.
Trying to gauge an opponent's
limits is particularly fun.
Although, I do occasionally
blunder and go too far.
At this rate, I have
to use Lariat again.
Got to time it
just right.
No! You can't match his
speed in the water.
And he's raised his
guard because you
used the octopus legs!
Just retreat for now!
[Eight-tails]
Use cover!
Eh?
It's ink.
A smokescreen, eh?
He really is an octopus lout.
However...
With my body merged to
Samehada like this, I can
detect chakra through my skin.
And now I believe your
chakra is close to zero.
[heavy breathing]
Bee!
Ngh!
I'm coming!
Bee!
Eight Tails turned out
to be disappointing.
It would be bothersome if you
regained consciousness and
went into Tailed Beast State.
So I think I'll remove
your legs just to be safe.
He stole away most
of my chakra, too!
Damn it! Get up, Bee!
[Eight-Tails]
This is really bad!
Although my blade
doesn't cut cleanly!
What?! What's the matter?
Gaahh!
Don't tell me you've become
attached to the Eight-Tails?
You've really taken that
much of a liking to his
chakra, Samehada?
[gasp of life]
Giving him chakra
it stole from me?!
Very well, shall we make it a
fair trade, weapon for weapon?
Heh heh. This will do fine.
It looks like it has
a nice, sharp edge!
Now's my chance!
A pencil?!
That was so close!
Not close enough for you!
That's what you were
trying to get, huh?
Bee. I'm sorry
we're late.
My brother!
The Raikage?!
How'd you find us?
[Cee]
Such a giant bubble of
water is visible even
to the naked eye.
And I could sense the
Eight-Tails' and Bee's
chakra mixed up in it.
[Darui]
You really went to town
absorbing someone else's chakra
and using it for yourself.
It was way too obvious.
Found out, after all.
Ngh!
Damn Samehada.
It's giving Eight-Tails
more chakra!
Let's do it.
Okay, my Brother!
Water Style! Super Shark Bomb!
[Raikage & Bee]
Double Lariat!
I must say, you
two sure are fast.
Hmph.
Hey, bro!
Y'aghh!
How dare you go wandering
off on your own!
Even your non-dominant arm
does me a lot o' harm,
so sound the alaaaaaarm!
[Gaara]
This is also a battle
to protect you.
[Gaara]
Naruto, you once told me that
you would become Hokage one day.
[Gaara]
Well, I've become Kazekage.
If you've truly resolved to
become a Kage, Then you're
going to have to do what needs
to be done as Sasuke's friend.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"As One's Friend."
[Gaara]
I will make sure to
protect you at all costs.