[gasp]
I didn't know Lee continued
with that training...
[Thinking]
We are in the middle
of the Chunin Exams...
...What are they thinking?
Shira! I will show
you how serious I am!
I really should warn you,
Shira's super strong, you know!
[building power grunt]
I have become super
strong, too!
I believe this is going
to be my last fight.
Last fight...?
Here I come!
No way! Their speed's
incredible!
A battle between two powerful
fists is not something you
get to see very often.
He stopped my
jutsu...
He blocked every one?
I would have liked to
fight him, too...
Amazing! I have not faced a
taijutsu user this strong since
Guy Sensei and Neji!
He has great technique. I feel
his passion in every punch.
Lee&the intensity of your
training shines through!
[grunt]
Lee! I'm very grateful to you.
Huh...?!
You see, it's all because of
you that I can be a shinobi.
Back then, Lord Gaara
said to me...
I've met someone like you. He's
a shinobi from the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
Through sheer perseverance, he
has become a fine shinobi.
And Shira...I think you'll be as
splendid a shinobi as he is.
It might've been your fists
that changed Lord Gaara.
Not true! That
was not my doing.
[grunt] Instead, it was
your perseverance that
moved Lord Gaara.
Lee, I'll show you my
gratitude in earnest!
Yes, well said!
That is the creed of those
dedicated to taijutsu!
They really seem
to be enjoying this.
Maybe Lee has finally
met someone he can
consider a true rival.
You can only go so
far training alone.
But to surpass your limits,
you need...a rival.
Oh...? Do you have
a rival, Neji?
My rival...?
It may be the Hyuga way to cave
in to destiny, it's not mine!
If you think it's futile to
fight, then don't! Just
stand there and take it!
I'll change the way
of the Hyuga clan...
After I become Hokage!
You're the only one
who can be my rival&
So hurry up and come
home, Naruto!
Neither of them has
delivered a decisive blow.
They're just sizing each
other up right now.
Huh? They're not fighting at
their full potential?!
(Neji)
More like fifty percent.
But how much can a body endure?
If they stay evenly matched...
No...They are not quite equal.
Huh? What do you
mean, they aren't?
They're equal in speed
and in the number of
moves that they possess...
...But Shira's physique is
much bigger than Lee's.
(Neji)
In boxing, weight influences
the intensity of the blow...
...They may look evenly matched,
but with Lee's smaller build.
So Lee's sustaining
more damage?
I'd say that he should
be feeling the effects
very soon...
Blow for blow, Shira's punches
are harder than mine!
At this rate...
Lee...!
The stance he's in...
Don't tell me Lee
plans to use the Lotus!
It's too risky!
But he is an opponent who
is worth that risk!
[power yell]
Yaa!!
No way! The First Gate
will not open! Why?!
You hit my Chakra Points and
stopped the flow of my chakra!
As a taijutsu user, too, I know
your strengths and weaknesses.
And that you're versed in the
Hidden Jutsu the Eight Inner
Gates!
[grunt]
From now on, I mean business!
Shira's switched his mode!
He's getting serious now!
Let's go, Lee!
What's happening?!
Suddenly his attacks are
relentless and accurate!
This is--!
[gasp]
The sound!
What sound?
Shira's attacks are
totally silent!
We taijutsu users are able to
counter supersonic moves because
we've honed all our 5 senses...
...one of which is hearing.
I remember...
...Lee said he once fought a
shinobi from the Hidden Sound
who gave him a hard time!
This time, it's the
exact opposite!
Shira is making
no noise at all!
Yeah, but... how?
Byakugan!
Now I see! It's the
theory of the owl.
What? The owl?
Yes. Did you know owls can
fly without making a sound?
Owls have special comb-like
feathers that muffle the sound
of their flapping wings.
Using chakra that only
works with taijutsu,
he's cloaked himself with the
same type of feathers.
To come up with something like
that all on his own...
What a waste for someone
like that to be an enemy.
[grunt]
Silent Fist! See if you
can handle this!
[grunt] How can I...?
All the effort is pointless
unless you believe in yourself.
[Rock Lee's Thoughts]
Yes! I have trained and worked
just as hard as Shira has!
Nine hundred ninety-nine!
One thousand!
[panting breaths]
And now we will do one
thousand sit-ups!
What?! Seriously?!
Seriously!
Wait, wait, wait! Just hold
on, there, Lee, all right?
Enough bodybuilding!
I think we all have to accept
that you're in far better
physical condition than we are!
Yes, but. Guy Sensei, I
have never beaten you
or Neji even one time!
Yes! That's because you haven't
been using your noggin!
What does using my head
have to do with taijutsu?
A lot!
'Cause mental visualization is a
fundamental part of taijutsu.
Before I weave a sign,
I'm already seeing a
hundred moves ahead.
What!?
Is such a thing
even possible?!
Of course! Through visualization
alone, thanks in part to
fighting Kakashi so many times,
I can see as far as one thousand
moves ahead.
Th-that far?
[laughter]
Wait, is that true?
Who knows?
For example, if I were to come
at you and attack with a
right Seiken Fist...
Lee...what would your fiftieth
move after that be?
Huh?
What technique is your fiftieth
move going to be?
My technique&?
Maybe...
A right-hand thrust!
No. Wrong.
Well, then&A clockwise kick!
Correct! So what's your
hundredth move?!
Let me see... Hm.
Perhaps a left heel kick!
Wrong! The answer's a
counter-clockwise kick.
Huh?
Watch, I'll prove it
to you right now!
Ready?
Hm!
Hiya!
Forty-eight,...forty-nine...
[gasp]
(Guy Sensei)
Continue!
Whoa, Sensei was
right all along!
Ninety-eight,...
ninety-nine... One Hundred!
He's right again!
I get it...! Sensei's
making it happen!
[panting]
That is amazing, Guy Sensei!
So what is your trick?
It isn't a trick. I simply made
you move the way that I wanted
you to.
That's it. There
is no more.
You made me move...?!
That's right! I just used
counters that forced you into
making certain moves.
In battle, there's a sequence to
techniques and jutsu.
When you control that flow,
predicting what comes next
isn't hard at all.
Just now, I controlled the
flow of my opponent,
who though more physically fit
than me, lost steam before I
did!
It is true! Guy Sensei, you
are not even breathing hard!
By controlling the flow
of our battle,
I was able to deplete your
stamina while preserving my
energy.
There aren't many chances to
take down a foe in the midst
of battle.
All attack strategies are
just attempts to create
such a chance!
And that's what I meant
by using your head!
[Rock Lee Thinking]
That is right!
From opponents I have faced
before, I pretty much know the
patterns Shira will use.
All I need to do is control the
sequence of my opponent's moves.
Then, even if his moves are
silent, I can anticipate his
fist.
Yes!
How did--?
Lee isn't getting
hit anymore!
It seems that Lee finally
remembered that training
session.
He's countering so fast! I can't
wait to see when you're giving
it your all, Lee!
[grunt]
[Thinking]
He missed the chakra points...
...What is going on?
Was it by chance?
Guy Sensei would be able to
activate the Sixth Gate
instantly.  Even if I cannot...
[strength building roar]
Now! The Third Gate
of Life! Open!
He went straight to
the Third Gate?!
He's trained that
far? I had no idea!
So that's one of the rumored
Eight Inner Gates...
Well then...
[strength building roar]
Seven Heavenly Breaths!
First Activation!
Second Activation!
Third Activation!
What is he doing?!
It's a taijutsu breathing
method Shira invented himself.
He inhales large amounts of
oxygen to invigorate his whole
body.
When he's performing this
technique, his lung capacity
increases by nearly four times!
So it's his version of the
Eight Inner Gates, huh?
No way. He thought of
that on his own?!
Those two really
drive home the fact...
...that there is no
limit to perseverance.
No kidding!
Lee! Shira! Do your
best, both of you!
Here I come, Shira!
Good!
Not yet!
Fourth Gate of Pain! Open!
Fifth Gate of Closing! Open!
Argh!!
So this is what you're like
when you're serious!
My chakra...My sound-muffling
feathers are getting blown away!
I'm starting to hear the
sound of your wings!
[grunt]
Leaf Hurricane!
I'm not done...
His wound's opened
up again! Shira!
Shira!
Are you okay, Shira?!
I'm fine...
Well, I guess that we will
have to postpone this match.
Lee, I envy you.
I wish that I could
have trained under
Guy Sensei, too.
Shira, why did you
release my Chakra Points?
So you noticed?
I wanted to fight you when you
could give one hundred percent.
As I expected,
you're very strong...
...It was a great experience.
What are you saying?
You were too reckless!
Shira. I want you to have this.
Guy Sensei gave it to me long
ago. This is what helped me
become strong.
It is unique, with superior
breathability and wicking
properties,
and it lets you move easily!
You will definitely feel a
difference!
And you will love it
immediately!
Wear this and it will be
like we are brothers!
Thank you, Lee. I accept it.
Shira, you said earlier that
this would be your last fight.
Over in the Land of Wind,
there's a battalion that guards
the northern border.
That battalion never leaves its
station. The environment there
is extremely harsh,
so there are hardly any
candidates for the position.
It's my intention to go
and volunteer for it if
I pass these Exams.
[grunt]
It's by my hometown.
My parents are sick. I
want to be near them.
Which means that I probably
won't see any of you again
after this.
I understand how it is...
Shira, I really had no idea!
I guess that I won't see
you around either, Yome.
You're gonna follow Shira
and go with him, right?
[flustered squeals]
I don't have any regrets about
my life whatsoever.
But I'm certain it would have
been a lot more interesting if
I'd had a friend like you in it.
I am going to remember that as
your greatest compliment to me!
That's just how I mean
it-as a compliment, Lee.
(Rock Lee)
Now we have both scrolls!
Then let's head
straight for home base!
Two Heaven scrolls...When should
I break it to them...?
(Sand Proctor)
According to reports from the
investigative team,
two members of the Hidden
Waterfall's Team Fuu, Tocchi
and Kun, are not genin.
It's believed they're jonin
named Kegon and Yourou.
Damn Hidden Waterfall...
What are they up to...?
Hold on...
Huh?
I'll handle this
situation myself.
-What?
Keep this information
between us only.
-But, sir...!
The Second Exam will
continue uninterrupted.
Got it?
What's Lord Gaara thinking?!
It'll be sundown soon.
Yeah...From here, we can
sense the enemy right away.
It's the perfect
spot to make camp.
Hey, where's Fuu?
Huh...? She was here
just a second ago&!
[groan]
Fuu!
That brat! She's so impulsive.
[gasp] What is she...?!
Poke-poke!
[gasp]
Huh...
Fuu!
Huh?
Don't run off like that!
Damn it! What if someone from
another village attacked you?
You're extremely valuable
to the Hidden Waterfall!
Okay, I get it! Be right there!
Damn it, guys! If you
make a fuss, you're gonna
get us found out.
Fuu...
So she's a...
(Kiba)
Cool trick, huh?
I wanna try to wrap things
up in a seriously cool way
for the Second Exam.
(Hinata)
I think that's a good idea!
It's kind of like something
Naruto would do, or...
(Kiba)
This has nothing to do with him!
(Hinata)
I wonder where Naruto and Master
Jiriaya are training...
(Kiba)
Let's focus on passing
these Chunin Exams.
That way we can get
a leg up on him.
(Shino)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Escape vs. Pursuit."
(Kiba)
Let's go, Kurenai's Team 8!