[bubbling]
-What is that?
-That's what Master
Jiraiya was talking about.
The Nine-Tailed
Fox spirit's cloak.
-[yells]
-That's the
Jinchuuriki's power, huh?
No wonder his punches
have such impact.
-It burns.
-Listen carefully, Kakashi.
At some point the
Nine-Tail's chakra
may leak out of Naruto's
body and literally
take on the form of
the beast inside him.
-You're serious?
The chakra will
take on its shape?
-Well actually, it's
more like a cloak.
-The Nine-Tail's cloak, huh?
I see.
-If the cloak should ever
appear again, take caution.
-Huh?
-Now listen.
You have to stop it
while there's one tail.
Wait any longer and you'll see
something you wish you hadn't.
[crashing]
[MUSIC - NOBODYKNOWS, "HERO'S
COME BACK!!"]
[groaning]
-Already, huh?
Easy, Naruto.
He's not thinking rationally.
It'll be dangerous to
try to get close to him.
JIRAIYA: If the need
should arise, use this.
It'll suppress all the chakra
in his body immediately.
-Well, it looks like
we're going to be OK.
[panting]
-Are you all right now, Naruto?
Master Jiraiya, what
on earth did you see?
-Well, that was
certainly interesting.
Someone's coming.
[panting]
-Finally caught up to you.
-Sakura.
-You found us.
Nice work.
-We felt a huge tremor
a few minutes ago.
-I'm glad you're here.
So you guys did it?
-Yeah.
-It looks like you're still
having some trouble here
though.
-Unfortunately.
-What about Gaara?
Where's he?
All right.
-I don't believe it.
Sosari was beaten by that
little brat and the old hag.
Leaving a thing of eternal
beauty for the future?
Yeah right.
All he did was get killed.
He was over confidant
about that puppet,
even though it fully
exposed his weakness.
Oh well.
It was still an ending
worthy of an artist.
-Good work, Neji.
Good work, Neji.
-Heh.
Child's play, actually.
-I get it.
Byakugan.
One of the kekkei
genkai of the Leaf.
Just like the Sharingan.
You used those eyes
of yours to sneak up
from my blind spot, hm?
This is my first time
seeing it in person.
I'd be curious to
see how it differs
from Itachi's Sharingan.
But I think my escaping takes
precedence at the moment.
-Ha.
You're looking at Team
Guy here, my friend,
the number one
squad in The Leaf.
You're not going anywhere.
-That is a promise.
-I hope you're ready.
-It's Guy's team.
-Not bad.
-Severe Leaf Hurricane.
-Look like I won't be
able to outrun them.
-Here I come.
-Eight Trigrams Air Palm.
-[grunts]
-Persistent bunch, aren't they?
Hm.
Now where was it?
Down there.
-He's dropping.
-Watch it.
We don't know what
he's planning.
Stay on your guard.
-Roger.
-Be careful, everyone.
He's a long range fighter
who uses explosives.
[chewing]
-I think it's about
time I revealed
my ultimate work
of art. [swallows]
-He's concentrating all of his
chakra into a single point.
Oh no.
Everyone get out of
here immediately!
-Art is an explosion!
-We're never going to make it.
-What's going on?
-It worked.
Just in time.
-Sensei.
Hey, are you all right?
-I'd expect no
less from my rival.
-I don't get it.
What did you do?
-Sent the explosion off
into a different space.
-You sent it somewhere?
-The Sharingan's visual jutsu.
-I am not sure I
understand really,
but it seems the enemy
has been defeated, Tenten.
Do you agree?
-What the-- are you kidding?
What the hell are
you asking me for?
-More importantly,
is everyone OK?
-Sakura, can you?
Sakura.
[crying]
-Why?
Why is it always Gaara?
If he dies like this--
He's the Kazekage.
He just became the Kazekage.
-Try to calm yourself,
Naruto Uzamaki.
-You shut up!
Just shut up!
If all of you Sannin
shinobi hadn't
put a monster inside of
Gaara then none of this
would have ever happened to him.
Did you ever even
consider how Gaara felt?
Did you ever even ask?
Calling us Jinchuuriki.
What gives you the
right to label us?
Who are you to decide
someone else's fate?
[sobbing]
-Naruto.
-I couldn't save Sasuke.
And I can't save Gaara either.
For three years I've trained so
hard but nothing has changed.
[sobbing]
-Lady Chiyo.
That jutsu.
Lady Chiyo.
[MUSIC - ALUTO, "MICHI TO YOU
ALL"]
-Up until now everything
I've done has been wrong.
But at least here
in my final hour
I can find finally do
something right for a change.
All of the elder generations'
failures in the Sand
and in the Leaf can
now be put behind us.
May the future that
awaits you be different
from the way things
were in our time.
-Next time, "The Legacy!"
[MUSIC - ALUTO, "MICHI TO YOU
ALL"]
-Today's subject is an event
that shook the Leaf Village
to its core, the attack of
the Nine-Tailed Fox spirit.
The aptly named Nine-Tailed Fox
is a creature out of legend.
No one really knows
why it attacked,
but it brought
the greatest power
in all the five great nations to
the very brink of destruction.
The village was saved from
this unprecedented crisis
by the fourth Hokage.
In exchange for his
own life, the fourth
sealed the Nine-Tailed Fox away
within the newly born Naruto
Uzamaki.
Judging by the type
of seal, the Hokage
likely believed Naruto would one
day be a powerful shinobi who
could use the Nine-Tail's power
for the good of the village.
So you're shouldering a
heavy responsibility, Naruto.
-An order of miso ramen.
-Well, once step
at a time, I guess.
-Don't hold back on the pork.