-You came.
-Yeah.
Are you all right?
-Yes.
-Hold on.
Why are you here?
You worried about Hotaru, too?
-Hardly.
It was just coincidence.
Besides, these guys
didn't come for Hotaru.
-What do you mean?
Those guys, who are they?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): That mask.
I see.
Their real target is--
-Master!
-Why are the Hidden Leaf here?
-I'm going to need you
to let that girl go.
-No.
-OK, then.
If that's how you
want it, then we'll
just take her back by force!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll.
-I'll take the
guy in the middle.
You take the guys on
either side of him,
and we'll attack together.
-Got it, but these ANBU--
-We'll let it play out.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
We need to find out
what they're doing here.
-Master--
-Hidden Jutsu, Kirisame.
-What the heck's with this rain?
-It's a jutsu that dissolves
any chakra it touches.
It's called Kirisame.
-Why, you--
-Go.
-Stop it!
Back off!
-Let's go.
-Water whip!
-Wood Style Jutsu!
-Master!
No!
-That'll keep you
quiet for a while.
-What the hell are you doing?
-Naruto!
Wait.
Our team's on assignment.
We've been charged with
keeping that girl safe.
Please return her to us.
-That's right!
Hand her over!
-You ninja, you're ANBU Black
Ops from the Hidden Mist.
And you're after this man.
Isn't that right?
-They're ANBU Black Ops?
Wait a second.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I get it now.
Then that Utakata is--
-Then Utakata must be
listed in the bingo book
as a rogue ninja, and these men
have come here to capture him.
-So let me get this straight.
Those ANBU Black Ops guys
aren't here for Hotaru.
They want him.
-She has nothing to do with you.
Please release her.
-How about a deal?
We'll trade her for him.
-No.
We can't make that deal.
-What?
-She seems to be very
attached to this man.
If we simply let
you take him away,
there's no doubt
she'll follow you.
She'll be in danger,
and we'll be in trouble.
So we can't turn
him over to you.
-Then we won't give give her up.
-If we're forced to
resort to battle,
our actions could
have far reaching
effects, even full scale war.
Are you willing to risk that?
-The Hidden Mist?
-Captain Yamato?
MALE VOICE: Men of
the Hidden Leaf.
-Huh?
-I'm the commander of this unit.
Talk to me.
I'm Tsurugi, head of the
Hidden Mist ANBU Black Ops.
It's certainly not our desire
to escalate this impasse
into a war between our nations.
Perhaps it is still
possible to negotiate?
-It is.
I'm listening.
-I know you.
-Let us meet alone.
Just the leaders of
our two teams, I mean.
And Utakata, as well.
-I'll agree to that.
You two, stay right here.
[theme music]
-Then we're in agreement.
Until you complete your
mission with the girl,
we will postpone
apprehending Utakata.
-As soon as her safety is
guaranteed, I'll notify you.
-Keep in mind that
should you fail
to honor the agreement
that we've made here today,
war between our nations
may be inevitable.
-I understand.
-You guys are too much.
I'll be doing
exactly as I please.
-I don't think so.
Until our mission ends,
you will remain with us
under our supervision.
After that, what you do is
between you and the Hidden
Mist.
-Very well.
-Tell me, just what
did you do, Utakata?
-That information is
none of your business.
-My apologies.
-I wish to speak
with him alone now.
-All right.
I'll wait over there.
-What happened?
-How'd it go?
-Oh, well enough.
-Where are they?
-They're having a
private discussion.
-Is it true?
I mean, is Utakata
really a rogue ninja?
-Yeah.
-Look, don't cause us trouble.
Just surrender,
and come back home.
-Why would I do that?
Why would I go back
just to get killed?
-The village has changed.
Our old nickname
no longer applies.
We're not the Blood
Mist Village now.
Things even seem peaceful.
But the balance of power
between the five great nations
remains extremely
tenuous and delicate.
The importance of what you
possess increases, and research
into its use has also increased.
The village needs that
power, so you definitely
won't be killed if you return.
Trust me.
-I don't think I can
trust anyone anymore.
Master, no!
Please stop.
Please!
[scream]
-You know why.
My master tried to kill me.
And that thing
that's inside me--
-Boar, boar, monkey,
rat, snake, snake--
[scream]
-Without question, I sacrificed
myself for the village.
I trusted my master, and
did all that he said.
And in return, he betrayed
me and tried to kill me.
[scream]
-What?
This power!
Wait!
No!
No, stop!
Stop!
[roar]
-No, Utakata.
You're wrong.
Harusame did not
try to kill you.
You must believe me.
It wasn't like that at all.
He performed that terrible
ritual not to bring you harm,
but to separate
that thing from you.
He was trying to save you.
-You actually think
I'm going to buy that?
You're either lying,
or you've grown senile.
-It's true.
-My master-- no, that man
used me and tried to kill me,
and that's all there is to it.
And then, as a result,
he ended up dying.
If you ask the villagers,
they'll all say that I killed
him, even if I didn't.
-Please, Utakata,
just come home.
Then you can see
everything for yourself,
and you'll know that
I'm not lying to you.
-No thanks.
-Then we'll have no
choice but to kill you.
You know that.
-Do as you please.
And I shall do as I please, too.
-You're all right!
-Let her go.
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, master.
-That's enough!
I told you already,
never call me that again.
Do you understand?
-Men of the Hidden
Leaf, as agreed,
we will retreat for now.
Let us hope that both our
missions will be successful.
However, we will
continue to watch
you to make sure that
you honor our pact.
-Understood.
-Farewell.
Scatter!
-That was fun.
Now, then, where do you
think we should go from here?
-I believe that it would be best
if we avoid Tsuchigumo Village.
-Yes, Sai, you're right.
It's quite clear now the
place is no longer secure.
Hotaru couldn't be
kept safe there.
Perhaps we should return to Mt.
Katsuragi.
There we'll be able to plan
what our next move will be.
-I'd like to go back, too.
I want to make sure
that Tonbee's OK.
-But the ones who came
after the forbidden jutsu
may also return there.
It could be unsafe, as well.
Let's meet up with
Tonbee and Sakura,
then decide a course of action.
And Utakata, you're
coming with us, too.
-Hey, you OK?
-I wonder why he doesn't
want me to call him master?
-A monstrous crime.
He killed his own master, and
then fled from the village.
HOTARU (VOICEOVER):
What could have happened
between Sir Utakata
and his own master?
NARUTO: There's no
way we can know what's
going on with Utakata
and the Hidden Mist.
But still, I don't
think that's important.
I mean, if you've
already decided
you want to be his
student, it doesn't matter.
-It does.
I have to become strong,
and restore my clan's honor.
So I have to learn from him.
-I know what you mean.
You just want him to teach
you everything he knows.
-Well, it's not quite like that.
-Yeah.
I felt something
similar, myself.
I don't remember my parents.
Not one bit.
-Oh?
-Maybe that's why when I
traveled with the Pervy Sage,
I wondered if that's
what it really
felt like to have a father.
And I'll admit it, I
acted like a spoiled brat
with him sometimes.
But the thing is,
training isn't easy.
Not by a long shot.
You have to think things
through for yourself,
and you have to learn the
techniques by yourself.
Otherwise, you'll
never get any better.
If Pervy Sage hadn't
been my teacher,
I wouldn't have even
figured out the basic stuff.
You're not alone.
The thought that someone's
near, that they're
watching over you, that
can make you stronger.
-I understand.
I really envy you, Naruto.
So just like you say,
I'm going to think
of Sir Utakata as my master.
-Huh?
Hey, you look pale.
-No, I'm-- I'm OK.
-Huh?
Hey.
Hotaru-- you're burning up.
And you're hurt, too.
Is that from the fight?
Captain Yamato!
-Let me.
I need some medicinal herbs.
Let me see.
The dokudami plant should
be abundant nearby,
around where it's damp.
A purple plant, with
leaves shaped like a heart.
-The purple is underneath
the leaves, right?
-Yes, that's right.
-Got it.
-So, what's wrong?
-Hotaru's ill.
Please, leave it to me.
-All right.
-If that plant grows
best in damp areas,
I guess the river bank would
be the first place to look.
Huh?
There.
That must be what
he's talking about.
Huh?
What?
Are you kidding me?
It's jut a chameleon plant!
There were a ton of these
the whole way over here!
Dammit!
I took too long.
What the-- What in the hell?
What is that?
-The Tsuchigumo clan's
forbidden jutsu.
It was-- it was
engraved onto her.
-How could they do that?
-To hell with forbidden jutsu.
To hell with our clans.
To hell with our masters.
And to hell with all
the selfish people
who do atrocious things
to those who serve them,
without a hint of remorse.
They think of those beneath
them as mere vessels.
As vessels with no choice.
-Hotaru.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Tonbee, what is this?
-En no Gyoja left behind a way
to extract the forbidden jutsu.
-It's clear to me that our
clan no longer has the strength
to keep the
forbidden jutsu safe.
To prevent its misuse, we have
no choice but to destroy it.
NARUTO: Destroy it?
But what'll happen to
Hotaru if you do that?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, Heir to Darkness.
Dammit.
There has to be another way.