(Kakashi) Please make it in
time!
[gasps]
Huh?
(Kakashi/Obito) Rin!
Thank you, Rin.
Obito and I will be joining you
shortly.
We can catch up then, all three
of us together once more.
[grunts]
Rin...
This time let's...
(Obito) Spend some alone time
together. Just you and me.
Kakashi would just be in the
way. So I'll leave him here.
[groaning]
But why?
We made up our minds to...
(Kakashi) Your power is still
needed here!
[groans]
(Real Zetsu) We need to infuse
more chakra again.
Mother, let's teleport to the
Root Time-Space. You'll recover
faster there.
Why save someone
useless like me?
Don't you mind me. Just focus on
the enemy.
[grunts]
[grunting]
(Obito) Naruto, Sasuke, and
Sakura. This is a crucial time
for them.
Kakashi, as someone who'll
support the next generation,
it's too soon for you to die.
[gasps]
(Real Zetsu) It's totally
useless, Naruto. He's a goner.
He'll rot away like trash and
die!
[grunts]
No, Naruto.
He's completely right. Don't
waste your chakra.
Why do you sympathize with him?
He was originally your enemy,
remember?
(Real Zetsu) Then again, Obito's
now a traitor to us, too.
A loser on all fronts.
(Real Zetsu) Hated by both ally
and foe. No family or friends to
morn him.
He's all alone, with no legacy.
He lost those precious to him.
Couldn't even fulfill his
dreams.
And after being used up, he's
helpless now.
He's a fool full of only
mistakes.
Why you! How dare you!
You're right.
Rin. Once again...
Let's create a world where you
can exist again.
(Obito) I shall...
...sever the nexuses...
...of this world!
[labored breathing]
[labored breathing] Now go on.
Until the time when I will be
revived.
(Real Madara) You shall be...
Who are you?
Madara Uchiha.
A world made up of only victors,
peace, and love. Such a world
can be created, too.
If you allow all of us to
collaborate, you can learn how.
Let's go, Konan, Nagato. We
can't trust these guys.
Don't you dare approach us
again.
You will eventually
realize it, too.
Who are you?
You are going to be very useful
to me.
[gasps]
Summoning Jutsu!
[roar]
[screams]
[growl]
[roar]
Minato Sensei.
[groaning]
Very well. I hereby declare war
on you all. The Fourth Great
Ninja War begins now.
They're all stalwart warriors.
Also, they're not the only pawns
that I possess.
Very well, we'll join forces.
They will all come to know
despair, thoroughly!
[roar]
[grunts]
[gasps] What?
[screams]
You're right. It's an end worthy
of the criminal that I am.
[grunting]
[gasps]
My Visual Prowess is back!
[grunts]
[gasps]
We've been here before.
She changed worlds again?
Naruto!
I'll handle the diversions.
Obito is beyond help.
(Sasuke) Come with me.
I'm going!
Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it!
Enough. Thank you, Naruto.
(Obito) After fighting you...
I feel like I've woken up.
(Obito) You and I are both
powerless shinobi.
You...
No, everyone actually. Shall
eventually just end up like me.
There's no way that I'll ever
end up like you! How many times
do I have to say it?!
My dream is to become the
Hokage!
There should be no reason to
keep fighting for a world like
this.
(Obito) No matter, it's coming
to an end in a few minutes.
So why do you keep on fighting?
No matter what, I never go back
on my word.
That is and always will be my
Ninja Way!
[screams]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Don't overdo it. Let's call it a
day.
No.
I'm not giving up! I made a
promise, that I'm gonna become
the Hokage!
[chuckles]
It was as if when I looked at
you, I saw my past self.
And regretted the current me.
But for some reason, it
also made me happy.
(Obito) When I was a kid, I'd
imagine myself as the Hokage so
often.
I think you brought back that
indescribable feeling of
exhilaration and uncertainty.
[crying]
Don't cry, Obito. You'll
just get laughed at.
I know.
Besides, the world of
shinobi is all about fighting.
There's no peace to it.
I promise that I'll put an end
to that.
(Asuma) Hey, you're not the only
ones.
Don't forget all of us, we're
here too.
Yeah, that's right.
Rin. I just...
(Obito) What did you say?
(Kakashi) The higher-ups have
decided.
Obito, you have been
chosen as the next Hokage.
But you're just as qualified.
A supporting role suits me
better.
(Kakashi) I'm sure Rin would say
the same thing.
But, if you screw up, I won't
hesitate to step up as a
candidate for Hokage myself.
[scoffs] You'll what?
[chuckles] Just do your best.
[chuckles]
All this paperwork! Every day!
It's driving me mad.
It can't be helped!
You're the Hokage now.
[groans]
And besides, doing this
certainly beats having to fight
every day.
That's for sure.
[children laughing] The Hokage!
Hi!
Making your rounds,
Lord Hokage?
I guess!
Yeah, right! Come on, you're
just messing around, aren't you?
[scoffs] Speak for yourself.
What was that?
You wanna go?
Cut it out!
Hey, what'd you hit me for?
(Sakura) Because you were rude
to Lord Hokage!
Seriously, it's so peaceful,
thanks to you.
Not quite. It's thanks to
everyone who worked hard
for the sake of the village.
It'd be nice to tell
Rin about it someday...
Yeah.
(Obito) Imagining the village,
comrades, and me as Hokage...
Even after all that's happened,
just the thought of it seems to
fill up the hole in my heart.
[chuckles]
Is it because I'm dying? I find
myself rambling all of a sudden.
[grunts]
(Rin) Don't act tough and hide
your wounds.
I'm always watching, you know.
You promised me you'd
become Hokage, Obito.
Listen, I want to stop this war,
too. Just like you. I truly want
to save the world!
And that's why I've decided I'm
gonna stick by your side and
watch over you!
You told me that saving you was
pretty much the same as saving
the whole world, remember?
[gasps]
[crying]
Well then, since I'm keeping an
eye on you, you can't hide
anything from me anymore.
[crying] Mhm.
Go for it, Obito!
Become Hokage, and show me just
how you're gonna save the
whole world!
And that's another promise for
you to keep.
Let's go!
A lot more suffering
likely awaits you, Naruto.
However, just keep on forging
ahead like always, without
changing.
(Obito) You once told me...
That never going back on your
word, is your Ninja Way, right?
Yeah.
Naruto...
You better...become the Hokage!
I will!
[gasps]
[chuckle]
Hmm?
(Real Zetsu) That pesky traitor
vermin's finally dead, huh?
Though as insects go, his
persistence was like a roach's!
[laughing]
Don't laugh at Obito!
Naruto...
Naruto.
If you keep resisting, you're
only going to end up pitifully
crumbling to dust...
just like him!
As someone who tried
to become Hokage...
(Naruto) Obito is...
[gasps]
Nothing but awesome to me!
Rin!
I've been waiting.
Really? Sorry about that.
It seems you got lost
along the way.
Yeah.
Lots happened before
I could come here.
Rin, I...
Didn't keep my promise.
[disagreeing]
I'd say you did your best.
Huh?
(Rin) I've been...
...watching you. All along.
Let's go!
[crying]
(Rin) Come on, Obito.
(Obito) Rin, do you mind waiting
just a little longer?
(Rin) Obito?
(Obito) Just a bit before we
move on.
You see, I'd kinda like to make
one more detour along the way...
(Rin) [chuckling] Who do you
want to save this time?
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Sharingan
Revived."
(Rin) I'll be waiting, here.