That's the First Hokage?
The real Hashirama touted
as a God of Shinobi?
It's that shinobi
Orochimaru again!
What's going on?
I suspect what's going
on is that he undid
the Reaper Death Seal.
The very same thing that
sealed us away, and then
performed the
Reanimation Jutsu.
No way...
You solved how to
undo that Jutsu?
How, Mr. Orochimaru?
You underestimate
me, Minato.
It was originally a Sealing
Jutsu of the Uzumaki Clan.
I extensively researched
the ruins and scattered
documents of the
now-extinct clan
since I lost my jutsu.
Well, Lord First...
It appears that we've
been recalled into the
world of the living.
Hm...
Who the hell are you?!
Wha-?
Oh, uh...
The Fourth Hokage, sir.
Oh ho! The Fourth
Hokage, huh?
Nice, nice!
The village has
remained stable, then!
Uh, I'm not actually
sure if it has or not.
Because, you see, I died and
was sealed away much earlier
than the Third Hokage was.
Hm, is that so?!
In a different incident
than when I was sealed
away with Sarutobi?
Yes, sir. Completely
separate one.
So who is the Fifth, then?
Your granddaughter,
Princess Tsunade.
Tsuna, huh?
Is the village okay?
Is there a reason to worry?
She was my first grandchild!
I spoiled her rotten!
In the end, she even
picked up my gambling
habit, I'm afraid.
[laughing]
He's not quite what I
expected of someone
considered to be
a God of Shinobi!
[laughter]
How do I put it? Uh...
It's the Reanimation
Jutsu again. The jutsu
I devised, used
so casually!
Well, it really isn't all
that complex a jutsu.
But, you shouldn't
have created it.
Hm?
Lord Second...
Many of the policies that
you created and jutsu that
you developed caused
problems down the line.
Even now...
Why you! Are you planning
to attack the Leaf again?!
I took away your jutsu in
exchange for my own life.
Yet even now, you still-!
And then, at this time you
revived me, your former
master, to pit me
against the Leaf?!
[sigh] Conflict no
matter what era, eh?
For sure, it can't be
called a great jutsu.
Tobirama, that's why I
told you that time to-
Be quiet, elder brother.
I'm trying to speak
to this stripling.
What?! But I...
Shut up!
[groaning]
God of Shinobi?
So not dignified!
Please do not misunderstand.
I do not have any
more leanings in that
direction at all.
That's why I didn't
suppress your personalities.
Certain circumstances
are at play this time.
I am merely creating
a stage for discourse
per his desire.
I am Sasuke Uchiha. I
want to ask you Hokage
some things.
[gasp] You, Sasuke?!
You belong to the Uchiha, do
you? Of course you'd stick
with a scoundrel.
Tobirama!
I thought I told you to
stop saying things like that!
You're too soft,
elder brother!
It doesn't matter.
Third Hokage... Why'd
you make Itachi do it?
So I take it you
learned what happened.
Itachi's dead...
I killed him to avenge
the Uchiha clan.
Afterwards, I learned the
truth from Tobi and Danzo
and I swore vengeance
upon the Hidden Leaf.
However...
I want to hear it
straight from your mouth.
Everything regarding Itachi.
So it came to that...
I not only had him kill
his brethren and bear the
false charge of traitor.
But also keep tabs on
the Akatsuki by himself.
Since he was young, Itachi
paid attention to the
teachings and signs of
our predecessors no
one else gave heed to.
He was a sensitive
child who understood our
village's past and shinobi.
Perhaps due to that,
the trappings of a clan
never bound Itachi.
He was able to think about
the future of shinobi and
the village, and
always had misgivings
regarding those futures.
Even at the age of seven, he
thought quite like a Hokage.
We left everything to
Itachi, in his hands alone,
and he executed his
missions perfectly.
He slaughtered his entire
clan, stopped a revolt, and
prevented a coming
war all by himself.
He even infiltrated the
Akatsuki as a spy to
protect the village.
All on the condition that
I protect you, Sasuke.
[gasp]
So all of it's true...
This is all just part of the
Uchiha's cursed fate.
Though I can't
believe they're on the
brink of extinction.
They even plotted a
coup d'état, did they?
I'd envisioned it might
come to something like that.
The rebellious elements
bearing Madara's will had
been smoldering.
But you're the one who drove
them to it, Lord Second.
It could be said
that the seeds were
sown with the Uchiha-Leaf
Police Force you created.
What's that?
Those who control
crime also tend to be
very easily disliked.
The more authority such
a group has, the more
conceited it can get.
By building the Police
Station next to the prison
under the pretext of
monitoring criminals,
you conspicuously shoved
the Uchiha Clan to the
margins of the village.
That helped foster
Madara's followers.
Tobirama! Didn't I emphasize
to you many times not to
slight the Uchiha?!
Huh?!
I gave them posts they
were very qualified for.
That if another Madara
emerged, I thought he
could just be dealt
with right away.
As you know, elder
brother, the Uchiha
are a clan
possessed by evil!
It's like Madara left a
psychological scar on you,
to cause such
fear of the Uchiha.
You stripling. You
do not know Madara.
Second Hokage, a
question for you...
What is it about the Uchiha
Clan? What do you know?
[sigh]
All right...
The Senju and Uchiha
Clans have a long history.
That is, a long history
of battling with each other.
In fact, the two clans
were once bitter enemies.
I know that much!
But how are the Uchiha
possessed by evil?
It was said that in contrast
to the Senju Clan, who based
their strength on love
the Uchiha Clan's
strength was based on
the power of their jutsu.
However, the
truth is different.
No clan feels deeper
love than the Uchiha.
And that's why
they suppressed and
sealed it away.
What do you mean?!
Once a member of the
Uchiha comes to know love.
It's as if all their
previously checked
emotions are released.
Strong love and power
exceeding even the
Senju's awaken.
But why is that a problem?
It should help the bond with
the Senju, this super-strong
power of love, shouldn't it?
Except that it is
quite problematic.
This great power hides
within it the possibility
of losing control.
When an Uchiha has known
love, then loses that deep
love, it is replaced
by an even stronger
hate that changes them.
I've seen it happen quite a
few times. And that's when a
special condition emerges.
A special condition?
When an Uchiha writhes in
agony over the loss of a
great love or from
disappointment in
themselves, a unique chakra
is released in their brain
and reacts with
the optic nerves.
Changes appear
in that person's eyes.
This phenomenon is called
the Sharingan, eyes that
reflect the heart.
The Sharingan taps into
the power of that person's
heart, rapidly increasing
their strength along
with the power
of their hate.
There were many sensitive
people among the Uchiha, and
nearly all exposed to strong
emotions were taken by
darkness and fell to evil.
The deeper the darkness
gets, the greater the Visual
Prowess, till that
person can't be stopped.
Just like Madara.
Madara cared intensely
about his younger brother,
likely even more so
than your brother.
I thought I had arranged and
guided things such that the
Uchiha's power
could be harnessed
to serve the village.
Although, if their
self-destruction benefited
the village, then so be it.
Either way, in the
end, they were of use
to the Leaf Village.
Tobirama, stop saying such
things! You are speaking to
an innocent Uchiha child!
What's all-important is the
village. The village is the
keystone. I know you know
that, too, elder brother.
I don't care.
For I am neither
innocent nor a child.
It's not the basic tomoe
pattern. He's got the
Mangekyo Sharingan.
First Hokage, I
ask you this...
What does it mean to be a
village? And what does it
mean to be a shinobi?
A village? And what
a shinobi is, huh?
My brother, despite
having been used by
the Leaf Village, still
defended it with his life.
And he died proud that
he was a Leaf shinobi.
Just what is this village
that one strives to protect
even if it means
killing one's family?
Or one's own death?
And what are shinobi who've
created such circumstances
and consider them
to be acceptable?
I'll listen to your response
and find out the truth.
And then I'll make
my decision.
Whether to declare vengeance
on the Leaf. Or...
Orochimaru...
Yes?
You once tried to destroy
the Leaf Village.
At first, I believed it when
you said that it was on a
whim. But now I
know it wasn't.
What was the real reason?
Vengeance against the Leaf?
You brat full
of Uchiha evil!
In that case...
[groaning]
[gasp]
Lord Second!
Tobirama!
Now we're talking presence!
Like, seriously!
Lower your finger.
Oh, all right. Don't rile up
your chakra, elder brother.
[laughter] Sorry about that!
[sigh of relief]
Wow, that's incredible!
You haven't changed a
bit, Lord Hashirama.
[harrumph]
Well then, Sasuke. You
had a good older brother.
A shinobi even
greater than I!
I don't mind telling you
more about the village,
but it'll take time.
If possible, please tell the
child everything he wants to
know quickly. We don't
really have much time.
Why is there no time?
There's a war going on.
Madara Uchiha's been
revived and seeks to erase
the world's shinobi.
[weary sigh]
Always conflict, no
matter what era.
I definitely do sense
some powerful chakra.
Over in the direction
of two o'clock.
That's Naruto and the Nine
Tails' chakra. I see...
You did it, Naruto!
And you're fighting
together, even now!
It seems to be the truth.
I do indeed sense
Madara's chakra.
Then we ought to head
right to the battlefield!
As you're all under the
control of my Reanimation
Jutsu, your movements
can be restricted.
If you must, you may head
down to the battle after
we're done talking.
No, we can talk later!
Do you truly
understand this?!
The gravity of Madara
being revived?!
Still, I'm staying
with this child.
If the explanations that you
give don't satisfy Sasuke, I
may use all of you to
destroy the Leaf now.
The timing
couldn't be better.
Agh! Curse this jutsu!
Orochimaru, is it?
You seem to be
misunderstanding
something.
The fact that you've made
the Reanimation Jutsu more
precise since last time
shall be your downfall.
Now that all of us here
been revived at nearly
our original power,
this Reanimation Jutsu
of yours will not
be able to bind me!
Don't forget, I'm
the one who devised
it in the first place.
Brother, you must
agree there's no choice.
I have to act!
[gasp]
Well, Sarutobi, you
certainly raised
quite a shinobi.
To be praised by the God
of Shinobi is an honor.
[laughter]
He acquired my
cells and enhanced his
power to bind us!
Tobirama, your instincts
have dulled a bit.
Damn him. Now that I take
a closer look, most of his
body is composed of
my brother's cells.
Now, then...
First Hokage Hashirama.
He's different. He could
undo my binding at any time.
I'll have to be careful
not to let down my guard.
Listen, Orochimaru,
do not fret.
I shall prioritize undoing
the ill feelings that are
binding this child.
Of course I can't know
what he'll decide after he
finishes listening to me.
But I do know that if we
ignore him now, he will
definitely become
the next Madara.
In that case, even if the
war ends and we win, it
would be pointless.
[annoyed sigh] Do as
you please, elder brother.
Now then, where exactly
should I begin this tale?
Hm, yes...
In order to tell you about
village and shinobi.
[angry growl]
Wood Style: Wood
Dragon Jutsu!
I must first speak of the
Uchiha and Senju Clans.
[defiant roar]
Wood Style!
Wood Golem Jutsu!
Wood Style, Wood
Expulsion Jutsu, was it?
Perfect for taking
on difficult beasts.
Hm?
He wrapped his Susano'o
around the Tailed
Beast like armor!
Madara, you crafty fox!
I can read your
swordsmanship!
Wood Style: Laughing
Buddha Jutsu!
[growl]
At this rate, the land'll
be completely obliterated.
It's best to move
this to the seashore!
No, you don't!
There! Just try
grabbing ahold of that!
Now what?!
Summoning!
Five-Layer Rashomon!
With this!
That'll change
the trajectory!
All the way to
the other shore?!
Hashirama...
It has been a while
since we've fought
each other all-out!
You can see that I have
changed, can you not?
You're going to lay waste to
everything? To all we've
accomplished up
till now, Madara?
Nothing will come of us
battling each other...
This fight will only hurt
village and shinobi!
This is disrespectful
toward our brothers
and our comrades!
You know nothing of my-!
I don't want to
have to kill you!
Are you implying that
you could take me
down at any time?
I'm not! I mean
we're friends!
Enough of all this!
I've already reached it!
[angry roar]
Then so be it...
Sage Art: Wood Style.
Shinsu Senju Veritable
1000-Armed Kan'on!
Here I go, Madara!
Come on, Hashirama!
[attacking yell]
Just aim it a little
higher than you'd expect.
That's the trick.
Yeah, I know! It'll reach
the other side if I simply
put my all into it! Who
the hell are you, anyway?
First name's Hashirama.
But I can't tell
you my last name.
Hashirama, huh?
That was...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Hashirama
and Madara."
...my first encounter
with Madara Uchiha.