Now.
How strong am I?
That's just pathetic.
Your hatred, it's weak.
Shut up.
You're far too soft
and forgiving.
Just shut up!
The greater the hunger for
revenge, the greater the hate.
The power of hate gives
you the strength to kill.
Your hate's weaker
than mine, far weaker.
That's enough!
Heeyaaa!
Heehehh!
[pain]
Nnnyegh!
[pants]
Sasuke!
[growl]
Dagh!
Rrgh!
Daagh!
[Sasuke]
Naruto!
You have to save Sakura!
[Sasuke]
I lost everything once.
I don't ever wanna have
to see that again.
My trusted comrades,
falling right in front of me.
[pants]
I wasn't able to do anything.
Na! Ru! To! 2K!
Uzumaki Barrage!
From Naruto's Handbook!
Yeeaahhh!
...!
[Sasuke]
Naruto just gets
stronger and stronger.
I can tell just by
looking at him.
He has some kind of
enormous power inside him.
And sometimes,
it scares even me.
So how?!
How can I become stronger?
And how can I
get my revenge?
"Rift"
So he's come back to
the Village, huh?
And he's after Naruto??
What does this mean?!
Damn!
It's been a long time,
Sasuke.
[gasps]
Itachi Uchiha.
I hope you're ready,
to die.
Well. The Sharingan.
[Kisame]
Itachi, who is this kid?
He's my younger
brother.
[gasps]
[Kisame]
That's strange, cuz the way
I heard it the whole Uchiha
Clan was wiped out.
By you.
This is who he was
talkin' about.
[Naruto]
The one he
wanted to kill.
[seething anger]
[Itachi]
You're not even worth killing.
Foolish little brother.
If you wish to kill me
one day, foster your
hatred and despise me.
Surviving in such an
unsightly manner as this.
By all means, flee.
Cling to your
wretched life.
It's just as you said, brother.
I've fostered my hatred
for you all this time.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose.
To kill you!
It ends here!
Huaaa!
[crack]
Aaghh!
Sasuke!!
Damn! Rgh!
Forget the legs.
Maybe I oughta start off
with those arms of his.
Huh??
[Itachi]
Master Jiraiya.
I know he's the one
you're really after.
You're right.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatsuki are after.
And we will have him.
Huh?
No way you're getting Naruto.
We'll see about that.
Actually, this is
all very convenient.
I can eliminate you
both at the same time.
Stay out
of this!
Huh.
Hm.
The only one...
who's going to
eliminate him...
...is me!
Go away.
You don't interest
me at the moment.
Huagh!
Sasuke no!
Agh! Aht! Aghh!
Why you lousy!
No Naruto! Don't butt in,
mind your own business!
Just back off!
This fight is mine!
[Jiraiya]
Of course. Revenge.
And now, finally--!
[gut-punched]
Uwaggh!
All these years and
nothing has changed.
How can it be?
Uwagh! Huagh!
Gahg!
I've trained for so long,
just to kill him!
For so long!
What have I been doing,
all these years?
Was it... Was it
all for this?
[Itachi]
You're weak, Sasuke.
And for the next
twenty-four hours,
Relive that day.
That does it,
I'm through
standing around!
Huh??
Ninja Art Toad Mouth Trap.
Too bad for you,
Itachi, Kisame.
Rrrgh!
You've both just
been swallowed by
the Mountain Toad.
This toad has a sensitive
digestive tract,
so don't upset him.
[Jiraiya]
It must be humbling to know
that you've been reduced to
toad bait. He he he he!
You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
You never will.
Kisame. Come!
Stop!
He's getting away!
A ninja hasn't been born yet
who can survive this
powerful stomach.
Nyyaah!
Huh?
Hey!
Pervy sage!
Huh?
They both
got away!
[Naruto]
Sasuke!
Sasuke! Talk to me,
are you okay, Sasuke?!
Sasuke!
Urgh! Damn it! No!
What happened?!
What did that guy
just do to him?!
[Jiraiya]
It's Itachi's Sharingan.
It seems his visual
prowess is attacking
Sasuke's mental state.
Seems Sasuke's taken
on a lot of damage.
Will he be okay?
[Jiraiya]
We'll just have
to go find HER.
Another of the
legendary Sannin,
the Queen of slugs and elixirs.
[Naruto]
Hang in there, Sasuke.
I swear I'll find this Tsunade.
And then she'll fix you up,
good as new.
What's up?
So, Pervy Sage.
What exactly do those
guys want with me anyway?
Hmm.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not you they want.
It's what's inside of you.
But what the heck
is this thing?
I don't even
really know!
Some horrible demon that
terrorized the Leaf Village.
That's why everyone's
so afraid of it, right?
So why do these guys
want it so bad?
The Nine Tailed Fox
has appeared in times
of consequence,
all through the ages.
As powerful as any
act of nature.
men trembled before it.
As for what they would want
with that malicious monstrosity,
That's a hard question
to answer, Naruto.
They might be thinking
of somehow seizing
control of that power,
bending it to their will.
It's a bitter pill to swallow,
knowing that those two will
be after you now.
But that is your fate.
Not to worry, though, after all
you will have me around!
Ah well!
I'm just gonna have to hurry
up and get stronger, then!
There's no choice!
[Sasuke]
Where am I?
Good, you're out
of the woods.
[Sasuke]
I...?
Sasuke!
[sobs]
Heey, you're back!
Huh?
You can be pretty
thoughtful, Naruto.
Nah, I didn't do
anything special.
You're a
good friend.
[chuckle]
[Itachi]
You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
You never will.
Look I brought
you some apples!
Aah!
Wha? Sasuke!
Hey. What's that look?
Naruto.
I want you to fight me.
What!? We're in a hospital,
and you just got patched up!
Shut up and fight me!
Huh??
...
Do you really think
you saved me?
I don't care if she's the Fifth
Hokage. you shouldn't have
gotten her involved in this.
What's that!?
Hey! Sasuke!
Wait, don't do this!
Naruto, say something!
Actually, this
is perfect.
I was just thinking 'bout how
I wanted to kick your butt.
What's this weird feeling?
My lower belly's all tight.
And... and I'm getting chills.
Heh!
What's so funny?
I'm not laughing
'cause it's funny.
I'm just psyched.
'Cause I know that today is
the day when I finally beat you.
What did you say?!
You're right. Naruto is the
prize that the Akatsuki are
after. And we will have him.
Don't talk nonsense,
you inept loser.
I won't be such a loser
after I win today, will I!?
Go away. You don't
interest me at the moment.
You. An idiot like you
has no business acting
all high and mighty!
Ha! What happened to the
calm, controlled Sasuke?
Am I makin' you nervous?
It looks like you picked
a fight with me and now
you're too scared to go
through with it!
Is that it?
Let's just do this.
Put on your headband
and we will.
Not to worry,
I don't need
that thing.
Just do it! Come on!
You know puttin' your headband
on is a testament to fighting on
equal terms as a Leaf Shinobi!
See, there you go acting all
high and mighty again!
No, he's already....
[Sasuke]
You don't honestly believe
that we're equals?!
Can I? Can I really
keep up with him?
What?!
Heck yeah I do!
No, I don't.
All this time, I've never
once thought that I was
inferior to you in any way!
You're everything I've
always wanted to be!
You're a complete embarrassment!
Just stop it.
Only because next to me, you're
embarrassed at how weak you are!
Isn't that right, Sasuke?!
Just stop it!
Narutoooo!!
Sasukeeee!!
STOP IT!!!!
I'm not done [yet]!
HAAAAAAA!
Stop! No!!!
Too late--!
Can't stop--!
Auhh!
What do you two think
you're doing up here?
That was a little intense
for just a sparring match,
wasn't it?
What's wrong
with you two?
[pained grunts]
Heh.
[Kakashi]
Sasuke.
You you've really got
to watch this sense of
superiority you have.
Huh?
That Chidori...
It was not the size
you'd aim at a comrade
from the Leaf village.
Were you really going
to kill him, Sasuke?
Hmph.
That hole in the water tower...
How did?!
Agh!
Naruto...
How far have you...
I'm assuming it was you who
taught him that technique?
I know you want to protect
him from the Akatsuki.
But still, to
entrust him with a
jutsu like that...
After all, he could've
killed Sasuke.
Aren't you a fine
one to talk.
Teaching the Chidori to
someone like Sasuke.
I knew he was a hot-head, but I
never imagined he'd be willing
to use a jutsu that powerful
against a comrade
from his own village.
To Naruto, Sasuke is a comrade
and a rival at the same time.
In fact, it's the
competition between them
that keeps him going.
That's why he won't
stand for it when Sasuke
tries to belittle him.
He's been dogging Sasuke's steps
every inch of the way, since
their first days at the Academy.
As far as Naruto's
concerned, what you and
I think doesn't matter.
There's only one person
whose approval he really
cares about: Sasuke.
On the other hand, it's hard
for Sasuke to watch Naruto's
strength and skills develop
at such an astonishing rate.
He's come along so fast,
Sasuke must feel like
he's standing still.
[Jiraiya]
You mean revenge.
His hatred of Itachi may be
driving him on too fast.
[Kakashi]
Sasuke can't acknowledge
Naruto's abilities.
He's afraid that if he
does acknowledge them,
he somehow diminishes his own.
[sigh] It can
be hard work
maintaining
a rivalry.
On top of everything else,
the both of them are
burdened by a dark past,
That neither one had any
control over at all.
Damn it.
Damn it!
We are the Sound
Ninja Four.
We're here on orders
from Lord Orochimaru.
You guys might
wanna think twice
about doing this.
Because I am in a really
bad mood right now.
Oh, just stop all of
your prattling, you
little weakling.
Did he call me weak?!
C'mon kid.
I wanna play Do-Re-Mi
on those ribs of yours
'til they crack!!!
What?! Orochimaru
left a Curse Mark
on Sasuke's body?
Yeah. And he said Sasuke
would come looking for him
hoping to find more power.
I see. I didn't
realize that
had happened.
Orochimaru, huh?
Yeah, I ran into him
not too long ago.
You did?!
He was incredibly powerful.
The guy is bad news.
Come on,
everything'll
be fine!
Uh?
Sasuke would never let
a guy like that sink
his claws into him.
He's already
a powerhouse!
It's not like he needs
that kinda help, ya know.
[Naruto] [flashback]
Don't worry,
I guarantee it!
Yaaagh!
Huagh!
Uwagh!
You should
come with us.
Lord Orochimaru
offers you power.
What is your purpose
in this life?
To stay here in this
backwater village, hiding
with your little friends?
Surely you haven't
forgotten...
Itachi Uchiha?
Don't lose sight
of your purpose.
Life in this village
is little more than
bondage for you.
So sever your ties and
leave this pathetic place.
If you can do that,
There will be no limit to
the power you can wield.
Remember your purpose!
My goal... is to kill Itachi!
For that, I must have power!
[Naruto]
Maybe I was the only one,
who thought that
we were friends.
I can't help it.
I just can't bear the thought,
of seeing you taken away,
by someone like Orochimaru!!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Parting.
The rivalry between Sasuke and
me reaches a boiling point.
You're going back to the Hidden
Leaf Village, if I have to drag
you all the way there!