-Sakura, do not fear.
I am here with you.
You just step back now, dear.
Assault Blade!
-If you insist on defying
me, you leave me no choice.
So, are you ready to join
that boy as another addition
to my collection, Granny Chiyo?
-What-- what is that thing?
-What you see there is
not Sasori's real body.
-I kind of guessed it
wasn't his real body.
What is it, then?
-Ah.
That's merely a puppet.
-But then, where
is his real body?
A puppet master has to
be pulling the strings
from somewhere, right?
-His real body is
insight that one.
-Inside?
-Puppet masters aren't
so good at close combat.
Manipulating their
puppet during battle
leaves them wide open to attack.
It was to overcome that
weakness that Sasori
created this puppet.
It serves as his armor,
and his weapon, as well.
It's Sasori's specialty, Hiruko.
-You seem to know a lot
about it, Lady Chiyo.
-I know everything
about that puppet.
-But do you know how I prepare a
new specimen for my collection?
First, I drain its blood.
Then I remove all the organs
and wash it inside and out.
Make it nice and clean.
And then, after I've preserved
the body against decay,
the final step is to fill
it with hidden weapons.
As the hag said, this
one is called Hiruko.
It's only one of the
specimens in my collection.
Once I've added
you and the girl,
I'll have collected exactly 300.
This is my art.
[theme music]
-Gaara.
-Are you really sure you want
to waste your time on me?
Hm?
Kakashi-sensei
with the Sharingan?
You know, my man Sasori is
probably a more dangerous
opponent than I am, as
much as I hate to say that.
His idea of art is very
different from mine.
-You call it art, do you?
-What do you mean?
-Long, long ago, when he
lived in the Hidden Sand,
he was esteemed as
a master craftsman,
admired for his many
extraordinary puppets.
But his true passion was
for making puppets out
of the living, then adding them
as specimens to his collection.
He calls this
monstrous conduct art.
That puppet there,
Hiruko, he was a shinobi
who lived in a nearby village.
Sasori turned him
into what you see now.
A puppet that retains the shell
of its previous physical form.
It's called a human puppet.
-A human puppet?
-And the same fate awaits you.
Will soon become another
of my works of art.
-This puppet's highly skilled
in attack and defense.
Deadly at both.
The first thing to
do is find a way
to force Sasori out of there.
-And how are we
supposed to do that?
-The trouble is that public
is full of hidden mechanisms.
Without knowing
what they are, it's
difficult to anticipate
exactly how to counteract them.
-On the other hand,
Lady Chiyo, you
know a lot about how
that puppet functions.
Meaning we have the advantage.
-So I thought.
That's why I was so sure I'd be
able to deal with him at first.
-What are you saying?
-But now I realize
that I was wrong.
-What?
What do you mean, wrong?
-Now that I've had
a better look at it,
this one is different in ways
from the Hiruko puppet I knew.
The Hiruko I used to know didn't
have that shell on its back.
He must've heightened
its defenses.
And that left arm is new to me.
Not to mention the
hidden mechanisms.
We have to assume they've been
refined and improved as well.
-So what do we do?
-If we are to
defeat Sasuri, We'll
have to first destroy Hiruko.
But that will require
enormous destructive power
that I simply don't have.
Not nearly.
But Sakura.
You do have it.
With all the training
she's giving you,
you wield the monstrous strength
of Lady Tsunade herself.
-Right!
CHIYO: Listen to me, Sakura.
You must somehow
get close enough
to use your monster strength
to smash that puppet.
But to do that,
you will first have
to avoid every attack that his
hidden weapons launch at you.
You must dodge
every one perfectly.
You can't risk even
the slightest scratch.
-Because of the poison, right?
-Exactly.
As you know, the smallest
cut can be fatal.
-Here goes.
Hold him down!
-Right.
-Before you can
ever get to him, he
will strike at you with
all his hidden weapons.
To survive, you must understand
and instantly anticipate
the puppet master's moves.
-I'm not sure I'll be able
to do either of those.
-Yes, it's true.
This kind of challenge requires
far more battle experience
than what you possess.
-All right, then.
What do we do?
-Take a good look at me.
What do you see?
Simply a worthless
old bag of bones?
Well, look again.
Leave this part to me.
Just count on me, Sakura.
Even his experience
doesn't compare to mine.
Sasori knows this,
which explains
why he hesitates and doesn't
dare to attack us recklessly.
For someone who hates
to be kept waiting,
it must be very frustrating.
What he doesn't know is I've
already made the first move.
Sakura.
Come a little closer.
I'm going to tell you a secret.
Together, we shall finish him.
-What are they up to?
I can't make out a word
the old hag is saying.
-Understood.
Ready when you are.
-Are you sure?
Well, it's about time.
I really hate to
be kept waiting.
Don't you?
-No need to worry, Sasori.
We'll end it quickly.
-Ah.
It seems they've started.
How confident are you in that
young girl and the old lady?
You really think they're good
enough to handle my man Sasori?
Huh?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He wants
to get me out of the way
so he can fight
Naruto one on one.
But this guy defeated
the Kazekage,
one of the five great Kage.
I don't Naruto on his
own could handle him.
-Go on, Sensei.
Go to Sakura.
I'll handle this.
-Huh?
-Go on, Sensei.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it!
I'll save Gaara!
-Good.
It would have been
very disappointing
if you'd been
beaten that easily.
-Let go of him!
I'll never let you have him!
SASORI (VOICEOVER): They
were ready for that one, eh?
In that case--
-Now die!
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
They dodged every one?
Impossible!
The old hag, I can understand.
But this-- this girl?
But how?
And Granny Chiyo's just--
just standing there.
Is this girl mocking me?
Is she really attacking
me head on all by herself?
Now.
What?
something stopped it?
Of course.
Chiyo.
-Now, Sakura.
Now!
Strike it down!
-Right!
-I'll get Gaara.
Nothing can stop me!
-You're quite an unusual
Jinchuriki, aren't you?
I thought you were
all sullen loners who
didn't care about anyone else.
To date, we've destroyed two
Jinchuriki, not including him,
of course.
But nobody ever tried to
save them from us before.
Not a single friend or neighbor.
Not a soul came to their aid.
In fact, it seemed
like most people
were happy to finally
be rid of them.
You cant forsake one of
your own kind, can you?
You feel connected to
this pathetic creature.
Such a shame.
Gaara died when the One
Tail was extracted from him.
Very soon now, the same
thing'll happen to you.
-If Gaara's dead,
you're gonna pay!
CHIYO: Heh.
So, you finally come out, eh?
-Is that his real body?
-Come, now.
Let me get a good look at you.
I've come all this
way to see you.
I've waited 20 years.
I want to see my
grandson's face.
[theme music]
MAN: Welcome back to
What's My Profession.
And here's today's
final challenge.
Can you guess what
this person does?
NARUTO: The guy's covered
in a cape from head to toe!
SAKURA: I know.
It's a famous actor, right?
[buzzing]
NARUTO: Then a really
muscular carpenter?
[buzzing]
SAKURA: Does the job
require a uniform?
NARUTO: Give us a hint.
MAN: No hints.
SAKURA: I don't know!
MAN: Time's running out.
SAKURA: No!
NARUTO: Wait, hold on!
-Aw, too bad.
Now let's have our guest
take off that cape.
NARUTO: Next time.
Sasori's Real Face.
[theme music]
NARUTO: A word from the
Society for Leaf Tourism!
This is the most
famous sweet dumpling
shop in the whole village.
Even people with a serious
sweet tooth like Anko-sensei
swear by it, so
you know it's good.
-Well, maybe, but it doesn't
look all that good to me.
-Trust me on this one, granny.
This place is the best.
When Itachi and Kisame
slipped into the Leaf village,
where do you think they
stopped for dumplings?
Right here.
-Oh?
Even the Akatsuki.
Well, I suppose
this is something
I should try before I die then.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Die?
What's she talking about?
She looks fine to me.
Wh-- What is it?
Granny.
Hey!
Granny!
[scream]
Oh no, she's-- Oh no, oh no!
Help!
Somebody call the
Medical Corps, quick!
[snickering]
Huh?
-Just kidding.
Fooled you, didn't I?
Ha!
-Very funny.
Give me a break.
-Ha ha!