Whoa! Is that thing the--?!
That's--!
No mistake.
[gasping]
[grunting]
Yeah...
That's him!
[roaring]
Ten Tails!
[angry roaring]
But I thought the statue's
evil chakra had disappeared!
[growl] They got us!
He doesn't have those kinds
of emotions or feelings!
He can't be sensed.
He's natural energy itself,
the same as that which
circulates around this
world, that you can
feel in the soil,
water, and air.
It would be a different
story if you tried it while
engaged in Sage
Mode, though.
Right, gotcha!
Well then, if you say
he's all Nature Energy
then I can check
him out if I do this!
Forget it, Naruto. If
you try to do that...
...all you'll see is
how immeasurable it is.
[chuckle]
You're not kidding!
I had planned to capture
those two before the Ten
Tails fully revived, but
they're surprisingly good.
I want to start the Infinite
Tsukuyomi Ritual now.
That massive genjutsu
requires time
to summon the moon.
They'll interfere with
the jutsu. It'll go more
smoothly if we use
the Statue's power to
get rid of them first.
Don't you agree?
Madara, you just want
to test out Ten Tails'
power, don't you?
That's why you--
You're just like a child.
Nope. You're Wrong.
Children are impatient,
touchy fools, nothing more.
[angry roar]
Hey, here comes
a big one.
You really think
we can do this?
Don't think you can hide
under your tentacles 'cause
you're scared! But
first, hand Guy over!
I can heal him up later on.
And Kakashi and Naruto, too!
Yeah!
Heads up!
[grunting]
Listen up. First, we
keep our distance and
see what move he makes!
We'll counter it and
hit him with a big blow
as close as we can get.
Like I said earlier.
Nine Tails, you're
acting like a captain.
Huh?! Got a problem
with that?!
Nope! In fact, I
feel kinda happy!
[chuckle]
Save that line for after
we've won! Let's go!
Huh?
[angry roar]
Man, he's fast!
There was no time
to see his moves!
Damn it!
[angry roar]
[charging roars]
[growl]
[defiant roar]
Go now, Eight-o!
Tailed Beast Bomb Barrage!
There's no real
need to dodge them.
I'd like to preserve
Ten Tails' power as
much as we can.
This is...
...not good!
It's on you now!
Persistant, I'll
give them that.
Listen, Naruto,
don't tell me--
Bushier Brow Sensei,
don't worry.
Nice control, Naruto!
You got them in
nice and close!
We focused too
much on the Ten Tails.
I'm sorry about that
leg, but here we go!
Kamui!
Yeah!
To our enemies it may
appear that we left one
octopus leg behind, but...
Bee! Eight Tails!
Operation Octopus Pot!
Sorry for the sneaky plot!
I'm smashing this
right into his eyeball!
Get him!
[gasps]
[groaning]
Two flies are buzzing
above us too.
[grunt]
Ten Tails' tail?!
Naruto!
[grunting]
Naruto, you really
are a lot like me.
[grunt]
That's right. You're
merely younger than me.
Eventually...
Eight-O and
Octopop, forgive me!
Just another Shadow Clone.
[grunt]
[painful grunt]
Kurama! How could you fall
apart at a time like this?!
That was eight minutes,
it's longer than before,
but that's the limit.
I have to infuse and
build up my chakra.
I guess that we
have no choice.
That hurt!
Fool, ya fool!
Bee! I need to rest,
too. I'm also at my limit.
So I can't get
healed yet?
Pulling something as massive
as Eight Tails in and out
sure comes with a
correspondingly
large cost. I'm
drained already.
Seems the Eight and
Nine Tails have run
out of chakra for now.
Your favorite, Shadow
Clone Jutsu? It's forbidden
high-level ninjutsu,
but upping the
number of losers won't-
I'm not a loser!
Don't, Naruto! It's
meaningless to create Shadow
Clones that'll split
up your chakra even
more. They might be useful
as diversions but not for
decisive hits.
And if you go down
we'll lose this war.
You were always just
a motley crew anyway.
Huh?! We're a
m-m-m- motley wha?
You are pathetic.
He's saying it's pointless
to merely increase the
number of heads if
all of them are empty.
You and I are both
powerless shinobi. You...
No, everyone, actually...
...shall eventually
just end up like me.
There's no way that I'll
ever end up like you!
How many times do I
haveta say it?!
My dream is to
become the Hokage!
You needn't worry.
Everything will
go as planned.
No jutsu is mightier than
the Infinite Tsukuyomi.
I'll make you Hokage
inside this jutsu.
So just disappear along
with the rest of the world!
[gasps]
What the--?!
He missed?!
Deliberately?!
About time!
Kakashi! Guy!
Sorry we're late!
I can't believe he shook off
my Byakugan-aided, spot-on
Mind Transfer in
just two seconds!
You still managed to shift
that big thing's aim off.
So good work!
Naruto, are you
doing okay?
Yeah!
Just because Hinata's here
doesn't mean you have
to act tough, Naruto!
Beetle Jamming Jutsu!
Hidden Mist Jutsu!
We're here, Naruto!
All right, good! We won't be
so easily detectable now.
Lord Bee! You're
in way better shape
than I expected!
Lord Bee! You look
seriously wounded!
You know what, Omoi?
You worry too much!
Guy Sensei, do not tell me
you unleashed the Hirudora?!
Lee!
I'm sorry we're late,
Captain Kakashi.
Sakura, first of all!
Yeah, I know!
The Sensory Water
Sphere won't maintain its
original shape. We better--!
Inoichi! Ao! Confirm
the situation!
-Roger!
-Okay!
First Company has
arrived on the scene!
Second Company
has also arrived!
Third Company has arrived!
Fourth Company has arrived!
Fifth Company has arrived!
The Medical
Unit's here, too!
Sensory Unit's
arrived as well!
You call that hiding?
Wind Style! Art
of the Gust Blade!
You see? Were not a
motley crew anymore!
We brought something with
us. It's called the Allied
Shinobi Forces Jutsu!
The world's greatest, most
invincible, super-duper
ninjutsu, y'know!
A jutsu that trumps
the Infinite Tsukuyomi.
Remember that!
The Allied Shinobi
Forces Jutsu?
Isn't that a
bit of a stretch?
We're gonna stop the both
of you with this jutsu!
You're wrong. Why won't you
realize that it's completely
meaningless for
you to stop us here?
This jutsu of yours will
crumble to dust after the
war. Then someone
on your side will
eventually attempt what
we're doing anyway.
There is no victory,
no matter how
much you struggle.
Get it through
your head, already.
Hope doesn't exist
in this world!
So what? I don't care!
I'm gonna say it does!
It is pointless to argue if
there is or isn't something
during war. How 'bout
we just settle this thing?
When there's a difference of
opinion, you usually go by
majority rule, don't you?
Well?
Good idea. Okay...
We'll call it after we've
erased all of you. And...
I guess I should've
expected that. But...
This world...
-Is going to end!
-Is not gonna end!
Let's go, everybody!
This is the final
deciding battle!
[war cries]
Scatter!
Good job on buying
us some time, Naruto.
Was it enough time to
come up with a strategy?
Thanks to you, I'll be able
to relay it to everyone!
Kakashi told us the
masked man is Obito Uchiha.
But there's no
time to be shocked.
For this fight, we need to
take and maintain the upper
hand and not give 'em
any chance to counter!
Our intel shows that our
enemy boasts impressive eyes.
So first we'll impede
their movement by
destroying their vision.
Hidden Cloud!
Lightning Style!
Flash Pillar!
Gale Style!
Laser Circus.
[groaning]
Ah, their true aim
is to blind Ten Tails!
With the two jutsu from
earlier, Mist Jutsu and
Beetle Jamming.
Along with the large
volume of airborne dust
just stirred up by
the Gale Style.
Hidden Sand, now!
Wind Style: Air
Current Dance!
We'll not just destroy their
vision completely but thwart
them from even
sensing us at all.
And since their sheer bulk
prevents them from hiding,
we'll be able to take
full advantage of
the situation!
We just revealed our jutsu
to him a short while ago,
and he's already
incorporating them into
the battle plan! Leave it
to Shikamaru's old man.
Like father like son!
This will make it
impossible to sense them.
We'll just mow them down
with Ten Tails' attack!
Hidden Stone, proceed now!
Yes, we're on it!
Earth Style:
Vast Mobile Core!
After shutting down
their senses, we'll
immobilize them!
Once we drop Ten Tails,
pour in the quicklime!
Lava Style: Quicklime Jutsu!
[roaring]
Hidden Mist!
You're up next!
Water Style:
Water Bomb Jutsu!
We'll add water to the mix,
fill up the pit, and rapidly
stir up the quicklime!
Hidden Leaf! Finish this!
Sarutobi Clan
members! Let's go!
Fire Style: Majestic
Flame Jutsu!
Dry it with the heat
of Fire Style.
Let it set and,
presto! Immobilized!
Unbelievable.
Who would've thought that
the shinobi from those five
villages could work
so cooperatively.
Without stopping Ten Tails,
we wouldn't have the chance
to go after Obito
and Madara.
To them, Ten Tails is
just a tool to aid in
activating their jutsu.
If we take down those
two casters, the Infinite
Tsukuyomi can't launch!
However, it's best to assume
that Ten Tails' power can't
be suppressed for long.
Only physical attacks work
on Madara. So shinobi with
taijutsu skills, you
guys go after him!
Obito can slip through all
moves and jutsu, but
according to intel,
only for five minutes.
Coordinate with the Medical
Unit and continuously attack
for more than five minutes!
Don't let up!
Naruto, that's right,
it's now time for your--
Allied Shinobi Forces Jutsu!
They're so pitiful.
Yeah.
This hope that they're
clinging to doesn't exist.
[chuckle] Just like their
very lives, at this point.
It seems the Ten Tails
is quite ready.
Don't just stand there
spacing out, Naruto!
This is a battlefield, and
we're at war! People die!
Naruto, your power is
crucial to the plan.
So until we're able
to execute it...
We must protect
you, Naruto!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Ties
That Bind."
The Hyuga are the
mightiest among the Leaf!