UTAKATA: I believe
that's my seat.
-Huh?
Utakata?
-It's Tonbee.
He wants you.
-I leave it to you.
-Again.
- He sure went through
a lot of trouble
to set up this many traps
just to guard an open field.
Talk about going overboard.
- As we speak,
someone is setting off our traps
and rapidly
approaching our fort.
In case this is a
malicious attack,
I have alerted the Hidden
Leaf, in accordance
with the Leaf
master's instructions.
It's impossible for
any ordinary person
to get close to this fort.
But if an enemy does succeed
in reaching this place...
- If the three of
us work together,
we should have no trouble
fighting them off.
We'll show them.
-Why did they target this place?
What reason could they
have for coming here?
- My guess is the forbidden
jutsu that our clan possesses.
CHUSHIN: All those traps.
Once you get past 'em,
there's a huge ravine.
And on top of that, on the
other side, there's a barrier.
You think these people are
a little cautious, or what?
Am I right,
or am I right, Nango?
You tell me.
-Yeah.
CHUSHIN: Was that it?
You're not a man of many
words, are ya?
- Enough of your
babbling, Chushin.
Understand?
You know what they say.
A loose mouth reveals
an empty brain.
-Funny.
I'd say you're the one who
looks bad every time you
open your mouth, Benten.
- Going to such extremes
as they have shows
they're protecting
something valuable.
Get in position.
That must be it.
Ha!
-What?
The barrier...
it's been penetrated.
-These men...
they mean business.
-Benten.
-I'm on it.
-Now we climb this mountain.
TONBEE: Lady Hotaru, take this.
We must keep your grandfather's
forbidden jutsu safe,
so you and our guest,
Utakata, must go.
Escape to the secret
village in the mountains.
-What about you?
-I shall follow you soon.
Now hurry.
-No way.
If we go, we go together.
- The enemy is at our
doorstep as we speak.
This is no time for arguments
and self-indulgence.
-Huh?
-Are you coming?
-Please go, Lady Hotaru.
Utakata, wait.
I beg of you,
take good care of Lady Hotaru.
- I'll repay you for
your hospitality.
-Whew, that was a close one.
This isn't going to
be an ordinary climb,
is it, Akaboshi?
- Considering what
we've been through,
there's gotta be something
pretty special waiting for us
at the summit.
- Lady Hotaru,
you must be extremely careful.
Whatever happens, you must
not leave Utakata's side.
- Tonbee, you have to promise
that you'll follow us.
Promise me.
- Lady Hotaru, think of your own
safety now, and nothing else.
TONBEE (VOICEOVER):
Lord En no Gyoja, I
promise to buy them as
much time as possible.
I will protect Lady
Hotaru, no matter what.
[theme music]
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade,
we just received this.
-This can't be.
[boom]
[groan]
-Lady Katsuyu.
-Oh.
Kakashi.
-Really?
Lady Katsuyu came
this far to greet us?
-No.
She didn't.
-Hm?
-There must be trouble brewing.
The only time...
- The only time Lady
Tsunade uses Lady Katsuyu
is when there's some
kind of emergency.
-Got it.
So we're dealing with
an urgent situation.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I
know how you feel, Shino.
When you're not allowed to
finish what you want to say.
-What?
A secret treaty?
-Yes.
Back during the Third
Great Ninja War,
the leader of the Tsuchigumo
clan, En no Gyoja,
passed down a jutsu which was
responsible for wiping out
an entire village.
The Third Hokage
demanded that such
a dangerous and
destructive jutsu
be classified as forbidden.
And in exchange for
that, the Hidden Leaf
agreed to provide them with
aid whenever the Tsuchigumo
clan found itself in danger.
KATSUYU: Kakashi, you are
to report to the village
for debriefing about
your last mission.
-Understood.
We're battling against time.
Team 7 will go with Captain
Yamato, and head for Mt.
Katsuragi immediately.
-Right.
- But you're not
coming, Kakashi-sensei?
-Do you have a problem with me?
- Uh, that isn't what I
meant, Yamato.
TSUNADE: En no Gyoja passed away
a year ago, and the fort on Mt.
Katsuragi is now occupied
by his granddaughter
Hotaru, and a servant.
Whoever is attacking the
fort is undoubtedly after En
no Gyoja's forbidden jutsu,
and we must prevent them
from getting their hands
on that jutsu at all costs.
-But why did you send Naruto?
TSUNADE: It's a counter
measure against the Akatsuki.
To keep him safe
amongst friends.
-Gen!
-Ko!
-Zet!
-Ka!
CHUSHIN: Did this
feeble old man really
intend to protect the
whole fort by itself?
-Who cares?
It still took
longer than planned,
so hurry up and start searching.
-So that's it, huh?
The fort of the Tsuchigumo clan?
Hm?
Captain Yamato?
-Hm?
- So, have you figured out
what happened here yet?
-Doesn't look like a fight.
Sai.
Report.
- I found fresh footprints
heading directly
toward the fort.
The enemy is a group of four.
- These kunai are from
traps around the fort.
The enemy tripped them,
but seemed to escape injury.
- Then there must be
other traps in the area.
- We'll simply follow
the trail of the ones
that the enemy has
already triggered.
-Good idea.
Because that way,
we'll get to the fort
without setting off
any of the other traps.
- Where's the forbidden
jutsu of En no Gyoja?
-Look, you've lost this fight.
You might as well tell us.
-I know nothing.
-Playing dumb is pointless!
-The granddaughter.
-Hm?
-Yes.
En no Gyoja has a granddaughter.
Perhaps she can
tell us where it is.
-Did you help her to escape?
-You think she has the jutsu?
Is that it?
Hey!
-Stop.
Enough.
I know where we can find her.
We've run out of time here.
Seems like somebody
else is trying
to interfere with our mission.
- Looks like we've
reached a dead end here.
-We'll just lay a bridge across.
Wood Style Jutsu.
- Not too shabby
there, Captain Yamato.
- You mean you're
glad I came along?
-Don't push your luck.
Let's just go.
Hang in there, man.
We've got you.
- He's weak,
but he still has a pulse.
He'll be OK.
-We're a step behind them.
Sai, go on and check the
area, and see
if there's anyone else around.
-Right.
-Good.
He's finally coming around.
-Don't be afraid.
We're from the Hidden
Leaf, and we're
dispatched here to
provide assistance.
And I presume that you're
Lady Hotaru's servant.
Is that correct?
-That's right.
I'm Tonbee.
Lady Hotaru is on her way to a
small village in the mountains
that the Tsuchigumo
clan uses as a hideaway.
- I found a collapsed
opening in the hillside
behind the mansion that
looks like an escape route.
-Yes, that's it.
That's how she got away.
-OK.
We'll follow to make
sure that she's safe.
Sakura, I want you to
remain here with him
and continue to tend
to his injuries.
-Yes, sir.
- Naruto, Sai,
it's time for us to move out.
-Utakata?
There's something I
wanted to ask you.
When we reach the
hideaway, will you still
continue to teach
me jutsu there?
-Continue?
I don't recall
teaching you anything.
-Don't recall?
What about all the lessons
you gave me back at the fort?
- Whatever you learned,
you learned on your own.
Besides, after we reach the
village, you won't need me.
- But there's nobody
that's stronger than you
in the village.
Nobody!
And I want you to teach me.
There's no one else that
I'd rather learn from.
You saved me the
first time we met.
Don't say you've forgotten.
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER):
Stubborn fools.
[panicked shouts]
HOTARU (VOICEOVER):
What was that jutsu?
It was amazing.
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): Now that
they've discovered my location,
I'll have to stay out of
sight until things quiet down.
-Are you all right?
You're hurt.
Please,
come back to our fort with me
and allow me to tend
to your wound there.
You came to my aid,
so you must let me help you.
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): Fort?
-Try to hold on.
I'm going to go get some help,
so don't move from this spot.
Just stay here.
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): Dammit.
I used too much chakra.
HOTARU: Ever since that
moment, I've
wanted to be just like you.
- But I didn't actually
save you that time.
-You did!
- The ninja who attacked were
coming after me, not you.
I merely fought them in
order to protect myself.
I wasn't trying to save you.
- Even so,
after watching you handle them,
I knew that I wanted
to be strong like you.
No, I must be strong.
I simply have to be.
That's why I wish to
learn your amazing jutsu.
- And being strong is
all that matters to you?
-What do you mean?
- I fear you would
end up regretting
that I was your teacher.
You don't really
want to get mixed up
with someone who's a wanted man.
-I don't care about your past.
I trust you.
No matter what happens, I will
always consider you my master.
-I'm not your master!
Don't call me that!
Damn.
-Get away from that girl!
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER):
A shadow clone.
How annoying.
-Give it up!
You're comin' with me!
-No!
-Huh?
HOTARU: He's not your enemy.
He's protecting me!
-Naruto!
Please forgive Naruto for
jumping to conclusions.
Your servant Tonbee
had informed us
that only you had come this
way, Lady Hotaru.
- So Tonbee's still
alive and well?
-Don't worry.
He's fine.
He's under the
care of our medic.
-I'm so glad.
YAMATO: From here on out, you'll
have our protection as well.
-Listen, I'm really sorry.
-You can take over, then.
I leave it to you.
-Hm?
Uh, sure.
I always complete my
missions, so... huh?
-She's all yours.
Take care.
HOTARU: Utakata!
-Hold on.
Where are you going?
-Can't you stay?
At least for a little longer?
Until we reach the village.
-Those guys are strong.
You can rely on them now.
-I don't need bodyguards.
I need someone to teach
me jutsu of my own.
Come with me.
I beg you!
I'll take my training
more seriously than ever!
I'll endure any hardship, and
I'll never, ever cry about it!
And I'll never again
call you master.
I promise you.
And you're not my master!
-I told you not to call me that.
Master.
I'm not foolish enough
to be called that.
[theme music]
- Just why are you
people following me?
- 'Cause we're your
bodyguards, that's why.
HOTARU: I have no need for that.
I can protect myself just fine.
You Hidden Leaf ninja may leave.
NARUTO: You're talking nonsense!
YAMATO: Oh well,
I guess we'd better just
do as she says and leave.
NARUTO: What?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, Successor
of the Forbidden Jutsu.
YAMATO: Now, now, don't worry.