This is
unbelievable.
I know. I had no idea
that he could do this!
Lord Tsuchikage's transporting
the whole island!
[Tsuchikage]
Damn it!
My back's going
to go out again,
I just know it!
Are you certain about this?
Wouldn't it be better
to go by sea?
And we don't really have to
fly quite so high, do we?
Don't be such a
fool, Akatsuki!
You want that giant
snake to sniff us
out again?!
[Akatsuki]
Aww!
Hmm.
Looks like we're
almost there.
"Assemble! Allied
Shinobi Forces!"
The world flipped
over again!
I don't get it!
What is up with this
crazy island, anyway?!
Captain Yamato went outside
to check on what's going on,
but he hasn't come back.
You don't think something's
happened do you?
He's still busy
investigating the
situation, that's all.
Don't you worry
about it.
But I've finished
the mission!
And now I want to go back
home to the Hidden Leaf
Village and wait for Sasuke.
Between the two of us....
We made a promise.
How about now?
No, not yet. Be patient.
The next time you use
your eyes, the world will
be as if it were new.
I, for one,
cannot wait!
Hmf. I really couldn't
care less about this war
of yours, you know.
I will be the one to
destroy the Hidden Leaf.
[Ranka]
Anko, you really should get some
rest. You've been working
practically nonstop, here.
War is at our doorstep.
So right now, we have
to gather as much intel
as we possibly can.
Especially if that intel is
able to save our comrades.
[Muta]
They're back!
You're kidding!
The white snake that
slithered by earlier.
Its chakra is Kabuto's.
This is the hideout,
for sure.
I had my grubs
explore the area.
They've found significant
signs of life underground.
Tokuma, look down! Four o'clock!
With your Byakugan, you can
tell us what's down there!
Please do it,
Tokuma!
Byakugan!
[Tokuma]
[gasp]
No, it... can't be!
What did you see?
Tell me!
Ranka! Prepare to
contact Headquarters!
There's so many of them...
Hey, how come I have
to stay inside here,
but the animals get
to go outside?!
♪ Impatient Naruto, cool it.
Rush too much and you'll
rue it.
♪ You still haven't mastered
Tailed Beast Chakra control.
♪ So your training I'll
personally patrol!
♪ And when we finish with
these drills Tailed Beast
chakra will feel like it's
just an extension of you.
♪ It'll seem like your arms
and legs, it's true!
Yeaaahh!
Whoa!
Catch 'em with your
Tailed Beast Chakra!
Whoa!
♪ Stack 'em like
building blocks,
use your chakra and the Tailed
Beast's to balance those rocks!
Whoaaaa!
Haahaha!
He took the bait!
Nice work, Bee!
And now it's your turn.
Okay. I'm using the Nine
Tail's chakra, right?
I need to stack these blocks
so that they don't fall over.
All right! Here I go!
I've got this!
Huhh??
No, no, that's way too wild.
Right now, you may have a little
control, but it really needs to
be fine-tuned, child.
He's completely
destroyed that rock!
It's hard for him
even to grasp it?!
Damn it! I'm gonna do this!
All right, one more time!
Easy... Easy...
Keep it together... gently...
You gotta put the
spirit in but leave
the power out, yo!
Yes!
Don't be satisfied
with only one,
or you'll never
get it done!
The first one's easy,
but the next
isn't so breezy.
Great job, Lord Bee!
This training will buy
us plenty of time.
[Gaara]
The time has come.
Looks like that old Fence
Sitter has brought all of
them here safely.
We'll hide Turtle Island along
with Bee and the Nine Tails back
at the rear of our headquarters.
You have any objections?
Princess Tsunade?
It's fine.
Very well. Then I will go
and welcome Lord Tsuchikage
when he arrives.
Come on...
Stay put...
just like that...
don't fall...
[rumble]
Whoa! No, no, no!
He was so close!
It wasn't his fault,
but because Turtle
Island moved.
Which means we
must've arrived.
We're finally
here, gramps!
D'esh!
Ow, my back!
That's because you
keep on overdoing it!
I bid you a hearty welcome,
Lord Tsuchikage!
Tell us, what's
the situation?
Both the Eight and
Nine Tails are safe.
However, we were attacked,
and the Wood-Style User
who was guarding the Nine
Tails has been captured.
He was taken? So you're
saying he wasn't killed?
Well that means the enemy
will have more intel on us!
Let's just get going.
I'll explain more inside.
I'll have you
begin the process
of strengthening
Zetsu.
Of course. But first we have
to extract intel from Yamato.
Only, you can't
kill him, okay?
I need him if you
want me to make the
Zetsu stronger.
It would be very easy to
extract intel if I use the
Rinne Ningendo Jutsu.
But then of course he would die.
Are you certain that
we need him alive to
make Zetsu stronger?
Yes.
[Madara]
Venom? So that's how he's
suppressing the Wood Style.
Damn Kabuto. He's studied
Hashirama's cells thoroughly.
I'm using a drug on him that
I developed to keep
Hashirama's power inhibited.
But don't worry. I'm not
gonna use it on the Zetsu.
He must know that I
cultivated all those Zetsu
from Hashirama's cells.
If he were to use this
poison on them... Hm.
He really looked into my
scope and plans, Orochimaru.
N-Ngh! I can't move.
I can't even put my
own decisions into
action like this!
That means, at this rate...
Damn it!
Please, forgive
me, everyone!
Even without the
Rinnegan's power,
We can extract all the intel we
want using the combination of my
truth serum and your Sharingan.
And once we know who
exactly we're facing,
I can select their worst enemy
to send out against them.
There's simply no sense
in us wasting our chakra
when we don't have to.
Huh?
A message from
the Leaf!
It must be new intel!
Retrieve it at once!
[Shikaku]
X marks the enemy's hideout.
It's in a location known as
the Mountain Graveyard.
If we go by land, we'll
pass through the Hidden
Steam and Hidden Frost.
[Gaara]
Advise both villages'
nations to evacuate!
[Shikaku]
According to the Infiltration
and Recon Unit, there are a
hundred thousand enemy forces.
When moving such a large
regiment, only a fraction
is likely to come by sea.
But we'll be in a real
bind if they surround us.
Which means the victor
will be decided by whoever
makes the first move.
Convene the Commando
Unit immediately!
Then have the main battle
regiment divided up into
companies as well,
and have them run through
their formations.
Right!
And make sure that the
logistics and medical
unit is well supplied
with medical ninja tools!
Shikaku, go and help the
intel unit check their
chain of communication.
Roger that.
Find Ao and the
Sensory unit.
And tell them
to hurry up!
Yes ma'am!
Tsuchikage.
These were just completed.
Here is yours.
Oh! They're
ready, are they?
Take it.
Oh! The headbands for the
Allied Shinobi Forces, eh?
They're great! Nice job!
I designed the symbol myself.
Former enemies who once battled
against each other have been
combined into one shinobi force!
And we samurai shall team up
with you shinobi as well.
Now, let's get to work!
Mmm!
Next!
Here!
I'm Kankuro of the Sand,
and I've been named captain
of the Commando Unit.
So your name's
Kankuro, is it?
But what should we use
for your nickname?
Huh?!
Are we really gonna
be okay with a young
kid as our Captain?
What if... what if...
What if because of
his inexperience, he
messes up and panics,
and then I'm forced to
take over and become
the acting captain?!
Oh man! What'll I do then?!
Augghhh!
The headbands have
all been distributed!
We've double-checked all
the medical supplies.
Provisions all
accounted for.
Oiink!
Huh?
Dgh! Who is in charge
of the livestock?!
One of the pigs
has escaped!
Huh?
The Captain's arrived!
Everyone line up!
I've been ordered to lead the
logistics and medical unit.
My name's Shizune.
It's very nice to
meet all of you.
There's one thing that I want
you to remember, no matter what.
This child is not for eating!
Ooo Ooo!
Hi. You're Inoichi,
aren't you?
Who're you?
My name is Tenga, sir!
I've heard a great
deal about you!
I was hoping I
could interview you
and record you.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
Aoba. Boy, you sure have
had a rough time out there.
It's just...
Yamato...
[sympathetic sigh]
Put it out of
your mind for now.
We of the intel unit will
oversee all communications.
Intel must be transmitted
accurately and quickly if
it's to be of any use.
That means in order to do our
jobs well, we have to remain
calm at all times, no matter
what information we might hear.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
A war. So this is it.
You said that your
name was Cee, right?
And this is your very
first war, isn't it?
Yes.
We are the "eyes" of the
Allied Shinobi Forces.
So the performance of our
unit can greatly influence
the tide of battle.
Don't let your
guard down.
Right. I understand,
Captain Ao!
All of you stay
focused and alert!
Right!
I heard that they were
going to split all of
us up into five units,
but I figured that they'd
at least try to group us
together by village.
No, that isn't
going to happen.
This is a war,
you know.
Yeah.
He's right.
This is no time to
be competing with
other villages!
Yeah.
The main regiments are
made up of five units,
each specializing in
different areas of warfare.
The First Company: Mid-Range
Battle Unit contains shinobi who
excel at mid-distance combat.
It's mostly those who
specialize in weapons.
The Second Company: Close-Range
Battle Unit specializes in
hand-to-hand combat.
The shinobi in that unit will
be fighting on the front lines.
The Third Company:
Intermediate-Range Battle
Unit provides support to the
close- and mid-range units.
Its shinobi require
speed and strength.
We're the Fourth Company:
Long-Range Battle Unit.
We'll provide the link
between the intel units and
those on the front lines.
And in addition, we have
to shield the support
units behind the lines.
The Fifth Company:
Special-Range Battle Unit
uses specialized ninjutsu
and tactics.
They have a Special Unit?
That's right. In war,
anything can happen, so
you have to be prepared.
Sure, we were
organized into units.
But it's just wishful
thinking to believe that each
team will operate without a
hitch all the time.
Also, some units may find
advantageous battlefield
positions while others don't.
Situations like that are
when we'll rely on shinobi
with Secret Ninjutsu.
Well, I can't say for sure that
they've thought of everything.
But considering that
eighty thousand shinobi
have all been organized
into units this rapidly,
Seems Shikaku Nara has
done an amazing job.
You know, you'd better
not embarrass your dad.
So this is it, huh?
The war's about to begin.
Captains!
[cheering]
[Shikamaru]
Captain of the First Company,
the Raikage's right-hand man,
Darui of the Hidden Cloud.
Captain of the Second Company,
Kitsuchi of the Hidden Stone.
Captain of The Third Company,
our own Kakashi.
Captain of The Fifth Company,
General Mifune of the
Land of Iron.
The Captain of the Fourth
Company-our company-and
also the Commander-in-Chief
of all battle units,
is Gaara the
Kazekage.
[cheering]
It's time.
Summoning!
Reanimation!
First we have former
Akatsuki members:
Itachi, Sasori, Deidara,
Kakuzu, and Nagato.
Then former Jinchuriki: Yugito
the Two Tails, Yagura the Three
Tails, Roshi the Four Tails,
Han the Five Tails,
Utakata the Six Tails,
and Fuu the Seven Tails.
Next, former Kage: the Second
Tsuchikage, the Third Raikage,
and the Fourth Kazekage.
And, Explosion Style Gari;
Demon of the Mist, Zabuza;
Ice Style Haku.
Hanzo of the Salamander,
Granny Chiyo of the Sand,
Kimimaro of the Kaguya Clan.
From the Leaf: Asuma Sarutobi,
Dan, Hizashi Hyuga.
And a collection of other
exceptional shinobi.
What's more, I've
incorporated Hashirama's
live cells from Yamato.
Looks like they've
adapted quite nicely.
A hundred thousand White Zetsu
enhanced by the strongest
ninja of all time.
[chuckle]
Magnificent!
Let's go.
The Fourth Great
Ninja War,
Begins now!
[Naruto] [younger]
Agh! That look!
That look in his eyes.
It's the same look that
everyone gives me.
No, it's stronger than that.
But...
...it's not for me.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Meeting.
Sasuke and I, we have
a bit of history.
He pisses me off!
[Lee]
Ahh! My bodysuit shrank!
And I do not have anything
else that is clean that I
can wear today!
Wait, I know!
With a breathing technique
passed down through
generations, I can control
my muscles' elasticity!
[hyperventilating]
Yes!
Fight! Fight!
AAHHHH!