[panting]
[playful fighting]
Huh?
(Kiba)
Granny? I'm
coming in!
Here! A care
package from
your daughter
and her husband.
Oh my! Thank you
ever so much!
Here's a letter
for you!
[happy barking]
Hey! It's Kiba!
Yeah, he's been a big
help. He volunteered
to be the messenger
for the entire Village!
Look at those
two! Always
together...
[small laugh] You
were like that once!
Huh?
Remember? How you
were completely
stuck to Sasuke?
That's just cause we
were both on Squad 7!
You were the same way!
I don't mean that!
Did you really forget?
I mean when you
were stuck for real!
Oh! That's right!
(Naruto)
Now I remember!
We were on a mission
to retrieve a treasure
that belonged to a
Feudal Lord's sister!
A treasure that had
been taken by thieves!
We've received intel
on the thieves who
took the golden statue.
They're either on land on
this forest path, or they're
sailing by boat and will land
somewhere in this area.
So, we'll split into
two teams and wait for
them in both locations.
Now, to keep the teams
balanced, I'll be on
one, and you three
will be on the other.
Hold on, what
does that mean?
Are you saying that
Sasuke needs all the
help he can get?
No! He means
YOU!
I know I'm not up to
your level yet, but I
doubt you need three
on one team!
So why don't you
take Naruto off
my hands?
You subtract his
skill from yours,
and we'll be even.
[gasp] Sasuke! is this
just a clever ruse so
that you and I can be
alone together!?
Ugh! Come on!
You've gotta
be kidding!
Why would my
skill subtract
from his!?
Simple, because you
have nothing to add.
WHAT!?
Oh! Sasuke wants to
be with me so much
he can't even wait!
You're as annoying
as he is...
[screaming]
[gasp]
Pay attention now.
Uhhh??
I'll watch the pier,
and you three will
keep and eye on this
path in the forest.
If the thieves
appear, notify
me right away.
Do not underestimate
them. Our mission is
to retrieve a stolen
golden statue.
We must proceed with
the utmost caution.
If the thieves appear
at my location, I will
send a signal with this.
When this lightning
barrel is tossed
into the air, it will
release a thunderbolt.
Once you verify that
it went off, rush
straight to the location
that it marks.
You better be
careful with that.
I don't wanna get
zapped again!
Remember, you
three are not
to act on your
own...
[groan]
[gasp]
It's the thieves!
[struggling
grunts]
[grunts]
You idiot! Be careful
with that treasure,
you hear me!?
Yes! Sorry,
Boss Jako!
(Jako)
Get it together!
Yes sir!
(Thinking)
The treasure's in
that wicker box?
This is it!
This is my
big chance!
You're amazing,
Naruto! You're
so much cooler
than Sasuke!
You really showed
him up!
Huh!?
(Thinking)
Don't tell me he's
planning the same thing!
[scoff]
(Thinking)
I'm not gonna
lose to him!
Huh!?
[gasps]
Whaaa?
What is this!?
[struggling grunts]
[shouts]
[shouting]
Damnit! They
took the treasure!
(Thinking)
What do they think they're
doing!? We're supposed to
notify Kakashi Sensei first!
Huh? There's
another one?
[gasp]
Ahh!
[cringing]
[grunts]
You two! Give
me that treasure
back!
No way!
Forget it!
Then take THIS!
Ahhh!
[grunt]
I'm not gonna
lose it now!
[whimper]
[screaming]
Damn!
So the Hidden
Leaf's coming
after us, huh?
Were those two
the only ones
with you?
[stubborn grunt]
[gasp]
I know that
there must be
more of you...
Yeah, that's why
you tried to send
that signal to
reveal our location!
Pft!
[gasp]
It's pretty
cool, isn't it?
Clearly I'm a natural
born thief who's
rotten to the very
core of his being...
So rotten, in fact,
that as you can clearly
see, even my chakra
has become befouled.
Those two friends
of her's escaped
downstream...
We'll split up and
search the river
until we find them.
And then we'll
take back our
treasure...
What do we
do with her?
(Jako)
We'll bring her
with us and keep
her as a hostage,
[panting]
I can't believe
they stole something
as ridiculous as
this- this teddy bear.
The thunderbolt...
The signal to warn
Kakashi...
It didn't go
off, did it?
Oh... no.
Maybe Sakura
couldn't release it.
You think Sakura
was captured!?
Huh?
[grunt]
Huh!?
What... What?
...WHAT IS THIS!?
What!? What's
going on!?
We're stuck
together!
Ready!? Pull!!
[grunting]
[defeated groans]
[charging shouts]
[painful grunts]
[weary sigh]
[screaming]
[kissing]
[gasps]
Why do I
always end up
kissing you!?
You took the
words right out
of my mouth!
[embarrassed sigh]
Don't worry!
You'll see
your friends
soon enough!
After they return the
treasure, I'll make sure
that you're all back together
again, in the after life.
Your ninja, but even
ninja become helpless
if their hands are tied!
(Thinking)
Sasuke...
Naruto...
Sakura...
While we're stuck
like this, Sakura
could be...
Ahh!
Naruto! Stop,
you idiot!
Hang tight, Sakura!
I'm coming to save
you right now!
Listen! Just
wait you loser!
[grunting]
Ah! Ooof!
Just what the
hell are you
doing, Sasuke!?
I mean, don't you
even care what
happens to Sakura?
Look, we will
save her! But we
can't do anything
when we're like this!
Saving her no matter
what stands in the way
is what a true friend
would do!
I.. I just--!
(Naruto)
I don't want people
to say that I'm scum!
Who doesn't care
about his friends!
Those ninja who
abandon their friends
are even worse than
scum...
Yeah, fine! But
joining up with
Kakashi is still
the right move!
It'll increase
our chances of
survival!
Look don't talk
to me about our
chances!
That just depends
on how hard we
work to save her!
No way I'll
let her die
over this
stupid thing!
You idiot!
Naruto! Stop it!
Damnit! Damnit!
Damnit!!
But someone who
doesn't take his
mission seriously
is scum too.
[sob]
Gotta pee.
You what!?
I said...
I gotta go
take a leak!
Hey! What in
the hell!?
Oh, uh, okay.
One handed then.
What!? Cut it
out! Not so close!
You're gonna splash
it on me!
Listen, I'm sorry.
But if you gotta go
then you gotta go.
Just hold it!
I can't!
[arguing]
Huh!?
Ahhhh!
[grunts]
Don't get in
my way, Naruto!
Are you kidding!?
You're the one
who's in my way!
Stop! Give us back
the treasure!
[screams]
Multi Shadow Clone
Jutsu!
[gasp]
You can't weave a
sign like this, idiot!
You need two hands!
It's like I said
before... We don't
have a chance!
I know that now!
[grunt]
Naruto! Stop this!
No. No way!
If you're not in,
I'll cut my arm
off, then go!
I'm gonna beat
this guy! And
then go and
Save Sakura!
[grunt]
[frustrated gasps]
You're always
so reckless!
Ooof!
Heh heh! Alright!
Let's go!
If those guys came this
far, they'll probably
find us before we can
meet Kakashi Sensei.
If that's the case, it'll
be faster if we just make
this guy tell us where Sakura
is and save her first.
Sasuke...
However... to
succeed we have
to work together
perfectly.
Huh!? Got it!
Ooohhh... I
just remembered...
I gotta pee.
[gasp]
[sigh]
Me too...
[chuckle]
What do you mean
Sugaro still hasn't
reported back yet?
Ya know... I
wonder...
(Sasuke)
You're wondering
right!
(Naruto)
We got him!
(Thinking)
Sasuke...
Naruto...
There!
Tsk!
Ha! That's right!
We're back and
free at last!
Only a Feudal Lord's
sister would own a
statue like that one!
And that's exactly
what managed to
pull us apart.
(Thinking)
So their hands
are free now?
Here's our offer:
We'll let you have
this back, in exchange
for our teammate!
Refuse, and I'll
pulverize every
one of you!
Trust me, that
won't be a problem
now that my hands
are free!
We're both ninja.
Surely you don't
think mere robbers
can defeat us!
You can't!
[grunt]
Ha! Tell me, why
are you gritting your
teeth so hard?
(Jako)
You're sweating. You're
veins are practically
popping out of your skin!
Alright then! If
you're truly free
then come over here!
(Jako)
Come on!
Just as I thought.
Their hands are
still fused!
Get em!
He called our bluff!
Then we have
no choice...
Why you!
Huh?
Ahhh!
Naruto!
Right!
Argh!
[painful grunts]
Oh no...
not that!
(Sakura)
Guys! Look out!
[gasp]
That treasure is
all mine!
[attack roar]
Even like this
we can take that
guy! Let's go!
Right!
Ahhh!
[attack shout]
Don't even
think about it!
Fire Style!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
No way! A
hand sign?
Heh! No. Even if we
could weave signs,
we couldn't infuse
chakra like this, idiot.
Don't treat me
like a fool!
But we do
have a combination
attack!
What!?
Pachinko Jutsu!
Ahhh!
[chuckle]
(Kakashi)
Well, maybe it can
be welded down and
re-cast...
Though, that's
a pretty big maybe.
(Sakura)
Oh, Sasuke!
Thank you!
Whaaat? He didn't
do it by himself,
you know Sakura...
This is getting
ridiculous! Can't
you do anything
Kakashi Sensei!?
Look, that thief
already told you
guys!
It'll just crumble
apart on it's own
in two or three days!
If I have to put
up with him that
long, I'll kill him!
I should be the
one who's saying
that!!!
[laughing]
Uh. Uh-oh.
I've gotta go.
Again!?
Yes, again. And
this time it's
number two!
You've gotta
be kidding me!
Don't you dare,
Naruto!!
C'mon! We already
peed together,
what's the big deal?
This is so
much worse!
Those who abandon
their friends are
worse than scum...
These three overcome
their differences so
easily...
[chuckle]
(Kakashi)
The main purpose of
this mission is to
rescue the hostage.
(Kakashi)
That mean's we'll have to
confront the bandits who are
stealing the Village's crops.
(Asuma)
Their hideout's located in
a natural fortification.
(Asuma)
And they have three
forts guarding the
only way in.
(Asuma)
But the trickiest challenge
will be outwitting their
clever leader, Baji.
(Shikamaru)
Then I guess that's
just what we'll have
to do.
(Naruto)
NExt time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Team 10's Teamwork"
(Shikamaru)
I'm counting on
you guys!