Well, we finally made it!
It's been over two years
since we were last here.
Do you think he'll give
us what we came for?
All we want to do is
rebuild the Hidden Leaf.
I can't imagine why he
wouldn't want to help us.
I hope you're right.
Ninjutsu is all about
being challenged!
[gasps]
[chuckle]
Looks like he hasn't
changed at all.
Not one bit!
As I'm sure all of you
are aware, the village
is short-handed.
So teams dispatched on
D-rank missions will be
made up of genin only.
But Guy Sensei...
With Lee still recovering
in the hospital, we can
only form a two-man team!
Yes! And that's why we're
shuffling things around!
[gasp]
We're going to shake things
up and totally reimagine
our current team formation!
Now say hello to the
new face on Team Guy!
A new teammate?!
But who?!
♪ [fanfare]
Naruto?
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm the new face,
whatever that means.
What?! He's our
new teammate?!
Aw, I thought we'd get
someone really cool!
Yeah.
Well I'm sorry to
disappoint you!
With Naruto rounding out this
three-man team, you'll be
assigned a D-rank mission.
Oh, I see. Then I'm here to
take Bushy Brow's place.
Lee's gonna be just fine!
I check in on him at the
hospital regularly!
Rest assured, young one!
Aagh!
So what's our mission, then?
All the details
are in here.
You'll be the team captain
for this mission, Tenten.
Huh?! What?!
Ordinarily, I'd pick Neji.
But for this mission,
you're the best choice.
Me, really?
Well, now that that's all
settled, I'd better get going.
Good luck, guys!
Wait! Guy Sensei!
I can't believe
he just took off!
Well? What's the
plan, Captain?
Uh!
That's right, I'm the team
captain for this mission!
I don't know, maybe
Neji should lead us.
Quiet, new guy!
I'm the captain,
and that's that!
Can't... breathe...
I can handle this!
I'll make sure this
mission succeeds!
Calm down, it's just
a D-rank mission!
All right, then!
Come on, you guys!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
You got this all wrong, guys.
Deploy! Team Tenten
This is it.
It's just a hut.
Yep. The Hidden Leaf Ninja
Tool Research Lab.
Back when this place
was originally built,
it was inside the
Hidden Leaf Village.
Our mission today is to
procure a thousand kunai
and a thousand shuriken,
and to see if there are
any new ninja tools that
might be available.
Why do we have
to get so many?!
There's no way we can
haul back all that stuff!
Now I get why Tenten was
chosen as the captain
for this mission.
Hmm?
[Neji]
It's because Tenten's
scroll uses the
Transportation Technique,
which allows her to store
various ninja tools and
then summon them whenever
she needs them.
The Trans...
Transportation
Technique?
You know the Summoning
Jutsu, right?
Yeah.
This technique Is simply the
ninja tool version of that.
Oh. Well, then,
that means,
We don't need to carry
anything back with us at all!
Yes, that's
exactly right.
New ninja tools, huh?
What's up, Captain?
You okay?
I wonder what these new
ninja tools will be like.
Ninjutsu is all about being
challenged!
Huh?
Let's go!
Hey! Wait!
Just hold on!
New ninja tools!
[panicked fretting]
Huh, I wonder what went
wrong with the experiment
this time around?
Are you
Sir Iou?
Huh?! Yes, I am, and
what can I do for you?
We're here on
Hidden Leaf business!
Oh, of course,
welcome!
So--
Fire!!!
Uh...
Hey!
I understand you have
some new ninja tools?
Sure do! Would you
like to see them?
You bet!
Shouldn't we discuss the
regular tools, first?
No, this is a
captain's decision!
Hmmm. Shoseki,
bring them in.
Yes!
Here they are!
First, take a look at this!
[Iou]
A Double-Bladed Kunai!
A Double-Bladed Kunai?
It has two blades to
make it even deadlier!
Twice as much, actually!
Yahh!
Yeow, that stings!
Oh, by the way, those
blades are coated
with poison, so be
careful with that.
Sure, now you tell me.
A kunai like this is way too
dangerous for the wielder.
Precisely! And that's
just why I made this!
The Double-Handled Kunai!
No blade?!
But that's
pointless, then!
Not your cup of tea, huh?
Well, how about this?!
Thousand-Bladed Shuriken!
[Tenten]
You can't even hold it!
[Iou]
Instead of a Chained-Sickle,
a Sickle-Chain!
[Neji]
Didn't expect that.
We can't use any
of this junk!
What was that?!
Do you have any
other ninja tools?
Of course! If these don't
interest you, I have something
really big I can show you!
Something big?!
Yes, please!
It's called a
Ninja Shuriken!
Hey, why do I
have to do this?!
Neji!
Let's switch places!
How's this work?
This beauty is a shuriken
that carries a ninja
pilot who can change its
direction as it flies!
Do you see this lever here?
Simply turn it left or
right to steer, okay?
Yeah. Right.
Now let's launch
this thing!
Aaaahhhhh!
Naruto!
AaAAAaaAAAaAAaAAAaa!
The lever! Quick,
pull the lever!
Huh?
Hwaaaahhh!
Any other
ninja tools?
No. That's all
I got right now.
[Naruto]
Arrrgghh!
Your lab was kicked out
of the village because
everything you made was
a big failure, right?!
Failures are
really challenges.
[sigh]
You don't deny it, then?
I think we've seen
enough of the new tools.
Please fulfill this
supply request:
a thousand regular
kunai and a thousand
regular shuriken.
But the regular ones
are no fun at all!
Just get 'em ready!
Okay, okay!
[hammering]
This work is so boring,
isn't it, Shoseki?
Can't argue there, Sensei.
It's boring, all right.
Please, guys.
Just normal ones.
We aren't leaving
without our order!
[sigh] What a
let-down...
Hey, what's the matter,
Captain? You look
so disappointed.
Oh, it's just...
I was hoping for
some new ninja tools.
But not those, huh?
The other members of Team Guy
mostly specialize in
close-contact fighting,
so in battles I often have to
hang back and provide them
with back-up from a distance.
Oh, I get it.
Don't get me wrong;
I don't mind doing that.
But I was really hoping that I
could find some new ninja tools
that would allow me to fight on
the front lines for a change.
[Naruto]
If that's all you want,
then stop thinking so
much and just do it!
Huh?
[chuckle] You really like
the simple approach.
I'll give you that!
Huh? I do?
Yeah. And I think you
just might be right.
[Neji]
Hey.
Huh?
Hm?
[Tenten]
Yes, Neji?
The fish
is ready.
Oh!
Then I'll just go and let
Sir Iou and Shoseki know.
Where are they?!
[Neji]
They must've run off.
[Tenten]
What?!
Ugh! Boy, those
two are completely
useless.
What now,
Captain?
Are we heading
home or what?
Hmm.
Hold on.
[Tenten]
It's true that their
inventions are useless.
But their enthusiasm for
inventing is genuine!
[Naruto]
I guess.
But so what?
I don't believe that
Sir Iou would simply
abandon this research lab.
Neji, Can you
search this area?
Sure.
Byakugan!
[Neji]
There!
You found it!
What's this?!
They must be up ahead.
This trap is so obvious!
Now just stand back;
I'll destroy it!
No, wait!
Hyaah!
Hey, what do you think
you're doing, Captain?!
Look there.
You got this?
I'm on it.
Incoming!
Rotation!
[phew]
That was pretty
close, huh?
Neji.
I've got this.
Okay.
Right there!
You did it!
Not yet!
[clattering]
Here they come!
You got them all
with one attack?!
Come on.
This is--!
Hehe! Wow, cool!
Just amazing!
The brilliance
of that blade...
What impressive design!
All of them are just
so beautiful!
I want to take them
all home with me!
Now Neji, Naruto,
start bringing these
tools over to me!
Boy, I sure hope
they all fit!
Heavy!
Yeah, what's going on?
This thing won't budge!
Hey! You can't take
my masterpieces
without permission!
[Tenten]
We're asking you to
please share these ninja
tools with our village!
Forget it! Heh!
Huh?! But why won't you?
The user is essential
when it comes to
these weapons.
I don't want my work handled
by someone who doesn't know
what they're doing!
Still, I am impressed that
you bypassed my traps.
Sir Iou, I've trained
with all different
kinds of ninja tools.
Getting past those
traps was easy!
Hmm.
[under breath]
get that thing.
Then let me test your
skill once more!
there's another ninja tool
I recently developed.
Oh? What's that?
This is without any doubt
my finest masterpiece,
and I call it Jidanda!
Jidanda?!
[crash]
Huh?
[klaxon]
What's going on!?
Oops! My bad.
I set off one
of his traps.
And a lame one too.
I barely felt it!
Who are
you two?!
Oh, we're just here
to pick up some of
those ninja tools
you've been making.
I'm allied with
the Hidden Leaf!
There's nothing for you here,
so the sooner you leave us
alone the better!
Heh. The Leaf village is
in chaos right now.
That's how we slipped across
the border so easily!
Rrrgh!
[Tenten]
Stay back, Sir Iou!
Hey, look!
You were right, Kusune.
A three-man team
made up of brats.
The Leaf must be even
more short-handed
than we thought!
Neji, take the left;
Naruto, the right.
I'm gonna provide back-up
and guard Sir Iou.
Right.
Scatter!
Get 'em,
Kusune!
Right!
What are those?!
Doesn't matter!
Heh!
Damn it!
Heh.
Ow!
But how-?!
No, it can't be!
Those are two of my
prototype ninja tools,
Dako and Tsuru-Kame!
But how did those
two get them?!
Forgive me
Sensei!
What's the
matter, Shoseki?
The funding from the Leaf
Village wasn't enough to
maintain our research,
so I sold off some of
our ninja tools...
You did what?!
The men said they
were just collectors,
and you told me those
tools were only prototypes.
Yes, but any weapon can
potentially be used in
battle, you fool!
And besides, even if
they're prototypes,
they're still my
inventions!
They're ours now!
What?!
Augh!
Naruto! No!
The Dako is a spear the
wielder can direct to
stretch, contract, and bend!
[gasp]
Uah!
[Tenten]
Neji!
Tsuru-Kame has a
built-in mechanism for
firing ninja tools.
Heh heh!
Did I get him?
Huaah!
What?!
He's mine!
I'm shutting you down!
Uagh!
What weak points do
those weapons have?
There aren't any!
But you said they
were just prototypes!
I called them that merely
because I was using the data
gathered from their development
to create an even more
powerful ninja tool.
Please, I really
need to use it now!
[Iou]
It is...
The Jidanda!
Those brats are pretty
good at close combat.
you'll be fine if you
keep your distance.
I wouldn't be
so confident.
Huh?!
Because I'm your
opponent now!
Hup!
That thing is...
Jidanda?!
How cool!
That thing
looks awesome!
'Course it's
also enormous...
And heavy!
[Iou]
It's not about strength!
It's about your technique!
Technique...
That's Iou's
new invention?
Hand it over quietly,
and we'll let you live.
No, this
is mine!
Then we'll just
take it from you!
[gasp]
Damn!
Neji!
You're going down first!
Eagh!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let's go!
Heh. Rapid fire!
Agh! Augh! Ah!
Oof!
Neji! Naruto!
I've gotta do something!
I'm the team captain!
Rgh! Of all the times for
me to run out of ammo.
Locked and loaded!
Whoa. Man, what
was that weapon?!
I don't know.
All right.
Let's end this.
Guys! Get out of the way, now!
Huh?!
Waah!
She used the handle
to attack us?!
That thing stretched
just like my spear does!
You got this?
Yeah, you bet!
Ha!
Just stay back and let
me handle this one!
Uh... Okay!
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
She intends to control
it through the recoil
of the explosions!
Ha!
Go!
Those blasts aren't just
to move that metal ball.
They also create a
defensive shield.
Go!
Hrrrrah!
I'll stop her!
Right!
We did it!
Nice job!
Now... Go!
Eyaah!
No way!
[relieved sigh]
[woozy groans]
[Iou]
Well done!
You handled Jidanda
like a champ!
Thanks, Sir Iou!
Does that mean you're
going to let me have
Jidanda for my very own?!
Ah, no, sorry.
What?
I noticed a few adjustments
that need to be made to it.
Shoseki, let's
get started.
Thank you, I'll go ahead
and take that, please.
Hey! Wait!
But you can't!
You know, you really
are quite adept with
ninja tools.
You may take all the first-
rate weapons you like.
[sigh]
We did complete the
mission, Tenten.
Yeah, you shouldn't be
disappointed at all!
And I gotta admit,
you were really
cool, Captain!
I guess
you're right.
Well...
Thanks!
Are you ready?
Huh?
Okay!
I hope they're done making
the adjustments to Jidanda!
[Kotetsu]
We've reached
Training Ground Zero.
[Naruto]
Come on! Let's hurry up and
catch that damn ostrich!
[Shino]
The way I see it...
[Rock Lee]
Whoever we face,
I will defeat them!
[Kotetsu]
By the way, have you three
ever teamed up before?
[Naruto]
Mm, uh, nope!
[Kotetsu]
I have my doubts about this.
But I guess we'd better get
started on our mission!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Animal District."
[Kotetsu]
What in the hell are
those things, anyway?!