What's wrong?
The enemy's disguising
themselves as allies!
That means you
could be an enemy,
too!
We can't trust
anyone!
What is going on here?!
There's confusion
spreading everywhere
in the allied ranks!
What?! Granny?!
Uh! What up, bra?
Bee! Get your eyes
up here now! Have
some respect for
the Hokage!
Oh no, Bro! I'm just
shocked, that's all.
I promise you I meant
no offense.
It's just that the
Hokage's jugs are
definitely immense!
We're here to stop you!
You will not pass!
It looks like Naruto's
in control of the Nine
Tails' power. Well done,
Naruto.
Such immense chakra!
Listen, Bro, please.
You gotta let Naruto
go free. This is a
personal plea. I can
can vouch for him,
that I guarantee.
Enough! Silence! We're
fighting to protect you
both! If you're captured-
The enemy will complete
their jutsu. And the
world will end. Iruka
Sensei told us.
So why are you doing
this?! Are you both
fools?!
(annoyed grunt)
It's because of all
that! It's because
they're protecting
us! I can't stand
that people are
dying for me!
So what if we do
manage to win this
war?! And only I'm
left!
It just isn't
worth it!
I don't want that!
But it would be better
than the whole world
ending! That's the
reason why people are
prepared to sacrifice
themselves to protect
you!
I can't sit here doing
nothing! Not when I'm
unharmed and people are
out there fighting for
me! That's not the
kind of person I am!
I can't!
Besides!
Enough! You still
shall not pass!
If you won't listen...
He can keep up with
me in this mode?!
What is that punch?!
Man, it's powerful!
Gotta avoid a direct
hit!
Granny Tsunade, you
understand, don't
you?! I can stop
this war, I know it!
Let me go!
Please, Granny...
I'm a part of the
Allied Shinobi Forces
now, Naruto. And the
orders I've been given
are to stop you. Even
though I'm Hokage, I still
can't act independently
on this matter!
(disappointed sigh)
All right. I understand
the position that you're
in, Granny. So...
I'll force my way out!
Faster this time!
How's this?!
You're fast, old
man Raikage.
Nine Tails Chakra Mode
is able to match the
Raikage's speed! That's
just incredible!
There's no shinobi
who's faster than I
am. Not since the
Fourth Hokage died!
Huh?! Wait, you
knew my dad?!
Yes, we exchanged
blows many times.
I found him to be
a noble man.
A finer shinobi
never lived.
Jiraiya, one of the
Leaf's three great
shinobi, called him
a Child of Prophecy,
a savior.
But even with all
his power, why is
he not here to
help? Because he
underestimated the
tailed beast. You
are his son, have
you learned nothing
from his sacrifice?!
You continue to talk
of uncertain outcomes,
and yet-
You know what?
Just stop it.
Don't talk about
my father.
Back then, when
you were first
born...
Minato said, "I'm
a father now!"
And he cried!
And...
He was ready to
die for his son.
He sealed half of the
Nine Tails' overpowering
chakra inside himself.
Stopping the upheaval
in the world. Dealing
with Madara and the
calamity he wanted to
unleash. He left it
all to his son.
He died, bequeathing
everything to you,
Naruto. Believing in
you!
My dad...
He believed in you
with all his heart!
You're wrong! The
Fourth Hokage did
not fail that day!
If you continue to
insist on going...
I will kill you
right here and now!
What?! No! Raikage!
That will at least
buy us a little time
until the Nine Tails
is revived.
And then our enemy
will be forced to
delay his plans!
Looks like you
want to die.
Wait!
Bee! What is this?!
Ah! He stopped him!
You kill him, and it's
the same as killing me
and the Eight Tails,
you see why? If we die,
the enemy's plans
would also go awry!
To let Naruto go to
the battlefield, my
life I'd gladly yield.
Octopops...
Raikage! You can't make
arbitrary decisions
without the other
Allied leaders!
I won't allow it,
Supreme Commander!
My duty to the Allied
Shinobi Forces is to
ensure victory in this
war! And I'll do
anything to achieve
that!
Then like the Eight
Tails said, why target
Naruto over him?
If push comes to shove,
then I'm prepared to
kill anyone, even my
own younger brother!
But if I have to
choose, then the one
I pick is Naruto!
Bee is the Jinchuriki
who can control his
Tailed Beast's power,
which makes him a
stronger military
asset.
Now let go, Bee!
No way, fool
ya fool!
Listen to me, you
Jinchuriki can't
just run around doing
whatever you please!
You belong to your
nation and to your
village! You maintain
the balance of power
for your people.
Yours is a very
special existence!
You can't do whatever
you want! You must
understand your
position!
That might be so, but
inside of me, hidden,
there's something
personal called spirit
that I can't abandon,
no matter what may
happen.
Because with that
gone, I'm just
another weapon.
(angry growl)
Just tell me why!
Why are you defending
this boy, Bee?!
We're bumping fists...
You gotta understand!
Can't you read what's
in my soul, my brother?
Doesn't seem like any
decent prospects this
time.
Okay, listen up,
all of you!
Only one of you can
prove worthy to
inheriting the title
of Bee.
Ay here is a candidate
to be named as the next
Raikage! You all know
that here in the Hidden
Cloud, each Raikage
is assigned a tag
team partner.
Someone who will draw
out the Raikage's full
power. And to be "Bee"
is to be the bodyguard
of the Raikage.
We'll test your
compatibility with
Ay, one by one.
Try to chop off this
dummy's head by teaming
up with Ay and using the
Double Lariat on it.
Remember! The Double
Lariat will only work
correctly if equal
strength is applied
from both sides.
If one side is too
strong or too weak,
the head will only
bend!
First, bump fists
with Ay to determine
how much power you
should use.
Then you'll test out
your Double Lariat
on the dummy!
Okay! Let's start with
you on the far right.
Thank you, sir!
I'm honored!
Ahhh!
Ahhahhahh!
Next!
Yes, sir!
Hnh!
Ahh!
Next!
Yes, sir!
(fighting grunts)
Next!
Yes, sir!
(attacking grunts)
Next!
Yes, sir!
Agh!
Next!
Yes, sir!
It appears that we
won't find anyone
this time, either.
If he'd had any siblings,
we wouldn't have to go
through all of this over
and over again.
Next!
Hm...
Wait, look, Lord
Raikage.
Seems we may have
found one.
Wheeeee!
(chuckle)
You're a bit of
an odd one.
Bump fists with
me one more time.
We two are brothers
from this day on!
Nice to know you, Bee.
Let's do it, Bee.
Show you know the
plan by bumping
fists, man. "Kay, bro.
Yeah!
Yeah! Eat up, now!
You can't keep up
with me if you don't
get bigger and stronger!
Okay, Brotha!
Our next mission is
a scroll recovery.
Wait, no way!
Yes, way!
'Kay, Bro?
Is he asleep?
Yeah...
Bee's a good shinobi.
He's got talent, too.
Though not really as
a rapper. You know
what I'm talking about?
(chuckling)
Yes, I agree.
He'll probably be
next, the Jinchuriki
of the Eight Tails
after me.
Have you heard for
sure if that's going
to be the elders'
decision?
No, no one's
said anything.
Both my old man and
my uncle failed. And
I'm not compatible
either.
Listen, as your
cousin, I think-
But come on, you've
kept the Eight Tails
under control up
until this point. So-
Just listen to me!
Only a Jinchuriki
would understand.
Even your close
friends look at you
differently after
the process.
Well, they might believe
that they're treating you
the same. But they're not
really...
You can never look back,
only toward the future.
But that future is filled
with darkness and loneliness.
Have you achieved
compatibility, if you
walk through life with
the shadow of your death.
It fills your whole
mind day in and day
out, until you become
so consumed you don't
know who or what you
are. It feels like
someone made a hole
in your heart.
And the Tailed Beast
constantly waits to
pounce on that weakened
heart and run amok.
You live with the
constant fear of
death. You'd soon
rather just die.
But still, you have a
knack for ninjutsu as
well as skill, ancestry,
virtue, everything!
True. That's the exact
reasoning that they
used then they chose
me to become the Eight
Tails' Jinchuriki.
But...
To be honest, none
of those things are
necessary to be a
Jinchuriki.
Oh? So what
is, then?
Having something that
can fill that hole
in your heart!
And what is it?
That something?
It can be anything.
You'll know it when
you find it. Because
it will keep you strong.
So, make sure
that Bee finds it.
Another failure. This
time, eight people were
victims of his rampage.
The Eight Tails' is very
powerful. He's much more
difficult to contain than
the Two Tails.
How much more can we
take? How much longer
will we have to go
through this?
The next Jinchuriki
is supposed to be...
...that child.
It's quite an honor to
be the Tailed Beast host!
So, now I pay tribute to
your sacrifice, no boast!
Yeah!
I don't think
he'll make it.
You brat! How dare
you kill my comrades!
So you continue to
insult me and treat
me with contempt?!
Let's do it, Bee.
Okay, you got
it, Bro!
Hold on! This brat's
Bee?! Then that means
you two must be the
A/B combo?!
So you must be
familiar with our
technique, then?
(scared gasp)
The Double Lariat?!
Bee, we still have a
long way to go before
the Double Lariat is
where it needs to be.
I'm still toning down
my strength to match
yours. You're going to
have to get stronger!
(insulted grunt)
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I got it, fool, ya fool!
How dare you address
your big brother as "fool,
ya fool!" This means
the Iron Claw for you!
I'm gonna surpass you
someday, you'll see!
And on that day, I'll
be carefree!
The trick to this
technique is keeping
both our strengths
equal. You're going
to have to bring
yourself up to
par.
That sounds ideal to
me. And I'll do it,
too, you'll see! Easy
as one-two-three!
'Cause talking down
to you is my fantasy!
(chuckling)
Such delusions will
have to wait until
you've honed your
Lariat!
This is it.
We'll seal the Eight
Tails inside Bee
tonight.
Yeah.
Having something that
can fill that hole in
your heart.
It can be anything.
You'll know it when
you find it.
So, make sure
that Bee finds
it.
Yo, what's up, Bro?
Hm?
In a little while
you're going to
become a Jinchuriki.
Everything's going to
change. Your life is
going to be very hard.
Oh! No sweat, I kinda
figured that might
happen.
Maybe I'll name that
octopus while I do my
own rappin'. I'll get all
eight tentacles clappin'!
Listen up, Bee. Always
tell me everything,
you understand me?
No secrets. Because
you're very special
to me! You and I are
the ultimate tag team!
(pleased chuckle)
Even with the Steel
Shell Seal, I wouldn't
be surprised if the
Eight Tails' goes crazy.
We'd better stay on
guard and keep an
eye on him.
Wheee!
The Eight Tails, that
be me, the rappin'
Killer Bee, on the
scene so take heed!
Yeah! Fa show!
The blonde hair and
the Teleportation
Jutsu! That's gotta
be the Leaf's Yellow
Flash! We gotta
retreat right now,
don't you think?!
So that's him. The one
who singlehandedly
stopped our recovery
of the Nine Tails.
And I know you. You're
the son of the Hidden
Cloud's Third Raikage.
You're called Unruly Ay.
I've heard that you're
quite fast yourself.
Hmph! We can take him,
the two of us, Bro!
Fool, ya fool!
Everyone, stay
out of this.
I'll fight them!
He countered me at
my top speed!
That's...
Forgive me, Bee.
You doing all right?
Whoa, no way.
Then is he the Eight
Tails' Jinchuriki?!
Not good.
That's the signal!
Minato! We need to
retreat!
That was nothin'!
At least, for the
Eight Tails', that
be me, the rappin'
Killer Bee!
You really are quite
brave. You overcame
being Eight Tails'
Jinchuriki, to be
your own ninja. You
have something very
powerful.
Hmmh! He's more
talented than
even I am!
No, it's more than
that. He already has
something even more
important.
Hm?
Ay, you have a very
fine family. As do I.
I suspect the next
time we meet, we'll
be fighting as one
Kage against another.
But if you don't figure
out soon what your little
brother considers most
precious to him, he will
be neither a
Jinchuriki nor
human.
Hmph! Don't try to
fool me with that
nonsense! You're not
getting away!
The Teleportation Jutsu
takes him to the kunai
marked with jutsu
formulas. I've noted
the location of most
of them.
If I can figure out
which one he'll pop
up at, I can get him
using my top speed.
Anyway, I have my
own responsibilities
so...
Go fly!
Now, which kunai?
I cannot fail now.
Hm?!
Oh no!
A Teleportation Jutsu
Formula on the Eight
Tails' tentacle!
Was that when
he did it?
I'm prepared for a
mutual strike. So shall
we stab each other with
these spikes?
You're my enemy,
but I'm starting
to like you.
You've got the moves
of a shinobi killer.
Even if you were to
kill Naruto, and
buy us some time until
the Nine Tails comes
back to life, I doubt
the next Jinchuriki
will be able to control
the Nine Tail's power
to this degree! Since
we don't have any idea
which way this war will
go, let's use all the
weapons we've got,
including the
Jinchuriki! I will
let Naruto pass!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Two Suns.
Now you're talking!
That's the Granny
Hokage I know!