Hey.
[Madara]
We really should talk,
Naruto Uzumaki.
Go to hell!
A Rasengan right
off the bat, huh?
You do know that doesn't
work on me, right?
Huh?!
Naruto, you just stay put.
Should've figured.
Kakashi of the Sharingan.
You're quick.
We won't let you get your
hands on Naruto that easily,
Madara Uchiha.
You did hear what I just said,
didn't you?
There are no attacks that exist,
that work against Madara Uchiha.
Even if you're
erasing yourself,
or this is just an
astral projection,
You'll still have to manifest
physically to take Naruto.
Otherwise you can't
actually take him.
I'll wait for that moment.
[Yamato]
You're in my
territory now.
[chuckle] Well, I
never imagined that
this would be easy.
I will admit I have
a plan in mind.
But at this moment,
I'm only here to talk.
Talk?
That's right.
I want to know what you did
that made Nagato betray me.
Naruto, you've
sparked my interest.
I don't care about
what you want.
What are you planning
to do with Sasuke?!
Come on, tell me!
Sasuke, huh?
Very well then,
I'll tell you.
About the man who's been
steeped to his very marrow
in the Shinobi World's
hatred and resentment.
The story of Sasuke Uchiha.
But Sasuke's story
cannot be told without
also telling Itachi's.
So first, I'll tell you
the truth about Itachi.
Where is Sasuke now?!
Answer me!
Well, since you
leave me no choice,
I'll give you a
little hint.
[crush]
Cee! Begin!
Sir!
You didn't have to kill him,
you know.
If we'd restrained and
interrogated him, we might
have obtained useful Intel
on the Akatsuki!
It wouldn't work; no one in
the Akatsuki has ever talked.
They're all completely devoted.
Okisuke, Urakaku.
Give the order to
find Sasuke at once.
Issue a number two
battle-ready state alert.
Yes, sir!
Lord Raikage!
You! One-eyed Mist guy!
Huh?
Keep that eye trained
on the Hokage!
Cee, and Darui! Come on!
I'm sorry about the desk
and the wall there.
Hey, Darui, quit yapping
and let's go already!
That Raikage is truly violent.
Even becoming the Kage hasn't
changed that unruly Cloud brat!
[radio] Number Two
battle-ready state
alert.
Search for the intruder,
Sasuke Uchiha.
Dispatch three squads
to the tower entrance.
Set up defensive line.
[radio static]
Roger.
Move out!
This is...
Karin, what's the matter?
The Samurai's movements have
suddenly become erratic.
I think they're looking for us!
[Suigetsu]
What?! But why?! We didn't do
anything to get their attention.
I bet that it was Zetsu.
Huh??
They're already gone.
Huagh!
"Racing Lightning"
[Karin]
It's no good.
There are too many!
We'll be found and
captured in no time.
That bastard.
I'll get him for this.
I see; so that's how they
use their chakra.
[gasp]
[Sasuke]
I'm very irritated right now.
Attack, and I doubt
I can hold back.
We could say the same to you!
He repelled them?!
His blade work is
similar to ours!
Karin, stop monitoring
those guys.
Find out where
Danzo is!
But what about
the samurai?
Don't worry about that;
I'll deal with them.
Locate Danzo!
[gasp]
Sasuke's chakra changed!
Eyyaahhh!!
Look at him! And this
is the guy who warned
me not to kill anyone!
What's this?
He's not the same
Sasuke he was before.
(slashed by sword reax, getting
kicked, being stabbed, one
samurai after another)
His chakra's thicker than
when he's in the Curse
Mark Second State.
And,
It's colder.
He's not alone!
[Cee]
Lord Raikage. There is one
chakra that is erasing
many other chakras.
I'm sure it's
coming from Sasuke!
Where?!
It's right below us!
Lord Raikage,
you're not going to--!
[gasp]
Something big is coming our way!
What's that?
[sounds of cave-in]
Hey! Kid!
I am going to teach you
the fear of true fury!
Sasuke! Don't go in alone!
He's lost it.
Water Style!
Water Wall!!
So he's the one.
Lightning Style!
Emotion Wave!
(slt om stab of discomfort reax)
D'yagh!
Boss, just as the Intel
reported, sasuke definitely
has Lightning Nature.
And Fire Nature, as
well. He's bound to
use Fire Style, then.
Darui, keep Water Style
ready at all times.
Got it.
How do they have so much
information about Sasuke?
Hey, there, the
one in the middle.
I recognize him.
These guys are Hidden
Cloud jonin. And the big
guy is their Raikage.
They won't let us pass easily.
Requesting reinforcements!
Sasuke got us!
I'll stop him!
He's going to attack!
Lightning Illusion!
Flash Pillar!
[Jugo]
He's trying
to blind us!
Sasuke!
No!
Jugo, relax.
It's just a genjutsu.
Should've figured, Sharingan.
Still.
You saw through
the genjutsu,
but it's too late!
Sasuke!
Aw, damn it;
that's just great!
My Executioner's
Blade's broken!
Well, it cracked when
we fought Eight Tails;
there's nothing you can
do about it now.
[growl]
He's safe! Nice, Suigetsu!
Who told you
to butt in?
Are you kidding me?!
What's with the
attitude, Sasuke?!
Not that I
don't expect it.
But we came to help!
Shinobi sure
fight rough.
Unbelievable!
Cee, check and see if
they've got other allies
hiding around here.
It'd be weak to have to
worry about more popping in.
I'm pretty sure that
there was one more.
But if I focus on that,
it'll be harder for me to
fight with you in the battle.
We don't need you to fight.
Boss and I are enough to
handle these guys.
If I keep after Danzo,
that Cee guy's gonna
suss me out.
Karin will probably extinguish
her chakra and just lie low.
she can do things like that.
[Jugo]
That guy in the back is a
Sensory-Type ninja, huh?
We gotta take him down.
I'll do it.
It doesn't look like
he'll ever rise again.
[Mifune]
Lord Ao, please confirm
whether the Hokage's Visual
Jutsu is still engaged.
[Ao]
No. Right now, the flow in
his Chakra Network is quiet.
The jutsu's undone.
[Danzo]
All of you just relax, it's not
a visual jutsu that I can use
that many times in a day.
[Ao]
Be quiet! I shall decide that.
For you are a man who simply
can't be trusted.
[Danzo]
I can't believe the Byakugan
fell into someone else's hands.
[Danzo]
If a Hidden Leaf Hyuga
turned traitor, I would've
taken care of them at once.
You're probably planning
to dispose of me now
that I know your secret.
Better think again!
I'll fight you myself,
if need be.
Especially since your Visual
Jutsu may be connected somehow
with the one that manipulated
the Fourth Mizukage.
[Mifune]
Lord Hokage,
all ninjutsu is
prohibited here.
You have lost trust
and credibility.
A shame, since I may
have still chosen you,
had you not resorted
to such tactics.
[Danzo]
But "may have chosen"
wasn't good enough.
I'm prepared to do whatever
it takes in order to
protect the shinobi world.
It's imperative that our
whole world unite as one.
Just as the First Hokage
Hashirama brought together
his clan and founded the
Hidden Leaf Village.
Now we must merge all
the villages and create
one shinobi world.
This shall never be
accomplished through
discussion and negotiation.
But it takes time and patience
to actualize one's ideals.
Impatience makes one
shortsighted and
invites failure.
That's what
happened to you.
[Danzo]
Taking the time to do it
morally and ethically will
result in no change.
And the Akatsuki will
eventually destroy the
whole shinobi world.
[Tsuchikage]
But your dream is
nothing more than
an impossibility!
It may sound noble, but in
the end, you'll only breed
distrust, ill feelings,
hatred, and resentment.
Why, Danzo!
We can't even
trust your words
at this point.
It doesn't matter whether
you trust me or not.
Results are necessary.
[Gaara]
If we can't even
trust each other,
If that's the state of our
world and of being human,
then we have no future.
Eh?
What does
that mean?
Without mutual trust
and understanding,
All that will remain in this
world is fear and terror.
I simply can't tolerate giving
up so easily, or any plan that
doesn't incorporate morality.
You pose such difficult
concepts so simply.
But you're a green brat
who knows nothing about
running a village.
Tch!
But I'll tell you what.
Now's your chance to ask
anything you'd like!
As your senior, I'll
answer any question
you have. Eh, Danzo?
[chuckle]
Say again,
old man?!
Don't do it, Kankuro.
He's still Tsuchikage.
He's a village leader!
Hold on.
Did she say
STILL a leader?
Ignore them.
Then let me ask you this.
Sure! Go head,
no holds barred.
Ask away!
When did all of you
forsake yourselves?
What?!
What a pure-hearted child.
Heh!
All right, Gaara,
what are we gonna do now?
We once worked with the Hidden
Leaf on their mission to
retrieve Sasuke. But he's sunk
so low he's joined the Akatsuki.
So, Sasuke Uchiha, huh?
Hey! Don't leave
without your guards!
Hey, Gramps, he scored
a point on you.
Oh, shut it!
Lord Tsuchikage,
What do we do?
Tell us.
Shall we join
the fight?
You fool! And what happens
if my back pain gets worse?!
But I want to see this
Sasuke who supposedly
took down Deidara.
Fine, do as you please!
But if you get caught in the
Raikage's crossfire, you'll die.
Stay out of his way.
All right!
What about you,
Akatsuchi?
I have to keep an eye on Lord
Tsuchikage in case there's
trouble with his back.
So I'll stay here with him.
Hm. Later, then.
Lord Danzo, please, sir, allow
one of us to venture forth and
retrieve the Sharingan.
[Ao]
All of you from the Leaf!
Just stay right where you are!
Lord Raikage has ordered you to!
No! Fuu, Torune- Desist.
For the present time,
we'll play nice.
Rwaaa ha ha ha ha!
I'll kill you all!!
His change in personality's
more surprising than his
appearance, You know?
Focus! He's got
unbelievable chakra!
WAAAHHH-hahahahaha!
I can't believe Jugo actually
gave in to his killer impulse
voluntarily this time.
What do you think the odds
are that he still remembers
we're both on his side?
Haahh!
Now who's first?!
You need to learn your place!
[gasp]
Hrrnng!
Gotcha!
Nice blade you
got there.
Well, I'm not giving
you mine just 'cause
yours is broken!
[straining]
Hrrghh...
[squeezed]
Hungh!
Well, that's one down.
I'm no weakling!
Mere Sharingan
can't take me down!
Lord Raikage's nerve
transmission and reaction
speed are on par with the
Leaf's Yellow Flash.
It's impressive those guys
are even doing this well!
But Lord Raikage used
Lightning Style Chakra to
augment his reflexes.
Not even the Sharingan
can keep up!
Plus, there's still--
Huh?!
Die!
Boss, no!
Point blank!
Did Jugo get him?!
What?! Lord Raikage hit him
and he still survived?!
[gasp]
This This has to be genjutsu!
These guys are using each
other's attacks to distract us!
I can't believe I fell for it.
Damn it!
Can't...
move...
Cee?!
[Darui]
Cee! Don't go to sleep
on the job! Get up!
AaaAAAAAH
ha ha ha ha!!
I killed him!
I just killed
the big guy!
I guess Jugo can be
useful, after all.
All right, they
can't detect me now.
This is my chance
to find Danzo.
[gasp]
Now, who's next?!
AAhh-haahhh!
Agh!
[Gaara]
It isn't too late for you.
You still have the chance
to go back, Sasuke.
[Sasuke]
So, if I were to return?
What is there for me?
[Sasuke]
I shut my eyes a
long time ago.
[Sasuke]
The things that I seek now
lie only in the darkness.
[Gaara]
Wait!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Sasuke's Ninja Way."
[Kankuro]
Gaara, don't let your
personal feelings interfere.