I'm not enjoying this.
I'm beginning to lose
patience with these shinobi.
Yes, just how long do they
expect us feudal lords to
remain cooped up in such
cramped quarters as these?!
Now, now.
What's the harm, really?
In fact, we should bestow
upon them meritorious honors
once the war is over.
Now, let's see. What do
you suppose that we should
call such decorations?
Is this the place?
[Feudal Lord]
How hard the wind blows
as we travel down this
long and winding road.
The scent that's on the
breeze reminds me of the
capital back in my youth.
You know, it isn't unheard
of for feudal lords such as
myself to end up as hostages
during times of war.
And it remains the duty
of our shinobi to
guarantee our safety.
Of course. This is exactly
why I'm here escorting you,
Feudal Lord of the
Land of Frost.
We should be reaching
your safe house shortly.
Now then, what's a
suitable title for the
shinobi's decoration?
Certificate of...
Ohh??
An enemy?!
But I didn't sense
anything at all! Did you?
Keep them away from
the Feudal Lords!
Mmm?
[guard]
Gotcha!
Huh?
So, this wasn't it, was it?
Damn! He got away.
All right, we have to get
word out to the other safe
houses immediately!
Ah ha! I've just thought
of a most excellent name
for that honor!
All right, listen closely
and tell me, what would you
say to the idea of calling
this new honor of ours,
"The Land of Fire's
Hidden Leaf,
Land of Wind's
Hidden Sand,
Land of Earth's
Hidden Stone,
Land of Water's
Hidden Mist,
Land of Lightning's
Hidden Cloud
Allied Shinobi
Decoration"?
Please I want all of
you to give me your
honest opinion!
So, what do you
think of my idea?
It's too long!
Why not just the
"Allied Award?!"
That will suffice!
No, no. That's much too short!
And it doesn't sound
distinctive enough.
The Feudal Lords seem a
bit oblivious, don't they?
What's all the fuss
over some decoration,
anyway?
Yeah, but that's
their job.
Besides, we need to
respect their orders.
Their medals and decorations
help define what honor is,
and we need that right now.
I mean, somebody's got
to set the standards,
don't you agree?
Well,
When you put it like that,
yeah, I guess so.
Of course, you aren't going
to get any decorations by
just standing around here
thinking about it, you know!
So stay alert.
We're gonna be
moving soon.
All right, Feudal Lord
of the Land of Frost.
We should be arriving
at the fifth safe house
in a short while.
You really have
five of them?
We do.
You see, my lord,
you're going to be rotated
between the various
houses at set intervals,
and as a result of that,
the enemy won't be able to
pinpoint your location.
Your bodyguards are all
seasoned warriors, as well.
Hm. Well, that does
set my mind at ease.
Excellent.
Hnh, Those fools.
They underestimate me!
I am Black Zetsu!
This land is me!
I am one with it!
"Battleground"
It's dull.
But I guess I'll have to show
them why I'm the one that's been
assigned to guard the coastline.
I'll launch the opening
shot now, then move in.
Lightning Style.
Black Panther!
Yaaaggghh!
Whoa!
Black Lightning!
Yeah! Captain Darui is the
only person that the
previous Raikage has allowed
to get a lightning tattoo!
I'm sorry about all that.
Hyaaaghh!
Above us!
I'm not gonna
let you get by!
Keep attacking!
Don't let up!
Hold 'em! Don't let
them break through the
barricade! Let's go!
[battle shouts]
My worst nightmare
has come true.
It's almost like--
No, this really IS
a Great Ninja War.
It's Choza.
Is it really?
Yes, I see.
You're all grown up, Choza.
That's right! And guess what?
I'm about to grow even bigger!
Now! Release!
Eight Trigrams Palm Rotation.
[distant fighting]
My brother.
Forgive me.
As a member of the branch
family, I should protect the
main family, yet I'm your enemy.
I suppose this is my
punishment for resenting
the main branch.
My body won't do what
I want it to do now.
In the end, it appears that
even my decision to sacrifice
myself for the sake of the
Village has been negated.
[Hizashi] [flashback]
I ask you: please give
Neji a message for me.
Tell him that I did not make
this sacrifice to merely
protect the head family.
But for my siblings,
family, and village.
So by my own free will, I
chose death! And in doing
so, I chose my own freedom!
This is just the fate in
store for me as a member
of the branch family.
But no such fate exists! Your
very own son has been fighting
hard to demonstrate just that!
And my daughter has, too!
Neji... And Lady Hinata.
Huagh!
Damn it! There's no end to this!
Haaa!
Are you doing all
right, Neji?!
Yes. Thank you, Hinata.
The branch family doesn't
live to protect and serve
the main family anymore.
We protect each
other as equals now!
So after all this time,
it's actually come to pass?
Then hear me, Brother.
That is all the more
reason that I wish to
fall by your hand!
Yah!
Even the wild geese know the
importance of formation.
When the leader of any
group becomes confused,
then the entire flock
that's following him
will be put at risk.
I'm too young and
inexperienced to do that.
So I ask you,
All of you.
Please, lend me your
strength for this fight!
You've got it,
Lord Gaara!
To victory!
Although I admit that it's
also an undeniable fact
that someone young
and charismatic must
stand at the helm.
Ngh! Hey! Watch it!
All this moving around
is making me feel sick!
All of you are
completely artless!
Hmph!
Just be quiet.
Keep it up and I'll be
happy to seal that
mouth shut too.
I'm not into S&M, thanks!
Let me out of here and I'll show
you what real art is! Hmph!
So annoying.
Uh?
Ngh!
We stopped. Hmph!
You, as well,
Granny Chiyo?
[Kankuro]
And...
Well, Kankuro.
That was very
nicely done.
It appears that you've
managed to outdo Sasori.
Huh? I know that voice.
Hey! If you're reinforcements
here to help me, then get me
out of here! It's stuffy!
I'm about to explode!
Hmph!
No. You're wrong.
You're stuck in there precisely
so that you can't explode,
Explosive Style boy.
Hm? Oh, yeah.
I guess you're
right about that.
But you don't have to
put it that way! Hmph!
I consider both the
Akatsuki and the shinobi
of the Five Great Nations
to be my enemies.
I don't really care to
help either of you.
But with this disgusting
jutsu controlling me,
my body moves against its will.
The Reanimation Jutsu again.
As if Granny Chiyo weren't
dangerous enough, these guys
look pretty scary, too.
It sure doesn't help that we
split up our fighting force.
Listen up.
We retreat on my
signal, you got it?
Roger that.
New tactical
orders in from HQ.
And we're to transmit
them to the front!
Get the plans to
the captains!
Yaaaggh!
Captain Kitsuchi!
We've just had word
come in from HQ!
We have new
tactical orders!
Tell me! And be quick about it!
[Shikamaru]
All right. Got it.
Sorry for the
interruption.
I've just gotten orders to take
half this company and join up
with the First Company.
What?! Half of our forces?!
Is HQ out of their minds?!
They're not, I agree
with their strategy.
It's a sound one.
If everything goes according
to plan, it'll be okay.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
But one thing troubles me.
Why? What's the
matter, Shikamaru?
Supposedly, the enemy has
a shinobi who possesses
the Kekkei Touta, which
surpasses Kekkei Genkai.
What?! The Kekkei Touta?!
Are you sure about that?
Kekkei Touta?
What are they
talking about?
Do you know,
Matsuri?
No, I've never
heard of it before.
Although, from
Temari's reaction,
it's something big.
Whoever it is must be
a formidable enemy.
You there.
How do you expect to
defend yourself against
the Kekkei Touta if you
know nothing about it?!
[both]
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Temari!
But, um, now can you
tell us what exactly
the Kekkei Touta i?
Give me a break.
You young ones really
don't know anything
at all, do you?!
The Kekkei Touta is...
Yes? The Kekkei...?
Touta... is what?
Shikamaru! Go on,
explain this to them!
What?! Why me?
You know why! I'm not good
at these kinds of things!
Just explain it already!
Ah, damn it. You know,
I'm the one who's supposed
to be giving the orders
around here, remember?!
Hey, hold up. I want to
hear this too, Shikamaru.
[[sigh] Well, then, I
guess I should start
with the basics, the
properties of chakra.
Generally, we all possess
one chakra nature.
Besides the nature you obtain
from training, that is.
There are different natures.
This is kind of simplistic,
but the more chakra natures
you have, the better.
That's why most jonin
worth their salt possess
multiple chakra natures.
Oh, I get it!
Yeah, but I
already knew that
much about it.
You'd better
know that!
However.
Some shinobi are different:
they're born with two
chakra natures.
They're able to fuse
those two chakras.
And, by doing so,
create new chakra.
They are known as
Kekkei Genkai shinobi.
Captain Yamato's Wood
Style is a combination of
water and earth chakra.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, it is.
And another example is
Captain Darui, who's now
leading the First Company.
His Gale Style's a
combination of lightning
and water chakra.
Got it?
Those guys are all
shinobi who possess
very rare jutsu styles.
Yeah, that's right.
But even stronger than
the Kekkai Genkai,
is what we call the
Kekkei Touta, in which
three chakra natures
are fused together.
[both]
What?!
Three of them?
It's almost beyond belief,
and it's very rare.
So rare, in fact, that of
all the shinobi in all the
nations, I only know one.
But the enemy has the
Reanimation Jutsu.
And they've brought
back a long-dead
Kekkei Touta shinobi.
He uses Particle Style.
He's Mu the Second
Tsuchikage.
[sigh] We'd better come
up with a strategy to
use against him.
Shikamaru, I don't get it.
Why would we split up our
forces when we're just about
to face an enemy shinobi as
formidable as that?
Yeah, I know. But it
appears that Headquarters
has taken that issue into
consideration, too.
We've been graced
by the presence,
of a rare ally who
possesses Kekkei Touta.
You didn't need to
get up, you know.
We can handle this.
Hmf. You're the one who
lit the fire beneath me.
Then let me ask you this.
When did all of you
forsake yourselves?
What?!
I'm going to retrieve here what
I had previously forsaken!
[shouts of battle,
clashing metal,
explosions]
Haaaa!
Super-Expansion Jutsu!
Raaghh!
Haaaa!
It's pitiful.
The jutsu of the Second Hokage
has snared us both, when we'd
already defeated him before.
You know what I
mean, Kinkaku?
I'm sorry to cause
you shame, Lords
Kinkaku and Ginkaku.
It's also hard for me to
dishonor the "two rays of
light among the clouds."
Ginkaku. Take a look
at his left shoulder.
This kid's wearing the Third
Raikage's Lightning Mark.
It seems he's
got some skill.
I'm sorry for the
disrespect, but I'm going
to have to shame both of
you a little right now.
I'm afraid that I might
even end up stripping
away the shine from
your gold and silver,
With just a single strike
of my Gale Style!
Though it'll be dull.
[Ginkaku]
I have to say, I really
don't like the tone you're
using toward your seniors.
But I'll shut you up!
[Kinkaku]
It simply seems that too
much time has passed.
In this day and age,
nobody knows anything
about us anymore.
Let's do this, Ginkaku!
[Ginkaku]
Sure thing, Kinkaku!
[Samui]
There's no doubt.
Those are the Gold and Silver
Brother's Ninja Tools!
[Darui]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Forbidden Words.
[Ginkaku]
They talk too much;
this'll be just perfect.