(Announcer)
Ninja Network News!
Good evening. I'm
Mabui of the Cloud.
I'm Shikaku Nara.
And today we'll be bringing you
the latest updates & breaking
news from the various
battlefronts via satellite.
But first, here are some
highlights from the battles
that continue to rage on
the frontlines:
On the desert front, the stand
off continues between Gaara's
4th Company & the reanimated
Kage.
On the coastal front, Darui &
his 1st Company sustained heavy
losses when the enemy summoned
a giant humanoid.
But they eliminated most
of the enemy force.
The Third Company under Kakashi
is sealing away the Ninja
Swordsmen one after another.
The Company has split into
smaller units and expanded
their range to take down
the remaining enemies.
Mifune's Fifth Company
has joined up with the
Commando Unit.
Deidara's escape was
unexpected, but they
were successful in
recapturing him.
Next, we have news
about White Zetsu.
His jutsu, with which
he mimics not only
someone's appearance but
also their charkra-
-has created chaos
within the Allied
Forces.
However, thanks to the
keen observations of
Sakura Haruno, a shinobi
with the Medical Unit...
Our genius strategist,
Shikaku, has been able to
draw up a strategy to
counter thst jutsu.
I'm, uh, refining the
strategy now... please
be patient just a
little longer...
Meanwhile, at the front,
Sakura has just begun a
press conference...
The purpose of which
is to get the word out
about White Zetsu.
(Reporter)
I understand you received
a love letter, but rejected
it right away? Is that true?
Uh, that's not what
this is about...
Is that the only
declaration of love
you've received?
Please, if we could
just focus....
(Reporter)
You reportedly said that you're
already in love with someone, so
who is it you're in love with?
(Reporters)
[shouting out questions]
What the hell does that
have to do with this
press conference!?
Wow, okay. Well, we were
supposed to run the
"Kosuke Kills" segment
in this time slot...
But we've received
an update just now.
According to this latest
news bulletin, the key
figures in the Fourth
Great Ninja War:
Killer Bee the Eight Tails, and
Naruto the Nine Tails, have
managed to persuade Lady
Tsunade and Lord Raikage...
...and at long last,
they are headed towards
the battle feild.
(Shikaku)
I'm amazed Naruto and
Bee convinced those two.
The satellite link with
Naruto and Bee is ready.
We'll find out if
they're both excited
about joining the
war effort.
Can you hear me,
Naruto? Are you there?
What just happened? Did
we lose the connection?
I wonder if the
equiptment could
be malfunctioning.
I'm not certain. Wait,
what was that? Okay.
Well, it seems we're
connected now.
Let's try this
again, are you
there, Naruto?
So, do I just talk
into this while I'm
running? Argh!
Hold on, stay put so the
camera can focus, and I'll
plant a kiss on ya, like
this! Mmmmmm!
(Naruto)
Hey! Outta my way!
What in the world
are those two doing!?
Don't they know we're
still on the air!?
If Kisame's intel is correct,
Naruto now has the same
ability as Mito Uzumaki,
the wife of the First
Hokage, to sense the enemy.
Naruto will have no
choice, he'll have to
battle White Zetsu.
It's all going
according to plan...
Today, the Senju's Will of
Fire shall be extinguished.
(Lady Katsuyu)
The 2 Kage who block their
path and refuse to let
them by are:
Lord Raikage and
Lady Tsunade!
Demanding that they
let him pass Naruto
makes his move...
The indomitable Killer
Bee is quick to react,
as he jumps in to assist.
Then, shockingly, Lady Tsunade
...steps in to let them pass!
Causing Lord Raikage to bellow
out a roar of disapproval!
But then, the two suns
inside of Naruto
soften his heart...
The lights of brotherly and
parental love burn so bright,
that they make the Raikage
squint!
And so, he relents and
lets Naruto and Killer
Bee go...
In an intense touching moment
between men, Lady Tsunade and
Lord Raikage agree to support
Naruto's decision!
Oh, wait, sorry!
Lady Tsunade
isn't a man.
I really don't know
what to say, I just
can't believe it!
To think that Lord
Raikage could be
persuaded like that...
Hmm.
Well, honestly I'm
not that surprised.
There's just
something about Naruto
that somehow makes the
impossible seem possible.
But, we might be playing
right into our enemy's
hands with this move...
Consider the enemy's
use of White Zetsu's
Transformation Jutsu.
It almost seems
deliberately chosen
to try to lure
Naruto out...
You're right. It
surely could be a
trap...
However, we have no
choice but to leave
this in Naruto's hands.
(Medical Ninja)
No one may approach
Lady Shizune's tent
right now!
Anyone making a move
toward it will be
considered an enemy!
So just stay put!
[groaning]
[grunt]
Everyone, stay put!
You must not move!
Sakura, come here for
a minute please. Take
a look at this genetic
profile data!
You got something?
It's even more like
Captain Yamato's than
it was at the Five
Kage Summit.
In other words, by now,
it's almost completely
identical to the First
Hokage's genetic profile.
So it has to
be true...
What are you
talking about?
How are all these
white things related
to the First Hokage?
All these white
Zetsu creatures are
essentially clones of
the First Hokage.
Or, rather, since there
are so many of them, they
must be like plants.
Harvested and cultivated
from the First Hokage's
cells in order to make
mobile botanical clones.
They even use a weak
version of Wood Style!
I still don't
get it.
But even if I don't, what
you're saying is that I'm
supposed to guard you against
plants, is that right?
Well then, how about you
two just use some termites.
Looking at this data, I think
Captain Yamato is being used
to make these clones stronger!
I'm sure of it!
I'll notify HQ
immediately!
I'm back. Those white beings
impersonating our troops are
causing havoc among them!
Perhaps it's too big a
coincidence, but I think
it's perfect timing to
let Naruto go.
I agree.
Sorry to jump in,
but we've received
a report from the
medical team.
It's data on those
white beings.
Let me see that!
Unbelievable! Madara and
Orochimaru's obsession
with the First Hokage has
created this?!
Botanical Ninja created
from Grandfather's body.
This is proof that Madara
has posession of the First
Hokage's cells!
He's cultivated them and
developed a way to replicate
them, which means he's probably
used them on himself, too.
It's no wonder that
he's lived so long.
Well, do we have
any idea of how to
destroy him, then?
No, the opposite.
Now we have no idea
what will defeat him.
I'm afraid it appears
that Madara really is
...immortal!
(Shikaku)
An immortal leader, his army of
mobile plants and reanimated
zombies...
There isn't a single
normal human being
among them!
We must notify Naruto and
Bee immediately about this
Transformation Jutsu.
(Shikaku)
Naruto, Lord Bee,
please listen!
I am speaking telepathically
to you both at the same time.
Now, listen to me, I've
got intel for you on the
enemy's battle strategy.
Pay close attention.
Oh. So that's what's
up with all the weird
fuzzy things that I've
been sensing...
Well, I guess that
I've got no choice
but to step up.
Yes, but remember Madara needs
the Tailed Beasts that you and
Lord Bee host in order for his
project Tsuki no Me to work.
That means you two
are still his main
targets.
I know, but trust me,
he won't capture me!
Then don't even think about
negotiating with him. You can't
reason with him, Naruto.
(Shikaku)
Madara is different than
Nagato, he has no interest
in peace whatsoever!
He's a truly evil man
who covets the whole world.
To control others, you
must possess the ability
to manipulate the
darkness in their souls.
Nagato just happened to
be easily influenced,
that's all.
Never compare
yourself to Nagato!
His methods were different
than mine, but he truly
wanted peace!
But you...
you're different!
[chuckle] No doubt.
[grunt]
That's really your
goal? To validate the
existance of the Uchiha?
Then why collect the
Tailed Beasts? What's
your true purpose, really?
Just what do
you want?!
Well, if I wanted
anything it would be,
to be a complete form.
And he's gonna control everyone
everywhere using genjutsu, isn't
that right? That's what this
project Tsuki no Me's all about?
Yes. So make sure that
you don't hold back.
A while ago I talked to
Madara in the Land of
Iron. He told me all about
the Uchiha Clan's destiny.
I know that he understands all
about hatred. He used Nagato and
he's the one who's manipulating
Sasuke's hatred, too.
(Naruto)
I know how
evil he is!
He doesn't act upon hatred,
he simply takes advantage
of hatred.
He's different from other
enemies you've faced.
Be careful.
It doesn't matter! I'm
stopping Madara, and I'm
stopping this war!
I'll act first, and
talk afterward.
(Shikaku)
I don't know about
Kabuto, but Madara is
apparently immortal.
Also, there are those
mobile plants augmented
with the First Hokage's
cells...
And those otherworldly
zombies... Nothing works
against them except sealing.
It's an army of the undead.
Beware of them too!
That's actually the
best news you can
give me, ya know?
'Cause it means that
I don't have to hold
back at all!
Huh? That's... Eff!
It's chaos out there
on the battlefield!
We've gotta get back and
defend the headquarters!
Rasengan!
Naruto!?
[groan]
Leave it all to
Naruto, here!
You tell me which ones
to attack and I'll get
on it just like that!
Everyone's an enemy!
Attack them all!
Let's do this,
Octopops! Come on!
Rasen-Rampage!
Rasen-Absorption!
(Thinking)
Naruto's attack is affecting
their Wood Style, they're
turning into trees!
(Thinking)
It's just like before.
You won't stop me that
easily! Now I won't be
so vulnerable to the
effects of your attack!
(Thinking)
Mini Rasen Shuriken...
[frightened cries]
[screams in agony]
(Naruto)
Summoning: Mayhem tecnique!
Argh!!!
Alright! Yeah!!
You learned from the training
drills! Can I take some
credit for the kills?
My Shadow Clones and Mr.
Gamahiro can stay here
and stand watch over this
area! Now let's go!
I'm gonna hit every
one of the battlefields
at the same time!
All right! Multi-shadow
Cone Jutsu!
[running breaths]
It's no good! He
caught up to us!
Th- that's...!
That guy is a Cloud
Ninja who possesses
Kekkei Genkai!
Magnet Style Toroi!
You're telling me the
Hidden Cloud has a
Magnet Style user?
If and when he attacks,
you have to-- Argh!
[grunt]
You fool! I said you
have to get out of
the way!!
What!? You didn't
say that!
I just didn't have
time to finish!
Don't you see!? His
Magnet Style puts a
magnetic charge onto
anything he touches!
And those things can
then transfer a magnetic
charge to anything they
touch!
The charge weakens with
each transfer. You're the
first tranfer point that
touched the shuriken...
...so the magnetic
power in your body...!
So, what's gonna
happen to me then!?
Right now, your whole
body is magnetized...
And the shuriken he
possesses are too!
Your body and his shuriken
are going to be drawn
directly towards each other!
[gasps]
Which means that you
won't be able to dodge
his next attack!
No way! You're telling
me I'm about to die!?
No! I don't
want to die!
(Naruto)
Rasengan!
[gasps]
Are you guys okay?
Have you been injured?
Huh? What was
that?
What's going
on out there?
(Cloud Ninja)
Lord Bee! What are
you doing here?!
Not much! You okay?
Yes, but you shouldn't
be here, sir! Those white
beings are disguising
themselves as us!
Yeah, I know.
(Thinking)
So, this is one of those
zombie guys controlled by
the Reanimation Jutsu, huh?
And sealing them like
this is the only way
to stop them...
We were running back to HQ
with Eff to tighten the
security there, but we got
separated...
(Killer Bee)
Eff and his team were
actually white beings.
(Killer Bee)
You gotta be careful
what you're seeing...
[frightened gasp]
Time to go, Octopops,
we gotta catch up to
everybody else now.
Yeah!
Hold on, if Eff and
the others were all
imposters... you!
No! Come on! I mean, both
of us were attacked and
almost killed by the
enemy, so we're okay!
We're both who
we're supposed
to be!
Oh yeah! Right!
[laughing]
I've got you!
Are you trying
to kill me!?
It's your own fault!
Now's not the time
for jokes!
(Tsuchikage)
We really can't
retreat any further.
It's time to make a
stand right here and
right now!
Yes...
The first thing the
two of us should do
is launch long-range
offensives.
We'll see how the
enemy responds...
Hm?
They were slowly
retreating... but
it seems that they've
made up their minds.
Fighting those from other
villages is understandable,
but I don't care to battle
my own village's shinobi.
Curse that Orochimaru
brat for controlling us
with this loathsome jutsu!
He will regret
doing this to us!
You and I have never
seen eye to eye, but
for the first time ever,
I think I agree with you.
Do not lament. It
is not all bad.
I'm sure that our
children have grown
and surpassed us.
They will make a
stand and they
will stop us.
I really hope
you're right.
Hm?
Incomming.
There are two
of them.
[grunt]
Woah, look! Now
that is a whole
lotta sand!
(Thinking)
It's the power of the
Shikaku, the One Tail!
So, he's kicking
off with the
Playing Possum Jutsu?
Gold Dust...?
I see...
You were the shinobi
who controlled Gold
Dust with Magnet Style.
You stopped it.
Nice.
Gold Dust is much
heavier than sand.
So if I simply mix
some Gold Dust into
this sand, then I'm
able to slow it down.
I'm impressed that you
knew how to counter it
so quickly and effectively.
When Shukaku the One
Tail would run amok,
I would stop his sand
just like this.
[gasp]
(Thinking)
It's not Shikaku...
It's Gaara?
[struggling grunts]
From above.
You're an old man,
Ohnoki! Do you owe
your long life to
Particle Style?
Patrticle Style! Atomic
Dismantling Jutsu!
This Particle Style of
his... my predecessor's
as powerful as ever.
His sand is even more
powerful than before.
Just wait for
the signal!
Tht was Particle
Style. Don't tell me
that's your former pupil
that brat Ohnoki!
Oh man. Now I really
do feel like I've
travelled through time.
Father, it's
been a while.
Yes, Gaara. But
where is Shukaku?
He is long gone...
And I... I am no
longer the Jinchuriki
that you've created,
father.
(Gaara)
I've become the
Kazekage!
(Gaara)
It is a leader's duty
to eliminate threats
against one's village.
(Gaara)
We must protect it.
(Fourth Kazekage)
It seems this Reanimation Jutsu
may actually have something of
merit to it after all...
(Fourth Kazekage)
Let me determine what
you may be worth!
(Fourth Kazekage)
Can you defeat me,
or can't you!?
(Karura)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "A Father's
Hope, a Mother's Love."
(Fourth Kazekage)
Karura... you...