It's no use! We can't
lose them!
Tango! Get HQ!
Hm!
The Commando Unit is
reporting in. They're
attempting to retreat,
but the enemy pursuit
team is closing in on
them.
A relief team from the
Fifth Company was already
dispatched.
Send them the coordinates
of the closest rendezvous
point and quickly!
It's just one faction,
but they're voicing
opposition vehemently.
They're saying that
samurai must remain
neutral, so they're
wondering why they
should team up
with shinobi.
So samurai should remain
neutral, should they?
They only say such
things because they
don't know the past.
But even more than that,
they don't understand the
current situation.
Some also say that a
shinobi war should be
resolved by the shinobi
themselves.
Yet these former foes all
keep squabbling... and they
still cannot find a common
ground to unite them.
How do they realistically
expect to end this war
without our help?
All of you, head out! And
show them how we samurai
fight!
Sir!
"Mifune vs. Hanzo"
I said I wanted out of
here! Hmph!
I can feel Orochimaru's
chakra pass through my
skull, seeping into my
flesh and bones.
I must succeed.
It's over there.
I don't care if it was
the Akatsuki or
Orochimaru!
Whoever reanimated
me is going to regret it.
Everyone is going to
think I've been playing
possum again! It's just
so undignified!
I'm trying to
concentrate! Be quiet,
puppet granny!
No, I won't! You shut up,
old man snorkel face!
Just a little further.
This distance should
work. Summoning Jutsu!
Huh?!
Do it, Ibuse!
The Poison Fog!
[grunting and coughing]
[coughing]
He resorted to poison
because he was tired of
chasing us?! Damn it!
I should be resistant to
poison... but my body's
going numb.
Are those reinforcements!
Hey, I'm over here! Hmph!
Gotcha.
No!
Lord Hanzo, I presume?
My name is Mifune, leader
of the samurai. I desire
to battle you!
We're saved.
Sorry we're late.
Are you all right?
Careful. The enemy uses
poison.
Our masks are specially
designed for fighting
shinobi and are
impervious to poison gas.
Here, put this on.
Thanks.
They need antidotes! Get
these Commando Unit
members to the Medical
Corps, stat!
Lord Mifune!
Assistance is
unnecessary! Stay out of
the way if you do not
want to get injured.
So you're Mifune. Why do
you side with the
shinobi?
No,... an even better
question is why stay with
the shinobi? You are
staunchly samurai.
To serve shinobi is against
your nature.
How can you still call
yourselves samurai?
You're wrong. We do not
serve the shinobi.
The one master that we
follow has never changed
since the olden days, and
that master...
... is called peace!
Peace?!
We pledge ourselves to
peace, and then we act
based upon that
conviction!
[chuckling]
The battlefield is
getting lively.
Now, then...
Lady Chiyo!
I haven't been playing
possum. You know that,
right, Kankuro?
Uh, yes?
But never mind that for
now. Hanzo controls a
venomous salamander!
I have fought against him
many times in my day.
That is why I know how to
concoct an antidote to
its poison.
I am also aware that the
salamander takes five
minutes to work up more
venom once it releases it.
That interfering hag is
blabbing my secrets!
Ibuse! Withdraw for now!
Heh.
Even though I'm being
manipulated
I won't be forced to
fight them right now.
Then you, Hanzo...
You must know who my
original foe in battle
was... do you not?
Uh--
I won't hold back from
fighting the Five Great
Nations!
All right...
I'll go.
Here he comes!
So solid!
[groaning]
[gasping]
You countered that quite
nicely.
You fight well... for a
weak man of peace and
neutrality, that is.
Don't look at me that
way. I once sought peace,
too.
I was going to unite all
the Five Great Nations
into one shinobi world.
But I quickly realized
that true peace does not
exist.
And when was that?
Battle after battle after
battle... The only thing
left and the end of it
all is death!
You pledge yourselves to
peace?!
You more than any other
know best what has
happened to the samurai.
Many samurai have become
shinobi instead, and your
techniques have passed
over to the shinobi.
Capture them!
Sorry, my body is acting
on its own and fleeing.
There is no longer a role
for samurai in this world
at all.
Shinobi have no devotion
to peace. They are
ruled by money and
ninjutsu and power.
Ahhhh!
They fight, they die, and
they leave nothing
behind.
And I am the same!
No, you are wrong. It's
not about life or death.
It doesn't bother me in
the slightest if I should
lose my life in the
pursuit of peace!
What drives me, pushes me
forward, is my conviction.
Yours has become warped.
According to the Samurai
Way, people themselves
are swords.
And thus one can live on
in others' memories, like
my famed sword Kurosawa.
Do not compare people to
blades! What can you
possibly glean from some
cold lump of iron?
Take your ritual of
seppuku... Why do you
samurai try to diminish
your own lives so much?
It doesn't make any
sense!
I've already explained
it. Our conviction lives
on forever!
Hah! Enough of this
nonsense! I shall erase
you samurai, once and for
all!
Huh?!
And I will keep you from
casting ninjutsu from
here on out.
You live up to your
reputation as an expert
swordsman.
So this is why they say
ninjutsu is useless
against you.
You left me no time to
weave signs.
And my two-step sickle
and chain attack...
Even those familiar with
it have never managed to
avoid it.
In the distant past, when
my name was still unknown,
we actually exchanged blows
once.
Though I doubt you would
remember it...
Oh? Then why aren't you
dead?
You shattered my sword
with that sickle and chain
and you slashed my head!
But even then,
somehow, I lived.
I see. So you were that
samurai...
I can't believe you
survived. I'll make sure
to finish you this time.
Sorry, but that's not
possible for you. I could
tell right from our first
exchange today why you,
who were once so
strong...
...could be defeated and
killed.
What?! What do you mean?
Quite frankly, I can't
believe a shinobi of your
caliber doesn't know.
Don't you remember how
you met your end?
[grunting]
Who are you?! To think
you could drive me to
this point!
Have you forgotten my
face, Hanzo?
You!
You're Yahiko of the
Akatsuki! But you're
dead! What's going on?!
You allied yourself with
Danzo and then betrayed
us.
You now only think of
self-preservation, you
piece of garbage.
Ah!
I once respected you.
But... you have changed
much.
Who are you?! How do you
have so much power?!
After everything that
you've done, you still
don't understand...
...why exactly it is that
you have lost.
[gasping]
Begone, Hanzo!
Stop!
What could they possibly
mean?
What is it that they see
but I do not?!
[gasping]
Be bathed in venom and
die! I've had enough of
your nonsense.
What?!
A sword that is
continuously honed will
gain renown and will be
passed on.
And what's more...
One who always stays true
to his convictions and
who defends them with all
of his might...
...shall become a hero
whose name remains sung
throughout the ages.
How?! How were you able
to cut me?!
There's not even a single
stain on his blade. Is he
that fast?!
Your conviction has
become warped. You do not
hone yourself as a weapon
anymore, you no longer
improve. You have lost
your sharpness.
Thus your blade
became sullied with blood,
rusted, its edge dulled.
And a dull blade is
worthless! Remember,
people are like swords!
You didn't remember me at
first, but have you also
forgotten your final
words to me after you cut
me down and left me there
to die?
[panting]
It's salamander venom.
My blade is coated with
it.
Fear not. The numbness
will take away your pain.
And within forty-eight
hours, you'll be dead.
Do you know why I am
feared as Hanzo the
Salamander? I shall
tell you my secret.
You can consider it
to be a parting gift
for you.
In my village, there once
lived a deadly, venomous
black salamander.
I was just a child, but
when the salamander died,
its venom sac was
implanted in me.
It was placed right
here,... in order to turn
me into a man capable of
producing my own poison.
And I'm now able to
poison people... simply
by breathing on them.
Of course, I was feared
as a child.
I had to use this
mask or I'd kill everyone
around me whenever I took
a breath.
Then... why didn't you...
take off your mask during
our fight?
I've done that in other
fights in the past. But
there are risks.
You see, this mask plays
one other role. It
protects me as well.
If the venom sac is cut
open during battle
somehow...
... then the concentrated
venom inside will vaporize
and escape.
And likely, I
will inhale it.
Even with my resistance,
I would not be left
unharmed. The gas would
paralyze me, too.
I wouldn't die. But I'd
be left vulnerable to
attack.
Against a skilled
opponent like you, I
must keep the mask on
to prevent that.
I can't afford to
give you an advantage.
Though it seems that you
wielded a dull blade.
People themselves
are swords.
Which means despite
my best efforts, I
wasn't sharp enough.
Let me tell you
something.
Death... is not the
end...
Uh!
Loss of conviction is the
end.
It's quite a nuisance.
It's hard to discern
someone's conviction just
by looking at them.
Even if you were to die
here, you wouldn't be
considered blunted or
dull.
It's your companions,...
who abandoned the fight
at the start, fleeing in
fear upon hearing my
name... who are
worthless lumps of iron.
[panicking]
Hanzo the Salamander!
Run!
You valiantly used your
body as a shield to
defend them.
[struggling]
I shall sing your praises
as a hero. So state your name
as compensation for your death.
Compensation for... my
death...
One thing... Just promise
me...
Name it.
Leave my fellow samurai
alone!
That is all I ask.
Uh!
Here's the antidote.
[gasping]
I told you that one
cannot tell if someone
has conviction or not...
just by looking at them.
But sometimes one can
tell by fighting that
person. And you're a
rare one indeed.
I shall spare your life
today. Although... it's
true that you've taken in
so much poison, there's
still a chance you may
die from it.
It is difficult to see
one's convictions
through.
I, too, have my own
conviction...
...to find a way to
somehow bring peace to
this world.
I'll use you as a test
case, to see if you will
die still embracing your
convictions.
Or if you end up just
surviving and abandoning
those convictions over
time.
You insisted on testing
me back then. Have you
really abandoned all of
your convictions now?
That is not something
that you can tell simply
by looking at someone,
I'm afraid.
Uh!
There is still a way to
stop me even though I'm
immortal now.
I told you before,
Mifune. Do you remember
it?
Stay back until the
opportunity presents
itself, and then seal me
away. You have done well.
Lord Mifune!
His poison!
No, it's fine, I'll be
all right. I have some
resistance to this
poison.
Although perhaps not at
this close a distance.
Therefore, all of you
will retreat with me. And
then prepare to seal him.
Now I can say for sure,
it was worth him surviving
that venom.
It's far enough.
We'll watch from here.
Lord Hanzo.
Mifune, one final
thing...
I entrust you with my
conviction!
Seppuku?! By a shinobi?!
He's disobeying the
orders embedded in my
tag?!
He killed himself?! Time
to switch him to mindless
mode then.
[struggling]
Ugh!
Why's he not moving?
Lord Hanzo would never
stand for taking orders
not from someone who
hides in the shadows,
manipulating others like
they're puppets.
He fought off the person
controlling him and has
won his freedom.
If you remain true to
yourself and your convictions,
you'll show that you're not
just a blunted blade.
Now seal him!
Yes, sir!
So they sealed him,
huh...?
[grunting]
I shall sing of your
praises and you'll live
on as a hero.
I hereby witness your
unwavering conviction.
Truly splendid, Lord
Hanzo!
Lord Mifune?
I've heard Lord Hanzo
doesn't have a proper
gravesite.
And that means... We must
find a suitable place for
him to rest.
What are you doing,
Choji! I'm an enemy now,
accept it!
Your movements are slow,
Choji! Pull yourself
together! The three of
us prepared for this!
I'm sorry. This is way
too much for me! I can't
do it! I can't take our
Sensei down!
I just can't!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: True Kindness.
Choji! Take me down, you
coward!