[theme music]
-Oh, Lady Chiyo, you--
-I don't get it.
What she's trying to do?
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
Medical Ninjutsu?
No.
-We have to get
back and neutralize
that poison, and quickly.
Our job here is finished.
We beat him.
-But more than that,
there's something I must do.
My job isn't done yet.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): So this
is what she was talking about.
-Is that?
KAKASHI: Yeah.
-Leave him alone, will you?
What do you think you're doing?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Lady Chiyo is
exchanging her own life for his.
-Sakura, what?
-It's gonna be all right.
She's bring him back.
-She's bringing him back?
What are you talking about?
I mean, how is
that even possible?
-This jutsu, only
Lady Chiyo knows it.
It's a special jutsu.
-Wait.
Are you serious?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Such
a convenient jutsu
should not be possible.
That chakra flow.
There's no question.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): It
comes at a considerable risk.
[groan]
-Not enough chakra.
[panting]
Come on.
-You can use my chakra.
Take as much as you need to.
That'll work, won't it, Granny?
Please?
[panting]
KAKASHI: Naruto and Gaara
are both jinchuriki.
Naruto knows how Gaara feels
better than anyone in the Sand
ever could.
After all, those
who are jinchuriki
have been treated the
same way in every village.
That's why he feels this
desperate need to save Gaara.
It doesn't matter
whether Gaara's
from the Sand or the
Leaf or anywhere else.
CHIYO: Place your hands
on top of mine, son.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
KAKASHI: Naruto's dream
is to become Hokage.
So the news that Gaara
had been made Kazekage
hit him pretty hard.
He was frustrated, but at the
same time, deep in his heart,
he was profoundly
happy for Gaara.
You see, Naruto has
another remarkable gift.
He doesn't need much time or
many words to make friends
with almost everyone he meets.
CHIYO: In this world of shinobi
created by frivolous old people
it's a great comfort to
know that new souls like
yourself have come along.
Up till now, everything I've
done in my life has been wrong.
But at least, here
in my final hour,
I can finally do something
right for a change.
The Sand and the Leaf, may
the future that awaits them
be different from the way
things were in our time.
This special power of yours
that Kakashi spoke about of,
that power will change
the future dramatically.
Become a Hokage the likes of
which has never been seen.
And as for you, Sakura.
-Yes.
CHIYO: In the future, help
those closest to your heart,
not some old grandmother
with one foot in the grave.
You're a lot like me, child.
So few women possess
such strong spirit.
You'll surpass your
master as a kunoichi.
I've little doubt.
Naruto, do an old woman
a favor, will you?
You are the only
person in the world
who knows the extent
of Gaara's pain.
He also knows your pain.
Please, look after Gaara.
-Gaara.
Gaara!
GAARA: Who is that?
Who's-- who's calling me?
Who is it?
This hand.
Oh.
It's just my hand again.
My hand-- me.
Who am I?
I-- I am--
-Gaara.
-Naruto.
What is this?
-They all came
running to help you.
You've had everyone
worried half to death.
-Lord Gaara!
Sir, are you all right?
Yeah!
[cheering]
Welcome back, sir!
-You sure had us worried there.
-No kidding.
You caused us a whole ton of
grief there, little brother.
-Ugh.
Will you two quit
putting on airs already?
Gaara's the Kazekage, Remember?
Ugh.
Show a little
respect, you nitwits.
-Gaara, talk to me.
How do you feel?
-Easy.
You shouldn't get
up too quickly.
Your body hasn't completely
recovered from the rigor mortis
yet.
-Oh.
Thanks be to the heavens!
I thought we'd lost him.
Without the Lord Kazekage I'd--
-Get a hold of yourself.
There's no way we'd
ever lose Lord Gaara.
Lord Gaara is the
hottest thing ever.
He's a quiet, cool,
strong, and elite warrior.
-Yeah.
Lord Gaara is totally
gorgeous, isn't he?
After all, he is Kazekage.
-If anything should
ever happen again,
I'll protect him
with all my heart.
-No.
I will!
-Get in line.
-Lord Gaara!
-I know I'm still a genin
and all, but come on.
Cut me a break.
KANKURO: Ah, don't sweat it.
Women always go
weak in the knees
for that cool,
elite type of guy.
So what can you do?
Am I right?
-I'm pretty sure Shikamaru said
something like that once too.
GAARA: He's known
the same pain I have,
and he taught me
that I can change
the path my life will follow.
One day, Kankuro, I'd like
to become something precious
to others too.
KANKURO: Naruto, thank you.
-Huh?
Hey.
Don't look at me.
It's granny over there that
you should be thanking.
She saved Gaara with some kind
of incredible Medical Ninjutsu.
She tired herself
out and fell asleep,
but I'm sure she'll be fine when
we get her back to the village.
KANKURO: No. She won't.
Granny Chiyo used "that" jutsu.
-What are you talking about?
Why won't she?
-I will.
-Huh?
KANKURO: She wasn't
using Medical Ninjutsu.
It was a Reanimation Ninjutsu.
Granny Chiyo is dead.
-Reanimation Jutsu?
-What are you saying?
How can she be dead?
-It's a ninjutsu that allows
you to bring someone back
from the dead in exchange
for your own life.
-It can't be.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): As I thought.
-Guy-sensei.
-Mm.
-Years ago, in our
Puppet Master corps,
a jutsu was secretly
developed to breathe life
into actual puppets.
Granny Chiyo led that project.
They did come up with a
method for it, however,
midway they concluded there
was too much risk involved.
It was classified
as forbidden jutsu
before human testing could
be done, and sealed away.
CHIYO: In this world
of shinobi created
by frivolous old people,
it's a great comfort
to know that new souls like
yourself have come along.
Up till now, everything I've
done in my life has been wrong.
But at least here
in my final hour
I can finally do something
right for a change.
The Sand and the Leaf, may
the future that awaits them
be different from the way
things were in our time.
This special power of yours
that Kakashi spoke of,
that power will change
the future dramatically.
Become a Hokage the likes of
which has never been seen.
-Fell for that one, didn't you?
I was just playing possum.
[laughter]
-Look at her.
I half expect her to
burst out laughing.
Her face is so peaceful.
-Yes.
Yes.
TEMARI: Naruto, there really is
something different about you.
It's true.
You do have the power
to change people.
Lady Chiyo always used
to say that she didn't
care about the future of
the Hidden Sand Village.
She wasn't the
kind of person who
would do something
like this for Gaara.
KAKASHI: Lady Chiyo entrusted
the future to you and Gaara.
It was a death
befitting a shinobi.
-Yeah.
Just like the Third.
-That's true.
-Hm.
I get it now.
I understand what
Granny wished for.
-Lord Gaara, are you all right?
-I'm fine.
Everyone, pray for Lady
Chiyo, and bid her farewell.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Lady Chiyo.
[theme music]
-We've finally gotten word
from the Sand Village.
Lady Chiyo was
the only casualty.
The Kazekage has been returned
to his village safely.
Teams Guy and Kakashi
completed their missions.
They're scheduled to
return in three days.
-Hm.
Sounds like it went smoothly.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): I'm a
little worried though, milady.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
What do you mean?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade, if I may?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- Return of the Kazekage.
[theme music]
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Gallery of memories.
TEMARI: Hey, Gaara.
-Hm?
-Check it out.
I found a bunch of old photos.
You wanna have a look?
-Let's see 'em.
KANKURO: Oh, hey.
These are from the
chunin exams in the Leaf.
TEMARI: Can you believe
it's been three years?
KANKURO: That's when
Gaara flipped out and went
on a rampage.
TEMARI: I don't what
was gonna happen.
Although, I never
thought Gaara could
be stopped by such
a knucklehead.
GAARA: We are greatly indebted
to Naruto Uzumaki and the Leaf
Village.
TEMARI: Well, we are
allies with them now.
KANKURO: Plus, we
helped them out
with the Hidden Sound Village.
GAARA: And I intend to maintain
that bond with the Leaf.
-Hey, by the way.
-Hm?
-You've got a million pictures
of Gaara and almost none of me.
What's up with that?
-Well, Gaara's kind
of a fan favorite.
Give the people what
they want, right?
-Oh, man.
That hurts.
-Sorry.