[music playing]
[bells jingling]
-Let's go!
[grunt]
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Impressive.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Nice.
He was trapped in midair
so he used his Shadow Clone
Jutsu to move himself
out of the way.
-Transform!
[yell]
[grunt]
-That'll be enough of that.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
He's growing up right
before my eyes.
Not only that--
[chuckling]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
--his timing
with the shadow clone
has improved as well.
-Ah.
-Not bad.
-Incredible.
-You've matured,
haven't you, Naruto?
However, you still
have a ways to go.
It's obvious you're
as impatient as ever.
You attacked before I even
had a chance to say start.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I didn't say start yet.
Now, let's do this properly.
Ready?
Start.
[gasp]
-Huh?
[MUSIC - NOBODYKNOWS+, "HERO'S
COME BACK"]
-Now let's do this properly.
Ready?
Start.
[gasp]
-Huh?
Aw, come on.
I can't believe he
tricked me again.
-Argh, you big dummy!
[music playing]
-You've done good work.
Do you remember who I am?
-How could I
forget, Lord Sasori?
-Of course he remembers.
It wouldn't be much of
a jutsu if he didn't.
Hm.
-They're still loyal servants
after regaining their memory.
[bells jingling]
[music playing]
-Is it ready?
Good, it's done.
Hm.
You can watch from
here, Sasori, my man.
-Hmm.
-Leave it to me.
I'll attack from above.
Beautiful, isn't it?
What do you think
of my creation, hmm?
-Just don't keep me
waiting too long, Deidara.
-Heh heh.
[music playing]
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
The One-Tail Shukaku's
jinchuuriki host,
Gaara of the Desert.
Hmph.
Let's see what he can do.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Now what
are you gonna do, Sakura?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Right, above, left,
behind-- only one place left.
[yell]
-Aah!
Oh!
Uh, huh?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Wha--
what ridiculous strength.
-Yes!
Nicely done.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
So, looks like
the Fifth Hokage's been
teaching her more than just
medical ninjutsu.
-The same quick temper
and monster strength.
Tsunade's turned Sakura into
a mirror image of herself.
SAKURA: Kakashi-sensei--
-Huh?
-Found ya, didn't I?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I really should
stop acting like such an
idiot when I'm around Sakura.
If I don't, she's gonna kill me.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): She infuses
her chakra together, focuses it
into her fist, and
releases it all at once.
Something like that requires
incredibly precise chakra
control.
Medical ninjutsu combined
with monstrous strength.
No, it's more than that.
After all, she's more
of a genjutsu type.
She might just become a better
kunoichi than the Fifth Hokage.
[bells jingling]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
You had your shot.
Now it's my turn.
[shutter click]
-That's one.
DEIDARA: Two.
[shutter click]
-Three.
They only have three
guards watching the skies.
Hmph.
I can't help but appreciate the
architecture of this village.
It's so-- artistic.
Just another reason why
it's truly worth destroying.
Hah.
Time for a little covert action.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
There he is.
The first thing a
shinobi must learn
is to conceal his presence
and remain hidden.
This is completely different
from that time before.
-Ninja must know how to
conceal their movements
and hide effectively.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Well,
they understand that much.
They've hidden well.
-Uh, huh?
-You and me, right
now, fair and square!
Let's go!
-You know, compared
to the others,
you're a little bit weird.
-Oops!
[grunt]
-Time for today's lesson.
This is shinobi battle skills
rule number one-- taijutsu.
[grunt]
-Ha!
Got ya!
I just need one shot!
-It won't do any good
if you can't hit me.
[grunt]
-Whew, that was a close one.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Huh?
-(IN UNISON) Yaa!
-Fine, bring it.
-Those bells are mine!
[bells jingling]
[growl]
[grunt]
-(IN UNISON) Get back here!
[gasp]
-Dancing Leaf Shadow?
[grunt]
-That's the attack
Bushy Brow uses.
-It's Kakashi-sensei's
copy ninjutsu.
[yelling]
-Now, where do I
find the real one?
-Right over here!
-Huh?
-Leaf Village
Hidden Finger Jutsu!
[gasp]
-Oh no!
NARUTO: A thousand
years of death!
KAKASHI: Aah!
-Now, where do I
find the real one?
-Right over here!
-Huh?
-Leaf Village
Hidden Finger Jutsu!
[gasp]
-Oh no!
NARUTO: A thousand
years of death!
KAKASHI: Aah!
[grunt]
-Darn it!
I thought I had him
for sure that time.
-I thought that was the end
for me-- in more ways than one.
-Haa!
[grunt]
[sigh]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
I remember when
this used to be a lot easier.
-I'm going to crush you!
Aah!
[grunting]
-Now you're mine!
Huh?
-Don't let your enemy get
behind you all the time.
-Eh?
KAKASHI: Leaf Village
Secret Finger Jutsu!
-No!
[grunt]
[moan]
-A thousand years of death!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
She's over there, huh?
Hm.
-Sasuke!
Where'd you go?
Don't tell me
Kakashi-sensei found you.
No, he can't capture my Sasuke.
I won't let him!
Whew, he didn't hear me.
I'm safe.
KAKASHI: Sakura, behind you.
-Huh?
[scream]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Even
though they've been apart
for two years, their teamwork
is still pretty good.
Although, I was hoping to find
out how this next volume ends.
-All right, Multi
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[music playing]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
The sheer number
of his clones always amazes me.
-Let's get him!
Yaa!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[yell]
[yelling]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
What a pain.
Looks like I won't
have time for reading.
-This is starting
to get interesting.
-They're doing pretty good.
Better than I thought.
-Just wait.
You haven't seen anything.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Now
then, what should I do next?
[chuckling]
-Huh?
Where'd that weird
thing come from?
Oh!
Ow!
-They're not weird,
they're perfect.
-What the--
[grunt]
-Look at those fools.
They have no
appreciation for art.
Huh.
[grunting]
DEIDARA: You have to feel art.
And true art is an explosion!
-Last time I heard
the bells, they
were coming from this direction.
I'm sure of it.
-But he might have let
us hear them on purpose
to draw us in, so be careful.
-That's right.
We can't forget who
we're dealing with.
[mystical roar]
-Huh?
-Oh.
[groaning]
-It's Sasuke.
-He looks hurt.
[groaning]
-Naruto, Sakura--
you've gotta help me.
I got away from Orochimaru.
I was able to escape.
Please, help me.
Naruto, Sakura, please.
-Too bad he's not real.
I'd give almost anything
to be able to talk
with Sasuke for a while.
[groaning]
-Release!
I don't want to play
with your illusions.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
SAKURA: Naruto, Kakashi-sensei's
behind that tree there.
-Darn it.
-Yeah.
Don't worry, I got this handled.
Rasengan!
-Well, Kakashi-sensei?
-Yeah?
-Is there something
you wanted to say?
I'm not exactly sure I
heard you clearly before.
-Shinobi battle techniques,
part two-- genjutsu.
-Oh my!
Huh?
Aah!
Someone there?
Oh!
I think I felt something.
What was it?
Ah!
What's going on?
SASUKE: Sakura--
-Sasuke!
[groaning]
-S-Sakura, help me.
Please, help me.
-Uh.
[scream]
-It was so much easier
to fool her back then.
-You'll have to come up with
something better than that.
If you think we're gonna fall
for that old trick again,
you're crazy.
-We wouldn't be that stupid.
-Really?
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
-Check it out.
The bells slipped off his belt.
-No, Naruto!
Don't!
NARUTO: They're mine!
[groan]
-You see?
You still fall for
the same old tricks.
Huh?
-There's no way I'd fall for
a dumb old trap like that!
[grunt]
-Huh?
-Substitution jutsu.
-Darn it!
-Why don't you ever
listen to me, you idiot?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
So the same old tricks
won't work on you, huh?
-Infiltration successful.
Hm?
-That's as far as you go.
-Ooh.
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
FEMALE REPORTER: I
don't know if you
can see the smoke
from the explosion,
but there's an
incredible battle going
on in the skies above
the Hidden Sand Village.
MALE NEWSCASTER: Can
you give us any details?
FEMALE REPORTER: It appears
an intruder has engaged
Lord Kazekage in a fierce battle
in the skies above the Sand
Village.
The residents are
watching in horror as--
[scream]
MALE NEWSCASTER:
Are you all right?
Ahem, it seems we
have lost audio.
We'll keep you updated as
we receive more details.
NARUTO: Next time, "The
Jinchuuriki of the Sand."
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
TSUNADE NARRATING:
Intelligence research report
by the ANBU Black
Ops-- Akatsuki.
The Akatsuki is a
mysterious organization
created by a group
of shinobi who
abandoned their own villages.
The organization
was created in order
to accomplish a common goal.
They wear dark robes embroidered
with a red cloud pattern
and engage in covert activities.
It is believed that
Orochimaru was once
affiliated with
this organization.
The Leaf has only encountered
two of its members.
Sasuke's older brother,
Itachi Uchiha--
he possesses the
Mangekyo Sharingan
and destroyed the Uchiha clan.
The other is Kisame
Hoshigaki, the former Phantom
of the Hidden Mist.
During the initial
contact, three
of the Leaf's most skilled
jonin, Kakashi, Asuma,
and Kurenai, were
defeated by this pair.
The Akatsuki's objective is
to obtain Naruto's Nine-Tails.
It remains unclear what
they intend to use it for.
Further investigation
is required.