Excellent! These
Sealing Tags will
stop us!
That was very
nicely done,
there, young
Kazekage!
What's this?!
[grunt]
What's going on? No!
Somebody stop this!
I wanna be sealed
away now!
It's entirely out
of our control!
Our bodies have been
programmed to automatically
counter an enemy's offensive
jutsu.
[grunt]
Here they come!
Quick, surround them!
Particle Style:
Atomic Dismantling
Jutsu!
[heavy breathing]
(Second Tsuchikage AKA Mu)
You've gotten
old, Ohnoki.
Nonsense!
[heavy breathing]
Without the Kazekage's
help and sensory skills,
you'll surely die, Ohnoki.
"The Mizukage,
the Giant Clam,
and the Mirage"
[woozy groans]
Hey!
Do not underestimate
my jutsu! You seriously
need to stand back!
For real!
For real?
Now, here are all
my weaknesses!
For real!
For real?
Yes, for real.
Now listen!
I use Shadow Style.
In other words, that
means Genjutsu.
And my summoning...
...is a Giant Clam!
[pained groans]
And I'm a
Lightning
Style User!
Line up your
Earth Style
shinobi to use
them as a shield.
And attack with
your Wind Style
shinobi!
Great, thanks for the intel!
You have any other details
you can tell us?
I'm not in
control of
my body!
There's no time
for more talk!
Come on!
All right!
Wind and Earth Style
shinobi, follow me!
Sealing Unit, you too!
Yes, that's right, Raikage.
Go on, get away from here.
If you and I stick together,
then these guys will never
be able to seal us.
So...
..Do you have
a strategy..
..Fifth Kazekage?!
(GAARA)
I'm leaving you
in charge here.
Huh? Seriously?!
We have to fight
him without you?
Hey, hey, hold on!
What kind of tactic
is that?!
Didn't you hear me?!
I am a Shadow Style User!
This Giant Clam
can cast a genjutsu
over a very wide area!
It makes you
see illusions!
Physical attacks
won't work!
I'm talking
about a mirage!
I can tell you have
no desire to kill.
No, of course not!
Why would I?!
I can't stand the idea
of being manipulated
by another jutsu user.
That's why I want you
to seal me as quickly as
possible, Kazekage! Hey!
Deal with him.
Come back!
You can count
on us.
We'll get
wispy whiskers!
Wispy whiskers?
How dare you
call me that!
I don't care about
the Reanimation Jutsu
anymore! I'll kill you!
[frightened goan]
I think he means it!
Huh?
[determined groans]
[sigh]
How awkward.
Let's get him, guys!
Yeah!
C'mon, let's do this!
I'm counting on you!
So show me what you
all can do!
Good!
Now you look like
you mean business!
Listen up!
I'll tell you
one more time!
Attacking the me
you see before you
is completely pointless!
Your sensory skills are
useless against me.
You shouldn't
underestimate me.
Stone Clone Jutsu!
So you'll overwhelm
me with numbers.
That might work.
Did we get him?
[gasp]
[small yelp]
Really?!
Do you people know
how to listen?!
I told you that
attacking this me is
completely useless!
This me is
only a mirage!
(Shinobi A)
So what should
we do, then?
Are you kidding me?!
First you need to
defeat my Giant Clam!
It's the one that's
been creating the
mirage all along!
Its shell is hard.
Use large-scale
weapons or Paper Bombs!
Yes, but...
What is it?!
We used them in
our last attack,
see?
[frightened gasp]
Uh, me?!
Come on!
Just hurry up and
retrieve all your
weapons!
Uh, right.
Sorry!
Everyone, quickly!
[tugging grunts]
Hey, that
one's mine.
Now where's
my weapon?
Hey, look!
A lot of 'em
are over there!
And you guys call
yourselves shinobi?
I'm sorry that this
is taking so long.
How awkward.
All right!
Let's do this,
people!
Target the
Giant Clam!
[throwing grunts]
Whoa!
Did we?
What?
Damn it!
I can't stand
this anymore!
Huh?
Look, will you
listen to me?
I keep telling you
the same thing!
That Giant Clam
there is also a
mirage, you
idiots!
You have to
go after the
real one!
Yeah, all right!
But where's the
real one?
[groan]
Just like I said!
It's hiding somewhere
back there behind me
using the mirage as
a cover!
[grunt]
Damn it!
How many times do
I have to say it?
Attacking this me
is useless!
Uh, well, actually I was
aiming for the Giant Clam
behind you.
I told you,
that's just a
mirage, you idiot!
Aw, I'm so confused!
I don't understand this!
Seriously! We don't
understand it, either!
Look, you guys..
(shinobi E)
Whispy whiskers!
[angry groan]
You're dead!
[frightened moans]
He means it!
Who said that?!
Apologize! Now!
I'm sorry.
[sigh]
How awkward.
Let's try an
all-out attack
again, you guys!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Really?!
Are you sure you
want to do that?!
Where'd that
come from?!
Behind you,
Tsuchikage!
[grunt]
No! Not now!
Particle Style!
Atomic Dismantling
Jutsu.
Huh?
Is that?
Planet Rasengan!
Is that?!
Naruto?!
Yes!
Damn it!
Lord Mu is a
Sensory Shinobi.
(Naruto)
Gaara!
Sand!
[grunt]
Using Sand as a springboard for
his attack. I see.
Dodge this.
My jutsu's faster
than yours.
[gasp]
[attack yell]
Good.
This is...
a violently rotating...
Rasengan!
Earth Style..
Weighted Boulder
Jutsu!
Thanks to that,
you're so heavy
now you can't even
raise your arms.
[stretching]
You used to hate
the other villages.
Now you work with
them so well.
I've learned that
it's worth living
a long life.
You can enjoy
change.
Don't let your
guard down yet.
I'm still...
Nice!
Way to go,
Gaara!
Oh, yeah, and you
were pretty awesome
back there, as well,
Shortly Gramps!
I am the
Tsuchikage,
you know!
Have respect!
What are you doing
on the battlefield,
Naruto?!
Why are you here?!
Err... well...
I, uh...
It's a long story.
You better be able to
provide an explanation
good enough to persuade
me!
(Shikaku)
That's not possible.
Huh?
So I'll do the talking.
This is Shikaku Nara at
HQ.
Lord Tsuchikage,
Lord Kazekage.
You were in the midst of
fighting, so I thought
I'd save the complicated
talk for later.
All right,
we're all ears.
But the fighting's
not over.
We must head
out soon.
You can brief
us on the way.
Hm..
[woozy groans]
You know, I'm really
not trying to win
against you, here!
[struggling]
You're just too
strong for us.
[groan]
Still, you
must seal me.
Otherwise, I'll remain
a puppet controlled by
your enemy.
And I'm loath to stay
like this, believe me!
Okay everyone!
Get up!
[struggling]
So that's it...
I can't believe even
the Raikage relented!
Very well.
I understand.
(Shikaku)
I'll cease
transmitting
now.
Right.
Naruto.
It's good you're going
to each battlefield to
identify transformed
enemies.
But as a former
Jinchuriki, I know...
The Nine Tails' chakra
you have. Are you really
sure that it's safe to
use it so heavily?
You know what?
I don't plan
to die until I
become Hokage.
Just because you're
Kazekage already,
doesn't mean you can
treat me like a kid.
I'll take the right
battlefront! Gaara,
Grampa Tsuchikage, you
guys go to the left.
Naruto, the Third
Raikage is on that
battlefield!
Got it!
And our opponent's
going to be the
Second Mizukage,
right?
Yes, the Genjutsu User.
Well then,
ordinary combat
methods won't
work against him.
[gasp]
I thought he
was right there?
Why do I bother
to keep telling
you it's a mirage?
Go pick them up!
Hey, you there!
What's that?
Are you talking
to me?
Yes, you! You're
from the Hidden
Mist, aren't you?
Aren't you familiar
with my jutsu?
Sorry, I only know
a little about you,
Lord Second.
I mostly just know
about the current
Fifth Mizukage.
[groan]
The Hidden Mist's
obsession with
secrecy is to
blame for this!
If I knew things would be
like this, I would've left
behind a more memorable
legacy!
[small gasp]
Uh, oh.
Hey! All of you!
Playtime's over!
You've gotta come
at me seriously now!
But we have been
serious this whole
time.
I have no control over
my body. It's casting
jutsu all on its own.
Damn it! I can't stand
being used like this!
It's my Water Balloon
Jutsu! Defend yourselves!
[shocked groans]
Huh?
[shocked moans]
It's Commander Gaara!
Hey, what took
you so long?!
Now, I hope this time
you'll be able to seal
me!
Yes, I
intend to.
I'm looking
forward to it.
Commander!
[grunt]
[screams]
[pained yells]
[frightened running]
[pained yell]
[grunt]
Don't look elsewhere!
Pay attention!
[heavy breathing]
Hey...
Is that all
you've got?
[heavy breathing]
I've been telling
you my weaknesses.
You guys are useless!
Yeah, you keep
telling us, but
it's not helping.
You're too strong!
[heavy breathing]
This is more like
oil than water.
Even if I use Sand as
a defense, it'll just
seep in and collapse it.
You tried to stop
Mu first, didn't
you?
You always have to
stop the strongest
opponent first.
That's what winning a
battle is all about!
We did.
[groan]
Oh, please!
It's obvious that
I'm the stronger one!
I mean, that Mu guy
looks like nothing
more than a half
dead mummy.
Am I right?
Maybe.
However,
appearances
can be deceiving.
You are strong.
Hm!
So finally,
you understand!
Hey! What do you mean,
"appearances can be
deceiving?!"
Your wispy whis-
Shhh!
[moan]
[angry exhale]
I already told you.
I'm not even here.
You're seeing my
giant clam's wide range
genjutsu. It's a mirage.
Physical attacks
are useless!
You must find the
Giant Clam quickly
and crush it! Or
this will never end!
Ah, yes.
You use sand.
I simply prefer to
let my actions do
the talking for me.
It's over there!
I see. You were
already searching
for it with your
sand.
That's why you
were distracted
and only focused
on defense.
Well, finally!
At last I get to
face a worthy foe!
Now hurry up and
defeat me, already!
[schocked grunt]
I used too much
chakra in my
battle with
Lord Mu.
I can't use
Particle Style
now!
Then I have
no choice.
I'll just have to
smash it to pieces!
Earth Style!
Stone Fist
Jutsu!
Just one problem.
[pained groan]
A weak punch like that
isn't going to be enough,
little Ohnoki. Put some
power into it!
You're not using
Particle Style,
you must be out
of juice.
You forget that I'm
not that Lil' Ohnoki
from long ago that
you made fun of.
Huh?
Earth Style..
Super Weighted
Boulder Jutsu!
Not bad, Ohnoki!
Not bad at all!
Oh, no!
I've done
it now!
The genjutsu's
undone.
[struggling]
My back!
In my heart, I always
knew you'd become
Tsuchikage one day.
[struggling groan]
But just look at you now!
You're nothing more than
a stubborn old fool with
a bad back!
I'll admit that punch
had some real power to it,
but you overdid it and put
yourself out of commission!
Hey! Hurry up and
escape, would ya?!
This is the Hozuki
Clan's Water Gun
Jutsu!
[pained groan]
Go on! I can't
stop myself!
(Temari)
No matter how many
times we attack,
there's no effect!
We haven't inflicted
any damage!
(Dodai)
We need a
more powerful
Wind Style User.
(Temari)
Well, I'm not a half bad
Wind Style user myself,
you know.
Honestly, in the Allied
Forces, there isn't a
stronger one.
(Naruto)
Yeah, there is!
Me!
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
"Paradox"
(Temari)
Is it a new Rasengan?
It just might work!