Yes, Kinoto?
Lord Danzo, there's
an urgent matter...
Hiruzen himself
is leading them?
Damn that meddling
old fool...
He has gone too far.
Kinoe, you here?
[scoff]
What are you
planning to do?
Kill me, Sensei?
But can you go through
with it, I do wonder,
Sarutobi-sensei?
Hm?!
Even with that...
No actually,
because of it...
Hiruzen simply won't
be able to kill his
student Orochimaru.
Sarutobi! Kill him!
For times just like this, we
have another secret meeting
place. Kinoe, go and wait
there for Orochimaru.
[harrumphing chuckle]
Lightning Blade!
You... [chuckle]
I like the look
in your eye.
However, I
don't want a fake.
[chuckle]
Aren't you cute one.
So, do you want to
taste his blood as well?
So, Lord Third, was it
you who set this all up?
[grunting]
Don't move!
[grunt]
So that's Orochimaru...
This emergency summons
has been issued for the
immediate capture of
Orochimaru, who
escaped during the
previous mission.
According to the intel that
we have received, he is
seriously wounded.
He won't be able to exit the
Land of Fire easily in his
current condition.
Listen carefully. The
knowledge, data, and jutsu
that Orochimaru
possesses are valuable
assets to the Hidden Leaf.
If it is possible at
all, we must bring
him back here alive.
If he's allowed to leave the
Land of Fire, it would be a
dire and perhaps even
fatal blow to the Leaf!
Therefore...
This has to be settled
before he crosses the
nation's borders. All of
you must do your very best.
Go!
You must still have a
lot of affection for
your former pupil.
It's hard to believe
that you of all
people would fail...
Of course, I'm
happy to cooperate.
For the sake of the Leaf,
I'll do all that I can.
Thank you for the offer.
I do appreciate it.
Against those eyes, I...
Next time I won't fail.
Summoning Jutsu!
What's going
on, Kakashi?
I need you to follow a
scent. It's Orochimaru.
Snakes can be very
difficult. The thing is,
they don't sweat.
But you just
leave it to me!
Who are you? How do you
know about this place?
Lord Danzo sent me here!
I've come on urgent business
regarding Lord Orochimaru!
Here. This is the
message from Lord Danzo.
There's no mistake.
This is Lord Danzo's
seal, all right.
What?! Lord
Orochimaru? The Leaf?!
That wasn't a
transformation!
His flesh was
really smoke?!
Give me the details.
I am Gotta of
the Iburi Clan.
Oh...
And I, well, my
name is Kinoe.
Tenzo!
Huh?
Yukimi!
Tenzo! Welcome home!
If Lord Danzo or Lord
Orochimaru were ever to find
themselves in unforeseen
circumstances, it was
previously agreed upon
that they would come to
this place to get help.
So Lord Orochimaru
will come here?!
Most likely.
[chatter]
We can control the
pursuit of the ANBU.
I'll be able to take
Lord Orochimaru out of the
country without fail.
Lord Orochimaru gave
us the gift of life.
We would do
anything for him.
Everyone, get ready to
welcome Lord Orochimaru!
[giggle]
Come with me, Tenzo!
What?! But, um... I...
Stand here for a second!
You see!
It's the same!
Since you were young...
I've been making these
marks to measure your height!
Oh I see, but...
Yukimi, enough.
That boy is not Tenzo...
He is, too!
But, um...
Who is "Tenzo?"
He's Yukimi's
younger brother.
But he's no longer here.
We placed him in
Lord Orochimaru's
care three years ago.
"In his care..."
Three years ago?
Then this mark is...
Even though we've both
been apart for such a
long time, I remember
what you looked like.
And finally,
you've come back!
I just can't believe
you've returned from
Lord Orochimaru's!
[gasp]
I'm sorry...
Yukimi...
Show him around.
Sure...
We use this whole area
as our clan's graveyard.
The trees?
Instead of using
headstones, we plant trees.
They say that the soul
finds refuge in the tree and
provides us with protection.
The soul?
Yes. The souls
of the dead...
Our ability to
transform our bodies
used to be incomplete.
We didn't have total
control over our
metamorphosis into smoke.
Sometimes, we'd just
transform without warning.
Or dissipate without
turning back into flesh.
Members of our clan
never lived for very long.
You didn't see many
elders, did you?
No...
So many died...
That's why we
planted these trees.
So many have died?
But then something
amazing happened:
Lord Orochimaru
found our Clan.
This symbol of
his, the Curse Mark,
stabilized our ability.
But unfortunately
the Curse Mark wasn't
a perfect fit either...
He said it was necessary to
do much more research.
That's why Tenzo had to go
away, he had to be sent to
Lord Orochimaru
to be a test subject.
Test subject...
The younger you are,
the stronger our
power manifests itself.
So he needed a
young test subject.
But that left you
as the only child
in your whole Clan.
It wasn't like he was
gonna die or anything!
At least, that's what
Lord Orochimaru said.
And even if I were to be
called up, too, I'd be able
to see everyone.
Including Tenzo.
To see... everyone?
Everyone...
What is this?!
What happened?!
This is...
What's wrong?!
It's so strange...
Who planted all these?!
Those children...
Tenzo is still...
[grunting]
We don't need
this one!
[gasp]
Or this one!
[crying]
Let's go.
Huh?
It seems I've nearly
reached my limit.
Just a little more...
What is this?
See how the roots twist
around to form the ceiling
and walls of this passage?
The whole interior is
a maze of hollow caves
just like this one.
It gets a bit tight
from here on out,
but we can still fit.
Where are we going?
Tenzo and I had a
secret hideout here!
[grunting]
[outside noise chatter]
You can hear
really well here.
That crevice up there leads
straight to the outside.
We used to come here
all the time to listen
to that sound together.
We'd talk about what the
outside world might be like.
Why don't you just
go out yourself?
Because there's wind.
There's wind?!
If we were to transform into
smoke while we're outside
and if a breeze blew at the
same time, then our bodies
would be dispersed.
We have to stay where
there's no wind,
like in caves.
More than anything, we
loved coming here to listen
to the strange and
wonderful sounds outside.
We'd try to guess what
we were hearing...
And what was going
on out there...
Tenzo and I would imagine
all kinds of stuff!
[gasp]
What's wrong?!
It's serious! Someone has
come down into our village!
Is it Lord Orochimaru?
Don't know. We
haven't been able to
confirm who it is yet.
Well, if it is him, then
we will welcome him.
If it is a Leaf
pursuer, then we will
take care of them.
Everyone, hide
and get ready!
Hey, are we really
going outside?
Yes!
But if you go outside...
Aren't you afraid
of the wind?
I really want to see it!
To find out where all
those sounds come from.
Together with
you, Tenzo!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Orochimaru's
Test Subject"
We'll be together,
just the two of us!