[Samurai]
What happened
downstairs?!
[Suigetsu]
We're the only
two survivors.
Two of Sasuke's men
are probably still
here somewhere.
You haven't seen them?
Nope. But, uh, maybe
they're dead, too?
It's such a mess
down there, you
wouldn't believe it.
No. A sensory type
ninja from the Hidden
Cloud confirmed that
they're still alive.
And he told us to
go capture and
arrest them.
Oh... really?
You two...
Take off your armor.
Oh, well... Looks
like they caught on.
Guess it wasn't such a
good idea after all.
[Naruto]
I don't get it, Sakura.
Why would you do
something like that?
Huh?
Sai...!
What's wrong;
what are you
doing here?
It's a clone.
I'm here to relay to you the
truth that Sakura wanted to say,
but wasn't able to tell you.
Uh? What she
wanted to say?
Hmm.
Just what do
you mean, Sai?
Tell us.
Sakura didn't come
to confess her love.
She came to tell you
something that she and her
Leaf classmates decided.
Yeah, she was acting
really weird. So she
was hiding something
after all?
I've come to understand
her feelings.
And why she couldn't tell you.
All right. Tell us, Sai.
What did they decide?
They'll dispose of
Sasuke themselves.
Your comrades are all committed.
And are ready to move.
As One's Friend
They'll dispose of
Sasuke themselves.
Your comrades are all committed.
And are ready to move.
Even Sakura, too?
Tell me, did she
actually agree to
something like that?
Sakura's completely
in love with Sasuke!
There's no way!
She couldn't have.
After the Akatsuki's
assault on our village.
Shinobi of the Leaf
can't support Sasuke,
not when he's an
Akatsuki, too.
Sakura isn't a fool.
Or a child who doesn't
understand the circumstances.
And the situation.
That's why she came all
the way here, to try to
tell you that in person.
[sigh]
Why didn't she?!
Why didn't she just
come right out and
tell me the truth?!
It's not that easy,
Naruto. You know that.
She knew that the
truth would hurt you.
Yeah, but still...
Saying she's given up on
Sasuke and declaring
that she loves you now,
frees you from the
burden of your promise.
[gasp]
Naruto... This is a...
once in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please, bring Sasuke
back to me.
But then you said you still
wanted to save Sasuke.
I think that's why she
couldn't tell you the truth.
She was being considerate
of your feelings.
And she probably already knew
what you were going to say.
Actually, Sakura had
asked us not to tell you
anything at all, Naruto.
She wanted to tell you herself.
She said that it was her duty.
Yes, but, if she predicted
Naruto's reaction,
Doesn't it mean that she never
intended to tell him the truth?
What's Sakura
planning?
I'm not sure.
This is just
conjecture.
But I think Sakura...
She's planning to
kill Sasuke herself.
Is that true?! Really?!
It's likely.
[Sai]
Please don't take
all of this on
yourself, Sakura.
I'm in Team 7
with you.
Also the others.
Oh, I know.
And thank you, Sai.
But don't worry;
I don't intend to.
Then Sakura smiled and said
she'd work together with us.
But even I could tell that
it was a false smile.
It's a lie. Sakura would
never do something like that.
She truly loves Sasuke
with all her heart.
It's because she loves him,
that she can't let him continue
to progress toward evil.
It's because she loves him
that she wants to save him
from this path of darkness.
Even if that means killing
him with her own hands.
That is how committed she is,
in her love for Sasuke.
Also, by choosing this,
She's prepared for
you to hate her.
[gasp]
I think that...
It's how she's atoning for
the lifelong burden she
feels she's forced upon you.
Sakura feels she has relied
on you too much in the past.
This time, she wants to do
everything herself.
But Sai. Why, then? Why are
you telling me all of this?
It's obvious that Sasuke
is making Naruto suffer.
But I think you may be, too.
Even though it
wasn't my intent.
I pushed Sakura
toward this action.
It's partly my fault.
So I had to tell you.
I can't just leave Sakura be.
I'm a member of Team 7.
I see.
Naruto's mind must
be in turmoil after
learning all this.
The question now is,
what's he going to do?
Ngh!
We have very important
news and everyone needs
to listen carefully.
We're going to tell
you what happened at
the Five Kage Summit.
It's been a long
time, Danzo.
We haven't seen other
since the Uchiha incident.
[gasp]
Foo, Torune. cover me.
You keep him occupied.
I'm breaking the seal
on my right arm.
Are you really going
to fight me, Danzo?
Madara. His full
abilities are unknown;
be on your guard.
Yes, sir!
Torune, we'll both attack
together for support.
Yes, I agree.
Mind Transfer.
Huhh?
He vanished into
the pillar.
Guess it's true.
He really can pass
through solid objects.
I guess so. But even
if you can't see him,
can you sense his chakra?
I can't. It's completely gone.
A Sensory Type with
Mind Transfer abilities.
You're from the
Yamanaka Clan, right?
He can dematerialize
his body so that his
opponent's attacks pass
right through him.
He becomes completely
intangible when he
needs to.
But if he wants to strike a
blow or touch something,
then he has to manifest.
All right, then.
aim for his counterattacks.
That was a very
thoughtful analysis.
The counterattack has
to be timed perfectly.
We'll attack one
after the other,
and then get him In
the second stage.
The first stage
will be a decoy.
Let me be the decoy.
He's already seen
through my Mind
Transfer Jutsu.
Your jutsu should
be the main act.
Right. Got it.
That technique.
Torune. Use your jutsu.
Now!
Hn... Uuggh...
Of course. He just pretended
to attack to trick us!
Damn it! We fell for it!
Awww. A jutsu where
chakra is poured in to
destroy an enemy's cells.
How bothersome.
Sorry, Foo...
I'll clear it now.
That's not chakra.
They're nano-sized
venomous beetles.
They're like bacteria.
Insects that devour
cells on contact.
Heh, I've heard of them.
[Madara]
You. You're a shinobi
from the Aburame Clan who
knows Hidden Ninjutsu.
You must be Shikuro Aburame's
brat. You've got antibodies
against those insects.
To think you're with
the Foundation.
Danzo, you 've got
yourdself an impressive
array of subordinates.
Torune, forgive me.
It's fine.
But don't relax.
Quick, see if you can
sense his location.
I'm ending this right now.
No!
He pulled in Torune!
My right arm's been
infected with beetle venom.
[gasp]
You're next!
I see.
I can't believe the
Summit got so chaotic.
But I guess with Danzo...
I'm not really too eager
to become Hokage...
And even with circumstances
being what they are,
I'll still need to go
back to the Hidden Leaf
Village and discuss this
with the others first.
Madara announced that
he was going to declare
war on all of us.
We don't have all the
time in the world, here.
I don't think it'll
take long to get
everybody's approval.
So let's have them proceed
as if you'll be confirmed
as Hokage, Kakashi.
It'd be worse if
the Akatsuki or
Madara strike first
and we're put on the
defensive because
we're slow to respond.
Well, I guess you're
right. Thanks.
And then
there's Sasuke.
[sigh]
I can't believe
he'd go as far as to
attack the Summit.
Naruto. I will have you know
that this is also a battle,
to protect the Eight- and
Nine-Tails, namely you.
So for the sake of
the shinobi world,
As Kazekage, I will make sure
to protect you at all costs.
And if, as an
Akatsuki subordinate,
Sasuke were to stand
against our Allied
Shinobi Forces,
I will not show mercy.
[Gaara] [flashback]
Sasuke, you and I
are quite alike.
We've both walked through
the darkness of this world.
So your eyes should pick up even
the faintest glimmer of light.
In the past or even
at this moment.
I shut my eyes a long time ago.
The things I seek now lie
only in the darkness.
I'm afraid that Sasuke
doesn't see you anymore.
The only thing he
sees now is darkness.
[gasp]
Naruto, you once told
me that you would
become Hokage one day.
Well, I've become Kazekage.
And if you've
truly resolved to
become a Kage,
Then you're going to have
to do what needs to be
done as Sasuke's friend.
We've said everything
we came here to say.
So let's go, Gaara.
We're going to head back
home to our village now.
Kakashi Hatake.
The Sand will proceed as if you
will be confirmed as the Hokage.
As an ally, we ask that
there be no confusion
in communications.
Understood.
I consider you a friend.
In the past, "friend"
was just a word to me.
Nothing more, nothing less.
But after meeting you,
I realized something.
What's important is the
meaning of that word.
What does it mean to you?
You must decide for yourself
what you can do for Sasuke.
Think hard on that.
Let's go.
[sigh]
Naruto.
He needs to figure this
one out on his own.
[Karin]
Here I am, all alone in
the dark with Sasuke,
taking care of him
while resisting every
urge in my body.
Just hurry up and
get well already!
Huh?!
Uaaa!
You scared me half to death!
Are you all right, Sasuke?
Cold as ever.
He'll never change.
But... still...
Let me out of here.
All right, don't fret.
That's just what I'm
about to do.
I even have a present
waiting for you outside.
So you're here,
Sasuke Uchiha.
You stay back.
You'll die if you
get involved.
Now this is just perfect.
Listen, Sasuke, and Madara.
I am going to take both
your Sharingan and add
them to my collection.
[Sasuke]
There's one thing
I want to ask you.
Is it true Itachi slaughtered
the Uchiha Clan because he was
following orders you and the
other Leaf elders gave him?
[Danzo]
It seems you alone
really were special.
Damn him! Itachi told
you everything before
he died, didn't he!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Danzo's Right Arm.
[Sasuke]
Don't speak any
further about Itachi!