[music playing]
-There's another
paper bomb over here.
-This will blow the
second it's peeled off.
We're just going to
have to detonate it.
-All right, then.
-We've got a paper bomb.
Drop what you're doing,
and find cover now.
-Ready?
-Mm.
-Now is not the time to be
talking about a new Kazekage.
-I'm just seizing
the initiative.
We have to be prepared for the
worst case scenario, don't we?
MALE SPEAKER: All that matters
now is finding the Kazekage,
and getting him back.
MALE SPEAKER: It's
obvious that our priority
is the safety of this village.
And our forces are spread
thin enough as it is.
MALE SPEAKER: Are
you out of your mind?
-Oh, excuse me.
Reporting, sir.
Enemy traps have been discovered
in the rubble blocking
the gate.
We are in the process
of detonating them.
No casualties.
But the explosions have caused
a portion of the entrance
to collapse.
Repairs will take half a
day longer than anticipated.
-All right.
Understood.
I want you to see to
it that every able body
we have is dispatched
immediately.
-Yes, sir.
-[sigh]
-Come on!
-[giggling]
LORD BAKI: (THINKING) Thanks to
Gaara, the sand village made it
through with hardly a scratch,
a blessing to be sure.
But it came at far
too dear a price.
-Reporting in.
We've located and
verified the bodies
of all the aerial watchmen, sir.
It's almost certain the
enemy infiltrated the village
from above.
MALE SPEAKER: Excuse me, sir.
-Yes, what is it?
-We've just gotten word
from the pursuit corps.
Kankuro was discovered
about half a day's journey
from the village.
He's unconscious,
and in bad shape.
-(THINKING) Kankuro.
MALE SPEAKER: Some of
the unit splintered off
to bring him back,
along with his puppets.
They're on route now.
LORD BAKI: And what
of the Kazekage?
MALE SPEAKER: The rest of the
squad are still in pursuit.
We should hear soon.
-Sasori, my man, you're late.
-Mm.
-What gives.
I thought you didn't like
to keep people waiting.
-I don't.
But time flies when
you're having fun.
-What the heck does that mean?
MALE SPEAKER: Oh,
don't get so touchy.
You accomplished your
mission, didn't you?
You secured the one tail.
Once we've wrapped
things up with him,
it'll be on to my target.
-Yeah.
But Sasori, the
one you're after--
-True.
I still don't know where he is.
It would be easier if he'd just
to come to me, wouldn't it?
-Well, yeah, I suppose it would.
What kind of Jinchuriki
is he, again?
-Oh well.
Even if we can't find him,
nobody's going to complain.
As long as I catch another one.
-We're coming.
Just hang in there, Gaara.
-Naruto, I know
you're in a hurry.
But quick breaking formation.
-I know, but--
-Don't lose your cool.
Master Jiraiya taught you
better than that, didn't he?
-Oh boy.
Temari.
MALE SPEAKER: Get him
into the operating room.
-[labored breathing]
-What is this, poison?
-Prepare an antidote now.
-Gaara.
Gaara.
-Gaara,, you mean
he's been-- (THINKING)
I knew something was wrong.
-We're two and a half
days out from the sand.
We should hurry.
-Right.
MALE SPEAKER: His wounds
aren't that serious.
The problem is--
-I know, the poison.
-Yes, sir.
It's one we've
never seen before.
We've no clue how to
develop an antidote.
-First Gaara, and
now Kankuro as well.
-Naruto is the prize
the Akatsuki are after.
And make no mistake,
we will have him.
-Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not you they want.
It's what's inside of you.
There's no doubt in my mind
it's the nine-tailed fox they're
after.
They might even be
thinking of somehow seizing
control of that
power, and trying
to bend it to their will.
-Naruto, will you
come on already?
Stop getting ahead of us.
-I can't take this anymore.
I know why they're
after Gaara and me.
It's not like it's a
mystery, or anything.
You know, too,
don't you, Sakura?
There's no point hiding it.
The spirit of the
nine-tailed fox
is sealed away inside of me.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Hey, look.
It's that kid.
Let's get out of here.
-Gaara and I are the same.
We both have monsters
locked up inside of us.
That's what these
bastards are after.
And that's the
worst part about it.
To them, we're just monsters.
All those bastards see
is the means to an end.
-A demon, huh?
My demon is as real as yours is.
I was born a monster.
-Everything about us
was exactly the same.
And he had to fend for himself
a lot longer than I ever did.
-(THINKING) Naruto.
-To them, I was a
relic of the past
that they wished
would disappear.
What then was left for
me in this existence?
Why go on living any further?
For a long time, I couldn't
find an answer to that.
But in order to live,
you need a purpose.
To exist for no reason,
it's the same as being dead.
-And now he's the target
of the Akatsuki, one more
thing we have in common.
Why should his life be so
full of misery all the time?
Why is it always him?
That's why I've got to hurry.
I don't have a second to waste.
This time will be different.
I'm going to be
there to save him!
-(THINKING) Naruto, Uzumaki.
I thank you.
LORD BAKI: He's regained
consciousness, you say?
-That's right.
He has.
But he's just barely able
to respond to us, sir.
-His condition has
worsened since yesterday.
-[moaning] Baki?
Is that you?
-Kankuro.
-It was, it was him.
[groaning]
-Please, don't try to speak.
You need your strength.
-The, the red sand.
-[gasp] I see.
So he's wrapped
up in all of this.
-Lord Baki?
-Oh, Lord Baki.
-Contact the pursuit corps now.
They're to turn
back immediately.
-Actually, we haven't
received any word from them
since they found Kankuro.
-I guess we're too late we have
no choice but to go to them.
-Sir, what is it?
-Nothing.
I'm going out for a bit.
-But, but-- sir,
the higher ups are
expecting a briefing
in the morning.
-You think you have time to
waste on reports right now?
We need action, not bureaucracy.
-Yes sir.
-(THINKING) We lose
Gaara for one a day,
and this is what happens.
I need the counsel of the
honored siblings, though
whether or not they'll come
to our aid is the question.
-You know, those food pellets
are only for emergencies.
And a girl at your
age should especially
be careful with the high
fat-- is she mad at me?
-You ever heard of sexual
harassment, old man?
-Naruto.
-Yeah?
-So tell, you've met
him before, haven't you?
-Huh?
SAKURA: Itachi Uchiha.
And he's, he's after
you now, isn't he?
You know, it's not like
I just spent my time
training these past
two and a half years.
I stole in Lady Tsunade's
library, and snuck
out of the village
as much as I could.
And now the one thing
that bothered me more
than anything else
finally makes sense.
-What I have is not a dream.
Because I will
make it a reality.
I'm going to restore my clan,
and destroy a certain someone.
I'm the only one who
can destroy that person.
I am an avenger.
That means I must be
stronger than my prey.
I need this training.
There's no time for setbacks.
-The person that
Sasuke wanted to kill,
it was his older
brother, Itachi,
wasn't it, a member
of the Akatsuki?
-Itachi Uchiha.
-Itachi Uchiha?
-I hope you're ready to die.
It's just as you said, brother.
I fostered my hatred
for you all this time.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose--
to see you die.
It ends here.
-You are definitely his brother.
If anything, your eyes are
even keener than Itachi's.
Very soon, Sasuke, you'll seek
me out and desire my power.
-That's the whole
reason he left.
He saw Orochimaru as
a way to obtain power.
But all that worthless viper
cares about is Sasuke's body.
And we only have six
months left to stop him.
-(THINKING) Sakura
knows about that, too.
-But Orochimaru used to be a
member of the Akatsuki himself.
All I'm trying to say
is, we can't give up.
The closer we get
to the Akatsuki,
the closer we are to finding
information about Orochimaru.
So the closer we get to them,
the closer we are to Sasuke.
(THINKING) And after
that, Itachi Uchiha.
He's tormented Sasuke for too
long, and now Naruto as well.
This time, it's my
turn to save them.
-[gasp]
It seems someone is here.
Hey, sis, you awake?
Hey now, can you hear me?
Bah!
You dead?
Ah!
-Fell for that one, didn't you?
-I was just playing possum.
[laughing]
-Cut it out, sis.
That was way too real, honestly.
Hmm?
-Honored siblings,
I have come here
to request your assistance.
We need you.
-Dusty ancient texts
should be bundled together
and stowed away on a high shelf.
Oh, what could we
possibly do now?
-An organization called the
Akatsuki has the Shukaku.
Failing to act only
invites disaster.
-This is your generation now.
You will just have to
deal with it on your own.
-You two have maintained
powerful channels
across the five great
nations, including
special routes
through allied lands.
There's only so
much intelligence
we can gather on our own.
--[sigh] We've been
retired for ages now.
We left behind our attachments
to this world long ago.
Although I guess it
would be nice to see
my grandson's face
one more time.
-This code work out
in your favor then?
-Hmm?
-It just so happens
your grandson
is a member of the Akatsuke.
Lady Chiyo.
[music playing]
MALE SPEAKER: Cherry
blossom season is here.
MALE SPEAKER: And with
it, great opportunity.
MALE SPEAKER: It's
that time of year.
MALE SPEAKER: A
time for winners.
MALE SPEAKER: The leaf
village jumbo lottery.
MALE SPEAKER: First
prize, 20 million Ryo.
MALE SPEAKER: Take a
chance, and strike it rich.
MALE SPEAKER: If you
don't play, you don't win.
MALE SPEAKER: Now
get busy living.
MALE SPEAKER: Or get busy dying.
MALE SPEAKER: Because
paradise awaits.
MALE SPEAKER:
Tickets only 30 Ryo.
MALE SPEAKER: It's
your big chance.
MALE SPEAKER: Your
once in a lifetime.
MALE SPEAKER: The leaf
village jumbo lottery.
MALE SPEAKER: Tickets on sale.
MALE SPEAKER: Tomorrow
morning at 10:00.
MALE SPEAKER: The life of
the stars is in your grasp.
FEMALE SPEAKER: OK, sold.
NARUTO: Next time, Sealing
Jutsu, nine phantom dragons.
[music playing]
SAKURA: The summoning Jutsu
is a space-time Ninjitsu
that allows you to
call on creatures
you've made pacts
with, using a scroll.
Naruto, why don't
you give us a rundown
of all the summoning
creatures we've seen.
NARUTO: Let's see.
There's Chief Toad, right?
Tsunade slug Katsuyu
and Orochimaru's Manda.
Oh yeah, and Pakkun too.
SAKURA: Don't forget Temari's
Kamatari and the Third Hokage's
Enma.
And in a slightly
different vein,
there's Tayuya's rage ogres
and Ukon and Sakon's Raashomon.
NARUTO: Oh, hey.
Come to think of it, Gai-sensei
had that ninja tortoise,
remember?
Although we only saw
him the one time.
SAKURA: The thing
I've always wondered
is where these creatures
are the rest of the time.
NARUTO: Well, that's no biggie.
Why don't we just
ask one of them?
SAKURA: Wait, you're not gonna--
NARUTO: No time
like the present.
Come on out, Chief Toad!
-Huh?
-Whoa!