-Will you spit it out?
What do you mean
destroying the village?
Come on!
That's old news!
-I mean the present village.
-Present village?
Wait!
That means, m'lady.
-Yes, I'm afraid so.
-No way.
Sorry, this whole conspiracy
thing just doesn't add up.
-OK, Sai has some
boss and he really
used to hare the
Third Hokage, but what
does that have to
do with destroying
the whole village
or Grandma Tsunade?
-Did you forget, Naruto?
Lady Tsunade was the
Third's favorite pupil.
-And it's not just Lady Tsunade.
She hand picked the entire
current Leaf hierarchy.
They embody the Third
Hokage's philosophy.
And you can bet Danzo is
none too pleased about that.
But even so, the vast majority
of people in the village
support the current
regime, so it'd
be quite difficult
to change things.
-The only way to shake
the current regime
would be to create
some sort of earth
shattering crisis
in the village.
Like when Orochimaru tried
to destroy the Hidden Leaf
village.
-Destroy the Leaf village?
-Danzo could be
conspiring with Orochimaru
to mount a fresh
attack on the Leaf.
And if they're
successful this time,
Lady Tsunade would certainly
be ousted as Hokage.
-You're saying that they wanna
wipe out the whole village just
for that?
SAKURA: It's not
the only reason.
After the current
regime falls, he'd
rebuild the village
as he envisions
and take center stage
as the new Hokage.
-The reason Danzo is
probably making his move
now is because three years have
passed since the last attack,
and Danzo thinks that's
enough time for Orochimaru
to have regained his strength.
YAMATO: Yes, that
could be part of it.
But Danzo also knows that
Orochimaru's position
is more precarious than before.
After all, he failed
the last time.
He's betting Orochimaru will
be willing to collaborate
with him.
Perhaps--
-When he attacks,
he'll get support
from inside the village.
-Exactly.
-Wait a minute.
You mean that Sai's
top secret mission--
-Maybe.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Wait a minute.
You mean that Sai's
top secret mission--
SAKURA: May be to join
Orochimaru's ranks
and become the conduit
between him and Danzo.
Danzo knew the odds were good
that we'd eventually encounter
Orochimaru, and that's why
he put Sai on our team.
-No way.
-Depending on what
might happen, I'm
afraid that we may have
to do something about Sai.
-You don't mean--
-Lord Orochimaru.
-I know.
It seems we're being followed.
-He might merely be pursuing us.
Or it might be a trap.
How do we proceed?
-Either way you look
at it, I do believe
this situation
calls for a corpse.
Am I right, Kabuto?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Eliminate?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sai.
SAKURA: But we can't.
Just like that?
-My clone is still
following them,
but we have no idea
what might happen.
We have to get on
their trail right away.
-But--
-All right.
Now you're talking.
Let's get going.
What?
-Naruto!
Naruto.
Are you OK?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He still hasn't
recovered from all that damage.
-Captain Yamato.
-Sakura, there's no time.
-Captain, I know we need
to catch up to them as soon
as possible, but he's-- It's
just, in Naruto's condition,
he shouldn't--
YAMATO: Then we'll have
to leave him behind.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Leave him?
How can he say that?
-He's a liability now.
Although he probably has
enough strength to make
it back to the village.
-Kakashi-sensei would
never talk like that.
-Sakura.
It's OK.
Let's go.
I'll be all right, Sakura.
I can keep up with you.
-Naruto!
-Sakura.
I think I know what
you're trying to say.
I've worked alongside
Kakashi many times
before in the ANBU
Black Ops, so I
know the kind of person he is.
And I know that I'm filling
in for him on this team,
but Kakashi and I
are quite different.
I'm sorry, but I can't
watch over you like him.
I can't laugh and say I'll
never let you get hurt.
-I will not allow
my comrades to die.
Trust me.
-You're no longer
ninja in training
who need to be
shielded from danger.
You're shinobi that must
surpassed Kakashi and bear
the Leaf on your shoulders.
We can't afford compassion.
If we stop now, we fail.
If we don't chase
after them now,
we'll never catch Orochimaru.
With Orochimaru, there's
no second chance.
-Sakura.
-OK.
-We can't waste any more time.
Naruto.
You strong enough?
-Always am.
All right.
Let's do it.
-Naruto.
-It's OK.
If I go back to the village,
then everything we've done
would've been for nothing.
-Naruto.
-Well, all right then.
But if you cause any delay,
we'll have to leave you behind.
You understand that,
don't you, Naruto?
-You bet!
-Then let's move.
-Is that--
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
Well, Orochimaru.
I have to hand it to you.
-Naruto!
-Sakura!
Sakura.
Hey, Sakura.
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
What's that wound from?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Chakra
from the Nine Tailed
fox must have entered
her through that wound
like a poison.
This isn't easy to heal.
Not even for a
skilled medical ninja.
Which only makes Naruto's
apparent immunity
to that chakra even
more astonishing.
-Oh, this was-- Um.
These are injuries
from Orochimaru.
It's OK though.
It doesn't really hurt.
I'll be fine in a sec.
-Well, all right?
Just don't push
yourself too hard, OK?
-Yeah.
-Let's take a little break.
Sakura is our team's
only medical ninja.
If she's not well, it could
jeopardize the whole mission.
-I said I'm fine.
If we don't hurry,
they might get away.
Captain.
What about what you said before?
-I'm sorry, but I can't
watch over you like him.
I can't laugh and say I'll
never let you get hurt.
You're no longer
ninja in training
who need to be
shielded from danger.
You're shinobi that must
surpass Kakashi and bear
the Leaf on your shoulders.
We can't afford compassion.
You're right.
I did say that, Sakura.
But we can't afford
to be too hasty.
After all, haste makes waste.
I mean, there's a big difference
between hurrying and just
being reckless.
NARUTO: Yeah, I agree.
Captain Yamato's right.
You're just too important.
You're the only medical
ninja on the team.
Not to mention your strength.
You're a monster.
You're a key part of
this whole mission.
-Can't you flatter me
without calling me a monster?
NARUTO: What?
I was just trying to
give you a compliment!
SAKURA: I don't wanna hear it!
NARUTO: You don't
like a compliment?
Sorry.
I was just-- OK, OK.
I stop.
I apologize!
YAMATO: Naruto.
-Mhmm?
-Since Sai's not with us,
you will be my partner
when we get into battle.
We should coordinate
our attack strategies
while we have the time.
Shall we?
-Yeah that's a good idea.
-They're not following
us any longer.
Our plan must've worked then.
-I think you're right.
-Ah, well.
At any rate, you did a
fine job as usual, Kabuto.
-I owe it all to
you, Lord Orochimaru.
With your constant guidance,
I've created countless corpses.
-We might have gone a tad
overboard, don't you think?
-Perhaps, but it's better
to be safe than sorry.
Oh yeah.
I had an idea Lord Orochimaru.
You might like it.
-Hm?
-What do you think about
having this one help
with our experiments?
Apart from serving as our
go between with Danzo,
he'll have lots of free time.
-Do as you see fit.
-So, they left a fake corpse.
Probably a jutsu from Kabuto.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sure
enough, this injury's
almost impossible to heal.
The most I can do
is ease the pain.
-This should be far enough.
-We're gonna work here?
-Yes.
But before we do--
[static]
Hold on just a moment.
My wood clone is making
radio contact with me.
-Yes, that's right.
There's subtle and unnatural
stitching along the scalp.
It's barely even noticeable.
Otherwise, it's a
near perfect match.
If we hadn't
anticipated this, we
would've been completely fooled.
They found out I was
tailing them so quickly.
I was confident,
but I guess we'll
have to be even more discreet.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): We're
dealing with Orochimaru.
There's no such thing
as too discreet.
NARUTO: Captain Yamato.
-Ah, yes.
That's all taken care of.
All right.
So what are we gonna do first?
-Before we work,
there's something
I think you need to know.
-Hm?
-The person who injured Sakura.
It was you, Naruto.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Hey, Sakura.
Isn't the Sai's sketchbook?
SAKURA: That's right.
-What's inside it?
-Don't ask me.
-He didn't write any words.
It's just pictures.
-Ah, Great.
Then how's that
supposed to help us?
-It might contain a clue
that could connect us to Sai.
SAKURA: Come to
think of it, this
is Sai's most prized possession.
Didn't he say it belonged
to his big brother?
NARUTO: Don't you
think those faceless
drawings are a little creepy?
Next time, The Unfinished Page!
[theme music]
YAMATO: Leaf
Crossing Super Quiz!
Hello, and welcome
to another big show.
Let's kick it off and
meet today's challengers.
-Bring it on!
-Ha cha!
-Round one, Land of Waves.
Hands on your buzzers.
A certain shinobi with the
nickname Demon of the Hidden
Mist got in
Kakashi's way when he
was heading to the Land of
Waves to escort Mr. Tazuna.
-Zabuza!.
YAMATO: Not finished yet.
One Shinobi was
picked up by Zabuza
and found his life
purpose fighting
as Zabuza's faithful servant.
He had kekkei genkai,
uses ice crystal mirrors,
has a sort of girlish face.
-Haku!
What?
YAMATO: Not finished yet.
The question is, who
were Gato's bodyguards?
The ones who disrupted
Tazuna's bridge construction?
-Do they even exist?
-I don't remember them at all.
YAMATO: Uh oh, time's up!
The correct answer
was Waraji and Zori.
-Nobody can know that!