-So that's his real body?
-I've waited 20 years.
I want to see my
grandson's face.
-What took you so long?
-I got back here
as fast as I could.
And besides, you're the one
who didn't send a replacement
border guard soon enough.
It was your plan, and it
completely fell apart.
-Really?
I carried out your
selfish request,
even though I had
just been poisoned.
You don't seem very grateful.
If you ask me.
Well then, shall we go?
-Yeah.
-Yes, sir.
-It can still move?
-Well played.
I should've expected no
less from my own granny.
No wonder even a kid like
that could dodge my attacks
so easily.
You can foresee my
attacks, old woman.
Then you control the
girl with chakra threads
using your Puppet Master Jutsu.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He knows.
-By the way, how clever of
you to attach chakra threads
to Hiruko's tail too.
Silly me.
I only noticed when
the tail's motion
was brought to an abrupt halt.
You did it when you threw
those kunai, didn't you?
The thread tied to the
knife stuck to his tail
once they were deflected.
-Good.
Even though I used the
tiniest bit of chakra
to keep the strings
undetectable,
you still figured it out.
-But of course.
Remember who taught me
how to play with puppets,
who drilled the talent into me.
It was you.
-Indeed.
But, unfortunately,
play time is over.
-You don't know
how right you are.
[gasp]
-So, do you still think
this'll be easy, Granny Chiyo?
-Lady Chiyo, is that person
there the real Sasori?
-I don't understand.
Your face is exactly the same.
You haven't aged.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
It can't be him.
They told me Sasori left the
Hidden Sand 20 years ago.
He couldn't be that young.
[theme music]
-Ah, damn it all to hell.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
There's noise
coming from inside the cavern.
No doubt about a battle's
already underway.
I need to know what's
going on in there, but--
NARUTO: I've had it.
Hand over Gaara right now!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): It's
only a matter of time
until my man Sasori takes
care of their friends inside.
But if he rushes out here, the
whole point of using this guy
to draw out that
nine-tailed jinchuriki
you will be for nothing.
NARUTO: You bastard!
You're not getting away!
Hold it right there!
-Naruto, no!
Stop!
-Just stay and help Sakura.
I can take this
guy, Kakashi-sensei.
-Ah, damn it.
Guy, come in.
How are things on your end?
GUY: Haa!
Hate to say it,
Kakashi, but I think
this is gonna take a while.
-Rotation!
If you're trying
to delay someone,
I can't think of a
better way than this.
-This is tough
when your enemy has
the same exact skills as you.
-I believe it will not
be very easy to bring
this fight to an end.
Your moves are good, imposter.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
At this point,
there's no way I
can help the others.
Sakura, Lady Chiyo, you'll have
to hold your own a bit longer.
-There's no chance I'm
letting you get away!
-Still chasing me.
Hm.
You'd better catch
up with me soon!
But when you do reach me,
I'll take care of you.
-Everyone stop.
-Wh-- Why'd you
stop us, Kankuro?
-We should all rest for a while.
-Do what?
What are you talking
about, Kankuro?
We don't have time to just
sit here and take a load off.
-Now don't be so impatient.
It's not like you to
lose your cool, sis.
[panting]
-I'm sorry that we
can't keep up, Temari.
-A few more minutes.
Then we'll be able to
start running again.
-Please.
Let us catch our breath.
-No discipline.
You people call
yourselves shinobi?
-You're asking the impossible.
Look at 'em, will you?
They took turns on border
guard duty 24 hours a day,
then the second they
get back to the village,
they're called to run out
here as fast as they can.
No matter how disciplined
these ninja might be,
you can't force them to
do more than they're able.
-No.
We can keep going!
We can't give in to
our own weaknesses
when Lord Gaara's in trouble!
-We must do everything
in our power
for the sake of the Kazekage!
-That's right.
To protect our dear Kazekage.
-Lady Temari, we're
ready whenever you are.
-All right then.
That's the passion I want.
-Now, now.
Let's not get too fired up.
-Lo-- Lord Ebizo,
what do you mean?
-Remember.
a good ninja never
loses his composure
under any circumstances.
When Kankuro forgot that,
and recklessly chased
after an enemy, he nearly got
himself killed, didn't he?
Look at yourselves,
all worked up.
You don't even realize
where we are, do you?
-What are you talking about?
-Well, for example, over there.
-Look at that.
-It appears to be the
aftermath of a battle
between the Akatsuki
and Leaf ninja.
-But that means--
-Indeed.
It is safe to assume
we have already
crossed into the territory
controlled by the Akatsuki.
There's no telling what
kind of dangerous traps
are out there waiting for us.
All of us must make our
way through this area
with extreme caution.
If the five of you were to
just go rushing in, especially
in your worn out
condition, you would
be annihilated in
no time at all.
[gasping]
-It'll be fine.
In fact, while
you get some rest,
I could tell you a story
about the old days.
It was a long, long time ago.
I'm sure you young people must
have heard something of it
before, what happened
with the Third Kazekage.
-Wait a minute.
The Third Kazekage?
-Yes, dear.
The one before our
previous leader.
The Third Kazekage was said
to be the most powerful
of any Kazekage, but then,
in the blink of an eye,
his mysterious disappearance
changed everything.
The village was
overwhelmed with distress
trying to find
their lost leader.
Looking back on it, you
could see how easily
people could let panic
cloud their judgment.
The Village Guard
became distracted,
allowing the enemy to invade.
Pandemonium ensued.
If they had taken
a collective breath
and dealt with things calmly,
the subsequent bloodbath
could have been avoided.
Now, I of all
people am painfully
aware of how eager
you must feel.
Even so, you must not
allow emotion to blind you,
else you'll repeat
the mistakes that
were made in the time
of the Third Kazekage.
-But, Lord Ebizo, how
does the story end?
Did they ever find out what
happened to the Third Kazekage?
-For years, the ANBU
Black Ops continued
to investigate in
secret, but no body
was ever discovered,
nor any sign
that the Kazekage
had been kidnapped.
-What's the matter,
Granny Chiyo?
Are you so filled with
emotion that you can't speak?
I'm not surprised.
It's our first
union in 20 years.
-Sasori, you--
SASORI: While I have you, let
me show you something special.
I guarantee it will move you.
This piece was particularly
difficult to acquire.
-Three?
What?
-But on the other hand, that's
what makes me so fond of him.
-No.
That can't be.
Impossible.
-What is?
What's impossible?
-It's him.
It's the Third Kazekage.
OK
-The Third Kazekage?
[chuckling]
-What do you think?
Doesn't he just take
you back, Granny Chiyo?
-The Third Kazekage?
Lady Chiyo, what does this mean?
-So this must be
what happened to him.
-Are you saying?
-It's been over ten years since
the Third Kazekage suddenly
disappeared from the
village without a trace.
We scoured the countryside
but could never find him.
The strongest of our
Kazekage simply vanished.
Sasori, it was you?
-Yeah.
And what if it was?
I'm not afraid of a
retired old woman.
You've got one foot in the
grave and you want revenge.
You can't even touch me.
-Retired?
One foot in the grave?
Maybe.
But if I hadn't hauled this
old body here to face you,
I would have died with
far too many regrets.
My own grandson.
It's bad enough you got yourself
mixed up with evil people,
but to think you could
betray your own village
and meddle with the
Kazekage for the third time!
-Third time?
-Orochimaru may have
been the one who
killed Gaara's father,
the Fourth Kazekage,
but Sasori was complicit
from the beginning.
And now he's taken Gaara
and the Third Kazekage too.
-Wait a minute.
I wasn't involved with the
death of the Fourth Kazekage.
That was all the doing
of one of my agents.
-If that's the
case, it's the same
as if you did it
with your own hands!
Do you claim you
weren't involved at all?
-It's true Orochimaru and the
Akatsuki have some history.
We've done some work together.
-So you were.
If you worked with
Orochimaru, then
you know all him and the
things that he's done.
Which means you have all
the answers I'm looking for.
-Hmph.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
-I'd love to stay and
chat, but unfortunately
I really must eliminate
the two of you,
and then go capture
that jinchuriki.
I do hate to keep
people waiting.
Sadly, there's no time to
answer your little quiz.
Well then, shall we begin?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Here he comes.
-Die!
-He's fast!
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Did
Hiruko's tail just fall apart?
-Slick move, old lady.
But how are you going
to block this one?
-No!
Sakura!
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Didn't work, did it?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
That was close.
SASORI (VOICEOVER): With the
old lady controlling the action
I'm not getting anywhere.
[groaning]
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Well, in that case--
-What?
Quick.
Hold your breath, Sakura!
-Poison.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Control her all you want.
It won't save her from the gas.
-Sakura!
[theme music]
LEE (VOICEOVER):
Guy-sensei, this is awful!
GUY (VOICEOVER):
What is it, Lee?
LEE (VOICEOVER): According
to new intelligence,
Kakashi-sensei is the star
of today's mini-feature!
GUY (VOICEOVER): What?
He gets a sweet deal
like that while we're
stuck down here fighting?
LEE (VOICEOVER): Well
then, we will just
have to take out these guys
quickly and join 'em there.
GUY (VOICEOVER):
Use the full power!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): We'll
never make it in time.
GUY (VOICEOVER):
And all our effort
will pay off, right, Tenten?
LEE (VOICEOVER): Wait.
Where is she?
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
She left all excited
saying she got picked as the MC.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Say what?
GUY (VOICEOVER):
Tenten, you traitor!
[theme music]
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): Notable
people in the Leaf Village.
Here there.
And now to introduce more
famous folks from the village.
This time we planned to
meet the Leaf's number one
tactician, Kakashi-sensei.
That was the idea, but he
still hasn't shown up yet.
It's pretty rude for a guy
to keep a lady waiting.
Huh?
-Sorry I'm late.
-Finally.
-I know.
Apologies.
But today I got--
-Anyway, now that our
guest has arrived,
time to find out all about him.
KAKASHI: Are you listening?
-Let's go.
He commands Naruto, Sasuke, and
Sakura as leader of Squad 7,
and he's one of the
village's top ninja.
Outside the Uchiha Clan,
he's one of the few
who possesses Sharingan,
and because he
can duplicate enemy
jutsu, he's sometimes
called Mr. Monkey-see Monkey-do.
-No.
I think you mean the Copy Ninja.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): As such,
Kakashi-sensei's only original
and most powerful jutsu is the
secret 1000 Years of Death.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): No.
That's totally wrong.
It's called Lightning Blade.
Tenten, is it just me or was
my intro the worst one ever?
-Oh.
Come on.
Don't be ridiculous.
[giggling]