Thank you,
Lady Hinata.
I appreciate all this.
Especially considering
that you're injured as
well.
No problem. Someone
took care of my wound,
so I'll take care of
yours!
The village is
so short-handed.
I've seen just how
busy Sakura is. This
is the least I can do.
Hey, Neji!
[chuckle]
Listen, Neji. We need
to ask you a big favor,
can we interview you?
Interview?
Yeah! You know how Naruto
played such a huge part
in the battle to save the
Village, right?
The younger kids at
the Academy asked us
to commemorate it
somehow.
We decided to do an article
in the Academy newspaper
about everything that
Naruto's accomplished.
So we're going around
interviewing everyone
we can.
Sorry, but you'll have
to ask someone else.
Aw... that's awfully
mean of you, Neji!
Yeah, I'll say! All the
younger students have
really been looking
forward to this!
Please help us!
Look! We're
beggin' you!
Please!
Oh, all right...
I'll tell you guys
a very special story.
[excited giggle]
"Neji Chronicles"
This takes place
about three years
ago.
On the day of the
Chunin Exam's final
round.
That year, the first Chunin
Exam was plagued with
problem after problem.
Feudal Lords and guests
from all over the various
nations...
...had gathered in the
Hidden Leaf Village to
witness the final rounds.
And in the midst of all that, we
received reports that a Rogue
Ninja named Orochimaru was after
Sasuke.
The Village tightened security,
preparing for every contingency
at every location.
But still, during the finals,
the Hidden Sand and the Hidden
Sound conspired to destroy the
Leaf.
It was something that no one
could have ever predicted.
The spectators from
the different nations
remained completely
immersed in the matches..
..unaware of what was
about to transpire.
Right around then, I was being
treated in the medical room
after having lost my match to
Naruto.
I thought I'd come
see how you're doing.
Are you okay?
Thanks, but
I'm fine.
Don't be too disappointed.
I mean, it was sheer luck
that Naruto won. I'm sure
you'll win the next-
Huh? Oh, I'm over that.
Huh?
Lord Hiashi came by
a little while ago.
I had always believed that those
of us from the side branch of
the Hyuga clan would never truly
be free..
..until the power of
the Byakugan was sealed..
..and our Curse
Marks disappeared.
But it seems Father
thought differently.
It's true that some
things can never be
changed
But still... Perhaps I've made
too many blind assumptions
about the way things are.
Neji.
Hey, let's go back
to the stadium!
Guy Sensei and Lee are there,
and Sasuke's match sure looks
like it'll be exciting.
Yeah, all right.
And then it
happened...
[gasp]
Orochimaru's attack
on the Hidden Leaf
had begun.
Whoa, what is
going on?!
You hear that?
No more cheering,
the stadium's gone
quiet.
Yeah. Something
feels different
now.
Byakugan!
The Hidden Sand betrayed us and
attacked alongside forces from
Orochimaru's Hidden Sound. Our
Village was thrown into chaos.
How could this happen?!
Fighting has broken out
in every corner of the
village.
Sand and Sound ninja
against the Leaf.
This is just like a-
I know.
It's like a war.
The two of us rushed
to the stadium to find
out exactly what was
going on.
But unbeknownst to us,
another incident was
already taking place.
Is that?!
Lord Elder!
[moan]
Kiba, hey are
you okay?
[groan]
What happened?
Later, Kiba told us that he'd
been watching over Lady Hinata,
after she'd collapsed due to
injuries from her match.
He was knocked unconscious
by enemy ninja disguised as
Anbu Black Ops.
[grunt]
Hey...
What the hell's
going on?!
Sounds like you're
alright now.
Lord Elder's wound
isn't fatal either.
[grunt]
Sir! What
happened here?!
We were attacked.
And our assailants
took Hinata!
[gasp]
They did what?!
Two ninja from the Hidden
Cloud who were here as
spectators assaulted us
and made off with her.
No doubt they saw an opportunity
to use the confusion to spirit
the Byakugan away from the
Village.
I tried to stop
them, but...
[grunt]
Neji, the Byakugan is
a top-secret jutsu that
your father protected
with his life.
We simply cannot
allow them to take
it! Go get them!
You must bring it
back, whatever it
takes!
[grunt]
I understand, sir.
Wait, Neji!
I'm coming, too!
No, this is
a matter for
the Hyuga.
But it's too
much for you to
handle alone.
Then count me in.
I mean, Hinata is
my friend.
And besides,
I know you don't
have a high
opinion of her.
I have my doubts that
you're actually going
to try very hard to
save her.
Kiba!
Fine, come with
me. Your nose
will be useful.
[sigh]
I guess a three-man
squad would make it
easier to track them
down.
You're wrong.  With Akamaru,
it's a four-man squad. We're
now a basic platoon.
[bark]
Let's go.
(Konohamaru)
I had no idea
that happened!
Didn't the Jonin
in the stadium
notice all of this
stuff going on?
I don't really know. But
even if they did, they
probably couldn't spare the
manpower to deal with it.
After all, the situation
was so precarious that
Genin like Naruto had to
be sent on A-rank missions.
I still can't
believe it! A war
suddenly breaking
out like that?
So much for the
alliance between
those nations!
We couldn't
pass up the
opportunity!
The Kekkei Genkai
who's secrets
may not leave
the Village.
The Hidden Leaf's
Byakugan is ours!
[sniffing]
There are two of
them, headed on
a straight line
through the forest.
They're going toward
the boarder we share
with the Land of Rice
Paddies...
Looks like they're
taking the shortest
route to the Hidden
Cloud Village.
We're familiar with all
the territory inside our
boarder, but not outside
the Land of Fire.
We gotta end
this before they
get too far!
[worried whine]
What's wrong?
Akamaru can determine
the enemy's strength
simply by sniffing
their chakra.
(Kiba)
These guys seem
like a real handful.
They must be higher
than Chunin level.
Our chances don't
look too good.
There are still
ways to win!
How about we
mount a surprise
attack, and--
[bark]
Huh?
Quick! Stop!
What's going
on!?
(Neji)
A trap?!
The enemy's
scent is all
over this place!
Yech...
What are they?!
So gross...
It seems that the
enemy has laid a trap
that's activated by
a persuer's chakra.
Incoming!
There's just no
end to those things!
And worse, by setting
off this trap, we may have
also alerted the enemy that
we're coming after them!
Damnit! We're
running out of
time here guys!
Then I guess
we only have
one choice...
Dragon Bomb!
Go, guys! I'll
take care of
these things.
But, Tenten!
Just go! I'll
keep them busy
for a while.
We gotta get
Hinata back, right?
Hurry!
Okay.
Well now...
...just how do
you guys wanna
do this?!
[wolf growls]
Come and get
me!!
(Moegi)
What!?
She faced them
alone!?
Yes, she did.
It might seem crazy,
but Tenten is a skilled
weapons specialist with
a wide range of attacks.
She had the best
chance of stopping
the enemy, and getting
out of there alive.
With time running
out for Hinata, we had
no choice but to have
faith in Tenten.
Damn those Cloud
Ninja! Laying a
trap like that
for us!
Although setting up
something like that
must have taken them
a good amount of time.
That's true. And
their scent back
there was still
strong and fresh.
That means they're
not too far ahead
of us.
Byakugan!
(Neji)
I found them.
Good! Okay, now
let's go ambush
them and get
Hinata back!
No, forget it.
That won't work
they're too
strong.
Alright, then
what's your idea!?
Look, don't try
to stop me. I'm
going in!
Looks like somebody
set off the trap we
left behind...
They comin'
after us?
Yeah, probably.
Let's move.
The boarder's just
a little ways ahead.
Right.
Palm Heel Strike!
[painful grunts]
I won't let you
get away with
stealing the
Byakugan!
Look, don't try
to resist us.
We're in too big
a hurry for this.
[gasp]
[coughing]
[grunt]
Byakugan from the
family's main branch
still works if the
wielder's dead, right?
[gasp]
Why you damned brat...
I say the only thing
we should bring back is
her head!
(Kiba)
Tunneling Fang!
[gasp]
Well, looks like
I made it in time!
Kiba!
Come on!
Let's go!
They found us!
Another brat!
I'll kill
them both!
[gulp]
What did you
do!? You couldn't
have excaped from
guys that strong!
Yes, you're right. Back
then we weren't powerful enough.
We were completely outclassed.
[exhausted gasp]
This is pointless,
kid. A Genin can't
stop us.
And we don't have
time to waste on
pathetic losers
like you!
What!?
Gentle Fist..!
Eight Trigrams
Sixty-Four Palms!
Two Palms!
[grunt]
Four Palms!
Eight Palms!
Sixteen Palms!
Thirty-Two Palms!
Sixty-Four Palms!
Now I get it.
You tricked us,
kid. Not bad.
(Mikage)
You're that Hyuga
kid who was in the
Chunin Exam...
What a fool!
Acting like he can
do this himself!
Heh! So you had us
chasing a decoy this
whole time, did you?
Look kid, just get lost.
We don't have use for an
eye from the side branch
of the Hyuga Clan.
I will not let
you past me!
Earth Style:
Mud Wave!
Do you really think
I'd let a Gentle Fist
user get anywhere
near me!?
[gasp]
Damnit!
[grunt]
An Earth Style
Shadow Clone?!
(Thinking)
He lured me
in...
It's all
over now!
Can't use Taijutsu
if you can't move
your arms and legs.
You're nothing more
than a caged bird!
[angry grunt]
After hating them so much
for so long, you still end
up as a sacrifice for the
main branch of the family.
(Mikage)
What a sad
destiny. I feel
sorry for you.
No, I didn't
come here because
I had to...
I came after
Hinata! Because
this is my choice!
Whatever. It all works
out the same. Since
you're here, you're
going to die here!
Mud Needle! Ha!
(Hiashi)
Rotation!
[gasp]
I'm sorry
I'm late.
Lord Hiashi!
Sir!
(Thinking)
Hiashi!? The
head of the
Hyuga!?
Eight Trigrams!
Air Palms!
[gasp]
[grunt]
Pathetic.
[gasp] Lord
Hiashi! Why
are you here!?
What about
Lady Hinata?!
My father gave me
all the details
about her capture.
She's fine. Ko's
on his way to
retrieve her as
we speak.
(Hiashi)
He also has a friend
of yours he picked
up along the way.
Oh! That's
good news!
But why did you leave
the Village? Why leave
that battlefield to
come out here?
Hinata's my
daughter. She's
precious to me.
And you are as well.
You're a priceless
reminder of my late
brother, Hizashi.
I can't believe
all of us made
it through that!
Neji, listen...
I'm sorry...
about the way
I acted before.
Eventually, the Cloud Ninja
who planned Lady Hinata's
abduction were identified
and captured.
It turned out that the
leaders of the Hidden Cloud
were involved, so we settled
everything internally.
And we avoided
an international
incident.
And that's the
whole story!
(All)
[sigh]
I had no idea
something like that
happened during the
attack on the Leaf.
Yeah! I didn't
know that, either!
Thanks, Neji!
That was a
really awesome
story!
I'm glad you liked
it. I had a feeling
it would be worth
telling you guys.
[giggle]
Uh! Hey! Hold
on a minute!
Is that really
all there is
to the story!?
We wanted one
about Naruto!
He has nothing
to do with it!
What are you
talking about?!
(Thinking)
He did for
me....
Um, Neji?
I'm sorry...
...this was
all my fault.
(Neji)
Please, look at
me, Lady Hinata.
There's really no
reason for you to
apologize to me.
(Neji)
You know,
it's funny...
I thought that I
had such a clear
understanding of
everything...
...I bore an
unwavering grudge
against the main
branch of the family.
And I never
questioned it...
...but I didn't
know the truth.
I blamed fate,
and held onto
my grudge.
But during our
battle, Naruto
explained.
He told me, Hinata,
that you were
suffering just as
much as I was.
He said that to gain
acceptance and respect, you
had been trying incredibly
hard to change.
I hadn't even
considered what
you were going
through.
He helped me to
understand just how
selfish and narrow-
minded I was being.
[gasp] Naruto
did that?
Naruto Uzumaki...
There's something
about him...
Yes!
Well he was involved
in the most important
part, so don't worry.
What part?!
Good luck with
the article! I
Look forward to
reading it.
[gasps]
Aww come on,
Neji! No fair!
You have to tell
us what the most
important part was!
It's all important!
Every bit. But without
Naruto, that story may
never have happened at all.
(Moegi)
But, we wanna hear
about something he
actually did!
(Neji)
Haha! Then maybe you should
have listened when I told
I told you ask someone else!
Ahhh!
Who the heck are
you, mister!? You
scared me!
(Kisuke)
Oh yeah? Well you're
the one who scared me
with that scream!
(Naruto)
Hey wait, what
are you doing
in my house!?
(Kisuke)
I don't know...
All of a sudden
I was just here!
(Naruto)
All of a sudden!?
What kind of lame
joke...?
(Naruto)
Uh... Mister? Could you
come take a look in the
mirror for a second?
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The man
who died twice
(Naruto)
G-g-ghost!!!