-It's gonna be tough
getting close to him now.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Such
intensity to these flames.
-90 seconds to go.
-Yes.
-Time to die, witch!
-Huh?
Let's finish this, boy!
-You wish.
I figured as much.
You attached a chakra thread
during our last go around.
But that trick won't
work a second time.
Too bad for you, huh?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
There's no time.
[theme music]
-What's wrong?
Don't wanna play?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
The antidote will only
last for one more minute.
-All right, then.
-It's water.
Sakura, get back!
-How long do you
plan to dance around?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
20 seconds left.
-Fine.
Be that way.
-No!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
15 seconds left.
-You were right, Sakura!
-Die.
-Lady Chiyo!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): The
antidote is working.
If I can just endure the pain--
SASORI (VOICEOVER): Useless.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Five seconds left.
Four seconds.
-You little--
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
-Get over here!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Three seconds.
Two.
-We were able to beat him just
before the antidote wore off.
We did it.
We really did it,
huh Lady Chiyo?
-Sakura.
Well done, child.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
I don't like this.
The kid's cooled off.
What are they planning?
Hm.
-Hey Sensei.
You ready, or what?
-Hold your horses.
Remember, I don't have
as much chakra as you.
It's going to take time.
[rattling]
-What are you so happy about?
CHIYO: That's right.
The fight has only begun.
I forbade even myself
use of this jutsu.
I never imagined I
would use it again.
But against you, I must.
Let's finish this here and now.
-It's said the ability
of a puppet master
is measured by the number
of puppets they can use.
I'd expect no less
from you, grandmother.
-There's so many of them.
10 at one time?
-Granny Chiyo's secret
multiple digits.
I've heard tell of their glory.
You once destroyed an
entire fortress with it.
Secret White Move
Chikamatsu's Ten Puppets.
The first Puppet Master
Monzaemon's ten masterpieces.
An exquisite collection.
However.
[rattling]
-I used these to destroy
an entire nation.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
He's grown so powerful.
-It's embarrassing, really.
How long does it
take to finish off
one little girl and an old bag?
I never thought I'd have to
resort to my best puppets.
Secret Red Move,
Performance of 100 Puppets.
It's showtime.
-Sakura.
That antidote of yours has
already worn off, dear.
Stay out of this.
Huh?
-It's not in me to give up.
Quitting's not an option.
-How silly of me.
You've inherited
Tsunade's strong will.
What's say we make this
the finale, though.
Are you ready, child?
-Yes.
-Hmph.
-Here they come.
Three Treasure Suction Crush!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
There's too many of them.
I have to find a way to take
them all out in one shot.
-OK.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
There's too many of them.
-You all right, Sakura?
-I'm OK.
-Good.
Stay sharp.
-Right.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
We've definitely
thinned out Sasori's puppets.
But conversely,
it looks like he's
focusing more intensely
on the ones that we made.
Only one antidote left, and if
either of us takes any damage,
we're going to be
in a lot of trouble.
-Lady Chiyo!
-Oh no!
-Are you all right
over there, Lady Chiyo?
-Don't you worry
about me, Sakura.
Right now, you just
focus on Sasori.
I'll keep the other
puppets in check.
-Right.
-Sakura.
Here, use this!
-Take this!
We did it.
-He can't move.
That sealing traps
every ounce of chakra
stored in a person's body.
Using his chakra threads
is impossible now.
It's over, Sasori.
-Lady Chiyo.
Quick.
Here's the antidote.
[thud]
[theme music]
GAARA: From the very
beginning, she was so bright.
NARUTO: Not to mention
how pretty she was.
LEE: (CRYING) She
was so beautiful.
She was my youth!
SAKURA: She had a lot
of nice qualities.
GAARA: True.
NARUTO: To think
she'd go so soon.
GUY: Let it out, Lee.
LEE: (BAWLING) Guy-sensei!
GAARA: Please, watch over us.
NARUTO: I'll never
forget you, Sakura.
Never.
SAKURA: Cut it out, you guys.
I'm still here!
NARUTO: Next time.
Impossible Dream.
[theme music]
SAKURA: Tales of the Kunoichi.
-Today's mission was
researching kunoichi.
We were each assigned
one woman to report on.
-Right.
SAKURA: I'll start us off.
With Team Guy's lone
female member, Tenten,
a master of just about
every ninja tool there is.
KAKASHI: A breath of fresh
air in that pack, believe me.
I devoted my time to
Kurenai, expert in genjutsu.
SAKURA: Huh.
I've never seen Kurenai-sensei
wearing a Hidden Leaf
vest before.
NARUTO: And I've saved
the best for last.
SAKURA: I'm not sure
your Sexy Jutsu counts.
NARUTO: Haha.
Get a load of all
that va-va-vavoom.
And now, to unveil my
new pervy ninjutsu!
-Ooh!
-Will you knock it off?
-Wow.
That might be a new record.
-Hmph.