[breathing]
[sneezing]
What is that..? A bug..?
What are ya doing here?
Long way from home, you
must be the adventurous
type. You headed for the
Land of Lightning, too?
Oh hey, speaking of bugs,
why does this remind me
of someone?
Lemme see... who
was it?
Hey. Is it true what they
say about a war starting?
Yeah. My Dad was telling
me all about it. Says
we're gonna pulverize
the Akatsuki.
It's true. We face a
conflict that will decide
the future of the shinobi
world.
Will you be going into
battle too, Shino Sensei?
Yes.
Oh man, aren't you
scared, Sensei?
You dummy. Our sensei
isn't scared of
anything!
No. You're wrong.
[gasping]
For real? You're
really scared?
No way...
But I'm confident that I
will come back alive.
How come?
It's because I have
friends. People I trust.
If I can block both
hands...
So you two were just the
decoy's for his attack,
huh? Sorry.
Fire Style! Fireball
Jutsu!
Ninja who specialize in
long distance jutsu tend
to be deficient in close
combat..!
[grunting]
So weak... But what do
you expect from an Insect
User?
[grunting]
Shino!
Are you all right,
Shino?!
[whining]
So weak... But what do
you expect from an Insect
User?
I see. So he got away,
did he?
We really screwed up.
Don't beat yourself up
about it.
Anyway. We received more
intel after your
encounter with him.
Turns out, he's a rogue
Jonin from the Hidden
Waterfall who's stooped
to banditry.
It's not your fault you
weren't a match for
him-what else could
you have done?
I'll make the report to
Lady Hokage.
We're terribly sorry.
And don't blame Shino
either, he did what he
could.
We would never do that.
But try telling that to
him-he's shut himself
up inside his of house.
That guy has so much
pride it's ridiculous.
Well, that's a problem...
Listen. I want you two to
help Shino get back on
his feet.
[gasping]
How are we supposed to do
that? He's never listened
to us before,
don't know how we'd
get him to start now.
Maybe so. But this is an
order.
I want you to head
over to the hot springs
on the south side of the
village.
Help Shino
unwind a little.
Uhh---
What do you want?
Man, you're on to us.
Shino? How is your wound?
Nothing to worry about.
What is it?
Ah come on, what's wrong
with us just coming to
visit? I mean, aren't we
all on Squad 8?
Chill, will ya? There's
no shame in getting your
butt handed to you now
and then.
And anyway, look, that
guy was a Jonin. Of
course he came out on
top, we're not even
Chunin.
It was practically a
forgone conclusion.
Buuut, then again, I know
you've always rated
your own skills pretty
highly and all, so maybe
it came as a bit of a
shock to you.
Kiba..!
There isn't some other
reason you've been
moping around, is there?
Don't tell me you
still let it get to you
that Naruto's always
forgetting your name?
Ah whatever, just shrug
it off. Not everyone can
be as keenly attuned to
people's feelings as we are.
No wait, I've got it!
You're bummed out
'cause you're the
only one who didn't get
tapped for the mission
to bring back Sasuke,
am I right?
[grunting]
Sure, it stunk, but hey,
you were already assigned
to another mission-I mean what
are they supposed to do, Shino?
Will you get lost!
'Fraid I can't do that.
But I was thinkin'. Maybe
we could head over to the
hotsprings south of the village.
Why?
Oh, it will be great,
Shino, just think how
much faster your wound
will heal!
I'm not going.
Yeah, I kind of figured
you were gonna say that.
Unfortunately, you're
coming whether you want
to or not. It's
Kurenai's orders,
old buddy.
Unbelievable. He's so
freakin' hard to be
around. Hasn't spoken
a single word to us since
we set out.
You can be just as
difficult as he can,
Kiba.
Well! We made it!
Time for some rest and
relaxation!
Yep!
Alright! Let's go have
a little soak, Akamaru!
Arf!
Yahoooo!
[yipping]
Oh, hey. You decide to
come in, too?
Is that a problem?
Uh, no!
Oh, wait a second, when
he's naked, he's not
gonna be covered in bugs,
is he?! Gross!
[gagging]
Aren't you coming in?
Well I guess seeing is
believing.
Of course I am!
Seems normal enough.
Uhh-- been in
here too long.
[exhaling]
[sighing]
[screaming]
What the hell?!
Huh!
Hey, Shino! Do you mind
if we train with you?
What're ya doing,
anyway?
Nothing.
Oh come on, Shino, why
are you giving us the run
around?
There's no
reason to hide it,
you're practicing
Taijutsu, right?
Hey, what if the three of
us trained together! I
mean, it is part of the
reason we came out here,
isn't it?
What's your angle here?
We're all gonna train out
here and make sure you
get stronger.
Look the truth is, we all
know that losing to that
guy bruised your pride.
Maybe this'll get you
back on your feet.
And hey, if we can get
some training in, and get
you feeling closer to
normal, we'll be
killing two birds
with one stone.
You're concerned you'll
be forced into close
combat while manipulating
your insects, right? So
you want to hone your
taijutsu skills. We
understand.
You want to
be ready for hand-to-hand
situations, in case any
enemy zeros in on you.
That's correct.
So why don't you let us
help you then, Shino!
Taijutsu training is
always more effective
when you have a partner
to work off of.
I know that my Taijutsu
skills might not be the
best compared to some,
but all the same, I still
think it would be a help!
I think the first thing
we work on is speed. If
you can overwhelm your
opponent with a constant
barrage of strikes, then
you can prevent them from
ever weaving any hand
signs.
No objections here.
OK, let's begin.
[grunting]
Alright then, time to
pick up the pace!
Whoa, Hinata's not
messing around!
Ah come on, man, she's
wiping the floor with
you-that doesn't bother
you at all?!
Of course not..! It's
because it's not my
place to judge anyone!
Uch! He even takes the
fun out of razzing him.
Shino! I want you to
imagine that you're
fighting that bandit
shinobi again!
[gasping]
So weak. But what do
you expect from an
insect user?
You're starting to get
the hang of it!
Not bad!-But you won't
always be facing a single
opponent!
Take in your
surroundings!
Beast Mimicry Ninja Art!
All-Fours Jutsu!
Once you've developed
your speed and awareness,
we'll focus on
visualization.
What do you mean,
"visualization"?
Oh, um... well you know,
the ability to see
through one's opponent.
Like knowing his
weaknesses?
And preventing him
from obtaining an
advantage? Having a
counterstrategy and
always keeping it in mind
when you fight?
Yes! Exactly!
Oh, now I'm with ya.
Once you're in the
thick of things and the
fists start flying, you
tend to focus only on what's
right in front of ya and
stuff like that can start
to fade a bit.
That's not a problem for
me though. When things
get hectic I have a whole
other back up brain.
Isn't that right,
Akamaru?
[whimpering]
[screaming]
What was that?! Should I
peek? No! I can't! But
I'm worried about the
others next door!
Shino is really
focused. I can actually
see him improving minute
by minute..!
Such amazing progress...
I've never sparred with
Shino before. I never
would have guessed he'd
be this good in close
combat.
All the same,
I won't lose.
Alright. Time for the
final test, Akamaru.
[growling]
Fang Over Fang!
What's the big idea?
You dodged that pretty
well. That was the final
test-good work.
What?
My Fang Over Fang is the
fastest ranked ninjutsu
they've got on the
books at the moment. You
dodging it from your
blind spot is pretty damn
impressive, Shino. I'd
say your training's complete.
You did it, Shino, and
that means Team 8 is back
on track!
Oh, yeah.
No. I am not
interested in being part
of this team anymore.
[gasping]
Why the hell not?
Because I have no right
to be part of it.
Without a doubt, I've
grown stronger, but I have
no faith in my ability to
watch your backs.
But, Shino--
I'm sorry.
[growling]
Hey! You got a lot of
nerve saying that to us!
Hinata and I have been
doing everything in our power
to get you back on your
lousy feet! And this is
the thanks we get?!
Believe me, I'm
grateful.
Don't give me that!
Stop it, Kiba!
All these years together
and I never once thought
you were this pitiful!
Arf, arf!
Uh!
You guys, look, this is
Kurenai's Sensei's
messenger pigeon..!
Hm. Get a load of this.
Hey Shino! That bandit is
somewhere in the area!
I'm gonna go after him.
B-but you can't-It says
not to engage until
Kurenai Sensei gets here!
Yeah I know, alright?
But I'm not talking
about fighting him.
Tracking is Squad 8's
specialty, we can at
least find him.
Look, whatever, I'm
going, okay? And this time
around, I'm not letting
him get away!
Fine, then I'm coming
with you!
Alright. Guess this is
goodbye.
Arf.
Shino, I don't understand.
Why didn't you dodge the
punch Kiba threw a
minute ago?
We both know you're
able to, now.
That's because...
I still believe that you
can protect us, Shino. I
know Squad 8's gonna be
safe in your hands.
It's just up ahead.
Byakugan!
Found him!
Remember, we just wanna
track him.
Right..!
They're here.
[growling]
I smell it too. Looks
like he's onto us.
He knows we're here-I
think this might become
more than us just tailing
him!
Head's up!
Fire Style! Red Spider!
Damn it..! Only way to go
is up!
Kiba! Careful!
We're surrounded..!
You guys again, huh?
I'd have thought
you'd learned your
lesson last time.
Blue Joro Spider!
Where do you think
you're going?
Fire Style! Flame
Hurricane!
[screaming]
Well, that's that.
Huh?
What the? Those are..
insects..!
Shino!
Oh there's the third
one..! Blue Joro Spider!
I can't do a thing
in here!
I'll start with you
first!
Shino!
I already know your
weakness, kid! Haaaah!
So weak. But what do
you expect from an Insect
User..?
What? !
Heh.
Come on, then..!
Impossible..!
I won't lose to you.
I'm not the same person
you fought before.
If close quarters won't
work..!
I can't weave any
signs..!
Not yet! Not by a long
shot!
[grunting]
How dare you hurt my
friends!
[grunting]
How dare you insult my
insects!
[groaning]
Whoa! He's strong!
Take this! Iron Tackle!
[grunting]
Hiyah!
Gentle Fist!
[yelling]
You ready, Akamaru!?
Arf!
Then let's finish him!
[yelling]
Hm? Oh, hey!
Kurenai Sensei..!
I guess there's nothing
left for me to do here,
is there?
Heh! You kidding-of
course not!
But let's give credit
where it's due-It was
mostly Shino's doing..!
Oh uh... Well, yeah.
[playful yipping]
Looks like Squad 8 has
made a full recovery.
Sure does. Shino, I don't
know what you were worried
about. I'd put my life in
your hands anytime.
Yeah, so would I..!
Well, I suppose I've
gotten stronger.
You don't have to justify
anything to us, Shino.
I suppose you're right.
I figured as long as I
was all the way out here,
I had to take advantage
of the hot springs.
It feels wonderful!
Just look at you three,
taking care of that guy
on your own. You've all
gotten so strong.
But I do have to admit, I
was about to panic when
it was just you and Kiba.
Wait, Kurenai-Sensei,
does that mean- does than
mean that you were keeping
an eye on us the whole time?
What are you talking
about?
It's just... How did
you know that that rogue
shinobi was hiding out
near these hot springs?
A coincidence, that's
all..!
Mm.
Agghh gross! Will you cut
it out Shino?!?!
[barking]
You'll understand one
day as well... There is
no need to fear battle.
Because thankfully...
... our friends always
have our backs.
Right! We understand!
Who was it again? For the
life of me I can't remember.
[sneezing]
Back during our academy
days... all the girls
idolized the same
woman. She always
seemed so strong and
beautiful.
And I'm no different. I
decided I wanted to be
like Lady Tsunade, the
legendary kunoichi.
It's a dream I've
never stopped chasing.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Ah, My Hero
Lady Tsunade!
This is a story from when
I was a little girl.