NARUTO: A Sand shinobi?
KAKASHI: What does this mean?
-I wish I knew.
Poor fool.
He went missing after
Gaara was abducted
while the village was
still in disarray.
-Is it possible he was
a spy for the Akatsuki.
CHIYO: No.
He served on the
council for four years.
LEE: Was he using a
transformation jutsu?
-No, Lee.
This jutsu is on a
whole other level.
-The Fireball Jutsu.
It was created by
the Uchiha clan.
It's their specialty.
-Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu.
-That attack was the real thing.
-Looks like you're
done too, huh?
-Yes.
I was out of chakra.
-Well, we did only give the
sacrifices 30% of our chakra,
right?
This jutsu's handy for creating
exact duplicates of ourselves,
it's true.
But with that
little chakra, it's
no big surprise our
stand ins were taken out.
The jutsu they can
use are directly
proportionate to how
much you give them.
-But it was more than enough
to buy us a little time.
-The jutsu wore off, did it?
But we were able to delay them.
That should be enough.
Well done, Itachi, Kisame.
-Aren't you forgetting someone?
Need I remind you where
the bodies for your jutsu
came from?
They were both my subordinates.
-Hmph.
You should be the
one thanking me.
It's only because of
my impersonation jutsu
they could join the
ranks of the Akatsuki.
Short lived as it was.
It's almost finished.
[theme music]
TENTEN: This means
the real one's still
holed up somewhere, doesn't it?
-I think it's safe to
assume at this point
that his goal was to gather
information and stall us here
for a while.
-If that is the case, we
have not a moment to lose.
-All right, then.
Let's hurry.
-It's over this way.
-Just as I thought.
They were clearly trying
to stall for time.
KAKASHI: That's an
impressive jutsu they've got.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
I never realized
you were fighting
against people as
strong as this.
-For them to use a
jutsu like this stall
us can mean only one thing.
It's worse than I thought.
The extraction of the tailed
beast has already begun.
-Huh?
-We're out of time.
We need to get to
Gaara right away.
-So, wait.
Hold on.
What do you mean by extraction?
-They're after the Shukaku.
If they can draw
out the One Tail,
they can create
a new Junchuriki.
-A new Jinchuriki?
-I told you, didn't I?
How the tailed beasts possess
power beyond all reckoning,
and how every land has tried to
use them as military weapons?
The Junchuriki is the
name given to those
who control that power.
-But earlier you said--
-The beasts are huge
concentrations of chakra,
and during the Great
War, every nation
competed for control and
them for military purposes.
They fought
relentlessly over them,
but the tailed beasts' powers
were beyond human imagining.
No one could control them.
Not for lack of trying.
There were, of course,
those who tried
to harness that great power
for their own purposes,
attempting to control the
beasts by sealing them
away inside of people.
By doing so, they hoped to
suppress the tail beasts'
great power, and then bend
that might to their will.
And the ones with
the tailed beasts
sealed inside of them, such
as our own village's Gaara,
are known as Junchuriki.
Junchuriki wield
unimaginable power,
thanks to their resonance
with the beasts they carry.
And if you count
Gaara, then all told,
there have been three Junchuriki
in the history of the Sand
village thus far.
It's up to you.
-There were several wars
fought using the Jinchuriki,
weren't there?
-That's correct.
-Then the people who become
Jinchuriki-- All right, then.
How are the tailed
beasts extracted?
-A couple of things are needed.
A sealing jutsu strong
enough to counterbalance
the tailed beast's
power, and a lot of time.
But were things to reach that
point, then the Jinchuriki--
-You don't mean--
-That's right, dear.
Once the tailed beast
is extracted, they die.
The others I mentioned,
the Jinchuriki who
came before Gaara, we extracted
the Shukaku from them as well,
and both died as a result.
-You always were quick to cry.
Huh, Sakura?
Hey don't worry.
I promise I'm gonna save Gaara.
-Don't you get it?
Naruto, I'm concerned.
-We better hurry.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Huh?
It's from Sis.
-You shouldn't be moving yet.
You're still recovering.
-I'm fine, OK?
Well enough to be
walking around at least.
Forget about me, though.
We've finally gotten
word from Lady Chiyo.
I can't just sit here.
-I see then.
You've heard about
that already, have you?
The news isn't good.
We've learned of
something terrible.
-Yura was a spy?
Incredible.
Four years, he sat
on the council.
How can it be?
-Yes, I know.
But it finally makes sense now.
That's how they were able to
break through our defenses
so easily.
And who'd have ever suspected
the head of our security
was partnered with the enemy?
-I don't understand
how this even happened.
We checked out everyone
when Gaara became Kazekage.
-We don't know the truth yet.
It's possible this fellow
was under the control
of some form of jutsu.
-More importantly,
why are there are
no details about the Kazekage?
She says nothing of
when Gaara will return.
The leader of one of
the five great nations
has been kidnapped.
By a lone pair of
outlaws, no less!
And if that's not bad enough,
it seems one of these vermin
is Sasori of the Red Sand.
We cannot allow a disgrace
of this magnitude to get out.
-If it were known the
Kazekage is missing,
there's no telling
how emboldened
the neighboring
lands would become.
Our most pressing need is
to elect a new Kazekage
and bring much needed
stability to the village.
-Nonsense.
We don't know that Gaara
isn't coming back yet.
-There are those of the
opinion that the village might
be better off if he
never came back at all.
-What are you getting at?
-Gaara is an unstable
monster carrying the One Tail
inside of him.
We thought he would
be easier to govern
if we made him the Kazekage.
There's no telling when
he'll go out of control.
He's a danger to us all.
I know Gaara resonated with
the Shukaku in the beginning,
but face it.
He's a botched
experiment at best.
Even his own father knew that.
The Fourth Kazekage ordered
his assassination for a reason.
I know there's many in
the younger generation who
look on him favorably, almost
blinded by their admiration.
But let's not bother
with pretenses.
Most of the village
looks on him in fear.
No one really believes in him.
-I don't care if you
are a council member.
I am not gonna listen to this!
-Let go of him, Kankuro.
You stand before the
statues of the Kazekage.
This is a sacred place.
-Listen to me, Kankuro.
Your anger is certainly
understandable,
but there's an element
of truth to what he says.
We have to face the
facts here, and this
isn't an issue of
how trustworthy we
believe Gaara to be.
-We have faced a similar
situation before.
The Third Kazekage
was also kidnapped.
There was much speculation
on his whereabouts.
The instability led to war.
Countries were devastated.
If we had focused on stability
at home rather than our search,
we would not have
come to such disaster
-So how come that didn't happen?
-The Third was like no other.
He was far stronger than
either of his predecessors.
And quite astonishingly,
his body was never found.
No one could even believe
it, that somebody as powerful
as the Third could
be killed so easily.
Something like that
must never happen again!
-We have to consider the best
interests of the village!
-That's why the borders
are being secured.
-When the Third
Kazekage went missing,
this village fell
into utter chaos.
Our enemies leaped
on the opportunity
and ripped through our
offenses like it was nothing.
Those borders are
our top priority!
-But there was no reason
to send Temari out there!
-Kankuro.
-What are you saying?
We originally had you
slated for that mission
along with your sister, but
you had to get poisoned,
didn't you?
-By assigning you and Temari to
the additional border patrols
here at home, we prevent the
younger folk of the village
from getting caught up in
some delusional attempt
to save Gaara.
-We sent Temari to a weak point.
An area that's been infiltrated
several times in the past.
Naturally, we wanted
a Jonin rank or higher
for such a mission.
-Look, I get it.
It's just that-- just
that, this is Gaara.
He's-- He's my little brother.
-Zetsu, Get rid of those two
we used for the impersonation
jutsu.
Understod.
-Itachi, What of our enemy's
number and abilities?
-It's a four man squad
from the Leaf, comprised
of Kakashi Hatake, Sakura
Haruno, the Nine Tails
Jinchuriki, Naruto Uzumaki, and
Chiyo, an elder of the Sand.
-Granny Chiyo.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Looks
like he hasn't entirely
gotten a handle on
that giant Rasengan.
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Opening up the Gate of Joy
really took its toll on him.
-Are you feeling OK, Guy-sensei?
-Huh?
Are you kidding?
My battery never runs down, Lee.
-Guy-sensei!
-I don't know.
He doesn't look so hot to me.
-What do you expect?
He just used the Asa
Kujaku, didn't he?
We need to let him
rest for a while.
-There it is.
-Am I missing something?
What did they want us
to guard this place for?
-I don't know, but
orders are orders.
We'll keep watch in 24
hour shifts, starting now.
-Yes ma'am.
-Stop here.
-Why?
What is it, Kakashi-sensei?
What's wrong?
-We're taking a short break.
-That's a very wise decision.
-What do you mean?
Come on.
You were the one who was saying
we couldn't waste anymore time.
If we just lay around here doing
nothing, Gaara is gonna be--
-Naruto.
Our pace has slowed
since we faced off
against that bogus Itachi.
-He's absolutely right, Naruto.
-If we take the
time to rest up now,
we'll ultimately reach
our destination faster.
Keep in mind,
tomorrow we may end up
facing the guys who
kidnapped Gaara.
We'll need our full strength.
-Yeah, all right.
I understand.
-So, this one was Kisame's.
Definitely worth disposing of.
-Well, let's get to
it then, shall we?
-Right.
[theme music]
MAN: With the break over,
both teams have set out again.
Team Guy from Point
A and Team Kakashi
from Point B, both racing
for the finish line.
MAN: Kakashi and Guy are
often called eternal rivals.
This is riverting.
MAN: Guy has said
this day will be his.
Bold words.
Bold words indeed.
MAN: They're both neck and neck
as they close on the finish
line.
MAN: Well, folks, We'll just
have to wait with bated breath
to see who will go
the distance and bask
in the glory of the victory.
NARUTO: Next time,
The Death of Gaara.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Hello again, from
the Society for Leaf Tourism.
Today, I'll be showing
Temari and Kankuro
around our hot springs.
Right now, you're looking at
the source of the water that
gets used in all our bathhouses.
The water in here is
piping hot, so be careful.
I have a few bad memories
from training around here.
-Come on.
Let's just hit
the baths already.
-OK, wait up!
-Ah.
This hit the spot.
TEMARI: Kankuro.
-Yeah?
-Toss over the soap.
-What'd, you forget yours?
-Heh heh.
Duty calls, huh?
I'll just bring it over--
TEMARI: No peeping!
Aw.
There's nothing like a
good, hot spring, huh?
-You said it.
I wouldn't mind a
sand bath back home.
-A sand bath?
-Sand coffin.
-Uh, yeah not so much.