I guess that's the
limit for now.
(gasp)
That hole earlier...
That man...
...is a village
guard!
(gasps)
(chuckle)
'Till next time.
(coughing)
He escaped...
But, Mr. Yamato,
who was he?
I'll explain...
We're going to
need reinforcements.
Whoa!
(giddy laughter)
Got it!
Here you go!
On me!
Here's your change.
Wow mister!
Thank you!
You guys are from the
Tonika Village, aren't
ya?
Huh?
Were you a guard
or something?
Oh...
Yes. Well, I was,
but I got fired.
It looks like you got
hurt pretty bad, though.
So what happened to you?
(uncomfortable gasp)
Eh...Oh, nothing.
Just an accident.
Huh?
Sensei!
Hey!
Sorry, sir!
Look, I caught some!
Check 'em all out!
Wow!
Yep, all thanks
to my skills.
Of course, I was the
one who chose the bait.
(annoyed grunt)
Oh. What! You didn't
get a bite until you
changed bait!
It's just some fish. I
mean, I don't even like
the way fish tastes!
Come on, Faz. Don't
be so picky!
They're hard
to eat, too.
I don't like the
way they smell,
either.
(annoyed grunt)
I bet my Mom would
make something better.
Enough, Faz! Face
it! Your mom is gone!
(crying)
Hmm...You used to
hum that tune back
in class, too.
She says that she
can hear it sometimes.
She hears it?
Right now?
So do you know
him, Shiseru?
The survivor from
Tonika Village?
Yes, he and I were
childhood friends.
We even lived together
when we were kids.
I used to call him my
"Big Brother."  In
fact I still do.
I haven't seen him for
a while, though. He's
put on a lot of weight
on since we were kids.
Anyway, I'm just
relieved that he
still remains his
old self.
He managed to
protect five kids.
Wow, that's amazing.
What's the matter
with you?
I don't know. But,
man I feel so bloated!
(giggling)
(sigh)
Wait here a second.
I'll see if he's
around.
Hm?
(shocked gasp)
Quick! Go!
Huh?
What's up?
Big Brother?
Sensei?
Why are we running away?
Because of the symbol
those shinobi had on
their headbands!
It's the same as the
ones who attacked
our village!
(shocked gasps)
Hey, hold up!
Please, just
wait a second.
We don't mean
you any harm.
Ahhhhh!
Come on!
Leo!
It's dangerous!
But we have
to get away!
C'mon, Sensei!
Mina...
Let's go!
Ahhh!
(shocked gasp)
Sensei!
Hold tight!
Naruto!
On it!
Sorry, Mina.
(shocked gasp)
(strained grunt)
No way!
Big Brother?!
Boy, you guys
are heavy!
I'm sorry I
overreacted. I
was just worried
for the children.
I'm sorry, too!
's okay!
(chuckle)
I see you've
already met
Shiseru.
And my name's Dokku.
I was their teacher
when we all lived back
in Tonika Village.
This is Leo.
Nice to meet ya!
You've got a lot
of guts! You know
that, kid?
Got that right!
This is Lando and Faz.
Uh, hi.,
Yeah, uh, hello.
This is Sora.
Pleasure to
meet you.
Good to meet
you, too.
And this is Leo's
younger sister.
Her name's Mina.
Hm?
Hey, isn't that vest
kind of big for you,
Mina?
Oh, that's actually mine,
or it was. But she likes
it so much and refuses to
part with it, so...
I see. Well,
put 'er there!
(scared gasp)
Huh?
Uh... Sorry
about that.
What's wrong, Mina?
Treasure...
Why would Kabuto
want something
like that?
That really isn't
much like him.
What exactly do you
suppose happened there
in the first place?
Years ago...
I was a scholar focused
on conducting archeological
research. In particular
during my scholarly career,
I studied quite a bit about
"The Hole." This contains
the results of my research
on the ancient writings
and legends about that
place.
I believe that in many
cases, that lore describes
actual historical events.
The master of the Great
Lake once created the
"Ama no Hoko". but it's
power was stolen by
something evil. This
evil despised all of
existence. And by using
the power it had stolen,
it tried to destroy
the world.
The power spread out
across the entire world,
and was on the verge of
destroying it all...
When just by chance, one
of the dead picked up a
shard of the power.
It turned crimson and
was enveloped in flames.
It sought revenge against
the evil one.
After a brutal seven-hour
battle in purgatory, the
one sheathed in flames
finally emerged victorious.
To prevent another evil
from stealing the power,
the crimson one divided
it into seven sounds and
sealed it away, to be
unlocked only by the
"Saezuri."
That is merely a
brief summary.
Saezuri...
Do you believe that
could be what Kabuto
came to steal?
(affirmative groan)
If it actually
exists, that is...
Ama no Hoko. What
could it be?
This is merely speculation,
but I believe it's something
that surpasses human knowledge.
Well, without a doubt.
That "Hole" feels like
it's hiding a deep,
dark secret.
However, even if he
aspired to steal the
treasure, that is no
reason to kill all
the villagers! They
were innocent!
Such a barbarous act
is utterly unforgivable!
I agree completely.
Kabuto will be made to
answer for his crimes,
I assure you.
Thank you. I am
counting on you.
Naruto.
(startled gasp)
Everyone's going to
the outdoor bath.
Heh?! You mean we get
to bathe together?
As if!
(awed gasps)
Wow!
Yeah! No wonder he's
a legendary hero.
You know, if you guys
train really hard, maybe
you'll be able to do
that, too!
Really?!
(focused humming)
Come on! Again!
It must be strange. Even
in a rural place like this,
you're famous! I have to
admit, I thought you'd be
much more fierce and
scary. But I'm shocked
at how young and easy-
going you are!
(embarrassed chuckle)
It's really amazing, though!
Your body must be able to
store immense amounts of
power inside of it!
Hmph! Nah!
When I was young, just
about your age, in fact,
I didn't even have enough
power to save one girl.
Shiseru! What's that?
You mean the scar?
I fell from a cliff
a long, long time ago.
What?!
It was about fifty
meters high, I guess.
Luckily, I fell onto
a tree, and it broke
my fall!
How did it happen?
It was all just a stupid
accident because I was
so careless.
Please, Shiseru, stop!
Brother kept warning
me, too. But I just
wouldn't listen.
Ahhh!
No!
Dokku really did that?
Yeah, he grabbed
me just in time.
And held onto me for,
it must have been
almost an hour.
I hated exercise,
so my arms were
weak.
I was so frustrated
and angry at myself.
(struggling grunts)
Ahhhh!
If I... If Shiseru
had died back on
that day.
I...
That whole mess. All
of it was my fault
start to finish.
None of the blame
is his...
I hated myself for being
weak, so to prove I wasn't,
I became a guard. I did my
best, but...
Well, I wasn't suited
to it, at all!
(embarrassed laugh)
After that, we drifted
apart. Even when I did
go to see him, there was
a wall between us.
And then before I knew
it, we were just like
two strangers.
But that night,
if I'd only...
If only I could have...
I was so happy to
see him after all
this time, but...
If only I'd had
more power.
If I were stronger.
Big Brother...
I bet he's over there
beating himself up
right now.
I wish that I could've
saved more of them!
All the people that
were dear to him.
He lost so many of
them.
(crying)
I can't do it!
It's impossible!
Sure is fun, though1
(chuckling)
Come on, Naruto!
Tell us your secret!
Sure!
I noticed something
was wrong in the
village. It was just
around bedtime.
All of a sudden, the
whole village was
engulfed in flames.
One of the shinobi
attacked me, too.
(painful grunt)
He was so strong. I
was certain it was
all over.
Huh?
He just suddenly stopped
moving. As if he were
a puppet.
And his strings
had been cut.
Must have been the
Reanimation Jutsu. It's
a Forbidden Jutsu.
It uses a sacrificial
body as a vessel to
contain a dead person's
soul, which is forced
back into life. It was
believed only the Second
Hokage and Orochimaru
knew how to use it.
And now it seems, under
the Akatsuki's control,
it's failed
The jutsu still
hasn't been perfected.
Tell me, Dokku.
Do you know about
this "Saezuri?"
You mean from the
ancient writings?
We believe that's what
Kabuto is seeking.
Do you know anything at
about the Saezuri?
Anything that might
help us?
You must take
these and run!
You can do whatever
you want with them.
Throw them away,
I don't care.
Just don't breathe
a word of this to
anyone!
No, I don't
believe so.
I understand. A Security
Unit's on the way. We'll
be joining up with them
tomorrow. And with their
help, we'll begin
our pursuit.
However, since a
sentry was captured...
To be on the safe
side, I'm going to
assign a guard to you.
Thank you very much.
Also...
About all the children
that you rescued from
Tonika Village.
Huh?
This village is willing
to make arrangements with
an institution to take
them in. What would you
like to do?
They're all
fast asleep.
(affirmative grunt)
The kids...
...actually laughed
today...
It was the first
time...
...since that night.
Kabuto...
The jutsu formula you
came up with is so
violent!
You didn't actually have
to kill everyone in that
village, you know.
But it was fun?
I suppose for you.
Hmph.
I've improved the jutsu
technique by adjusting
it to my chakra. It'll
be easier to control now.
And also, I need to
test situations
involving intent and
memory.
You still don't
have enough?
Am I supposed to
go looking for it?
Well, you certainly
like putting me to
work, don't you?
But that's fine by me.
It's something to look
forward to.
Naruto, of course.
I wish I could
see them!
Mama! Papa!
I can't stand how
much I miss them!
(crying)
Why are you
so lonely?
Huh?
Look, you're
not alone.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Power-
Episode 3."
Get out! Get out!
Get out!