♪
[birds chirping]
Man... Elder Brother
sure has changed...
He's just so strict!  I feel
like he's going to alienate
everyone else...
Oh!  There you are! I've been
looking for you, Ashura!
Taizo!
Have you finished with
your training for today?
Well, y'know, since Elder
Brother'll take over Ninshu, it
doesn't matter if I slack off a
bit...
...Or, you know, a lot.
I see... [groan]
Well, it's less pressure on me!
So, what's up?
Oh, uh, well, to tell you
the truth, I need a favor.
Huh?
(Taizo)
Can you use Ninshu to knock down
a few of the trees around here?
Huh? For what purpose?
Oh! Well, you see, if you were
able to clear a path through
this stretch of woods, we'd have
a shortcut to get to the fields.
It'd be easier on my mom. And
it's no big deal for you, right?
Oh, is that all? Just
leave it to me, then!
[bark cracking]
[crash]
Will this do?
Yeah! Thanks for
your help, buddy.
It wasn't a problem at all!
This kind of thing is easy.
[painful breaths]
Taizo!
Elder Brother!  What's the
meaning of this?
[gasp]
This man has committed
a serious crime.
He fell some trees, and
sold them for profit.
Whatever is in this village
belongs to everyone who lives
here.  That's the law.
And you're just as guilty
as he is, Ashura.
Huh? I am, too?
Yes, because you
were too gullible.
You allowed this man to deceive
you, and in doing so, you became
an accomplice to his crime.
Was needing a path
cleared just a lie?
My mom was really sick, and she
needed to get some medicine
quickly.
I'm sorry about this, Ashura.
I shouldn't have gotten you
involved.
Why didn't you just tell me the
truth?  I could've used Ninshu.
Yeah, I know, but my
Mom hates Ninshu.
She says that this
world doesn't need it.
Unfortunately, whether you
believe in Ninshu or not, a law
is still a law.
Now, You didn't know about this.
So just this one time, you will
be forgiven, Ashura.
Listen, Indra, perhaps you are
taking all of this too far.
Everyone makes mistakes
every now and again.
Passing judgment on them demands
that you exercise prudence.
Yes, I know that, Father.
At the same time, when a crime's
committed, proper punishment
must be carried out...
...since only then will it act
to deter future crimes.
Brother...
[groan]
Ashura!
Shh Let me get you out.
But--!
It's okay. I'll take full
responsibility for this.
[gasp]
Elder Brother--!
Well, Ashura... just what do you
think you're doing with that
man?
Please just look the other way!
He didn't do what he did
with malicious intent.
But the law is still the law.
Haven't you already made an
example out of him?
That isn't something you
get to decide, Ashura.
Listen, I'll convince
my brother somehow.
You just go.
Get outta here.
Thanks, Ashura!
I owe you one.
Well then, if you're going to
break the law...
[grunt]
...then you can take the
punishment instead of him.
[grunt]
Stop this, Elder Brother!
Ashura, why do we have a
system of laws in place?
What's the purpose of the
power Ninshu provides us?
If you can't answer such
questions yourself, then you
should just listen to me and
obey me.
Go calm yourself.
Elder Brother...
[gasp]
Oh, Father!
Today's the day
when Shiro died...
Back then, if Shiro and Elder
Brother weren't there,  I
would've died.
I'm alive thanks to
their strength.
[sigh] You know, you really do
possess a truly gentle heart.
The complete opposite
of Indra...
Well, Elder Brother's a genius.
He can do anything by himself,
and he has the power to do so.
That's precisely why.
Huh?
What do you think of the eyes
Indra possesses now?
What do I think about them?
Well, I'm a bit
intimidated, I guess...
(Thinking)
As I thought, Indra's Visual
Prowess wouldn't work with
Ashura.
Something the matter, father?
There is something ominous about
Indra's eyes that even I cannot
fathom.
Looking into his eyes reminds
me... of my mother's eyes.
Maybe the answer is something
simple, like that Elder Brother
can see things that other
people just can't see...
And what exactly would that be?
Well, it could be
something really
advanced.
Like the ideal version of
Ninshu or the future.
I don't know for sure since I
don't possess the Sharingan.
But all those years ago, when
he and Shiro saved me, Elder
Brother was very kind.
And I still maintain faith that
Elder Brother's heart hasn't
changed since then.
I'll train harder and do my best
to become someone that Elder
Brother can rely on.
(Hagoromo)
At that moment, I felt that I
understood for the first time,
why heaven had blessed me with
two sons... But then...
(Villager)
Hey, did you hear?
Yeah! Seems Lord Hagoromo is
finally going to name his
successor.
Master Indra or
Master Ashura, huh?
I wonder which of them
it's going to be...
There's no doubt!  It just has
to be the elder one, Master
Indra, since he excels at
Ninshu!
And now, I'm going to
pick my successor.
I don't get it. What
is this, Father?
After the battle in which I
sealed away my mother, I
scattered the Ten Tails' parts,
which hold powers
unknown to man.
My followers and I repaired most
of the damage the battle caused.
But as it says in those scrolls,
there are still two regions that
remain damaged.
Indra, Ashura. You are to go to
those lands and fix whatever
problems may have occurred
there.
After I see your results, I'll
decide whom I'll entrust
Ninshu to.
[gasps]
Lord Hagoromo!
Why, Father? Why
are you doing this?
I simply don't have enough
skill to inherit Ninshu!
In fact, I don't have any
desire to inherit it!
I'd be perfectly happy
helping Elder Brother.
That's for me to decide.
What will the two of you do when
you are out in the world, alone?
When I see that, everything
will fall into place.
Why do you think Father
chose to do this?
Don't worry.  I'm sure Father
will come to understand quickly.
Yeah!
(Gamamaru)
The younger one seems to have
matured into a kind and gentle
soul.
But it's the older one who's
inherited the power of the
Sharingan, huh?
You know, it's possible... that
out of consideration for his
older brother, the younger one
might not return home.
I'll deal with that
if it happens.
What exactly is it that you're
looking to test with this?
It isn't a test of anything.
The eldest may excel, but
because of his power, he
has no faith in love.
The younger one doesn't have
the same kind of skill, but
he overflows with love.
I'm sure that Ninshu will come
to exert enormous influence in
this world.
And in order for Ninshu to take
the true and proper path...
...both power and love
will be necessary.
I want my sons to grow during
their journeys.
...and, I hope, learn to nurture
Ninshu together.
Hey! Enough already!
Just come out.
You knew I was here, huh?
Are you all right?
Yeah! As you can see...
Thanks for what you
did back then.
Don't mention it. So,
what is it? What's up?
After you helped me get free, I
hid out in a shack on a hill in
the backcountry.
Then Gasuka and Edashi.
I have big news! Ashura
is leaving on a journey!
And that journey will
determine who the successor
of Ninshu will be.
Is what they said true?
Because, I mean, after I heard
that, I couldn't even sit still.
Listen, take me with you, okay?
Boy, I don't know about that.
Your mom's sick, isn't she?
Nah, she's okay now.  It seems
that the medicine really worked
well.
She's back to normal!
Besides, I told her about you,
and she said I should go and
help out.
But I thought that your mom
hated Ninshu!  So why--?
Aw, c'mon, those are
two separate things.
A man's obligation comes
before hating Ninshu.
You do realize that I'm
not gonna be coming home for
a long time, don't you?
What? Seriously?
I'm certain that Elder Brother
will pass this test with
flying colors.
And if I don't return, then
Father will have no choice but
to pick him as his successor.
I see. That's so like you.
So then, where do
you intend to go?
Yeah, where should I go...?
Hey, didn't your dad say that
the people in the area where
you're supposed to go are having
a rough time or
something like that?
So wouldn't it be bad if
you didn't help them out?
Oh, yeah, I guess
that you're right...
I'd better go, and I'll figure
out the rest of it later.
All right!  Let's do it!
[strong wind blowing]
Still, this place is
awfully far away!
[loud sigh]
According to the map, we should
be getting close by now, but...
[groans]
We're in trouble! We're
all out of water!
Hey, don't worry.
What? How can I not
worry about it?
You can't do any Water
Jutsu, can you?
No, all I'm able to
do is Wind Jutsu.
Well, then...
The Divine Tree; it's near.
Huh?
I'm able to sense
it with my chakra.
You know, a while ago, Father
told me that the Divine Tree
gave Ninshu Chakra its power.
Hey--!
[panting breaths]
Well, looks like we made it.
[birds chirping]
It's quite a surprise to find a
place as fertile as this right
in the middle of such a barren
area!
How could a village like this be
struggling like Lord Hagoromo
said?
What's wrong?
We've been surrounded...
[gasp]
And just who are you!?
We're nobody you need to worry
about.  We're merely travelers.
We've had a lot of robbers
targeting our village lately.
We're not robbers. Please
believe us.  We don't want
trouble!
Never mind, just get 'em!
Quick, Taizo, climb a tree!
[frightened cries]
Please, stop this! I have
no desire to fight you!
Well then get out of this
village right away!
[gasp]
Hey, are you all right?!
Don't touch me!
It's okay! Hold still.
I'll heal you.
I just hope this
actually works...
Amazing...
What's this ruckus about?
Oh!  Lord Elder...
(Taizo)
What a feast!
And we can really
eat all of this?!
Please don't hesitate,
just eat up.
And I apologize for
the rudeness earlier.
Don't worry about it, really.
You know... it's quite a shock
to see such a fertile area.
This land's barren.
Well, this village
is very special.
Special?
Anyway, there's not much to do
here, so please have a relaxing
stay.
[yawn] You're up early, Ashura.
This sure is a wonderful place,
isn't it? I mean, the food and
water taste great...
...and as luck would have it,
that girl you saved is quite
a beauty, too.
Nothing to worry about here.
Maybe you're right, but I can
still feel it, from over there.
Feel what?
It's Chakra.
Is that where the
Divine Tree is?
Yeah, probably.
Hey, where are you going?
I'd just like to
go to that hill.
Well, you can't. The Lord Elder
says that no one is allowed to
go near there.
Oh... really?
Go on, leave.
C'mon, Ashura, let's go.
All right.
Something suspicious
is going on...
Yeah, maybe there is a
problem here, after all.
Oh! Hey, I know you!  You're
that beauty from yesterday!
What perfect timing! So,
listen, we're planning on
staying in this village for
a little while.
I'm hoping you can
show us around.
This is Ashura and I'm Tai-!
My name is Kanna. So,
are you a doctor or what?
Uh, no, not really...
He healed you because
he knows Ninshu.
Ninshu?  I see...
That's it... Can you
heal illnesses, too?
Illnesses?
Come with me.
What's this?
A medical clinic.
Please, I... I want you
to cure my mom's illness.
Mother... She's been
unconscious for a long time.
(Thinking)
What is this? I sense
a strong chakra...
Could this be from
the Divine Tree?
[grunt]
It's no good. I'm not able
to cure this sickness with
my power. I'm sorry.
I see... Are all these other
people like your mother?
Are all these other
Yes.
Ashura... Come here...
These are graves, aren't they?
I guess it's no wonder that
this place felt so creepy...
And this illness caused
all of these deaths?
That's right.
There's no choice, I have to go.
[gasps]
Hey!  You're--!
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna
need you go to sleep.
[concentrating grunts]
Uh, what are you doing?
What were the Visual
Prowess signs again?
[thuds]
Huh?
This way is easier
and much faster.
[sheepish chuckle]
There's a cave here.
Let's check it out.
What is this place?
I didn't think it would
be like this inside!
I've heard legends about
the Divine Tree, but...
This is--?!
There's no doubt.
This is the Divine Tree.
♪
(Ashura)
That tree is a remnant of the
specter that almost destroyed
our entire world.
I've been ordered to do
something about it.
The power of the Divine Tree is
indeed making this land
fruitful,... but...
it's also making the
villagers ill.
(Hagoromo)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Ashura's Decision."
(Ashura)
At this rate...
♪