Who are you
aiming at?!
What can we do?!
You're too fast
for our attacks!
[groan]
I'll say it again.
I use Lightning Style.
And when I arm myself
with Lightning Style..
my speed and defensive
power exceed the limits
that my body normally
puts on them.
So unless you attack
with Wind Style, you'll
never be able to stop me.
But even with Wind Style,
we can't land a blow!
No...
wait a
second.
Wind Unit!
Attack Formation C!
[determined grunt]
Let's go!
[grunt]
Instead of doing it quietly,
she announces exactly how
they're going to attack!
Now!
Group Wind
Style Jutsu!
Wind Style!
Casting Net!
A wide-range jutsu
designed to overtake
my speed..
Splendid move.
[pained groan]
Yes! Now quickly,
everyone surround
him!
[gasp]
[frustrated groan]
"Paradox"
[heavy breathing]
No matter how many
times we attack,
there's no effect!
We haven't
inflicted
any damage!
Our only choice is
to batter him with
a consecutive, top
speed Blade Dance!
Huh?
That you,
Dodai?
Yes.
The Third Lord Raikage was
blessed not only with speed
and power but also extraordinary
physical resilience.
Even long distance Wind Style
attacks, the only ones that
can reach him, cannot deal
him a decisive blow.
We need a
more powerful
Wind Style User.
Well, I'm not a half
bad Wind Style user
myself, you know...
So how did he
actually die,
anyway?
In order to let his people
get away, he used himself
as a decoy and faced ten
thousand of the enemy alone.
It's said that he lasted for
three days and three nights to
buy his comrades enough time.
[gulp]
Now I need him to
buy me some time...
..so that at last I can
finish up summoning him.
I guess I'll take over.
[groan]
Honestly, in the Allied
Forces, there isn't a
stronger Wind Style
User than me.
Yeah, there is!
[stunned gasp]
[shocked gasp]
And that would be me!
Wait?! Is that Naruto?!
What is he doing here?
That feels like Wind Style
jutsu! Is it a new Rasengan?
It just might work, if it hits!
[shocked grunt]
No, that still isn't
good enough! Not with
his Cloak of Lightning.
Yeah, I know!
Raikage are always
super fast!
So that's what he
was trying to do!
It's no use!
He dodged
it again!
We gotta distract him
or we'll never hit him!
Huh?
Okay! When it
comes back.
This close up.
It's gotta hit!
[groans]
That Wind Style is strong!
This could actually work!
Sealing Unit!
Hurry up!
Move in!
Right!
Yes!
Huh?
What?! How?!
My Lord Third, you're
so strong that, frankly,
it's frightening!
No way!
Rasen Shuriken
didn't work?!
The look in Lord Raikage's
eyes changed a moment ago.
It appears that he's been
completely taken over.
Wait, is that?!
All of you men, move back
from Lord Raikage now! And
you Earth Style shinobi,
get a wall up immediately!
Everyone,
link up!
All right! Together!
Earth Style: Great
Mud Wall!
Disperse!
With me,
Naruto!
[yanked grunt]
[impact grunt]
Lava Style:
Rubber Wall!
But why?
Lord Third's most powerful
ninjutsu, the Piercing
Four-Fingered Thrust of Hell!
He pools Lightning
chakra into his
fingertips.
This strike complements
Lightning Style just
perfectly.
Like Kakashi Sensei's
Lightning Blade and
Sasuke's Chidori.
Everyone, get as
far away as possible,
right now!
No way! Since we know
where he's gonna come
through, we should all
focus on that spot!
Everyone,
En garde!
Yeah, I wouldn't mind a
little payback for all
of the times we missed
that guy before now!
Stop! Listen to what
the Cloud Shinobi told
you!
[groans]
[shocked groan]
[charging yells]
[attack yells]
No.
Those damned fools!
Huh?
[pained yell]
He's switched to the
Three Fingered Assault!
What is it with that
jutsu, anyway?!
It's way too strong!
He took down dozens
by himself in an
instant!
The fewer the fingers he uses,
the more focused the energy,
and thus the Thrust of Hell
gets more powerful!
It's the Third Lord's
Invincible Spear!
And he can handle it because
his Lightning Style also
makes his body impenetrable.
It's his ultimate shield.
Seriously, is that
old man even human?!
It's said he's the only
shinobi to have gone head
to head with a Tailed Beast
unarmored and unarmed.
Wow...
Raikage are nothing
short of awesome!
Huh?
What is it?
So, what's up
with that?
Up with what?
Just look!
That, there!
The scar on his chest!
If he's as impenetrable
as you say he is, then
how'd he get that?
He didn't even
flinch against
my Rasen Shuriken!
Oh, that.
He was wounded when
he stopped Eight Tails,
who was on a rampage.
Lord Third fought him
by himself to protect
the Cloud.
You mean the Eight
Tails hurt him?!
He stated that it was
the most shameful
moment of his whole
life.
But other than saying that,
he never spoke of it any
further at all.
Not even Lord Fourth
knows the details.
Hmm..
Okay, I get that ordinary
attacks won't affect him.
But if he got injured
fighting the Eight Tails...
And the Eight Tails'
strongest jutsu is...
Speaking of
Eight Tails!
Tailed Beast Bomb!
[grunt]
What should
we do now,
Lady Temari?!
I mean, if that
hero Naruto couldn't
even take him down...
What? Naruto
is here?!
The hero of the
Hidden Leaf village?
Where? Which shinobi
is he? I want to get
a good look at him!
Yukata! Open your
eyes, would you?!
Naruto's the one who
released that flashy
Wind Style jutsu just
now!
What?! Seriously?!
But how can that be?!
He's just about the same
age as the two of us!
Yeah, that's right!
He may be young,
but he still managed
to defeat Pain of the
Akatsuki!
But then how can we defeat
an enemy that even the hero
of the Hidden Leaf village
can't?
What do you think
I'm trying to figure
out right now?!
Except I can't 'cause
you're bothering me
with all your yammering!
You aren't short range
Wind Style users!
So just get back to
where it's safe!
Yes, Ma'am!
[sigh]
What are we
going to do?
Even Naruto's Rasengan
couldn't inflict any damage.
How can we fight this Raikage?
We'll have to consider
retreating. What a nuisance
these Kage are! Even one
who's all by himself.
This is our best chance
to stop him since he's
separated from the others.
If we retreat and
let him rejoin them,
it will only get worse
for us.
What do we do?
What do we do?!
Wait.
What is this?
Does Naruto
have another
jutsu?
[gasp]
This is a Tailed
Beast Bomb just
like Eight Tails!
I didn't think it was possible
for a Jinchuriki in human form
to handle such a heavy chakra
sphere!
[straining]
[straining harder]
[straining even harder]
[pained yells]
[grunt]
It isn't possible.
As I suspected.
What happened
just now?!
[grunt]
Damn it!
I still can't
do it yet!
His chakra cloak
has dissipated!
He can't do it!
Lady Temari! The enemy's
broken through our ranks.
Many of our forces were
injured!
Get the wounded treated!
Send them to the Medical
Teams!
And everyone else is
to maintain a standby
position at a distance!
[pained yells]
Are you
all right?
Hang on!
Hey, bendy guy!
I gotta talk to Octopops
and Eight Tails now! But
how can I get in contact
with them?!
You can go through the Comm
Corps and then have Intel
Unit Captain Inoichi Yamanaka
connect you with Lord Bee.
I gotta go look
for a Comm Corps
shinobi?!
You're in luck.
Why's that?
Because I am
a Comm Corps
shinobi!
Sweet!
Naruto!
Watch out!
[yell]
He's withdrawn his
Three Fingered Assault!
He's going to just knock
us out!!
Lava Style:
Rubber Sphere!
Hmm? Lord Dodai
of the Hidden Cloud!
What do you need?
Naruto wants to talk
to Lord Bee and Eight
Tails.
Can you arrange
that as quickly
as possible?
While the Third Raikage
is still chasing after
the dummy Rubber Ball!
He made it look like he
has me inside that ball,
but he pulled me out and
hid me behind a boulder!
Bendy Guy sure
thinks fast!
Thanks for that, Bendy Guy!
Now I'll have time to talk
to Octopops for a bit!
Lord Third is probably
going to catch on right
away!
So don't count on
having too much
time to converse!
Right.
Naruto, let me get this
straight: you want to
talk to Bee and Eight
Tails?
But aren't you with them?
You were supposed to be
working together!
Not right now,
we're not. And
besides- Look,
never mind!
Please, just get me
in touch with them
quickly. I don't have
any time to waste!
Naruto's gone on ahead!
Hurry up and finish your
business!  It's taking
forever!
The urge to pee
is beyond one's
control, y'see?
Huh?
Octopops! It's me, Naruto!
There's something I want to
ask Eight Tails directly!
Can you switch
with him and put
him on for me?
Relieving oneself takes
concentration, so right
now let me focus on my
urination.
This just isn't
the time for your
kind of interrogation.
I've switched places,
Naruto! What's going on?
You seem to be in a hurry!
Hey, Eight Tails!
You've battled the
Third Raikage before,
right?
Yeah, a long time ago.
He was really strong
and could take some
serious punishment.
Once, he even chopped
off all of my tails
with his move, the
One Fingered Assault.
So how did you manage
to give Grampa Raikage
that scar on his chest?
Huh?! Oh with my Tailed
Beast bomb, I think?
Maybe. Or, maybe not.
We both collapsed forward,
completely spent yet still
poised to attack. I don't
remember much beyond that.
Could it be?
Thanks,
Eight Tails!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What?! This is
different than
before!
Grampa Raikage is
headed here now.
I can sense him.
You just stay out
of the way, Bendy Guy!
There's something that
I want to try out.
I understand.
Rasengan!
Everyone!
Stay out of this fight!
And Sealing Corps, stand
by!
Yes, sir!
I don't know what Naruto means
to do, but that's an ordinary
Rasengan! Is that going to be
enough?
His Invincible Spear will pierce
through Naruto's arms and legs
without a doubt. I'll have him
brought back to me half dead.
Sage Mode: Frog Kumite!
With this, I can sense
danger over a wider range.
And it's faster.
Now I just need
to get out of the
way!
I can aim right
for his arm!
It worked!
t's just like I
thought it would!
I see, so that scar
on his chest.. that's
how it happened!
[victory grunt]
Yes, we did it!
[cheering,]
Yeah, all right!
Nice work, Naruto!
Yeah!
That was quite
a sharp move.
When I talked with him,
the EIght Tails told me
that when he fought
against the Third Raikage,
..both of them fell
forward, ready to
attack.
I just figured he must have
gotten the scar by stabbing
himself in the chest with
his own move.
That's why he was
always so embarrassed
about it.
A shinobi with an invincible
spear and an impenetrable
shield. It certainly does
pose a paradox.
I guess this shows
that Lord Third's
spear is more powerful.
Mhm.
You know, I'd say
the shinobi who has
the best shield is
now probably Gaara!
In my heart, I always
knew you'd would become
Tsuchikage one day.
But just look at you now!
You're nothing more than
a stubborn old fool with
a bad back!
I'll admit that punch had
some real power to it,
but you overdid it and put
yourself out of commission!
Hey, listen!
Hurry up and
escape, would
ya?!
This is the Hozuki
Clan's Water Gun
Jutsu!
[heavy breathing]
You were cooperative
until just now! What,
have you decided to
help the enemy?
I am a former Kage,
after all. And actually,
I am still helping you out,
only in a different way.
Which way is
that, exactly?!
If you can't beat me using
all of your abilities, then
you're worse off than me
you old fool!
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
"Terror: The Steam Imp"
You'll never win
against the enemy
boss this way!