(clanging daggers)
My optic nerve's connected,
now.
Fuu!
Wait!
Where are you going?!
We have both scrolls! Let's
just get to the central
tower!
No way! I don't want to! I
still haven't made any
friends, yet!
I just want to have a
little more fun before this
is all over!
Have you forgotten we're
taking the Chunin Exams to
make a name for
the Hidden Waterfall?!
We may not beat the
ninety-seven-minute record
set by the Kazekage when he
was a genin, but, if we just
focus, we could still take
first place!
Wahoo!
[gasping]
She's not listening!
[grunting]
Stay calm...
Yeah...
[grunting]
Fuu! The village chief would
be disappointed if he saw
you now!
Shibuki...?!
Yes! You know that bringing
glory to the Hidden
Waterfall is Lord Shibuki's
greatest wish!
[grunting]
Shibuki...
Please, consider how he'd
feel about this!
Okay...! I get it, you guys.
I guess I don't really have
any choice...
Lord Shibuki's wishes always
come first with Fuu.
I don't know why, but she
obeys whenever his name is
mentioned.
[grunting]
Uh! Fuu! Not again!
Uh!
Where are you-?!
I'm heading to the central
tower, where else?!
Wrong way!
[gasping]
If he's using the Sand Eye,
there's no danger to him
physically...
But, unless Gaara changes
his mind...
We can't let our guard down
even for a moment.
Gaara...
Let's get dinner.
I agree. It's starting to
get really late.
Not now. I'm okay.
All right.
He snubbed us!
Sure did.
[gasping]
[panting]
Hey! Where are we headed?!
The central tower, of
course.
Wait, we don't have both
scrolls, yet!
Use your head! The very
earth beneath us is to our
advantage!
Actually,... we don't have
the "Earth" scroll. Just the
"Heaven" one.
That's not what I meant,
Yukata.
Right now, any team with
both "Heaven" and "Earth"
scrolls knows that they'll
be targeted.
Which means they'll quickly
head straight for the
central tower.
However, the whole area
surrounding it has been
filled with traps.
Except this eastern route.
What, seriously? The eastern
route is clear?
That means everybody is
going to be using that
route, aren't they?
Yes, but... it also has
natural but hidden quicksand
pits.
[gasping]
Once you fall in, you can't
get out. So we'll get there
first, wait patiently, and
steal a scroll off one of
the unlucky ones.
You're so smart!
It does sound a bit
cowardly, though...
Do you want to pass the
Chunin Exams or not? We
can't let our pride get in
the way, right now!
Okay. Let's do it.
So... you're Houichi.
You're younger than I
thought you'd be.
Yes, I can 'not deny that I
am young.
However, since I was a
child, I've studied the
power of the Priest Bunpuku
to mold currents.
You said...
...Bunpuku?
Yes.
Gaara was chosen to become
the Kazekage, but he still
poses a threat to this
village.
Many fear what he could do.
I believe that measures must
be taken to control that fear.
The Chunin Exams is a
perfect chance, to extract
Shukaku the One Tail.
Ultimately,... this means
that Gaara must die.
Yes.
First, we must make sure the
Kazekage is alone, and lure
him to the tower.
Now, I'll release the
barrier that will obstruct
long-range sensory
perception.
This place is called the
Demon Desert in part because
of its massive, deadly
sandstorms, which offer
little hope of escape to
those trapped in them.
That's why the Sand
Investigative Unit uses
long-range sensory
perception and keeps a close
watch.
What's that?!
What could it be?
Whatever it is, it doesn't
look good!
However, if long-range
sensory perception fails...
what would happen...?
By now, chaos must be
breaking out at
headquarters...
What?! A massive sandstorm's
appeared all of a sudden!
Why hasn't it been detected
until now?!
I didn't sense anything
unusual occurring!
He's right. Me, either!
Could someone be trying to
interfere with our
long-range sensors...?
You mean like trying to
block your perception with
some kind of barrier?!
Who would do that?! And why?
Forget that for now and
focus on the safety of the
exam participants.
I thought that survival was
supposed to be a part of the
Chunin Exams.
This sandstorm is way too
big for them to handle!
There will be hell to pay if
they all die!
Damn it! What a hopeless
bunch...
The Second Exam is on hold.
We'll lead all the entrants
into shelters.
I leave the Kazekage to all
of you. I get the feeling he
might go and take matters
into his own hands...
Make sure he doesn't set
foot outside.
Right!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Teams One to Three are with
me.
The rest, with me!
Let's go!
I can't believe we didn't
detect a sandstorm of this
magnitude!
If someone's interfering
with us, who could it be?
I just hope nothing bad
happens...
Yeah...
Me, too...
What in the world is going
on?!
It is a sandstorm!
I kinda figured that!
[coughing]
So this is what one of the
Demon Desert's giant
sandstorms is like. It's far
bigger than I thought it
would be. Well, we can't
stay here, that's for certain.
[struggling]
This is bad, guys...
Yeah, that's why I said we
should just go straight to
the central tower!
Huh? Watch out!
Huh? Oww!
Huh?!
[groaning]
What's the matter?
What?
Oh, uh, it's nothing.
A sandstorm? That gives us
the home field advantage!
You really think now's the
time to say that?!
This is a bad one. We
haven't seen a storm this
big in a long time.
I know! I hope all the
entrants are okay...
Yeah, me too...
Lord Kazekage...!
He's fine. He's just sitting
there.
Oh, good.
Yeah...
I can barely even see an
inch in front of me!
It is just a little sand!
The central tower is right
up ahead. Let us overcome
this with gutsiness!
Byakugan!
This'll take a lot more than
gutsiness to overcome...
Let's look around and find
somewhere we can wait out
the storm.
I can't even open my eyes!
Yeah, the sand stings!
[coughing]
I... I can't breathe!
I can't... I can't do this!
Here!
This is a sand cloak!
[gasping]
The Second Exam has been
postponed! Come on, let's
get to the shelter.
Hey, don't just sit here and
give in to a sandstorm like
this!
Wind Scythe!
All right, now's your chance
to get out of here!
Uh! [grunting]
Come on, hurry!
Are you still doing
okay, Lee?!
Yes, it is just that my
Hidden Leaf cloak is not
much help against a
sandstorm as powerful as
this one, I am very sorry
to say!
All right, that's it...
Huh?
Eight Trigrams Palm!
Rotation!
Now, Tenten!
Just leave it to me! I'm
pretty sure I have something
that'll block this sandstorm!
Come on, we need to get
inside. We'll be able to ride
out the storm in here.
Great!
I am amazed you had
something like this handy.
Yeah, well, situations like
these are about the only
times I really feel useful.
That is for sure!
As expected.
You didn't have to agree
with me so quickly, you
know!
Uh!
I can't... walk any more...
Just hang in there! We're
almost at the central tower!
Are you really sure about
that, though? You keep saying
that, but we're still not there!
Trust me! I'm sure!
[yelling]
[gasping]
You see? This is the hidden
quicksand! I told you that I
was right!
That's what you're worried
about right now?!
[struggling]
Mikoshi!
[gasping]
Quick, grab on! We gotta
pull Mikoshi out of there.
Okay!
[grunting]
[struggling]
I'm still sinking, you guys!
Pull!
[struggling]
Very soon, now...
[grunting and groaning]
Yes! We've almost got him!
[struggling]
Quick! Grab my hand!
[screaming]
I can't stand this!
We'd better reach the
central tower fast or we'll
be swallowed up.
Keep moving, guys.
[screaming]
Huh?!
[quietly groaning]
Shibuki!
Everything will be okay!
And, I will always protect
you, Fuu.
[lightly gasping]
So, why?
Huh?
Why did you protect me,
Shibuki?
Because you're very
precious to me. Why else?
Huh?
That's why you have to
protect those who are dear
to you, too.
If people could just bond
with each other more, then
there wouldn't be any more
wars in this world.
So, the first thing you
should do is make a hundred
friends.
What is it, Fuu?
Huh?
The central tower's that
way!
Uh-
Huh.
Hey, are you listening, Fuu?
[grunting]
Lord Shibuki will-!
Please, for Lord Shibuki's
sake-!
I'm sure that Shibuki would
be very pleased with what
I am planning on
doing right now!
[gasping]
[struggling]
Uh!
[grunting]
All right, I've got you!
Just stay still! Here goes!
Come on!
Uh?
Huh?
My name is Gaara, I'm the
Kazekage of the Sand.
I'm Fuu from the Hidden
Waterfall.
Why did you save them?
You're taking the Chunin
Exams as well, aren't you?
Oh...
It's something that Shibuki,
our village chief, taught
me.
Um, Shibuki--?
Listen, Fuu... there might
be people who don't
understand you.
But, still... you must hold
dear the people that
surround you...
And, always do your best to
help them.
If you do, then, someday...
Then, I'll get to have a
hundred friends, right?
[gasping and chuckling]
Yes...
He taught me that if I
do stuff like this, then
one day
I'll be sure to have a
hundred friends.
I understand. So, that's
why...
Hm?
As I observed your behavior,
I was reminded of a certain
man...
And now, I can see why that
was.
What do you mean? What guy?
Who is he?
He was a lot like you,
actually. A long time ago
I was forced to face
him in battle.
And, he taught me that we
can learn to understand the
pain, sorrow, and joy of others.
Wow, really?! He sounds
exactly like the kind of guy
that I'd like to meet and
become friends with!
[groaning]
[grunting]
Hey, question... what scroll
do you guys have?
We just have the
"Heaven" scroll...
[gasping]
Here, take this "Earth"
scroll.
What?! Are you serious?!
You're a real lifesaver!
We can't.
Sorry, we can't accept it.
But, why can't you? I have a
new goal to pursue now, so I
don't need it anymore!
It's simple. Lord Gaara has
taught all of us many
things...
To break down barriers,
those we make for ourselves
and that others make for
us... to overcome and
win...
...to bring about the
results we want to
achieve.
Believe me, we want that
scroll more than anything,
but if we let you just
give it to us...
...we can't honestly claim
that we fulfilled the conditions
of the Second Exam.
We'll get one, all by
ourselves, and using our own
power.
Right. Got it!
Fuu!
I'll get in trouble if they
catch me... Well, I guess
that I'd better be on my way!
Good-bye! Good luck!
Thank you!
She's quite interesting...
I'm sure that we'll meet
again somewhere.
Lord Gaara... Prepare to
die.
Lord Gaara! What is this?!
I am the one that they're
after. There's no need for
you to get involved in this.
When our Kazekage is
threatened, it's our duty as
Sand Shinobi to fight!
Go! I order you as Kazekage!
You are to withdraw
immediately!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Targeted
Tailed Beast"
And don't say a word of this
to anyone!