-What's that?
What the hell's going on?
-Naruto is down there fighting
Pain right at this very moment.
-He's what?
-He's fighting Pain?
All by himself?
-Yes.
And he asked that
no one interfere.
-Then all we can do
now is have faith.
And trust Naruto.
[bark]
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-There's no mistaking it.
That's definitely Naruto.
-And he's battling
Pain all by himself?
-No.
Wait.
Lady Hinata!
-But Naruto's risking
his life for our village!
-If you interfere in
this kind of a battle,
then you're only going
to get in his way.
And doing so will put
him at great risk.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
[theme music]
-Chief Toad and the others.
They were all blown away!
-Ma, we must launch the
genjutsu right away.
-Performing the duet
in front of everyone
is always so embarrassing.
-Would you quit complaining?
Just do it.
-Yeah, yeah I know.
-Now, this genjutsu requires an
enormous amount of Sage jutsu
chakra, so it's going to
take a little bit of time
before the jutsu
really gets going.
-All right.
I'm gonna go for that
five second interval,
so when your chakra is ready,
just start the genjutsu.
-Remember.
You only have one
shadow clone left
that can make Sage jutsu
chakra for you, Naruto, boy.
Once he's gone, you can't
use Sage jutsu chakra,
since you can't stay
still during a battle
to build up more.
And your Sage mode will only
last another five minutes.
-Using shadow clones to help
you maintain stillness and make
Sage jutsu chakra
was a good idea,
but why didn't you just make
a bunch more shadow clones?
-It's like trying
to look to the right
and to the left
at the same time.
Naruto boy certainly tried, but
manipulating Sage jutsu chakra
is simply too hard.
At his current level
of proficiency,
two chakra-making shadow
clones was his limit.
-And on top of all that, I
can only create up to three
more shadow clones
for the battlefield.
If I make more than
that here, then the ones
manipulating Sage jutsu
chakra will get distracted.
-Yes, I see.
Well, either way, prolonging
things isn't to our advantage.
-I must say.
You're truly strong, Naruto.
This is the farthest that
Pain has ever been pushed.
But no more.
It's over.
Universal Pull.
We're going to end
this right now.
FUKASAKU (VOICEOVER):
Forgive us, Naruto boy.
Just hang in there.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Don't worry.
I won't kill you.
You are a precious Jinchuriki.
-Did you really think you
could hurt me with this move?
You shouldn't
underestimate Sage mode.
And now it's my turn to--
-Yes, you're right.
Sage mode is troublesome.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's happening?
I'm losing power.
Wait.
I get it.
This guy's ability.
He's sucking all the Sage
jutsu chakra right out of me.
-The Nine Tails has
now been captured.
FUKASAKU (VOICEOVER):
Just a bit longer
and we'll be able
to use the genjutsu.
Hang on, Naruto, boy.
-Not yet.
I'm not done.
-You're quite the
stubborn one, aren't you?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That's it.
Not being able to move right
now will be just perfect.
-Seems you've
accepted your fate.
-I guess you didn't
know about this,
but nature energy is
really hard to control.
-What is this?
FUKSASAKU (VOICEOVER):
That's it.
That Pain took in too much Sage
jutsu chakra from Naruto boy
and underwent petrified
frog transformation.
-Sage jutsu chakra.
Seems it comes with its
fair share of risks.
-All right.
We're finally down to just you.
-Well, unfortunately,
that's not correct.
-Huh?
What do you mean by that?
KATSUYU: These Pains
are only puppets.
There is another manipulating
these Pains from the shadows.
The real Pain.
NARUTO: The real Pain?
-All right.
We're ready now.
Let's do it, Ma.
-Gotcha!
-Geezer Sage!
PAIN (VOICEOVER): I've had
enough of that genjutsu.
INO: Shikamaru!
-Ino!
You all right?
-Yeah.
Except Lady Shizune.
-What?
Does that mean she's--
-Dammit, man, does that hurt.
I think every single bone
in my body's been broken.
SHIKAMARU: I see.
So that's what happened.
If we'd just been more
diligent, then this never
would've happened.
-We can't let Lady
Shizune's death be in vain.
It's up to us now to
solve the mystery of Pain
that she was working on.
We can mourn her loss after we
find him and this is all over.
-Shikamaru.
Settle down and go
a little easy now.
-No.
He's right, Shikaku.
The best way to make
ourselves useful
is to find the location of the
real Pain as soon as possible.
-OK, Inoichi.
But with your jutsu
mastery, can't you
catch and trace the enemy's
chakra back to its source?
-I already attempted
that, but the enemy's
been constantly changing the
chakra frequency they use.
A trace back's impossible.
Pain is quite adept.
-Pa, no!
-Bastard.
-Universal Pull.
So tell me.
Did this tame you, at
least a little, Nine Tails?
-What are you?
What do you want?
Why?
Why are you doing all this?
-You ask why?
Sometimes things
happen randomly,
and the reason only becomes
apparent afterwards.
These circumstances,
well, perhaps I
can try to explain it to you.
-We'll use Katsuyu as a conduit
and gather every piece of intel
from anyone who's ever
had any contact with Pain.
Even if they're
dead, there may still
be information that we
can glean from them.
We'll get answers, even if we
have to haul out dead bodies.
INOICHI (VOICEOVER):
Haul dead bodies?
-Wait.
I think that I just
figured it out.
I know where we can
find the real Pain.
-What do you mean?
-Can you lead us to
where he's hiding?
-Yes.
In the mind of that ninja,
the one from the Hidden Rain
village whom Jiraiya captured.
I saw that he and
his partner had
been assigned the duty
of transporting bodies.
-I've developed a knack
for this over the years.
I can tell this one's
probably a woman.
-The tallest tower in
this whole village,
you know, where we always
deliver the bodies.
-Delivering bodies?
-Right.
And what you said
triggered my memory.
Here's the thing,
it's basic knowledge
that someone who's
transmitting chakra signals
must be as close to the signal
receivers as possible, right?
In this case, that
ninja and his partner
happened to be
transporting bodies
to the tallest of the
numerous towers scattered
around the Hidden Rain village.
The very same tower
where it was rumored
that Pain was supposedly living.
-But actually, you know,
there's a rumor going around
that Lord Pain lives
in that tower, there.
INOICHI: Plus, that woman who
appeared as one of the Pains,
she looks identical to
the one that those two
ninja transported to
that particular tower.
So that place is
probably the laboratory
where those black, rod-like
chakra receivers were implanted
into corpses to
create the Pains.
-OK.
So how is that connected
to the location where
you think we can
find the real Pain?
INOICHI: He needs a location
that is the most efficient
for transmitting chakra signals.
And to send out signals
the farthest and widest,
the most logical place is the
tallest tower in the Hidden
Rain village.
-Of course.
And that means, now that
his puppets are here,
the real Pain must be in the
highest spot near the Hidden
Leaf village.
-Right.
We'll search each high spot
one by one until we find him.
-You asked me why
I'm doing all this.
But even if I told you
why, I doubt very strongly
that the knowledge would
change anything at all.
But let's say that I take the
time to explain it to you.
What do you think
would happen then?
-I have nothing to say to you.
-My goal is to fulfill the
dream even Jiraiya-sensei
was unable to achieve.
As I said earlier,
what I want is
to create peace and
bring about justice.
-Create peace?
Justice?
Are you kidding?
Give me a break!
You killed my master, and
my sensei, hurt my friends,
destroyed my village!
After all of the horrible
things that you've done,
don't you dare talk
about peace and justice!
-Then tell me.
What is your goal?
-First, I'm gonna
kill you, and then I'm
gonna bring peace
to the ninja world!
-Oh, I see.
That is noble of you.
That would be justice.
However, what about my family?
My friends?
My village?
They suffered the same
fate of this village
at the hands of you
Hidden Leaf ninja.
How is it fair to let
only you people preach
about peace and justice?
-What the hell are
you talking about?
-Once, the Land of Fire and the
Hidden Leaf had grown too big.
To protect their
national interest,
they forced feudal clans to
wage war against each other
and profited from it.
Otherwise, the people of the
villages would've starved.
As it happened, our little
nation and its villages
became the battlefield where the
great nations waged their war.
Each time they did, our nation
was ravaged and laid to waste.
After many such battles,
the great nation stabilized,
but our smaller nation suffered,
and it barely recovered.
You and I are both seeking
the very same thing.
We both want to
achieve the peace
that Jiraiya-sensei envisioned.
You and I are the same.
We're both motivated by our
desire for peace and justice.
The justice that
I have delivered
against the Leaf village
is no different from what
you are trying to do to me.
Everyone feels the same pain
when missing something dear.
You and I have both
experienced that pain.
You strive for your justice,
and I strive for mine.
We're both just
ordinary men who have
been driven to seek vengeance
in the name of justice.
And, if one comes to
call vengeance justice,
such justice will only
breed further vengeance,
and trigger a vicious
cycle of hatred.
Right now, we live
in such a cycle.
I know the past, and
can foretell our future.
It is the same as our history.
So we believe that human beings
simply cannot understand each
other, and they never will.
The shinobi world of ours is
ruled by hatred and hatred
alone.
-However.
Even I'm able to see that
there's entirely too much
hate in this shinobi
world of ours.
-There's too much hate?
-I've always wanted
to do something
about all of this hatred.
I'm just not quite sure
how to about it as of yet.
But I truly believe
that eventually, the day
will come when all people
will understand one another
and live in harmony.
-Boy, it sounds kind
of complicated to me.
-And if I can't find the
solution to this problem,
then perhaps I'll entrust you
to find it instead, eh, Naruto?
-Yes sir.
I can't turn down a request from
my master, can I, Pervy Sage?
-So, Naruto.
How would you
confront this hatred
in order to create peace?
I want to know what
your answer is.
-I don't know.
I don't have an answer.
-But you see, that is why
I formed the Akatsuki.
To break the cycle of hatred.
I can put an end to it.
But I need the Nine Tails.
I must have his power in
order to achieve that goal.
I'll use the power
of all nine beasts
to create a tailed
beast weapon many times
stronger than the one that
flattened this village.
Strong enough to wipe out
an entire nation instantly.
-A tailed beast weapon?
-I'm going to show the
world what true pain is
and stop all the wars with the
terror that pain will inspire.
I shall lead the world down the
road to stability into piece.
-But if you do achieve
peace like that,
then the whole thing is
nothing but a big lie!
-Human beings are not the
most intelligent of creatures.
This is the only way that
peace can be achieved.
Of course, after
several decades,
that pain too will
eventually fade with time.
It will no longer
act as a deterrent.
Humanity will
return to war again.
This time, they themselves will
use the tailed beast weapon
against one another and
reconfirm what true pain is.
-And then, for a time,
peace will briefly
be restored again, in the course
of this endless cycle of hatred
begetting more hatred.
This unbearable pain will
give rise to momentary peace.
That is my dream and my goal.
[coughing]
-Nagato.
Please don't push yourself.
You've already spent
so much chakra.
-Peace is now within out grasp.
[theme music]
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I'm
here because I want to be.
I used to be such a cry
baby, always giving up
before I even got
a chance to start.
I almost took the wrong
path so many times.
You have changed who I am.
Your smiling face
saved me, Naruto.
That's why I'm not
afraid to protect you.
Even if--
NARUTO: Next time on
"Naruto Shippuden."
Confessions.
I will protect Naruto,
no matter what!
[applause]
-Hey, Hinata.
-Oh, Sakura.
-What's the deal with
the new ending credits?
-Uh, I don't know what you mean.
-How dare you take the
place of me, the heroine,
and have the entire
ending all to yourself?
-Uh, but I don't
know anything about--
-Yeah?
Then explain that!
-Uh--
-What?
Did you bribe the
animation staff
to put you in the
ending or something?
-No, I wouldn't do such a thing!
-And bicycles?
I mean, come on!
If you're a ninja, then--
-Give it a rest, Sakura.
-Naruto.
-There are fans of Hinata
on the staff of the show,
and I guess that they just
got a little out of control
this time, that's all.
-And what does that mean?
-Besides, just
listen to that song!
They keep repeating bicycle
throughout the entire thing,
so the only choice any
animator would have
is to put her on a bicycle.
-Hm.
That is true.
But that isn't the point!
Hey, all you animators, make
some new ending credits with me
in them, or else!
You hear me, guys?
[theme music]