[Kotetsu]
Hey, over here!
Don't you think we can
still use this timber?
Looks like it.
However...
Hm?
There's nothing left of
what was built by the previous
generations of Hokage.
Everything's gone;
who could've imagined
that this would happen?
Yeah, except the
Hokage's legacy isn't
just the village.
[Yamato]
That's right.
Yamato!
All of us...
... are still here!
Wood Style!
Row Houses Jutsu!
[impressed]
- Ah! Yes!
- All right!
At this rate The Village'll be
rebuilt in no time at all!
[panting]
Oh, sure. Easy for you to say.
Is Granny Tsunade still
in a coma, Sakura?
Yeah.
I just... There are still so
many things that I never got
the chance to say to her.
Oh don't worry.
Lady Tsunade will wake up
really soon, I'm sure of it!
I mean, she's really strong.
She's the Hokage. You'll see.
What am I consoling him for?
I'm the one who needs
cheering up...
[sigh]
[Tazuna]
Super long time no see, Naruto!
Sakura!
Huh?
It's great to see our
hero again! Hey, Naruto!
Hold on, is that...?
Huh?
Inari and Old
Man Tazuna?!
Inari! Boy, you
sure have grown up!
And you're even
older, old man!
Shut it.
I'm working as a
carpenter now.
I accepted the Hidden
Leaf's commission, and here
we are to help rebuild!
I figured that we'd at
least say hello to you
guys while we're here.
Sakura, you're even
prettier than I remember!
[chuckle]
Really? Think so?
[Naruto]
How long has it been,
about two years?
Or Three years?
Or longer?
[chuckle]
And to think,
that kid's all grown up!
[chuckle]
Inari's Courage
Put to the Test
[Naruto]
Agh! I can't find
it! It's gone!
Ugh, just stop
whining already!
Aw don't you
understand,
it's gone!
Teuchi gave me a coupon for
one free order of ramen, and
I know that I had it with me!
Aww!
I bet I forgot it at
Old Man Tazuna's place.
Hey! You can't
just leave!
I'll be right back, I swear!
Ugh. He's so
irresponsible!
What a loser.
Oh that boy.
If this takes too long,
then we'll have to hurry
back after this mission
to make our report.
Kakashi Sensei, why don't
we leave him behind and
just go back ourselves?
Sorry, no can do.
Sasuke, you're going
to have to go and
bring Naruto back.
Are you serious?
Now, now...
Sometimes detours are
part of teamwork, too.
[Tazuna]
Ichigaku?
I've never heard of this place.
I found it in the room
where those kids from the
Hidden Leaf were staying.
Huh?
After a mission, I
always eat ramen there.
Every time.
Wow. It's really
that good, huh?
It's the best!
And I'm not
exaggerating
either,
when I say my body
and spirit are made
from Ichiraku ramen.
I'll take you there if
you ever come to visit.
It'll be my treat!
This thing must
belong to Naruto.
Hold on, I'll be back
in a little bit!
My, my.
Yaaahh!
What are you doing?!
Watch where you're
throwing those things, jerk!
That's payback for not
being a team player.
Huh?
You've wasted enough
of our time already.
Let's head back.
Okay, I get it.
[hmph]
I will, right after I take
care of my business!
Haa! Like I'd ever take
orders from you, bonehead!
Why, you...
[Yamabuki]
Look, it's Inari.
He's been acting super
stuck-up ever since he
helped break up that
Gato smuggling ring.
Heh.
Agh!
What's the big idea?!
You know.
You're stuck-up!
But you're really
a crybaby!
I'm not a crybaby!
Just leave!
I'm in a hurry.
Trying to act
tough, huh?
Like you'd try something
by yourself.
Yeah, that's right!
What're you gonna do now?
Your ninja friends
have already gone home
to their village!
[Zouri]
Oh yeah?
Well, that's good news.
No way, it's them!
It looks like it was
worth waiting after all.
[gasp]
Man, you really don't know
when to stop, do you?!
All right, then...
Just relax, Sasuke.
I'll only be gone a
little while.
Hmph.
Weak!
Ow! Hey, you jerk!
You don't have to
kick for real!
Huh?
Agh!
Just give it up,
would you?
[Tazuna]
Hey! What are you
two doing here?
Old Man Tazuna!
Talk about perfect timing!
You see, I forgot something
back at your place.
Wait, let me take a guess:
A little piece of paper?
Mmm-hm!
Inari really wanted to
make sure you had it,
so he ran off a little while
ago to take it to you.
Auhhh!
[Inari]
What's going on,
why are you still here?
And why is your
whole gang with you?
I thought Naruto kicked
you all out of the village
a long time ago!
Kicked us out? Heh!
We were just waiting for
those troublemakers to
leave before we came back!
Yeah, and with them
gone, there are no more
ninja around here
to stick their noses
in our business and
get in our way!
Just what're you planning to do?
Ah!
We're taking over here!
And we're going to make Gato's
business bigger than ever!
[Naruto]
Inari!
Hey, where are you?! Inari!
That's so weird.
I was sure that
he'd be somewhere
on this road.
Rrrgh!
Hey, Sasuke!
Get over here and
help me look too,
would you?!
Listen, Inari went
looking for you.
This doesn't involve me.
Aw, come on! Whatever
happened to teamwork, huh?!
That's the only reason I'm
here with you right now.
Show some gratitude, loser.
Rrrgghh!
I'll... show...
you... gratitude!
Hey, where're
you going?
Shut up!
I need to go
take a leak!
Huh...?
What's my ramen coupon
doing way out here?
Wait a second.
Look there.
[Naruto]
What is all that?
[Sasuke]
It's faint, but those
are signs of a fight.
Huh?!
Something happened here.
Inari...
[thug]
I've got an idea;
why don't we ransom off those
kids to make some money?
Whatever. The best plan is
the one we already have:
to be the next Gato!
Booze and money.
We'll take
everything we can.
[laughter]
Hmf.
You know what, I feel
like cutting something.
Where's that kid...
He'll do fine.
Enough; cut it out.
That's a bad habit.
[sobbing]
I wonder what
they're gonna do...
What's gonna happen to us?!
We all thought we
finally got rid of Gato.
And now...
Waaaah!
Don't cry.
Huh?
Our crying won't
solve anything.
It won't. Naruto was the
one who taught me that.
Inari?
We fight back.
Otherwise, we can't
protect what's dear to us.
Uh...
This is bad.
It's only a matter of time
before the rain washes away
all traces of their trail.
Then we just have to figure
out another way to find them
before that happens.
Please be okay...
[Inari]
Is everyone ready to go?
[Akane]
Yeah.
We have to run back to
town and tell the
grown-ups what's going on.
Right!
[loud rattling]
[gasps]
Oh, no!
[rattling]
What's that?!
It's the
kids' room!
D'agh!
You guys!
Those brats are
gettin' away!
[Sasuke]
These marks are fresh.
It looks like a sword
made them.
Huh? I recognize it!
I've seen this mark before!
The stragglers from
Gato's group, huh?
[Sasuke]
Up ahead.
Naruto, Let's go!
Right!
Find them!
They're around
here somewhere!
Damn kids runnin' off!
We gotta do something fast,
or sooner or later,
they're gonna find us.
I'll go distract them.
Uh!
Don't be
ridiculous!
But if they catch you,
then they'll...
If I don't, then
we'll all be killed!
Mmm...
Besides...
I have an idea.
Where did those
little brats go?!
[rustling foliage]
Huh?!
Found them!
Over that way!
Inari...
Come on!
Let's go!
It's do or die time.
Please Dad. protect me.
[Tsunami]
Where could Inari be?
Usually isn't late...
You're right.
[knocking]
What is it?
I'm afraid The kids who went
out to play haven't returned.
Yeah, my Akane
hasn't come back yet.
And neither
has my son.
We think Yamabuki is
missing as well.
They were last seen earlier
today going into the woods
with your grandson Inari.
You're in a heap of
trouble now, kid!
We won't let you run
off like that again.
I have an idea!
Maybe we should just
cut off one of your legs!
Just give up.
You can't win.
[gulp]
I can't believe it, he jumped!
Go on! Get down there now!
Hey, Dad? Did you really
swim all the way through
those rapids to fix the dam?
Yeah, I did that,
among other things.
You know, that's
pretty amazing, Dad.
I mean, I can't even swim!
Well, let's change that!
Swimming is
something everyone
should learn to do.
Yeah, but,
I'm kinda scared.
Don't worry.
Listen, you've got two arms.
You can do anything!
Keep on moving those arms!
Just paddle hard;
you can do it!
I can't, Dad. I just can't!
The water's so cold.
This way! Don't stop!
But I'm not moving
forward at all.
I can't do this!
Wait! I have to stop!
It's all right.
I know you can
do this!
Come on, Inari!
[Naruto]
Inari!
[gasp]
Quick! Grab my hand!
Yes! Ha!
Why are you here?
How come...?
How come we're here??
'Cause of you!
You did an awesome job!
your friends were able
to escape and then
they led us here!
The guys are okay?!
Looks like we're not going
to have the time to chat
about that right now.
You're the brats from
the Hidden Leaf!
You gotta lotta nerve
showing up here!
It's just two kids, you guys!
Go get 'em!
Yeaaahh!
Naruto!
Heh. So you think
you can outnumber
me, do ya?
All right... Let's go!
Haaa!
You stay here okay?
Mm.
Thanks, you guys.
Ha ha ha ha!
Weaklings, all of you;
you're nothing
compared to me!
Unless you take me by
surprise, I can do
this all day lo--
[Sasuke]
Demon Wind Shuriken!
What?!
Yagh!
Bring it on!
I'll pulverize you!
No, don't!
Aht!
Agh!
Come on. This is
just way too easy.
Don't underestimate us, boy!
I'm going to have to
kill you for that!
None of you clowns
is a match for us!
[gasp]
Haaaa!
Ah!
Damn! They may be kids,
but they're still ninja!
We gotta go!
But we'll be back!
Rrrh...
Huh? What?!
Did you really think
we'd let you come back?!
This is the end of the
line for you guys!
[gasp]
Grandpa! Everyone!
We'll never let thugs
like you have their way
in our land ever again!
Ah...
Some remnants of Gato's group
were up to no good, eh?
We're turning you in to the
authorities so you can never
do something like this again.
What happened?!
A little while ago,
you were a bunch
of big cowards!
[Akane]
Thanks, Inari.
Akane!
Sorry. Guess the three
of us misjudged you.
Ah!
[chuckle]
[Naruto]
It's nothing
to laugh at!
Ulp!
Agh! You know how
worried you had us?!
You are such a...
You're such a...
Naruto...
Sorry...!
I just...!
I'm sorry!
[both crying]
They're crying
like babies!
It's okay at
times like this.
[crying]
Oh yeah, I almost
forgot I had something
to give to you, Naruto!
[sniffling]
Oh, don't worry.
I still have the coupon.
[gulp] It's gone.
You probably lost it in the
river. Just forget it.
[crying]
DAHHH!
[Inari]
Now Akane and our old friends,
they're carpenters
just like me.
They're all working
right over there.
You see?
Wow, what a surprise!
We're grateful that you
helped us on that day,
and with Gato
the time before.
Because of you,
the Land of Waves has
become very prosperous.
That's right! And now it's time
for us to return the favor!
The first thing I'll build is...
Ichiraku! Just you watch!
I'll build you an amazing
noodle house!
Inari...
[chuckle] Thank you,
that would be great!
[Naruto]
What's up with that
pathetic stance?
He can try for a hundred years,
and he still won't get
revenge like that!
[Sasuke]
Hey Naruto, where
are you going!
[Naruto]
I gotta train that
guy from scratch!
[Sakura]
He's gone!
Are you just going to
let him take off like that,
Kakashi Sensei?
[Kakashi]
It's fine. There isn't
much to do until we
leave tomorrow, anyway.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Naruto's School of Revenge."
All right!
Let's begin our lesson!