Allied Shinobi Forces Jutsu!
They're so pitiful.
Yeah.
This hope that they're
clinging to doesn't exist.
[chuckle] Just like their
very lives, at this point.
It seems the Ten
Tails is quite ready.
Fifth Gate of Closing! Open!
So this time, they're coming
after us, not the Ten Tails.
Well, it is basic strategy
to take out the enemy's
brains, isn't it.
Just like we planned,
take down those two, the
brains of Ten Tails!
But in order to do that,
they would actually need to
stop the Ten Tails!
[gasp]
[groaning]
What?! I thought we had
immobilized Ten Tails!
You okay?! Damn it...
[gasp]
My shoulder's dislocated!
Look at the Sensory Water
Sphere! It's practically
like a small planet.
But that's impossible!
Then we didn't
immobilize Ten Tails?
It merely stopped moving
on its own to amass its
power and transform?
So how can
we stop it, then?
We can't target those two!
But we have to find a
way to stop that thing
or else it's over
for all of us.
[worried whine]
I'm about to pee
my pants, here.
[growl]
Don't just freak out;
infuse your chakra!
And be prepared to move when
we get the plan from HQ!
We must immobilize
Ten Tails or else we
won't be able to go after
the brains that are
manipulating it.
But how?! Even with the
jutsu of my clan, which
specializes in
immobilizing, the effect
would be miniscule
compared to the amount
of chakra expended.
Inoichi! Link me
up with Kakashi!
Roger!
Kakashi, it's me!
Huh?
I want to confirm something
about the intel from the
last battle sequence.
It is going to begin getting
more difficult to control
the Ten Tails.
Reinforce your bond with it
using Hashirama's cells.
We should take this
opportunity to check out Ten
Tails' power, while it's
in its current state.
First, we should--
Yes, let's show every
last one of them...
...what despair is!
Shikaku, I've
gotta go for now!
What it is?!
This is... No way!
Lord Shikaku!
Lord Inoichi!
My Kamui won't be in time!
Displace it upwards
with Earth Style.
Gotcha!
Whoa, that far away?!
It's much greater than
the other Tailed Beasts!
What power!
It's shakey from just
that little counter.
Its control isn't
perfect yet.
The next one!
[roar]
Unbelievable! A distant
city, gone like that! Huh?
It's been acting weird! It
seems to be aiming afar!
So every city and
person is within its
range of fire, huh?
That means the Feudal
Lords, everyone guarding the
villages plus all
of the citizens of
each nation are at risk?
The reason for this war
is so our shinobi on the
battlefield can protect
everyone else.
But those two want to
remove that reason.
[roar]
That's the direction of--!
This, This is...
What's is it, Lord Ao?!
Please listen
to me calmly...
Right here, huh?
Shikaku... What now?
Just keep doing
what we must do.
I have a plan to stop
Ten Tails, our final act.
Put me through to
everyone on the battlefield.
[grunt]
Finally got them.
Now we've smashed the
Allied Forces' brains.
Simple basic strategy.
Shikamaru...
We're in the middle of a
war. So don't waste any
words on me.
Or on Ino.
We have to do
what we have to do.
Just like father said.
Wait, hold on! What the
heck just happened?!
You are the key to our
whole plan, Naruto.
No, not that!
I'm asking what happened
to Shikaku and Inoichi!
[screaming]
Neji! Rotate clockwise!
Right!
Eight Trigrams
Palm Rotation!
A- Amazing...
Don't just stand there
spacing out, Naruto!
This is a battlefield
and we are at war.
People die!
But if we're defeated
and lose this war
everyone will die!
Of course. I know that!
Shikamaru's and Ino's
fathers might say that as
shinobi, they're glad they
died before their children.
The same as my father did.
Listen, Naruto! Your power
is crucial to the plan.
So until we're able
to execute it...
...we must protect you!
Hinata!
Just know this! The
Hyuga are the mightiest
among the Leaf!
I was hoping to take them
down before they started
with the speeches but
it is difficult to
control the Ten
Tails well.
I suppose this ought
to do until the next
transformation.
But afterward
I suspect that
only Jinchuriki will
be able to control it.
Though for me to become
the Ten Tails' Jinchuriki,
I am going to need to become
fully and truly alive.
Not just hosted
within a corpse as
a mere Reanimation.
Reanimations are good
for big suicidal attacks.
But the reason you haven't
launched the Ten Tails'
Tailed Beast Bomb
at them, blowing
yourself up as well,
is that I'd get caught
in it and die, too.
And the reason that
would be a problem is,
for you to truly be
brought back to life and
become a Jinchuriki,
you will still need me to
sacrifice myself and perform
Art of Rinne Rebirth on you.
In short, you're in a very
delicate position right now
where you're
entirely at my mercy.
Don't forget that.
Well, well, well, my
little rug rat has become
quite the wily fox.
You realize that I've
never really considered
you a comrade.
[chuckle]
Well, so be it.
All right, why don't you
decide our next move, then?
We continue.
They will all come to
know despair thoroughly.
[roaring]
Wood Style! Cutting
Sprigs Jutsu!
[painful grunts]
My Mountain Jutsu
should at least slow it
down until Nine Tails'
strength returns.
But I need time to build up
chakra! Hold on, everyone!
Cha!
So many! My Rotation
can't keep up.
[grunt]
Thanks, Neji! I can
activate Sage Mode now!
I can't keep relying on
you geniuses! It's my turn!
[chuckle]
Rasen Shuriken!
[attacking grunts]
Here's a few more!
[screaming]
Eight Trigrams:
Air Wall Palm! [grunt]
Damn it! A focused attack!
There's too many!
Hinata's and Neji's Air
Palms won't be enough!
Byakugan!
[gasp]
Earth Style! Mountain
Jutsu! Now, go!
[attacking yells]
Get the Medical team!
Hurry! There's a
critical injury!
Hurry!
No...
I think I'm done.
Neji...
Neji, no!
[sigh] Naruto...
Hinata is willing
to die for you.
So remember you hold
more than one life...
In your hands.
[crying]
And it seems that
my life may have
also been one of them.
But why?! Why did you-?!
You can't die here!
You were gonna
change the Hyuga!
Long ago, those
words of yours
freed me from
the shackles of fate.
Why would you go
so far for me?!
Even give up
your life?! Why?!
Because you called
me a genius.
Because after all,
unlike me, you're
not a failure, Neji.
Father, I finally
understand
the freedom you felt,
choosing to die
in order to protect
your comrades.
Didn't you say you
wouldn't let any of
your comrades die?
Naruto!
I'll never let my comrades
die! No matter what happens!
You said, "I'll never
let my comrades die."
Those were your words.
Now look around you,
and try to say them again!
I said, try to say
those words again!
As the bodies of your
comrades grow cold in your
arms, take in their deaths!
Neji's really dead?!
Hizashi, forgive
me. Neji is--!
This will just
keep happening.
And all of your flippant
words and ideals
will become lies.
This is the end result
of ideals and hope.
This is reality.
Naruto, what is there here
for you in this reality?
Your mother and father are
gone. Your Master, Jiraiya,
too. And if you keep
standing against us,
you'll continue to lose
your friends one by one.
This shall become a
world where no one who
acknowledges you
will exist.
Obito...
The only thing
that awaits you is
your worst nightmare,
which you know very well!
Solitude!
You have become
almost exactly like
the old me, Obito.
Naruto will fall shortly,
which will break the will of
the Allied Forces.
So why keep living
in reality, huh?
Now come join us, Naruto!
Neji just said that
in your hands
you hold more
than one life.
Do you understand
what he meant?
Do you?
"I'll never let
my comrades die."
Those words and
the conviction behind
them are not lies!
For he stored them in
his heart and lived them
out till the end!
Neji really did!
It isn't just you.
It's all of us.
We all hold those words
and feelings in our hearts.
They're what bind
our lives together
and make us comrades.
If we were to all give
up and discard those
words and feelings.
Neji's act'll have
been for nothing.
And that is when
your comrades truly die!
For you are no longer
comrades then.
That's how I feel.
So, please, stand up
together with me, Naruto.
Because never going
back on one's word...
That is also
my Ninja Way!
Naruto...
Hinata is willing
to die for you.
So remember you hold
more than one life.
Of course it's
more than one!
Don't forget
about me, either!
I know that! My
bonds are serious!
I'd never abandon
my comrades!
But the truth is, Neji...
Stop whining
and complaining!
I'll clobber you and
take over your body for
good this time, dammit!
Did you forget this, too?!
Your mom and dad did the
same thing Neji did right
after you were born!
They sealed their archenemy,
me, inside you, left the
future to you, and died.
Your life was already linked
to two others' right from
the time that you were born!
Will he just stand back and
see how Naruto responds?
It seems Naruto
makes him uneasy.
Enough!
[roaring]
Slow down! You're
going to harm yourself
and the Ten Tails!
So? I don't care!
The Ten Tails'
hide is tough!
They're gonna hit us!
Recharge complete!
Be careful, Master Bee!
Go get 'em!
Take this!
Lord Bee!
Don't go overboard!
There's no need to worry.
Protecting the Alliance
is my territory!
[gasp]
That's right. It wasn't just
Mom and Dad, either.
Yeah, all those others, too.
I have a connection to
so many other people!
Hinata, thank you!
It's all thanks to you
standing by my side.
And Neji...
Thank you, too.
Naruto's hand is so
big and so strong
and most of all...
Hinata, let's do this!
Yeah!
It's so comforting!
I haven't been able
to save many a comrade.
An existence where one can
only await death inside a
cage. Nice analogy
for this situation.
You're all like
that brat who just
died a pointless death.
Neji's will isn't dead yet!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Those Who
Dance in the Shadows."
[attacking yell]