I'm a Jinchuriki, too. The
Akatsuki are hunting all of us.
So I'm not just an outsider.
The Akatsuki always capture
a Jinchuriki alive.
And that means your master may
still be alive right now.
What??
Are you serious?
Forget Sasuke. You need to
go rescue your master first.
You sure about this?!
Like really, really sure?
I told you, didn't I?
No way our master would
die as easily as that!
Tell you what, I'll come
along and do what I can
to help you rescue him.
And give you all that I've
got on the Akatsuki.
Hey, you know what, there,
blondie? You're pretty sharp.
Come along with us.
And tell us all
about Sasuke!
Naruto...
Just let me handle
this, Sakura.
So, kid... What's your name?
[Suigetsu]
Naruto?
This Naruto guy
really defeated Pain
all by himself?!
[White Zetsu]
That's right.
He's become
extremely strong.
In fact, I think
he's stronger than
Sasuke right now.
Heh.
I don't care about that.
What is a problem is this
Five Kage Summit.
So what do we do?
The Leaf Village is gone now.
And if our target, this
guy Danzo, is going to this
meeting of the Five Kage,
then shouldn't we
head over there, too?
Hrmf!
Huh? What? Do you
think I'm wrong
about that?
We, the Taka, will take the
Hokage's head at the Summit.
New destination.
Sounds like a plan.
So, how do we find out where
is this Five Kage Summit's
taking place?
Agh. This situation's
becoming annoying.
Zetsu.
My clone will
guide you there.
Ugh... Yech!!
Okay, follow me!
Do you think we can
really trust these guys?
We'll keep an eye
on them for now.
If anything seems suspicious,
then I'll get rid of them
with my Amaterasu.
There's something I've been
meaning to test out, anyway.
[Black Zetsu]
Things are going well.
Well, I never thought
Nagato would use that
Gedo Art of Rinne Rebirth
that he developed for me
and for such a
thing as that?
I can't believe
he betrayed me.
Even if Sasuke
surpasses Nagato,
it's meaningless if
we can't control him.
I have no intention of
linking him to the Gedo
statue anytime soon.
It's wiser to just
keep an eye on him.
[Black Zetsu]
I can't believe you
foresaw the possibility
that Nagato would die.
As a precaution...
But we've definitely
fallen off my ideal path.
Thanks to Naruto Uzumaki.
He's caused all our
well-laid plans to shift.
What's next then?
Do we go, too?
We're done with moving
ahead cautiously.
Put a rush on
Project Tsuki no Me!
The Eve of the
Five Kage Summit
[Karui]
This'll do.
All right, come on,
let's hear all about
this Sasuke guy.
Tell us everything you know.
Anything you can about him.
What's the matter?
Spill it!
I'm sorry. I can't.
There's no way I can
sell Sasuke out.
Quit playing around!
You can't take it back
after all that.
All the same, Sasuke is
a Ninja belonging to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
He's a comrade!
And I'll put my life on
the line to help 'im!
That's the way of our Village.
Naruto... This is a...
once in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please, bring Sasuke
back to me.
Well, come on!
Say something!
To be a ninja means that
you must confront hatred.
And every one of us must
battle against that hatred.
And If one comes to call
vengeance justice,
such justice will only
breed further vengeance.
And trigger a vicious
cycle of hatred.
I know that I'm only being
selfish, But I won't sell
out Sasuke like that.
Why you!
I get your need for vengeance;
believe me, I do!
But if you guys hate
enough to kill Sasuke,
My friends won't just sit back
and accept what happened.
It'll be an eye for an eye!
And the vicious cycle will
start all over once again!
The people you love will
keep killing each other.
Yeah, whatever! Your Sasuke
is the one who started it all!
So I don't care!
We are going to kill him!
Well, just where do
you suggest that we
take our hatred, then?
I mean, what could
you do about that?
[frustrated grunt]
You guys can
beat me up instead.
Get it all out.
I offer myself.
Look, kid, just get
off your high horse!
All right, then, let's test
your little theory out.
See if I can really
get my feelings out.
How's that?! And that!
And that!
[continues punching]
And that! And that!
How far did Omoi and Karui
have go to gather Intel?
We're in foreign territory;
I hope they're not
causing trouble...
But all this damage to the
Hidden Leaf Village...
Who could've stopped a foe
powerful enough to do this?
[Villager]
Sometimes I still can't believe
that he took on the
Akatsuki all by himself!
I confess I never
thought Naruto would
come this far!
Yeah, he's a true
hero, all right!
He should be
Hokage one day!
Yeah, you said it!
You got that right!
[Shizune]
I'm afraid it's true...
Apparently Sasuke
really was seen wearing
Akatsuki clothing.
I see...
Sasuke really is
one of them, then...
Sakura... I'm sorry...
[punching]
[Foo]
I've sent two of my best,
Dajim and Terai, after Anko.
[Foo]
Should we move to eliminate her?
We are at a crucial juncture.
I want to avoid any
mishaps that could worsen
our circumstances.
Increase the number of troops.
Make capturing Kabuto a higher
priority than Anko.
That one... He may know of my
relationship with Orochimaru.
Kabuto possesses all of
Orochimaru's human
experimentation data.
We must obtain it.
I'm certain it will be most
useful in regards to my right
arm and right eye.
Foo, Torune, you stay here.
Terai, Go. I leave
Kabuto's capture to you.
Yes, sir!
And now, I must prepare and
depart for the Five Kage Summit.
We can only bring two
retainers to the Summit,
except in special cases,
I have decided that those
two shall be you, the two
best among the Foundation.
Masks are forbidden.
Remove them.
In terms of armament,
what are we allowed?
Don't concern yourself
with any limitations.
I trust your discretion.
Sir.
Torune.
Have your subordinates
keep an eye on Naruto.
I doubt that Sai would
do anything to betray
the Foundation.
But it pays to
be cautious.
Sir.
They are to make certain
that the Nine-Tails does
not leave the Village.
[panting]
You bastard.
Listen to me!
No amount of pummeling
will make me feel better!
But I'll keep going
until you spill it
about Sasuke!
[gasp]
Look, don't interfere.
He was the one who asked
for this all on his own.
She's right.
Just stay out of this.
Naruto, There's no need
for you to be beaten,
not on Sasuke's behalf.
Shut up. It's my choice.
[Naruto]
There was a time when I
really hated Sasuke's guts.
But when I look back,
I gotta admit it was always
fun being around the guy.
Sasuke... is my best friend.
It took a while, but now
we have a special bond.
Sasuke keeps causing
you so much pain.
If I were you...
If you interfere,
I'll pummel you, too!
[gasp]
That's enough
already, Karui.
Knocking these guys
around any more, isn't
going to get us anywhere.
I know you
agree with me.
You know, you could cut him
some slack; he did promise to
help rescue Lord Killer Bee.
Oh, yeah? What? And you're not
going to question if he really
means it like you usually do?
You're usually so
obsessive-compulsive!
Naruto!
Even if he's a foe, I like
this guy. He's someone who'd
never sell out his comrades.
Real men don't choose
their words lightly.
Even if you beat him,
He just won't betray
Sasuke.
He's the type who will
never go back on his word.
Huh?
Captain Samui!
Omoi, Karui.
How goes the Intel-gathering?
The two of you haven't
been causing any
trouble now, have you?
[denying]
Mm-mm! mm-mm!
Look, never mind that!
Lord Killer Bee may still be
alive, we have to save him!
Listen to me, we're going
to have to track down all
the Akatsuki hideouts!
And? Then what? We can't go
in there alone. These people
captured Lord Killer Bee!
You're suggesting we check
out the who-knows-how-many
Akatsuki hideouts one by one?
We need Intel.
We need analysis first.
We mustn't repeat the
errors we made that
time with Yugito.
We'll just take the
Hidden Leaf's data
directly to Lord Raikage.
Especially since
there's so much of it.
[Naruto]
Ngh, Take me...
with you, too... please.
I'd... like to help you guys...
rescue your Jinchuriki.
Naruto!
Besides, there's something
I'd like to talk to the
Raikage about.
Talk to Lord Raikage?
Are you kidding me?!
Karui...
So this child is Naruto.
Naruto Uzumaki, the one
everyone in this village
is talking about.
You're an unknown
entity, and right now,
when he's on the road
under minimal guard,
I cannot have you
meet Lord Raikage.
...
Karui, Omoi, let's go!
We're approved to
inspect the Intel on
Sasuke and the Akatsuki.
It's going to take time
to copy it all, so I
need you two to help me.
Sai...
Yes?
Please take me to
Kakashi Sensei,
and Captain Yamato.
Okay. Here.
[Sai]
I'll go get the first aid kit.
I'll be right back.
[Kakashi]
Hey...
What's with
that glum look?
Kakashi Sensei!
[Kakashi]
I see...
So that's what
happened to Naruto.
Kakashi Sensei.
Hmm?
This link between
Naruto, Sakura, and
Sasuke hurts them.
Is that bond really
so important?
Why do they keep trying when
it causes them so much pain?
Sai, You're watching
Naruto for Danzo, right?
Well, that's--
Relax. It's all right.
Jumping in to help Naruto...
isn't something a lookout does.
I think you've started to
realize it too, Sai.
You really ought to have
Sakura treat these wounds.
Nah, it's fine.
Plus if she sees me like this,
it'll only cause more trouble,
trust me.
Besides, I heal fast.
I'll be okay in no time.
Sai...
Hm?
What you did before...
Thanks for helping me.
Sure!
Boy, they really
worked you over.
Hee.
Ngh! Ow!
Sorry!
Look, you need to take it
easy for a little bit.
No, I'm going to
see the Raikage!
Ah!
Naruto what are you saying?!
The Five Kage Summit is soon!
Every Hidden Village
has agreed to travel
restrictions and no
unnecessary missions!
What do you hope
to achieve?
I'm going to convince him to
forgive Sasuke! No matter what.
But you don't have the
Hokage's necklace that
seals the Nine-Tails!
As a Jinchuriki you must
not leave the Hidden Leaf!
It's bad enough that you
sprouted eight tails
during that last battle!
We're lucky the Sealing
Formula triggered and
stopped Nine-Tails.
But what about next time?
Besides, I'm in charge of
reconstructing the Village.
I can't stay close to
you all the time!
[Naruto]
I met the Fourth Hokage.
Huh?
The one who stopped me from
becoming the Nine-Tails,
was the Fourth Hokage.
(taken aback reax)
What does he mean?
The Fourth Hokage's dead!
The Sealing Jutsu he used,
the Reaper Death Seal,
still holds many mysteries.
He probably stored some
of his own mental energy
within the seal spell.
And that's when the
Fourth Hokage told me,
The Nine-Tails incident sixteen
years ago, was caused by the
Akatsuki guy with a mask.
He's so strong even the Fourth
Hokage struggled against him!
He said the masked one's pulling
the strings. He was probably
just using Pain the whole time.
If Sasuke has joined
the Akatsuki,
that means this masked
guy is using Sasuke, too!
It's just as Lord
Jiraiya feared.
I can't believe that man
was behind the incident
sixteen years ago.
He bears the Sharingan.
And a grudge against
the Village.
The only rogue Uchiha capable
of summoning the Nine-Tails,
Is Madara.
Eh?
Without a doubt,
Anything's possible
if Madara's involved.
So he's actually still alive.
Madara...
With that vision of yours,
and a chakra more ominous
than my own,
You're the spitting
image of Madara Uchiha.
Who is this guy, Madara?
A former Hidden Leaf shinobi
and Uchiha clan leader who
battled the First Hokage and
lost, and was never seen again.
This Intel needs
to be reported to
the Council. Sai?
Yes?
You must report this to
the Hokage at once.
Oh. Right.
Naruto. What else did the
Fourth Hokage say to you?
Huh?
Fathers tend to have a lot
they want to tell their sons.
There was one other
thing he said;
he believed in me!
Good!
Naruto, you go
to the Raikage!
Huh?!
Yamato and I will tag
along as your escorts.
Whaaat?!
[Yamato]
Nononono,
This is a bad idea!
[Kakashi]
What? Don't you even want to
hear what I have to say before
you make up your mind, Tenzo?
[Yamato]
Hey! You're not supposed to call
me by that name, remember?!
[Kakashi]
Now, now...
[Yamato]
Naruto, are you serious about
going to meet the Raikage?
[Naruto]
Of course. I'm going
to convince him to
forgive Sasuke.
[Yamato]
But that being said,
you don't even know
where the Raikage is!
[Kakashi]
I bet you could help;
you're good at stuff
like that, right?
[Kakashi]
I'm counting on you!
[Yamato]
What?! Oh sure, you make
it sound so easy...
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Enter the Five Kage!"
[Kakashi]
Let's get this mission started!