Why you...
You whelp!
How dare you!
What the hell?!
(screaming)
Hey, hey, hey...
No way...
That's...
How dare you do such
a thing to Ginkaku?!
You're going to pay!
Now he looks...
just like the Nine
Tail's Jinchuriki!
What is...
that thing?!
There's still
more?!
It's been quite a
while since I've seen
that happen to Kinkaku.
That means...
Ginkaku's a goner.
Ahhhh!
The red and blue
balance of your Tailed
Beast chakra looks
good to go!
So do it, Naruto!
Here I go!
Tailed Beast
Rasan-
Concentrate!
Didn't work, huh?
That time you were
so close, it's too bad.
Why'd you lose your
focus?! It's so sad!
What the hell was
that just now?
Oh man, this is
really not good.
(Chuckle)
I'm really sorry!
Too late for that!
Whoa!
What? What's
that? Is he
a Jinchuriki?
Thanks. I sure do
owe you one. But still,
just what is that thing?!
Now that we're allies...
I believe it's about
time that you knew
the whole story!
Long before Madara
Uchiha tamed the Nine
Tails, the Hidden Cloud
put together a mission
to try to capture
that cataclysmic
force!
That's when the Nine
Tails devoured Lords
Kinkaku and Ginkaku.
And then after two
weeks, he expelled them!
What? Expelled them?
You mean from his
behind?
Come on, show some
respect, and contact
HQ immediately!
We need to know how
to counter that!
Right! Sure!
Where are the
reinforcements?!
And what's the status
of Darui's First Company?
They've caught
Ginkaku, one of the
enemy's strongmen.
But it seems Kinkaku
has donned the Nine
Tails Cloak and is
running amok!
The time's come,
Mabui! Start
preparations!
Right!
If Kinkaku has
transformed, we
can't stop him!
He has a Nine
Tails' Cloak?!
Even if he does
possess the Nine
Tails' chakra, how
can he undergo
Tailed Beast
transformation?
They were inside of
the Nine Tails' for
two weeks.
And supposedly they
survived by eating
the Nine Tails'
stomach lining.
No one else has ever
eaten the Nine Tails'
Chakra rich flesh.
No...actually, I
take that back.
I've heard that some
in the Cloud tried to
copy feat by eating
Eight Tails' legs.
But they all died
without becoming
Jinchuriki.
Those two brothers are
special. Perhaps they're
direct descendants of the
Sage of the Six Paths.
All right, so what
do we have to do to
take him down?
There is only
one way.
It's true Kinkaku
has enormous chakra
and power, that fact's
undeniable.
However, we can still
use their fifth and
final Treasure Tool
against them.
Come with me.
If I could just seal
him away in the
gourd too...
But I need Kokinjo
to squeeze out his
spirit word.
And I can't see the
rope on his arm while
he's covered by the
Nine Tails' Cloak.
I can't get it...
Sir, a message!
HQ's sending you the
Kohaku no Johei, the
Amber Purification Jar.
I see! Thank you.
It'll be way better
than this gourd.
This is the Kohaku no
Johei, one of the five
Treasured Tools. It was
used to seal away
the Eight Tails.
It doesn't seem like
anything special.
You don't need the
other tools for it to
work. All you do is
say the target's name,
and if they respond,
their voice is
recorded and they're
trapped inside.
It's all we can
take from the
Gold and Silver
Brothers.
We'll send it to
Darui so he can
seal Kinkaku!
But the situation is
urgent! It'll take too
long to transport this.
Lord Raikage...
Everything's ready!
I can send it to
Darui now!
Mabui's jutsu is
object teleportation,
which moves at the
speed of light.
It's the reason why
she's my secretary.
But if that used to be
one of their ninja tools,
I'm sure he knows how to
counter it, as well.
So we need to figure
out the best way
to make him respond.
Right. I've got an
idea to try...
Any strategy that you
come up with is sure
to work. You handle it.
Go on, Mabui!
Ethereal
Transmission
Jutsu!
Make sure you
get him, Darui.
We've both got
exceptional
subordinates, don't
we, Tsunade?
You got that right.
(painful grunt)
Here it is!
The Kohaku no Johei...
That used to be ours!
I see. They're going
to try to seal me
away, are they?
I'm glad we have this.
But Kinkaku knows how
this tool works. How am
I supposed to seal him
if he knows all
its tricks?
Well, HQ came up with
a strategy. Until I
know what it is, I'll
just keep this safe!
Sorry about that, but
I can't afford to
let you catch me.
Fire Style Squad!
Protect Darui!
Now!
Let's go!
(screaming)
Water Style Squad!
You weaklings!
Earth Style Squad!
I'm sorry about this...
Double Black Panthers!
Do you think
we did it?!
(gasp)
(screaming)
Ahh!
I'll tear you
apart!
(screaming)
They were all
taken down...
...by one man?
A barrage of Fire,
Water, Earth and
Lightning Styles had
no effect...
I'm so sorry,
everyone...
Shikaku, I can't
hold this jutsu
for long.
I know, let's
do this.
Darui...
It's Shikaku from
Headquarters!
Listen up...
I've been waiting
to hear from you...
You have the Kohaku
no Johei, right?
For this plan to be
successful, the Ino-
Shika-Cho Formation is
absolutely critical.
Please, hold on
until we get there.
Ino-Shika-Cho?
But Shikaku and
Inoichi are still
at HQ.
They're so far
away, and we've
lost so many men
already...
Holding it on is
such a tall order.
Where'd he go?
(forceful grunt)
Kikuchi, sir!
Sorry I'm late!
Reinforcements!
We've been waiting!
Now we can keep
on fighting!
HQ has a plan.
We'll strike at
Kinkaku with the
Ino-Shika-Cho
Formation.
Until they get here,
we have to hold
this location!
(cheering support)
They're on their way
right now? Then there's
no way we'll fail
to hold this line!
Shikamaru, Choji,
Ino, listen up!
I'm currently talking
directly to you via
Inoichi's jutsu. Listen
closely to what I'm
about to tell you.
I see...
So that's the
plan, huh?
I understand.
So we're supposed to
fight this legendary
monster Kinkaku who
nearly killed the
Second Hokage!
Things are becoming
a real drag.
Oh, man! I'm
getting scared.
Hold on! You boys
better not wimp
out on me.
Legends become
exaggerated over
time. And when an
old legend is
surpassed, new
legends are born!
He may have the
Nine Tails' power, but
we have the power of
the Ino-Shika-Cho bond.
The teamwork ninjutsu
of Ino-Shika-Cho is
one of the most
celebrated legends in
and of itself! Have
confidence and pride
in that!
Don't back down!
We must hold the line,
no matter what!
More reinforcements!
Sorry we're late!
So that's him?
How could he
do all of this?
Huh?
Reinforcements!
The Second Company
and the Fourth
Company's here!
So, uh, do you get
the feeling there's
a lot of hope
riding on us now?
That's the kind
of people we've
become?
It's making me
kinda nervous,
though...
Well I guess we're
just gonna have to
live up to their
expectations!
Hey, wait! They're
just the kids! Not
the real Ino-Shika-
Cho!
(disappointed groans)
Yeah... I kinda
figured they might
say that.
I did too...
Hey, come on now!
We're gonna start a
legend of our very
own, right here!
So let's get
going, guys!
Yeah, I
heard that.
Mmm-hmm!
Everyone, cover them!
(fighting grunts)
All of you are
merely third-rate
underlings!
Come on...
You're wimps. As
if you could bring
me down.
Human Boulder!
Why you!
Ahh!
Shadow Possession
complete!
One petty trick
after another!
Ugh! He's got a
lot of power!
Ha! This is nothing!
I can break this!
He broke the
Shadow Possession!
Die!
Now that was
excellent timing.
Whew, I got him!
Mind Transfer
Jutsu complete!
All right!
Kinkaku!
Yes!
Ahh!
Come back,
Ino! Now!
I can't believe
that we... touted
as the shining
light of the Cloud
...could be taken
down by the likes
of them!
Gold and silver coins
may be much shinier
and worth more than
bronze coins are.
But pool them, and
bronze coins are
worth more than gold
or silver alone.
You may be gold, but
it seems that you
were only fool's gold.
And that's why
we defeated you.
Sorry, but I told
you I was going to
strip away your gold
coating.
Ino!
Choji!
(coughing)
For being afraid,
you did really well,
Choji!
I think I must have
sweated off fifty
pounds from all that.
Well, if that's all,
then you're fine. You
look exactly the same
to me, Choji!
It all went
as planned!
(chuckle)
Good work, Choji!
(giggle)
Ino, you've gotten much
better at your speed and
with your control over
the Mind Transfer.
Units Six through Ten,
you help the injured
get to the rear! And the
rest of you, follow me!
(cheering)
I sealed away Kokinjo,
the rope that squeezes
out Spirit Words,
along with Kinkaku...
So we can't use the
other two ninja tools.
But, where'd the
Bashosen fan go?
Choji, Ino, Let's go!
Already?
C'mon, get up!
(fighting grunts)
Agh!
It's him!
Long time no see,
Ino-Shika-Cho brats!
If I remember
correctly, you're
Kakuzu...
We took the Kin.
The Gold Shogi
General is ours.
And we know
the moves...
Of Kaku the bishop.
You're good, so
we'll attack.
The brat who uses
shadows. Your being
here means only one
thing...
You must have
taken down Hidan.
Did he get his head
chopped off again
while he was praying?
Or since he's not
here, does that mean
he's still alive out
there somewhere?
Who even cares if
he's dead or alive?!
Hmph! So I'm on
defense with no rook
and my gold and silver
general's taken?
And this one
makes it five...
Wait, that's right.
If he's got five
hearts now, we gotta
stop him five times.
Yeah, you're
right about that.
I think it's time
to start the game
in Kaku mode.
(painful grunts)
Hmph! By the
way...
We've got our own
gold and silver shogi
pieces taken from
your side, too.
Don't you want
to know who
they are?
Lady Tsunade's
love, Dan Kato!
And also...
Your former teacher,
son of the Third
Hokage, Asuma Sarutobi!
(gasps)
Asuma Sensei!
The next episode is
a special one! Sakura
suddenly comes falling
out of the sky!
The shock of a
hard landing causes
her to lose her
memory!
Everyone in the
village lends a hand
to help her regain her
memories, but...
Just what in the
world is going on
here, anyway!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Road to Sakura.
I wonder if I'm
even in this one?!