Naruto...
Please, let all of us deal
with this Madara! I swear
we'll finish him off!
It'll be our first step in
stopping the curse of
hatred we've all been
under until now!
Like Madara, we Kage are
also guilty of stirring up
hate in the past.
It's our responsibility
to make things right!
Rest assured and
leave this to us!
And you...
You go and take care of the
other Madara, my boy!
That act will become the
first step in promoting hope
for the future.
The old one or the new one,
it doesn't really matter...
Only by defeating both
Madaras will we be able to
bring this war to an end!
We will all defend you
by fighting on this
battlefield!
So protect us through your
actions by fighting over
there on that battlefield!
Now, Clone Naruto... I entrust
you with this message from
all the Five Kage.
We'll win!
Yeah!
We'll win! For sure!
Hey...
Just chill out,
Naruto! Fool, ya fool!
Damn it, that thing is
really hard! I didn't
even crack it...
I could've simply passed
through you. But I guess it
doesn't matter if you
can't even crack the mask.
That cannot be all
you can manage.
What about your Nine
Tails power?
Lava Style: Scorching
Rocks Jutsu!
Whoa, yo!
Water Style: Aqua
Mirror Jutsu!
These guys...
...have the same
strength we do!
Is this-?
This jutsu Is it Utakata?
Get away from that girl!
A Shadow Clone?
Give it up; you're
coming with me!
No!
He's not your enemy!
He's protecting me!
Huh?!
This chakra I'm sensing...
Utakata, you were
a Jinchuriki?
You, too, huh?
I'd heard some rumors
that you'd gone missing,
but I really didn't
know what to believe.
So the Akatsuki got you?
Yeah...
After we went our separate
ways I ran into them, laying
in wait for me.
This is it, master; this
is the place where I first
met you.
Hotaru, will you wait here
for me for a little while?
Why, is there a problem?
I'm meeting the Anbu Black
Ops. I'm tired of all this
running.
I want to get permission
to travel and train you.
Great!
No response. Strange... Did
something happen to them?
The Six-Tails'
Jinchuriki Host...
Are you the ones who killed
Tsurugi and his men?
I'm going to build an
entirely new world. And
for that, I need you.
Well, really, I need the
Tailed Beast that's
inside you.
So that's it, then...
Now, Six-Tails.
You are mine.
[defiant yell]
So you're finally taking
this seriously.
[angry roar]
Ah yes, there it is. The
power that we're seeking...
[angry roar]
Summoning Jutsu!
Go!
[angry growling]
Six Tails is ours.
[defiant roar]
[growling]
I expected at least this
much of a fight out of you...
[growling]
Now come to me, Six Tails!
[attacking roar]
[roaring]
Please Hotaru...
You have to, you have
to live, live...
My master...
But why did you do it?
Why did you go into the
forest by yourself?!
If you'd just escaped
with Hotaru, you'd still be-
The Shinobi Tracking Unit
from the village was in
the forest. And I'd grown
tired of running...
I wanted to reconcile
with the village and
finally live in peace.
I wanted to stop living like
a fugitive always without a
home.
And I wanted to spare Hotaru
the pain of living a life
constantly on the run.
Utakata! But you--
I wonder why I even started
feeling that way. Why did I
wish for a dream like that?
I suppose it doesn't matter.
It's all meaningless now.
I convinced myself that the
master whom I'd once trusted
had betrayed me...
And so, I closed
off my heart.
I don't know how to trust
people anymore. And yet...
Hotaru was willing
to put her faith in
someone like me.
Hotaru was also burdened
with a fate she hid from
everyone around her.
In that way, she was just
like we Jinchuriki are.
I don't know, maybe somehow
she sensed that underneath
it all, the both of you
were very much alike...
Hotaru...
[sobbing]
I never wanted
to hurt anyone.
And yet, I hurt Naruto
and Sir Utakata with
my very own hands!
But look: I'm right here.
Naruto and I are fine!
[sobbing]
I saw it happen...
Hotaru...
I'm sorry... I betrayed
you, Sir Utakata.
Somebody like me should
just disappear along
with the Jutsu!
Don't say that!
I will not allow it!
A good student should
always listen to her master.
Did you say "master"?!
Come on.
Let's go.
Thank you.
What is it?!
What's wrong?
No!
You must leave!
Sir Utakata...
Please, just get away
from me! Go, run as
fast as you can!
Hotaru!
I've done all I can; I can't
suppress it any longer... Any
moment, the Forbidden Jutsu
is going to tear me
apart and explode.
It's all right.
Sir Utakata...
Just trust your master.
I was like a bubble floating
aimlessly in the wind
before I met Hotaru,
but then she showed me
the path to the truth.
I made up my mind right then
and there that I'd become
Hotaru's master...
How ironic that just as I
was about to make good on
my decision to start a new
life, my life was
taken from me.
Then I was resurrected, only
to discover I have no will
of my own and am forced
to walk a different path.
The ones who are
manipulating you also
used the Akatsuki,
and right now they're
determined to put the entire
world under their control.
Are you just gonna do what
someone like them tells you?
If you see Hotaru again, you
might be forced to fight her
without even being able
to say a word to her!
Inside, you still possess
the will to take yourself
back!
This fight is
meaningless for you-
Naruto...
I don't know if it's only
because of these strange
circumstances or not, but...
I just shared my true
feelings with you. Thank
you for listening...
Naruto!
Water Style: Bubble Jutsu!
Close one. Thanks
a lot, Octopops!
Huh?
Secret Ninjutsu!
Scaled Sneak Jutsu!
Yo, my shades are the best.
Light, with my eyes, don't
mess!
I can still see their evil
intent, too. This'll be
easy!
Yugito's here, too. Seems
these guys are all former
Jinchuriki.
On top of that, each of them
has a Sharingan in one eye
and a Rinnegan in the other...
They were robbed of their
lives, turned into pawns,
and then had those
disgusting things implanted
into them. Poor Yugito.
If things had gone
differently, you may
have ended up like
that, too. For real!
To see them all like that
fills me with rage and
grief. But me not getting
eyes like that is still
a big relief...
Your shades would hide them,
anyway. But if you don't
want to end up like that,
don't let your guard down!
Madara's eyes are the
exact same as that, too.
His new mask has got two
holes, not just one like
before.
That's not the only
difference. I had to
custom make this mask.
It's battle grade tough.
So the left eye that you
always kept hidden was a
Rinnegan just like the ones
belonging to Nagato and
to the other Madara.
We'll stop both of
you Madaras. You can
count on that!
Did you just say "both?"
Summoning Jutsu:
Reanimation.
Th- That's-!
Surely you didn't think that
I'd come unprepared to a
meeting with you?
See? You cannot refuse me.
Why you-- Where
did you get that?
Oh, I have my needs...
But don't worry, I haven't
told anyone else about this.
Damn that Kabuto...
What're you talking about,
"both," Naruto, ya fool?
That's Madara right over
there, ain't it, fool ya
fool?
[chuckling]
You can call me by my
past name, Tobi.
Now that the war has begun,
names are irrelevant.
Madara... Tobi... Call
me whatever you wish.
Who are you?
Just tell us, who
are you, really?
Nobody. I don't want to be
anybody. I just want to
fulfill Project Tsuki no Me.
That will be enough.
It is not worth living in
this world where only
despair exists.
You Jinchuriki had Tailed
Beasts forced upon you.
All you've ever experienced
is despair...
Am I wrong? Surely, you
ought to understand my
despair, at least a little...
And just who the hell
are you to decide...
...that having a Tailed Beast
makes me feel despair like
that?!
Even if you think that
this world is worthless.
Do you seriously think that
you can get away with
starting a war like this
and then just come along
and try to play that
you're nobody?
You piss me off...
I'm going to tear that
mask right off your face!
Sounds good, but
me first! Yeah!
Try to remove this mask...
...you'll end up
broken to pieces!
[confused gasp]
Eight Tails...
Nine Tails...
You shall be mine and then
I will achieve Project Tsuki
no Me!
What's going on? I thought
that their Tailed Beasts
were extracted from them!
I can only assume that
they were made back
into Jinchuriki after
they were reanimated...
This is just like the
time that I fought the
Six Paths of Pain.
It's the Rinnegan! Their
eyes are linked, hooked
up to each other!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Jinchuriki
vs. Jinchuriki!"
It's like Nagato's
Gedo Jutsu!