[sobbing]
You, there! Mistress?
What's the matter?
[shrieking]
[screaming]
[panting]
What's wrong, mister?
It just appeared, out
in the field!
What appeared? Is some
robber wanting to try
out his new sword?
There have been so
many disturbances
lately.
No, nothing like that!
It was a faceless thing!
What? Faceless? You
mean...
...faceless...
like this?!
AH! Where's your face?!
[laughing]
Sorry, I'm sorry. That
was just a wood clone.
Captain Yamato. That's
going too far!
[screaming]
I couldn't resist,
Naruto. What a
scaredy cat.
You know what, Captain
Yamato...? Your face is
bad for my heart.
Don't be upset, Naruto.
The fog's so thick,
there's nothing else to
do but tell stories.
Yeah, but a grown man
like you telling ghost
stories? Something's
wrong with you!
You're too easy to scare.
That's why he keeps
freakin' you out.
[chuckling]
I don't know what you
mean... Humph. Stories
like that don't scare me!
Oh, really? Okay,
then, Naruto, I'll tell
you the best one yet.
It's said that it appears
on foggy nights such as
this...
What's "it"?
It sails on darkened
seas, led by black crows
that guide the souls of
the dead.
A giant will o' the wisp
perched on the mast
announces its presence.
Then out of the fog
emerge the dead's mortal
remains...
And when you see it,
you're doomed to take a
journey by sea to the
land of the dead.
"It..." is the ghost
ship!
Souls of the dead...?!
[gasping]
You don't mean
this fog, do ya?!
That's right. The ghost
ship appears out of the
fog, Fog that's just like
this.
I'm just kidding! Ghost
ships don't exist! They're
just stories.
Oh, yeah, sure! I knew
that! I mean, of course
there's no such thing as
ghost ships!
I didn't believe you for
a second.
Oh, is that so? Well,
you could've fooled me.
Uh...
The wind just picked
up...
What's going on here...?
[gasping]
What in the--
It's a ghost ship!
No way. It
can't be...
"The Cursed Ghost Ship"
Aw, come on! You guys
aren't seriously thinking
of boarding a ghost ship,
are you?!
Naruto, there's no such
thing as a ghost ship,
not in real life.
Of course there is! Look
at that.
That ship's exactly how
Captain Yamato described
it.
Yes, I agree it's
suspicious-looking.
However, maritime law says
we must examine all lost ships.
Look at it this way, the
sooner we check it out,
the sooner we'll be back
on our own boat.
Just accept it.
Oh, just great... If this
is the plan, I should
have stayed back with
Bushier Brow Sensei!
[groaning]
Naruto...
It's all about guts! If
you have them, whatever
you face-
You're seasick! Get over
that with guts!
C'mon, back me up here,
Aoba!
Huh?
[balancing]
Wait!
Hey...! Aoba? Captain
Yamato?
[pounding and sweeping]
Hmm?
Man, I am busy, busy,
busy here!
Hey...
[grunting]
My face isn't the
floor, you know!
Busy, busy, busy...!
Heh!
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Busy...!
Busy, busy, busy...!
Yo, kid!
He's not joking about
being busy!
Oh, okay! That's how you
steer the ship!
Huh?
Boy, you sure do a good
job with this broom!
Hands off!
Huh?
The Captain gave that to
me. It's very precious.
Oh... Sure thing...
Man, I gotta say, for
a kid, you sure do put
in a lot of work. Isn't
it hard by yourself?
Tell you what, why don't
I help you out, here?
Well...
Two hands are better than
one!
In fact, a whole bunch of
hands will be even better
than just two of them!
I kinda get the feeling
that you won't be willing
to talk to me unless you get
to finish all your work first.
[grunting]
Here ya go! Here ya go!
Huuuuuuuuuuaaah!
[stretching]
Boy, am I tired!
Say, mister--
Hm? You can call
me Naruto, kid.
Naruto. I'm Hishaku.
Well... nice to meet you.
Hey, you're a ninja,
aren't you, Naruto?
Are you strong?
Of course, I'm strong!
I'm gonna be Hokage
one day!
Hokage...?
Yeah! The strongest and
most important ninja in
my whole village.
Oh, really, is that
all? Then my Captain is
even greater than your
Hokage.
What?!
The Captain's strong,
too, and not just
important. He's also kind
and considerate!
I'm gonna be captain,
one day, too!
Now, just hold on!
My Hokage is strong and
important and kind and
considerate just like
your captain!
And not just that, but
generous, too and uh, the
best!
No, my Captain is!
Hokage!
Captain!
[growling]
[laughing]
I guess we both have
something that we're
aiming for!
Mm-hm.
Hey, um, teach me that
thing!
What thing?
You know, the way you
tapped the broom before,
like a drum or something.
That was really awesome.
Thanks, it is pretty
cool, huh?
The captain taught it
to me. He also gave me
this broom.
Oh...!
You mind if we join
this conversation?
So, listen, Captain
Yamato. I took a look around,
but it's just an ordinary
ship on the inside.
Seems we're in luck.
It isn't a ghost ship
at all.
[laughing]
A ghost ship?! That's
just a silly superstition.
Okay, but--
Isn't that light made by
the souls of the dead?
What, the glow on the
mast?
No way! Now, among
sailors, that light is
considered to be a sign
of good luck...
But it's just static
electricity!
Static- elec-?
But what about the crows
up there?
You don't normally see
crows on the ocean.
You're right, but they're
not crows.
They're just seabirds
that got dirty 'cause of
the ash from our
smokestack!
Oh... Seriously?
Now... No more talk about
this being a ghost ship.
Aoba and I took the
liberty of checking the
ship's interior...
We didn't find any
other sailors onboard
besides you.
What happened to them
all, Hishaku, do you
know?
Yeah, I mean, a ship of
this size requires at
least several deckhands
in order to run it.
Hey, that's right.
Where's the captain
you mentioned?
Mm.
The crew is all gone...
So, then... something
happened?
Yeah, that's right...
Deep beneath the ocean's
surface, there lurks
something.
That's even more terrifying
than any ghost ship!
It's come back!
What has?
The monster! The
legendary creature!
The Skeleton Crab!
Crab?
But this isn't just some
ordinary crab! It's
huge, the size of an
island.
Its shell is hard as a
rock. And if you're
caught between its
pinchers, it's over!
It can crush
anything!
And the barnacles that
are attached to its shell
can swallow a person
whole!
[gulping]
The Captain and the
rest of the crew--
That monster killed
all of them.
Naruto! Ninja are strong,
right?
Please destroy it! You
have to avenge the Captain
and the crew!
[gasping]
[grunting and gasping]
Captain!
[grunting]
Captain Yamato!
[screeching]
It'll get us again!
Just leave this to me!
I'll destroy this thing,
Hishaku!
Quick! Aoba, take Hishaku
to our ship!
Tell everyone what's
going on!
But, you-
There's no time to stand
here and talk!
One of us has to save
Captain Yamato and stop
that monster.
And the other has
to warn our ship!
Each of us can only do
one of those things.
And you can probably
explain everything to the
others more calmly than I
can.
Naruto's really grown
up...
You got it! I'll go and
warn the others!
Naruto... aren't you
scared? How can you take
on that giant beast?
I told you! I'm gonna
become the Hokage.
If it's for my comrades,
I'm not afraid of
anything.
For your comrades...
Hishaku... You're still
so young.
You must live. Your whole
life's ahead of you!
I'm so scared, Captain!
Please! Stay with me!
I've had this broom since
the first day I climbed
onboard this ship.
But Now it's all yours.
[gasping]
These bristles may be
worn down, but they carry
my spirit in them.
If you take it, then I'll
know for sure that it's
in good hands.
But, Captain...
[screeching]
I still have work I have
to do.
It's my job to stay with
the ship right till the
very end,
for all of my loyal
mates who believed
in me.
That's a ship captain's
duty.
Just watch! I'll avenge
your captain and crew, I
promise!
That's the hero who saved
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Naruto Uzumaki.
Come on, let's get back
onto our ship.
Mm.
It's time to pay for what
you've done!
If you aren't some ghost
crab, then you don't
scare me one little bit!
Rasengan!
Damn it!
Man, that shell's
hard. How am I gonna
get through it?!
Huh?!
[grunting]
Ugh, not only is that
thing strong, it's also
fast!
[gasping]
Aoba, our ship is swaying
badly! What's going on?
Just hang on. We have
to get out of this area
as fast as we can.
Naruto's doing his best
to buy us time with that
beast.
[gasping]
Captain, help me! Give me
the courage I need!
Captain Yamato!
I can't do anything big,
or I could hit Captain
Yamato!
But I have to save him
fast!
Damn it!
Not good...
Everyone, give me
strength!
Uh!
[horn blowing]
[grunting]
Our ship's free!
Huh? Did Hishaku do
that?! Thanks a lot!
Captain Yamato!
I was careless. I
can't believe I got
caught like that!
Don't worry about it.
Huh?!
[gasping]
Hey, Naruto!
Now's our chance, Captain
Yamato! But that thing's
shell is incredibly hard!
All right, then. I'll aim
for the soft area
under its belly!
Wood Style Jutsu!
Go get 'em,
Naruto!!
You got it!
Well? Can you give me a
little of your courage,
Hishaku?
Uh-huh!
Get ready to say goodbye,
you monster!
Rasengan!
Good job, Naruto,
you did it.
Yeah! Thanks to
my pal Hishaku.
Way to go, kid. Your
dream came true before
mine.
I haven't known you for
long, but still, you're a
great captain.
Kind of like the Hokage!
Thank you, Naruto.
I know that I'll always
feel some regret...
...cause I wasn't able to
fight with the others
back then.
But now, since you've
avenged all my shipmates,
the heaviness in my heart
is gone.
Aw, come on... I was
only able to take down
that crab because of you.
I'd say... You and I are
shipmates now after going
through that!
That's for sure!
Huh?
It's time to say
good-bye, Naruto.
Huh?! What's going on?
What-?! Hey! Where'd you
go, Hishaku?!
[horn blowing]
Huh?
Hishaku! No one blames
you for what happened.
You know what your
problem is? You're too
honorable, kid.
You couldn't bring
yourself to rest in
peace, so neither could
we, until now!
[laughing]
I'm sorry, you guys.
What? You don't need to
apologize.
All of us were just so
glad when that damn crab
got hit. And that was
thanks to you!
[cheering]
All right, how about we
liven things up the usual
way?
Right!
[pounding and sweeping]
Naruto! Goodbye!
Thanks! Take care!
Huh?
Right. I will! Same to
all of you!
Goodbye! Have a
safe journey!
Wha--- what
the hell?
[screaming]
A ghost ship!
The rudder isn't working!
This sure is some storm,
isn't it!
What's going to happen
if we can't escape this
current?
It should be fine! If we
continue like this,
we'll get back on
course.
All right, then it's
straight on to the Land
of Lightning from here!
Wait, Naruto... !
Something's coming!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Battleship
Island!
It's an attack! Wait,
what is that...?