[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I'm a frog.
A frog.
-Can you hear the froggy song?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Become one with Gamatatsu.
-Can you hear the froggy song?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Read his
thoughts, and respond to them.
-Yes, I hear the froggy song.
-Ribbity, ribbity.
-Ribbity, ribbity,
ribbity, ribbity.
-Can you hear the froggy song?
-Yes, I hear the froggy song.
Ribbity, ribbity, ribbity,
ribbity, ribbitt, ribbity,
ribbity.
Naruto, you don't look like
you've opened up your mind yet.
Don't focus on his
movements so much.
Try and feel Gamatatsu's
emotional vibes,
then channel them
using your own style.
-I'm trying!
-Ow!
-Uh-- heh, heh.
Um-- sorry about that.
-(SINGING) Everyone, look,
Gamakichi is singing.
Hear his noble song!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit,
ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Everyone, look,
Gamatatsu too is singing.
Hear his noble song.
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit,
ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Connect
with Gamatatsu's heart.
-Whoa.
Check out that cloud.
It looks like a big cream puff.
Yummers.
GAMAKICHI (VOICEOVER):
Well, maybe their thoughts
are as one.
-Whoa, hey.
Gamatatsu, did you
just feel that?
-What do I look like,
an amphibian psychic?
[laughter]
-Hey!
A butterfly!
-Huh?
-1, 2, 3, shoot.
1, 2, 3, shoot.
-Who's my main man?
-Gamatatsu!
-That doesn't
really show you guys
are in tune with each other.
-Can you hear the froggy song?
Yes, I hear the froggy song.
Ribbity, ribbity, ribbity,
ribbity, ribbity, ribbity,
ribbity!
-I can't move anymore.
Huh?
-Here.
You look like you could use one.
Trust me, kiddo.
Everyone who knows you
can see it plain as day.
-Huh?
-Gamatatsu, Gamakichi, Sakura
and Tsunade, and myself.
Every single one of
us knows how hard
you've been working lately.
And the only mystery
is how you keep it up.
-I don't know.
Don't like the idea
of giving up, I guess.
And Sasuke.
-Hm?
-I can't help but wonder
what he would think.
If he'll ever look at me and
acknowledge all that I've done.
-That would be great,
wouldn't it, kid?
-Hm?
What?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): I shouldn't
tell him about the Akatsuki.
-Hey, you two.
Up and at 'em.
-Hm?
-I have a few things to take
care of, so I'm heading out.
I want both of you guys to
go back to the Leaf Village.
Help Naruto with the
rest of his training, OK?
-No problem.
We'll take care of it.
-There'll be some snacks
in it for us, right?
-Yeah, yeah, sure.
I'll be counting on you.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
Keep at it.
One day you really
will be Hokage.
Hold onto that unyielding
gutsiness of yours.
No matter what.
TSUNADE: A new enemy?
PAKKU: That's right.
A formidable one.
I saw a bit of their handiwork.
TSUANDE: Which is why
you're giving me this.
There's something inside
that crystal, isn't there?
-The enemy's jutsu took
out one of Shino's insects.
Kakashi wants it
analyzed right away.
TSUANDE (VOICEOVER):
It can't be.
Does that mean the
rumors are true?
-Shizune.
I want this analyzed.
Get it to the lab.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Say what?
Are you telling me he
just took off again?
-Afraid so.
But here, he ask me to
pass this along for him.
-Give it.
-Round up all your stuff, kid.
We're going home.
-Hm?
What is it?
-Look at that.
This high up, you can
see the whole valley.
We just came from down there.
-Lord Orochimaru
will be waiting.
Come along, now.
-Yes.
Of course.
-You smell something, boy?
[whine]
-Kiba, you find anything?
-Nu-uh.
Not even a whiff,
Kakashi-sensei.
-My Byakugan's not picking
up anything, either.
[screech]
-A bat?
-There are some signs.
-Huh?
Where?
-I'm talking about
one of my insects.
Don't get so excited.
-Just your bugs.
Don't do that.
Last count, you had something
like 10, 000 of them, OK?
The fact that you found one
isn't really that surprising.
-But this one came in
contact with the enemy.
And the fact that it survived
makes it an asset to us.
-What kind of asset?
-It presumably got hit
by the enemy's jutsu.
Yet it's still here.
-What are you saying?
It's developed some
sort of immunity?
-Could be.
And my insects have
a short life span.
A few hours at most.
It wouldn't take long to breed
more of them that are immune.
-Are you kidding me?
That's amazing.
-It's just a possibility.
I don't know if it'll work.
But I should try to find
as many survivors as I can.
-Don't worry.
We'll help you look for them.
-Right.
We can handle it.
-That's all right.
-What do you mean?
-I'm the one who
should look for them.
You need to stay put.
if you guys start
tramping around,
you'll end up stepping on some.
I can't have that.
-If you're going
to shoot us down,
you could be a little
nicer about it.
-I didn't want to waste time
dancing around the issue.
-I think we're all set, then.
Shino will start
rounding them up.
The rest of us will get
back on the enemy's trail.
-Fine.
Let's go, Akamaru.
[bark]
[laughter]
-Snake eyes again.
Sorry, fellas.
-You wouldn't be cheating,
now, would you, bro?
-Course not.
I don't know what to tell you.
Some of us are just
born lucky, my friend.
-Sure.
That's why I'm losing.
You'd obviously have
no problem with me
inspecting those
dice of yours, right?
-She's late.
-Aw, man.
Come on.
One more roll.
Huh?
-You want to try?
It's a good way to kill time.
Ignoring me, huh?
Well, that's fine.
I have to say, though,
it's a little surprising.
I can't believe you're still
here, waiting on Guren.
I don't know.
You seemed so defiant.
I thought you'd have used
this opportunity to escape.
-There's no point in running.
I'm no match for her.
-Well, well.
I wasn't expecting that.
So you're going to fall in
line like a good boy, huh?
-What about you lot?
You in or out?
-Us?
-You knew the deal
from the beginning.
That we'd eventually
have to fight
for our survival in that place.
You formed a group.
Banded together
to survive, right?
I can see it.
[laughter]
-Sharp one, aren't you?
We did, indeed.
It's not that surprising,
though, is it?
When your back's
against the wall,
it's good to have
friends, right?
We agreed to take care of each
other when push came to shove.
The ones who overestimated
themselves and failed
to use their heads--
they're all dead.
The way I look at it, we made
it this far using brain power.
Though I suppose if that
battle had gone on any longer,
we would have eventually gone
and turned on each other.
You, however, didn't
need anyone else.
You were strong
enough on your own.
When we were fighting
individually,
we had to make sure we
kept our distance from you.
But there are four of us now.
As long as we all stick
together, we can't be beaten.
Now we're all one big family,
though, working under Guren.
You can be a team player,
can't you, big guy?
Huh?
-Man.
She couldn't find a
better hideout than this?
I mean, seriously, what's
wrong with Guren, leaving us
in this creaky old dump?
-I'm going out on patrol.
Find anything out there?
-Akamaru?
What is it, boy?
-Deliver this information.
Fast as you can.
-I thought you said you
were going out on patrol?
-Just clearing my head first.
I'm heading out now, actually.
-All right, then.
I'll go with you.
-Hm?
You're full of
surprises, aren't you?
Does this mean you're
following my advice?
-A dog whistle?
-Yeah.
Akamaru said he
heard one for sure.
-Does that mean our enemy
is working with a dog, too?
-I kind of doubt it.
Trying to cover up human
scent is difficult enough.
With a dog, it's
near impossible.
And if they had a
dog, Akamaru and I
would have smelled him by now.
-So then, why a dog whistle?
-Wish I could tell ya.
-Know where it came from?
-I have no idea.
But they're not that far off.
That much I do know.
-I've finally made it back.
The first order of business
is to stop at Ichiraku.
I need to recharge a
bit before I train.
KONOHAMARU: Brother Naruto.
-Huh?
-I'll bet you were working
on a naughty new jutsu
out at the hot springs, right?
So I might as well show
you my latest Sexy Jutsu.
-Ah!
Wait a second, Konohamaru!
[scream]
-You think buying
me one bowl of ramen
makes up for the
konk you gave me?
-There's a time and place
for that kind of jutsu,
and that wasn't it.
Summoning Jutsu!
-Oh, man.
So these two guys are
your summons, Naruto?
-Actually, I usually
go even bigger.
But these two small fries should
do for right now, I think.
-Who are you kiddin', here?
You're our dad's henchman,
in case you forgot.
-Come on, just be cool, OK?
I'm trying to impress
this kid over here.
Now then, my amphibian
friend, let's get to work!
-Hey, brother.
I wonder what
today's snack'll be?
I'm on pins and needles.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Aw, man.
I completely forgot
about the snacks.
-Uh, I think we'll save the
treat for after our training
today.
-What the-- you called us here,
and you don't have any food?
I'm so out of here.
Come on, big brother.
-OK, OK, I got it!
Snacks!
Will you go get us some
snacks, Konohamaru?
This should cover it.
-Yeah, no problem.
-Sweet!
-Snacktime, snacktime!
-His eating habits are gonna
put me right in the poor house.
Huh?
What the-- you
finished 'em already?
-Awesome!
This guy's a pro!
-And disgusting.
All right, listen up.
Help me out today,
and Pervy Sage'll
give you more snacks than you've
ever dreamed of in your life.
Now come on, let's get to work.
-Roger that!
So--
-Well, we were focusing on
the timing when we stopped.
Why don't we just
pick it up there?
-What were we doing, again?
-You go ahead and
spit out some water,
and when the timing is right,
I'll layer in my chakra.
You got it?
Now fire off that
water pistol of yours,
and I'll try to time
out when to come in.
-Water pistol.
I don't get it.
What water pistol?
-You know.
Just use your water style jutsu
to shoot out a beam of water.
-So, water style?
-Huh?
-Hey, brother, can you
explain to this guy
that I can't do
that sort of thing?
-You're a frog!
Water style is your strong suit!
-It's the truth.
He can't do any sort
of water style jutsu.
-You've gotta be kidding me!
Then why the hell have I
been training with him?
-He can only do what he can do!
Quit yelling!
-Then you swap in, Gamakichi.
What's the big deal?
Are you gonna help
me out, or what?
-I-- I can't.
-Yeah?
And why's that?
-Come on.
-What are you muttering about?
Say what?
I can't hear ya.
-It's just I'm--
-Come again?
Speak up, already.
-It's just water style--
-Spit it out, will ya?
-I don't do water style, either!
-What?
[theme music]
KAKASHI: How'd it go?
Any leads?
-I wasn't able to find anything.
-Yeah, same here.
The weather's making it
hard to pick up a scent.
KAKASHI: Not surprising
in this downpour.
-Hm?
Look.
Even the bats are
taking shelter.
Since--
-Kiba, what's wrong?
-So that's it, huh?
I know what the dog
whistle was about.
Kakashi-sensei, if
I'm right, the enemy
may already know our position.
NARUTO: Next time,
A Night Of Rain.