-[grunt]
-Lady Chiyo.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
How is she still moving?
Is the old bag still
controlling her?
No.
She couldn't generate such
complicated movements.
Not in her condition.
Somehow that girl is
moving on her own.
But how?
I know my poison affected her.
-Sakura, how can you be--
-I used the antidote.
Thank goodness it worked.
-An Antidote?
But when did you get that?
-The same time I made
the antidote for Kankuro
in the Hidden Sand Village.
SAKURA: I never imagined
I'd find such a wide variety
of medicinal herbs here
in the Hidden Sand.
-Well, we try.
Our soil's not very well
suited to growing them.
We can't grow much scurvy
grass, for example.
SAKURA: That's all
right, there's enough.
I can make three
doses of antidote.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I was
barely able to make three.
I gave one of them to
Kankuro to heal him.
-That's right, drink it all.
-[gasp] [coughs]
-There, you should
be all right now.
Just lie back and rest.
And don't move around
'till the numbness passes.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I knew
our adversary used poison,
so I brought the rest with
me in hypodermic form.
-Of course.
And that's how you--
-Yes.
I used one of the
doses on myself.
Catch is, the antidote is only
potent for about three minutes.
While it's working,
whatever poison
you're exposed to gets
converted into harmless protein.
-I understand.
-That's why I didn't
try to fight back.
I didn't want Sasori to
know I had this antidote.
I knew he'd reveal his plan
once he let his guard down.
I had to take the chance.
So I waited until the
last possible moment.
This is it.
There's only one dose left.
Here, I want to keep
this with you Lady Chiyo.
-Hm.
[gasp]
-What's wrong?
Are you OK?
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Wait a second,
there's no way the
poison was neutralized.
-[gasp]
-I'll just let the
poison take Its course.
You'll wish I hadn't.
Your suffering will
be unimaginable.
But it will be over in
less than three days.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Don't tell me
they analyzed the poison
I used in that fight.
Impossible.
Even if they were
somehow able to isolate
the individual
components, they wouldn't
be able to prepare an
antidote that easily.
The antidote is prohibitively
difficult to mix.
If there's even the
slightest mistake--
Even I needed to reference
the mix ratio table,
and I created it.
-Don't worry, I'll heal you.
For the next three minutes or
so, his poison won't effect me.
Which means we don't have a
lot of time to finish this.
-Right.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
Did the witch do this?
No.
I've got more medical skill
than anyone in the Sand Village.
Certainly more
than the old lady.
There's no way she
could have cracked
a poison this intricate.
Hmph.
Isn't this kid a
medical ninja too?
And if memory serves, she's
from the Leave Village.
The Leaf's current
Hokage is Tsunade,
and she's known as a
world-class medical ninja.
That's it.
She made the antidote.
[theme music]
-Thank you.
My had feels fine now, Sakura.
-Oh?
Good.
[heavy breathing]
[yell]
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
Powerful attacks, evasion,
healing wounds.
All of that must use a
considerable amount of chakra.
Her body has probably
already reached its limit.
-So annoying.
This is taking so
long, I'll never
get back to my man, Sasori.
I know, I'll use the rest
of my detonating clay,
and show him what a
real artist can do.
However, if I'm
going to do that,
I'll have to get rid of
the copy ninja first.
It might have taken awhile,
but this is worth the wait.
-[grunt]
-What?
These aren't like the
bird ones from before.
They're smaller.
Is that so they won't get
picked off by shuriken?
Why so many?
Judging from the size
of their hind legs,
I'd say their special
ability is jumping.
And I guess it's going to come
down to a battle of speed.
Naruto, wait up!
-You're slowing me
down Kakashi-Sensei,
I'm going on ahead.
-Don't do anything reckless.
-Yeah, yeah I know.
--[sigh] This might be a
bit of a sticky situation.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I staunched
the major bleeding anyway.
Time to refocus the rest
of my chakra to attack.
We've only got three
minutes to do this.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
Three minutes,
or we won't have another chance.
-We're running low on time.
Are you healed enough
for a fight Lady Chiyo?
-Let's go, Sakura.
It's time we put an end to this.
-Got to think.
I can't waste time
having a staring contest
with these things.
If I leave Naruto on his
own, he could lose control
at any moment.
They won't put me
fall back and build up
enough speed to break past them.
They're maintaining
this distance.
In that case-- Come on, guys.
Stay right on my tail.
There they go.
Huh? [gasp]
-That takes care of him.
Hmph.
-That wasn't-- Kakashi-Sensei.
-At last.
Now it's just the two of us.
-[growl]
-Aw, don't scowl like that.
And here I was about to
let you see your friend.
-[growl]
-Oh that's right,
you're a Jinchuriki too.
I bet seeing him like
this drives you crazy.
-Give him back right now!
-Don't do it.
NARUTO: Kakashi-Sensei.
-Aw, man.
I could've sworn you just
bought it back there.
-Sorry.
But it wasn't the
real me that blew up.
Next time you should
teach your critters
to tell the difference between
a real human and a shadow clone.
That is, if there
is a next time.
-Don't move!
-I could say the same to you.
It'll be all right.
We will get Gaara back.
So calm down.
-My man Sasori is
going to yell at me
again for not being prepared.
What can I say?
Planning out every little
insignificant detail
ahead of time just
isn't my style.
I prefer to stay
flexible dealing
with unexpected situation.
Developing that kind of
sophisticated mindset
is the mark of a true artist.
Let's see, what to do now.
-Listen Naruto, you're not
used to fighting an opponent
like this.
And that's not all.
You're a close combat fighter,
he excels at long range.
That makes him your worst enemy.
There are only two ways
to beat this kind of foe.
One is to force him to
fight up close and personal.
Your only other option is
to beat him at his own game.
-What?
How can we do that?
-Depending on which
strategy is chosen,
you'd either need a
long range specialist,
or someone on your
team who can use long
range ninjutsu to support
that kind of distance combat.
If you don't have
one or the other,
then there's no way
you'll beat him, period.
Now if you had the superior
intellect of Shikamaru,
that would be a different story.
-Spell it out, will you?
Which one are you,
Kakashi-Sensei?
-Ah.
Me, huh?
Well I have a superior intellect
like Shikamaru, I'm a Jonin,
and I can sustain
long range battle.
-Then we meet all the
conditions, right?
-That's why I told
you to calm down.
-Well let's hurry
up and get to it!
-It's not as simple
as it sounds.
We can't just chase after him.
He'll never leave himself open.
-Now you're within range.
-[gasp]
-[chuckle]
-Well my mission is to clear.
-He infiltrated the
Hidden Sand Village
and defeated Gaara
all by himself.
And even more dangerous, he's
a member of the Akatsuki.
-Well, I suppose I shouldn't
go easy on them, huh?
-It's a tough challenge.
All we can do is try and
punch hole in his defenses.
We're going to have
to work together.
If you were following
my train of thought,
then keep listening.
I've got a plan.
-OK Sakura, Let's get him.
-Right.
SASORI (VOICEOVER): Hmph.
Fine, I'll admit it, she's
more impressive than I thought.
Never thought I'd see the
Third Kazekage destroyed.
And it's probably a waste
to use other human puppets.
-I haven't been forced to
solve a problem this way
since I joined the Akatsuki.
I wonder how long it's been.
-[gasp] Wh-- What is that?
-Now I see.
The reason he looks exactly
the same as the day he left.
Of course age
doesn't affect him.
The reason is staring
us right in the face.
-Oh, yes.
It's been awhile indeed
since I last used myself.
-He's actually a human puppet.
-You all set?
-Yeah, I got it.
Don't worry.
-Here we go.
-Hm?
What the--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Hold on,
if his entire body is a puppet,
then that means all of the
weapons hidden inside his body
are covered with
that poison as well.
-Something wrong?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It's
already been over a minute
since I gave myself
the antidote.
-I'm sorry, weren't you
supposed to finish me off?
Well if you aren't
going to attack me--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): The
effects of the antidote
will wear off in less
than two minutes.
That's all I've got.
Somehow I have to draw him into
close combat and defeat him.
And I've got to do it fast.
-Then I'll have to
make the first move.
You think you can hide from me?
Well, what are you
going to do now?
[theme music]
ANTIQUES HOST (VOICEOVER): And
now, time for Antique Ninja
Treasure.
Today, Lady Chiyo has
brought us a unique item.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): It's one of
the First Puppeteer Monzaemon
finest works.
ANTIQUES EXPERT (VOICEOVER):
If this is genuine,
it's a historical find.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
No ifs about it.
ANTIQUES HOST
(VOICEOVER): And what
does the owner think it's worth?
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Worth?
Please, it's priceless.
ANTIQUES HOST (VOICEOVER):
OK, and what about our expert?
ANTIQUES EXPERT (VOICEOVER):
Well, it is a truly fine work.
ANTIQUES HOST
(VOICEOVER): Oh, looks
like they made a decision.
Open the bidding!
BIDDERS (VOICEOVER): 1,
10, 100, 1,000, 10,000.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
Puppet Fight, 10 Versus 100.
-Hey, Sasori my man?
-Yeah?
-I was wondering, why did
Orochimaru leave the Akatsuki?
-Well Itachi ditched him.
-Hm?
What does that mean?
-Orochimaru developed
a re-animation jutsu.
He takes over people's body
so he can live forever.
The story goes, he
tried to use the jutsu
to take over Itachi's
body, but he failed.
-Really?
-Since then, Orochimaru
has been switching
the younger and
stronger bodies, one
after another, trying
to live forever.
-Ha.
That's stupid.
-Hm?
-Transient beauty that's
gone in the blink of an eye.
Now that is truly valuable.
-What's the point
of having anything
that's gone so quickly?
What's valuable is having
something that never wears
away, that lasts
for an eternity.