I'm certain.
It's Orochimaru's.
An old hideout.
That's just like Kabuto
to take advantage of an
old asset.
Wait. They're with us.
Captain Mitarashi.
I've come with an order
from the Village.
Sai will return home.
And you are to continue
the mission to track Kabuto.
We are here to assist
you with that.
You can give me
information, too;
Yamato rushed back in
the middle of a mission.
So what's
happened?
The Akatsuki mounted
an attack on the
Hidden Leaf Village.
It's destroyed,
and many injured.
And Lady Tsunade
is in a coma.
What did you say?!
And now, Lord Danzo has
taken over as Hokage.
How'd such a thing
happen so quickly?
I can give you all the
details later on, Captain.
Well, Sai?
Right.
Sai and I spent a
lot of time together
on this mission.
But he remained
distant to the end.
Lord Danzo...
is now Hokage?
The essence of a ninja
is to operate in secret.
But there are times when a
man who moves in the shadows
must step out into the light.
And for me, that time is now.
I hope that I can
count on your
continued loyalty.
[all]
Yes, sir!
The Sixth Hokage Danzo
[sigh]
What to do...
What now?!
It's just, what if there
are a ton of really
pretty girls in the
Hidden Leaf Village?
And what if all those
beautiful women
totally come after me?
I was trying to figure
out what I'd do.
Oh, yeah, I see!
Why not just date all
of them since you're
such a ladies man?
Left and right,
up and down!
Yeah, but,
When it's time to leave
the Hidden Leaf,
What if they tell
me they love me and
can't bear to be
separated from me?
What am I going to do
when that happens?
I'm scared that they'll
suggest a suicide pact!
Do you want to be
drowning in girls or not,
which is it?!
Look, we haven't even
reached the Hidden
Leaf Village yet!
Stop getting so carried
away about the damn
girls! It's creepy!
Come to think of it, Karui,
maybe a handsome guy with a
super good-looking face
will hit on you.
Just say handsome guy!
But you know, now that
you mention it, a
handsome, rich, famous
ninja smitten with me...
That wouldn't be very
far-fetched, at all!
You're overthinking things.
There's no way.
No way at all!
That's enough...
...out of you, you idiot!
What are you doing?
What if that stone hits
a boulder and smashes
it into pieces...
And those pieces destroy
an even bigger bolder and
cause a big rockslide...
And those rocks fall
onto the Hidden Leaf
Village, and wreck it?
You're the one that's
thinking too much,
you idiot!
[Karui]
No way...
I didn't do it on
purpose, it was
just a little rock!
Oh Karui, what have
you done this time?
There's no way.
Come on, let's
find someone.
Hey, you! Who are you?!
I'm Samui of the
Hidden Cloud.
I am a messenger from our
leader, the Raikage.
From Lord Raikage?
Please pardon our welcome
earlier. We're all a bit on
edge since the attack.
I was surprised not to
run into any Hidden
Leaf lookouts,
and then to find the
village in such a
state, What happened?
Hey, here's that stone you used
to destroy the Leaf Village.
It was the Akatsuki.
Precautions are being taken,
You want it?
and security will
be tightened shortly.
Aah! That thing had
nothing to do with it!
In any case, I need to
arrange an audience
with the Hokage.
I bear a letter from the
Raikage addressed to her.
Well, actually...
Is something wrong?
That hurts!
Don't tell me I'm going
to get a lump on my head!
Enough!
Unbelievable.
What horrible timing.
There hasn't been a single
piece of good news coming
through the coded channels.
This is calling for
a Five Kage Summit
Conference!
There, you see? Wait, what?!
What's that?!
The Hokage's
comatose?!
Yes, but I'm her aide, so
I can simply accept the
letter on her behalf.
If it's uncertain when
she'll regain
consciousness, The
acting Hokage will do.
I'd like to have the letter
read, And replied to.
The Raikage cannot wait.
Yes, but...
That woman there is no
longer the Hokage.
I was recently appointed
the Sixth Hokage.
Now hand the letter
over to me, and I'll
answer it.
No! It can't
be! Danzo?!
What's wrong? Does Lord Raikage
want a reply or doesn't he?!
Sasuke, hmm?
So it has come
to this.
Sir? Your response?
[Kiba]
There they are!
Hey!
Huh?
Kiba!
What's wrong?!
Listen up.
And just
stay calm!
Lady Tsunade's been
relieved of her title!
What?!
Yeah, the Sixth Hokage is
somebody named Danzo.
I don't know much,
but I think he's some
behind-the-scenes guy.
Did you say Danzo?!
Danzo...
This can't be good.
And that isn't
the only shocker!
The Sixth Hokage declared
Sasuke a Rogue Ninja and
approved his elimination!
Wait, just what do
you mean by that?!
I don't know, I'm just
telling you what I heard!
It means they can't
wait until Lady Tsunade
recovers. It's not
unreasonable.
But Kakashi...
Sasuke's a Rogue Shinobi.
Standard operating
procedure is to erase him.
It's only because of Lady
Tsunade that he's been
allowed to live this long.
Well, then, I'm going
to talk to Danzo!
Sakura, wait. Barging
into his office won't
solve anything.
How dare they do this
when Lady Tsunade's
unconscious!
And what about Sasuke?
You can't expect me to
just keep quiet!
And I'm going
with you, too.
Calm down,
both of you.
At a time like this,
staying calm is crucial
or everything will get
out of hand.
And how are we supposed
to stay calm?! I won't
let them go after Sasuke!
I said wait!
Danzo has already
anticipated your
exact reaction.
So you go see
him, then what?
We won't do anything
violent! We're only going
to ask him to change his
decision about Sasuke!
Do you really believe
that he'll agree with
whatever you have to say?
No way.
It may be just the Feudal
Lords' appointment without
the Jonin Assembly's vote
of confidence yet,
but Danzo is Hokage.
If you play this wrong,
you'll be thrown in prison.
Fine, I don't care!
I'm going!
Yeah, me too!
Wait, guys. Just hold up.
[Kakashi]
Naruto, the Nine-Tails
is inside you.
Yeah, I know that;
what about it?
Look, Danzo would
like nothing better
than to confine you
to this village.
Do you really want to be
locked up in jail?
Because that's exactly
what he wants.
And then you won't be able
to go look for Sasuke.
Don't make a
scene right now.
Tch!
[Sai]
You wanted to see me?
Observe Naruto.
If you see anything
out of the ordinary,
report it to me
immediately.
Yes, sir.
Um...
Excuse me, may I ask
you a question, sir?
What is it?
Naruto...
What do you plan
to do with him?
Don't worry.
Naruto is the
Village's hero
right now.
All of the villagers trust and
love him. Even more than they
do me, the Sixth Hokage.
If I were to do something
to him now, it would affect
my new position.
This a crucial time,
right before the Jonin's
vote of confidence.
Still, Naruto is
a Jinchuriki.
And as such, it is
the Hokage's job to
watch over him.
I will not be lenient,
as Tsunade was.
I understand, sir.
Very well. Dismissed.
Can I really relax?
[Sakura]
Sai!
Hey, we were just
looking for you!
Yeah, we really
gotta talk to you.
What is it?
Please, tell us what you
know about Danzo.
Sai!
No, I can't.
What?! Why not?!
No way. Then you're
back on his side!?
No, It's nothing
like that.
To speak about Lord Danzo is a
physical impossibility for me.
Because of this.
What is
that thing?!
Is that a Curse Mark?
Yes, it is. A jutsu cast
by Lord Danzo himself.
If I try to talk about
him, my body becomes
completely paralyzed,
unable to speak or move.
In the Foundation,
Every member bears one.
He's a cautious man.
Lord Danzo and the
Foundation work in
espionage.
Behind the scenes, they've
done lots of dirty work to
protect the Leaf.
Which is why we have to
take steps to prevent
any intel leaks.
Such as making sure we
can't spill a word even
if we're captured.
But that's so extreme!
I mean, putting a
Curse Mark on your own
subordinate!
That's awful!
That may be true, but
it has allowed us to
keep the Leaf safe.
His methods may be heavy
handed, But he cares deeply
about the Village. Like you.
But if that's true, then why
did he overturn Lady Tsunade's
decision about Sasuke?
Danzo's planning to
dispatch Tracking Ninja
to go after him!
Ah!
What, really?
He didn't mention that.
Sasuke--
Go on, keep talking. Tell
us all about this Sasuke!
You guys seem to be such
good friends with him.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Don't kill him!
[Karui]
I know!
Well.
Sakura!
Sakura! You okay?
They're from the Hidden Cloud.
You can tell by their headbands.
Why are they here?
What the hell do
you guys want?
We just overheard the
three of you talking
about Sasuke Uchiha.
We want to know about him,
and you're going to tell us.
Why? What does all of
this have to do with you
Cloud ninja anyway?
A whole lot! 'Cause Sasuke
Uchiha of the Leaf,
Assaulted the Hidden
Cloud Village!
[gasps]
You heard him;
your Rogue Shinobi
kidnapped our
beloved master!
We don't even know if
he's dead or alive!
That's... a lie!
Sasuke...
Why would he ever do
something like that?!
How the hell should we know
the Akatsuki's motives?!
The Akatsuki?!
What are you
talking about?
Uggh! You guys are
trying my patience!
Of course, Sasuke's a
member of the Akatsuki!
It's because you let
your Rogue Ninja run
loose that Lord Raikage
dispatched us here!
We've already gotten
the Hokage's permission
to get rid of him!
Sasuke... kidnapped
their master?
We will avenge
our master!
We're going to
take down Sasuke!
Sasuke...
How could you do
something like that?
What's happened to you?
Hey, Sasuke.
His chakra came out of nowhere!
How is that possible?!
[sigh] Talk about
bad timing.
How the hell did you know
where I was, anyway?
Do not take me lightly.
I have powers beyond
your comprehension.
So what do you
want from me?
Team Taka left the
Akatsuki a long time ago.
We have no further
business with you.
I warned you that you
would die if you
betrayed the Akatsuki.
What are you
talking about?
The hunt for the
Tailed-Beasts.
But we already captured
the Eight-Tails for you
and handed him over
like you asked!
That was a substitution.
In short, you blundered.
Eh?
Huh?
It seems Eight-Tails
pulled a fast one on you.
I was watching him with the
Sharingan the whole time.
He had no opportunity
to make a clone!
Ah!
It must have been when I
sliced off that tentacle!
Honestly, all of you
have disappointed me.
So what do you want
us to do about it?
I mean, it's not our
business anymore!
Wrong. You will complete the
job you were assigned when
you were with the Akatsuki.
Having said that,
you can forget about
the Eight-Tails.
I have decided to
have you carry out a
different mission.
And? What if we decline?
Then we'll fight it out
right here. And you won't
be able to go to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
We'll push through!
Huh?
It's a little too
late to go to the
Hidden Leaf, anyway.
I passed right through
him, just like before.
Is this one of his powers?
Your objective seems
so futile, now.
It's sad, really.
And what does that mean?
The Village Hidden in
the Leaves is no more.
What are you
talking about?!
[Black Zetsu]
I can explain
everything that
happened in the Leaf.
W-what is that?!
Relax. He's an
associate of mine.
So, who's the
new Hokage?
[White Zetsu]
It's that fellow Danzo.
Just as I anticipated.
Danzo?! He's Hokage now?!
Yes, one of the
high-ranking elders
of the Leaf Village,
who backed your
brother into a corner,
That's the man who's
become the new Hokage.
Just what the hell
happened in the
Hidden Leaf Village?!
My subordinate,
Pain, destroyed it.
And thanks to both you
and Pain showing off,
it seems that the
Five Kage are going
to take action.
The Five Kage?
They're convening a
Summit Conference.
[White Zetsu]
Allow me.
I'll explain it all.
Now tell us everything
you know about Sasuke.
And I don't mean just
his ninjutsu style
and his abilities.
But also any data
that you've collected
about his companions
and the Akatsuki,
and information
about their past
activities, too.
You lie. There's no way.
Sasuke would never
join the Akatsuki!
Listen, are you sure?
Yeah! He had on
the Uchiha crest!
And his face
matches the list.
But that's...
No, it can't be true!
[crying]
What are you crying for?
We're the ones who
should be weeping here!
But tears won't bring
back Lord Killer Bee
or Lady Yugito!
If you have time to cry,
you have time to tell us
about Sasuke!
Please, hold on
for just a minute.
Are you serious?!
Just listen. When the
order to take down
Sasuke was approved,
The Intel that the Leaf
has on him should have
been handed over to you
and your people.
Leave these two alone.
It's not necessary to
pressure them.
Yeah, I know, you're right.
And our captain is busy
waiting for the data right now.
But we just figured
that we'd try to get
additional information
from anyone who might know
something, that's all.
We can't sit and
do nothing!
Not when our
master's gone.
We don't even know
what happened to him!
I will avenge Pervy Sage!
I can't just sit around
here doing nothing!
But outsiders like you guys
probably have no idea what
we're going through now.
Is your master a
Jinchuriki?
How did you know that?
I'm a Jinchuriki, too.
The Akatsuki are
hunting all of us.
So I'm not just
an outsider.
The Akatsuki always capture
a Jinchuriki alive.
And that means your master
may still be alive right now.
What?
Are you serious?
Forget Sasuke.
You need to go rescue
your master first.
You sure about this?!
Like really, really sure?
I told you, didn't I?
No way our master would
die as easily as that!
Tell you what, I'll come
along and do what I can
to help you rescue him.
And give you
all I've got on
the Akatsuki.
Hey, you know what,
there, blondie?
You're pretty sharp.
Come along with us.
And tell us all
about Sasuke!
Naruto...
Just let me handle this, Sakura.
So, kid,
What's your name?
Naruto Uzumaki.
[Naruto]
I can't. There's
no way that I can
sell Sasuke out.
[Karui]
Quit playing around!
You can't take it back
now, after all that!
[Naruto]
I know that I'm
only being selfish.
But if this continues,
the vicious cycle will
start all over again!
[Karui]
Your Sasuke is the one
who started it all!
[Omoi]
Just where do you suggest that
we take our hatred, then?
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
The Eve of the Five Kage Summit
[Sai]
Naruto, why do you go
so far for Sasuke?