So this is Kabuto? He's
kind of gross, huh?
This thing sticking out. It
looks like some kind of
huge--
Just leave him
alone, Suigetsu.
She's still alive.
Listen, what do you guys
want with me after all this
time? Why did you go out of
your way to look for me?
Oh, yeah, that's the thing!
Wait, where is it?
We found something
incredible in one of the
hideouts.
Now where is it...
Earlier, you said that you
and Itachi stopped Kabuto's
Reanimation Jutsu, right?
But if it really worked the
way it was supposed to...
why's Madara still here?
No matter what darkness or
contradictions lie within
the Village...
I'm still Itachi
Uchiha of the Leaf!
You're the only one I can
count on, best friend.
Protect the village. And the
Uchiha name. Both of them.
As I told you, There's
something important
I have to do.
I see...
So it wasn't
stopped, then...
Can't you see that I'm
talking to Sasuke?! Don't
interrupt me like that!
Anyway, never mind all that.
Here!
Take a look at it!
See? Amazing, isn't it?!
With this scroll,
Taka can take over the
entire shinobi world!
This is it!
Huh?
The all-knowing...
Now...
I need to go meet
up with someone.
I'm leaving.
Huh? Meet who?
Orochimaru.
Huh?! What are you
talking about?
You already killed
Orochimaru, remember?!
I wanted you to use
this scroll to...
Don't you think it's
possible that someone as
tenacious as Orochimaru
might not be killed so easily?
Even though I find him vile
and repulsive... I still need
him to do something for me.
Clan... Village...
It's time to go see
the all-knowing!
I don't get it. How can you
talk to Orochimaru?
And who exactly is this
all-knowing person?!
That isn't something you
need to know right now.
I don't get this. But it
doesn't really matter.
Anyway, you can't!
'Cause Orochimaru must
never be revived!
You're planning on asking
Orochimaru for help in
trying to control the power
of the scroll, aren't you?
But you don't have to! You
can learn to do it on your
own, I know it!
I mean, that's why I looked
for you. And that's why I'm
giving the scroll to you!
There are still things only
Orochimaru can do.
Sasuke, just listen...
You were Orochimaru's
favorite, weren't you? His
star pupil? So why can't you
do it?!
Suigetsu...
Just don't.
[gasp]
What?
Don't underestimate
Orochimaru.
What?! You idiot! I don't
underestimate that guy at
all! It's just the opposite!
You do!
The only reason that you
defeated Orochimaru was
because both of his arms had
been rendered useless by
the Reaper Death Seal!
You've always
underestimated him!
You know, even if he is
revived somehow, he probably
still won't be able to use
his arms!
But he'll still be
dangerous!
He's going to come after
your body again!
If he finds out about this
war, he's gonna want to
be a part of it.
He wants to destroy the
Leaf too, remember?!
And that means Taka
will get all mixed up
in this war, as well!
Is that what you want?
We've only now surpassed our
mentors. This is supposed to
be our time to shine!
Look, nobody wants to see
Orochimaru ever again!
Hasn't he caused us enough
trouble?
Shut up, Suigetsu.
Please, just go dig out a
piece of Kabuto's flesh and
bring it over here to me.
Huh?
You don't listen to me, but
for some reason you expect
me to listen to you?
Fine. I'll do it.
[sigh] So that's how
it's gonna be, huh?
Are you really sure about
all this, Jugo?
You want Orochimaru
to return?!
I don't mind. Sasuke's
will is Kimimaro's will.
I will abide by it.
You're the same as always.
But what is even going on
here?
This is called Sage
Transformation in my
village.
Just like my original
transformation. But in all
my copies, it's called Curse
Mark Transformation.
We've got to seal
that curse mark.
Curse Sealing!
So the reverse is...
Curse Unsealing!
[gasping scream]
Who would have imagined...
...that it would be you of
all people who would
facilitate my return!
Oh! Hi, there!
Long time no see!
Orochimaru, there's
something that I want
you to do for me now.
You don't need to
bother explaining it.
I have been watching
from inside Anko.
I secured my Sage Jutsu
Chakra into those Curse
Marks.
They are like pieces of
my own consciousness.
Then you know about
the war, as well?
Yes, of course.
And I just have one thing
to tell you about that,
Suigetsu.
[gasp]
And that is... I have no
interest in this war at all.
Huh?!
I mean... it is
someone else's war.
The only thing I'm
interested in now...
...is your body! Yes, that's
right, my dear Sasuke.
I told you!
Then again, it's not as if I
currently possess the
strength to steal it away
from you.
I wonder about that...
What is your intent in
meeting with them?
There's... too much
that I don't know.
I plan to ask them
everything.
Everything, huh? There's no
need to know it all just
yet. You are still a child,
after all.
No, you're wrong.
I treated you as though you
were a child. I thought you
needed my protection.
I was unable to
trust your strength.
But now I think...
Perhaps you could've changed
Father and Mother...
...and the rest of the
Uchiha as well.
If I had only come to you
from the start, looked
straight into your eyes and
told you the truth...
I'm not a child anymore.
I can't stay a child.
And whatever you
do from here on...
I want to discover what
started all of it.
To find out what I'm
supposed to be, and what
I'm supposed to do.
Are you questioning
your vengeance?
Not at all. Not my quest for
vengeance itself, not a bit.
After reuniting with Itachi,
my hatred toward the Hidden
Leaf has grown even
stronger.
It's just...
I want to understand how
even in death, Itachi could
call himself a Leaf
Shinobi...
...and care about and try to
protect the village that
dishonored his name.
Who was Itachi? What is a
village? What is a clan?
That is why... I have to know
everything, so I can finally
have the answer.
I need to see and decide
for myself what to do.
He's no longer the boy who
was manipulated by Itachi...
or me... or Tobi.
What a strange sensation...
He's going to siphon all of
Kabuto's power and then kill
him! So you'd better stay
alert and watch out!
He might catch
you off guard!
The current you...
...isn't half bad.
I told you he'd steal
Kabuto's power!
No, you're wrong on
that. He undid the
Sage Transformation.
He took back his own chakra
that was inside Kabuto, not
any of Kabuto's chakra.
Very well, then. I
will help you out.
Come along.
And just where are we going?
[chuckle] A place you
actually know quite well.
Shall we be on our way?
[roaring]
The statue's been acting all
weird since it swallowed
those objects earlier.
Wait, that was...
Don't tell me...
I would have preferred
bringing it back in a
completed state, but...
Watch closely! And surrender
yourself completely!
The return of Ten Tails! And
the beginning of the end of
the world!
[angry roaring]
So that's it! The Gedo
statue was Ten Tails'
actual body!
Huh?! What does he mean?!
What's the Ten Tails?!
But what's going on? Back
when he declared war at the
Five Kage Summit...
[angry roaring]
He claimed the purpose of
this war was to collect the
Nine Tailed Beasts' chakra
to revive Ten Tails.
He doesn't possess Eight
Tails and Nine Tails yet...
So is he bluffing?
Don't be careless.
Approaching him is deadly!
Oh!
It's only a fragment, but it
is not lacking in power.
Have we given him one
octopus arm's worth of
chakra?
We're always dropping
rhymes, but maybe we messed
up big this time... Yo...
Yeah!
He got a bit of Eight-O's
chakra from back in the day.
Now we're sweatin' 'cause
holmes is here to stay.
It's not a-okay!
Eight Tails' octopus
arm chakra, huh?
So just a piece of a Tailed
Beast is sufficient?
Naruto, you felt it
too, didn't you?
[angry roaring]
That jar and gourd
contained my chakra.
Yup...
[angry roaring]
Let me take over,
Naruto. I'll explain.
About Ten Tails, too.
You listen from in here.
Kurama? You know
about Ten Tails?
Yeah! Of course!
Listen up, all of you!
Huh?
That voice!
Naruto's switched places
with Nine Tails, pow!
So just relax, he'll explain
it to us. Nine Tails and
Naruto, they're real tight
now!
If just a portion of a
Tailed Beast is sufficient,
that statue already has a
piece of Eight Tails'
and my chakra in it.
Nine Tails, too?!
The jar and gourd that guy
summoned and fed to the
statue were two of Old Man
Six Paths' treasured tools.
They possess powerful
Sealing Jutsu that can seal
away anything. Once you're
inside, you cannot get out.
So...
Sealed inside the jar was
Kinkaku. And Ginkaku was
sealed inside the gourd.
I suspect they were brought
back with the Reanimation
Jutsu, used in the war, and
then sealed away.
Kinkaku, Ginkaku, the
Sage of Six Paths...
Sure, all of them are
legendary names. But what in
the world do any of them
have to do with Nine
Tails' chakra?
There was a time long ago
when the brothers challenged
me to a battle.
I simply devoured them.
However, they survived and
fed on me from the inside.
And, in doing so, they
absorbed my chakra.
So Kinkaku and Ginkaku both
possessed some Nine Tails'
chakra, then...
And the guy in the mask took
the two of them from Darui's
First Company as an
insurance policy for
reviving the Ten Tails.
That's consistent with
the report from HQ.
But since they're just
fragments of Eight Tails'
and my chakra, who knows
what form the revived
Ten Tails will take?
We must act before Ten Tails
fully comes back to life.
Kakashi...
You speak your
mind far too easily.
You're a man for whom a
life of regret is fitting!
You bastard... Just who in
the hell are you, anyway?
What would be the point in
telling someone who can't
remember faces?
Kakashi, like you said, if
we're going to make a move,
now's our chance.
[angry growling]
Old Man Six Paths used to
say that Ten Tails' full
revival would signify the
end of this world.
So, is Ten Tails
really that terrible?
I get that he's got Ten
Tails, but just how
powerful is he, anyway?
He's the aggregate of all
the Tailed Beasts' chakra,
One Tail through to me.
He was the beginning of
chakra and a creator-god
of many nations.
Ameno-hitotsuno-kami,
Datara, Deidarabotchi: he
has many names.
He drank the oceans, split
open the earth, hoisted up
the mountains. He's the
progenitor said to have
created this very land.
Simply put, he has the total
power of all nine Tailed
Beasts.
Honestly, I couldn't take
him on by myself and hope
to win.
But if he only has a piece
of Eight Tails and me, who
have the most chakra out of
the nine, it may be worth a try.
You are all mistaken.
I don't need Ten Tails to be
revived at full capacity.
[gasps]
My end goal is a Super
Genjutsu, the Infinite
Tsukuyomi!
I will put the entire human
population of this planet
under a single genjutsu.
A single world that belongs
to nobody. One perfect world
without war or ill feelings.
Only within a single
collective consciousness
where the individual has
been cast aside can
truth be found!
The world no longer needs
hope, a future, or famous
heroes.
Even if incomplete, once Ten
Tails is revived, the
Infinite Tsukuyomi Jutsu can
be achieved,
and reality will
come to an end...
And all that will exist will
be a single unending dream
that will last for all
eternity!
[angry roaring]
Kurama, switch back!
Look, I had...
I had my Father. I had my
Mother. And I had Pervy
Sage.
Kids love looking up
to their heroes!
That's why I can run forward
without hesitation!
And I will become the
greatest Hokage of them all!
That's my dream, and I won't
give up on it, you fool!
Even if you don't want your
youth to reach an end...
Your dreams still have to
come to an end at some
point!
Yeah... Dreams must be
fulfilled.
Yo, check it: Dreams,
dreams, lots o' dreams
abound, even out here on
this battleground.
I dream of women's boobs, so
round! When dreams are
fulfilled, that is where
truth is found!
You've got guts, Bee,
telling us about your, uh,
preferences at a time like
this...
[harrumphing chuckle]
Individuality makes you
lose sight of the truth.
My words as a nobody are
words guided by the absolute
truth of the world.
[attacking yell]
[angry roaring]
Your window is the
instant he tries to pull
you in, that's when he'll
become solid.
If you attack him normally,
you'll just pass right
through him.
So go for the counterattack!
Create an opening through
close combat! Avoid using
big moves!
Thanks, but I already know
that! That's why I created a
clone!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Secret of the
Transportation Technique."
Naruto! Just keep going!