(Gengo) The minute that Sasuke
returned to the village...
people stopped paying attention
to you.
That doesn't matter. Do you
believe something like that
would bother me?
(Gengo) You might consider
yourself a member of Team 7...
but I wonder if they think the
same of you.
I won't fall for your cheap
attempts to convince me. I'm...
Uh?
(Ro) Look there. That must be
the inn where Lord Sai stopped.
That's right. And now, look
slightly above it.
(Shikamaru) That's the only
checkpoint leading into the
village of Tobari.
Unless we're able to find a
way past it, we can't get into
the village.
Hmm?
Yeah, but still, are you sure
this get-up is, like, really
necessary?
It looks very becoming on you,
Soku.
[sighs]
(Shikamaru) Look, I had to bend
over backwards...
to get a coal vendor's traveling
permit for this disguise.
If you have any better ideas
about how to get past the
checkpoint, let me know!
Rest assured. We will surely be
able to deceive the enemy's eyes
with this ruse.
If we just kill the lookouts,
it'll be, like, easy to get past
the checkpoint!
If we were to do that and the
Leaf's involvement were
discovered...
it would mean big trouble.
(Shikamaru) Besides, we think
that Sai's entire team was taken
down around here.
Don't underestimate the enemy.
(Soku) If we stay too long,
we'll just like, increase the
chances of the enemy finding us.
All right, listen
up, both of you.
Hmm?
Huh?
[clearing throat]
I think especially now, on
this mission, it's crucial that
all of us trust each other.
And trust really first begins,
I'd say...
when teammates are
genuinely able to believe in
their comrades.
Did you get that out of, like,
some weird book?
I think Lord Shikamaru is simply
trying to do his utmost...
to behave like a good leader
should.
(Shikamaru) Quit trying to
analyze me! [groans] Forget it.
The point is that this mission
requires teamwork.
Uh.
What're you doing?
Like, take a good look.
Silence Shinobi?
[grunts]
Soku! [grunts]
Don't take action by yourself!
I'm like, better at this
sort of thing alone! [grunts]
[grunts]]
I got him!
(Shikamaru) [sighs] Oh, great.
You just ruined our disguise!
This situation's taken a
problematic turn.
Aw man, guess we're back to
square one for our strategy.
[chatting]
What can I get you?
Could I just have
some water, please?
Sure. Help yourself.
Hmm?
Well, anyway.
I heard that the checkpoint
to get into Tobari is right
around here somewhere.
Is that true?
I've got nothing to
say to outsiders.
Hmm?
(Shikamaru) The "demon killer,"
huh?
(Merchant) Oh! You know the
game, do you?
I do. Mind if I play?
(Merchant) What good luck,
finding an opponent in these
remote parts!
You're a welcome sight
indeed!
So does that mean you're
traveling alone?
I've come here to Tobari
because I need to hire a
shinobi.
But they're busy
checking into my background
and what not.
So, I've had to wait here.
Village of Tobari, huh?
I've actually been hoping that I
could do some business there
myself.
Well, be warned, going in and
out of there is a real hassle.
(Merchant) Unless you have this
pass, it's practically
impossible.
(Shikamaru) Ah, you got me!
Didn't expect that move!
[chuckles]
(Merchant) It was my only chance
to play that.
(Shikamaru) By the way...
why did you end up choosing
the Land of Silence?
There are other lands that would
be able to accept shinobi
requests.
Well, first of all, it's the
price.
I don't care who does the work
itself...
whether it's the Silence or the
Hidden Leaf or anyone for that
matter!
(Merchant) After all, shinobi
are dispensable.
They're merely tools you use
and then discard.
[grunts] Please excuse me!
Huh?
Are you trying to sabotage our
strategy?
It's all because we let guys
like that say whatever they
want that...
like, shinobi are always
looked down upon!
Even so, that's no reason to
kill him.
I only wanted to shake him up
a little bit, that's all!
For all your talk, you're,
like, the one who doesn't
trust us!
Then start acting with more
caution and discretion!
[grunts]
There something you want to say?
You bet there is! There's no way
I'm gonna mess up a mission by
being, like, overcautious!
[groans] That girl.
Do you think she's acting
unusually rash?
It's my conviction, that perhaps
more than anyone else...
Soku fears the peace that's
being established in the world.
(Ro) She worries it will spell
the end of shinobi.
I presume she's determined to
make this mission a success...
to prove the value of shinobi
to the world.
So much blood was shed to
achieve this peace, which
we've sought for so long.
And frankly, it's ridiculous
that some people can't stomach
it.
(Ro) Lord Shikamaru...
you proved your mettle and
worth as a shinobi in the
Fourth Great Ninja War.
Soku never had a chance to do
so.
Such is the sorrow of the
generation that came too late.
I see. And so what about you,
Ro?
You have a lot of experience
in combat, don't you?
All I did was manage to
stay alive somehow.
(Silence Shinobi) All right! No
one move!
Hmm?
(Silence Shinobi) We're here to
confirm your identities.
Until we do, you won't be
allowed to leave the building!
Hey!
[gasps]
What happened?
The shinobi we left in the
ravine must've like, been
discovered.
[grunts] They moved faster than
I thought they would. Huh?
(Merchant) I'm not doing
anything!
No, don't! We can't afford
to make a scene now.
Then what are we
supposed to do?
I don't know yet!
I'm thinking!
(Ro) You two.
[grunts]
We have a visitor.
Back off!
Just what do you
think you're doing?
(Ro) We owe you our lives.
(Komori) There's no need to
thank me!
I have plenty of reasons to hate
those guys from Tobari on my
own!
They're always barging in,
acting arrogant.
My name's Komori, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
Uh,  yeah, well we're, uh...
Look, you don't have to tell
me anything you don't want to.
I mean, I'm sure that everyone
has a thing or two they'd like
to keep hidden, am I right?
Hmm.
Komori, we're looking to get
into the Village of Tobari.
Do you know of any way to get
past the checkpoint?
That's gonna be a tough one. But
why do you even want to go
there, anyway?
We just have some business
there.
Shh! Someone's here!
[squeaking]
Oh, man, it's just a mouse!
Don't scare me like that!
(Shikamaru) Hey! Hold on!
What don't you understand about
waiting until we can find a way
to get through the checkpoint?
Like, if we take too much
time, we could lose our chance
to kill Gengo!
But it's too dangerous
for you to go alone.
You're absolutely not to act
on your own!
Look, the only thing that I
wanna do is, like, prove my
abilities!
And I refuse to be held back by
some stupid rules!
Enough, Soku, grow up! This
isn't some kind of game that
we're playing here, you know!
What a drag.
What's that?
Sometimes I think that I'd
have more freedom if I lived
in the Land of Silence.
You mustn't make such reckless
statements.
Wait a minute. You're not
getting any weird ideas about
deserting the Village, are you?
'Cause that's a serious crime.
Rogue Ninja are hunted to the
ends of the earth...
and are always punished to the
furthest extent of shinobi law.
(Shikamaru) You are aware of
that, right?
[grunts]
Lord Shikamaru, I don't think
that she's serious. Isn't that
right, Soku?
Like I care!
Hey, we aren't done talking
yet!
[chatting]
[sighs]
(Komori) Hey.
Huh?
Something put you in a bad
mood?
Like, it's none of your
business, okay?
I may not know exactly what
happened, but don't just give up
'cause you're discouraged.
Look at me. I'm forced to
take on a menial job like this
one.
But still someday, I'm
gonna have a big inn of my
own!
Yeah like, nobody asked
you.
(Shikamaru) [grunts] That kid.
I hope she actually knows what
she's supposed to be doing
here.
I'm certain there's no need to
worry about Soku.
All I want is like, to
make my power be useful.
So, you're a shinobi, then?
Yeah, but it's a secret.
Right, sure, I understand.
Everyone in my village has
gotten used to peace and because
of that, they're too timid.
So, like, at this rate, I
should've just gone to the
Land of Silence.
But surely you're not really
thinking of deserting your
village, right?
I mean, isn't that
a serious crime?
Like, yeah, I know it is.
[sighs]
But this talk has made me
feel better. I oughta, like, be
getting back.
Okay.
Actually, how about I come
along with you?
You really don't have to do
this, you know.
Eh, I'm used to getting yelled
at around here. So, I'm
really good at apologizing!
[chuckles]
(Shikamaru) Ro, you saw that
look in her eyes, didn't you?
(Ro) You're over thinking
things.
Listen, if Soku truly is serious
about deserting the village...
then we're just going to have to
silence her. Can you do it?
Hmm.
Well, could you do it or not?
Desertion is a serious crime. So
if we were to learn that Soku
really means to...
(Ro) then I shall not falter.
[grunts]
[gasps]
I knew it! Like, I don't
consider them comrades or
anything anymore!
Hey, wait!
Soku.
I guess I don't really have a
place where I belong now.
What if, I told you there was a
safe route to the checkpoint...
and you could make it there
without being discovered?
Would you be willing
to risk it?
(Komori) It's the long way
around, but if you follow the
river...
you can reach the checkpoint
without being seen.
(Shikamaru) Hey!
[gasps]
What are you doing lurking
around here?
Oh, I was, uh, looking for the
mouse that got away before.
Have you seen Soku around?
Uh, no, I haven't seen
anything at all!
What is going on here?
[grunts]
(Shikamaru) Hey!
Uh.
Answer me again, but look me
in the eye!
(Shikamaru) Where's Soku?
I said that I don't know!
Hold on, Is she heading
for the checkpoint? Did she
desert us?
That's it, isn't it?
Uh.
That's inconceivable! Soku
would never desert the
village!
To find out for sure, we're
going to have to catch Soku
and ask her directly.
[sighs]
(Silence Shinobi) Stop there!
All right, just who are you?
I deserted my village!
I want my skills to be of
use here, for this land!
[grunts]
[sighs/grunts]
[gasps]/grunts]
If you interfere, we'll kill
you!
Seriously, a Rogue Ninja? A
kid like you?
Like, your age doesn't
matter. It's your ability that
means everything.
Well now, at least you can talk
the talk!
What the?
[gasps]
Next time I fire, it won't
just be your leg.
Uh, look, don't be offended.
It's just that lately, we've had
a whole lot of rats sniffing
around this place.
Just recently, in fact.
That's right.
(Silence Shinobi) An ANBU from
the Leaf.
Hmm.
So do you mean it? At your age,
you really want to desert your
village?
I'm just sick of their
ridiculous, old-fashioned
rules.
And, like, with my skills, you
won't regret taking me on.
All right, then! Great! I
like you already!
And as for skills, you do
have an interesting
technique.
[grunting]
(Silence Captain) It's funny,
though.
Two of my men on
reconnaissance were killed
recently.
Your technique inflicts the same
kind of wound that took them
down.
I wonder how that
might have happened?
Would you care to explain?
Things aren't looking too good
for you, are they...
(Silence Captain)
Young lady.
(Komori) She's okay!
[gasps]
(Soku) Komori?
I'm sorry I couldn't say
anything.
But I had to test you in
order to make sure we
could trust you.
Hmph. After she took down
two of our comrades? How
could we?
They attacked out of nowhere.
I had no choice.
Anyway, I got into a fight with
my teammates, so I've made up my
mind to leave my Village.
It's true. I've been watching
her all this time, Captain.
She really did split from her
group.
Yeah, well, it still
seems kind of fishy.
If you don't believe me, I
don't mind if we, like, fight
it out, right here and now.
(Shikamaru) There you are, Soku!
[grunts] So, Komori, you were
pulling the strings this whole
time, huh?
I gotta say, you guys are
pretty quick. But still, take a
good look around.
(Komori) There's no way you can
win!
Listen, you understand
the gravity of this, right?
Deserting's a serious crime.
(Shikamaru) Hand her over to us
right now.
You interfere, and
I won't hold back!
What's it gonna be? Will you
turn her over?
[chuckles]
How interesting.
This is your chance to prove
what you told us. Show us
you're serious!
[grunts]
I'll help you, Soku!
I don't need your help! This
is my problem to take care of!
[grunts]
Lord Shikamaru, I implore
you! Think this over!
Soku has her reasons for doing
this. Don't be reckless!
Are you going to
betray me now, too?
Uh, you misunderstand!
[grunts] I'll just have to take
care of you first!
[gasps]
[grunting] Lord Shikamaru!
The two of you, working
together? [gasps]
[grunting]
Soku.
How could you?
[heavy breathing]
[grunts]
(Silence Captain) Nicely done!
I don't sense any
chakra. He's dead.
You did it, Soku!
I think that you'll be very
useful to us. Come!
All right! That's it! You're
pretty much one of us now.
I mean, you'll have to go
through some rounds of
questioning and stuff...
but you'll be released soon.
In exchange for the intel
you have, you'll be- [grunts]
Like, I'm gonna need you to
go to sleep for a little while.
[grunting] Damn it, that was
tougher than I expected it to
be!
I thought it went quite well.
I know that Soku said that she'd
make it appear that we'd died
when she attacked us.
But still, that hurt a lot.
We owe that boy a
debt of thanks, too.
Oh man, it's just a mouse!
(Ro) At that time, I used my
chakra abilities to fake the
presence of a shinobi.
Yeah, and his unexpected
reaction was our lucky break.
An ordinary kid wouldn't have
responded to chakra like that.
And then he performed exactly
as we predicted he would.
(Ro) But what Soku was
bemoaning.
She truly meant half of what
she said...
Perhaps you weren't aware of
the extent of the risk.
If she'd actually been serious
about fighting us...
she could've killed us both
any time she wanted.
You know, the thing about
trust is...
you have to believe in your
comrades first, just like I
told you guys before.
(Ro) As I expected of you.
(Shikamaru) [chuckles] Don't
tell Soku, okay? It'll just go
to her head.
I like, heard everything.
[gasps]
Your logic's, like, totally
naïve, Shikamaru.
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me you actually
meant to hurt me back there?
If you want, I can,
like, try it again.
Uh well, maybe some other
time.
Anyway, how'd it go?
(Soku) I kept the lock open. As
long as we go quickly, no one
will notice.
Just perfect.
Hmm.
(Soku) About Gengo, we have
like, nothing on him.
And no one knows anything about
the inside of the castle.
(Ro) It seems the man known as
Gengo rarely appears in front
of others.
(Shikamaru) Did you hear
anything about Sai?
(Soku) No. Nothing at all!
(Shikamaru) Well, it seems
this Gengo is a very cautious
man.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Shikamaru's Story, A Cloud
Drifting in the Silent Dark,
Part 3: Recklessness."
Let's expose this guy for what
he really is!