[Karin]
Hey, where'd that
white guy go?
Hmf.
Got it?
[Black Zetsu]
Yeah.
Then begin.
"A Painful Decision"
If only Lady Tsunade would
wake up from her coma,
I know she'd fix this
whole mess with Sasuke.
Sakura,
[Sai]
Excuse me.
Oh, Sai.
Sakura, We have to talk.
He did what?!
That's right.
In order to
protect Sasuke,
He took all of her abuse.
[panting]
You bastard.
[Sai]
But he never sold out Sasuke.
Not only that, In order to
prevent you from worrying,
he asked me to keep it quiet.
Naruto...
And now he's
on his way,
to ask the Raikage
to pardon Sasuke.
What? Why would he
be so reckless?!
Wasn't Kakashi with him?!
I doubt that would've
stopped him.
Kakashi Sensei
believes in Naruto.
Even if it's a long shot,
Kakashi wants to
give him a chance.
If Lady Tsunade had been there,
she'd have done the same thing.
[Sai]
Sakura.
Recently, I was assigned to Team
Kakashi to take Sasuke's place.
So I still don't really
know all of you very well.
And I'm not good
with emotions.
Also,
What?!
Have you told sakura
how you feel?
No way. I mean,
how could I?
I'm the guy who couldn't
even keep my promise to her.
I don't know what
promise he made to you.
(ct taken aback reax)
[Sasuke] [crying]
Naruto, This is a once
in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please, bring Sasuke back to me.
[Sai]
However...
Even I am able to see,
that Naruto's
in love with you!
[gasp]
Well gosh Sakura, you must
really care about Sasuke, huh?
I get it. I can see that
deep down this must be
really painful for you.
I know you must
be suffering.
Don't you worry one bit.
I'm gonna bring Sasuke back.
I promise you that
on my life, Sakura!
Listen, Sakura, I'm still
gonna keep my promise;
I won't give up!
It was the promise of a
lifetime! I really meant it.
Completely.
I said I would.
So I will.
Don't forget, my Way
of the Shinobi means,
That I'm always gonna
stand behind what I say!
[crying]
[Shizune]
Sakura...
Seems Naruto has
shouldered the burden
of his promise to you.
And plans to for the
rest of his life.
[Sai]
I don't know what
you said to Naruto.
But it's really no different
than what was done to me.
It's like a Curse Mark.
[gasp]
It's obvious that Sasuke is
making Naruto suffer,
But I think you may be, too.
[crying]
Ino...
Stop crying, Ino!
Hey! Don't talk
to her like that!
You know how Ino's
felt about Sasuke
all these years.
Yeah but it can't be helped!
D'ugh.
Things are different now
than they were before.
You sure about this?
If that's Ino's reaction,
How will Naruto and Sakura feel?
Let's leave it to Shikamaru.
He always knows the right
thing to say.
Remember that his first mission
as squad leader failed.
He still feels
responsible for that.
Yeah, I know. Just
imagine if we had somehow
gotten Sasuke back home.
It haunts him.
That's why Shikamaru
volunteered to convince her.
[Shizune]
Wait a minute! Naruto genuinely
wants to rescue Sasuke,
it's not just because of
his promise to Sakura!
Don't you think that's true?
[Sai]
Yes, I totally
agree with you.
But, both Sakura and I,
and everyone else, rely
on Naruto too much.
I've been watching Naruto
lately, and I think I figured
out what he's feeling.
It's sadness.
And then when I
think about Sasuke,
I get a burning
feeling in my gut.
And I've come to know
that that's anger.
So for Naruto's sake, as well
as that of the Hidden Leaf,
we must not rely solely on
Naruto anymore.
We have to take
action ourselves.
Sasuke is...
[Shikamaru]
Sai's right.
[Shizune]
Shikamaru!
We're not kids anymore.
We need to stop the Akatsuki.
And then,
We have to stop Sasuke.
I came here to talk to
Team 7's members and
get their consent.
Consent?! Please
don't tell me that--
Yeah, that's right.
We can't allow a war to
break out between the
Hidden Leaf and the Hidden
Cloud because of Sasuke.
Let me try to put
it another way.
Just hear me out.
If the Hidden Cloud did kill
Sasuke, there's no way you
or Ino, or especially
Naruto, would just let it be.
And if any of you were to lash
out recklessly and get killed by
Cloud ninja,
Neither I nor Choji,
nor Inoichi, or even
your parents would
just sit still.
We'd go out and avenge you.
Then the other side
wouldn't remain quiet.
They'd retaliate, too.
If Choji or I were to get
killed by Cloud ninja,
Well, then, our fathers
would just head out.
Before you know it,
we'd be at war.
According to what the
messenger from the Cloud said,
they already consider Sasuke
an international criminal.
If Sasuke continues to align
himself with the Akatsuki,
the hatred spreading
through the country
will only grow.
So I believe it's time for
the Hidden Leaf Village to
deal with Sasuke ourselves.
You understand
what I'm saying?
Right, Sakura?
That's why I want your consent.
Sakura, will you--
[Sakura]
Shikamaru...
[sigh]
Please. Just don't.
Don't say anything more.
I'm sorry,
Sakura.
But regardless of what
your answer is, I'm going
to have to act, to protect
the Leaf's future.
I'll talk to Naruto, too.
Where is he right now?
Naruto's gone,
he went to the
Land of Iron.
To meet with
the Raikage.
Ahn! He's willing
to go that far!?
Well, I guess I should've
known that this whole
thing was gonna be a drag.
[Sakura]
I want to be the one
to talk to Naruto.
What??
Sakura!
[sniffles]
Since he's the fool
that fell for me...
I want to do it.
Let me take on
that role.
I'm the one who's caused
Naruto the most pain.
I'm always messing up.
Just one failure after another.
I don't want to make any more
mistakes. I don't want to fail!
I'll do it.
What?! Let the Hokage lead
the Allied Shinobi Forces?!
If all of you approve this,
I will gladly and humbly
accept this position.
Rrgh.
[growling]
Why the Hokage?!
This man is also
known by the moniker,
The Shinobi of Darkness!
We cannot let him take charge!
Then who else?
My village has not
produced even one single
member of the Akatsuki.
Such a crucial role must be
filled by the most trustworthy!
It ought to be me!
[Mifune]
I cannot agree to that.
What did you say?!
Huh...?!
[Mifune]
I am well aware that a certain
amount of intensity and strength
is necessary to assemble
and lead a force of
powerhouses such as these.
But someone such as yourself,
whose acts are ruled by his
emotions,
would probably end up
splintering an allied force
just like you did that desk.
Rrrgh.
I am simply stating my
unbiased opinion as a
neutral party in these
discussions, Lord Raikage.
Lord Kazekage is still
too young to spearhead
such a venture.
He does not have much pull
with other nations, and his
title of Kazekage alone
will not be sufficient.
Lord Tsuchikage, on the
other hand, is too old and
gives the impression of
one whose power has waned.
He has also used the
Akatsuki too often.
He's the least trustworthy
among you here.
And since Lady Mizukage's Hidden
Mist is suspected to be the
birthplace of the Akatsuki,
There is some concern about
possible intelligence leaks.
People might wonder
if there are spies.
We don't know why the
Akatsuki are gathering the
Tailed Beasts or what they
intend to do with them.
But we do know that
we can't let them
have the Nine-Tails.
The Nine-Tails belongs
to the Hidden Leaf.
Thus, I feel it
appropriate that the
Hokage be named as leader.
[Raikage]
Regardless of any
other concerns,
I would never agree to an
Allied Shinobi Force that
would compromise the
security of my village!
Something's just not
sitting right about this.
I need to check it out.
Chojuro.
Hm?
Prepare for battle.
What?!
Byakugan!
What?! What's this?!
How could this be?! The color
of the chakra in Danzo's
right shoulder and right arm,
and his right eye as well...
There's no mistake.
It's Shisui Uchiha's!
He was a formidable foe
that I fought against once.
I'll never forget that color.
Lord Hokage! Please
show us the eye you
keep covered under
that bandage.
[gasp]
What?
Eh?
What's the
meaning of this?
[Ao]
I believe you stole Shisui
Uchiha's eye and transplanted
it in place of your own.
It's Shisui Uchiha's?
[stunned gasp]
[Mizukage]
The man who was praised
alongside Itachi
as the Uchiha most gifted
in the use of Visual Jutsu?
Yes.
His particular jutsu let him
enter the minds of others,
make them go through phantom
experiences of his own choosing,
and manipulate them.
It was such a top-notch
Visual Jutsu, that one
never even caught on to
having been manipulated.
Hokage! Don't tell
me Mifune is...
[stunned gasp]
But how could...?
[gasp]
Wait, is that--?!
My right eye is also a
precious spoil of war, from
a battle against the Hyuga.
So I'm not really
one to cast blame.
But you cannot trick my eye.
I was able to penetrate the
genjutsu cast upon the
Fourth Mizukage.
And thus, you see--
How dare you!
Well, hello there!
One problem after another.
Now what?!
Is he Akatsuki?
Seems so.
Guess what? Sasuke Uchiha
has snuck in here!
I wonder... where do you think
he could be hiding right now?
Any guesses?
What is all this?!
Sasuke
Uchiha?!
Is it him?
What's he
doing here?!
He's the one with
the Sharingan?!
Who took down
Haku and Zabusa?
[gasp]
Who is he?
A member of the Akatsuki.
I believe his name is...
It's like a game
of hide and seek!
Let's all try to find Sasuke!
Come on!
Rgh!
Tell me where Sasuke Uchiha is!
Rrrrrr!
Give me an answer, right now!
Rrrrghh!
Whoa, this guy
is super fast!
Hrk!
Refuse to answer and
I'll show you no mercy!
[Naruto]
Sasuke...
Where are you right now?
And what are you thinking about?
Do you ever think about me,
or Sakura, or Kakashi Sensei?
Even a little bit?
You defeated your
brother Itachi.
You got your vengeance.
Do you feel relieved now?
Or is it even more painful
than it was before?
Sasuke, why won't you
come home to the Leaf?
Has hatred completely
consumed you, Sasuke?
Have you really just become
an ordinary criminal?
I... I'm not sure who you are
anymore. Or who you were.
[Madara]
Hey.
We really should talk,
Naruto Uzumaki.
[Karin]
This is bad.
[Jugo]
What's the matter, Karin?
[Karin]
The Samurai's movements have
suddenly become erratic. I think
they're looking for us!
[Suigetsu]
What?! We didn't
do anything to get
their attention!
[Jugo]
I bet it was Zetsu.
He's gone now.
[Suigetsu]
That bastard! I'll
get him for this.
[Karin]
There are too many!
We'll be found and
captured in no time!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Racing Lightning."
[Sasuke]
I'm very irritated
right now.