[music playing]
KISAME: Finally, it's about
time you settled down.
[sigh]
What a handful this whole
thing's turning out to be.
[thunder]
[crash]
-Huh?
Kisame, you're back.
-That's right.
But having to bring him
back without killing
him was quite a
bother, I'll tell you.
[thunder]
[music playing]
Here comes that rain
we were expecting.
-It looks like a big storm.
-Come on.
Let's go find some cover,
otherwise we'll catch a chill.
-Our leader is waiting for
word that we captured him.
Immediately after we secure
him and bring him in,
the sealing of both the
Three-Tails and Four-Tails
is to take place.
-So we make him wait a little
before the sealing begins.
I mean, it's not
like it's really
going to make any difference.
The sealing takes a
long time, anyway.
[music playing]
-It looks like he's dying.
You should handle the
elderly with care.
-You only say that because
you don't know this guy.
Nabbing a jinchuriki who
uses the Corrosion Style
jutsu of the Four-Tails is
way harder than you think.
But you probably can't
understand my pain,
not having battled
the fellow directly.
-Hm.
-Well, I suppose it's
really my own fault
since I insisted on going alone.
Should I take care of
your objective, as well?
-You need to try and
settle down, Kisame.
-Sorry, I'm just a little tired.
I want to get this hunt
for the tailed beasts over
with, already.
-There isn't any need
to be so impatient.
This is going to take some time,
and that just can't be helped.
-Well, I'm not so
sure about that.
There are only a few
more to find, right?
And don't forget,
it's been decided
that we're going to seal
the Nine-Tails last of all,
or else it will
disrupt the balance
and the sealing statue will
come crashing to the ground.
At least that's what
our leader said.
We all have to capture the
jinchuriki alive anyway, so
why can't we trap him now
and just keep him imprisoned?
-Huh, fine with me,
but it won't be easy.
Don't forget that
Deidara failed.
If we're to seal
the Nine-Tails last,
then we might as well
hunt him down last.
Besides, the Akatsuki's
been too conspicuous lately.
If we take the Nine-Tails
jinchuriki right now,
it will only rile the Hidden
Leaf Village all the more.
-Ha, do you really believe that?
-Not only is the Hidden
Leaf Village strong,
they have deep connections
with other villages.
If word gets around,
then it will only
make our jobs that much harder.
It's wiser to collect
everything up to the Eight-Tails
with as little
commotion as possible.
-I see.
I guess you're right
about that, Itachi.
-And there's the summons--
-I guess we just
got caught dawdling.
PAIN: You are late.
-We were just
finishing capturing
the jinchuriki when
you contacted us.
And then we had to tie him up
to make sure he couldn't escape.
It took us longer than
expected, but here we are.
-I have some urgent information
that I need to relay to you.
Orochimaru has been killed.
-Ha, it's been 10 years
since he left the Akatsuki.
At least we've been spared the
task of killing him ourselves.
Who cares if he's dead?
I wanted him gone
as much as I wanted
the Zombie Pair eliminated.
-Hidan and Kakuzu
were our comrades.
Don't say such things.
-Sorry.
So, who were the ones
who did them in, anyway?
-It was the Hidden Leaf.
-Kakashi and the Nine-Tails
jinchuriki's team--
-Yes, they're extremely
strong, that team.
No wonder Deidara
got pummeled by them.
-Tobi, just keep
running your mouth,
and you'll push me to my limit.
Hm.
-Ha-ha, your limit?
Just calm down, Deidara.
You mean that you'll
get explosive, right?
As we all know, you
have such a short fuse.
-How dare you, Tobi!
[growl]
-That's enough, Deidara.
You're just proving
that Tobi's right.
[scoff]
-Ha, you got in trouble
with our leader.
-But Tobi, you do talk too much.
Show some respect.
-OK, sorry.
-And we are supposed to get the
remaining jinchuriki with them?
[sigh]
-Killing Orochimaru
would take someone
with very special
skills, so who did it?
-Sasuke Uchiha.
-Too bad.
I wanted to be the one
to bring Orochimaru down.
-Hm.
Sasuke's good, but I'd
expect nothing less
from Itachi's kid brother.
-He's in the process of putting
together a team of his own,
all of them troublesome shinobi.
-What do you mean?
-You should remember
one of them--
one of the Hozuki brothers
of the Hidden Mist.
-Seigetsu?
That's a name I haven't
heard in a while.
-And Bipolar Jugo, so you need
to be on your guard, Itachi
and Kisame.
Odds are, they may be
targeting the two of you.
And the rest of you should
keep Sasuke Uchiha firmly
in you minds, as well.
After getting information
about Itachi and Kisame,
they may come after the
Akatsuki as a whole.
-Kisame, what kind of guy
is this Suigetsu like, hm?
-It's been 10 years, but he
was a cute kid, a real prodigy.
He was called the
reincarnation of Zabuza,
the demon of the Hidden Mist.
-What are you?
Are you a fish out of
water, or something?
Quit sitting down every few
minutes to hydrate yourself.
-Ha.
Well, they sure seem like an
interesting lot, don't they?
Hm.
-Look, don't get involved.
You're only going to
stir up more trouble.
Just leave me out
of it, all right?
-Enough.
Itachi, Kisame, hurry up
and get the Four-Tails.
We'll seal him at the same
time as the Three-Tails.
-Understood.
-Now, that's just great.
I thought we'd get a chance to
rest a little bit, at least.
-We have no choice.
Let's hurry.
[music playing]
[theme music]
TSUNADE: We target a
member of the Akatsuki
who has the highest chance
of leading us to Sasuke.
Well, I can certainly
see the logic in that.
But Itachi Uchiha?
Well, how do we play this?
-If we can take just one of
the Akatsuki into custody,
I wouldn't think that it'd
be too difficult for Ibiki
to get information out
of whomever we capture.
-I've already issued an
order to that effect.
Each team is to try and capture
a member of the Akatsuki.
And if they succeed, then
they'll bring that member in.
KAKASHI: Most likely that
will prove to be difficult.
SAKURA: Kakashi Sensei--
-I'm afraid we won't be able to
make them talk quite so easily.
Even those that we've
already encountered
have been far too dangerous.
We couldn't even consider
taking them into custody.
-So what should we
do, Kakashi Sensei?
-We can only be patient, keep
looking until we find Itachi.
-I can't take it.
Let's take a break, already.
-Keep complaining and
dragging your feet like this,
and we're never going
to make it there.
SUIGETSU: Well, excuse me.
But unlike you, I have a
very delicate constitution.
-What?
Look, why don't you just
go evaporate already,
you water monster.
-Hey, here's a better idea.
Why don't you get lost?
Didn't you say you had
somewhere else to go.
[grumbles]
-Enough, we're here.
-Hm?
[screech]
[music playing]
-This next one is big.
-You're here.
All right, we will begin the
sealing with the Three-Tails.
[music playing]
Everyone, assemble.
Let's begin.
-This is it.
-I got to say, this is
one sketchy looking place.
-Let's go.
-Uh-huh, a hideout in a
wasteland like this one, huh?
I never heard of it.
-This isn't Orochimaru's.
It's a munitions store the
Uchiha clan used to use.
We'll outfit ourselves
with supplies for battle.
-This is like a maze.
All the passages look the same.
It must be easy to
get lost in here.
-Man, this place feels
depressing and stifling.
I mean, it's hard to breathe.
DENKA: Hm, I'm sorry to
hear you feel that way.
-Hm?
-Ha, it's been a long
time, Denka and Hina.
-Well, if it isn't
our Sasuke boy.
-So tell us, what
can we do for you?
Meow.
So tell us, what
can we do for you?
Meow.
-We need weapons and medicine,
as well as some other supplies.
We need to prepare for battle.
-Are those really--
-Ha.
Yeah, they're talking tanuki.
Come here little guys--
[hiss]
-Whoa!
-They're ninja cats, so
be careful and respectful.
Or they'll tear you apart.
-You want to warn us about
stuff like that beforehand?
-So, did you bring us a present?
Meow meow.
-Here, a bottle
of catnip for you.
-It's my favorite, meow.
-Follow me, and I'll
take you to Granny Cat.
[meows]
SASUKE: I am
grateful, Granny Cat.
-It has been too long
since I've seen you.
I'm sorry you're
in such a hurry.
-Yeah, I have an important task.
-Now, you're not a
ninja cat, are you?
No you're not.
-No good.
Even the extra, extra
large doesn't fit.
-Sorry.
-So it's true.
You're still going
to go after Itachi.
To think that I've known the
both of you since you were just
wee little things Never did
imagine it would come to this.
Now, you are the only
two remaining Uchiha.
And yet, you must
kill each other.
SASUKE: We'll be going
now, but thank you for all
that you've done.
[sigh]
-Nothing fits him, Granny.
Don't we have any larger clothes
for him to try on around here?
[groan]
-Did you check in that box?
-- -I did.
They're all too small.
-Then just wrap him in
that curtain over there.
We're not running a clothing
store here, you know.
-But Granny Cat, that's so rude.
They are paying us, you know.
-There.
PERVY SAGE: Hunt Itachi
to find Sasuke, huh?
All right, say we find Itachi.
What then?
-About that, I have an idea.
Can you spare some
time to discuss it?
[crowd noise]
-Huh?
Naruto, you don't
look pleased at all.
-Pervy Sage-- so, what are
you doing here, anyway?
-Well, it's been awhile,
so I thought, perhaps
I could share a meal
with my apprentice.
-I don't know.
You buying?
NARUTO: Man, what is
up with Kakashi Sensei?
We're all ready to go and he
shows up and stops everything.
-That's just the way it is.
Lots of preparation goes
into missions like this one.
-Like what?
-One small team isn't going
to be enough to pull off
the kind of thing
you have in mind.
-What do you mean?
I don't understand.
-Well, look.
If Itachi is killed, Sasuke
has no reason to show up.
And so, we have to come up with
a way only to detain Itachi.
And doing that requires
a coordinated effort
involving more ninja.
Kakashi has his hands full
putting that very thing
together, right now.
-So, that's the plan.
-But we're dealing
with Itachi here.
He's an extraordinary ninja,
so ordinary methods won't work.
-Yeah, you're right.
And we can't simply follow
him around, I guess.
-What, and just bring Sasuke
back when he shows up.
I'm sure that you
know this, Naruto,
but Sasuke has grown
so powerful that he
was able to kill
Orochimaru himself.
-I'm well aware
of that, trust me.
But I made a promise.
I told Sakura that
I'd bring Sasuke back,
and that just what
I'm going to do.
No question, I promised.
I don't go back on my word.
PERVY SAGE: There's
only one thing that
matters if you're
a shinobi, and it
isn't the number of
jutsu you possess.
All you do need-- the
guts to never give up.
-It's all about guts.
That's what I believe.
That's my ninja way.
-I see you're just
as foolish as ever.
-Yeah well, I can't help it.
I am your apprentice, after all.
-Good grief, I got myself
one rude apprentice.
-What are you talking about?
Rude, what's that even mean?
-Exactly that, and thank
you for making my point.
-You think I'm rude?
Give me a break.
This coming from a
no-good pervy old man.
-Here, just eat this.
-Ooh, hm.
The roast pork at
Ichiraku is just the best.
[slurp]
[music playing]
TOBI: Man, sealing a tailed
beast is such a pain.
And there's even more
after this round?
Just thinking about
it all makes me tired.
-Now then, where to?
Hm.
-Wait, what do
you mean, Deidara?
Sorry, but I really have no
idea what you're trying to say.
-What do you think I mean?
Do we go for the
Nine-Tails jinchuriki who's
team is led by Kakashi, or do
we deal with Sasuke Uchiha?
-Frankly, I don't think
that we should mess around
with either one.
I mean, we've achieved
our objective.
Sasuke is not even
a tailed beast.
He isn't our concern.
-Are you kidding me?
I owe them all some pay back.
The Nine-Tailed jinchuriki
for punching me,
and Kakashi for
taking my right arm.
Hm.
And Sasuke, I must punish
him for killing Orochimaru
when I wanted to be the one
to deliver the final blow.
-Oh, great.
Once this guy decides, he
just won't listen to reason.
DEIDARA: Did you say something?
TOBI: Uh, no.
DEIDARA: Hm, we're leaving.
-That Deidara has
gotten so worked up.
And all that fuss is over
going after your little brother
or our target, that
Nine-Tailed jinchuriki.
Are you OK with that, Itachi?
[thunder]
-Time to go.
[music playing]
-I'm impressed.
You've planned this well.
-This is awesome.
But wouldn't it be better
with even more people?
-It's not simply a matter
of manpower, Naruto.
For this job, two teams
working together is ideal.
We're only after
one or two targets,
so two teams will give
us the right amount
of strength and flexibility.
Anymore, and we could
be detected too easily
and have difficulties
within our chain of command.
Plus, it would
hinder our mobility.
PERVY SAGE: Restraining an enemy
requires a lot more technique
than just killing him does.
In assembling the
teams, we thought
it wise to select ninja
whose skills compliment
each other's, ninja who are
used to working together.
-Well, I can't see you doing
much better than these ninja.
-Thank you, my lady.
I believe that we're
ready to set out now.
But what miserable weather
for a mission launch.
-Come on guys.
Let's go, already.
-I think the rain is
perfect for cooling down
those who are a
bit too fired up.
TSUNADE: Let's make it official.
I hereby authorize the
mission to locate and detain
Itachi Uchiha.
All of you, be careful,
but make certain
that you complete the mission.
GROUP: Right.
[theme music]
-Each search team is
basically comprised
of one ninja and
two ninja hounds.
Just in case the jinchuriki,
Naruto, is attacked,
Yamato and a sensory-type ninja,
Hinata, will accompany him.
-Thanks, Hinata.
-Sure.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Now listen.
You know we're after
Itachi and Sasuke.
But even if you
find either of them,
don't engage them yourselves.
Just meet at the rendezvous
point and inform us.
Now, scatter.
NARRATOR: Next time, "The Hunt."
GROUP: Good night, everybody.
SAKURA: Man, that was a
tough recording session.
-Hey Sakura, how about
we go get some ramen?
SAKURA: No thanks.
-Shut down, again.
-Um, Naruto--
-Huh?
What's wrong, Hinata?
-Well, I just-- if it's OK--
-Yeah, what?
-Um, I--
-Would you just
spit it out already?
-I think it's that lately, her
only line has been "Naruto."
-Yeah, that's true.
-Maybe we can just record it
once and use it every episode.
-What?
-It's the director's idea.
-It may be the same
line, but I say it
from the bottom of my
heart each and every time.
-Oh, So when you're embarrassed
-Naruto--
-When you're ecstatic--
-And when you're angry--
-Naruto--
SAKURA: Upset--
KAKASHI: Worried--
-Naruto--
TSUNADE: Happy--
PERVY SAGE: Scream it out.
-Naruto--
NARRATOR: Genius, we can
use those for a long time.
[whimper]
-No, no way!