[gasp]
[straining]
It's no use. You must open your
eyes Shikamaru.
Quit messing around. It's just
that I really hate getting woken
up when I'm...
...fast asleep!
[sigh]
(SHIKAMARU) Silver-4c, pawn-3f,
rook-4b, rook-4h...
...bishop-3f, pawn-1f, pawn-1d,
pawn-2f...
...then king-6b...
...king-6h, king-7b...
...king-7h, silver-6b...
(SAI) You're really hanging in
there.
The average shinobi probably
would've given up long ago.
(SHIKAMARU) I'm busy playing
shoji with past masters. I don't
have time to get bored.
I have to say, I do admire your
stubbornness.
You can learn a whole lot from
the game of shogi.
For example, no matter what
position you find yourself in,
there's always a way out.
Are you planning on getting out
of this situation? I look
forward to seeing that.
Hey, can you at least give me
back my lighter? I just can't
seem to calm down without it.
After you accept Lord Gengo's
beliefs, you can have it back
right away.
Why would you want to follow
a guy like that, Sai?
(SAI) Let's just say, that I
found the place where I belong.
And that wasn't the Hidden
Leaf?! I mean, come on! You were
a member of Team 7, weren't you?
Then why didn't Naruto come to
find me?
You and I have never been
particularly close, so why were
you the one who came here?
Naruto doesn't even know a
single thing about this whole
situation.
All of this was solely my
decision.
But even so... if it had been
Sasuke or Sakura, then surely
Naruto would've come.
(SHIKAMARU) I bet Gengo was the
one who put these ideas in your
head, right?
There's no doubt that Gengo
somehow controls people with his
words.
Just snap out of it, wake up!
I woke up a long time ago, when
Lord Gengo first gave me a new
will to follow.
[gasp]
Humph!
Wait!
You have more to say?
I promise that I'm gonna find
a way to undo Gengo's jutsu and
save you.
(SAI) I'd accept your fate if I
were you.
Otherwise, things will get much
worse for you.
[grunt]
(SHIKAMARU) You're part of the
Hidden Leaf! Don't forget that!
[grunt]
Pawn-4e, bishop-3c...
...then Knight-3g... No, I
can't...
I don't have enough pieces right
now. The king's gonna get away.
Hm?
[pained grunt & groan]
Hey, Ro? Is that you in there?
(RO) That voice... Lord
Shikamaru?
Listen, Gengo! Those two were
just obeying my orders!
If you're gonna kill someone,
then let it be me!
[pained groans]
(SHIKAMARU) Remember Ro, as long
as you're still alive, there's a
chance! So don't give up!
You better not die on me!
(RO) [pained groan] Fret not, to
me this is but a trifle.
(SHIKAMARU) What happened to
Soku? Wasn't she with you? She's
okay, isn't she?!
Hm? [gasp]
(GENGO) Why do you insist on
serving Feudal Lords
(GENGO) and incompetent people
who do nothing but oppress you?
That's, like none of your
business!
(GENGO) Remember the way those
people looked at you? What did
you see deep in their eyes?
I don't remember!
(GENGO) But you do! It's stuck
to your mind and won't go away.
Isn't that true?
(GENGO) Remember the eyes that
stared at you!
The suspicious eyes that feared
me and tried to discriminate
against me...
(GENGO) Why must someone as
proud and mighty as you...
(GENGO) surrender your life
for people like that?
(GENGO) Why pledge loyalty to
those who would only hold you in
bondage in return?
(SOKU) They're just using
me...?
(SOKU) Everyone's an enemy.
[gasp]
(GENGO) There's nothing to fear.
Now, turn. And accept
everything.
[gasp and grunts]
(SOKU) [panicking]
And with that, a new will has
just been granted to you.
[grunt]
(SAI) I've brought him, Lord
Gengo...
I apologize to you for the rude
treatment. As I'm sure you know,
I can't let my guard down.
I don't intent to talk to you,
It's obvious you're trying
to control me with your words.
(GENGO) You're starting to look
more like your father.
[grunt]
Forgive me, but I looked into
your background... into your
family and your friends...
And also the fact that you came
to this land to kill me.
[grunt]
(GENGO) Why do you people keep
trying to oppress us?
[grunt] And when exactly did we
do that?
This land hangs by a thread.
We barely have any natural
resources here, and the ground
lies fallow.
We're merely trying our hardest
to survive, and that's all.
(SHIKAMARU) Yeah, right. And
gathering up Rogue Ninja...
(SHIKAMARU) What's your motive?
Are you planning on starting a
war?
You're wrong. I'm not gathering
them.
They come to me of their own
free will in search of
salvation.
In search of salvation?
(GENGO) Have you never
questioned the way that shinobi
currently exist in the world?
Without war, they are no more
that hunting dogs for Feudal
Lords and the rich.
Is that truly a fitting life
for a shinobi?
What are you trying to say?
People come here because they
want to be real shinobi.
The alliance of nations that the
Leaf's currently a part of...
...is only going to maintain a
dark, tenuous peace
and will bind shinobi with
meaningless laws.
There will always be those who
reject such a peace.
This land is merely the
current gathering place for
them.
There always have to be some
rules if you're going to
maintain peace.
Your "peace" is just a falsehood
being forced upon us by the
Great Nations.
The Tailed Beasts you keep
are the proof of that.
[grunt]
(GENGO) Had you used one, this
land would be completely
helpless before you.
(GENGO) Isn't that so?
But we don't have any intention
of using a Tailed Beast for war
ever again!
Do you actually expect us to
believe that?
While you're keeping all the
Tailed Beasts to yourselves?!
Isn't that just a pretense the
Great Nations made up?
Quit jumping to conclusions!
(GENGO) Then why don't you prove
it? Give this land a Tailed
Beast.
(Grunt)
(GENGO) I believe the Hidden
Cloud has an extra one, don't
they?
(GENGO) Then we wouldn't
worry, and we could trust and
believe in you.
You know that we can't do that.
No, of course you can't. You
may espouse peace out in the
open...
...but deep down, beneath the
surface...
the fact of the
matter is that you don't trust
small nations like ours.
But that isn't enough of a
justification for you to go to
war!
I'm sure there's gotta be
another solution!
Another solution, you say?
Come with me.
There's something that I'd like
to show you, then.
(Grunt)
HUH?
What is this...?
Crops suitable for human
consumption aren't able to grow
at our land's elevation.
So the people here all live in
poverty, and they have very
little to eat.
If we just had a product to
sell, something to add value to
their lives...
(GENGO) This flower is the
result of a selective breeding
program.
(GENGO) You've seen it here and
there in the wild, haven't you?
But all of it was just for
nothing...
(Gasp)
(GENGO) This flower wilts the
moment it's taken out of this
village,
(GENGO) due to our unique
environment.
(GENGO) Why did you choose to
become a shinobi?
(GENGO) To file papers for the
rest of your life?
Who knows?
Heh.
Most likely, that isn't the
case.
After all, you still train every
day in order to hone your
skills.
(GENGO) You use those skills to
defeat the enemy and protect
what is precious.
(GENGO) That's the way a shinobi
should live.
(GENGO) That's the way your
father, lived. And your mentor,
too.
(Grunt)
And just how would you know
that, huh?!
In all probability, you're
hoping that you'll be able to
measure up to them both someday.
And yet in a world where peace
has become the norm,
is there really a way for you to
accomplish that?
(GENGO) It's because of war that
shinobi abilities were able to
develop so remarkably.
(GENGO) If instead there'd been
continual peace,
(GENGO) you never would've spent
all those priceless moments with
your friends.
(GENGO) Can you really say that
I'm wrong?
(Gasp)
(SHIKAMARU) If that's the price
for peace,... then I'll gladly
throw down my weapons.
You're not really speaking from
the heart.
(SHIKAMARU) You can feel your
own abilities weakening, can't
you?
(Gasp)
Now, Shikamaru...
(Grunt)
Get away from me!
You two, stand down!
(labored breathing)
(GENGO) Don't be frightened,
Shikamaru... Just... lower your
weapon...
(SHIKAMARU)
(heavy breathing)
(GENGO) Yes, that's it...
First, why don't you just try to
calm down? Take a deep breath.
Do you like it?
The scent of my precious flowers
is nice, isn't it?
(Gasp)
Come on now...
(SHIKAMARU) I see... so, that's
it...
(Grunt)
Certain flowers produce scents
that have the ability to stir up
people's memories.
That's what you've been using to
brainwash people. That's "the
will" you've been giving them!
Unfortunately, that discovery
won't get you anywhere.
(GENGO) You can't defy me.
Where are my comrades? Where are
Ro and Soku?! Bring them to me
now!
(RO) We're right here.
(Gasp)
(SHIKAMARU) Huh! You two?!
(SHIKAMARU)
(Gasp)
(SOKU) Like, Lord Gengo has
given us a new will...
(GUARD) Find him! Don't let him
escape the castle!
Please, Shikamaru, it's useless
to try to hide.
(heavy breathing)
(Grunt)
Oh, man... My shoulder is still
numb... Nice shot, Soku...
Huh?
I can't use my Shadows with
these clouds.
My rook and bishop
advantage is gone, too. Not
good...
Hmmm...
The "Climbing Silver" move,
right off the bat like that?
To penetrate the enemy's line
sometimes you have to be willing
to risk a bold move.
If I escape now, the risk for
the Hidden Leaf will increase.
That's what you told me
back then. So, I guess
that time has come for me...
Just stay calm. There's still a
chance that an opportunity will
appear.
(ASUMA) You know what?  I'd say
you were most like the knight.
Climbing Silver to break through
enemy lines... or maybe just a
knight that jumps far... Hmm?
Hmm...
(SHIKAMARU) I guess that I have
no choice but to jump back into
the den of the king...
(RO) Lord Gengo, are you sure
it's all right to leave the
search for Shikamaru to Sai?
(SOKU) Like, it'll be bad if he
gets out of the castle.
(GENGO) Oh don't worry.
(GENGO) If he's cornered, he's
the type to throw himself into
an even more difficult situation
(GENGO) to escape. Isn't that
right, Shikamaru?
(Gasp)
So, you knew I was here, huh? ú
That's no fun.
I was certain that you'd never
leave this lighter behind.
(SOKU) Like, you came back just
for that? Boy, you're really
something!
Surrender and be captured!
(Grunt)
(Gasp)
(SHIKAMARU) Well if the floor
won't work, then there's always
the ceiling.
(Gasp)
(RO) Below!
(RO) Can't move!
All right...
(Gasp) Lord Shikamaru,
release me!
To break a genjutsu, the theory
is to bring down the one who
cast it.
(SHIKAMARU) What do you say,
Gengo?
Impossible. There's nobody who's
able to resist my words.
Sorry... but you're gonna have
to be my shield for a while, Ro.
(GENGO) Fire! Don't worry about
hitting Ro!
(SHIKAMARU) Yeah, go ahead. Just
make sure you aim straight.
(Grunt)
Stop, Shikamaru! You can't
resist my voice!
Don't tell me that you?!
(GENGO) You purposely let Soku
hit you in the ears in order to
dull your sense of hearing?!
(SHIKAMARU) Alright this is the
knight's jump!
Huh!
(Gasp)
Uhh!
You were so close, Shikamaru. So
very close!!
(SAI) Please stay back, Lord
Gengo. Just leave this to me.
Nicely done!
(SHIKAMARU) Gengo!
(Gasp)
(RO) You won't get away this
time!
(Gasp)
(Roar)
Damn it!
(sigh)
(SHIKAKU) Damn it. Girls just
keep beating you up...
(SHIKAKU) Weren't you going to
become a stronger leader for the
sake of your friends??
(SHIKAMARU) Dad... I... I just
don't think I'm cut out to be a
Shinobi.
(disappointed sigh)
(GENGO) Is he dead?
(SOKU) I didn't, like, kill him
yet.
In the end, he had no chance
against the three of us.
(SAI) How pitiful...
(SHIKAMARU) I'm at my physical
limit. Even the air feels heavy!
Man, this is such a drag...
(Gasp)
Huh?
Hey, Shikamaru. ú You okay?
Don't you dare go dying on us
now!
(Chuckle)
No way! ú You guys?!
But ú what're you doing here?
Oh... ú Okay, I'm still
dreaming...
(TEMARI) Shikamaru!
(SHIKAMARU) T-Temari?!
I expected more out of you!
Why're you just sitting there,
dazed like that?!
Shikamaru!
Take it easy, Temari!
Yeah, or else he really could
die...
Oh, just shut up!
That's what you get for lying to
me back at the Allied Forces
Summit.
(SHIKAMARU) I'm sorry, Temari.
Huh?
(Chuckle) Thanks to you, I've
come to my senses.
Shikamaru...?!
Sorry, but can you take over for
me here? I have one more guy
that I still need to take down.
You mean Gengo?!
(SHIKAMARU) Huh? How'd you
know that?!
Lord Hokage told me everything.
And I had a hell of a time
getting it out of him, too...
(SHIKAMARU) I don't want to know
what you did. I don't even want
to imagine it!
(Grunt)
Shikamaru, is it okay if we
crush these guys?
They're brainwashed, but they're
our comrades, so be gentle ok.
(SHIKAMARU) Oh and could you
wake them up, too!
Like, shut your mouth.
Hold on!
Huh?
(TEMARI) You're forgetting
something.
Uh!
(Gasp)
(TEMARI) He probably knows
you're coming and has laid traps
for you.
I hope you can win
as banged up as you are.
(SHIKAMARU) I'm no sacrificial
pawn.
(Grunt)
Oh!
Well, all right then!
(chuckle)
Okay... it's time for
our final moves...
Gengo!
TO BE CONTINUED...
(GENGO) The Leaf is still that
important to you?
(SHIKAMARU) Damn right it is!
(GENGO) Then I'll let you in on
a little secret...
(GENGO) What would you think if
I told you I've sent my
followers,
(GENGO) with the will I bestowed
upon them, into all the
Hidden Villages?
(SHIKAMARU) What's that?!
(SHIKAMARU) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:
"Shikamaru's Story, A Cloud
Drifting in the Silent Dark,
Part 5: Dawn."
(GENGO) And you don't have the
means to stop it!