[music playing]
[theme music]
-I have two bells in my hand.
And the fact that there
are only two means--
-That one of us will lose.
-Very sharp, Orochimaru.
-Hey, if I get a bell then
you go out with me, Tsunade.
-Fine, but when you lose don't
bother me anymore, all right?
-Yeah, all right!
Let's do this!
So many chances, here goes.
Ah.
[laughing]
-I told you, I won the bet.
So you get tied up.
And you have to
stay away from me.
-Oh, just shut up, stupid
flat-as-a-board Tsunade.
What did you just say to
me, you little brainy perv?
-Now, now, I'd
say, that's enough.
Tsunade and Orochimaru may go.
-Bye.
-Hmm.
-Uh, you're hopeless Jiraiya.
How can a ninja keep falling
into such obvious traps?
-Can't help it.
-Perhaps you're simply lacking
a purpose to give you direction.
-Like what?
-Let's see, what can we do?
Yes, we can try that.
That just may work.
-What?
What is it?
-Don't get too excited.
Just watched this.
-Huh?
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Whoa, cool!
-It's the Summoning Jutsu.
It's simple, really.
You make a contract in
blood with an animal.
And then you can
summon that animal
at any given time using the
transportation technique.
I want to make a contract
with that one too, right now.
-Sorry, but that you can't do.
-Uh.
-In the same way that
every man is destined
to a different fate,
so too is the animal
to whom he is entwined.
So what animal am
I entwined with?
-Before you can
make such a contract
you need to become more adept
at infusing Chakra and making
signs.
-What?
Come on, are you kidding me?
More training?
-You will always find
the answer to any problem
within your training.
Jiraiya had found a purpose.
And from that day on, he began
taking his training seriously.
However--
-Infuse more Chakra.
Study up on making signs.
[grunting]
-I must master the
transportation technique
or else.
Oh, come on.
Will I ever be ready
to make a contract?
Why do I put myself through
all this rough training anyway?
-If I were to have
a boyfriend I'd
choose Orochimaru over
a brainy perv like you.
The answer is simple.
I just have to become
the ultimate ninja.
And then I'll sweep
Tsunade off her feet.
Now that I know what I need to
do, there's no time to waste!
-Well, look at that.
He's discovered his purpose
for becoming a ninja.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
And not just Tsunade.
I'm going to get all
the pretty girls.
Let's see,
concentrate my Chakra.
Make the seal.
Boar, dog, bird, monkey, sheep.
-No!
Wait!
There's no telling
what will happen
if you use the transportation
technique without making
a contract!
-And go!
[screaming]
[whimpers]
[groaning]
-Where am I?
[hissing]
-Wait!
Hold it right there!
I, the great master,
Jiraiya, will fight.
Ha!
Now, that's the way you do it.
-Hmm--
-Uh--
-It's a human child.
-Uh, are you seriously
a talking toad?
-To think that a human
would come to Mount Myoboku,
I never thought I'd see it.
-Wait, what do you mean by that?
-Master Fukasaku,
it's a human child.
-So I see.
You have arrived at last.
-You say that as though
you were expecting
me to show up all along.
-That's because we
knew you were coming.
The Great Elder predicted
this very happenstance.
-One day, a human child will
stumble into Mount Myoboku.
And I will give that child
the power of the toad
as well as the prophecy.
And that is the very
essence of the dream
which I have dreamt for myself.
My very own prophecy.
-But wait, if I'm
that human child, then
what does the
prophecy say about me?
-Well, I'm afraid I don't know.
-What?
You don't know?
-You must stay here
and train and wait
for the Great Lord
Elder's prophecy.
-Wait, wait, hold on.
I made up my mind
to become strong
so that I'd be popular
with the girls,
not so I'll be
popular with frogs.
-There's no point
in complaining.
Your destiny's your destiny.
And that is that.
-My destiny?
-Yes, you did manage to come
to Mount Myoboku after all.
That is proof enough
that you are, indeed,
the chosen one that the
Great Lord Elder spoke of.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
The chosen one, huh?
I like the sound of that.
Training here and
becoming strong,
that's pretty tempting too.
FUKASAKU: From that
day forward, Jiraiya
divided his time between Mount
Myoboku, The Village of Toads,
and The Hidden Leaf Village.
He spent the days of his youth
learning Ninjutsu and training
to become a sage.
However, it was
nowhere near as simple
as Jiraiya had thought it
would be when he first started.
-Without a doubt, I've gotten
stronger since coming here.
But Tsunade is as cold as ever.
Well, not just that.
If I was destined to
be the chosen one,
should my purpose be
merely to impress girls?
Is that really the
only reason that I'm
trying to become strong?
-Jiraiya!
Jiraiya!
-Yeah?
-The Great Lord Elder
has summoned you Jiraiya.
-What?
The Great Lord Elder did?
-Yes, you must hurry.
He has seen your
prophecy at last.
-What?
Are you serious Bunta?
You summoned me?
-Well, how nice.
So you've finally come.
I'm glad.
But uh, who are you again?
Lord, this is Jiraiya.
Jiraiya.
He's the human child.
-Oh yes, of course, I
remember it all now.
My, my, you sure have grown.
-You're the one who summoned
him here in the first place,
you great senile geezer.
-Ma, how dare you?
You musn't refer to The Great
Lord Elder as a senile geezer!
Have some more
respect, would ya?
-Now, now, let's not fight.
Spouses must do their
best to get along.
Oh, and by the way,
um, who are you again?
-He's dreamt of you Jiraiya boy.
And as you are no doubt aware,
his dream was not just a dream.
It was a prophecy of the future
which he will now tell you.
So listen carefully.
-Yes sir.
-I shall now tell you.
I will relate my dream.
You, who are singularly pervish
shall become a great ninja.
And once you do,
you shall acquire
an apprentice of your very own.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Pervy?
Ugh, I can't believe he
remembers that, of all things.
-That apprentice
will become a ninja
who will bring about a great
change in the ninja world.
That is what I
foresaw in my dream.
-What kind of great change?
-Either great stability
or great destruction,
the likes of which this
world has never seen,
but which of these
two, I cannot say.
-So it's either
one or the other.
What does that mean exactly?
-You will be the one to guide
this revolutionary change.
And eventually there
will come a day
when you will be forced to
make it critical selection.
-To make a selection?
-Yes, and whatever
choice you end up making,
it will direct the way that this
great change is going to go.
-What must I do in order
to make the correct choice?
-In my dream I see you traveling
around the world writing books.
-Writing books?
But what for?
-I do not know.
But perhaps it means
you shall travel widely,
seeing all things
in this universe.
-But Great Lord Elder,
have any of your prophecies
ever not come to pass?
-No, never.
-So you're going to start
traveling, is that right?
-Yep.
At this point in my
life I just can't
be a guide to a revolutionary.
And I certainly don't know
how to make the right choice
in my prophecy.
-Oh.
-I think what I need now is
time to see more of the world
and meet different people.
-I see.
-So as foreseen in The
Great Lord Elder's dream,
I'll journey
throughout the world
and maybe write a book too.
It seems that that's my destiny.
FUKASAKU: While Jiraiya
journeyed and searched
for the meaning behind The
Great Lord Elder's dream,
the state of the world
grew steadily more chaotic.
The peace that existed
between the five great nations
grew fragile.
Aggression between the
lands escalated greatly.
And within land's
borders, internal strife
increased as well.
And everywhere people began
to suffer great hardships.
-Young man, may I ask
why you're traveling?
-I'm searching for my destiny.
-Oh really?
-I journey from land to land,
as I was foretold in a dream.
[baby crying]
-Oh my, what's wrong?
-Here, have one.
It's milk candy.
It's just a puppet.
-This child tells me
destiny is in something
that you search for.
Destiny is something you
latch onto when it appears.
An age of war is coming.
My mechanical skills are
useless in times of peace.
But some Lord may pay a
high price for my services
in battle.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
So he's a Shinobi too.
And he's chosen to ride the wave
toward the age of destruction.
That will only hasten it.
-Come on, let's
do something fun.
Please?
-Mm.
-What's that you're
writing anyway?
-Just scribblings for now.
Basically, it says that writing
on the wave of the times
can never bring about
the revolutionary change
that we need to achieve peace.
-You know, if you really want
to change something, change me.
-Mm, I suppose you're right.
That does sound
like a lot more fun.
-This is fraud!
You think I'm going to pay
for something like this?
-Hold it right there.
I'll take over now.
If you want to fight, fight me!
-Dammit, how can
fate be so cruel?
I've worked hard to better my
land with what little knowledge
I have, all for the
sake of my clan.
And yet--
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
So this guy's
dissatisfied with the way
the world is going too.
Here pal, have a drink on me.
You know, I've been
searching for my destiny too.
But it's been proving
quite elusive.
-Huh, it's useless
to search for that.
My people simply
don't stand a chance
against the Shinobi villages
of the great nations.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Ugh,
is that all this guy can do,
complain?
-You're wrong, you know.
-Hmm?
-I am a teacher in a village.
And what I do there is
show the children just
how they can fight back when
they find themselves facing
a harsh fate.
So what, education
can stop a war?
Enough of your useless lecture.
Is he a Shinobi too?
-No.
It can't stop a war.
But perhaps at the least
I can teach the children
new skills that will enable
them to make better choices.
-Let me ask you, just what
are those choices then?
-Life or death, of course.
Those are the choices.
The only lesson that I'm
truly capable of teaching them
is how to survive.
-Hmm.
(VOICEOVER) That's
not good enough.
I must find the
revolutionary who
can bring peace
to the world, then
make the choice that
will get in there.
-Huh?
-To bring destruction on this
world or to bring about a peace
unlike any we've
known, it all depends
on the commitment
of each person.
-Hmm, could he be the one?
Hey, you up there.
You just might be the person
I've been looking for.
-Oh really?
-Tell me, how would you
bring peace to this world?
-This world is careening
toward an age of war, strife
and sadness.
And nothing can stop it.
-You just said, it depends
on people's commitment.
So how do we go about changing
these people's destinies then?
-All we can do is
pray and have faith.
That's all any man can do
in a world like this one.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Hmm,
this man isn't the one either.
-What's that?
Bah!
If this was just an
ordinary village why would
a Shinobi do this?
[breathing heavily]
That Shooter Kinjutsu, you're
from the Fuma, aren't you?
Why are you attacking
villagers living in peace?
-You're a Shinobi too.
-I'm journeying in search of one
who will become my apprentice.
-Ha, why waste time on
something so tedious?
The balance of power between
the lands is teetering.
And we're standing on
the verge of a great war.
That village was
destroyed because of a tip
that Shinobi had infiltrated it.
-All that because of a mere tip?
-It's destroy or be destroyed.
In this world you
hesitate and you die.
-Huh?
Smoke bomb.
[grunting]
-You're pretty
good, you know that?
-If you're a Shinobi too
than I cannot let you live.
Look, just give up now.
This is our fate,
the fate of Shinobi.
-Can I-- say something?
-I don't want to hear it.
Just die!
-Give up, huh?
Yeah, about that--
-Even if you do take me
down, another assassin
will attack the village.
As long as we're cursed to live
in this world of the Shinobi
there can be no peace.
-The Great Lord
Elder's prophecy said
that I'm destined to train
the Revolutionary who
could at last bring peace
to this troubled world.
But in all my travels,
I haven't even
come close to finding
this apprentice.
FUKASAKU: Even at
that early stage,
battles were inevitably being
fought between the lands.
Jiraiya was forced to put his
journeys on hold and return
to the Hidden Leaf
Village to do his part
alongside the other Shinobi.
-Tsunade, we are at war.
-Orochimaru-- to erase
this sadness from the world
of the Shinobi I must find
the revolutionary from
the prophecy.
I must choose the one who
could bring peace to all of us.
FUKASAKU: The flames of war
that have consumed so many
throughout history finally drew
in Jiraiya and his comrades.
The conflict that they
entered would one day
be called the Third
Great Ninja War.
And afterward, thanks
to their exploits,
Jiraiya and his
compatriots would
come to be known as
the legendary Sannin.
[theme music]
JIRAIYA: Boy, it sure
isn't easy coming up
with ideas for writing a book.
The hero of this one
has seen too much
of the world of the
Shinobi, where fighting only
breeds more fighting.
It's a world filled with hate.
I want him, somehow, to wipe
away the hate and create peace.
And yet, it's so hard
to think about how
to build up the
story to its climax.
What am I going to do?
Next time, Tales
of a Gutsy Ninja,
Jiraiya Ninja Scrolls, Part Two.