Thanks for the food!
[exhaling]
Boy, that sure filled me
up! 'Course, it doesn't
compare to Ichiraku
Ramen! But what can?
[grunting]
What's that?
[screaming]
Oh, it's you again! Why
don't you just give up
already?!
Look, my business isn't
with you. You're just
the chaperone. I want to
fight the princess that's
next to you!
Never! I will not allow
that!
Lady Shizuka, you don't
need to dirty your hands
with the likes of him!
This is my destiny.
Please just stand back.
Huh?
How is it you always look
more beautiful? Now
hurry; I want you to be
my wife!
Huh?
Uh?
Nadeshiko Style! Roaring
Hurricane Kick
[yelling]
Huh?!
[screaming]
You'll pay for this!
[cheering]
Incredible, Lady Shizuka.
But now please wait at
the inn. I will check on
the travel arrangements
we've made for the ship.
Thank you.
Whoa, man, that lady...
She's some shinobi. But
it has nothing to do with
me!
Sir! Please wait!
Huh?
From that headband you
wear, I see that you're
a leaf shinobi.
Huh? Oh. Yeah.
May I ask you... about
the Legendary Sannin,
Lord Jiraiya?
Uhh--
Do you know anyone who
was his student?
"The Kunoichi of
Nadeshiko Village"
What a surprise, to
find the person we're
seeking, right here.
We were about to board a
ship to sail to the
Hidden Leaf to find you.
Yeah, it was quite a
surprise to me, too to
hear Pervy Sage's name
out of the blue like that.
How'd you know about me?
Didn't Lord Jiraiya tell
you?!
About what?
Then I'll tell you...
Your Master Jiraiya had a
connection with my
village that began years
ago.
Don't lose him, girls! We'll
teach him what happens to
those who infiltrate our
village!
Just great... I only came
here to do a little
research for my next
novel.
[sighing]
[chuckling]
They're so cute,
but so dangerous. Huh?
Just give yourself up.
Uh! Sorry, but I
just can't do that.
[grunting]
Mister Gamaken! Secret
Technique! Exit Jutsu!
I'm quite ungraceful so,
hang on!
Get him!
Right!
Uh! That's cold!
That's rejuvenating.
Huh?
I didn't expect you to
chase me this far.
The technique you
displayed last night was
simply incredible.
But you didn't just come
here to tell me that, did
you?
I've seen your skill and
want to make a request.
Like what?
Hidden Leaf Jonin Lord
Jiraiya... Please duel
with me, and marry me if
you win.
Stop! No! Where is this
going?!
Nadeshiko Village is
matrilineal. It's made up
of only women.
What?! Seriously?!
Those who wish to be
leader leave the village
to find strong men and
challenge them.
And then, if those men are
triumphant, they're brought
back to be our husbands.
It's the law of
our village.
Their duel was a clash of
well-honed ninjutsu
skills... But in the end,
the match was never
actually decided.
[gasping]
So they made a promise.
The duel would be
postponed.
And if their rematch
never came to be, their
students were to seek
each other out and finish
the fight.
So you're saying
that...?!
Hmm.
You're to duel with Lady
Shizuka, with the reward
being her hand in
marriage.
M- Marriage?!
Listen, this is all way
too sudden for me!
It's not sudden at all.
It was decided years ago.
But this is the first
time I'm hearing about
it!
Sorry, but that's your
problem! Besides, a
promise is a promise.
We'll be in big trouble
if you refuse!
Yeah, but I'll be in
big trouble if I agree!
Anyway--
...let's just forget we
ever had this conversation!
No! Wait!
You will duel. I vow it!
[laughing]
A marriage proposal, just
like that, huh? You're
quite popular!
It's not like that, I'm
telling you!
Just 'cause Pervy Sage
made some careless promise,
I have to pay for it now!
[chuckling]
[sighing]
You know... We are on a
secret mission, here, in
case you've forgotten that.
We can't get involved in
any foolish distractions.
Should we move up our
departure?
Yes, good idea.
Luckily, we've gotten all
of our supplies
restocked.
So let's go to bed early
and leave first thing in
the morning.
[snoring]
[grunting]
I shouldn't have had so
much tea...
Huh?
Eeeeh.
Uh, time out, okay? One
sec...
Stop following me, would
you?! I mean, just leave
me alone, all right?
You can't escape me. You
are a prime candidate for
a husband.
I already said no! What
more do you want out of
me, anyway?!
I know that it's your
village tradition and
all. But all it is to me
is weird.
I'm not taking
part in any duel!
But--
If you really want a
fight that badly, go pick
on someone else, would
you?!
Please don't say such
things!
[gasping]
Lady Shizuka doesn't
enjoy this at all,
either, I assure you!
She's always been
kindhearted and
compassionate.
However...
I wish we could stay like
this...
Well, then why
don't we?
We can't!
I understand the position
you're in. But... It's just
ludicrous to pick a husband
only through battle.
But, Sagiri...
I know that I'm only a
lowly tradesman who's
been allowed into the
village.
I'm not a strong
warrior. But I love you
more than anything.
I just want you to be
happy. So I'll do
everything in my power to
change the village's law!
And some day, I will
succeed! I swear it.
No one knows for sure,
but some say it was a
plot concocted by a few
who were concerned about
the village's future.
He was attacked and taken
down easily... To prove
that he wasn't fit for
the Nadeshiko.
That's horrible...!
And from that day onward,
Lady Shizuka locked away
her heart.
She stopped herself from
feeling love... So she
could never again lose
someone she cares for.
She's only thought of
fulfilling her duty...
of seeking out and
challenging the strong.
It's as though... she
was punishing herself
for what happened.
And that's why you want
me to fight her?!
You're the student of the
formidable Jiraiya, who
fought our previous
leader to a draw.
You may be able to put an
end to Lady Shizuka's
struggles.
I am fully aware that
this is a selfish request,
but please--will you agree
to fight Lady Shizuka?!
I don't believe that
we're being watched
by anyone.
Then we should be okay
once we leave this port.
[chuckling]
You just gave up your
chance to become a groom.
This'll buy us a little
time, at least...
Naruto, I'm deeply
grateful that you've
agreed to fight this
duel.
Well, I'm really sorry,
but I didn't come here
to fight...
I just came
to talk.
What?
Look, I heard about what
happened to you. And I'm
sorry. But this whole
thing's weird!
You may not be here to
fight, but I am.
Now let's find out how
strong you are.
This will do fine.
Earth Style! Iron Prison!
I'm not gonna do this.
Don't try to fight
destiny. Please, allow
me to begin.
[grunting]
Nadeshiko Style! Roaring
Gale Chop!
Nadeshiko Style! Aerial
Dance!
Damn! She's got
a lot of those!
You are indeed strong,
Naruto.
But you can't just keep
dodging.
All right!
Spinning-Waltz!
There's just no end to
them!
Gale Fan!
[gasping]
Looks like it's all over.
Yeah, I guess so.
[gasping]
Now it's over.
A diversion in the second
stage... No one's ever
gotten behind me.
Just deliver the final
blow, then.
No way. I told you I
didn't come here to
fight.
I'm not interested in the
duel.
Then I'll take the woman
for myself!
Huh?
[laughing]
Now I've got you!
What a cowardly attack!
This trick is less than
nothing!
[chuckling]
[screaming]
This is called the
Hundred Puppet Bind. It's
a jutsu that drives bolts or
anchor points into my target.
...each time one of my
hundred puppets is
beaten.
And now, you've become my
puppet.
That means... the puppets
from before were all for
this?
You coward!
Yes, I've done it! And
now Shizuka and Nadeshiko
Village are all mine!
Let her go!
Huh?
We were still talking.
Let her go, now!
Just shut up! It's none
of your business! Get
lost! I'm going to take
her away from here and-
Huh?
[gasping]
Rasengan!
[screaming]
But why save me...?
I've had just about
enough of this! Don't
be ridiculous!
No, not that! You had a
chance to defeat me
before!
And would you have been
satisfied if I did?
[gasping]
Because it's "destiny," you
locked away your heart and
your whole self just to go
look for a husband?
That's crazy!
I mean, maybe I don't
know much about marriage
and stuff...
But aren't you supposed
to be in love with someone
first and be attracted to
who they are deep inside?
Yes, but that's--
There's a girl I love.
Her name's Sakura.
Uh!
Well actually, It is
pretty one-sided on my
part.
[sighing]
Sakura is completely in
love with this other guy
named Sasuke.
She tries so hard,
pursuing him and trying
to win his love.
When she's at it... her
smile is the just about
the cutest thing you've
ever seen.
I can't explain it, but
before I knew it, I was
in love with her.
Of course, even if I do
feel that way, I would
never, ever try to force
her to love me.
I'd be no different from
that guy just now!
[chuckling]
So early on, I made up my
mind. Just like Sakura
always tries so hard to
win Sasuke over...
I'm going to try my
hardest to win Sakura
over!
I see. But my destiny is
different...
It's not destiny! It's
just some rule your
village made up!
And rules were meant
to be broken!
But... But how?!
[chuckling]
You're smart and strong.
Use your abilities to
put an end to it!
[gasping]
I'm not sure that I
explained it well... but
that's what I wanted to
talk to you about.
Naruto!
Captain Yamato!
You did it again! You ran
off on your own!
[gasping]
That's the second time
you've fooled me with a
Shadow Clone.
I hope you're prepared
for the consequences.
Oh. Um. I...
No!
We're just about to set
sail.
I'll be right there.
You take care of
yourself.
When your mission is
over...
Yeah?
When you go back home,
are you going to tell
that person that you love
her?
No. I don't think I can
bring myself to do that
yet...
For right now, I
think that I'll just
keep watching over her.
And you're satisfied with
that?
Of course, nothing would make
me happier than if she
chooses me someday. But,
either way it's okay.
I just want Sakura to be
happy. That's all that
matters.
I just want you to be
happy.
Sorry, but this fight
ends now.
You see, unfortunately,
I've already given my
heart to another woman.
Although it is pretty
one-sided on my part...
No kidding... even
for someone like you?
She's lost all the people
she's loved, one after
another.
So now she simply rejects
love in order to keep her
heart protected.
I've sworn to watch over
her. It's my duty, and I
won't abandon it.
Even when there's no
reward in it for you?
[laughing]
As if I care about such a
little thing as that!
No, I'm just going to
surround her with love
and hope that she finds
happiness!
That's all
that matters!
I understand. Well, then,
I guess for now let's
call this a draw.
Then... I'll have to
challenge this man's
student!
Shizuka...
There's no doubt you bear
the burden of your
destiny. However...
There's no need for you
to lock your heart
away...
Lady Shizuka...
Lets go, Tokiwa.
I will become stronger,
and then one day, when
the time is right...
Yes...
It's true. A war that
will decide the future of
the shinobi world will
soon begin.
It would be a lie to say
that I'm not afraid. But
whatever happens, I'm
confident that I will
come back alive.
The reason is because
I have friends that I
trust.
Next Time on Naruto
Shippuden: Friends You
Can Count On.
You'll understand,
too, one day.