I'll have to
teleport it away with me!
Here, you can
have this back.
[gasp]
Don't worry.
I only teleported a clone.
I marked him earlier,
that time before when we
had made contact with him.
That's amazing!
You can copy my dad's move!
Nice, Second
Great Stone Face guy!
Lord Fourth is
actually using my move!
Plus, that is
"Lord Second" to you!
-Hm?
-[chuckling]
Wood Style: Wood Dragon!
[roar]
Out of my way, Madara!
I don't have much time
but there's something
I've got to do now!
Wood Style:
Wood Golem Jutsu!
Now I'm going to take
another chunk of you!
[painful gorans]
Amazing!
They're on another level!
So this is the
battle capacity
of our predecessors?!
We'd just get in
their way if we went out
there and tried to join in.
In a battle like
they're waging we'd be
of no use whatsoever!
Ino, please!
Got it.
Even a small power
can be helpful
depending on
how it's used.
Shikamaru?
We may not be any help now,
but there might come a time
when we will be needed.
So don't take your eyes
off the battlefield in
case such a time arrives!
Our power could change
the course of this world!
We can't afford to relax
and let our guard down,
even for one second!
Yeah!
He's right!
[chuckle]
Shikamaru, you would
make a great Hokage.
The ability to sway people's
hearts is practically a
requirement for any Kage.
This is just like
the time back then.
Madara, at one
time, we were friends!
We both shared
the same dream!
Hashirama!
How long will you keep
saying such childish things?
It is not possible
to show each other
what is inside of us!
Do you really not get it?
Hashirama!
Madara!
The end result will be
different this time, though.
So when are we supposed to
make our move, Shikamaru?
You should try to think
for yourself a little
more once in a while!
First, we need
to figure out the
circumstances of their battle.
Also, what's
going on down there?
Well, did he get him?
He blocked it, huh?
He's fast.
We can't hit him
with ordinary jutsu.
I'll have to use my
Rasen-Flash Super-Circle
Dance Howl Stage Three.
I'll create an
opening for us all with it.
You're, uh a bit of a
comedian, aren't you?
I would normally make fun
of all your jutsu names.
Except this guy is no joke.
Amaterasu!
Sasuke!
Naruto!
I said I'd make an
opening for you!
I'll create an opening!
No way, we'll both do it!
We'll let Dad and the
others be the main act!
I saw you amassing
chakra in your left eye.
Hardly a surprise attack.
So frustrating...
Come on, Fourth, let's go.
A clone's Flying
Raijin will be too slow.
Let's combine
and reciprocate
our Flying Raijin.
Go ahead and put your
mark on me, as well.
Yes, sir.
Plus with these
bodies, we can still
move after being hit!
Naruto!
This time, I'll match
your chakra level using
my Sharingan, got it?
All right, all right!
I mean, there's no need to
turn this whole thing into a
competition, you know!
-Inferno Style: Flame Control!
-Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
Pincer attack?!
You two are the main act!
Distracted by
what's in front of you?
Now!
Reciprocal
Round-Robin Jutsu!
Flying Raijin Jutsu!
I name it the Scorch
Style Nimbus Tempest!
Keep going as planned!
[attacking yell]
They switched places
by teleporting with
the Flying Raijin?!
Hinata!
How're Naruto and Sasuke?
They're both... smiling!
Smiling?!
Both of them?
Yeah.
[harrumphing chuckle]
All right!
So, did you guys get him?!
We made a direct hit
before those black
things could protect him.
I'm pretty sure
he felt that one!
[gasp]
It had no effect at all.
We have to avoid those
black transforming spheres.
And our attacks
have no effect on him.
His offense and
defense are so fast!
What a pain.
He's even more perfect
than how I imagine
myself in my dreams!
I mean, he's just perfect!
You've got a point.
It's like he's truly
obtained dreamlike power.
There's something odd.
What is it?
You only lost an arm.
Dust should be swirling
around in order
to restore it by now.
Our reanimated bodies
aren't regenerating.
I now possess the same
power that the Founder
of Shinobi possessed.
You can no longer measure
me by the standards
you're used to.
Don't tell me
that your jutsu--!
What does he mean, the power
of the Founder of Shinobi?
Listen, Fourth.
Don't get seriously wounded
even though you've got a
reanimated body.
I think he's using a jutsu
based on Shadow and Light
Styles that
nullifies all ninjutsu.
In short, if he hits your
reanimated body you'll be
unable to regenerate
could even die!
[gasp]
Also assume that
right arm of yours is
permanently gone.
In which case, we'll
need to fight him
even more carefully.
But since ninjutsu
won't work on him,
this'll be tricky.
How about
physical attacks?
Let's try it.
Sasuke...
What is it?
You and I going to have to
take the lead on this one.
Think you can you keep up?
Don't
underestimate the Uchiha.
All right, then!
I'll up my Kurama Mode
and go deeper into
Tailed Beast State!
Uh oh...
Are you trying to
make things even worse?
You're as goofy as your
father, so much so
that even he's dumbfounded.
S-Sorry.
Kurama!
Come on, lend me some more
of your chakra, would ya!
Just hold off on
Nine Tails State!
But he's not someone
we can beat without it!
If you want to enter into
Perfect Tailed Beast State,
fight in normal
mode for now!
[sigh]
Syrup Gun!
A Mount Myoboku toad?!
What was that, Gamakichi?
If you wanna make a move,
do a diversion or combo!
Sorry, Naruto. We're rapidly
approaching the time limit
for the summoning.
I just wanted to
repay that guy with a
little parting shot!
Thanks for the
effort anyway, Gamakichi!
Now go rest up, okay?
Sorry about this.
Huh?
[gasp] Is that?
Obito!
I thought what you
wanted was to become Hokage.
Why are you doing this?!
You want to know why?
This is my chance!
You're going to
lecture me now?
Bit late for that, Sensei.
Don't you think?
You're always too late
when it matters most.
It seems that Rin and
Kakashi are totally
surrounded.
Sounds like all of the Mist
guys appear to be jonin or
ANBU Black Ops.
What's Minato Sensei doing?
Who?
I'm asking what the Yellow
Flash of the Leaf's doing!
Hm, it seems that he's on
some different mission.
At a time like this?!
Rin, once again...
Let's create a world
where you can exist again.
I'm glad my
teacher was a Hokage.
It made it easy to give
up on becoming Hokage!
He defeated the Anbu Black
Ops assigned to Lord Third,
got past a highest-level
classified barrier and knew
The Nine Tails' Seal would
weaken during childbirth.
Are you Madara Uchiha?
No, that would be impossible.
He is dead, after all.
In the end, it
doesn't matter who you are.
But why attack
the Hidden Leaf?
What would you
like to hear?
I could say I did it on a
whim, or that I planned it,
or that it's for war...
Or that it's for peace.
If only I had realized that
man was Obito, I may have
been able to stop him!
And then, I might have
been able to prevent
Kushina's death.
I might not have
had to make Naruto
into Nine Tails' Jinchuriki.
If only I had
noticed that he was Obito!
Perhaps the shinobi
world wouldn't have
ended up like this either!
You were my teacher,
and yet you didn't
realize it was me.
That's just who you
are, fundamentally.
How pathetic!
You died a hero Hokage, but
now, exposed as a disgrace
in front of your son.
That's right.
A Hokage is a pitiable
existence compared
to what I am now.
Apparently, the kid's
not a total goofball.
He's caught on!
You have no right to make
fun of the Hokage when you
couldn't even become one!
Naruto, what are-?!
Especially not my dad,
who actually was Hokage.
How dare you
put him down!
That worked?!
I don't get it?
It's effective!
So it is just as I thought!
Ninjutsu may not work, but
it seems Sage Jutsu does!
The toad from Mount Myoboku
used Sage Jutsu, and his
attack wasn't
nullified or erased.
You bastard!
Amazing, Naruto!
What's going on?!
His Sage Jutsu is working!
He's even mastered
the same Sage Jutsu
as Jiraiya Sensei.
Seems he's grown into
quite a son, eh, Minato?
It's no wonder that he
managed to sweet
talk my other half.
Dad, I don't know if
this will work or not,
but I've got an idea.
Naruto!
Face it, Minato's useless.
He wasn't even able to
protect your mother.
Nor his subordinates.
You know what
tomorrow is, don't you?
It's the anniversary
of their deaths...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Day
Naruto Was Born."
The day both
your parents died.