[Growling]
[Roaring]
[Screams]
Hmph!
[Growls]
[Screaming]
You sure you should be
spending your time on me?
Because it seems like you've
got bigger trouble on your
hands...
Don't underestimate
us.
[Chuckles]
Are you going to do
something about that , too?
[Naruto Struggling]
Hmph!
[Coughs]
Naruto!
Is this the end?
Are you going to
die here...?
Boring good for
nothing...
[Sinister Chuckle]
I'll lend you power!
Power?
[Roaring]
Control...
...your power.
Control...my power?
Naruto!
Hmph!
I can't...let it
end here.
I'm certain that you'll
be able to find the answer,
Naruto.
I believe in you...
Completely.
[Screaming]
[Gasp]
[Screams]
[Roaring]
[Growling]
[Painful Howl]
[Screams]
[Roaring]
Amazing.
But..that...
isn't the Nine
Tails...
It's a different
transformation.
Naruto...
Kabuto escaped...
Naruto!
[Gasp]
Dokku!
It's too dangerous here!
You have to get away!
Yes...But we have to
stop that .
I...
We're aware. Just
leave this to us.
It's true that I was fired, but
I used to be a village guard.
Protecting this place...
The "Hole."
This is my duty now.
[Gasps]
I understand.
Huh?
You can't do it
alone.
No! Forget it!
It's dangerous!
You think you can get there
by yourself? In your current
condition?
Let's go. Please.
Ehh.
Sensei...
Huh?
Please don't go!
Yeah, stay!
Sensei!
Kids, I...
[Sigh]
[Whimpering]
Now, Faz...don't be such
a picky eater.
Eat even if it doesn't taste
good. You need to become strong.
To look after the
others.
[Whimpering]
Lando, as the oldest,
you're in charge.
If anyone's in trouble,
you help them.
Do your best.
[Whimpering]
And Sora, make sure
you take care of everyone.
[Whimpering]
Especially Mina...
Watch over her.
[Whimpering]
Now Leo. There may be some tough
times ahead, and some sad times
too, I'm sorry to say...
...but, but do your best.
Okay?
[Whimpering]
Mina...
Please, Mina!
I'm sorry I hurt you
that day.
Only you were able to
sense that Naruto wasn't
himself.
I didn't see it.
I'm sorry!
Things may be difficult
for a while, but...
Hang in there. Do your best.
You and the others must be
strong.
You have to live...
[Crying]
[All Crying]
We weren't together for
long, but we had a lot of fun.
We sure did. They were
such happy times.
Thank you,
so much.
Yes thank you.
I love you all.
I love you too.
[Whimpering]
You three! Keep them
safe. I beg you.
We will.
You can count
on us.
Mhmm.
Shiseru!
[Chuckle]
[Gasps]
Get em' Sensei!
Shiseru!
[Roaring]
[Hissing]
[Growls]
[Heavy Breathing]
Brother!
[Grunting]
If...
If we actually make it
out of here alive...
What?
I said...if
we survive...
Let's get married!
[Gasps]
[Heavy Breathing]
You finally said it.
Then...we'll just have
to make it. No matter what.
[Grunting]
[Hissing]
Hmph!
[Screaming]
Look! There it is!
The "Saezuri!"
If we could get this thing
to work somehow...huh!
It's the book that Chief
used to carry around!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Gasps]
[Roaring]
[Howl]
Ahh!
[Chuckles]
[Laughing]
Disonasu said you use a
combination of sounds...
Like what?
I have no idea.
[Three Notes Hummed]
Wait...!
[Mina Humming Notes]
Huh?
That's it!
Mina's melody!
Yes! The one that she's
always humming to herself!
Now...
[Sinister Laughter]
[Roaring]
Kill! Destroy! The
entire world!
[Xylophone Music]
[Humming to the tune]
I think this'll work!
[Grunts]
Naruto!
[Growling]
Huh?
[Roaring]
[Gasps]
Naruto!
Not good!
He's lost all control of
himself!
What?!
[Roaring]
[Painful Roar]
Hmph!
[Gasp]
Shiseru!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Gasps]
Shiseru...!
Quick climb up!
[Grunting]
I can't! It's dislocated!
It's what?
Sakura! Quick you have
to heal me!
Hurry!
[Roaring]
[Screams]
Naruto.
[Roaring]
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
The Nine Tails is too strong! I
don't know how long I can keep
restraining him!
[Gasp]
He's just hurting...
Mina!
What are they...
Huh?
[Heavy Breathing]
[Roaring]
[Grunting]
I can't!
We have to try
something else!
[Roaring]
Hmph!
[Screams]
[Gasp]
Roaring]
[Roaring]
Don't give up.
[Whimpering]
Brother, you can stop.
I've made my
peace with this.
No! I won't let
you go!
You must! Go! There's no time!
You have to stop the "Amo no
Hoko!"
No! Like hell I will! I'm not
going to watch the person I love
fall! Not again!
No! Never again!
I've loved you! For as
long as I can remember!
It's why I held on so tightly
back then! But...I'm so sorry!
That's why I will never
let go of you again.
And if I do...then...we'll
fall together!
I've been in love with you
too! All these years!
You have...?!
Yes, always! Even as I grew
tall, and you grew fat and bald.
Even as you became more
indecisive and afraid, and kept
turning away from me!
All that time, I
still loved you!
You did?
[Whimpering]
But Dokku...
Who's going to protect
the children? You're the only
one now!
You're the only one who can
save them! And save their future
too!
But...but..I...
Naruto...
Please save them...
To protect...my friends...all
those dear to me.
I want...to save
my friends!
My mama...
And Papa...
I believe...
I believe in you...
In the good in you, and
in your power. In you!
Naruto please!
Oh, please!
Save them both!
Because they're our...
[All]
Cause those two are
our mom and dad!
[Whimpering]
Please, go save the world.
And, protect the children.
I love you.
So much, my beloved.
Huh?
[Gasps]
[Whimpering]
Naruto...?
Dokku! Hurry up
and stop that thing!
Huh!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Hissing]
[Grunts]
Don't get in his way!
You hear me?!
Huh!
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
[Humming]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunting]
Hey! Don't just
stand there!
Help me!
I have nothing left
to learn from you now.
What are you talking about! The
Reanimation Jutsu's still
incomplete!
I was able to gather more
than enough data from this
recent battle.
Oh, and, I'm going to take the
strong one's you collected with
me.
You bastard!
[Grunts]
Go ahead, get your
revenge.
Why?
I've no use for him.
And I never liked
him anyway.
[Grunts]
Wait! It was him! He attacked
your village! He was controlling
the Shinobi! No! No!
Stop! Stop!
[Sword Noise]
[Grunting]
[Whimpering]
[Laughing]
Huh?
Big brother Naruto!
[Sigh]
[Laughing]
Man you guys are heavy!
Thank you for saving
my life, Naruto.
Yes thank you.
So much.
Thank you.
Sure!
Dear Naruto, it's been quite a
while. I hope that this letter
finds you well.
As you may already know, the
Saezuri, which controlled the
Ama no Hoko in the Hole...
...was given to the land of fire
for safe keeping, taken to a
secret location, and sealed
away.
The townspeople found out about
the tragedy that took place in
the village...
...and many people have come
here to pay their respects.
It fills my heart with
gratitude, and peace.
Also, and sometimes I still
can't believe it, Shiseru and
I have gotten married!
We've officially adopted the
children, and we've all moved in
together.
As you know they're a pretty
lively bunch! They're quite the
handful, but with them around...
...every day is filled with joy.
Mina just had a birthday. She's
five now!
All that red hair of hers has
turned completely black, and
so have her eyes.
We're not sure, but we think it
might be the result of the
decreased power and influence of
the Hole.
Once again, I have to thank you
for everything that you did for
us.
The only reason that I'm able to
spend my days in happiness with
Shiseru and the children, is
because of your power.
I hope from the bottom of my
heart that you will continue to
use that power for good and
the benefit of others.
And that if your friends ever
find themselves in a time of
need, your power will be able to
save them.
In closing, I offer my sincerest
hopes that your happiness will
only continue to grow.
Thank you again.
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Hissing]
I think it's time,
that I go see him.
Madra! I'll never forgive you
for bringing back the Jinchuriki
with the Reanimation Jutsu!
I'm stopping this war!
Naruto can sense encroaching
danger. He'll have no choice but
to join the battle. It's all
according to plan!
Today, the Senju's Will of Fire
shall be extinguished!
Next Time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Naruto Enters the Battle."
It's time to make my appearance!