♪
[crickets chirping]
I'll soon reach the limit of the
Chidori's destructive power.
I need to make it evolve
further... But how?
Father...
What's the use if I can't even
ask him for advice?
I've made up my mind.
I'll surpass him...
Father, do you have a moment?
(Fugaku)
I'm busy now.
Come back later.
Big Brother...
Join us, Sasuke.
This is important.
I see... And have you made up
your mind about this?
Yes, Father. I decided after
working closely with Lord
Fourth.
He seems to be serious
about changing the treatment
of the Uchiha Clan.
I believe that he's trustworthy.
[low groan]
However... That means that
we must change as well.
We have put far too much
distance between us and
everyone else.
It's become an obstacle to
reaching an agreement.
Well, then? What are your
thoughts about all this?
We must demonstrate to them
that we have no ill will.
As a clan that's part of this
village... we must pledge
loyalty to Lord Fourth...
...and do our very
best to cooperate--
So you're telling us they'll
only accept our conditions if
we show them obedience,?!
No, that isn't the case.
This is just my
personal observation.
But that's just too convenient-
(Fugaku)
Be quiet, Sasuke.
This is Itachi that's talking to
us... I'm sure that he's thought
things through.
(Sasuke)
But...
Besides, we have long hoped to
find a way to participate within
the government.
At first, our ancestors chose to
live here after fighting in wars
that sought blood for blood.
We must strive to find
common ground.
I thank you.
(Sasuke Thinking)
You always do this, father...
I realize this may be sudden,
but I've been given a request
from the Hokage.
Hm. You are quite
the cunning one.
First, you make sure that
I'm in an agreeable mood...
Guarding a VIP from the
Feudal Lord's office...
It's a direct request
from the Feudal Lord.
The Leaf will dispatch
an escort unit.
It's a long-term mission.
(Fugaku)
If we accept this mission,
failure's not an option...
Let's go through
selections right away.
[angry grunt]
It's always like this.  Father
only cares about Big Brother.
No matter how hard I try...
Why did I think that you
would be like Itachi?
Your older brother would've
handled all this far better
than you have.
This is Itachi that's talking to
us... I'm sure that he's thought
things through.
Every single time! He
never acknowledges me!
See?  Didn't I
tell you, Naruto?
Sasuke has managed to
completely master Chidori!
Yeah, you're right!
I told him I'd learn my jutsu
first, but he's surpassed me!
Sasuke! I brought some snacks.
Wanna share them?
[grunt]
You're annoying.
Huh?
[gasp]
(Sakura)
Sasuke...
Hey, what do you think
you're doing, Sasuke?!
Apologize to Sakura!
Don't you order me around.
A loser has no right to talk...
I'm not ordering you around! And
I'm not a loser, you know!
I caught up to you, didn't I?!
You just can't accept that
that's the truth!
Why, you...!
Oh yeah, know it all?
You really think that you're
equal to me?  That's impossible!
All right, do you wanna put that
to the test right now?
Fine by me.
Both of you, stop.
[attack yell]
Naruto!
Sasuke!
Stop it!
Huh? Dad? What...?
I'm sorry... but fights are
forbidden inside the village.
Tsk...
[gasp]
(Sakura)
Lord Fourth...
Thank goodness
you're here.
I'm sorry, Sakura-
[grunt]
Where is he!?
[groan]
[gasp]
Uh... Sasuke!
What was that power?!
How did he..!?
[panting breaths]
I will never acknowledge you.
I promise you... I
will take you down!
You know, when I developed the
Rasengan, it wasn't so that I
could hurt my friends.
So, why did you so that?
I was frustrated.
[gasp]
I've been trying so hard
to catch up to him forever.
But he just... he refuses
to acknowledge me.
[sigh] You know, Naruto,
people's feelings can be
complicated.
But,,,
But I...
I'm never gonna give up!
It may be impossible now, but
I'll become stronger...
And I'm gonna get him to
acknowledge me someday!
I'd thought that you were
listening when we had our
conversation the other day.
So you're criticizing me again
without hearing the facts?
What are your intentions?
Nothing at all.
I'm just not going to expect
anything from you anymore.
I choose to follow my own
path from here on out.
What?  "Your own path?"
Yeah, that's right.  And I want
that path to lead to power.
But before that, I
have one request.
All right!  I'm gonna train
super hard again today!
What is all of this racket this
early in the morning?!
[big yawn]
Okay! Here I go...
(Sakura)
Naruto...!
Sakura?
What is it?
What's the matter?
It's awful.  Sasuke's---!
Huh?
Is it really true, Dad?
Is Sasuke seriously gonna
leave our team?!
Yes, it's true.
His father came
by earlier to inform me.
Starting today, Sasuke is going
to become a new member of the
Leaf Police Force.
Why'd he do that all
of a sudden?!
And what's going to happen
to us? I mean, what'll
happen to Team 7 now?
Well...
I'll go ask him myself!
(Jiraiya)
Hold it... Just hold on there!
What's the big idea, huh?
(Minato)
[clears throat]
Sasuke has already left for
the Feudal Lord's office.
The Uchiha have agreed to take
on a long-term mission escorting
a VIP who's from that office.
What!?
They'll be using the
Uchiha's Elite Unit.
Sasuke wants to shadow and
learn from the more
experienced shinobi.
He made a strong
appeal to join them.
Sasuke did that?
But it's... This is
all way too sudden!
We weren't even able to patch
things up between us yet.
[groan] Come on, Naruto, do you
have to be a complete idiot?!
I mean, you should be a little
happy for him, at least!
Yeah? And why
should I be, huh?
Because he volunteered for this
mission in order to hone his
skills.
I'm guessing that he probably
made up his mind to do so right
after getting into that fight
with you, 'cause it made
him realize something.
Huh!? You
mean, he also--?
Yeah, that's right.  Just like
you, he "doesn't want to lose."
At the very least it means he's
aware of you and your skills.
Oh, I see.  [giggle
(Jiraiya)
But it's not the time to relax!
Sasuke will become
ridiculously strong...
...and then when he comes
back, he'll be able to
crush you and defeat you.
No!  Not good!
I have to train, too!  I have to
start right now!  Hurry!
All right, that's the spirit!
And don't worry! I'll be sure
to root for you from distant
skies.
[happy laugh]
Hey, wait, just hold on a
second, here, y'know!
What was that distant skies
thing that you just said?!
I mean, aren't you gonna stick
around a while and help me
train, Pervy Sage?!
What can I tell ya? My
wounds are fully healed.
So I have to set out in search
of Orochimaru before too long.
No way!
[hearty laugh]
Hey, now, don't get so
depressed, Naruto.
I'll watch over your training
when I have a chance to.
Come on! You're always so
busy! Never mind, Dad!
[embarrassed chuckle]
Hey, I have an idea! Why
don't you take me with you?
Uh, what!?
You want to go on the
journey along with him?
Yeah!  It's the perfect idea!
I'll be able to get lots of
training done out there
while we're on the road!
Uh, well, I... Um,
Jiraiya Sensei?
Well, I wouldn't mind it.
But I wonder what Kushina would
have to say about this.
She's really strict when it
comes to The Three Prohibitions
of the Shinobi...
All right then, we're just gonna
have to convince her, won't we!
C'mon! Let's go!
(Jiraiya)
Damn it, you're so
self-centered!
Um, uh, so then I guess Naruto
is leaving the team, too?
I'm so sorry.
I'll start looking into where
you can transfer right away...
No...
For now, I actually wouldn't
mind being kept on standby.
Oh, but...
So later, when Naruto returns,
we'll have our old team back
together.
And maybe there's... even a
chance that Sasuke could
have a change of heart!
Of course.
Besides... while the two of them
are away, there's something that
I want to do, as well.
I think that it'll be
a good opportunity.
Lady Tsunade, Please... I'd like
to learn that jutsu that you
mentioned before.
I can't be the only one on the
team who's lagging behind.
I like that look on your face.
Fine. But I'm warning you,
I won't go easy on you.
(Sakura)
Of course!
Are you sure about this?
I brought you onboard because
Captain Fugaku asked me to.
But everyone else in the unit is
ranked way above you.
The days at the Feudal Lord's
office will likely be long and
hard.
I'm looking forward to it.
Setting aside my father and
brother, you're the most
skilled among the Uchiha.
While my brother's on the
Hokage's detail...
...I'd always assumed that you
would become the next captain.
And that's why you
volunteered for this?
I have a goal that I'm
determined to reach.
And to achieve it...
All right... It's
fine by me.
Go!
Hey, I've been thinking about
what you said before...
It's just that, Orochimaru
is a bad guy, right?
So why do you go out of your way
to try to find him, then?
Despite what he's now become,
he was once my friend.
But one day, he went
off the path. I should have set
him right back on it then.
But... I couldn't
stop him.
Oh I see.
And I can't help but think that
if only I hadn't let him go then
He could still be here in
the village right now.
And frankly, I don't want you to
have the same kind of regrets.
Huh...
At the same time, I
haven't given up yet!
I know that I'll bring
him back one day!
Heh! Alright!
You really didn't have to come
down here to see me off...
That just wouldn't do, y'know!
Listen! You gotta observe the
Three Shinobi Prohibitions!
Jiraiya Sensei is way too lax
about them, so don't you dare
imitate his bad habits, got it?!
I'm sorry... She insisted on
seeing you two off and-
That goes without saying,
y'know!
What if Naruto picks up bad
habits while he's out with
Sensei gathering intel and he
turns into a total
degenerate?!What then, huh!?
I already worry enough about his
antics and recklessness as it
is, you know!
Look, don't worry!
If he gets in my way, I'll just
transport him away to Mount
Myoboku or someplace.
What?  Mount Myoboku?
[gag]
Whatever food they serve
you, just hang in there.
Huh? Oh.
(Shikamaru)
Hey!
Be careful on your
journey, okay?
Hey guys.
And don't go overboard
with your training!
If you try too hard, you're
gonna make all of us back here
look like we're slacking off.
What're you talking
about?! We're gonna
be working hard, too!
There is just no way that I'm
gonna be a genin forever!
I'll have you know, that I'm on
track to go straight to the top.
I even have a place
to train already.
Huh?! When did that happen?!
Well, I'm not going
to lose to Naruto!
Heh. I get it!
(Jiraiya)
Hey... Let's go, already!
All right! I'm
totally ready now!
Okay, goodbye!
I'm off, y'know!
(Danzo)
I can't believe that a shinobi
of your caliber failed...
If that plan had just succeeded,
we could've been rid of the
jonin who support the Fourth
Hokage in one swoop!
And increased our
political influence.
Oh. You can't blame
it all on me.
The plan failed because
of the shinobi that
Hizashi had assembled.
Since you installed Hizashi to
head up the plan... some of the
blame lies with you.
Hm...
I did what I was supposed to do.
I expect the contract
to be honored.
I understand.
So what are your wishes
for the next vessel?
Well, let's see... Itachi would
have been an ideal choice,
actually.
But it was too late this time...
The next time around, he'll
be past his prime.
All right, I see...
Then I'll have to choose
another suitable candidate...
...one who possesses even
stronger qualities than Itachi
and will reach his physical
peak in three years.
Yes. I'm counting on you.
Someone young, beautiful,
and strong.
An ideal body...
[attack cry]
[attack yell]
Not yet! Wait!
[grunt]
Chidori Stream!
[panting breaths]
All right. Good!
[happy sigh]
You're going back to the Leaf
Village as soon as your
replacement arrives, huh?
(Sasuke)
Yeah.
I've learned
everything
I can here.
Besides, I still have that
goal that I need to fulfill.
I realize that it's none
of my business, but...
Sometimes it's good to
have a goal to focus on.
And yet at the same time,
getting too attached to a goal
can lead someone off the correct
path.
I hope you'll try
to remember that.
I don't need you to
get involved in this.
Thanks for the
last three years.
I want to make sure with my own
eyes.  But I guess I can't since
I'm stuck here.
You're back. I read
through the report.
Only the elite were
sent on that mission...
But you've developed into a
shinobi second only to Shisui.
It's not a big deal.
Very soon now I'm going
to surpass Itachi!
Hmf. Listen to you,
such confidence...
This is...
(Fugaku)
A lieutenant's armband for
the Leaf Police Force.
It's very easy to
just run your mouth.
But now here's your chance to
demonstrate your skills in a
real mission.
I look forward to it!
I've returned to dispel the
humiliation of that day.
And this time... I'll take you
down and prove to you who's
stronger!
(Third Hokage)
The recent activities of the
Leaf Police Force are
indefensible!
(Minato)
I believe that this is
a form of protest.
(Minato)
They're annoyed because their
situation hasn't changed.
(Minato)
They're losing patience.
Especially the younger
generation.
(Minato)
And the one at the center
of all this...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Difference in Power."
(Minato)
...is the clan's most gifted
member... Sasuke...