(sigh)
It sure has been
lonely around here.
Since the Fourth Great
Ninja War began.
Sis! Sis! Check that
one out! Boy, that
thing's really trucking
along, isn't it?
Whoa...
You ants sure
work hard!
Your children must be
waiting for you with
hungry bellies. Hang
in there, guys!
(horrified scream)
Taku, no! What
are you doing?!
Sorry, I couldn't
hold it any longer!
(relieved sigh)
The elite ninja of
the Hidden Leaf have
formed an alliance
that's unprecedented
in the history of the
Five Great Nations to
fight this Fourth
Great Ninja War.
The question before
us now, as we worry
about the well-being
of our families in
these turbulent times,
is how we'll protect
the village while
those ninja are away.
But remember, we are
warriors, too!
In the past, each
time there's been
a Great Ninja War,
our village has
found itself
shorthanded.
And as a result, rogue
bands have come after
our valuables like
hungry vultures!
Like those poor ants!
So all of us who
remain here must
stand united as
one!
What're you babbling
about? Sure, we've
had incidents like that
before, but every time
we've just beaten
the stuffing out of
our attackers!
No, what I mean-
Isn't that Big Brother
Shikamaru's mom?
Boy, she's
really intense!
Yeah, I'll say!
You got that right!
The Leaf Mom's
Association has been
around for decades!
Don't underestimate
the mom's of the
Village!
And Big Sister
Sakura's mother
seems pretty
fired up, too.
Everyone's afraid of
us! No one's going to
come here and attack
us! Don't you think
so Mrs. Yamanaka?
That's right.
Well, yes, that has
been the case in the
past, it's true, but
I think we should
consider every
possibility right
now, just to be
on the safe side.
I mean, there's no
telling what a band
of rogues like the
Akatsuki might form
again and make a
move on the Hidden
Leaf Village!
And I just thought
that working together
would be a good way
to raise our morale
in this difficult
time. But never mind
now...
Stop mumbling! We'll
be fine! We'll do
things like we
always have!
That's right! We
can't afford to let
fear change the way
we lead our lives.
We're all just going
to keep laughing,
crying, getting angry,
and laughing again!
And when our husbands
return, we'll welcome
them back with smiles
and open arms. If we do
that, then all our
lives will simply
go back to normal!
Yeah! Good for
you! You tell
them girl!
Mind your own
business, four-
eyes!
What?! How dare you!
Huh?
Uh... Is it okay
to leave things
like this?
What if Ebisu Sensei
is right? What if
rogues actually do
attack the village?
Yeah, right. Come on!
What we should really
be worried about is
that we're so young
they wouldn't let us
go to the battlefield!
If only... I were
just a little bit
older!
Watase! You're
so cool!
(annoyed grunt)
You know, protecting
the village is also an
important responsibility!
Hnh! Give me a break!
Ninja only earn their
reputations through
what they do on the
battlefield!
Protecting the
Village won't win
us any honor!
(frustrated grunt)
Grandpa, I wonder what
you would've done if
you were in a situation
like this.
Well, I guess that
since you were Hokage,
you'd be out fighting
on the battlefield.
Konohamaru, I've
been meaning to
ask you. So, tell
me...
...Do you have
the Will of Fire?
The Will of Fire?
Yes, it's a strong
will to protect the
village, no matter
what it takes.
To protect the
village...
Konohamaru!
Huh?!
Trouble! Big
Trouble!
What's going on?!
Just a little while ago,
my mom asked me to get
her some medicinal
herbs, so I headed to
the mountain on the
east side of the
village, and that's
when it happened!
What?! Seriously?!
Suspicious ninja
in the forest?!
Yeah, I saw a
ton of 'em,
Konohamaru.
Huh?
I couldn't believe
how many! Maybe
a hundred!
You saw a
hundred ninja?!
Hey! Konohamaru!
We're in seriously
big trouble, here!
What? What happened,
Udon?! And what's the
deal with your hair?!
You gotta hear this,
Konohamaru! I was
in the forest to the
east, foraging for
some matsutakes, and
that's when I saw it.
When everybody finally
comes back from the war,
I'm going to give all of
them a whole bunch of
these delicious
matsutakes to eat!
I'm gonna roast all
of them up! It'll be
awesome! I can almost
smell them right now!
Hold on...
Ahhhh! Hot! Hot!
Before I knew it, it
was a raging inferno!
Ahhhhh!
Good, huh? I can't
wait! I'm going to
eat them all up
right now!
The way that these
were roasted...
I wonder...
Like a fire-style
ninja, or one who's
skilled with-
Ahhhhhh!
What's wrong?
The western side
of the village!
What?
On the west
side, too?!
There were a whole
bunch of these
humungous giants!
A giant ninja?
What's a giant
ninja?
A ninja that's a
giant! What do
you think, Moegi?!
That's not an
explanation!
Man, what's going
on here?
Guys!
Listen to this!
To the east of
the village...
Now we're back to
the east side?!
I saw a ninja
that was using
the Rasengan!
Did Big Brother
Naruto come back
home?!
No, it wasn't him.
What?! No, that
can't be! The only
ones who are able
to use the Rasengan
were the late Fourth
Hokage and Old Man
Jiraiya.
And among the living,
only Big Brother Naruto
and I can use it!
That's not all!
This guy created
the Rasengan with
his feet!
What?! His feet?
Yeah, and once he
did, he kicked it.
I can throw the Rasengan
with my hands, but just
barely, and to do it with
your feet... I don't get
how that's even
possible!
We're all cursed!
Now what's going on?!
A Tailed Beast
curses this
village!
Did she say
Tailed Beast?!
It's happening again!
A Tailed Beast is
attacking the village!
We're cursed, I tell you!
Granny! Where did
you see it?!
In the forest
to the east!
And you're sure
that is what a
Tailed Beast?
Of course! And this
time, it had taken
the form of a bear!
It's a curse!
We're all cursed!
A bear?!
Wait a minute. Let's
just take a moment to
sort through all this
information.
Something's in the
forest to the east. And
something's in the west,
too. That means, in other
words, they're
surrounding us!
(shocked gasp)
We're in big
trouble here!
Sorry, Konohamaru. I
have trouble believing
that's possible. If
anything were foolish
enough to come here,
those mothers would
just chase the enemy
away.
Hmph! I said what I
said in hopes of
strengthening our
sense of unity.
But now it seems to me
that maybe I should've
just avoided getting
involved entirely.
Konohamaru, no more
procrastination! You
have to stay focused!
You should be
training!
So, go on!
Listen! They're
coming! The enemy!
Giant ninja are coming
to attack our village
while it's vulnerable!
What?!
They can breathe fire!
Oh, my!
And they can use
the Rasengan!
Oh, dear!
Frightening!
And they also have
a giant bear with
them, too!
(chuckling)
We can't rely on the
adults to handle this
any longer!
So we, the young
generation, are gonna
have to protect the
village ourselves!
Yeah!
Enough, Konohamaru!
Stop pretending that
you're the Hokage
around here!
I don't care if
you are the Third
Hokage's grandson!
What's that?!
Listen to me! From
now on, real skills are
what count. That's how
it was for Naruto, too.
The loser of the
Academy has now
become the hero of
the village. It's
also rumored that
he's the closest to
being selected as
Hokage after the
next one. Don't you
get it? These days
connections like
what family you're
from don't matter.
All that counts is what
you've accomplished out
on the battlefield.
Nobody cares about
looking after the
village!
Really?! Just how
selfish are you?!
Let's fight!
Yeah! Let's go!
(attacking grunts)
(crowd cheering)
Do you have it
in you, Watase?!
The Will of Fire?
What does that mean?!
Go on, get him,
Konohamaru!
You can take
this guy!
It's the will to protect
this village no matter
what it takes!
If someone doesn't
possess the Will of
Fire, then they could
never become Hokage!
Hah! Yeah, right.
And you think you
have it, huh?!
(painful grunt)
(shocked gasps)
No way...
We're both on the
same side. I don't
want to hurt you!
You idiot! I'm the
one who's hurting you!
If I fell to your
kunai, you'd be the
one hurt! You'd have
to the bear that burden!
And that's why I'm
trying so desperately
not to lose now!
Konohamaru!
(annoyed grunt)
No matter what it
takes, I will protect
the village!
Even for just
one person!
Konohamaru, where
are you going?!
Uh, hold up,
Konohamaru!
Moegi, is this where
you saw all those
ninja earlier?
Yeah, I'm sure.
This is where I
was, too. When I
saw all that fire.
Right. Wait! Did
you guys hear that?!
Hey, what's
the matter?
Ninja jumping from
branch to branch...
Ninja breathing
fire...
Ninja who use Rasengan
with their feet...
A Tailed Beast
in bear form...
The hostilities forced
us to flee from the Land
of Frost and come here to
the safety of the Hidden
Leaf Village. All the
performers you see here
make up the Illusion
Circus. I hope that
you'll remember
to come see us!
(stunned gasp)
The only ghost was
the one in our
imagination.
It's just like that
old saying goes...
What do you mean
our imagination?!
How could you two
ever mistake a
circus troupe for
enemy ninja?! Aw,
what a mess!
And I made such a
big deal out of this!
This is just so
not cool!
What's that?
Big trouble!
Come on! Quick!
They're on the way
toward the Village!
Like you said!
No...
Actually...
They came from
the west! Without
warning!
The west?!
Anyway, Watase told
me to get you! So
so come on, let's go!
Take me there!
(frightened screams)
We are the Sumo Wrestlers!
We'll take on both ninja
and samurai! And win!
This whole village
now belongs to me,
Yokozuna!
What's a Sumo
Wrestler?
Dunno. I've never
heard of them before!
A group of giants
in the forest to
the west...
The western side
of the village!
There were a whole
bunch of these
humongous giants!
I get it! That piece
of intel was the only
one that was real!
(painful grunt)
(painful grunts)
Bring it on, kid!
(painful grunt)
Watase!
Hang on!
I'm coming!
Oh, no you don't!
Hey! Wait a
minute!
Get out of the way!
All of your husbands
aren't around because
they are away at war,
aren't they?
And while they're gone,
we're going to take
everything valuable that
you have in this village!
There are still idiots
like you around, huh?
What a joke! It makes
no difference whatsoever
whether our husbands
are here away!
The Mom's Association
will protect this
village with our Will
of Fire!
The Will of Fire!
What a load of hogwash!
All right, boys, let's
go teach these women
a little lesson.
(attack yell)
Attack with
everything
we've got!
(hitting grunt)
Protect the
children!
(attacking grunts)
They're incredible!
To those who possess
the Will of Fire...
Everyone in the whole
village is considered
to be a true family
member.
The desire to
protect one's
family...
...is universally
understood, and it
builds very strong
and deep bonds
between each and
every person in
the entire village.
As long as everyone
in the Hidden Leaf
embraces the Will of
Fire, the village can
weather any challenge,
no matter what it may
face.
Grandpa, so this is
the true meaning...
...of the Will
of Fire.
Ahh! No! Retreat!
We give up!
No escape!
Wait! Konohamaru!
(frightened screams)
Out of the way!
Move it! Now!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(charging growl)
Here, take this!
Rasengan!
(painful screams)
Wow, Konohamaru,
I've really gotta
hand it to you.
All right! I'll
carry on the
Will of Fire!
Huh?
(everyone cheering)
Come on! Lift him
up! Let's celebrate!
Oh, no! You
don't have to!
Up you go!
Ahh!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Well, it's almost
dinner time!
With both Ino and
my husband gone,
I guess it's
leftovers again!
It's too much trouble
to cook just for my
husband, who's lying
around the house like
a slug. What do you
say we all have
potluck?
Yeah, that's a great
idea. I'll just bring
over our leftovers
from lunch!
Sounds good!
You're our leader,
Konohamaru! I mean
Big Brother Naruto's
got nothing on you!
(giggling laughter)
You know, I sure
could get used
to this!
(giggling)
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Bro, hold up!
Naruto's gotta
get through!
If you continue to
insist on going,
Naruto, I will
kill you!
I can vouch for
him, that I
guarantee!
Why are you
defending this
boy, Bee?
We're bumping fists!
Can't you read what's
in my soul, brother?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Secret
Origin of the Ultimate
Tag Team!"
Because you're
very special
to me.