I had nothing at all.
It's still not enough yet!
This still... isn't...
who I am!
And that is why I've
kept on adding to myself.
So what I want right now
is not your lecture,
but instead your
abilities and intel.
Not only are you a Leaf
Shinobi, you're of the
famed Uchiha bloodline.
You possess Sharingan that
have awakened the Mangekyo.
You also bore many secrets
and stopped a war...
And you had many jutsu
and a lot of power.
Itachi, you possessed
many things that
made you who you are.
There is no finer foil to my
Reanimation Jutsu than you.
And my pawns are
part of my power.
You exaggerate...
The reality is, I failed.
[harrumphing chuckle]
No... earlier.
Even though I may have
mocked the Uchiha name in
front of you, I have
to admit that I'm
actually still quite
envious of it.
The Uchiha name merely
indicates a bloodline and
clan membership.
It's meaningless for
you to claim it.
From the very beginning,
I was nobody...
I had nothing.
I bet he's from that city...
Where that recent
battle was just fought.
Where are your parents?
Don't worry. Just relax. I
can help. I'm able to do a
little Medical Ninjutsu.
Wait, how about...
Kabuto, as in helmet?
So simple.
That was fast.
It's just what
he's wearing!
It's best not to overthink
things sometimes.
Until I was given a name and
a place to call home....
You think that claiming
a name is meaningless?
It's not.
It does hold
meaning for me!
Are you sure it would
be bad to kill him?
As it is, we're stuck
playing catch-up!
I already told you no! He
controls the battlefield
right now. Be patient.
Is the Izanami
still not ready?!
He's about to attack!
Don't worry, Sasuke. I'm on
it. It's just going to take
a little more time.
Lord Orochimaru said
this to me once.
Sakon! Demon Twin Jutsu!
Jirobo! Earth Style:
Terra Shield!
If you want to know who and
what you are, all you need
to do is gather
every last thing
and piece of information
that exists in this world!
Kidomaru! Spiral Web!
These threads can't
be cut with a blade!
Amaterasu!
Kimimaro!
Macabre Bone Pulse!
Bracken Dance!
He's laid down
the spider silk
all the way
to the back.
I'll get the back,
Brother. Take the front!
Can you still
use the Susano'o?
Yes.
Inferno Style!
Flame Control!
They ran to the back, huh?
Too bad it's no use!
Tayuya! Demon Flute:
Chains of Fantasia!
Are you okay, Sasuke!
Genjutsu, huh?
Even your precious
Susano'o can't block
out sound, can it?
I knew it...
Now that I've immobilized
you, all that's left is...
To absorb you using
Lord Orochimaru!
[gasp]
Well, Sasuke? How about it?
Do you remember this?
You recognize this
current form of mine?
That's--
Thanks to you,. I was
finally able to take Lord
Orochimaru into
my own body...
After you had
killed him!
That's right!
I've achieved it at last!
This is my true form!
Remember, I said that all
the laws and principles of
Nature, which
Lord Orochimaru
researched and compiled for
so long, are now stored and
being used inside of me.
The only thing that
was missing...
...was Lord
Orochimaru himself!
But now, as you
see, I possess
him inside of me, too!
I really can't thank
you enough, Sasuke!
Kabuto... You are
not Orochimaru.
It's fine to imitate
someone you respect...
But don't remake yourself
into him to that extent.
You do realize a majority
of people start out by
mimicking another person
they admire, don't you?
Just like the way
Sasuke emulated you.
[gulp]
Wow, Itachi! You nailed
every target, even the one
in the blind spot
behind the rock!
All right, now
it's my turn!
No, Sasuke. It's
time to go.
[grunt]
What happened to the new
shuriken jutsu you promised
to teach me, huh?
It'll have to
wait 'til later...
I have an important
mission in the morning.
And I need to
prepare for it.
You're such a
big fat liar.
Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
Hmph!
Okay, just watch this!
Hm?
Hey, be careful!
[screaming]
Keep excelling like
this and you'll be
just like your
brother in no time.
Father... I wanted you to say...
"that's my boy"... to me...
Such behavior is just a
process to help one mature!
Don't use it as a cloak to
deceive yourself, like
you've done!
If you've attached your
self-value to something
external to you...
Even something admirable
and praiseworthy.
Then you gain nothing.
I'll say this
one last time.
Don't mislead yourself with
lies. Those who cannot
acknowledge themselves
will invariably fail.
Fail?!
The way I am now?
How could I fail?!
Sasuke... Look
into my eyes!
[gasp] That's
right! Of course!
Genjutsu! Sharingan!
Tsukuyomi!
I shall now engage the
Izanami. Which means that
you have already failed.
Is it over?
You, a genius that always
had everything, would never
understand at all...
The only thing I want is to
be who and what I am!
I won't let anyone
interfere!
Sas... uke...
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
Water Style:
Giant Vortex Jutsu
[groaning]
[gasp]
You're just repeating
the same old moves.
Makes it easier
for me to counter.
I already told you, with
this body I have the power
to recover from any wound
you try to inflict, so
attacking me is
pointless.
Since I shut off my vision,
genjutsu won't work on me.
You two have no
chance of winning.
Your fate is already
entirely in my hands.
All thanks to the Uchiha's
other Forbidden Jutsu.
That is...
Well, then...
Shall we put that boast of
yours to the test, Itachi?
The Izanami!
Sasuke... do not
leave my side.
This feels like déjà vu.
But you bore me...
So let's put an end to
this fight, already.
Your fate may be in
my hands now...
But only you can truly
decide how that fate
shapes your destiny.
Remember all that
I've told you.
You have to think hard.
Sorry, but I have
absolutely no idea
what you're
talking about.
Anyway, that's enough of
your word games.
I will have everything
that I want!
I'm the strongest of all!
That is a simple fact!
He who forgives himself and
acknowledges his true self...
[growl roar]
Is the most
powerful of all!
Losers like you...
...should be quiet!
This is...
What's going on?
What is he doing?
How?! My horn had
already been cut off!
How? I cut off my sight...
I should be invulnerable
to genjutsu.
But this is clearly...
[screaming]
What did you do to me?!
I have you in
my Visual Jutsu.
Huh?
Impossible!
It's the Izanami!
How?
Well, it doesn't
matter anyway.
Because no one
can stop me now!
I am all-powerful!
As I told you... I hold your
fate in my hands right now!
Itachi Uchiha!
If this is a genjutsu...
Release!
Huh?
[growling]
Just stay calm... This is an
Uchiha Genjutsu. And since
Itachi cast it, it won't
be easy to release.
But there are many ways
to undo a genjutsu!
It's useless.
Remember all that
I've told you.
Of course! I'll just copy
the same trick that you
two used before!
Tayuya!
Demon Flute:
Chains of Fantasia!
This will switch Itachi's
control over this
genjutsu to Tayuya.
Ahh-ahh...
[scream]
Then I'll do this!
Sage Art! Inorganic
Animation!
There, this whole area
is under my control!
Better retreat for now...
[confident chuckle]
Damn it!
Don't mess with me!
He cannot escape this loop.
He'll remain stuck
inside this samsara.
So this is the other Uchiha
Forbidden Jutsu, the
companion to Izanagi.
A jutsu that decides fate...
This is the Izanami.
So Kabuto's trapped inside
the loop that you created?
No, the Izanami is a jutsu
meant for stopping the
Izanagi. There's an
escape route that's
built into the loop.
What does that mean?
What I am about to tell you
is the story of the Uchiha's
Izanagi and how the
Izanami came to be.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Izanagi and Izanami."
The Uchiha Clan's history of
conflict. I understand.