Lost Bonds
Are you tellin' me that
all the things we did
together in Squad Seven,
mean absolutely
nothing to you now!?
No.
Not meaningless.
One thing was worthwhile;
our friendship.
We became best friends.
We're best friends?!
Why're we fighting?!
I just told you.
Because we're friends,
there's more meaning
in destroying you.
[gasp]
[panting]
You finally awake?
A dream.
Where am I?
You lost consciousness.
You really had us all worried.
Kakashi Sensei
and Sai?
I see.
Why?
Why'd it turn out like this?
Hey, Naruto.
You should rest a
little longer.
Come on now.
Sasuke... you're...
Hey, did you know that
everyone in the Uchiha
clan was killed?
Hmm?
Yeah, I heard my
father talking about
it a while ago.
Sasuke's the only
one who survived.
[Naruto]
I was actually kinda
glad back then,
[Naruto]
'Cause I wasn't the only
one who was alone anymore.
But Sasuke was so good
at everything he did.
Well done, Sasuke.
excellent example!
- Yeah! Way to go!
- You're so cool!
- Wow!
Hah! Stuck-up
and a show-off!
I could do that, too,
if I wanted to, you know!
He was so different than me.
Go!
Nnng!
That's why I picked
him to be my rival.
Because I wanted to
be just like him.
Even though we were
both on Squad 7,
Sasuke was always a
step ahead of me.
The reason I trained so hard
was because I wanted to catch
up to him, even just a little.
Heh.
"Am I at my strongest?"
I just want the answer to that.
I can only find out
by fighting the
strongest, the best.
And the best of the
best are all here.
Naruto.
You're one of the ones
I want to fight.
Huh?
That made me happy.
It was the first time Sasuke
acknowledged me as an equal.
A'right, why don't you
introduce yourselves.
One at a time.
[Naruto]
But he...
My name's Sasuke Uchiha.
And I hate a lot of things.
I don't really like anything.
What I have is not a
dream, because I will
make it a reality.
I'm going to restore my clan,
and destroy a certain someone.
[Itachi]
It's been a long time.
Sasuke.
Itachi.
It's you.
Sasuke!
Itachi.
You die!
This is who he was
talkin' about.
The one he
wanted to kill.
It's like you said, brother.
I've fostered my hatred
for you all this time.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose.
To kill you!
It ends here!
Sasuke. You decided to
live only for revenge.
[Sai]
It's true that I was given
a classified mission to
find and eliminate Sasuke.
[Sai]
But I'm through
following orders.
[Sai]
From now on, I
think for myself.
And Naruto, you can
help me remember.
Bring back those old feelings.
I don't know much
about you, Sasuke,
but Naruto and Sakura,
are willing to risk
everything, all for you.
They don't want to lose
their connection with you.
They would give anything
to protect those bonds!
I might not
understand it clearly.
But you, Sasuke.
You must understand it!
[Sasuke]
You're right.
I did understand.
That's why I severed them!
You see, I have a
different bond now.
Between my older
brother and me.
It's the bond of hatred.
What about the bond,
between Sasuke and me?
Let's just do this.
But first wear your headband.
I'll wait for you.
I don't need that thing.
Just do it! Now!
There's no point!
'Cause you won't be
able to make a scratch
on my forehead!
So what?!
You know puttin' your headband
on says we're fighting on
equal terms as Shinobi!
[Sasuke]
There you go acting all
high and mighty again!
You don't honestly believe
we're equals, do you?!
Heck yeah I do!
All this time, I've never
once thought that I was
inferior to you in any way!
You're an embarrassment!
Next to me, you're
embarrassed about
how weak you are!
Isn't that right?!
Narutoooo!!
Sasukeeee!!
Please, stop this...
Blast!
STOP IT!!!!
Stop! NOO!!
Too late!
Can't stop!
Whoaa!
[Kimimaro]
Lord Orochimaru has
already acquired the
Immortality Jutsu.
He's immortal, but that
doesn't mean his body can
maintain itself forever.
Before his flesh decays,
a strong, new body must
be made into a vessel for
his soul.
You mean,
He'll use Sasuke's body!?
That's right. He will.
No way! I can't let you!
[Naruto]
When Sasuke turned his back on
the village, I really believed
I could bring him back. But...
Just snap out of it
already, will ya?!
What the heck do
you know about it?
It's not like you
ever had a family
in the first place.
You were on your own right
from the beginning!!
You don't know
anything ABOUT it!
I'm suffering 'cause
I HAVE those ties.
How on earth could you
possibly understand what it
feels like to lose all that?!
[Naruto]
In the end, I guess I didn't
really understand Sasuke at all.
I only thought that I knew him.
Why, Naruto?
Why would you go
so far for me?
It's the first time,
That I've ever had
a bond like this.
That's why I'll
do anything I can,
to stop you.
I'll admit it.
You're definitely strong.
It's because,
You know the pain of solitude,
In just the same way that I do.
And...
It's that pain that
makes us stronger.
Which means if I can
just break that bond,
I'll be able to achieve
even greater strength!
[Sasuke]
Ya know where we are?
It's called the
FINAL VALLEY.
The perfect setting
for this fight!
Right, Naruto?
Grr!
I guess that we're at the end of
this fight. And all our fights!
How are you feeling?
I had them make some
rice porridge for you.
Eat. It'll help you get
your strength back.
I was... I was
dreaming about Sasuke.
You're going to come back to
the village with me, Naruto.
That's a direct
order from Kakashi.
(cm mild determined reax as
stands)
Mmm?
I'm sorry, Naruto.
Let Kakashi handle Sasuke.
Got it?
Fine. Let me rest some more.
Then we can head
back to the Village.
You really should eat
something, you know.
You need to keep up
your strength.
No, thanks.
I'm not hungry.
Sasuke said he was going
to sever his bond with
me and become stronger.
And that I could never
understand his feelings.
Hey, you were friends
with Orochimaru way back,
right Pervy Sage?
Why did he desert the
village and decide to
destroy the Hidden Leaf?
Orochimaru went through a
profound change After both
his parents were killed.
And that's when he became
obsessed with Forbidden Jutsu.
I don't know if he was trying
to resurrect his parents,
or to wreak vengeance
on the village that
he held responsible
for their deaths.
My parents weren't killed, so,
Like you, I was accused
of not being able to
understand anything about
him or his feelings.
Perhaps he was right,
And I didn't understand a
thing about him after all.
However,
Even I'm able to see that
there's entirely too much hate
in this Shinobi World of ours.
There's too much hate?
[sigh] I've always
wanted to do
something about all
of this hatred.
I'm just not quite
sure how to go about
it as of yet.
But I truly believe,
that eventually the day
will come when all people
will understand one another
and live in harmony.
To me, Pervy Sage was
irreplaceable.
He was like... family.
That's why...
I'm afraid Jiraiya-boy
has died in battle.
Huh...?!
When I heard that
Pervy Sage had died,
For the very first time,
I really understood what
Sasuke was talking about.
The pain of losing a bond.
[snoring]
Huh?
Naruto, C'mon, let's go.
You ready?
I really don't feel like
going outside right now.
Give me a little longer,
would you?
Good. He still hasn't caught
on that I'm just a Shadow Clone.
So do you finally
comprehend pain now?
Unless you come to know the
exact same pain you can't truly
comprehend someone else.
And even if you
comprehend them,
you may not truly
understand them.
That's the truth, Naruto.
That is why it's useless for
you to chase after Sasuke.
People change.
Sasuke is no longer the boy
that you knew long ago.
Sasuke chose this
path all on his own.
And the first thing is for
you to give up on Sasuke.
[Jiraya]
To be a shinobi, you need more
than strength and jutsu.
You must become smarter.
The longer that you're a fool,
The harder it'll be for you to
live in this shinobi world.
If being smarter means what
you say it does, I'll remain
a fool my entire life.
Well, Pervy Sage,
I guess I'm a big
fool after all.
Ah!
Kakashi Sensei's chakra.
This way!
Sakura, don't do
anything reckless.
I'm not sure.
This is just
conjecture,
But I think Sakura,
She's planning to
kill Sasuke herself.
Sasuke has shouldered
the entire burden of
the Uchiha's hatred,
and intends to strike
deep into the world
with that curse.
[Madara]
That hate is his most
powerful weapon, his friend,
and the source of his power.
That is Sasuke's Ninja Way!
You know what they say, Naruto?
When two shinobi are powerful
enough, they are able to read
each other's thoughts simply
by an exchange of fists,
without ever uttering
a single word.
You've always been
naïve, Naruto.
Tell me, do you
know my thoughts?
What's on my mind?
Sasuke. Now I really understand
how you feel, what it's like to
have a close bond ripped away.
You just said you
consider Sasuke to be
like a brother to you.
What if Sasuke were to attack
the Hidden Leaf Village?
What would you do then?
Why would..? No, there's just
no way that Sasuke would ever
do something like that!
Sasuke is still a blank
canvas. He can easily
be dyed into any color.
If he resists,
would you be able
to stop him?
Or even kill him if need be?
[gasp]
Could you weigh Sasuke
against the Hidden Leaf
on a set of scales?
I would defend the Village!
And I'd find a way to stop
Sasuke without killing him!
You're such a child.
All your tales are
nothing but mere fantasies.
Shinobi must be capable of
making very harsh decisions.
We'll brand the Akatsuki
as wanted criminals.
Once we do, not only I,
but the whole world
will hunt Sasuke down.
You bow your head for a
criminal and beg mercy to
keep your comrade safe.
In the shinobi world,
that is not friendship!
And If you've
truly resolved to
become a Kage,
Then you're going to have
to so what needs to be
done as Sasuke's friend.
I don't even know what the right
thing to do is anymore. But...
You Hidden Leaf brat!
Think more deeply on what
it is you ought to do.
The shinobi world is not so
indulgent as to suffer fools.
I consider you a friend.
In the past, friend
was just a word to me.
Nothing more, nothing less.
But after meeting you,
I realized something.
What's important is the
meaning of that word.
What does it mean to you?
You must decide for yourself
what you can do for Sasuke.
Think hard on that.
Sasuke.
If I see you,
If we meet, I think
I'll know the answer.
[Kakashi]
Sakura, there's no need for
you to bear such a heavy burden.
After all, it was my cowardice
that drove you all apart.
Perhaps I was trying to
convince myself that once
again it could be like it was,
back in the old days.
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
The Burden.
I'm sorry I was such
a careless teacher.