{happy running breaths)
Elder Sister Hinata!
I've been waiting for
you! Now come on! Let's
go play ninja!
(small gasp)
I'm sorry, Hanabi.
I can't right now.
Aww! Pretty please!
Just for a little bit?
(Natsu)
That will not do,
Lady Hanabi.
But I'll play
with you!
Please be on your way.
Okay. See you later,
Hanabi!
No! No don't go!
Elder Sister!
This is boring.
Well, I'm sorry, but
it can't be helped. Lady
Hinata is the successor
of the main family.
Yeah, but...
she could play
a little...
The Hyuga's a distinguished
clan. Within the Leaf, we're
the only ones who possess the
Byakugan, the most touted
of the Kekkai Genkai. As the
future leader of the clan, Lady
Hinata has a veritable mountain
of knowledge that she must learn
Now... here you go.
Ahhhh....
Lady Hanabi?
Lady Hanabi!
Oh dear. Where in the
world could she have
run off to?
Ha! I found Elder Sister!
[groan] I didn't get
to play with Elder
Sister at all today.
Hm?
Elder Sister Hinata!
I'm sorry that
I'm late.
Nuh-uh! Not
at all!
[fighting jabs]
Hiyah!
Huh? Oh...
[quiet snoring]
[marketplace chatter]
You know what?
Elder Sister came
to visit me yesterday!
With her training, she
must be tired! I hope
you thanked her properly.
I couldn't!
She fell asleep!
(giggle) Okay. But
thank her next time.
(Naruto)
Hey! What's the big
idea, buddy!?
I don't want you here!
You're nothing but a pest!
But I wasn't even
doing anything!
I mean, I was just
looking at the
masks you have...
Why you pathetic
little loser!
Here, is this
what you want!?
(Naruto)
[grunt]
Then just take it
and get lost!
And don't come back!
Natsu, who's
that boy?
Oh. Well... It's
like the shopkeeper
said...
Just stop, all right!?
Just stop looking
at me like that...
Listen closely. You
must never go
near that boy, okay?
Mhm.
Oh, is it
study time?
Uh huh!
I can write my whole
name now! I even know
some kanji!
Look! Lots, actually.
Really!
Lady Hinata, don't
keep Lord Haishi
waiting.
Right. See you
later, Hanabi!
Okay!
She's training, huh?
Focus, please.
You can't go out
to play until you've
finished your work.
[groan]
Done! Here!
Oh, that girl...!
Hiya!
Whoa...
(Thinking)
So strong, yet
so kind...
... I want to be
just like her.
Hiya! Hiya!
(Thinking)
I want to be more like
Elder Sister, even if it's
just a little bit!
[groan]
Elder Brother Neji?
Why do I have to be
her sparring partner?
Please just let me
train on my own.
No. Not yet.
Continue.
Let's keep going.
Please, Neji.
Tsk. Very well then.
Hiyaaaaa!
[gasp]
(Thinking)
He's acting
different today...
What's wrong, Lady
Hinata? This isn't
child's play now.
[gasp]
[determined grunt]
Hang in there,
Elder Sister!
[grunt]
[gasp]
That was nothing!
And you expect to
fulfill your destiny...
...as leader of the Hyuga!?
[grunt]
[screaming]
[gasp]
What is...
My head...!
[groaning]
[screaming]
The brazen fool...
(Thinking)
What... is
going on?
What was that...?
Were you peeking
into the training
hall?
Mhm.
I see.
That man... one second
he was fine, and the
next he was in pain...
And that pattern on
his forehead...?
It's the Curse Mark:
Caged Bird, that's
passed down within
the Hyuga.
It's called the Curse
Mark: Caged Bird?
That's right. It
reacts to the main
family's hidden seal.
If it's used on you, it
can easily destroy all
of your cranial nerves.
You mean... that
before when...
Yes, when Neji threatened
to do harm to Hinata, Hiashi
used the power of the hidden
seal to stop him.
But why would
he do that?!
Hmm.
The main family of the
Hyuga Clan carries the
solemn duty of protecting
the Byakugan.
There are times when we must
rule over the side branch
families using absolute fear,
the fear of death.
Absolute fear...
of death.
And naturally, there are some
in the side branch families
who oppose this...
...those who harbor
resentment towards
the main family.
Even if we 're hated, it's
all for the sake of the
Hyuga Clan that we
possess this skill.
So you mean, that
all of us...
Listen well, Hanabi...
All of us are born into
this world bearing our
own destiny, carrying it
inside of us.
In our lifetime, that
destiny never changes.
Well, that's unusual!
You aren't in a rush
today!
No, not...
today...
[Thinking]
I wonder if that man
is actually stronger
than Elder Sister...
[fighting slaps]
Awful! Why did
you hesitate? Hit
with all your might.
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much.
Do you really think that
Hinata's up to this?
[sigh]... Because
of her nature, Hinata
isn't very good at
confrontation.
Perhaps she is
simply too kind.
In that case, she
can't protect the
Hyuga.
[sigh]
Huh?
(Thinking)
What is she doing
out here...
Hm.
Okay! Clone Jutsu!
[weary sigh]
Clone Jutsu!
(Thinking)
Wasn't he
the one...?
Why is Elder Sister
here with him?!
Elder Sister...?
[fighting grunts]
(Elder)
I'm coming in.
Hiya!
Aaaahh!
But those two are
five years apart
in age!
Lady Hanabi's amazing!
How did your training
go today, Lady Hanabi?
It was the same
as usual...
You seem really sad.
But you've had so much
fun with it before
today...
Yeah...
After observing for a while,
I believe it will be hard to
let Hinata take over as head
of the main family.
A decision will
have to be made
soon.
[sigh] I understand.
However, I'd like
to make a request.
You two will participate
in a mock battle today.
[gasp]
(Haiashi)
I want to see all the skill and
power you've gained so far.
Do not go easy on each other.
Fight with the
intent to kill.
(Hyuga Man)
Fight to kill?! He doesn't want
them to hold back at all!? What
is Lord Hiashi thinking?
Hinata... You're the
successor of the Hyuga
Clan...
This is your chance to
show me you're worthy
of that.
Yes, sir...
(Thinking)
But... I'm supposed
to fight...
(Hiashi)
Begin!
(Thinking)
Elder Sister Hinata...
Both of them
are amazing!
(Thinking)
There's no end
to this!
(Thinking)
There!
[gasp]
[sigh]
Father, I--
Falling to Hanabi,
who's five years
younger...!
[gasp]...
[sob]
(Elder)
Hinata will probably
just serve the village
as a Genin.
Oh, I see.
It seems sad, but we
cannot allow a failure
like that to become
out successor...
...this is her
destiny...
That you were born possessing
strength surpassing that of
your elder sister is also
destiny...
Hanabi, you must hone
your skills to the
utmost for the sake
of the Hyuga.
Yes...
[Loud clanging]
[panting]
Stand up, Hanabi.
I will take Hinata under
my wing. But are you...
sure that's what you want?
She is your first
born and heir to
your household.
The life of a Genin
can be dangerous and
brief.
Do whatever
you will.
[gasp]
(Hiashi)
She's of less worth
than her sister five
years her junior...
...the Hyuga Clan has
no use for such an heir.
[gasp]
If you have
nothing more to say,
leave us now. We
have work to do.
All right.
(Hiashi)
Continue, Hanabi!
Yes.
(Thinking)
If elder Sister can't do it, I
have no choice but to do it.
I will protect the Hyuga.
This... is my destiny!