[theme music]
‐Hrrh, haah!
‐Ungh!
‐Haah!
Yaah!
‐Weaklings have no
place in this fight.
All right, now I'm
ready for you, Kakashi!
[footsteps]
[squawks]
TOBI: If you're going
to cover yourself,
don't forget your butt.
Huh?
[grunts]
Look at me, I'm
like a schoolgirl
in love with her professor.
Wha‐‐ Deidara, look at me.
You're not still angry?
Hey, let's be friends and hunt
for the Three‐Tails together.
‐Go away!
‐[gasps]
Aw, come on.
If we don't get to
work, the others
are going to chew us out.
Cut me some slack, will you?
Hey, I know, I'll let you
take a peek under my mask.
‐I said get lost!
‐Deidara!
You keep acting so mean,
and I might leave for real.
[groans]
Guess I have no choice.
I'll just go search
all by my lonesome.
‐[grunts]
‐Heyaah!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): So this
is the power she kept hidden.
‐Heyahh!
Rrarh!
You seem so persistent.
And yet when your ink
drawing doesn't quite work,
you head for the hills.
Isn't that how your
ninja arts work?
‐You should know that
my ink has other uses.
‐Huh?
Aargh!
[hissing]
[grunts]
‐Ninja Art, Ink Flush.
‐Aw, what's wrong?
Why can't you attack?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
I don't get it.
Why didn't she release all this
power the last time we fought?
‐Rrrh!
Playtime's over!
Crystal Style, Burst
Crystal Falling Dragon!
‐What?
‐This is it!
[growls]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
She can turn
anything she touches
into crystal.
So water, earth, and wood
styles have no effect.
However, this will!
Did that do it?
‐How naive.
‐[groans]
Aah!
‐A valiant effort, Kakashi.
‐Huh, those three
dragons were just
a diversion to keep me here.
‐For all the big talk I've heard
about your mighty Sharingan,
it really wasn't much.
Oh, well, let's end this.
‐[grunts]
‐Don't bother.
‐Where is it?
Where is it?
Actually, where the heck am I?
Huh?
Oh, I've happened upon an
awfully suspicious lake.
Hm?
What in the world
are they doing?
They're from the Leaf Village.
‐Uh!
‐Hold it, Ino.
Focus your chakra
on the barrier.
‐Eh, right.
‐Barrier?
No way.
That's impossible.
Hm?
What's this?
There's another one.
That's a new face.
‐Those Leaf ninja must be
looking for the Three‐Tails.
‐Huh!
Oh, well, guess I'll just
kick back and watch the show.
‐Time's ticking.
What do you say we finish this?
‐[grunts]
Uh!
Kakashi Sensei!
‐Uhh.
‐Prepare to die!
What?
Agh!
[buzzing]
‐Huh!
Shino!
‐Just in the nick of time.
So they're ready?
‐If they weren't I
wouldn't be here.
‐Well, well.
Now, look who's here‐‐
the insect user.
I hope you know that your
jutsu won't work against me.
Big waste of time!
[crackling]
What did I tell you?
Very useless.
‐I don't know about that.
‐What the‐‐ uh!
[crackling]
[shattering glass]
GUREN: It can't be.
‐Now, your jutsu
won't work against me.
You see, these insects
can evolve instantly.
And they built up a
resistance to your jutsu.
‐You did it, Shino?
No way!
‐Impossible.
My Crystal Style has
never been defeated.
‐Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
There's no way you're
getting past me now, lady!
‐Uhh.
KAKASHI: You're cornered.
‐Huh!
‐Now, tell us where Yukimaru is!
‐Why do you care?
Uh, oh, I get it.
You want that boy's
power as well.
‐No way!
It's not like that!
‐I wonder.
Ugh!
Huh!
‐Now, her Crystal
Style has been sealed.
‐You better start talking!
Where is Yukimaru?
‐Ugh!
You little punk!
[grunts]
‐Is that‐‐
‐There's Guren.
Hm.
‐Uh!
Ugh!
What is this stuff?
Mud?
Ugh!
‐It seems that crystal can
mend itself instantaneously.
‐Damn it!
How are we going
to stop this lady?
‐Focus your bug
attack on one spot.
‐Uhh.
Is that you, Guren?
‐[grunts]
I won't make it.
‐Lightning Blade!
A mud wall?
‐Gozu?
‐[grunts]
‐Gozu, why?
Ugh, what are you doing?
Argh!
Let go off me!
Let me finish the fight.
Gozu?
Ugh, ugh!
‐Uh?
‐I won't let you get to her.
Aargh!
‐Aargh!
‐[gasping]
‐Kakashi Sensei,
are you all right?
‐Yeah, but Guren got away.
‐Agh!
She was the key to
finally finding Yukimaru!
‐It's a shame because my
insects performed flawlessly.
But she escaped anyway.
‐OK, we'll split up and search.
Naruto, go with Shino.
Sai, with me.
‐You told me that the
enemy was formidable
and was burning with
a passion to fight!
‐What's the deal?
They were kind of lame.
‐Well, yeah.
It's like he was a
totally different person.
‐I bet the others aren't going
to be much of a challenge
either.
‐Humph.
‐Don't let your guard down.
‐Uh, yes.
‐Remember, even Kakashi had
his hands full with her.
The crystal user is no joke.
‐I cannot wait to face
her in battle and test out
my taijutsu!
‐We'll split into two groups.
Lee and Tenten, guard the
Sealing Team by the lake.
We'll join up with the others
fighting the Crystal Style
user.
Got it?
‐Got it.
[dog barks]
‐What?
I will not be fighting
the Crystal Style user?
‐You can never be‐‐
‐Aargh!
‐‐‐sure where the
enemy may appear.
I said don't let
your guard down.
LEE: Yee‐‐
LEE AND TENTEN: Yes!
‐Huh?
See that?
‐Yes, I know.
It's closer.
‐It's directly below us.
‐I sense it.
‐We're moving past the search
mode of the Four‐Corner Sealing
Barrier.
Keep your breathing steady.
Here we go!
ALL: Four‐Corner
Sealing Barrier.
Bind!
‐We'll lower the net into
the water very quietly.
We can't let the
Three‐Tails detect us.
‐See, it is the
Three‐Tails, Deidara.
Wait, he's not here, is he?
Huh?
Does he intend to stop them?
‐Huh?
Enemy!
‐Uh!
‐Keep concentrating.
HINATA: But‐‐
‐Leaf Hurricane!
‐What the‐‐
HINATA: Lee!
Tenten!
‐We took care of the
enemy on the other side,
so we hurried here.
I am glad we did.
And now, that I am
here, I will not
allow you to lay a
finger on these four!
‐The others should have
stopped you in your tracks.
‐You mean, your friends?
They were no match for us!
RINJI (VOICEOVER): Damn!
Kigiri and the others.
‐I am your opponent now.
‐Tch.
‐What?
He's running away?
TOBI: Oh, this is bad!
At this rate, the Three‐Tails
is going to get sealed.
But if I go out there,
I'll be outnumbered.
Right, Deidara?
Oh, yeah, he's not here!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Completely useless, all of them.
That Leaf ritual will
seal the Three‐Tails.
They would rather no one gets
the power of the Tailed Beast‐‐
unless I stop them.
Yukimaru.
‐Guren.
Please, the white camellia
can't become a red one.
Come back.
Promise me you will.
‐Go‐‐ Gozu, why did you‐‐ oh.
Hm.
Yukimaru?
[gasps]
‐Aah!
[grass‐whistle music]
‐[gasps]
No, that grass‐whistle.
Uh, ha‐ah, uh, no.
That's‐‐ that's impossible.
Huh.
[sobs]
[screams]
[grass‐whistle music]
GUREN (VOICEOVER): Was I
responsible for that boy's
mother?
Did I do it?
No!
MAN: Guren?
‐[gasps]
‐Ready to go?
‐You're here.
But I thought you returned
to Lord Orochimaru's hideout?
‐Something more
pressing came up.
Those Leaf ninja have started
to seal the Three‐Tails.
‐Huh?
‐We'll use Yukimaru to
control the Three‐Tails,
then obliterate their
pesky little barrier.
‐Uh, huh, Kabuto,
we need to talk.
‐This isn't really the
time for a chat, Guren.
‐But I must know.
If we force Yukimaru to unleash
his hidden powers, please,
you must tell me
what will happen.
‐I see.
Is that all you're
worried about?
‐I have a right to know.
Tell me!
‐Why are you so upset?
Live or die, Yukimaru's fate
has nothing to do with you.
‐No, Kabuto.
It does.
‐Aw, so even the devil
sheds a tear now and then.
You've murdered countless
people over the years.
To think, you actually have
a soft spot for Yukimaru.
That's a shocker.
‐This one is special.
‐Why?
Because you murdered
the boy's mother?
‐How did you know?
‐Hah, that's nothing.
It's just as Lord
Orochimaru predicted.
He knew that you would develop
feelings for the child.
Why do you think he
chose you for this?
If you prefer, I can
inform Yukimaru for you.
That the kind and
gentle Guren, whom
he believes is the one
he can come home to,
is actually the evil villain
that killed his mother.
‐Stop it!
‐Fine, as long as you carry out
my orders without hesitation.
‐Tenten, stay alert.
We do not know when the enemy
will be appearing again.
‐You made him feel close to you.
‐[laughs]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Lord
Orochimaru, I hate to admit it,
but you were absolutely
right to select that woman.
‐Guren will grow
to love Yukimaru?
Is that even possible?
‐Hm.
Kabuto, you have much
to learn about people.
The more time you spend
with another person,
the stronger your bond becomes.
This is simply human nature.
‐Really, my lord?
‐And with those two‐‐ well,
their ties run quite deep,
it's likely that Guren
will disobey my command
and betray me.
And when she does‐‐
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): I suppose
that moment has arrived,
Lord Orochimaru.
[music playing]
‐Sai, how is it?
‐I'm not picking anything up
from the Crystal Style user.
‐She used up considerable
chakra during that last battle.
Now is the time to strike.
I don't want to let her recover.
SAI: Agreed.
I'll widen the
scope of my search.
‐Come on!
Where did she run off to?
‐Naruto, patience is the key.
‐Yeah, I know.
But that kid, I just
got to find him.
Next time, "The Battle
Over the Barrier."