As I explained to you on
the way here, the mission
that our team has just
completed was to obtain
a Hidden Jutsu from
the Cedar Village.
Stealing Hidden Jutsu.
Up to your old tricks,
huh?
Well, go on.
Sorry, but after getting
the Hidden Jutsu. I left
to go and tend to another
matter.
I'll take over, I
was there, after all.
Lord Raikage...
Hm?
Leave it...
What?! A  smokescreen?
Do they think we're
a bunch of fools?!
Leave it...
Who are you? Are
you from the Cedar
Village?
(sinister laughing)
No, we are not shinobi
of the Cedar Village.
We have no homeland,
nor a master other
than ourselves.
People seek us out,
and we fulfill their
wishes.
The Cedar Village came
to us and their wish
is...
Death to those who
stole the Hidden Jutsu
of the Cedar Village!
They're mercenary
shinobi, huh?
Lightning Attack!
(painful grunt)
(sinister laughing)
What's wrong, Karai?!
Karai, are you okay?!
(angry growl)
How dare you!
(evil laughter)
We are the wandering
phantoms of the forest!
Nokizaru!
Nokizaru?! No way!
Nokizaru Troops, huh?
Shinobi who hunt other
shinobi...
Lord Raikage!
Huh?
Karai, he's in
no condition to-
Stop it! I'm
fine! Let's go!
(laughter)
That's all it takes
to get them to run?
What cowards!
(angry growl)
Lord Raikage! Please,
sir, do not let the
enemy provoke you!
There should be a
town ahead where we
can lose 'em.
That's the Raikage of
the Cloud?! Hmph! What
a disappointment!
(taunting laughter)
Do not underestimate us!
Lightning Rat Tremor!
(painful grunt)
No! Nigai!
Ahhh!
Just get away!
Please, listen!
Don't come any
closer!
Nigai!
You bastards!
I won't let you
get away with this!
(powerful grunts)
No, Lord Raikage!
Don't do it! Nigai
and I both used jutsu,
and it caused something
strange to happen inside
our bodies! If you use
one, too-
Step back, Karai!
Ahhhh!
Perhaps they realized
I meant business that
time and were scared
off. But whatever their
reasons for leaving
were, they did not
appear again.
Strange, I wonder why
they backed off. They
were the ones who
instigated the fight.
Also, Nigai used his
jutsu, and it caused
him to explode. Karai
used a jutsu as well
but apparently noticed
the change in his body
and quickly suppressed
his jutsu to prevent an
explosion. The bomb-like
chakra mass on his chest
is still absorbing his
jutsu's chakra and
causing him pain.
And Lord Raikage
manipulated his
chakra to create the
most power of all
and yet he remains
safe and sound!
You sure about that?
What?!
You can't tell by
looking at him, but I
sense that the same
type of chakra in that
lump is also inside
the Raikage.
What are you talking
about? I mean, I feel
perfectly fine!
(surprised gasp)
Yes, for now...
I'm pretty sure this
lump is an Exploding
Bug. Something only the
Nokizaru Troops have
been successful
in creating.
You've seen what it
does. Once it finds a
host, it keeps absorbing
chakra and growing until
it inevitably explodes.
And the size of this
larva merits grave
concern.
Huh?
Huh? Did you feel
something? The larvae
start out invisible
to the naked eye, as
tiny as the cells
in your body.
You mean?
Yes... You fell into
the enemy's trap from
the moment that you first
made contact with them.
Larvae scattered into
the atmosphere with
that explosion of light.
You breathed them in,
completely unaware.
(gasp)
So then why does the
Raikage seem okay?
Yeah!
Why don't I have one of
those chakra lumps like
Karai and Nigai?
I was in the exact
same situation as
them!
And also, I cannot deny
that I've been manipulating
chakra quite a bit.
Especially earlier when
we were arm-wrestling, I
used a good amount of
my chakra.
(chuckle)
So the unruly brat of
the Cloud grew bigger
but didn't grow up, huh?
How dare you say that!
Oh, relax!
At least just hear me
out before you start
yelling at me again.
(calming sigh)
First of all, we shinobi
activate our jutsu by
manipulating chakra.
The amount of chakra
that we need for any
given jutsu...
Well, this is just a
generalization, but
it's largely dependent on
the level of that jutsu.
We adjust the amount
for each jutsu we use.
The stronger the jutsu,
the more chakra we need.
So we store up chakra
inside of our bodies
so that we can use it
at another time.
Hold on...You mentioned
that earlier, you and the
Raikage were arm-wrestling.
Don't you also use up
chakra when you use your
physical strength?
Yes. However, in that
case, the Raikage didn't
use his chakra for strength.
Instead, to counter my
physical power, he used
speed to push me back.
Naturally, one uses
chakra to create
speed, too.
However, converting chakra
into speed consumes that
chakra instantly.
So there's not enough
time for the Exploding
Bug to absorb it.
I get it, but does that
mean I'm going to end up
like Karai or doesn't it?
Yes, exactly.
We all use a little
chakra even for normal,
everyday activities.
Until the Bug's removed,
you must remain inactive.
But you're saying that
it's possible to get
rid of it?
Of course! A simple
surgery should be
able to remove it.
Shizune, get
ready to operate.
Got it.
And...
Please wait! I'd
like to assist
if I could!
Thank you.
What is it?
Oh...Um...We'll have
to operate on your
subordinate first. He's
facing a greater risk
since the Bug in him
is closer to detonation.
Hm. That's fine by
me. I want you to
save Karai first.
No! Please, wait! You
have to let Lord Raikage
go before me!
Impossible!
The surgery itself is
simple, but if the
Exploding Bug has
wormed its way too
far into the Chakra
Network...
...it'll take considerable
skill and experience to
remove it! And don't forget,
that thing could explode
at any moment now!
That means the surgeon
is going to be taking
a risk of dying as well!
So I won't listen to
anymore of your nonsense!
All right, Tsunade,
enough. I'm fine with
this choice. Please just
tend to Karai first.
Hmmh, I'm sorry. I
got worked up. But
there's still another
reason why we can't
do your surgery yet.
The Exploding Bug that's
infiltrated your system is
too small for the human
eye to see.
Until it grows larger,
there's nothing we can do.
And yet at the same
time, we can't have
you just wait.
We don't know how much
chakra it takes for the
Exploding Bug to grow to
maturity and detonate.
It could take very
little for all we know.
You must promise me,
Raikage! You'll let us
handle this surgery as
we see fit.
Also, that you won't
exert yourself at all.
All right, Tsunade.
I give you my word.
(attack yell)
(shocked gasp)
Huh! Well, it looks like
you'll be able to keep
that promise!
What is it?
Just a bug.
(shocked gasp)
What's the matter?
It's nothing to
worry about.
In any case, our target
is definitely inside that
abandoned building over
there.
Sounds good. And what's
the status on the Raikage?
No change.
Are you sure he actually
inhaled the Exploding Bug?
Yeah, no doubt about it.
Both the timing and the
distance were completely
spot on.
Then why?
Why isn't the Exploding
Bug inside him maturing?
Well, if I knew that,
then none of us would
have to be out here
spying on them, would we?
Enough of this, I
say we just attack
them.
Waiting around like
this is more boring
than I can stand!
Don't be stupid. One
of those guys in there
could explode at any
moment now!
So if we all just go
rushing in there, then
we could end up being
killed as well!
Don't lose sight of what
our goal is. We were
hired to get that scroll
back, but it must be
returned undamaged.
Alright, I think it's
easiest to negotiate
a trade. The scroll in
return for removing
the Exploding Bug.
And if the enemy dies,
that doesn't matter, as
long as we retrieve the
scroll intact.
Because it means
that we'll all get
paid in full.
Now listen, it seems
that some newcomers are
here to help the enemy.
As a safeguard, we'll
plant Exploding Bugs, once
all of our enemies have
gathered in one location.
I've brought the
antiseptic wash.
Yes, thank you.
Can I help with the
surgery? I'd like to
learn for future
reference.
Sure, I'd
appreciate that.
Are you able to perform
hemostatic jutsu?
Yes. You can
count on me.
Good, that'll be
very helpful.
Please, go around to
his other side. You
can assist from there.
This will save a lot of
time over controlling
the bleeding and doing
the extraction myself.
I owe you, Amai.
Thank you.
You bet. Don't worry,
these guys are the best.
Lady Tsunade will get every
trace of that Bug out.
All right, now, We're
going to start the
anesthesia, so please
just relax.
Are you finally ready
to begin the surgery?
We are. We've just given
him the anesthetic. It
should begin to take full
effect in just a
minute or two.
All right, Tsunade
Karai's in your
hands now.
Shizune, take
care of it.
What was that?! You
won't be wielding the
scalpel?! But I thought
you would be the one-
Silence, Raikage!
Shizune will be
doing this!
Don't you tell me to
shut up! I recognize
that you're the best
Medical Ninja around,
and that's why I
came to you!
Look, don't worry.
She's a highly skilled
Medical Ninja! And
besides, you gave me
your word, remember?
That you'd let us do
this as we see fit.
You're right, I did.
But you'll be sorry
if anything happens
to Karai!
Don't worry, I'll
step in if I have to.
Listen, why don't you
go downstairs and take
a nap while you're
waiting?
How's it coming,
Shizune.
Good. We're
ready anytime.
Alright, begin.
Very well, then. We'll
start the procedure to
open the chest cavity and
remove the Exploding Bug.
Please start your
hemostatic jutsu.
Right!
What's wrong?!
It's okay! The Exploding
Bug just started to grow
for a second there.
My god! How am I supposed
to keep my word to stay
still with all this
going on?!
Huh? What is
it, Tsunade?
What's wrong,
Tsunade?
Blood?
Oh, I see...
So you suffer from
hemophobia. You're
afraid of the sight
of blood.
It all makes sense
now. That's why you
left the surgery up
to your subordinate.
Excuse me, I'm
going outside to
get some air.
What a truly debilitating
condition for a Medical
Ninja to be afflicted with.
Nawaki...
Dan...
Shizune, tell
me something.
I'm in the middle
of surgery!
I know that! I'm not
asking you to stop,
just to talk.
Tsunade is right up there
with Jiraiya and Orochimaru
as one of the Legendary
Sannin of the Leaf.
What on earth could
have happened to
make her fear blood
this way?
I confess, I'm curious
too. Even though Lady
Tsunade isn't from the
same village as we are,
she exemplifies what
Medical Ninja strive
to be.
But the suffering that
we all witnessed in
her earlier...
I understand.
What you must understand
is Lady Tsunade's had
two important people in
her life. The first one
was her younger
brother, Nawaki.
But on the day after
his birthday, after she
had just given him his
present, he was killed
in battle during the
Third Great Ninja World
War.
And the second was the
man she promised to share
her life with, Dan Kato.
He was my uncle, too.
Tsunade, I don't want
to die yet. There are
so many things left
to do.
Don't try to talk!
It can't be. I
can't die here.
Not this way.
Not yet.
Please, don't worry,
Dan. I've stopped the
bleeding. Just save
your strength.
You're going to
be all right.
Thank goodness.
That's a relief.
Come back, Dan!
Don't go! Don't
leave me!
Don't go!
(screaming)
And ever since that
day. Lady Tsunade has
been traumatized.
Well, then, I suppose
that I too, must have
been in shock from
seeing Nigai die.
Otherwise, I never
would've gambled our lives
a Medical Ninja who has
completely lost it.
Lady Tsunade
hasn't lost it!
(shocked gasp)
The Exploding Bug's
been entirely removed.
The surgery's finished.
Please, close him up.
Yes, ma'am!
Also, Lady Tsunade
hasn't lost her
Medical Ninjutsu
abilities.
So I'll continue to carry
on for her until she gets
back on her feet, and she
will, because she has to!
For her sake and
for my late uncle,
too!
I won the bet
back then.
What's that?
The reinforcements that
Amai called up quickly
rushed over, and the
Nokizaru Troops seemed
to have given up.
Hmph! It was
all merely
dumb luck!
Well, then what's the
connection between
overcoming your
hemophobia, and
Naruto winning the
bet that the two
of you made with
each other?
It's...
No! Don't die!
Don't die!
Naruto's tenacious
life force.
...To be Hokage...
To be Hokage,
that's my dream!
And that intense drive
to become Hokage.
Once more, one
last time...
I just felt like
betting on Naruto
again.
Huh?! Are you telling me
I went along with a silly
bet that had no stakes
whatsoever?
Hnnh! It's too late
to complain now. You'll
just have to suck it up.
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
I've been prepared for this.
Ever since the Allied Shinobi
Forces was formed!
Oh, that's right!
Of course!
The First Hokage's
pendant is what I
want to see! C'mon
Naruto, show it to me!
I don't have it
anymore.
What?!
Ha! I think that when
the Nine Tails got
called out before, I
ended up destroying it.
Yeah, but, wasn't
that thing super
important?!
It's okay. Granny and
I don't really need
something like that
anyway.
'Cause we keep our
promise to each other
deep down in our hearts.
Yeah!
Let's hurry!
I bet everyone's
waiting for us!
You revel in killing.
I hate to think we're
both called shinobi.
Stop being so full of
yourself. Who gave you
permission to wield the
Executioner's Blade?!
That blade belongs to the
Seven Ninja Swordsmen of
the Mist! An outsider
wielding it?!
I don't like it
one bit!
Going up against these
two alone is going to
be rough, but...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Danger:
Jinpachi and Kushimaru!"
Looks like you're
backed up against
a wall, buddy!