I didn't expect to lose
this many of my pawns.
And retrieving unique
corpses turned out to
be a failure.
So then, what's my
next move?
Reanimation Jutsu?
It's a summoning?
Yes that's right.
The Second Hokage is
who originally
developed it.
But then he
sealed it away
as a Forbidden
Jutsu.
Such a waste...
So I set about
restoring it.
You're taken with someone
else's jutsu, Lord Orochimaru?
It's quite
remarkable.
Naturally,
I've made a
few improvements.
As you can see...
There's still much more
room for refinement,
though.
I need more personal
information material.
Hm? Personal
information material?
And what does
that mean?
Why, flesh and
blood of course, ideally
from legendary shinobi.
Now, I've collected
what materials I could.
But from this point
on, I want you to
help me, Kabuto.
I will find a way
to perfect this jutsu.
I understand,
Lord Orochimaru.
Maybe it's time for me
to stir things up a
bit on the battlefield.
[exhausted sigh]
Are those guys allies?
They are!
Hey!
So, it's a Sealed
Reanimation huh?
That's right.
Inside's Toroi, the
Cloud's Magnet Style
user.
I'm amazed that
you two guys
could seal him.
Oh no, actually, Naruto
showed up and helped
us out big time!
A renowned shinobi
controlled by the
Reanimation Jutsu.
He must be
turning in his grave.
A long time ago,
my dad went on a
mission with Toroi
and was killed.
What? Seriously?
I'm guessing that
burden was just too
much for my father.
Hey, look there.
A Reanimated Ninja!
There's still
another one left!
We gotta seal him
fast!
Summoning Jutsu.
What is this?
It's a huge ambush,
that's what it is!
Contact HQ for
reinforcements!
Right!
To think I'd have to
resort to sending
you guys out on
the battlefield.
Our orders, are to
retrieve the sealed
Reanimated Ninja.
Hey, don't order me
around! I won't listen
to a Leaf Ninja!
Enough bickering!
We are no longer
part of this
transient world
of flesh and bone.
It's annoying, but we're
being controlled, and
all of us have the
same orders to follow.
[grunt]
I'll give the
orders here!
All units, prepare
to attack!
Who are you?!
The Red Cloud of Dust!
Daimaru of the Wind!
[startled gasp]
So, you've
heard of me
have you?
No one has
heard of you.
What?! That
can't be!
You must've
died before me!
But anyway, we're being
controlled. Nothing we
can do about that.
Whether we're being
controlled or not,
let's just get this
over with.
Honestly I really don't
want to die...again.
Oh, stop your
complaining, would ya?!
All units, attack!
We have the
advantage of numbers!
Incoming!
Be on your guard!
It's like an entire army!
The size of the Allied
Forces but Reanimated Ninja!
If we fight them
face to face..then
we're all..sure to
die.
All of you, attack!
[fighting efforts]
Quick, fall back!
You all stay away!
Ah, not good!
[startled yells]
All of them are...
so weak!
Maybe they're
only genin!
No, this is
no good!
Who was it? Who said
that we had the
advantage here?!
[yelp]
Everyone attack!
Sealing team, advance
as well!
[grunt]
We can do this!
Seal them all!
Wait, all of those
reanimations...don't
tell me.
I've revived many, but
harvesting their
personal information
material was a real ordeal.
It's essentially
just grave robbing.
Sometimes they're so
rotted, you can't
even tell who it is.
I had a lot of
failures along
the way.
[fighting in the distance]
Are these the failures?
All they have is
numbers! Attack as one!
Musai? Is it you?
Is it really you?!
You mean...You're
my father?!
What?!
That guy's
your dad?!
Is he strong?!
Hardly. You didn't
even get past Chunin
class, right?
Why, you fool!
Just lie and say
I was strong!
There it is!
[gasp]
They're coming
right this way!
What?!
You must be careful Musai,
because our orders are-
To take back the
powerful pieces
that I've lost.
That is what all
you pawns are for.
[agonizing screaming]
What's going on?!
This is...not the
right one, Kabuto.
Yes, I agree,
Lord Orochimaru.
Who are you guys?!
Listen, out of
curiosity...
You aren't the
Magnetic-Style User
Toroi, are you?
What? Are you
kidding? No way!
I can't even hold
a candle to a
shinobi like Toroi.
What do we do
with him, Lord
Orochimaru?
Hmm...
Let's keep him for now,
he may come in handy.
I'm sorry, but
I cannot disobey!
As it strange as it
may sound, I'm
going to rescue Toroi!
I will not allow
that. We'll
protect him!
Over there!
That's the reanimated
force we got the
report about!
All of you, stay
focused and attack!
Alright!
Reinforcements!
Is that...No way!
Huh?
Hey big bro over
here, it's me!
Over here!
What?! You?!
You've been
reanimated?!
But why?!
Listen, how's
my family? My kids?
They're all just fine,
they're doing well in
the village.
Oh, that's good.
I'm glad they're okay.
Your wife even got
remarried a while
back, and she's
really happy now.
What?!
She did?!
She got married
to someone else?!
Well I guess
I can't blame her.
I hate to do this
to kin, but I must
seal you.
Are you...Over here!
Hey, it's me! It's me!
Huh? What the hell?!
Why'd you get
reanimated?!
I couldn't say it until
now, but I was wrong.
Can you find it in your
heart to forgive me?
Oh, listen
forget it.
That entire mess is in
the past now.
Besides, you're
dead anyway.
You forgive me?!
I forgave you
long ago!
Really?!
Sorry, gotta
seal you dad.
Wait! First...
What...?
During that mission, I
fought alongside Toroi
until the very end, for
the village!
Please make sure
that you tell
Lord Raikage!
Sure, dad. I will.
[grateful grunt]
[roars of battle]
Yes! More
reinforcements!
They've sent in
quite a few of them.
We have to keep
them occupied.
Leave it to me.
Swirling Smoke Jutsu!
What's this smoke?!
Just ignore it
and attack!
Platoon! You will
follow me now!
I said not to
order me around!
It is really quite
tragic to be forced to
fight when there is
no desire to fight.
I can't believe it.
They made peace with
themselves!
Just who do you mean?
Those four guys from
the Hidden Cloud.
Even after all this
time they were able to
clear their consciences.
Do you still harbor
any regrets?
Of course! I did die when
I was very young. It'd
be strange not to.
To tell you the
truth, I have
some too.
And you, Monk?
Death is the destiny
of every man.
You're quite
enlightened.
Perhaps, but not during
my lifetime. What
about you?
I felt no lingering
attachments in life.
Although now...since I'm dead,
I do feel some regrets.
Regret is a completely
ridiculous topic
for you to talk about.
Besides, I didn't reanimate
you merely to have
philosophical discussions.
I've just returned.
How'd it go?
There's no mistake.
It's Gari, the Stone's
Explosive-Style User.
Been rummaging
for corpses again?
[annoyed sigh]
At least call it
grave robbing.
Whatever you call it,
you're still exploiting
the dead,
Don't mock him, Sasuke.
You have done very
good work, Kabuto.
Yes.
Anyway, Orochimaru,
I'm ready.
What are you
having me do today?
Don't be so hasty.
Today's training
will be special.
After Lord Orochimaru
was killed, I was left
alone once again.
However...
But my story's
different.
Instead of reaching beyond
Lord Orochimaru, I stubbornly
kept clinging tightly to his
power.
Now I have a much better
idea of how you must've
felt, Naruto.
You made me see...
And so I decided that
I would try to be like you.
That's why my path's
clear to me.
I'm going to use what
I was able to absorb
of Lord Orochimaru,
To become a better,
stronger Kabuto Yakushi!
[struggling]
[pleased reaction]
[painful cries]
[surprised gasp]
Oh, I see
In thought you
were Sasori.
But you're his grandmother.
At last...
Zabuza Momochi.
You'll carry on once again
as one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist.
[struggling effort]
Are you Hanzo of
the Salamander?
What? No, I'm
the right hand man
of his right hand man.
I'm Heiji of the
Rain Shelter.
[annoyed sigh]
[painful scream]
Are you Chiriku of the
Guardian Shinobi Twelve?
Sorry, but I am not.
I am Chiriku's mentor.
My name is Chukaku.
Oh! So you're
actually stronger
than Chiriku?
Oh, uh...
No, I'm afraid that
I am merely a scholar.
[defeated sigh]
A motley crew of failures
is what this group is.
But still, I think
you'll be useful.
Alright, just do it.
Do you think we got
all of them?
I don't know...
Some could've escaped
under cover of the smoke.
Contact Headquarters. Tell
them already sealed
reanimated ninja were
targeted.
And see if everyone
else is safe.
I see it!
Right there!
Hurry up! We must
rendezvous with
Gaara's men!
Lady Temari! There's
a message from HQ. We
have to turn back now!
What was that?!
It appears that someone
known as the Third Raikage
is sealed in there.
Well, I guess that means
we're supposed to revive him.
Leave it to me!
[screaming in pain]
It's a barrier.
Earth Style: Sand Dance!
The barrier's broken
but...I cannot
undo this.
That is one stubborn
Jutsu Formula.
Then first, we'll have
to decode it.
Looks like it's my turn...
Although I have no
desire to do this.
Can you do it?
Jutsu Formulas do fall
under this monk's
special expertise.
[grunt]
[chanting]
That's not
bad at all.
Blade Dance Jutsu!
[painful screaming]
It took forever to
seal the Raikage.
We're not going
to let him come back!
[excited chuckling]
Temari!
Huh?!
Oh, how I've longed
to see you, dear Temari!
[shocked reaction]
She knows him?
I don't know.
Da-Daimaru?!
How did you ever become
one of the reanimated?!
I have nothing to lose
now so I'm just gonna go
ahead and say it!
Uh, say what?
Alright then, here
goes nothing...
Temari...I have
always loved you!
Wind Scythe!
[yelling in pain]
Oh, well. I guess
that was to be expected.
I am a reanimation
after all.
But Temari, at least
do me the courtesy of
telling me how you
really feel about me.
Look, when we were kids you
were mean to me every
chance that you got, and now
you tell me this?!
Oh...Sorry about
that back then.
Since I'm dead, I can say it:
You were always on my mind.
Then why were you
so mean to me?!
Aw, come one, soften
up a bit! You can't
help that!
Yeah! I mean, that's
just the way boys are.
What way is that?
The way he was!
I think that it's really
beautiful, Temari. The
way he declared his
love for you!
Even more so
now that he's
passed on!
It's so romantic!
He only had the courage
'cause he's reanimated.
Actually, I'm kinda
surprised that you
were reanimated.
Hey, come on! I'm
Daimaru, the Red
Cloud of Dust!
Like the forgettable
C-rank mission where
you lost your life.
Your name is unknown.
You're not famous at all.
Uh, Temari? Did
you hate me back then?
Not at all, you were
a lot of fun.
But best of all, you weren't
scared that I was the
Kazekage's daughter,
and Gaara's older sister.
So you mean...
If I'd lived, you
would have dated me?
Nope. No way
No way.
Damn, you are just
brutally honest.
But I like that
about you!
There's someone that
Temari already likes,
you know.
Yeah, she's in
demand.
Ugh, I should
have known!
What are you talking
about?! There's no one
that I like!
Look, just get this
over with and seal me.
You know, back when I
heard that you had died
I was very sad, Daimaru.
Seeing you now must
be the hand of Fate.
Did you cry over me?
Did you? Hm?
Nope. Sorry, I
didn't cry.
Sealing team!
Make it snappy!
Right!
Well, so long Temari.
So long, Daimaru.
Now then...
Be careful. He was in
the Foundation as
Danzo's bodyguard.
He's dangerous.
As you know, we cannot
defy the orders we've
been given.
So keep your distance.
Blade Dance Jutsu!
Was that a Clone Jutsu?
Notify Headquarters
about him!
We'll rendezvous with
the Main Company.
Will do!
Come on.
I couldn't retrieve
the pawns I lost.
But this one has
turned out to be
quite a find.
Please hurry! You have to
seal me soon...Or you'll
all be destroyed!
Good job finding me.
My insects led me.
Judging by your appearance,
I can only assume that
you've been reanimated.
Do you remember my
Venemousa Beetles?
Hurry, call for
reinforcements. You
can't stop me alone.
You're wrong. I'm
probably the only
one who can.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Shino vs. Torune!
Let's settle this,
just the two of us.