(Black Zetsu)
Countless nights passed...
...Chakra had been dispersed
to those who are unworthy.
...The seal that caused such
deep humiliation has now been
shattered.
...May the infinite
moonlight guide you...
...Use my body!
Become one again!
...Yes!  Awaken, god almighty!
...Progenitor of all chakra!
...And thus... the tale of
revival concludes here!
[explosions]
It's chakra!
[screams]
[shouting]
This is really bad, Sasuke!
This chakra's way stronger
than even Ten Tails'!
Stop them before they move!
[gasp]
[grunts]
You're like two moths
flying into the flame!
I'm gonna absorb the chakra
from the both of you, too.
Damn it!
[gasp]
(Naruto)
Isn't she the one Super
Gramps mentioned?!
(Sasuke)
Kaguya Otsutsuki!
♪
[shout]
[gasp]
Sasuke...!
Huh?
[crash]
Sasuke...!
Naruto...!
[frightened gasp]
(Kakashi)
Those two ought to be okay...
But Sakura... don't make any
careless moves right now!
These two, they are,
Hagoromo and Hamura's.
No, rather they are
Indra and Ashura.
Then it was Hagoromo who
gave them the jutsu.
(Thinking)
Sasuke! Naruto!
Thank goodness!
...Who is she?  Why'd Madara
suddenly become her?
(Sasuke Thinking)
This chakra, It's far greater
than Madara's!  I can't believe
such a person existed!
Hagoromo knew she'd appear.
That's why he entrusted us with-
(Kakashi Thinking)
Obito.
What are your intentions?!
(Kaguya)
Ninshu, No, you said shinobi,
It's futile to speak to you
about that,
...when all you do is
tamper with chakra, without
knowing its true meaning.
...This place... this land
is my precious nursery.
And that means I cannot let it
be damaged any further.
So let us put an end to
all this fighting...
Huh?
Then...
Here , that is...
(Kaguya)
I shall erase... all of
you here, instead!
[grunt]
No way!
Is that lava below?
Is this a genjutsu?
Summoning Jutsu!
Sasuke!  Over there!
[grunt]
What're you doing?
Help them, not me!
(Sakura)
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
(Naruto)
How--?
Huh?
(Sasuke)
Kakashi Sensei tied one end of a
scroll onto his kunai and used
it just like a rope.
For Obito, he just pinned him
to the wall with a kunai. But
Nice, Kakashi Sensei! Way to go!
(Kakashi Thinking)
Sorry to be so rough
with you, Obito...
[gasp]
I was right. It's
not a genjutsu...
(Thinking)
Don't tell me She summoned an
alternate dimension all around
us?
Eyes forward, Naruto.
Naruto I'm going to be
completely frank with you...
Our whole world will come
to an end if either of us
dies in this fight.
Only your Six Paths Power of
Light and my Six Paths Power
of Shadow can seal away that
being in front of us.
If we're not able to do that,
humankind will be exterminated.
The two of us can't afford
to die, no matter what.
Kakashi Sensei and Sakura just
happened to be near you when the
Infinite Tsukuyomi was launched.
That's all.
You understand, don't you?
Yeah, I get it...
[gasp]
I know what you're saying
and that you're right.
But still... this is also one of
those times when your body just
moves on its own...
(Naruto)
Like on that bridge...
You beat him, Sasuke!
[worried gasp[
Why- Why did you,
save me?
You should see the look on your
face...You- you look like a
total loser.
But why...?! Why'd you save me?!
I didn't ask for this!
I don't know why...
I just did.
[groan]
[gasp]
my body, just moved... there
was no time to think...
...loser!
But never mind that. Because I
know that you get what I mean,
too, Sasuke.
(Thinking)
Sasuke's right...
...Back then, Sasuke
did act subconsciously...
[sob]
(Thinking)
But... Thank you, Naruto...
[gasp]
[scream]
Damnit!
Huh? No!
Now...!
(Thinking)
Byakugan!  Damn it!
My hawk's Chakra
Points were hit!
[shout]
(Thinking)
I'll have to use Susano'o!
[gasp]
Madara's rods are
disintegrating...
At last I can move...
Now if I can just get...
(Tobirama)
...to the spot where I sensed
that massive chakra...
I might learn something.
But... that chakra
suddenly vanished...
They've dissolved.
Did they defeat Madara?
[grunt] I've got
to get to Naruto!
Just one more time...
Naruto, you're...
[gasp]
You can levitate?!
Oh--!
(Thinking)
Right. When he was enhanced
by Six Paths' chakra,
Madara levitated, too...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Take care of Sakura
and Kakashi Sensei.
Six Paths' Chakra.
You act triumphant just because
you have a special accoutrement.
However, no matter
what kind it might be,
All chakra belongs
to me and me alone.
Now, one more time...
I shall reunify all chakra!
[gasp]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[charging up yell]
[grunt]
Sasuke! Now!
[large explosion]
[grunts]
Sasuke...! [grunt]
I can't stop!
[grunts]
[gasp]
Huh?
Even Susano'o is useless.
Let's get Obito down while
we have the chance.
For a second, I forgot that
you're able to use that
Teleportation-like jutsu now.
(Naruto)
You had me worried there!
It's just like this foothold.
We've both benefitted
from Six Paths' power.
But if we're not able to
seal her away, all of it
will be meaningless.
Yeah.
[gasps]
[sobbing]
(Kaguya)
My children, with whom
I shared my chakra.
(Naruto Thinking)
I... can't move...
(Kaguya Thinking)
Now come to your mother.
Sasuke! She's taking our chakra!
Kaguya seems see her children...
when she looks at the two of
you.
Isn't that sweet?
She who was sealed away
by her own children,
poor, pitiable
mother...
Why did Six Paths Super Gramps
seal away his own mom?
I thought that he sealed
away Ten Tails...
It appears that you have
a misconception.
Black Zetsu, just who
and what are you?
I am Kaguya's child.
Wait, you're what?
(Sasuke Thinking)
His aura suddenly seems
different...
(Black Zetsu)
I recorded everything that
happened while Mother was gone.
And molded it as well.
The tale of shinobi... is the
tale of restoring Mother.
It's what?! What does
that mean?! What are you
even talking about?!
That you know Mother's name...
means you must have met
Hagoromo.
I knew that it was possible,
depending on the reincarnates'
power.
And to receive the power to
seal away Mother as well.
Huh?! But we're gonna
seal Ten Tails!
(Zetsu)
Indra and Ashura's reincarnates
cooperating this closely is
rare.
You two know nothing.
Let me tell you her tale while
I absorb all of your chakra.
Like I just said, Mother was
sealed away previously by her
own children.
It was said to have been...
a most powerful seal.
The jutsu that transformed Ten
Tails into a Catastrophic
Planetary Devastation core...
and turned it into the moon.
But just before the seal took
hold, she gave birth to me,
in order that she could
one day be restored.
I'll show you all of it.
I don't have any candy to give
you, but the  puppet show is
about to begin.
♪
(Tenji)
Are you telling me that she
came from the heavens?
(Chief Vassal)
Yes, sir!  This woman was found
on the spot where the light
fell.
(Tenji)
Tell me your name?
(Chief Vassal)
Answer him!
The man before you
is Lord Tenji, king of
the Land of Ancestors!
(Kaguya)
You asked for my name...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Kaguya Otsutsuki."
(Kaguya)
I'm the one who protects
the Divine Tree.
♪