Yeah?
Mr. Rosso. We've got a job for you.
The Mamma Aiuto gang is on the move.
The Mamma Aiuto gang? I don't know, I'm kind of busy.
We need you to protect one of our
ships that's carrying a fortune in gold.
Is that all?
Well,
uh, there's a group of school girls on board, too.
Now that is going to cost you.
See here, bounty hunter, no price
gouging. We've got a contract with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm on it.
Stop the ship!
Stop the ship or we'll sink it! You hear me, idiots?
Look at that! Seaplane pirates!
Someday I'm gonna get off my lazy
butt and give this thing an overhaul.
Are you seaplane pirates?
Yeah, that's right.
So we're your hostages?
That's right, too.
It smells like you never bathe.
You know you're sharp!
How cute!
Could use some blood.
Hey! Hey! Come on, kids. We're in a hurry!
Boss, do we have to take all 15 of them?
Yeah, it's not nice to separate them from their friends.
Looks like I'm late.
Porco, hurry!
The Mamma Aiuto gang have taken the girls and the gold.
They went that way! They went that way!
No! Not that way! Wrong way! Wrong way!
Calm down. I know what I'm doing.
That Mamma Aiuto gang is so cheap,
they'll fly till they're just out of sight, then hide
on the nearest island, Just to save money on gasoline.
Damn.
Don't give out on me now.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Yeah. That's my girl.
That can't be good. I better get this job done quick.
There they are.
What the heck is this, a sightseeing plane?
This is pirate country.
They know better than to be out here.
Porco Rosso!
I can't believe it. I love you, Porco!
Hey, girls, get out of here.
You can get yourselves kidnapped
in these skies, sweethearts.
What's this?
Looks like we're safe.
Hey, look, we're flying!
What's going on down there?
Now, girls, this is not a playground.
Hey, can't you shut them up?
I told you that we shouldn't have taken them all.
My nose!
Can we come up?
Yeah, all right.
Just don't let the boss know.
Wow.
Great view.
Hey, look! What a pretty red plane.
What? Where?
That was Porco.
Yeah.
All right. Let's get this thing over with.
He's back!
It is Porco!
Cut it out!
I can't see.
Ha-ha!
Uh... That's not good.
The engine stopped.
We're gonna crash.
No, we're not! We've got another engine.
Hey! Don't just sit there! Shoot him! Shoot him!
You keep missing him.
I think he's better than you.
Quiet down.
Signal from the pig.
"Surrender now. You lose, jerks."
Never!
Here he comes. I'll get him this time.
Whe..
Wow!
Where'd he go?
Oh, He's great.
He's hiding.
Help! Help!
We're gonna sink! Let's get out of here.
We're not gonna sink. This is a seaplane!
No, no, no!
That's not good.
We're sinking!
Stop them! They're valuable hostages!
Get back inside!
Girls, out of the water! It's dangerous!
Don't worry. We all belong to a swimming club. Watch this.
No! No! No! Don't do it!
Whee!
Signal from the pig!
Hey, watch me, too!
He says, "Hand over the girls and the gold, and I'll
let you keep some loot so you can repair your ship."
I'd hate to put you jerks out of business.
We get to keep some.
That's generous.
We're not giving in, you idiots!
Come and get it, pig! I dare you!
Gotcha.
Uh-oh.
My gun's jammed!
Wait, that's not good!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
We surrender! We surrender!
Nice pig! Nice pig!
Bye-bye, pirates! Bye-bye!
So that worked out well.
It's really nice of him not to kill us.
Show more ambition! You're a pirate!
Porco, I gotta go peepee.
Come on.
What?
Come get me.
Hey, get out of here!
Wait, don't touch that! You're...
Hey, get down from there! Don't...
Put your clothes back on!
Whee!
Hey! All right, get down!
"Another triumph for Porco Rosso."
It's a good thing we pirates are banding together, eh?
We've got to do something about that stupid pig.
So, your American here can help us?
The pirates of the Adriatic
can't have an American protect them.
That's embarrassing.
No, it's not. Look at him. His
grandma's cousin was Italian.
And besides, Curtis is the only pilot
who can beat Porco. And for 10% he can...
10%? I'm not going to pay that.
Shh.
Quand nous chanterons
le temps des cerises
et gai rossignol
et Merle moqueur
seront tous en fete!
Les belles auront
La folie en tete
et les amoureux, de soleil au coeur!
Quand nous chanterons
le temps des cerises
sifflera bien mieux
le Merle moqueur!
Mais il est bien court
le temps des cerises
ou l'on s'en va deux cueillir en revant
des pendants d'oreilles
cerises d'amour aux robes pareilles.
Here you go.
Good evening.
tombant sous la feuille
en gouttes de sang
mais il est bien court
le temps des cerises
pendents de corail - qu-on cueille revants.
The pig's here.
Look what's waddling in.
...sensation like that...
Shh!
Usual.
J'aimerai toujours
le temps des cerises
c'est de ce temps la
que je garde au couer...
Mr. Rosso! Congratulations on
defeating the Mamma Aiuto gang again.
Did you know you've taken in twice the
reward of any bounty hunter this year?
And, sir, how does it feel to be
the top bounty hunter in the Adriatic?
And let me ask...
Hey! What do you think you're doing? Get your hands off...
Shut up and listen to the song.
Yes, Sir.
She sure is incredible.
I just might have to take her back home with me.
I bet she could make it big in America.
Although, she will have to stop
singing in French all the time, of course.
Hey, cowboy, is that your plane out front?
Yep. I don't mind saying she made me a
bit of a celebrity in the racing world.
So you're the one who beat the
Italians in the Schneider Cup.
That's right. But what I'm best at is aerial combat.
These pirates tell me that you got a
pretty good reputation in the skies.
I'd be careful if you plan on
making a deal with those pirate gangs.
Not only are they lying cheapskates,
not a single one of them knows how to bathe.
That's for sure.
Hey! We heard that, you stupid pig.
Well, look at this.
All you handsome pirate bosses at one table.
You're not here to cause problems, are you?
Never.
Not us.
You know my rule. You eat in my restaurant, not fight.
Of course, Gina. We would never
fight within 50 miles of your place.
We're even getting along with the pig. Aren't we?
Mmm-hmm.
Be good, boys.
Wish me luck.
May I help you?
Back off, Curtis!
Hey!
Porco, tell me about your rescue.
Next time, when it's just the two of us.
Eating all alone up here again?
So, what do you think of that American fly boy?
He's something else, isn't he?
As soon as he saw me, he asked me to marry him.
So I told him of the three pilots I've married,
the first died in the war,
the second died in the Atlantic,
the last one, he died in Asia.
So you've heard something.
I got the call last night.
They found his remains in some remote part of Bengal.
It's strange, Marco.
I've been waiting to hear something
for three years, but now I can't even cry.
I just feel numb. Maybe I've run out of tears.
Yeah, well, the good guys always die.
Cheers. To a good man.
Marco, I want to thank you for keeping an eye on me
and my restaurant all these years.
I just can't tell you how much
your friendship means to me.
Well, you know, it's a great place, except for that
ugly photograph you keep hanging on the wall up there.
Hey, that's my favorite picture.
I can't believe you scribbled over your face.
That's the only picture left of you as a human.
How are you ever going to break
that stupid curse on you, Marco?
Face it. I'm a pig.
That American's gonna be trouble.
Hey, that's Porco Rosso. Let's alert the captain.
I'd like it only in 20s, please.
Yes, ma'am.
I envy you, Mr. Rosso. I wish I
could make money the way you do.
Here's this month's payment.
That's the last you owe on the seaplane.
Let's see.
How about buying some patriotic
bonds, to help serve our nation?
Sorry, I'm a pig. I'll leave that to you humans.
Hey, there, Mr. Rosso. We've got your gun ready.
Give me some ammo, too, Kid.
Yes, Sir.
A lot of commotion in the streets.
Sure is. Looks like our islands
are in for a change of government.
If so, you bounty hunters will soon be outlaws.
Laws don't mean anything to a pig.
That's a good point. They don't
mean much to us weapons dealers either.
Here are the bullets. Are you sure you want the usual?
We've got new armor-piercing ones that explode on contact.
Hey. Easy, kid, I'm just a bounty
hunter. I'm not fighting a war.
Come again!
So what's the difference between
fighting a war and bounty hunting?
If you make money from war, you're scum.
But if you can't make money from
bounty hunting, you're an idiot.
How in the world can we be in debt? This is ridiculous!
We miscalculated.
We didn't take quite enough money to cover our repairs.
The other pirates are here.
Man, this is embarrassing. I can't
believe we have to work with these losers.
It's the stupid pig's fault, boss.
Look at that. Those Mamma Aiuto
guys can't even afford paint.
It's embarrassing to be seen with them.
All right, I guess we're all here.
Hey, you in back. What happened to our Mr. America?
He's flying in the sun.
Typical American.
Target sighted.
Queen of the Mediterranean at 10 o'clock.
That ship's kind of big, isn't it?
That's why we're doing this as
a group. Don't be such a sissy!
We're having engine trouble.
You go on ahead, we'll back you up.
Don't try to chicken out! We stick to the plan!
We share the cost of repairs if one of us gets hit, right?
No, you babies! Everyone is
responsible for his own expenses!
Even for the ammo?
What do you think?
We're having engine trouble.
No, we're having engine trouble.
Engine trouble here.
Shut up, you sissies! Let's get fighting!
Attention, all passengers.
We are now being attacked by seaplane pirates.
Do not be concerned.
The Queen of the Mediterranean cruise line
has anticipated this possibility,
and has equipped our ship with
two top-of-the-line fighter pilots.
Now launching, from the main deck, in plane number one,
the Black Stallion, Signore Bulkar.
Thank you! Thank you!
And in plane number two, the
Wolf of Tibere, Captain Visconti.
Go get 'em, boys!
Go get 'em!
I didn't know they had security.
No!
Oh, they're panicking. I'll have to win this thing myself.
Get off me! Help! Curtis!
Make way for the American!
Yee-haw!
All right, I give up.
I'm gonna have to take this baby to Milan for repairs.
And with the help of American Donald Curtis,
the air pirates shot down
the Queen of the Mediterranean's two security planes.
After stealing all the valuables from the ship,
the pirates left the following message.
We're coming for
you,
Porco Rosso!
Get off me!
I repeat, "We're coming for you, Porco Rosso...
Argh. Ack. Argh. Get off me."
You really expect me to wait here?
Forget it. I'm off to Milan.
Luscious food, a soft bed, beautiful women.
There we go.
Come on, baby. Just hold out until Milan.
I don't like this weather. I better duck below the clouds.
Come on. Come on, girl. Come on.
That's it. That's right. Just stay with me, baby.
Porco!
What?
Fight me, pig! One-on-one.
No, thanks, Tex. I'm kind of busy.
If you run away, I'll tell everyone you're a chicken.
Chicken, pig, what's the difference?
Whoa. I'm out in the open.
Oh, come on, baby.
I hit the pig!
You didn't hit anything. My engine died, you idiot.
He's down! I'm a bona fide celebrity. Yahoo!
I need some evidence or no one will believe me.
Let's see. Ooh.
Gotcha!
Obnoxious red paint. That's proof.
I might just take it back to Texas as a gift for Ma.
Hurry, it's an emergency. Marco's been shot down.
Wait, Miss Gina!
There's a phone call for you!
Porco's alive! He's on the phone right now!
You can take it at the front desk. Hey! Wait!
Marco, are you all right?
I was just about to go and search for you in my boat.
I'm fine. A tugboat gave me a lift.
Thank God.
And I've slimmed down, marooned on an island for two days.
So ll look pretty good.
Although, not as sexy as that American fly boy.
I'm sure he'll be stopping by your
place. So tell him we'll meet again.
Anyway, I'm off to Milan to fix my plane.
You're in Italy? You idiot!
The Italians have a warrant out for your arrest, remember?
I don't care how great your mechanic is
over there. You get back home, you hear me?
I don't want to yell at you, Marco.
But if you keep acting so
pig-headed, you're going to end up dead,
and I can't bear to go to another pilot's funeral.
Come home, will you?
Sorry, baby. Got to fly.
You jerk!
"Is Porco Rosso dead or alive?"
Good question.
Hey, Porco, I thought you would
come here tonight, so I waited up.
She really took a beating this time.
It looks like you're missing half of the plane.
Wouldn't it be easier to build a new one?
I'm attached to this one.
All right. It's your money.
Hey. Look out, I'm gonna back her in, okay?
So, tell me, Piccolo, where'd you find the girl?
That's my granddaughter from America.
Keep coming, keep coming. Yeah, that's good.
Wow.
Gorgeous fuselage, isn't it, Grandpa?
Great lines.
Not many workers around who
can do a job like this these days.
Well, there's no resemblance.
Mmm?
Are you sure that girl's your granddaughter, Piccolo?
Keep away from her.
Fio, you all right getting the plane off the rig?
Sure, no problem.
I've got to outfly an American named
Curtis, or my business is in the toilet.
Curtis, huh? I've got just what you need.
What do you think?
This would give me some extra kick.
Don't ask how I got it.
All I can say is that it came from an Italian
seaplane that lost the Schneider Cup to Curtis in 1927.
But it wasn't the engine's
fault. The mechanic was an idiot.
I'll tune this up just right.
But don't tune it up too delicately.
I'm not flying this thing in a race, you know.
Hey, you're talking to the god
of engine work here. Trust me.
You plan on taking all of my money?
Quit whining.
These days, money's barely
worth the paper it's printed on.
You're coming up short.
Give me the money you've got in your pockets.
I need that. I've got to pay for
meals, a hotel room, more meals.
You can stay here. Meals
included. I won't charge you much.
So, Piccolo, I haven't seen your
sons around. Are they all right?
They took off to find work.
They took off? Then who's going to design my plane?
Fio will do it.
Fio? That cute little girl?
Don't be such a pig.
She's a talented engineer, even better than my sons.
No dice, pal, I need a professional.
I'm taking my worthless money somewhere else. Sorry.
Wait!
Are you leaving because I'm a
woman? Or is it because I'm too young?
Actually, it's both, kiddo.
Okay. That's fair.
But tell me what you think it takes to make a pilot great.
Experience?
No, it's intuition.
I just knew you weren't gonna say experience.
Grandpa said you flew solo your first week
and were a great pilot right from the very start.
Isn't that true?
Hmm.
Yeah, but that was in 1910, when I was 17.
Seventeen? That's the same age I am.
I can't help being a woman, but
I guarantee you I have the talent.
If I don't do a good job, you don't have to pay.
Okay, Grandpa?
She's my granddaughter, she'll do fine.
Now with me, I was fixing engines at the age of 12.
Why don't you sleep on it? That's your bed. Breakfast
is at 7:00. I've left you a clean towel in the bathroom.
Good night!
You still don't have enough, but since you're a
good friend, I've decided to loan you the rest.
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
You were up all night?
Here's a rough draft of the design.
So what do you think?
I tweaked the wing section a bit, which should
make the plane fly at least five knots faster.
Look, I dug up the original blueprints.
The design is really radical, huh?
Wooden monocoque wings, with extreme angles of incidence.
I've never seen anything like it.
Yeah, they only made one, then
they decided it was too dangerous.
No pilot could fly it.
I found it covered in dust in a warehouse.
I can see why.
With the wings angled like that, I'm really
surprised you could even get it off the water.
Takeoffs and landings can be a little bit tricky.
But get her up to speed, and she handles like a dream.
Why don't you try increasing the angle
of incidence by half a degree on the wing?
The rest looks fine.
So you're giving me the job?
Oh, thank you for trusting a woman.
All right, you've got the job. But on one condition, Fio.
No more staying up all night, or
your work will start getting sloppy.
Also, it's really bad for your complexion.
You got it.
To be honest, I couldn't sleep last night
because I was afraid you wouldn't give me the job.
I should sleep fine tonight.
I'll go make us some coffee,
and then I'll get back to work.
This is so exciting! I can't wait to start building.
Don't tell me that she plans on
building the whole plane by herself.
This is my niece, Monica.
Nice to meet you.
This is Silvana, my other niece,
and her four daughters, Sophia,
Laura, Constance, Valentina.
Fio's big sister, Giliora.
Sandra! She's my cousin.
Marietta, good to see you.
My sons' wives, Maria, Tina, Anna.
And the three old hags showed up.
Porcellino!
Are you girls really still alive?
You bet. We thought we'd get in on the action.
You're not here to help build my plane, are you?
Yeah. We need to get some poker money.
So, this is the crew, huh.
Uh, don't you have any male relatives?
All the men are gone.
They had to look elsewhere for work.
This is work. Get them back.
Women are great. Don't be such a pig.
You'll see, they're very hard workers.
Yeah, but we're not baking a cake here.
Heavenly Father,
we give you thanks for putting bread on our table,
and for giving us work when we
were on the brink of bankruptcy.
Please forgive us for building a
fighter plane with the hands of women.
Amen.
We'll eat, then work on baking that cake.
This is here.
You're going to whip the pants off Curtis with this.
What do you think? Too delicate?
I think this might be bad for your shed, Piccolo.
Yeah? Wait till we turn it up to full speed.
Hmm. You want to add a trim tab?
Yeah, can I?
I don't know. This is going to cost a lot of money.
It's a great idea, but we've already gone way over budget.
See what the client thinks.
Porco?
Would you stop looking at me like that, Fio?
Just do what's best.
That's great! I've already talked to the manufacturers.
I can get the order filled right away.
I love you, Porco!
I'll give you three months to pay the bill.
Maybe I should just become an air pirate.
You like Fio?
Hmm?
Don't touch her.
Don't worry. Just looking at her makes me tired.
Ferrari, look at you. You're a major now.
Marco, you're crazy. What are you doing back in Italy?
I make it a rule to come and go as I please.
The secret police already know you're in the country.
Were you followed?
I gave them the slip.
You've got to get out of Italy now.
I've seen your arrest warrant,
deserting the Italian Air Force,
entering the country illegally,
being a blatantly unpatriotic pig.
This is no time to laugh, Marco.
They've got it in for you. They
want to confiscate your plane.
Man, this movie stinks.
Marco, why don't you come back to the Air Force?
I've got influence now. I could work something out.
Thanks for the offer, but I'd
rather be a pig than a fascist.
Then you better keep your plane out of the skies.
The only way the Italians will let
you fly is if you fly for our country.
I only fly for myself.
You really are a pig, aren't you?
You realize, if they catch a pig,
they won't give him a fair trial.
I understand. Thanks, Ferrari.
Give my regards to the guys.
This movie's really great.
All right. I'll try to look out
for you, but I can only do so much.
Sure.
Well, so long, friend.
Hey, Porco. Need a ride?
Slide over.
I borrowed this truck so we can
take your seaplane to the lake.
We're ready to give it a test flight.
No test flights. I'm getting out of here today.
That's ridiculous. I refuse to
give you the plane without testing it.
Plus it'll take at least a day to take
the plane apart and transport it to the lake.
I don't have a choice.
I want you to take a good look
behind us, will you? Do it slowly.
That's the fascists' secret police.
They're following us.
Following us? What for?
Because they like my pretty red plane.
Problem is, they don't like me flying it.
Hey, are you a spy or something?
A spy.
That's the last thing I'd ever
do, kid. I only look out for myself.
But you were a hero during the war, right?
Well, this is really strange if
you haven't done anything wrong.
I couldn't agree with you more. Hold on.
How about we try another direction?
Looks like you've done this kind of thing before.
Every time I go to Milan, kiddo.
The plane's ready when you are.
Hey!
Two secret police are hiding
out back, and three in the front.
Ooh, this is so exciting!
Calm down, woman. You're rambling.
What?
Thanks.
Take care.
I will.
Fio! What do you think you're doing?
I'm rigging up my seat. Just
give me about five seconds, okay?
You are crazy if you think I'm
letting you fly home with me.
Shh. The secret police will hear you.
Flo...
There's a warrant out for my arrest, you realize.
This is not a joy ride, sweetheart. So if you...
Hold this for a second, please.
Thank you. Look at this.
Ta-da!
I just whipped this together and it fits perfectly.
It's a bit of a tight fit in here, but it should do.
Would you hold this, please?
Fio, this is way too dangerous. I'll
be taking off from the canal out back.
I don't even know if I can get her off the water.
Mmm-hmm.
I know, that's why you need to have the engineer with you.
So I can make adjustments to the plane.
Don't you get it? I'm off to fight Curtis.
I will have bullets flying over my head.
I can handle that.
I'm responsible for this plane,
and I want to do my first job right.
Think about it. I'm a known womanizer.
I live on a deserted island in a small tent.
That's great. I love camping.
That's not the point.
Take her.
I'll give you a good deal on her
salary, and I know she'll come in handy.
Besides, I want you back in business so I can get paid.
You're this girl's grandfather?
It'll be good for her.
And I'll install this so you two can chitchat.
So you're okay with turning her into an outlaw?
Mmm-mmm. I'm going along as your hostage.
See, that way all my relatives can tell
the police they had no choice but to help you.
So please, Porco. Let me come. I can help you.
You better take out one of those machine guns.
What?
There's not enough space in
there, even with your tiny butt.
Now, take out a gun.
Thank you!
And, you know, my butt is bigger than it looks.
I'll have the gun out in two seconds.
If we hang around here much longer,
even the old ladies will want to come.
That'll cost you a lot of moolah.
Grandma, get out of the way!
Hey, Fio, you bring back souvenirs.
I will.
Contact!
Open the door!
Go!
Get down!
Help! He's kidnapped our girl! Fio!
Bring Fio back!
Whoa!
How's the steering, Porco?
It's crazy. It's just like you, Fio.
It's even harder to handle than before.
Stop the plane. I'll make some adjustments.
No, we don't have time. I'll
get her up in the air somehow.
I can't get enough lift.
Porco, there's a ship!
Get up!
Come on, baby!
The aileron's hitting the water!
Use the trim tab!
The what?
It's the crank on your right!
Hurry!
Got it!
Here we go.
Gorgeous. This is such an incredible view.
Is that plane following us?
It's someone from the Italian Air Force.
Hey, looks like my old buddy Ferrari is here.
What's he saying?
He says the Air Force has a trap for us up ahead.
He'll show us how we can get out of here.
If we fly low all the way home,
we should stay out of their range.
Thank you very much, my friend!
Thank you!
Very funny, you jerk.
What did he say?
He said, "Cute girl. When did you start babysitting?"
Hmm?
"Alas, a solitary rose blooms in a secret garden."
That's my favorite line from a screenplay I wrote.
Mr. Curtis, why are you trespassing in my garden?
I have something special to show you.
It's from Hollywood.
"Dear Mr. Curtis, in regards
to the screenplay you sent us..."
"We'd love to produce it and
will consider you for the lead."
The script's title is The Rose of the Adriatic.
That sounds wonderful.
Really? Then it's settled.
Gina, come to Hollywood with me.
I've got great aspirations. I'm
already a big celebrity as a pilot.
Soon I'll be a Hollywood star, and then...
There's more?
The President.
Wha...
What's so funny?
I'm serious. Don't you want to be the First Lady?
Gina...
I find your humility very charming.
So you'll come with me?
No, I can't. I have a long-standing bet going here.
I bet myself that if a certain man comes
to visit me when I'm out here in my garden,
then the two of us will fall in love.
But that fool only comes to my restaurant at night.
He never stops and shows his face in the daylight.
Porco? I thought he was dead.
You fool.
He left without landing. Well, I guess I lose again.
What? You'd choose that stupid pig over me?
That's right.
Love is a little bit more
complicated here than it is in America.
Falling in love happens to you all the time.
So have fun in Hollywood, little boy.
Little boy?
Hey, watch it with the acrobatics.
You made me bump my head.
I was just saying hi to a friend.
Gina of the Hotel Adriano?
She was that lady in the white dress, wasn't she?
My grandfather told me that all the seaplane
pilots of the Adriatic fall madly in love with Gina.
That's wonderful, Fio.
So, is Gina really your friend?
Or are you in love with her, too?
It's time to refuel.
Turn around, quit yapping and get your butt in your seat.
What? Hey, wait!
Hey, what's a girl doing on Porco's plane?
Where's Porco?
He's having a serious conversation with my dad.
Both the new government and the old Royalists
have started striking up deals with seaplane pirates.
You're not gonna make a penny
hunting your pirates these days, Porco.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Well, sounds like you're out of a job, Porco.
You should join up with one of the two factions.
They'd pay good money for skills like yours.
You betcha.
Especially after Curtis goes back to America.
America?
You're the ones who should be going to America.
"Farewell to freedom in the
Adriatic and to days of wild abandon."
What is that, Shakespeare?
No, it's Porco. See you later.
So long.
Porco, the price of gas here is ridiculous.
He's charging us three times what we pay in Italy.
Don't be such a crook. Be reasonable.
Here in the Adriatic islands, we
don't dilute our gas like Italians do.
Can you please explain that to her, Porco?
Just pay the kid, Fio.
Then plant your butt that's bigger
than it looks back into its cubbyhole.
We're taking off to my hideout.
Fine, the gas money's just gonna go on your bill anyway.
So when do we fight Curtis?
No need to now.
I'm out of a job. No one's
hiring bounty hunters these days.
But what about your honor?
You can't let Curtis run around
acting like he shot you down.
I'm a pig. I don't fight for
honor. I fight for a paycheck.
Oh, wow.
It's beautiful.
What a fantastic hideout.
It feels good to stretch my legs.
What're you doing? You're on my foot.
Hey! Hey!
Well, looks like my hideout's not so hidden anymore.
Boss, we caught the pig!
Get off me. Out of the way!
Move, move it.
You're finished, pig.
It's payback time...
We've got a score to settle.
A girl! We got a girl here!
She's cute.
So what?
Half of the world's population is women, idiot.
Hey. Fio's no ordinary girl. She's
a first-class seaplane engineer.
Huh?
But she's so young. And pretty.
Girl engineer. Are you sure?
She redesigned my plane, and
now it flies better than ever.
She's young, but she's a genius.
You really mean that?
Hey, I never lie about my seaplane, kid.
Treat her with respect.
She came along just to make sure I pay my bill.
So you're in debt, too? It serves you right.
Hey, what do you say we smash his stupid, red
plane to bits and leave him here to rot in debt?
Smash it? You'd destroy a work of art?
It happens to be a one-of-a-kind Savoia S.21.
We realize it's a nice plane, but we have our reasons.
Yeah? What are they?
Well, it's kind of complicated.
You call yourselves seaplane pilots?
Step aside! Watch the shoes.
My grandpa has been telling me stories
about seaplane pilots ever since I was born.
He always says that seaplane pilots are the most
honorable and trustworthy fighters in the world.
Every time they fly, both the
ocean and the sky purify their hearts.
So they're braver than any pilot in the sky,
and they are mightier than any sailor in the sea.
Yeah.
Miss Fio, thank you.
You make me proud to be a seaplane pilot.
And you should be.
I can tell you're not about money or revenge.
You're about honor.
That's right, Fio!
Yeah! To honor!
Now, that girl is something else.
Okay, Miss Fio.
We respect you, so we will not
destroy the plane that you made.
But we still hate that stinking
pig's guts, and we want payback!
Slice him into bacon!
What are you morons talking about?
You can't gang up on a fellow seaplane pilot!
Where's your honor?
You all should be completely ashamed of yourselves.
A real seaplane pilot would never
fight in a pack like a bunch of cowards.
Look at Porco.
He came back here just so he
could have a rematch with Curtis.
And defend his reputation,
like a real seaplane pilot should.
So if you want to fight Porco
honorably, then you fight him in the sky.
One-on-one.
I'd fight Porco, but my plane has engine trouble.
You big liar. Quit making excuses.
What should we do, boss?
She did make some good points.
We have to pick someone who can fight Porco.
I think we should talk to Curtis.
Wait a minute, ask him to fight the pig again?
Only Curtis can beat him.
Our contract with him has already expired.
Howdy, fellas.
Look, it's Curtis!
What's he doing here?
I followed y'all.
I knew you'd get into trouble without me.
Nice going, Fio.
Look at the mess you've gotten me into now.
Here, hold these.
So you wanna challenge me to a rematch, do you, pig?
Why should I give it to you?
I won once already, and my
contract with these boys has expired.
Well, give us a proposition. What do you want?
Hmm.
Beautiful.
Tell you what. If I win, will you marry me, darling?
That's what I want.
Fine with me.
But if Porco beats you, then you
have to pay off the debt he owes me.
Don't do it, Fio.
Back off!
Miss Fio, are you quite certain you want to do this?
You should ask him, not me.
These bills are kind of expensive.
No, they're not.
Are you gonna fight or not?
I will gladly fight for the woman that I love.
Good.
All right!
The fight will take place first thing tomorrow morning.
And since Fio is doing such an
honorable thing, my gang will host.
Yeah!
Hey, we'd like to host, too.
So long, Miss Fio!
This is ridiculous.
So long!
Bye-bye!
Shut up! Just go home already!
Okay.
What on earth possessed you to make that deal?
Well, I'm sorry.
I guess I shouldn't have intervened.
I'm just a stupid little girl.
Fio, I should thank you for saving my life back there.
You really put yourself on the line.
So thanks.
It looks like we're in this thing together now.
So you'll fight Curtis?
He could win, you know.
You've got more honor.
"Honor."
Well, I hate that word, but somehow,
when you say it, it doesn't sound so bad.
What's the matter with you? Are you cold?
Fio.
Oh, boy.
I'm shaking all over, my heart's pounding like crazy.
I guess I was really scared.
I just didn't know if you would fight for me, Porco.
Whoa. What are you doing?
I need a swim.
Oh, no!
What? What's wrong?
I really blew it, Porco!
I should've padded those bills.
Curtis would have paid us a lot more.
You're right.
Marco?
Hmm?
Can't you sleep?
I saw...
Maybe it was a dream.
Go back to sleep. We've got a big day tomorrow.
Porco?
Yeah?
Why did you turn into a pig?
All middle-aged men are pigs.
You know, I've heard a lot about Captain Marco Rossellini.
My father was in his fighter unit.
He told me that Marco once landed his seaplane
in a raging sea to save the life of an enemy pilot.
I think that's amazing.
I got it! What if I kiss you, Porco?
Huh?
Yeah, you've heard of the fairy tale where the girl kisses
the frog and it turns him back into a handsome prince.
Come on.
You've gotta save it for somebody
special, for crying out loud.
Don't you like me?
You're a great kid.
You know what, Fio?
Seeing you makes me wish I'd never given up being human.
Now go to sleep.
First tell me a story. Then I'll go to sleep.
All right.
Here's a winner.
It was the last summer of the Great War.
We were flying over the Adriatic on a routine
surveillance patrol, headed toward Istria.
My good buddy Berlini was right beside me.
He had just gotten married to Gina of the Hotel Adriano,
and I was his best man.
But the war called, so we had to go
back into battle right after the ceremony.
Suddenly, we were in the middle
of the worst dogfight of my life.
Friends and enemies were falling all around me like flies.
I had three planes trying to chase me down,
and all I thought about was myself.
Soon I realized I was the only one left from my unit.
But the enemy never let up.
I flew my guts out trying to get away.
My hands and feet went numb.
I could feel myself starting to black out.
I was sure I was going to die.
Then suddenly, everything around me turned white.
White?
Yeah. It was the strangest thing I'd ever seen.
The light was so pure, I figured I must be in heaven.
Then I realized I had just flown into a cloud.
! was so exhausted,
I couldn't hold onto the stick to fly my plane.
But the plane just kept on flying.
It flew by itself?
Yeah.
It was perfectly quiet, and the sky was beautiful.
Then I saw this strange band of white high above me.
Berlini! I thought you were dead!
Come back here! Where do you think you're going?
What about Gina? You can't
leave her alone. Let me go instead.
Hold on!
When I came to, I was skimming just above the sea,
all alone.
God was telling you it wasn't your time yet.
You think?
Seems to me he was telling me I was a
pig and maybe I deserved to be all alone.
You can't believe that. You're a good person.
No, the good guys were the ones who died.
Or maybe I'm dead and life as
a pig is the same thing as hell.
Now go to sleep.
That stupid kid, he sold me rusted cartridges.
I think you're a great human being, Porco.
And I'm glad you're still around.
Good night!
Hurry and place your bets. Don't miss out on the action.
The odds are eight to seven, Curtis
over Porco, that's eight to seven.
I've got two box seats left, two
seats. And three in the bleachers.
Come on, get your ice cream.
A hundred on the plane.
That's what we pledge?
Too many people here.
Bunch of morons. They're turning this into a big party.
Are all these people here air pirates?
No, you've got trash from all over the Mediterranean.
Gangsters, smugglers, gamblers.
Yeah, you might have a handful of
respectable people, but I doubt it.
Wow. Not only do I get a wife,
I'll be getting even more famous.
Ten minutes to start. Ten minutes to start.
Listen up!
This is a fight of honor between
Porco Rosso and Donald Curtis,
so if one of you fights dirty, you'll be
disrespected by seaplane pilots for eternity.
Off the stage, loud mouth. We
didn't come to hear a speech!
Pipe down!
Quiet down!
The next person I hear whining is dead meat.
Why not drop a bomb and really get some quiet?
This fight will decide the fate of
Miss Fio, who we all love and respect.
So keep your mouths shut! You got that?
If you do, clap your hands. Clap now!
Let's get started already.
Shut up, pig. We're following official procedures.
Now, both of you place your bets on these chairs.
Thank you.
Set it down, moron!
If both sides are satisfied,
you should shake hands or something like that.
Forget it. I like to keep my hands clean.
Fine, let's just get on with it.
We'll go to the church as soon as this is over.
Ah, don't worry, Fio.
According to my sweet mama, it isn't the love that counts.
Hey. Hey!
Miss Fio, can we take a picture with you?
We even took a bath.
Okay. Everybody ready?
Ready.
Cheese!
Smile!
Over-under, three minutes, with Curtis the favorite.
This is great.
We should get them to do this every month.
Fifteen seconds to start.
Wow. I've got chills.
Five seconds.
Four, three, two, one, go!
Go, go!
Curtis is up first.
It looks like this is going to be a one-sided fight.
Give me those.
Porco, what are you doing? Get some altitude!
He'll be eating bullets if he climbs up now.
He's being tricky.
It's harder for Curtis to hit
him if he's close to the water.
Aha! You're trying to make me
waste my bullets, aren't you??
Look at that. Porco gave him the Loop.
What's the Loop?
The Loop is what made Porco the ace of the Adriatic.
He's got me.
He's gonna shoot!
Look, he's not shooting.
What's wrong? Is his machine gun jammed?
I think I know what's going on here.
Porco won't shoot a pilot.
He'll only shoot the plane.
Look. There, he's in perfect position.
Come on! Shoot!
Nope, he's not going for it, just as I thought.
If the pig shoots now, he'll kill Curtis.
I bet he plans to tire Curtis out,
and then shoot his engine up instead.
What a show-off.
Porco.
Are you messing with me? Come on, shoot!
Ha! I bet your gun is jammed, isn't it?
Serves you right, pig!
They're coming towards us!
So you want to play games with me, is that it?
Don't kill us, kill each other!
Curtis pulled away from the pig!
Jump! Jump!
Hey, watch the money!
Amazing! The pig's leaving vapor trails.
Unbelievable.
I have never seen a dogfight like this in my life.
They sure are crazy.
Hey, the fight's going to be
over. What's taking her so long?
I don't know. She's in her room with the door shut.
Boy, I really don't want to miss this fight.
Is she coming or not?
Gina, Italians know about fight.
Get the pig out of there.
Ferrari.
Oh, Marco.
I hope I'm not too late.
I can't believe they can keep this up.
Looks like the pig's fading.
Go on, Porco, hang in there!
Must win.
I'm not handing Fio over to a jerk like you.
He's got Curtis's engine in sight.
It's over!
No, no! Don't jam now!
Gotcha.
Huh?
What?
It can't be jammed.
It's not jammed. You used up all your ammo, you idiot!
That's not good.
And no second gun, thanks to Fio's big butt.
I refuse to end this fight with a draw.
You stupid cowboy. There's no
way you can hit me with that.
Oh, yeah?
You think you can hit me from
there? Come on. Give me a break.
You think that's funny?
You're not even coming close. Throw something already.
You throw like a girl.
You don't even know anything about girls.
Shut up, pig!
What's going on up there?
Come on, Porco!
They're coming in!
Wait, you're a bet. The bets can't run off, Fio.
I go where the money goes.
Wail for me!
Why, you crazy pig!
Come and get it, cowboy!
Come on, put 'em up.
Fine with me, you weakling.
No!
Porco!
Get up, pig.
You're cheating!
Shut up!
Hick!
Come on, Porco. Block! Upper cut!
Hit him! Hit him!
Now we've got a boxing match.
The bets are still open!
Taking bets! Taking bets here!
Can't you fly this plane any faster?
Sorry, ma'am, but I'm afraid the engine will overheat.
Seaplane pilots are all idiots.
End of round five!
Hey, Fio. Did you see that left hook I threw?
I'm gonna finish you off in the next round.
This time, I'm sending you to dreamland, Curtis.
Get him, hit him, hit him!
I'll make prosciutto out of you!
Come on, you big womanizer.
You're the one that's a womanizer.
You fall in love with every woman you meet.
You're the one hogging all the girls.
Why don't you pick one? Gina or Fio?
What are you talking about?
You can't have both.
Gina says...
Don't you say "Gina," like you know her.
Gina says that she's been waiting for you.
For years now. She's been wanting to
meet you in that stupid garden of hers.
She loves you, pig.
Huh?
Porco!
The bell sounded before he went down.
Come on. That's a knockout, start counting!
Nope, the round is over. Back to your corner.
There they are. The Air Force hasn't arrived yet.
End of round six.
Round seven.
Gina does not want me, you liar.
I'm not lying. Why would I make that up?
So you want Gina?
You can't have Fio.
That's Gina's plane.
Hey, it's an emergency signal.
One. Two.
Whoever gets up first wins.
Four.
Excuse me, let me through, please.
Six.
Seven!
Gina! Wait!
Eight.
Marco. Marco, get up.
I don't wanna see you breaking
any more hearts, you hear me?
Nine!
Yay!
Porco!
The winner!
Porco, thank you!
Yeah. Piece of cake.
Now listen up, everybody.
The Italian Air Force is on its way here.
So anybody in trouble with the
Italian authorities better move on out.
Come to my place. Drinks are on the house.
Okay, gang, let's scram.
Mr. Curtis, the fight's over.
Hey, boss! Come on, hurry up!
I'm trying to be classy, you idiot.
You're a great seaplane engineer.
Keep it up, Miss Fio. Bye.
Thank you.
And keep up the bathing.
And I wanna say thanks to you, too, Mr. Curtis.
Next time, I'll propose to you formally and skip the bet.
Okay.
But I already know my answer.
Fio, you're going with Gina.
No! No!
I'm going with you. You said we were in this together.
Gina, take her to a respectable society, please.
You always do this, Marco. It's just not fair.
Sorry. Off you go.
Let's go.
Here come the Italian Air Force.
I'm going to draw them away from the others.
You wanna help?
Sure...
Hey! Your face! Wait! Wait up!
Turn around!
Get away from me.
Come on, let me see.
Porco flew rings around the Italian Air
Force, and they never caught up with him again.
I stayed with Gina for a while,
and we became good friends.
But soon, I decided it was time to go back to Milan.
Through the years, there have been a
few wars and a good deal of turmoil,
but my friendship with Gina has remained strong.
I am now president of the Piccolo Company,
and we're busy designing all sorts of radical new planes,
but I take time out every
summer to visit the Hotel Adriano.
The old pirate gangs still hang out at Gina's bar.
Mr. Curtis still writes to me sometimes, although
he has yet to become President of the United States.
He says he still fondly remembers
that summer in the Adriatic.
And as for how Gina's bet turned out,
well, that's our secret.