[Music]
The Seven Stars...
You're familiar
with them, correct?
If I'm not mistaken,
it's a group consisting
of several Shikabane.
Shikabane exist because of the
regrets and obsessions people
have as they die...
They stay here to act
on their desires, right?
But these Shikabane
decided to start a club?
Saki!
I understand that
this seems impossible.
Regardless of how
unlikely the case,
these Shikabane have
banned together.
Here's what we
know so far...
Each member has seven stars
carved into their skin...
Their plans don't
necessarily include
just killing
human beings...
They also have been known
to target other Shikabane
that cross their path.
I don't get it.
If they're not just
in it for the kill,
what else could they
be trying to do?
I don't know,
but we'll figure it out.
Make sure to give these
pictures to Keisei.
Yes, sir...
May I ask why?
Now is not the
time to explain...
He will understand
what needs to be done
once he receives them.
Kamika!
I'll just be
a moment, sir.
A few scriptures appear
to be unaccounted for.
See to it later.
Right now, the Seven Stars
pose a bigger threat
than missing scriptures.
There's Shuhou and Shujou
factions of the sect?
Yes.
These factions have been
created within the Kougon Sect.
The second in command,
the Gon Dai Sojo,
is part of the
Shujou faction.
He has an opposition
to the manner
in which Shikabane Hime
are implemented.
Does he really think
they stand a chance
without the help of their
indentured corpses?
He thinks they are capable of
creating a world without regret.
[Laughter]
Let me see if I'm
understanding this correctly...
The Shujou is about
to assume the lead.
With the Shuhou
losing control,
Shikabane Hime will
no longer be a threat?
Our focus should be on
targeting contracted monks
and their Shikabane Hime.
The Shuhou faction
will suffer.
You seem to have
done your homework...
Better than expected
of a traitor.
Being that you lost
your precious casket,
what else do you
have to offer us?
I can create
another casket.
We have one condition.
Not only do we know little
of your true intentions,
but you're a human...
We have no reason to
believe we can trust you.
What can I do?
You must prove yourself...
Convince us that you have
abandoned your trivial emotions.
What is this...?
This water drop?
Hands off!
You're not worthy...
To touch Hokuto
of the Seven Stars.
I'll show all of you
what a mere human can do...
All that remains of my
emotions is the desire
to annihilate
the Kougon Sect!
[Laughter]
He's here!
Let's go!
Ouri's here...!
Hurry up and hide it!
Oh, there
he is! Run!
So it looks like the kids
don't like me anymore.
Nothing could be further
from the truth, Ouri.
Yeah, right.
Did you think we'd
forget your birthday?
Oh... Yeah,
I see.
Incredible.
It's a zadan technique.
Being that I never
practiced it seriously...
I'm not sure if
this is any good.
You can get a pretty good
defense with Shikimi
and spirit threads.
Overall, the scriptures appear
to be woven in superb accuracy.
Looks good enough to
rival a Level 3...
Maybe even a Level 2
class Buddhist instrument.
Good to know.
Isn't the traitor monk's
casket pretty strong...?
Wouldn't it work
just as well as this?
Where did you find all
of these scriptures?
Please don't tell me you took
Sojo Takamine's scriptures!
I may have pilfered
through them the other day.
Senior! That place
holds scriptures,
some of which are
known to be priceless!
For the most part,
I selected them at random.
Just a few might be
considered national treasures.
I assume...
You're planning to use
this as a catalyst
for your zadan technique?
Actually... Can you hold
on to it for a while?
It's insurance...
Just in case.
Senior...
Saki...
Aragami.
Oh, great...
She's here.
I asked her
to come here...
I thought it was best if the
two of us saw them together.
Okay... Here's the medicine
for the spiritual trauma.
Take this one
before eating...
After meals...
And this one
before bed.
Great...
Thanks.
Takamine said you'd know
what to do with these.
Are you sure it's them?
Keisei... Are they
the next assignment?
Yeah... Probably.
So...
I've been waiting
for you, Seven Stars.
Still pretending you're
not getting involved?
I'm not... All I was
going to say is that
I remember seeing that
girl the other day.
You saw her...? Where?
At that Order of Eternal
Life Research place.
Why would you go
to such a place...?
It's a front for some
kind of religious cult.
I was just curious
about it...
I thought another religion
might have a way
to save people like you.
What are you talking about?
I know you could have
become a Shikabane...
Working as a Shikabane Hime was
the only alternative for you...
But that's just led you
down the path of despair.
Despair...?
Far from it...
This wasn't forced on me,
I asked to become
a Shikabane Hime.
You okay?
I think you're putting more
than enough meat in that...
Don't you?
Think I got this big and strong
by being a vegetarian...?
Meat is good...
And good for you.
What about
all those spices?
Why are you
using so many?
A long time ago, I got into
the habit of experimenting
with all kinds of
spices and seasonings.
Didn't really
have a choice.
Someone was very
picky about food.
Are you talking...
about me?
Now let me think.
I believe I've told you
that I was very young
when my parents died.
There were people who helped
me out during that time...
They were the head family,
the Hoshimuras.
Hoshimura?
Once I completed my training
at the head temple...
I left the
Hoshimuras' house.
After leaving...
I only went back there
every once in a while.
[Music]
I was soon sent to
the Sekuu Temple...
Where I met Riko
and her mother.
The temple...
And the Dai-Rin House were in
pretty terrible shape then.
Restorations...
Took quite a lot
of time and money.
Soon, you entered
into our lives.
For ten years,
it seemed as though everything
was how it should be.
That all changed
when I received news
that Shikabane murdered
the Hoshimura family.
The ones responsible were
a group of Shikabane.
We realized soon after that
it was the Seven Stars.
Are they the ones I saw
in the pictures earlier?
Keisei...
Old man... Why?
The daughter of Hoshimura
possesses the talent.
You're to become her
contracted monk immediately.
She's out of control.
Her experiences have left
her full of anger and hatred.
We have her restrained,
it's the only way to stop her
from becoming a Shikabane.
If we do not create
the contract now...
All that she was
will cease to exist.
Wait... I can't!
There's already a connection
between the two of you...
A contract with you
is the only way.
Makina, I...
Keisei... Please...!
Make a contract with me!
Do you completely
understand...
What becoming a
Shikabane Hime means?
I'll do anything...
Keisei, I need you
to fight by my side.
The monsters that
did this must pay...
Avenge my family and me!
Before, you told me that Makina
didn't become a Shikabane Hime
in order to earn
her way into heaven.
The Seven Stars aren't
your average Shikabane.
Try not to get
involved in this one.
But... You're involved.
I made her a promise...
To fight by her side.
I understand now,
Brother.
When I first found out,
I just wanted to stay mad at you
for keeping
such a big secret...
But that was before I really
knew about this world...
You know?
Yeah.
I know the Kougon
Sect killed Minai.
Trusting them is impossible...
But you're different.
You're still
the exact same person
I've known all these years
and I can trust you.
You told me monks are here
to protect the living...
And that their purpose isn't to
try and save those already dead.
Sorry.
Hearing that really
makes me happy.
Ouri... I'll make sure
you get a very special gift
for your birthday tomorrow.
A limited edition Zenbunose
Puchitoo life-sized figure!
Tomorrow.
Sorry, sir!
Here you go.
Thank you
so much, mister!
You're really sweet!
I'd say Ena is quite the
theatrical performer.
Once he reveals his true nature,
he's rather intolerable.
My god, Regardless, he
was able to create a bond
between himself and Ouri.
Now all we have to do
is wait for nightfall.
Yes.
Now... This
is going to be fun.
Keisei...
Keisei.
Everyone in the
area is asleep.
Doesn't that seem
a little odd?
Must be a
Shikabane's curse...
But you'd think
they'd realize
that it won't have an effect
on either one of us.
They do know.
It's a challenge,
they're calling us out.
Looks like they wanted
minimal distractions.
Job well done.
[Mew]
Crap!
What is it?
What do you
want from me?
Are those...
Bruises?
And to think that
Shikabane have the guts
to attack us directly.
It just shows you the
level of intelligence
we're working with.
The Seven Stars.
Or... The traitor monk.
Would the two of you like
to venture another guess...?
You're both so close.
The Incredible
Lotus Flower.
Is that the Hoshimuras'
little girl...?
How time flies.
You really do have a knack
for making foolish choices...
I see that your arms and
legs have grown back.
Remember how you begged and
pleaded for your life
with those bloody stumps?
It was so cute.
Seven Stars.
I am Kowaku!
Akasha...
Has your desperation really led
you to consort with Shikabane?
I would hardly call this
an act of desperation,
my dear old friend.
What's your purpose here?
To rid the world
of the Kougon Sect
and their pitiful
Shikabane Hime.
I figured I'd start off
with the two of you.
You and I grew up together,
we studied at the same temple...
We were friends.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
I'm a different
person now, Senior.
Our history doesn't
concern me in the least...
I may have walked
in your shadow then,
but that's all
in the past.
You hadn't even the
slightest indecision.
We are not
to seek death...
Nor are we to fear it.
That is the only way to save
the distraught masses.
You have become a great
contracted monk.
The two of you
should really think
about becoming
contracted monks also.
Having a powerful Shikabane
Hime to fight alongside
doesn't seem
like a bad idea.
The second the
opportunity comes around,
I'm going to make
a contract with one.
Making a contract is
serious business...
I don't think I have
the stomach for it.
Why is that?
It takes a lot to ask
these little girls to put
their lives on the line.
Besides... I'm better off
fighting alone for a while.
Perhaps someday...
I might be willing
to risk it.
I believed what you
said that day...
Deep down a part of me
felt you were right.
Which is why...
When I learned the truth...
I simply couldn't
accept it.
Accept what...?
The truth?
I must shed my last
threads of humanity.
My transformation will be
signified by your dying breath.
I shall be reborn...
I will subsist by
accepting death.
I find it very amusing
how much human beings rely
on conversation.
Your outfit...
You were a monk before
you became a Shikabane?
How perceptive...
That is how I know...
Monks are just humans
who want to play heroes...
But the thing is they
can't save anybody.
Admit it. You're trying to
rescue your damsel in distress.
All you're doing is taking
her from one hell to another.
Monks are nothing more
than cheap illusionists.
Though I'm sure you try
to convince yourselves
that you're
making a difference.
Do you ever shut up?
Just as I expected...
You haven't had the chance
to perfect this casket
as your catalyst.
He couldn't have captured
another hundred and eight
regrets so quickly.
If I use my zadan technique,
I should be able.
First thing you learn in battle
is to hide your weaknesses...
Fortunately, I'm familiar
with your Achilles heel.
Your reason for leaving
the safety of the building
and coming out into
the open is simple.
People that you made an oath
to protect lie asleep
within those walls.
What are you
waiting for? Go!
You may need me.
Don't worry about me.
I finally found
myself a decent fight.
You can't let
him get inside!
Looks like it's
just the two of us.
Die, Kowaku!
The barrier
is still intact.
I made it.
Ouri?
Brother... There's
something happening.
Yes... Never mind that...
why are you here?
You should
have fallen asleep.
Falling asleep...
isn't an option...
Tonight...
Just got
very interesting.
[Music]
The long night that
seems to go on forever...
The tears you thought had
dried up begin pouring out...
Go ahead and cry.
The dawn is still in
the distant future.