[Music]
What?! Mount Goryo?
Are you serious?
Yes. He told me he was
going up there to train.
But, wait, Ouri called you
and told you this, didn't he?
Well, yeah. He said that he
needed to do it to become a monk
or something like that.
Didn't make much sense
but he sounded serious
about quitting school.
And about you and him...
I was just wondering...
You serious about Ouri?
Uh, what?
When Makina
saved my life,
it was then that I learned about
the existence of Shikabane.
I never knew about
any of that before.
Since then I've been
thinking a lot about death.
I've always thought
that death seemed scary.
But after all
this time thinking,
I've decided that there is
also a certain sweetness to it.
I wonder what it is
I'm searching for.
I'm rescuing you...
Makina...
We're not buying it.
Why not? They did a better job
on this one than the last.
You never told me what
that call was about earlier.
They said that a Shikabane
of Keisei Tagami
has appeared
somewhere nearby.
Is that possible?
It certainly isn't
in this case...
The guy was immune to
the kind of obsessions
that would cause
that to happen.
Then we're not gonna
bother with it, right?
I mean we still have to deal
with the traitor monk business.
Not quite...
We'll see...
I mean this obviously
has something to do
with Makina
Hoshimura's curse.
I don't want to, but
I have to say it...
Don't you think this
would work out better
if we walked away and
let Makina die...?
Because if we let things stay
as they are now, Ouri will--
Let the living worry about
the living, Akira...
We have only
one job to do...
And that's to kill
what we have to kill.
[Gun firing]
Oh, that's not nice.
You keep firing
your little gun...
You might
actually kill me!
So, Takamasa...
Tell me how I'm any different
from your beloved Itsuki here?
Word through the grapevine
is that this lovely young
lady died in a car accident...
Did you?
Yes, I did.
See, we're the same...!
I died in a car crash.
Did you know that,
by any chance?
Oh, I knew.
Then tell me something...
Why does she get to be
a Shikabane Hime
while I'm just put down
like a rabid dog?!
Answer me, Takamasa!
You are just another
Shikabane to me.
You should've made me
a Shikabane Hime...
or, I guess, a
Shikabane Prince!
[Laughter]
We can only make girls
within a certain age range
into Shikabane Hime.
It's a limited technique that's
been passed down among us.
Nothing more.
Well, it's not fair...
It's not fair
and you know it!
You're a murderer...
You've killed people...
That's why you're
being judged here.
And you're running around
killing all the Shikabane...
Who's gonna judge
you for that?
I couldn't forgive them
when it happened to me.
And I held this
grudge against anyone
behind the wheel of a car.
I followed my feelings.
That's all I did.
I mean, that's what you would
call someone's 'nature', right?
Everyone has his own nature.
I just followed mine.
You monks live hiding
your true nature,
which makes me
more human than you.
You can't deny it!
So I will be the one who
casts judgment today!
It's presumptuous of me
to call it my nature.
But yes, I have it.
And I do hide this strong
desire deep inside.
I don't know how many times I've
wanted to listen to my heart...
To do exactly
what it says.
That's what he's
talking about...
It's his own desire.
But I know
I can't give in...
so I suppress it.
I know that my heart isn't
the all or end of me.
This is how people live.
We all carry on while
resisting our nature.
That's what it
means "to live".
That's the point
behind it all.
You let your nature conquer
you, and you're no longer human.
Itsuki, kill him!
How could you
do this to me?
Tomoharu...
One day
I'll apologize...
when I join you in
the world beyond this.
Well, Takamasa...
How'd I do?
Just fine... And
you're pretty, Itsuki...
very pretty.
This is the truth behind
the Shikabane Hime, Ouri...
Know it.
Tomoharu has been
inactive for 4 years.
Someone must have
instigated him,
brought him
into the open...
Was it the traitor monk...
If so, that means the Seven
Stars are on the move...
Woo-hoo!
Look, it's my favorite
little pervert!
Ouri, hi!
Flesh...
You got Itsuki in your sights
for a little booby grabbing?
[Laughter]
Looks like the situation
here is all wrapped up.
Good -
we found you...
I wanted to let you know that
Makina has been taken back
to the head temple!
Because of what's
happening with her curse?
Yeah, but...
Honda left a message that a
Shikabane resembling Keisei
had appeared and some
monks went missing.
Then I'm going back
to Mount Goryo.
I'll ride with you.
Ouri...
I don't know what's going on,
but Makina is a Shikabane Hime.
She isn't human.
Don't forget that.
Ever.
What's the matter, Makina?
Why are you running away?
Makina, come back
here, please....
Mother, I missed
you so much...
This ecstasy
is unreal...
Inspectors...?!
What is this?
Happiness...
Right now they're
all experiencing
their greatest happiness.
They get to experience
this emotion, relive it,
and then they die
when it peaks.
There's someone I know
who just adores the power of
release these people experience
during such moments.
Death is the
greatest happiness.
And I want to relive that
happiness as much as I can.
Don't worry, Makina...
That's not the one you
have to worry about.
Your opponent
out here... is me.
Makina,
what's wrong?
You're not Keisei.
Not true.
Of course, I'm Keisei...
I'm Keisei's
Shikabane.
Don't you recognize that?
You're a liar!
I understand.
You can't shoot me.
You're not Keisei.
Do you want to know why I became
a Shikabane after I died...?
I know you do,
Makina.
It was my regrets...
My deep obsessions...
The desire
to see you...
You heard me
right, Makina...
I'm in love with you.
Don't come near me!
You're not him...
How beautiful it is...
something so strong
falling apart so swiftly.
Simply exquisite...
Makina... You can
always change, too.
Hey...
This fella's not
gonna be of any help.
Ouri...
Sadahiro... Akira...
Hey Rika...
This is them right?
What are you
two doing here?
You're Sadahiro Mibu.
Tagami and you contracted
at the same time...
But I heard that you had
left this all behind you
and returned
to secular life.
Then I'd appreciate you
keeping it that way.
I know Makina's gotta be
around here somewhere...
And I heard there was a
Shikabane of Brother...
No, he'd never
become a Shikabane.
But how do you know that?!
Listen to me, kid.
You just need to get out
of here...
Walk away. Forget everything
you've ever heard
about Makina Hoshimura
or the Kougon Sect.
Forget all of this
insanity you've seen...
It's not too late for you
to live an ordinary life.
That's impossible! I can't
forget the things I've seen!
Listen, you idiot! I don't give
a crap if you think you can't.
Just do it!
People live their entire lives
by focusing on one or two things
to motivate them...!
So just try to be happy
and live like that!
Worst advice
I've ever heard.
Go, Ouri.
You have to go now...
You can get
through to Makina.
I know you can
if you hurry!
Well, you're still her
contracted monk, aren't you?!
I have the feeling
you're misunderstanding
this situation, lady.
My name is Rika Aragami.
The granddaughter of
Aragami's old lady...
That certainly makes
this interesting.
[Gun firing]
Sojo Takamine believes that
some of the Inspectors
including Honda are taking
questionable action
under Gon-Dai-Sojo
Shiou's orders.
Gon-Dai-Sojo is trying to
eliminate the Shikabane Hime
in an attempt to retain
power for himself...
But he's keeping
one in particular
on a very tight leash.
As well as her contracted monk,
and not to kill Shikabane,
but to kill people!
You probably won't believe
me when I tell you...
but the only reason I'm here is
to kill the Shikabane of Keisei.
Look at that...
A pretty red balloon!
Don't touch that thing!
Uh, what?
Hold on!
This is one of the
Seven Stars' curses.
It grows as
it possesses humans
and collects
their happy feelings.
Akira...
we're leaving.
Saki!
Ouri, it's you!
Makina!
Where are you?!
Hey! Makina!
Where are you?
Stop all this nonsense.
Come on out of your
little hiding place!
I'll make you beautiful...
Like you've never known...
It's not Keisei...
Makina!
Come out!
It's not Keisei...
There you are...
And such an obvious place.
No...
I love you, Makina...
I always have...
I love you so much.
Please no, Keisei...
You son of a bitch...
You think I'll let you get
between me and my Makina...?
Don't stand there and
pretend to be my brother!
You alright?
Don't hurt him...
What are you
talking about...?!
Keisei would never
talk like that
and he'd certainly
never try to kill you.
This guy's probably just
one of the Seven Stars
who's pretending
to be Brother...
Don't you think
I know that?!
It doesn't matter to me.
I still can't hurt him...
I just can't...
I won't...
I can change.
I can...
I will continue
to grow more beautiful...
Now what do you fellas say we
get back to the task at hand?
Makina, stand up.
We should leave.
So you, uh...
You still consider yourself
to be my contracted monk?
I do.
Okay... And I assume this is
what you want out of life...
But I wonder if you still
do after I tell you this...
When Keisei was dying...
In those horrible moments
after he passed the bond to you
and you lost
consciousness...
He said something to me.
Please, please don't cry...
I want to see you smile.
In those fleeting seconds
I realized that
this was Keisei's regret.
I feared that
if I didn't smile,
the fact would twist
into his obsession;
that he'd
become a Shikabane.
So I smiled at him.
I gave him what he wanted...
I did what I had to do...
I wanted to keep Keisei
from becoming a Shikabane,
so I kept him
from living on.
In the end the one who
really killed Keisei was me!
It's okay...
because you wanted
to do it for him.
You loved him
that much...
Enough to send him
down the path he wanted.
I understand...
more than you know.
Maybe it's true...
Actually I know
it to be true.
I loved Keisei
so very much...
And I love him
even more now...
That's the one reason
that I couldn't accept the
contract with you, Ouri.
I know that
I killed Keisei...
but to forget about him
and move on to a new
contracted monk isn't in me...
I couldn't forgive
myself for that.
You don't have
to forget him.
If he's going
to live on...
then you and I...
Have to stay true to the memory
of his life, not his death...
A person's heart isn't the all
or end of who they are, Makina.
That may be true for people,
Ouri - but not for me.
Makes sense I guess...
I am a Shikabane.
You can keep
the bond with Brother
even while you're
contracted with me.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll hide your heart.
Sorry, kid, but
that's not possible.
Sadahiro...
Sadahiro... Didn't he
and Keisei know each other?
Unless she breaks the
bond with Keisei...
the stagnated Rune will
always remain within her.
Her regrets towards Keisei
will become a curse...
and that will
make you suffer.
Contracting with a cursed
Shikabane Hime is impossible.
It's not a curse, Akira.
And how's that?
It's just a tie between
Brother and Makina.
I won't let anyone
call it a curse.
Then what are you
going to do, Ouri?!
I'm telling you
it's not a curse.
It's their power!
Brother, Makina, and myself
all have these powers...
We put all of that together and
we can defeat the Seven Stars!
That's just how
I feel about it.
Hey, Makina,
where are you?!
Come on out!
He really does
a terrible Keisei.
That injury...
it should've killed him.
He's switched
bodies again.
The bastard's name is
Ena of the Seven Stars...
He has a curse that
allows him to switch
from one Shikabane's body
to another at his own will.
By doing this, he thinks
that he's achieving
some kind of beautiful
evolution.
No, you can't
take him on!
I know
I can do it...
I've stabbed
Brother once before.
I can do it again.
You were being
manipulated before!
That was
Ena's power then!
Every time I think of it,
it makes me want to throw up.
It'll be the same
even if it's a Shikabane
with Brother's face...
no one is going to have
to feel the things
that I'm forced to feel...
Makina and Sadahiro don't
have to know anything...
This is my burden
alone to bear.
Is that really
the case...?
I had no idea this face
meant so much to you...
Why don't I show you
a few more of them?
How about this...?
Which Brother do you
like the most, Ouri?
[Music]
In this world, there is
a certain kind of ecstasy
that can only be gained by
making some else miserable.
Everyone is possessed by
a "Monster Named Happiness."