[Music]
I loved Keisei
so very much,
and I love him
even more now.
What's the matter?
Don't worry about it.
Nozomi...
Uh... What are
you doing?
Say, Ouri...
Will you kill me...
please?
Please, Ouri...
Nozomi, stop this!
What are you saying?!
That you...
That you're the only one who
can help me find my happiness!
You're talking like
some kind of crazy person!
I just want
to be happy!
Your eyes aren't
playing tricks on you.
You again!
Ouri!
Quit fooling around.
Open your eyes.
A balloon!
You mean
you can see it?
Beautiful, huh...?
But it's more than
just a balloon...
This is my
happiness, Ouri.
Huh?
As I get happier,
it gets bigger and bigger.
Soon it will bring the
ultimate happiness - my death.
That's what you want?
Death?
Oh, yes...
it's my dream...!
I've been waiting
my whole life
to feel this
kind of ecstasy.
Nozomi...
Why did you do that?
I don't know what's
going on here...
but I know you need to get
your crap together...!
Nozomi!
Stay away from me.
I'm not kidding around,
what's wrong with you...?
You've been acting
so weird...
The whole school
is talking!
What?
I just...
I just want to be happy,
that's all.
Nozomi...
You're not hurt,
are you?
From the moment
you left town,
it seems like everything
she's done has been about you.
Are you still talking
about that...?
Inuhiko, there is nothing
between Nozomi and me...
I know this is a difficult
concept for you...
but you don't need a
reason to love someone.
Even if the...
The person you love...
Doesn't love you back.
I don't expect you
to understand.
It's just something that...
... that you can't help.
Believe me,
I understand...
I really do.
Ouri... don't disappear
on us like that ever again.
[Phone ringing]
Anything?
No answer...
I guess his...
phone's off.
What about the inspectors who
were supposed to be going over
to the high school?
We haven't been able
to reach them, either.
Something isn't right,
what should we do?
Shirae would be in charge,
but he's in the hospital.
[Dialing phone]
Hello, Makina?
Yes...
Seven Stars...
I saw another one of them.
He's a balloon creature...
I think his name is Toya...
But whoever he is,
I know I have to stop him.
Get to the school as quickly
as you can and let me know
what's happening there.
Itsuki and I are just about
to head over that way now.
No... there's still
a possibility
that this is
just a decoy.
Please, Guardian... you must
stay and guard the head temple.
But going by yourself is-...
Makina just
can't help herself
when it comes to dealing
with the Seven Stars.
If only Ouri was there...
He might have been able
to talk her out of going
to the school all alone.
That's it!
I'm going to the school!
Wait.
Makina is right.
Having lost two
of their members,
there's a very
real possibility
that the Seven Stars could
launch a full-scale attack.
Guardian Sougi...
it's imperative
that you and Itsuki stay
in the temple for now.
All right.
But then Ouri and Makina
will be left on their own!
None of us know what
this Toya is capable of.
We can't afford to
send out any more people
until we have a better idea
of what we're fighting against.
Senior... please give your
protection to Ouri and Makina.
What are you doing?
Hazama!
I'd advise you not to get
too close to Hokuto...
If she happens to take
an interest in you...
she will kill you.
I'm aware of that...
In order to understand someone,
she has to destroy them...
It's all she's capable of.
It's the way...
that she herself met
with her own destruction.
The Scripture on
Shikabane Hime laws -
did you find
it interesting?
The pieces of the puzzle are
starting to make sense...
You attacked the Hoshimuras in
order to steal the scripture...
You wanted to learn
about Shikabane Hime.
I have no reason
to deny it.
We needed that Scripture
so we could better
understand Shikabane Hime.
But there was another,
more important reason...
Creating a Shikabane out of
Makina Hoshimura, correct?
We needed a Shikabane...
to be Hokuto's enemy.
We needed a reason for her to
want to crush the Kougon Sect.
It hurts... it hurts...
it hurts...
it hurts... it hurts!
Hokuto has no obsessions.
Nor any regrets.
The child is simply what
she is: a pure Shikabane...
... which makes her perfect to
be the symbol for our crusade.
And it is your intention
to use this symbol
to annihilate
the Kougon Sect.
Is that not
your goal as well?
Well, the boy is gone.
I turned my back for a moment
and he just disappeared.
You mean Hizuchi?
He's always been hopeless.
I must agree.
He certainly doesn't like
Toya's way of doing things.
Just let the boy be.
He can no more fight his own
nature than the rest of us can.
How can you be so
relaxed about this?!
That's not your concern.
You just focus on
deciphering that Scripture.
That girl...
that's Nozomi Kasuga.
Makina, it's you!
You really shouldn't go
into the school right now.
There's something bad
going on inside there.
There's nothing bad...
It's just that everyone
is becoming happy.
Nozomi, do you know
something?
I know this... I've always
admired you, Makina...
That's a very
foolish thing to say.
... and when I asked
myself why...
the answer was
you were so beautiful...
Then I thought...
well of course...
of course
she's beautiful...
She's already dead, she's
eternal, how could she not be?
I realized then that's why
Ouri was attracted to you.
Ouri...? What does he...
have to do with any of this?
But that's alright.
Soon, I'll be dead too.
I'll be eternal!
Just like you!
Now watch!
How is it...?
Don't you feel happy?
The balloon takes your
happiness and swallows it
and just gets
bigger and bigger.
Just you wait...
Makina!
Are you all right?!
That...
that girl there.
You have to hurry
and catch her.
She wants to be...
a Shikabane.
The Seven Stars have
been using her...
But what about you?
Go! Hurry!
She wants you,
she's waiting for you.
Why do you struggle
like that?
You're so close to
being truly happy.
[Music]
You eat the
happiness of others...
I get it now!
That's not very nice.
Now what?
[Laughter]
Wonderful!
That was perfect!
Everyone died happy!
You bastard!
It's all right.
It was just a matter
of time, anyway.
Because once the monster called
"happiness" starts to grow,
it eats and eats and eats
until there's nothing left.
And you call
that happiness?!
Of course.
What could be better than
being allowed to die
at the very peak
of one's happiness?
What's so great...
about being murdered?
You've started feeling
happy, haven't you?
As you keep feeling
happier and happier,
so too will it grow...
the monster within.
Nozomi, stop!
[Laughter]
Nozomi, please!
Snap out of it!
You're just being
used by a Shikabane!
I'm happy!
So happy...
Ouri. I'm going
to be a Shikabane Hime.
What?!
I'm going to die and
become a Shikabane Hime,
just like Makina.
Then I'll be able to
be with you forever!
You don't know
what you're saying!.
Stop talking like that!
Forever, you and me.
I have had enough!!!
Ushi!. Sumi...!
What did you
do to them?!
They just want
happiness too, Ouri...
the same as me.
Are you insane?
It's not happiness you're
talking about, it's death!!
No, please!!
Nozomi...
If the balloon
breaks...
I'll die.
Nozomi, you've got
to snap out of it!
Ouri...?
What did you say...?
I can't think...
I don't know what
just happened.
But I'm happy...
I'm so happy because you're
here with me right now.
So...
so...
Oh, Ouri...
I want to stay
like this.
I don't want
to die, yet!
I'm not ready to die!
Oh! What's the matter?
And we were having
so much fun...
Stop!
I'm not finished
with you!
Oh no, what a shame!
It would have gotten
so much bigger!
Well, it's still big enough
to devour you, I suppose...
That's right.
When you were little,
you could just play
and not have to worry
about anything.
That's the kind of happiness
you're looking for, right?
You want to go back to that
simpler time, don't you?
You want to know
the truth?
It's possible...
that I might feel
happiness again...
Oh yes... once you and
your pals are all dead!
I think you stayed a little
too long at the fair!
What are you?
Lady... is happiness
the same thing as death?
I don't...
Understand.
I heard she came from
a poor lower-class family.
In her whole life she never
even had one decent meal.
Then one morning her
parents suddenly decided
they'd all go to an
amusement park for the day.
Daddy! Mommy!
[Laughter]
Hurry up, Mommy!
C'mon, Daddy!
Over this way!
We rode all the rides and
ate all the delicious food.
We had so much fun!
That was the first time I ever
played with my Mommy and Daddy
all day long!
I was so happy!
I thought that's what
happiness was: having fun!
I wanted it to never stop,
so I've been having more
fun ever since then.
It's my happiness.
And then, in the happiest
moment of her life,
her parents poisoned her
and themselves...
She still doesn't have
any idea she's dead.
That's why,
to her child's mind...
happiness and death are
exactly the same thing.
That's insane...
Death isn't happiness!
Insane, huh?
You died and became
a Shikabane Hime...
how else would you have
been able to fight us?
Isn't that happiness?
No, it isn't!
Surely you must know, deep
down in your heart of hearts...
that for most of us
there can be no higher form
of happiness than dying.
Hazama wants her, right?
Take her with you, Toya.
I have to go now...
I have business to finish.
[Crying]
I thought that you'd
want me to be with you...
if I could just become
a Shikabane Hime.
I thought
you'd look at me...
the way you
look at Makina.
Oh God...!
What have I...
I want to be alive
with you, not dead!
How could I have
been so stupid?!
Is that what...
my happiness looks like?
Nozomi,
we have to run!
Come on!
Brother, please
help me one more time!
Zadan technque!
Zadan technique,
you say?
You really think the gods
would allow you
to create a miracle
like that?
It's not possible...
You are the child
of a Shikabane.
Quiet, you.
This boy belongs to me!
Time to go now.
Nozomi!
Nozomoi! It's gonna be
all right now!
That balloon was her
happiness in physical form.
It was her second self.
Once it's disappeared, she
has nothing left to live for.
Nozomi!
Nozomi!!
Ouri, I...
please...
I want...
to be a...
a Shikabane Hime so...
So that we...
[Music]
You're beginning
to remember now,
aren't you...?
The Shikabane of your
dearly departed brothers.
Is it despair or joy
inside your scream...?
"My Mother Was Defiled."