[Music]
What is this place?
You wanted to talk
to me in person.
I figured it'd be a little
too much of a problem
for both of us if we were
seen near the head temple.
Don't you think?
There's a Shikabane Hime
that I need you to evaluate.
Now why would you be concerned
about one of them?
It's the daughter
of Hoshimura.
You mean Keisei's
Shikabane Hime...
I heard word that she's ill.
Those in the Shuhou
faction, like Takamine,
are all against
getting rid of her.
Is this your way of saying you
want us to take care of her?
After your evaluation,
if you see no chance
of rehabilitation,
well...
I wouldn't say that
he expresses it exactly,
but you know, he loves you
ladies more than anyone else
on this planet.
Yeah, so much he
wants to kill us.
You can't do this!
Why are you stopping us?
Akasha, you're the one who
wished that we, the Seven Stars,
establish the Kougon
Sect as our enemy.
Right, and for
that purpose,
we've spent the last 6 months
killing contracted monks.
But why now are you just
going to suddenly attack
the head temple?
Out of our way, tiny man.
If we don't hurry,
our toys will die.
We're just going so we can
examine that one Shikabane Hime.
Examine her...
You mean Keisei's
Shikabane Hime?
Have you forgotten...?
We are the ones who made
the Shikabane Hime
known as Makina Hoshimura.
I have sensed that her
life is about to end.
And it won't be fun for us if
she dies in her current state.
Are you saying
that Makina is
some kind of special
Shikabane Hime?
That's precisely
what I want to check.
Hokuto...
Those drops...
You're always producing
that kind of water...
Water...
Hokuto,
don't do that...
Please...
Oh, look. A bug.
What was that about?!
To Hokuto, everything about the
world you live in is abnormal...
See, her life was
ended before she ever
had the opportunity
to commit sin.
It's like she
was born to die.
To her, everything from this
world that touches her
is like a serrated blade
reaching to inflict pain.
You mean, she's never even
held hands with anyone?
She has an uncontrollable
power that breaks
the boundaries of the bond
with her contracted monk.
Any Shikabane Hime
possessed by that curse
needs to be purified before
she turns into a Shikabane.
Normally, something like that
shouldn't even take a month.
And seeing as we are
into the sixth month
of dealing with this,
Gon-Dai-Sojo is talking
about getting rid of her.
If we can avoid
killing her,
personally,
I would prefer that.
It's not right that
she's been stuck
in that purification
chamber for 6 months!
But the fact remains the curse
upon the Shikabane Hime
has yet to be removed.
I'm a doctor,
if you couldn't tell.
I need to examine her.
A Gon-Sojo should not
enter a place like this.
Who are you, pal?
The name I am known
by is Kurai...
I am an Inspector
for this region.
His Grace Gon-Dai-Sojo put
me in charge of this case.
Saki!
What are you doing
with that thing?
I know just what that mark
on your face means,
so you should also know
if you get involved
with Shikabane Hime,
your Enlightenment gets
that much further away.
So... what is
Heaven like?
What do you mean?
It's not that I'm
that interested.
But the other Shikabane Hime
are all doing what we do in
order to get into Heaven, right?
Yeah, that's what
it seems like.
The paradise or Heaven
we refer to is not a place
but rather when one becomes
unified with everything
by attaining Enlightenment,
thereby arriving at a world
with no grief or worry.
We as monks have
to perform virtuous deeds.
You, on the other hand...
A Shikabane Hime can't
attain this Enlightenment
until she destroys
108 Shikabane.
That's right...
But if Enlightment
requires us to leave
behind family
and friends,
the people we really care
about, then if you ask me
it would seem to make the
whole ordeal rather sad.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah...
Rika...
Rika, look down there!
I can't believe
the Shiryou gained entrance
to the head temple!
Shiryou is the form taken by
those who couldn't even attain
the level of regrets that
a Shikabane has, right?
They're eating whatever that
stuff is that's coming out
of Makina's body!
We have to do something
about this, Saki.
This black ink...
I've heard that this stuff is
supposed to weaken our power...
This'll be a tough fight!
The Shiryou are trying
to take on physical form!
Hold on, Saki!
Kamika...
Those Shiryou are
feasting on the Rune
that's leaking
from Makina's body.
This is all we can do.
Isn't Rune
in the Shikabane Hime
like the blood that
circulates in our bodies?
But it's giving power to the
Shiryou when they eat it.
Just sounds weird.
Rune is life energy,
which is purity itself.
It's provided to the Shikabane
Hime by a contracted monk.
But no matter how
pure something is--
if it stagnates,
it will begin to rot.
The problem we're dealing with
now is that rotting old Rune
is an invitation for Shiryou.
Meaning that it's
Keisei's Rune...
that's coursing through her.
Makina has strong regrets
regarding what happened
to her contracted monk...
Whether or not she knows it,
she's storing his Rune
and allowing it
to rot inside of her.
But she's got a new
contracted monk now.
If she received Ouri's Rune,
she would be fine.
The boy hasn't received
enough proper training
in these matters yet.
But, more importantly,
it doesn't matter
who the contracted monk is,
if Makina doesn't want
to accept his Rune,
this will end the same.
Then what are
we going to do?
If this continues, her own
Rune will be devoured...
and she will die.
Oh, I see now!
This is serious!
Who goes there?!
Sir?
Don't bother with it.
That's not our enemy.
Umehara...
Oh my goodness!
I dropped my specially-made
master detective coat
and hat back there...
I can't live the life of
a detective like this!
So he still
isn't back yet?
Oh... no...
It's been six months,
hasn't it?
What's this here?
Wait a minute!
Looks pretty tasty...
You know you could make good
money if you tried selling
a few of these to Ushijima.
Just kidding...
But you know, I didn't
have the slightest clue
that you were
so serious about Ouri.
Well, I just know
him a little.
We've talked
here and there.
That's all...
I mean, the
only thing I know
is that he took
a trip out of the town
shortly after his
brother passed away.
Seriously,
what an idiot.
The dreams he could be
realizing with Ms. Boobs McGoo
if he was just here now.
What dreams...?
And who on earth
is this Boobs McGoo?
You mean
you don't know...?
Ouri may look like
this innocent teenage boy,
but all he wants to do is
fondle girl's big ol' breasts!
Nooooo!
You don't have to hate
me as much as you do.
Would you just
get over here?
How's it been going?
Oh boy...
what a sad face.
I haven't had any luck...
Master Umehara says
that if I track the rabbit
by using the bond
tied between it and me,
then catching him
will come to me easily,
but I don't know...
Master may appear
the way he appears,
but don't let
that deceive you.
His warrior skills are tops
among all monks of our sect.
Tell me, Takamasa, in what
way do I appear exactly?
Why don't you take a
look at yourself, Master?
I found these on the ground.
Someone must've dropped 'em.
Pervy perverts!
Bet they're wandering
around here somewhere...
This is Mt. Goryo.
Even monkeys
don't come here.
He's such
a hopeless adult.
Reminds me of someone
I used to know.
Now... Try this again.
Tell me, what is a bond?
A connection that ties
one person to another...
I was thinking maybe
it's something like fate?
Sure, fate is a good
way of labeling it--
a connection divined
by the stars in the Heavens...
But the word 'bond' should
give you the feeling
of something more tangible...
Your hands.
Now a bond has been formed
between you and the rabbit.
All you have to do now is find
the light the bond shows...
Go ahead.
I'd like to find it, but
I don't see anything.
Just go.
Okay.
I wonder if it's
difficult for him...
he's been at this
6 months now.
Light is not the easiest thing
in the world to seek out
if you don't know
what you're doing.
That boy has been
so blessed in his life
that he's never had to seek
out the light on his own.
That's all this is.
Nooo!
Oh, not again.
I'm so sorry!
And here I was thinking
that young Japanese boys
are all shut-ins and only
interested in the 2-D universe,
but you're actually a fairly
aggressive pervert, huh?
I'm not!
Too bad for you, perv!
'Cause the only thing I'm
interested in is 2-D stuff, too.
I mean, check out all the
killer books I picked up today!
I had my suspicions that
the city bookstores
would have all the coolest
stuff and I was right!
Coolest stuff!
Yeah...!
Isn't it exciting?
There's the
moe-moe dojinshi,
"Zenbunose Puchitto" Summer
Festival limited editions!
You don't have to explain it
to me, Ms. Half Naked Chick!
I'm not half-naked,
and my name is Flesh,
if you don't mind, Mr. Plum!
You don't like "half-naked?"
Fine, then your name is Mud!
You got that? Mud!
I gave you money to buy
the Zenbunose figure,
Kinky version,
limited edition!
And you show back up here
with these filthy things!
Look, commercialism just simply
ruins any official products.
The real fans out there only
love the dojinshi magazines.
There's no redeeming
qualities to any of that smut!
I'll have
to confiscate them!
No!
They're my special friends for
tonight, thank you very much!
Special friends...
Seriously, I never should've
even considered contracting
with someone who died
in a plane accident
while she was on her
way to Akihabara...
If you keep acting mean to
me, then I'm gonna tell Touma.
Touma?!
Wait, please!
Not that!
Anything but that...!
Please?
Oh, Touma.
She's Master Umehara's
Shikabane Hime...
She's just taking
herself a little break.
Is she a scary person?
"Scary" might not
be the right word...
Then again...
I didn't know
a monk could contract
with two Shikabane Hime.
Contracting with two means
he has to give out twice
as much Rune.
Normally, a monk's
body can't handle that.
But Master can do it.
Which just indicates how
much training he puts himself
through regularly.
Probably a good thing
that I only have Makina,
considering how forcibly my
Rune was absorbed from me.
That's because of the curse.
Have you heard any word
on how she's doing?
If something happens to her,
if her condition changes,
then you should feel it.
You're her contracted monk.
Are you sure?
I can't even see the
bond with a dumb rabbit.
I knew Ouri had some kind
of feelings for her...
Noooo!
Sorry, Master, but Itsuki is
my Shikabane Hime, not yours.
And I'm gonna tell Touma.
I came here to tell you
guys something important.
Give me a break.
Sounds like another
load of crap to me.
Actually, it's true.
It's about Makina.
What...? You've
got news on her?
Yeah, but your going there might
not make much of a difference.
That said, would you
like to go see her?
Intruder!
Get him!
Traitor monk!
I'll see you
again someday.
Perhaps in the
land of the dead.
Don't move!
What do you think
you're doing,
bringing in that
defiled thing?!
You've got something here
that's defiled, too,
don't you, Sadahiro?
Shikabane can't normally
enter the head temple,
but by using your zadan, you
can certainly lead them here...
I guess it's true that you've
decided to join hands
with the Seven Stars.
Sadahiro,
you talk too much!
I guess you
know everything.
Why do it?!
"Why"?
Hazama...
of the Seven...
He's the one who killed
your Shikabane Hime!
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but Hazama didn't kill her...
I did it.
You what?
Get your damn
hands off of me!
Shikabane Hime...
They're defiled...!
Unforgivable--
You bastard!
He's after Makina!
To think he became
a Shikabane...
It would seem the Kougon
Sect's monks are lacking
Enlightenment...
Time to invite the Seven
Stars to the party...
Hope they're ready.
'Kay... It's here.
From monk
to Shikabane...
Shikabane Hime...
You defiled
Shikabane Hime!
That's it...
That's the regret
you carried away...
Leave her alone,
you bastard!
Makina!
Ouri...
He's a Kougon Sect monk!
Why would a monk bust
in here to attack you?
Because she is defiled.
But the Kougon Sect are
the ones who created her
and everyone like her!
They were made
to fight the Shikabane
and save people's lives!
They are defiled!
And if we stay
in contact with them,
we will become
defiled, as well!
And then I will never
attain Enlightenment!
But I won't
let that happen...
I will not
become defiled!
Trying to kill Makina because
you don't wanna become defiled.
What's wrong with you?
You're the filthy
one and you know it!
Listen, Makina...
They said...
They said that you
refuse to let Brother go.
Forget it!
For now, just right now,
take my Rune--
do whatever
you have to do!
If you don't,
you'll die!
But, Ouri,
I'm already dead!
Don't come near me!
The Shiryou
will attack you
if you don't stop
right where you are!
This is it...
I finally
see the light.
Ever since he died, the
two of us have been lost...
No one could forget someone
who was precious to them.
And when you don't,
it turns into regrets.
If remembering is the thing
that makes me defiled,
then I guess
that's what I am...
'Cause we're the same.
Makina,
are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't
protect Keisei.
I've been waiting
all this time...
Just to say that.
[Music]
Your arms and legs
were torn off
and still you
couldn't die.
On that day,
you cried
and begged for forgiveness
in a sea of blood.
Welcome, "my enemy."
Now, let us
kill each other.