Hmm...
Just what I thought.
This is far from
a healthy boy's room.
Makina...
Morning,
Brother...
Whoa!
What are you doing?!
Nothing! An older brother came
to check on his little bro',
that's all!
What's wrong
with that, uh?
What the hell is this?!
Hey now, settle down...
hear me out!
Consider this the friendly
kick-in-the-pants
I know you could use.
Feast your eyes:
"Moe Warrior
ZENBUNOSE Puchi-tto";
all incredibly rare,
limited edition memorabilia
that you can't
find anywhere!
Then you put 'em up
in your own room!
Get outta here!
Oh! You want
some privacy?
Say no more!
I understand, my man.
You want to me to go so you can
enjoy them all by yourself!
I'll kick your ass!!!
Hey, Ouri...
What?
Have you noticed
anything... unusual?
No, not really, why?
Well, I...
Um...
Actually you've been
showing up with wounds
in strange places, lately.
You say you fell from
your motorcycle, but...
I'll be careful.
And Ouri, you should
be careful too...
Lotion's in the basket!!
Your ass is grass, Keisei!
And don't come back!
Later, Ouri!
♪ If you just
can't go on...
♪ Please give your life
to mewhen you are gone,
♪ I will care for it,
♪ Hold it close to my heart.
♪ All for you.
Another one...
She didn't listen
to my song.
She loved your song!
But she was working, so--
Are you saying her job was
more important than my song?
Tell me this, then.
Is your job more important
than falling in love
with my music?
Well...?
Uh...
of course not!
It's impossible for anyone
to hold back tears...
when listening to the
beautiful voice of an angel!
That's what I thought.
♪ Shikabane all but dust,
♪ A shell of white rust.
Sorry to make
you come up here.
Well, she's certainly
to be commended...
There are many women who
might work until they die...
... but precious few who'd work
after they're already dead.
So tell me, can she
handle a comeback?
She says she's going
to sing no matter what.
Well, this isn't Tokyo.
If anything happens, you
know we'll take care of it.
Okay.
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
Who is this?!
And how in the hell did
you get this number?
It's about Kun.
She's being targeted.
What're you talking about?
Is this her stalker?
By a Shikabane Hime,
hell-bent on killing
immortal corpses.
Shikabane Hime?
What the hell is
a Shikabane Hime?
Tell me who you are,
you son of a--
[Disconnect tone]
Is this all
you could find?
Basically.
It's everything they had
from the past ten years or so.
Peppermint?!
What the hell!
What's this...?
Is the little boy whining
about being able
to use my library?
The library belongs
to the students!
No, the library belongs
to the StuCo president.
Just what are
you looking for?
Information about a fire
that supposedly killed
a family named Hoshimura.
A fire?
That's a tough one because
those don't always make it
in the newspaper, right?
Well, I'm just
following a hunch.
♪ "If you want to die..."
Kun-chan's hot!
Loser alert.
OURI.
Still going to
tonight's show with me?
Oh. About that...
I've got it all
planned out!
She's going to make
eye contact with me
and know she's in love!
Now first, we find out
where her dressing room is.
If she's not there...
I'm not going, Ushi.
Huh?
Shoot.
I so did not want
to go with my sister.
"Shikabane, uh uh uh..."
Hey, hey...
What now?
I know what this is about.
This has to do with
some girl, doesn't it?
No way. What?
Ok, then.
Explain why you're so touchy
whenever I ask you about it.
It's just, you know...
that name, Hoshimura...
I remember it...
Hello...
What?
Hoshimura?
I'll be right back.
That's when it started.
When Brother would come home
all bruised and beaten.
You should get a life.
How much of that
did you hear?
I notice those perverted
Anime posters are finally gone.
Yeah, I took the girls
away to a safer,
more loving place where
they can be appreciated
in the way they deserve.
Unlike this place,
where they keep getting
thrown in the garbage.
You expect me to have a
serious talk with that trash
staring back at me?
Can we talk?
Kun Osaki.
Princess of pop, her new
album's already number one.
However...
Kun Osaki is dead.
There were rumors
of her frailty.
That she'd fainted in the
studio recording her album.
Her publicist assured everyone
she was merely exhausted...
... but it was more
serious than that.
But, how could they have
covered up the death
of someone so famous?
In the world
of show business,
just about everybody's
connected to the underworld.
She's no different.
But I suspect
her manager's the one
with the necessary
connections.
Then that must mean...
He knows she's a Shikabane,
but he chooses to hide it.
People have been
disappearing around her
for quite some time now...
a news station employee...
cab driver, landlord...
too many to be
just coincidence.
Come to think of it,
she hasn't been on TV
or seen in public
at all for years.
You're right,
it's all a big cover-up.
Yes...
But for whatever reason she's
suddenly having a concert
right here in our town.
You're going to that concert
to find the source of her energy
so you can dissolve it.
Be careful, Makina.
Hello.
I have a delivery
for someone in
Kun-Osaki san's office.
Oh, yeah. Fifth floor
conference room -
got a big entourage.
Guess she thinks she
needs that many people.
Thanks.
Big entourage?
Excuse me, ma'am did
somebody order a--
What'd she do?
From that distance!
So you're the one who's
trying to kill our product.
We've heard
so much about you.
Move back!
How did you know
I was coming?
Somebody...
called us!
It doesn't matter
who called.
Would you like me to sing
for you, my biggest fan?
But you're dead, Osaki.
Eh, obviously not.
As long as I sing, I live.
Song's over.
Dead girl.
Get her!
Hold it right there buddy.
We know you're working
with the woman upstairs.
Who, little ol' meeee???
I'm not a wussy!
Hey!
You wussy boy!
No, I'm not, I'm not!
Wussy boy! Wussy boy!
All right, kids;
that's enough!
Stop annoying Ouri;
you know he doesn't like it.
We can't have any
fun around here!
So, did you find anything?
Well, as
I understand it...
Mr. Hoshimura had some
connection to our temple here.
What?
The Kougon Sect?
When my father died,
Mr. Hoshimura visited me
after the funeral.
I think he may have
been Keisei's senior?
I'm not sure.
But I never heard that
his house had burned down.
Is there an address,
or landmark I can go by?
Why don't you ask Keisei?
Keisei...
can't know about this.
The temple...
Hey! What the hell!
Get her!
Keisei!
There she is!
She's still alive?!
Hold it!
Hey! C'mon!
Get her!
Be quiet back there!
I'm sorry for
all the trouble.
We need Sojo Takamine
with the prefectural
police to get involved.
They can take
it from here.
The prefectural?
That's right. They're
the only ones allowed
to know anything
about Shikabane.
And they're also the ones
who most frequently deal
with the yakuza.
Understood.
My apologies.
It's ok.
We're sworn to protect
and defend you, Sho-Sojo.
I'm just doing my job.
Yes, but it doesn't make
things any easier for you.
I know how hard it must be
for you to have to attack
a living human being.
Hey, hey, hey!
There is some crazy
shit happening!
Ushi?
Ya hear? Kun-Chan's performance
has just been cancelled!
Something about a fight
between yakuza groups?
Nobody knows anything,
but somebody's saying
that Kun-chan was shot!
What? Someone
shot her?
Now they're saying the
hit-man was a woman?!
I just hope
Kun-chan's alright.
Things are getting crazy
in front of the CD shop.
I'll call you again later.
[Disconnect tone]
Makina...
Hoshimura...
So you can read.
Yes.
Me and my
entire family.
This is where
we're buried.
It's true?
It was a massacre,
when we died.
When they burned my
family in the temple.
But as a Shikabane Hime...
I'll have my
vengeance one day.
If you got that...
then please respect it
and don't ever show
your face to me again.
Why?
Of course. I want
to know more about you.
We are the dead.
We are defiled.
It's immoral for humans
to get close to us.
If you get
anymore involved--
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Are you okay?
Where are you?
I'm fine.
I'm taking care
of everything.
Were you hurt at all?
Who's that,
who're ya talking to?
Don't worry!
Okay?
To tell you the truth,
I was running away.
I had no plan.
I didn't even know
where I was going.
Or how or why
I ended up here at all.
I just found myself here.
Makina...
Tell your friend,
I'm sorry.
Huh?
About the concert.
I was only trying
to protect them.
You mean you're the
one who attacked Osaki?!
You should be resting.
I just tried
to murder a rock star.
I can't stay here.
Both the police and the yakuza
will be after me for that.
But.
I'm not about to leave
you here all by yourself.
It's just that Brother
sort of took me in
when I was three.
And had nowhere
else to go.
He said that he
couldn't leave me alone.
We may not really
be related...
but we're brothers.
Come on Kun, we have to
get you to a safer place!
I wanna sing.
I wanna sing!
Of course.
Even up until now, those
who you killed were even--
I didn't kill them!
Uh, yes, of course.
Certainly not Kun...
Those people interfered
with my song.
They interfered!
Kun-chan!
What a terrible song.
But it'll sound great
when you sing it in Hell...
it's just the living
who can't stand it.
That's really harsh!
You got smacked
by a dead girl!
Why are you with her?!
After all she's done.
She's the strongest
being I've ever seen.
Certainly more
so than you, little brat.
Well, damn.
What are you
still doing here?
I'll be just fine.
Like hell, you're fine!
Look at you!
...your wounds are getting
worse by the minute...
When I saw you before,
they started healing right away,
but now...
Shut up.
Each Shikabane Hime has
an emotional and physical bond
to a specific human.
And anytime that
human is nearby...
She receives his Rune,
or life energy.
With her body regenerated,
she is once again
able to utilize her abilities
to their fullest extent.
That specific human being
is referred to as...
a contracted monk.
Uh, Brother!
So you're "just
fine," are you?
I told you not
to come, remember?
What else could
I have done?
Of course I came,
I'm your contracted monk.
Stay here,
I got this.
Makina, hold her
back by using this.
Brother!
♪ If you just can't go on,
You had a beautiful voice.
That's why you always
wanted to sing, right?
♪ I will care for it,
But! Your voice
is no good anymore!
It's smothered by
your own twisted obsession
with eternal life and the idea
that you can sing forever.
You couldn't accept
your fate as a human,
so you abandoned
humanity altogether.
And now, no one wants
to hear your voice.
I understand your pain!
But your song is defiled now,
it speaks of nothing but death!
Brother!
This is Shikimi
grown in holy water.
Looks like it's working.
Makina...
you take over...
the only ones who can
kill Shikabane are...
those who were created
for that purpose...
Shikabane Hime!
[Music]
Your wounds...
Brother...
♪ I am an illusion,
♪ A shadow of life once loved.
[Music]
♪ All for you
♪ Fate has dealt you its hand,
♪ Trapped you in a world
you can barely stand.
♪ Will you cower there,
♪ Or rise up and endure?
♪ What to do?
♪ Rain has stopped falling,
♪ The sun has stopped shining.
♪ Our luck has left us
♪ On our own.
[Music]
A Shikabane Hime is
forbidden to kill humans.
But what happens when she
faces the one who killed
his own Shikabane Hime?
Beware "Traitor Monk"!