[Laughter]
Stop distracting me!
What're you doing?
You play that stupid game,
it annoys everyone around you.
Including me.
Whatever!
You're such a pain,
dude. Seriously.
I'm a pain?
Okay then, give it to me!
Shut up!
Hey!
Huh?
Dude,
I'm so bored.
Then you'll just have to
see me later, sweetheart.
What the hell
stinks so bad?
Get the hell away
from me, man!
Walk much...?
What's your deal, bro?
Hey... Don't I know you
from somewhere?
What's funny?!
Transform!
How is Senior
Tagami doing?
From what I've heard,
he's unable to move at all.
Its capabilities as a catalyst
have been greatly increased,
just as
you asked for.
Thank you
very much...
for doing this yourself,
Gon-Sojo Aragami.
I'm sure you can
understand your request
for a new catalyst
has raised my suspicions.
My intention is...
to open my zadan
in the next battle.
Itsuki and
Senior Tagami...
were injured because of me
and my lack of experience.
Senior Tagami destroyed
the traitor monk's catalyst
and in doing so,
received its curse...
This concerns me.
Isaki shall be assigned
as the deputy Guardian
in that district.
However,
we will continue
to have Sho Sojo Sougi
work there as well.
At least
for the time being.
Very well,
Takamine...
His Grace, the Dai-Sojo shares
my opinion on this matter.
According to witnesses,
Gon Dai Sojo...
Akasha was defeated
by a sniper unknown to us...
And we're having difficulty
identifying who they are.
For many years now, rumors and
whispers have circulated...
It is believed that
within the Kougon Sect,
there are those that not only
kill Shikabane, but humans, too.
Regardless of what
you've heard...
Our teachings don't
include killing people.
It happened...
five years ago.
One day, a group led by a
powerful Shikabane appeared.
This resulted in the formation
of a suppression unit.
Akasha was
in that unit.
All who knew of them believed
that they were impeccable.
However, this all changed when
the unit was suddenly unable
to be reached.
Along with an
inspection team,
additional contracted monks
rushed there in quite a hurry.
They weren't prepared
for what they witnessed.
Every contracted monk
had been annihilated,
as well as
their Shikabane Hime,
with one exception.
His Shikabane Hime
had been torn in two.
He stood there, just
holding her body together.
Carrying the depths
of hell in his eyes,
Akasha was
the soul survivor.
Even after investigating,
we still couldn't figure out
what the hell
had happened.
Before I knew it,
I was forced to resign
from the inspection team.
However...
A week later...
while he was in the process
of restoring her body,
he killed his own
Shikabane Hime.
Many monks were
killed that night.
Akasha also stole secret ritual
scriptures before he ran off.
When I found out...
I wasn't really...
shocked by the any of it,
strangely enough.
Are you telling me you
sympathize with a man
who murdered his
Shikabane Hime?
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
This is Parthenon.
Hey there,
boss...
Oh, hey, Ouri.
What's going on?
I hate to do this to you,
but my brother
has the flu or something.
Would it be cool
if I took the day off
so I could
take care of him?
I don't see why not.
Its not like we have customers.
No problem.
I hope that your brother's
injuries aren't too serious.
Something wrong?
Are you okay?
Everything is fine.
Tell your brother
to get well soon.
[Disconnect tone]
I don't think I told him
that Brother got hurt.
Did somebody
get hurt, Ouri?
Uh... yeah,
Brother did.
Anyway, what is this thing
you wanted to show me?
Good job,
Einstein.
Out of all the places,
the ribs?!
A blog?
Yeah.
In middle school,
the both of us were in
the kendo club together.
You got hurt again?
Oh, yeah... I fell off my
bike doing my paper route.
So... is this page loaded up,
the blog you're talking about?
Uh... yeah.
In the middle
of 8th grade,
he just started blowing off
assignments and then he just...
stopped showing up.
He ditched?
There was this 9th grader
who teased the crap out
of the lower graders.
I see...
Well... This looks
more like an epic poem...
Than a blog.
He used to just talk
about playing video games
and watching shows before.
But now,
he's completely obsessed
with constantly
updating it.
Here's where all this
starts to get weird.
"My birth"...
"It's just natural that those
in school and the kendo club,
as well as my parents
and relatives,
couldn't understand me."
"Now that things
have come to this,
I can't help but
feel pity for them."
"They did not get chosen."
"I will use this power
to better the world."
The other day,
one of the seniors in our
kendo club passed away.
What...? It was the bully you
were talking about, wasn't it?
I heard that he
was run-over by a train...
But I'm sure that was
just a coincidence.
I called... Mitsuyoshi a couple
of times to tell him about it...
but nobody answered.
Why are you telling me...
about all of this stuff?
Ouri... do you remember
when Inuhiko was telling us
about Shikabane?
According to the rumors,
a person that dies,
but can't move on will become
a monster called a Shikabane.
From what I can tell,
it's just an urban legend.
But have you ever heard
of something like that?
Can't say that I have...
You should just give
it a rest, sounds dumb.
You're right.
Besides, there's no way
Mitsuyoshi could be dead.
From what it sounds like,
the guy writing the blog
got killed by some
sort of electric shock
and became a Shikabane.
But he hasn't realized
that he's different yet.
Why are you lying
to those around you?
I lied...
About my injury...
and Shikabane...
I lied in the same way
that Brother did to me.
But I only did it
to protect Sumitori.
Perhaps he's not the only
one that needs protecting.
I know to leave the Shikabane
to Brother and Makina,
that's what
they're here to do.
I can't help them
in any way.
There's nothing for me.
I know what you
said is true.
Keisei is being dragged
into something
that has nothing
to do with him.
It's too late
to change things.
Is this all because you
want to get into heaven
or is it something else?
I'm not sure what all
Keisei has told you...
But I'm looking for the
Shikabane responsible
for the death
of my family.
My reason for being is simply
to kill those that killed me.
So don't get
the wrong idea.
We're not heroes or
champions out for justice!
Keep following me
around and you'll die.
And Keisei will die, too.
There's just...
I've been meaning to ask you
this particular question.
Are you and my brother,
uh... well...
are you two dating?
Wow, I was not
expecting that.
Makina definitely isn't one for
holding back when she's upset.
I couldn't have talked
about that blog right now.
Not with everything
else going on.
Are you dead?
Mitsuyoshi?
Now that you mention it,
I think I've seen him.
I haven't seen you.
You interested, baby?
No... I want information
on Mitsuyoshi.
You don't seem
sure about that.
What is it, monk?
Looking for your
collection plate, dude?
You lousy simpletons.
How dare you!
Bastard!
Isaki! Be careful,
it's dangerous.
Don't give me an order.
Let them live
their idle lives,
while we continue
to surpass them.
Isaki...
It's Deputy Guardian.
What?
Until Senior Tagami
has recovered,
I am acting
as the Deputy Guardian.
Understand? This is
my chance to be promoted.
Deputy Guardian... Yes.
You taste sweet.
Some idiot left a comment
in Mitsuyoshi's blog.
Destroying the Shikabane should
be easier than we thought.
We will need to kill at
least three more this month.
What did you mean?
I wasn't sure you'd show.
You're Mitsuyoshi, right?
Why did you ask
me if I am dead?
No one else will
show up, we're alone.
I'm not trying
to cause any trouble,
but I need you
to listen to me.
If I'm not
mistaken, he's-...
Senior Tagami's brother.
He can't stay off our radar
and out of our business.
The head temple still hasn't
cleared their suspicion of him.
This is a good opportunity to
see how things will play out.
But he...
You know Sumitori...
don't you?
Sumi... tori...
He talks to me...
He's really
worried about you...
Because...
Of all the strange things
you've written on your blog.
There's no way he
would worry about me.
Sumitori wasn't
any different.
He ignored me like
all the others did.
No, Mitsuyoshi.
You said...
that you were a hero, if you
were telling the truth...
There has to be
another way for you
to carry out
what needs to be done.
[Screaming]
Mitsuyoshi!
I...
I... I...
Mitsuyoshi!
Transform!
Shikabane!
And who do we have here?
I kill corpses whose regrets
keep them from dying.
I'm Shikabane Hime!
You, too?
So in other words,
you're pure evil.
Evil?
I'm not... what you
call a Shikabane.
I gained this new life
and became a hero in order
to do what is necessary.
Minai!
What are you doing?!
Hurry and
attack it already!
Yes, Deputy Guardian.
I will not forgive evil.
I will not forgive those
who make people suffer.
And you dare turn your
fist toward me in anger...
Evil!
The Shikabane...
Are contrary to all that
is good in the world!
I am different...
I am justice!
Minai!
He must be cursed.
Cursed?
When he became
a Shikabane,
his body wasn't the
only thing that changed.
His curse functions beyond
the laws of physics.
This is proving to be...
More difficult than I
originally thought it would.
The two of you know...
My brother?
Out of my way.
What's the matter, Minai?
Please give her a minute!
She's taken on
a lot of damage.
At the rate she's
going, she could...
Silence!
If you had just kept his
attention long enough,
she would have killed
him with one hit...
Damn layman!
Get up, Minai!
Please!
What's the matter...?
Why don't you attack me?
Not a single one
of your attacks
has even the
slightest effect on me!
I am immortal!
You are pure evil!
That's it!
Cursed or not,
I'll kill him!
I think I understand.
He can return all the
damage to the same place
on his attacker's body.
So that's the curse!
Minai!
Don't get
the wrong idea.
We're not heroes or
champions out for justice!
Keep following me around...
And you'll die.
That was reckless, Ouri.
Please stay out of sight.
Try and hide in
here for a while.
Isaki and I...
We'll take care
of everything.
Why do you listen
to someone like him?
Because this is how my
atonement is achieved.
What?
Before I died...
I murdered someone
close to me.
I was going to die
with him...
But to my surprise...
I didn't die...
I couldn't.
That's why
I have been sentenced
to live this
hollow existence.
You think being a Shikabane
Hime is a punishment?
What that Shikabane
said could be the truth.
Maybe he's
really justice...
And we are the evil
ones here after all...
I don't believe that...
No way.
That guy tried to use
me as a decoy...
But you rescued me.
Well I couldn't just stand
there and watch you get hurt.
So thank you.
Hiding is pointless.
Minai!
Just as I thought...
Makina!
Since I'm missing
my right arm,
I had no damage
when I attacked his.
This is the
first time I'm happy
that my body
is still regenerating.
How did you find us?
The head temple contacted us
with some questions
about your cell phone...
They said that Isaki
was investigating...
Why do you still keep
getting involved?
You weren't worried
about me, were you?
What?
You saved us.
You're my hero.
[Phone ringing]
Get it?
Man, I hate you.
[Music]
Who are you shedding
those tears for?
From this world, one of
the defiled has departed...
What more do you
need to know?
It's time to celebrate...
her "Serenity."