[Mew]
[Music]
You there, brother?
What happened to you?
She's cold!
She's dead...!
I mean, she's passed on...
Did she die from some kind
of an accident or something?
And why is she
here all alone?
You must stop this!
Guardian, please!
You can't!
Guardian, there's nothing
you can do in your condition.
The bond has
already been broken.
I recognize that man.
He's the one who comes from
the head temple sometimes.
His name is
Shirae, I think.
And that other guy was
calling brother 'Guardian?'
Where did he get
those injuries?
And just who the
heck is that girl?
Curious, aren't you?
She's Shikabane.
What?!
Something you will
become fascinated by...
soon enough.
Guardian Tagami...
It's my lack of skills
that caused the bond
to begin to break...
Still, it's not too late!
You'd be better off
to wait for a new one.
She's not an
object, Honda.
Keisei...
I'm sorry...
I'm certain that
she was dead.
Hagino... right?
You know, back at your home,
we found seven corpses
you tried to hide
inside a closet.
Those are the women who used
to live with you, aren't they?
What would you cops
do if you found
that your subordinates got
together and committed a crime?
There's only one answer.
You'd punish them.
Well, it's the same
for those women.
I just punished them.
That's all.
Then tell me what crime
those women are guilty of?!
They disobeyed my
instructions...
And that's a felony.
Ah!
Stop!
Hey!
He's getting away!
We gather for
this meal today, again,
thanks to the
protection of Buddha.
Hey... What're you
doing, Keisei?!
Don't call me Keisei, Shouta,
it's Mr. Head Monk to you.
And it's okay for a
Buddhist monk to steal food?
Listen, kids, this
is a strange world,
and in it there are many
people who seem respectable
but in truth are
consumed by evil.
Don't let anyone's
public appearance
or personality fool you.
You must see
through these individuals
to find the truth.
Yet another valuable lesson
taught to you by me...
What're you trying to teach
them this time, Tagami?
You see... As the man
in charge of this place,
I was seeing
to the kids' well being.
The land we're on may
belong to the Sekuu Temple,
but I am still the director
of this facility...
I want all of you to forget
what he just said, okay?
Instead, we're going to
divide Tagami's breakfast
equally amongst
the rest of us!
Come on!!
Yeah!
Excuse me, Director,
but is it okay if I leave
this stuff at the front for now?
You're moving out tonight?
Yeah, and I'm gonna ask my
friends at school to help me.
No, Hanagami!
You can't seriously
be moving out?!
My name's not Hanagami...!
It's Kagami, Kagami!
No...!
It's Hanagami...!
Hanagami!!
Owww.
Are you gonna take
all those with you?!
It was you, wasn't it?!
You put all these
magazines in with my stuff!
I don't think so.
That's your name written
across the front.
Maybe so, but it's written
in your hand writing!
I did it out of
parental love.
I thought you'd
enjoy them much more
once you started
living by yourself.
I'm fine on my own!
Besides, you're not
my parent, are you?!
You're right...
After all, you grew
up here same as I did.
Look, I'll always think of you
as a brother no matter what.
I don't understand why
you wanna leave us, Ouri.
Hey, I'll be close...
I'll be stopping by for
dinner all the time.
Sure, but
it'll cost ya!
See ya later!
Once school is over,
I'll come back.
So just hold on to my
stuff until then, okay?
Thanks!
He said he'll be working
two part time jobs.
He's that age where he needs
to feel independent...
Let him give it a shot.
Did you notice...?
He started saying he wanted
to live by himself
only when he saw
you laid up
after that injury you
received last year.
That's when it started.
I had no idea.
I know how often you vanish
and then reappear all messed up.
I've gotten used to it
over time, but Ouri hasn't.
So the Dai-Rin House is
actually closer to the school?
Yeah, but the rent here can
be higher than you'd imagine.
Which is why I'm not so crazy
about living by myself.
The real reason you
bailed is that the cemetery
behind your house just plain
creeped you out, right?
I've got enough
respect for the dead...
not to be scared by them.
Didn't you tell
me before...
that sometimes you've
seen dead people?
Yeah, since
it's a temple...
But it's never
frightened me or anything.
Which I think is what
the problem is...
So you guys gonna
help me move, or what?
Hey! Where are you going?!
Uh, I forgot, I've
got club activities.
And I don't wanna
do physical labor.
Oh, crap!
We better hurry!
I am!
Inuhiko, hi.
I told you not to call me
by my first name, right?
I hate it...
Anyway, so did you hear?
Hear what?
You know, about
the harem criminal.
A Harem...?!
I'd love to have a harem,
just for one day!
So... you must be talking
about that guy
who lived with all of those
women who turned up missing,
I heard about him.
Of course! It's all they talk
about on the TV news.
And last night they said
that after the police
executed a search
warrant on his house,
they found seven corpses
hidden inside.
Corpses...
So he really did
kill some of them!
Well, at least the police
have him in custody.
Actually he
slipped away...
The student council sent
a warning out to all of us,
since the cops said
it's more than likely
that he's lurking around
this area of town.
I guess your window of
opportunity to move has closed.
But, today's the only day
that I can take off
from either of my jobs.
This guy's house is near the
next train station, isn't it?
It just seems so unreal,
those corpses
being so close to us.
Yeah...
The suspect is said to have
lived with several women...
Normally, the Shikabane
of vicious criminals
like this guy don't appear
in town all that often.
Even with death row inmates,
when they become Shikabane,
they're taken care of within
the prison, secretly.
And the whole idea
of them getting shot
and killed by
the cops is rare enough
that I can't recall
it ever happening.
Regardless, this guy
became a Shikabane.
The police're hiding this.
But it happened...
He jumped off the 20th floor
of a building yesterday.
Alive... I'm alive!
I can't die!
I am immortal!
Shikabane are simply
corpses that reanimate,
due to intense regrets
and obsessions.
Both local police
and the government
as a whole
deny their existence.
But this guy
became a Shikabane.
And Shikabane kill humans.
Let's not forget that the
Shikabane of vicious criminals
sometimes have odd powers.
That's precisely why
we're asking you.
You're the Guardian.
I'll be the inspector,
as I always am.
And I'm on my own.
That's the entire reason
why we've bothered
to take in someone like you.
Honda!
Not like any of your
answers will change my job.
I'm gonna find this guy
and I'm gonna kill him.
Did you see that?
Is it a bird?
Mommy! Check it out!
Oh, my goodness!
What was that?!
Who would rent you
this rickety old thing?
Rent. This thing was free.
You know I was watching
the news earlier...
Yeah. The harem criminal.
Don't worry.
He's only after women.
I know.
Just be careful, will you?
Director... I don't
know what to say...
You've been so good to me.
Stop it.
Well then...
See you guys.
It was a woman from
Hagino's harem?
Yes, I saw her enter the
building on her own
a few minutes ago.
I guess Hagino
summoned her here.
The police are also
looking for her,
so we should hurry before
they catch wind of this.
What the hell
are you doing?!
I died and then
I returned to life...
I have become a
vampire immortal...
the chosen god to
reign over mankind...
Bullshit... You're nothing
but a Shikabane.
But how...?!
A Shikabane creating
another Shikabane...
I told you, my life
is now that of a vampire.
And these are my
faithful servants.
Are these women
Shikabane, too?
Or is he using some kind
of hypnosis on them?
Maybe you want
to serve me too!
Well well... You're not
human, either, are you?
Makina!
Dammit...
I gotta find
someone to help...
But what if everything I own
is stolen while I'm gone...?
Could it be?
She looks the same.
Of course she does...
Because it's her.
What happened?
She's dead...
again!
But you don't feel yourself
being scared, do you?
Instead, you're
fascinated by her.
You're unable to feel fear
when it comes to death,
and it scares you
that you're like this.
What are you doing?
This is what Brother
did when I saw her last.
That's a corpse
you're holding.
A Shikabane.
I know that.
I have to try.
Help...
me...
What are you doing?
Your heart wasn't
beating, so I helped.
Forget you saw me.
Your heart's
still not beating.
Knowing that... aren't you
scared in the least?
Not really...
You're alive.
Hey, hold on!
Makina!
How's your body?
It got revived...
and you're with me
now, so I'm good.
Shirae and the others are
watching the Shikabane...
Can you go?
Yes.
Just make sure that
whatever you do,
you don't attack the women.
Shikabane can't pass
their condition on.
We don't think those who
were attacked by Hagino
necessarily
become Shikabane.
Then, that means...
They're either
hypnotized somehow,
or they've admired Hagino's
charisma from the beginning
and fell prey to that.
Of course
it's also possible
they convinced themselves
Hagino is an actual vampire.
Either way, they're alive.
And I don't have the right
to kill living people.
No one has that right.
Not a living person
or a Shikabane!
What about the seven corpses
found in Hagino's house?
Do you think he killed
them all by himself?
I'm unsure.
It's possible that
he made those women
in the harem
kill each other.
But in any event,
it doesn't matter.
I know, I know.
Those women are alive.
And me... I'm dead.
You fell from twenty floors
up and yet here you are.
So I was right...
From time to time,
there's a corpse like you
born in the world...
You're dead,
but your will remains,
your body functions,
and you kill humans.
You're called Shikabane.
There's another
kind of Shikabane.
With the sole purpose of
killing those like you...
Out of fear,
pity, or ridicule,
people like to refer
to us by one name only...
Shikabane Hime!
Didn't you tell me
not to attack them?
All I did was help
them evacuate safely.
Come over here,
Shikabane Hime.
You and I are the
same, you know that?
We both feast on humans
and we live forever.
You and Makina
aren't the same...
what an absurd statement!
Wait, Makina!
It's too dangerous!
Dangerous?!
You should know by
now, I fear nothing!
There's only one way
to kill a Shikabane...
You gotta destroy
the brain.
Look at that...
You're scared of me now.
You lose!
Looks like...
they had fun.
I smell Shikabane...
[Music]
People have forgotten that
death lies close to them...
Because if they
ever remembered it,
they'd go
completely insane.
But soon they'll remember.
Next episode:
"The Game Continues."