[Music]
Cut it out, guys!
Hanagami's coming!
That's not my name...
It's Kagami!
That's enough.
Yaay! You
got in trouble!
You got in trouble!
Home sweet home!
I'd like to see you try...
But I think we both know
you'd be nothing without me.
You don't have what it takes
to make it on your own.
You think this
is a game...?
You think I like
repeating myself...?
Do you?
Please, just stop...
I said I'm sorry.
You belong to me...
I'll do what I want...
And I'll stop when I want.
The sooner you
learn that--
Bitch!
You're gonna let them
get away with it?
Shouta wrote "Hanagami"
in big black marker
on the back of my
favorite shirt...!
I'm so pissed...!
Its ruined!
You know how much
I love that shirt!
There's no way
I can wear it now!
I mean, would you wear
clothes like that?
Minai Ruo...
The man she murdered
was her boyfriend...
Afterward, she threw herself
off their high rise balcony...
However, this didn't
prevent her from walking
away from the incident.
This corpse still lives.
A Shikabane... right.
There is still some time before
her transformation is complete.
Keisei... It's my understanding
that you know this woman, right?
She looks familiar...
I don't know.
Well, think...
She worked at a store in front
of the train station...
uh... the place is...
A cosplay pub.
Cosplay...?
Oh, yeah. I haven't the first
idea as to what people ever do
at a place like that...
I can't say that
I've been to one...
I mean, what's
the point...?
It's a complete
mystery to me.
There's no use pretending,
we found this with her.
Tell me, Keisei...
Do you make it a habit of
leaving your business card
in these kinds of bars?
No... You've got this
whole thing wrong.
I was there on a social
studies field trip.
Yeah...
Wait...
I wonder if I have
met her before?
Whether you know
you have or not,
there's certainly
a bond between you two.
What are you getting at?
My point is that
it's come time for you
to make a contract
with a Shikabane Hime.
I'm doing fine.
Without a Shikabane Hime
to fight alongside you,
your abilities
are limited.
Please...
I'm handling myself well.
Don't let what happened with
Akasha fuel your actions.
Have it your way then...
We have no choice but
to deal with this woman
like any other Shikabane.
Kamika, would you
perform the ritual?
No, don't do it!
Wait, Guardian Takamine...
Let me be the one.
Isaki...
I, too,
am a Dai-Sozu...
I can also make a contract
with a Shikabane Hime...
If I'm allowed to do
that with this woman,
we'll be of great use
to Senior Tagami.
Contracting with a
Shikabane is no easy task...
A monk must posses
a bond and great virtue.
But we already
have a bond...
She and I have spoken in
town before on a matter
very personal to her...
If I recall...
Correctly...
She asked for some advice
in dealing with the man
she was living with.
They weren't getting along...
She stopped me because
of my appearance,
thinking I was someone
she could trust.
I believe that's
how it went.
I was concerned so we met
several times to talk.
Very well...
To me it sounds like
you couldn't ask
for a tighter
bond with this girl.
Sir...
A contract
shall be created...
All right...?
Keisei?
Yes.
My mind
is unlike others.
And my body is nothing
but that of a corpse...
Until either happiness
or death separates us,
my allegiance I pledge to
the decree and sectarian.
Contract.
Wake up, Minai.
What's for...
breakfast?
How stupid are you?
You're dead, remember?
What dead person
would eat?
What kind of skills
do you possess...?
Strength will only
get you so far...
If you're unable to
utilize a weapon...
You won't be of any
use in protecting me.
Protecting you...?
But why?
It's a Shikabane Hime's duty
to protect her contracted monk.
I guess...
I know some...
I can box a little.
Wait, are you talking
about boxercising...?
The weight loss program?
I got beat up a whole
lot when I was a kid...
I had to figure out how
to work my way out of it.
It's no surprise
you ended up with a jerk
that beat you senseless...
Show me some of these
boxercing skills.
Do it.
Show me what kind of
punch you've got in you.
You won't hurt me.
Now, do it.
You...
You stupid bitch!
What are you
waiting for, Minai?!
Attack him...!
Do it already!
Take him down!
I can't...
He's a person...
That's not a person...
It's a corpse...
A Shikabane...
one who couldn't die when
he should have like you!
Not fair...
I had no choice...
What gives you the right?
Isaki, No...
I almost got killed!
What the hell do I have a
Shikabane Hime for anyway!
Dammit...! Are you
even listening?!
That's enough...
This was her first
time fighting...
Lesson one...
You can't stop a Shikabane
unless you destroy the brain
or shred the body so
that it can't rebuild.
Pay attention to that.
Would you shut
your stomach up?!
Tell me you've been eating.
Uh...
Why would a deal
girl need food...?
He said that
I didn't need to eat.
Well, he's not lying...
A Shikabane Hime
can survive fine
as long as she receives enough
rune from her contracted monk...
But I bet you still
get hungry, though.
What's rune?
It's hard to explain...
Try to think of it as
a kind of bio-energy...
It flows into you via the bond
from your contracted monk.
You should see the bond.
A Shikabane Hime can see
a light flowing towards her
from her contracted monk.
That's the bond.
Can you see it?
This woman can't
seem to understand
such a difficult concept,
Keisei...
I've been saddled with
an unbelievable fool.
I dunno. What you're saying
sounds kinda weird to me.
Gon Sho Sojo Tagami
can't feel it...
He's almost certain
there is no bond
between Dai Sozu Isaki and
his Shikabane Hime, Minai.
Why not...?
The two of them made
a contract, didn't they?
Correct. But
something is failing.
He said...
It would appear
that the Shikabane Hime
isn't receiving rune.
Yeah, alright...
But what's that mean?
It means that she's
not a Shikabane Hime.
She's just a Shikabane that
happens to be harmless
by his side at all times...
We can never know
when she's going to turn
violent and rampage.
I thought the two of you...
Could investigate this
matter and get some answers.
Why not? I mean, we're
not here to target Shikabane.
Our job is to keep an eye on the
Shikabane Hime and their monks.
Come on...
We just got to this town
and already we're working.
A motorcycle?
That's right...
Before I died,
I'd gotten my
motorcycle license.
If I have a bike,
I think that fewer Shikabane
would get away from me.
You actually thought I'd
buy you a motorcycle...?
How thick are you?
I can't spend that kind of
money on a Shikabane Hime...
A motorcycle, food...
Get out of your own head.
Sorry...
What is it?
A Shikabane...
I think that might be one.
Hey, you!
Quick, get her!
Go get her,
Minai...! Hurry!
Get out of here.
A Shikabane...
Not a chance...
I'm Shikabane Hime.
See here.
My contracted monk isn't
far away from me right now.
With the rune that
I receive from him...
Any injuries I have will
heal and vanish in no time.
Now look at you...
You were walking right
alongside your contracted monk
when I shot...
And yet that bullet
wound of yours
shows no sign of healing...
Some Shikabane Hime you are.
I don't understand.
There isn't a bond between
you and that monk...
You're nothing but another
Shikabane to kill...
I can't sit idly by and wait
for you to go on a rampage...
I have to do this...
I'm sorry.
So this...
is punishment.
Minai, where are you?!
Dammit!
Go Isaki...!
Get out of here now!
Well, what happened
to the Shikabane?
It got away from me.
What happened?
We should lay off of them...
At least for a bit.
Something is...
Not right.
You should have told me
the second that it happened.
Sorry... I...
Now are you sure she said
she was a Shikabane Hime?
Yes... She also
mentioned something
about my injury not
healing right away.
Well, if you weren't such a dim
witted fool it would have...
It's that simple.
Oh...
I see...
I guess.
A Shikabane Hime...
I wonder...
Listen...
I'd just consider everything
she said as a lie.
Isaki, I'm curious...
About what?
It's just that...
I mean, you do
know me, don't you?
You told them I asked you for
advice on the street one day...
But I don't
remember doing that.
Even you're
beginning to doubt
that the contract between
the two of us is real...
Great.
It's not true.
I lied...
But the Guardian can never
learn of my deception
What would happen
if he did?
They'd separate us...
Who knows what else.
But before then...
Minai...
I need you.
Give me your hand.
You need me...?
What're you doing
here, Sadahiro?
Akira... Thought you
trusted me more than that...
I'm a little
disappointed in you...
Whatever.
Well, I don't...
So here's what we'll do...
You investigate Isaki
and I'll
investigate Minai...
Try not to get
them mixed up.
Just listen to me...
In this place, Isaki used to...
In this town, inai used to...
You'll understand why I lied
when I tell you why I did it...
There's a Shikabane I've had
my eye on for some time now...
He's been masquerading as a
monk at one of our temples.
Above all else, the Kougon
Sect fears scandal...
So they leave him alone...
Its time we stop him...
We're going to take care
of him on our own.
There.
He's in the back.
He's not here.
What do you mean?!
Shikabane...?
Wait a minute...
Shuuji...
Shuuji?!... What the hell
are you doing here?!
What are you up to?!
Hello, Brother.
It's exactly what
you think it is...
That was my
family's home...
That man was my
older brother...
I wanted you to do
what I couldn't...
I wanted you
to kill him.
He's nothing
but scum...
I hate him.
All he ever
thought about
was how to soak every last
cent out of our father...
He came up with a new
scam every time...
Money is the only thing
worth a damn to that bastard.
But my parents
didn't care...
No matter what he
did or said,
they always treated him
like he could do no wrong.
My brother inherited the
temple when our father died...
It wasn't long before he had
wasted the entire inheritance
to build that
ridiculous main hall...
I didn't have a choice.
Only a select few have
what it takes to become
contracted monks...
Don't you see?
I had to lie to them.
Still... You tried
to kill your brother.
I thought I could hide the whole
thing if I had you kill him...
I was going to report that
he'd become a Shikabane
after some kind of
tragic accident.
You've known this
entire time...
There is no bond
between you and me.
I had no idea who you were
before you became a Shikabane.
I needed a Shikabane Hime...
I thought that once
I'd become a contracted monk,
I'd take down one Shikabane
after the next...
I'd surpass Senior Tagami
and get a promotion...
I would rise to the
rank of Gon Dai Sojo
and finally be able to put
my brother in his place.
I know it wasn't
a perfect plan,
but I thought
I could do this...
If I lose you, I'll be stuck
where I am for rest of my life
with nothing
to show for it...
It was wrong of me
to send you after my brother,
but I was desperate...
I figured that I could at least
have that small victory...
Pretty pathetic, isn't it?
How long are you going to
continue standing there?
Just go already.
But, I...
You're not a
Shikabane Hime.
All you are is
another Shikabane.
You don't need rune.
Don't you get it yet?
Follow your regrets.
Go anywhere you want.
Do whatever it is you
please. I don't care.
I'm still...
What?
I'm still stuck...
Stuck here in the
middle of my punishment.
Punishment...?
How's that?
I did such a horrible thing...
I murdered someone.
This is my punishment...
You mean that being with
me is a punishment for you?!
What is it?
I can see.
See what?
I can see your face...
It's so clear.
It's dark where you're
standing but you look to me
like you're shining
brightly from within.
Are you serious?
There's a light that's
coming from you to me...
Could this...
be... the bond?
If I'm allowed to go
wherever I like...
then I choose to be by
your side from now on.
Why?
We're alike...
We need eachother.
[Music]
This is great...! How did
you even know about this?
Know what?
I love Okonomiyaki...
It's my favorite.
I didn't about
know that...
This is the only
thing I can make.
Would you mind
passing me the sauce?
Yeah, sure.
[Music]
So good!
About Isaki and his
Shikabane Hime...
there was a bond
between them.
Okay.
Although...
We do know the story Isaki
gave us wasn't the truth.
When Isaki was
a little kid...
he and his brother
didn't get along,
so he was left in
the care of a relative.
That relative ran an
Okonomiyaki restaurant.
Around that time,
Minai's family also happened to
be living in the same town...
Since both of her parents
were at work all day
and she was alone,
she came to that restaurant
by herself a lot.
The both of 'em
were just kids...
they probably don't
remember it very well.
But that bond
really existed.
The two of them were connected
and they never even knew it...
Sounds to me like this was
their fate all along...
So everything worked
out for the best, huh?
Yes.
Wonder if the same
thing'll happen to me...
If I'll meet my fate?
[Music]
Please...! Make a
contract with me!
You're Makina
Hoshimura, right?
Shikabane Hime of
Guardian Tagami...
Do it, Minai!
I'm Minai Ruo...
Shuuji Isaki's...
Shikabane Hime!
[Music]