[Music]
Please bless this food.
What are you saying?
You don't really think
I'd give you bad food?
Both the miso
and seaweed were...
Is that Ouri?
I wanna talk!
But the taste
just isn't right...!
I don't think
it should be this salty.
Salty...?
Um... Ouri...
You rinsed off
the seaweed, didn't you?
Rinsed off?
But...
I thought...
Isn't this the same stuff
Brother used to use?
Yes, and Keisei always rinsed
the excess salt off first.
He actually paid attention
to things like that?
Well, not originally,
I'll admit,
but once you came here to stay,
he most certainly did.
You know, you really haven't
come by to visit for a while...
Hey,Hanagami...!
Who are you trying to kid,
you can't cook!
Says you!
Did you and Keisei
have a fight?
I don't want you to fight,
it's not nice!
I, uh... I know,
you're right...
Senior Tagami, please!
You can't just
walk out...
They- They haven't
finished your tests.
Please get back in bed!
That old man stuck me in here
without even bothering to listen
to my side
of the story!
Would you please...
cut it out!
Eh? What's that...?
"Saki,...
Will you do
that again?"...
Got it!
No, Saki,
I said no such thing!
What is all
this fuss about?
Shikabane Hime Minai...
An Inspector went through
the appropriate channels
in dealing with Minai.
My little brother must
have seen what happened.
No harm was done
to your brother.
Your idea of harm might
differ from mine...
None of this is making
any sense to me...
How could an
inspector have...
Makina and the others
didn't have enough time
to locate her...
Who could have gotten
to Minai so quickly?
I see you don't have
an answer for me then...
Well, perhaps I'll
find someone who does.
How could he get
so worked up
about his stupid
brother like that?
I'm so jealous!
Hey... She
did it, not me...
I wouldn't have said
something like that!
Please, Guardian!
It's not allowed!
You must go back!
Please!
Guardian Tagami...
You are interrupting
His Grace, Gon-Dai-Sojo.
I'm aware of that.
I beg your pardon,
Your Grace...
But there was a
Shikabane Hime
who was killed by
an inspector the other day...
It is not permitted,
Guardian...
To speak of defiled
ones before His Grace.
Defiled,
you call them...?
I think
I must disagree...
I am aware that you
of the Shujou faction
tend to think
of them that way...
However...
for the Kougon Sect they
are absolutely essential...
the very instrument
of our philosophy!
Guardian Tagami!
Gon-Dai-Sojo...
Minai was-...
You should probably
stop right there...
Sho-Sojo Tagami.
I cannot oppose
a Shikabane Hime.
It's...
The D ai-Sojo...
He is here.
The Kougon Sect's number one and
number two are here together.
Dai-Sojo was meditating
close by here...
You have disturbed him!
Sho-Sojo Tagami...
Your work...
as a Guardian...
is appreciated.
Know that Sho-Sojo Isaki...
And his Shikabane Hime
will never be forgotten...
Tell me this...
Wasn't it your
younger brother
who led Minai right into
the hands of the Inspector?
Yes, it is true,
Your Grace.
Peace be with you.
Ahhhhhh!
You're looking a lot
less pale than before...
Ouri.
Is that right?
Did something
good happen?
No, something totally
AWESOME happened...
Isn't that right,
Ouri!
I don't know
what you mean.
Ouri!
Breast Goddess!
Nozomi...
I really need
to ask you something...
Got a minute?
Sure.
What's going on...?
Are you and Ouri
dating or something?
No, we're not.
I thought everyone knew that
Ouri was in love with Makina.
What...?
No, I...
With Makina?
Really? First time
we've heard about that.
I can't stand it,
I can't stand it!!
How are
you doing this?!
You must be releasing special
pheromones or something
to attract
all these women!
That's it,
isn't it?
Some secret cologne?
Where'd you get it?!
Mail order?
Internet?
Free sample in the back
of some magazine?
Ouri!
Come back here!
I have to know!!
Here it is.
Look at this.
I hear that this is really
becoming a popular religion
with a lot of celebrities
and rich people.
Ahhh... You know magazines...
they'll print anything.
You should really
read this article.
I think
you'd like it.
"Devout followers witness
this extraordinary ritual,
in which a young monk
walks deliberately
into the center
of a raging inferno."
"Flames completely
engulf the monk's body...
Though it seems impossible
for him to survive...
In a matter of minutes
his burns disappear...
And he stands
alive and unhurt."
"Founder Ooyatsuka
calls this...
'the Power
of Immortality."
Dying, and then
coming back to life...
Doesn't that
sound like Makina?
Shikabane...
What?
Uh... nothing...
Why are you
showing me this?
If I could join
this religion...
They might have a way
to make me just like Makina...
Right?
Hey, Ouri...
Wanna join them with me?
Join them...?
You're not
serious, are you?
Somehow I thought you
might understand... Guess not.
Why don't you
forget about her...?
Let it go and move on.
I know I should...
But I...
I can't do it.
No one seems to want
to talk about this stuff...
That life doesn't last,
we could all die tomorrow.
When I think about all
of these strange things...
I can't seem to stop myself
from wondering about Makina.
I wouldn't worry...
If you ask me...
I think you're way
too beautiful to die, Nozomi!
Damn you, Ouri!
He's having a good time
with Breast Goddess...!
I'm so jealous!
I can't stop thinking
about that article...
What if Ooyatsuka's religion
really did find a way
to save Shikabane...?
Maybe it's something
that the Kougon Sect
just doesn't know about...
It could save Makina
and all the others.
Um, Mr. Sougi?
I'm sorry I caused
problems for you, Genpaku.
I must admit I did
enjoy school life.
You've been released from your
temporary Guardian assignment.
Where will you go?
I'm thinking about
going to Mount Goryo.
Goryo?
Up in the Kougon
mountains?
Monks have trained there
for hundreds of years...
And now I would like
to retrain myself...
I need to work on perfecting
my own zadan technique.
I guess great minds
really do think alike.
Aren't those
zadan scrolls?
I stole them from old
man Takamine's office...
But being that I've never
been seriously trained
in the zadan technique...
It'll just be a quick fix.
Then... You think the
traitor monk will show up again?
I think this mass
outbreak of Shikabane
is only the beginning...
Don't you?
Don't you want to see
Ouri before you leave?
No... I'm going to the
cafe where he works.
A cafe?
Ouri told Makina that he
tried to hide Minai someplace.
I don't think
he could have known
that many other places
besides the Café Parthenon.
Some place the Inspector
was able to reach
before anyone else...
The Inspector had probably been
watching Ouri for some time.
Where is she?!
There's supposed
to be a daughter.
Where did she go?!
We can't find her!
We found her!
Please...!
Beautiful Life...
Eternal Life...
It radiates
like this fire...
And yet it can
never be consumed.
Isn't it beautiful...?
Not scary at all.
There, you see?
A beautiful life is
the true miracle...
Even more precious
than gold.
Gold!
The Founder's sweat
turned into gold!
Isn't it wonderful...?
You'll live for eternity...
and be rich forever.
If you were to
become a member...
One day soon you would feel
that same kind of power!
You do want to join,
don't you?
Ahhh... could I meet
the Founder before I decide?
Oh, the Founder rarely
appears in person,
but if you join,
of course...
Oh, yes! If you
become a member...
Uh... I'll have
to think about it.
Interesting little
religion you've got here...
Seems familiar somehow...
Shikabane...
You can burn them...
beat them to death...
and they come right back.
That's pretty handy for
an immortality cult...
Pretty lucrative as well.
Poor little puppet.
The show is over.
Fire...!
Flame high!!
Trees!
Trees take them!!
It's a curse,
isn't it?
Fools...! You thought
I was a mere human...?
I am a Shikabane...!
And I have a curse
that causes anything
I say to come true instantly!
It was the perfect
choice for me,
since I never
said anything true
while I was still
among the living.
Your obsession is
with words, huh...?
Fascinating.
I see...
Your curse must be how you've
been controlling this Shikabane.
I am well aware of
who you people are...
You're with the
Kougon Sect...
Don't you realize
that Shikabane are the
earthly equivalent of gods,
humans don't
even come close!
[Laughter]
What's so amusing?
He thinks we're
the Kougon Sect!
I can't say for certain that
the Shikabane are gods...
but I do know
they're made for killing,
for following the obsessions
they had when they were alive.
I also know that pretending to
be human in order to make money
is the ultimate folly.
Not to mention
that you would take
another Shikabane's
freedom away from them.
Who are you?
It just... Wasn't what
I thought it would be...
So vulgar somehow...
Do you think there are
any Shikabane here?
Now die!
By the power of my curse
I'm commanding you!
Be dead!!
Such a pity...
Since we're already dead...
that command is
rather useless!
All of you are...
Shikabane?
Well that
was overkill...
It was necessary.
If we're going to make our name
known and feared once again,
people must know
that Shikabane
are more than just regrets
and obsessions ...
that indeed,
we are Death itself.
Hello?
Anyone there...?
I'm a relative
of Ouri Kagami.
He works
at this cafe.
Sorry, pal...
We're not open.
Your voice...
I believe I recognize it...
I was under the impression that
you'd gone missing overseas.
I said we're closed.
It is you, isn't it...?
Please listen to me...
When I became a Contracted
Monk, I swore two sacred oaths.
One was to dedicate my life
to fighting evil
at the side of a
Shikabane Hime...
And the other...
Was to keep my brother
Ouri far, far away
from the work I had
chosen for myself...
I know now that they
contradict one another.
Even so... Maybe?
I'll keep it in mind.
Thank you.
Wasn't that...
Keisei Tagami?
Start packing up.
What?
Contracted monks aren't
supposed to know about us.
Remember? It's time
for us to go.
Awww! Just when things were
getting pretty interesting.
High time if you ask me.
We still have to find
that traitor monk.
Oh... What should we
do about our employee?
We have no choice...
The kid just worked without
pay this week, that's all.
Cheapskate.
What a pleasant surprise.
To think that you would
appear before us...
Better yet...
That you would
appear before me.
So tell us...
What do we get in return
if we sign on with you, monk?
You're Shikabane...
Acting on your desires is all
that you know how to do...
However... There are those that
would deny their true nature.
You mean Shikabane Hime,
don't you?
Precisely...
I desire to erase every last
one of them from this world!
Well... I think we might be
able to come to an arrangement
as long as we can agree
to annihilate the Kougon Sect...
We'll join you.
This here is Hokuto...
The brightest sun
of the Seven Stars.
I thought you were the leader
of the Seven Stars, Hazama.
The Seven Stars only exist
to allow her light to shine...
Hokuto is Shikabane itself,
and the very embodiment
of the world's nature.
Hokuto...
So you went
to work today and...
It was freakin' closed...!
They just closed the place
without saying a
freakin' word to me...!
And I was supposed to get
freakin' paid today!
How unfair...!
Here, you need
some more.
[Phone ringing]
Oh... Yes, the Order
of Eternal Life Research.
We knew that Founder
Ooyatsuka was a Shikabane...
but under pressure from
a certain political party,
we'd done nothing so far
but keep an eye on them...
but now...
Who did it?
It was seven Shikabane.
The security cameras
captured them perfectly.
Seven Shikabane...
Are you saying...
it was the Seven Stars?
I call her arms!
Legs!
Please! Why are
you doing this?
I haven't done
anything to you!
Please don't hurt me!
Please don't hurt me!!
How ungraceful...
daughter of Hoshimura...!
What a poor little
pathetic human...!
I'm afraid this is
the end of the line!
Seven Stars...
[Music]
Happy Birthday, Ouri...
I have a wonderful
birthday present for you...
It's a story...
But it's also
a very sad story...
a story all about
what happened...
"One Night."