[Music]
The two of you
can handle it!
Makina needs me!
You saw it, right?
Makina Hoshimura's
aberration...
I told you.
I realized that my Shikabane
Hime is an aberration,
and accepted it.
Where we're going, I'll be
able to prove it to you.
Dammit!
Takamasa!
Oh, my...
This isn't
really my taste...
but...
The beautiful, tortured look
on that Shikabane Hime's face
will be well worth it.
I'm really looking
forward to it.
Now then...
it's finished.
If I were to kill all of you
people, Keisei would feel sad,
so I'm being obedient.
That's all.
Oh...
Ah, Umehara!
He's come
to pick you up.
Inspector Honda...
We'll send her to the
purification chamber again...
That's a direct order
from the Gon-Dai-Sojo.
It's the Dai-Sojo's
own handwriting.
It seals all forms
of defilement.
Defilement...?
Well, if you say so...
What're you planning
on doing with her...?
Are you gonna throw her out
with the trash this time?
You sure hate me,
don't you?
Where's he taking Ouri
at a time like this...?
I sure hope the Genpaku
knows what he's doing...
I thought, that if the title
Genpaku is only given
to the strongest
monk then...
I should pick him
to be my contracted monk...
Seriously...?
You seriously
weren't told anything?
Is this about the
temple by any chance?
Unfortunately for her...
by then there wasn't time for
Itsuki to start looking around
for a new contracted monk.
Once you've been
given a contract...
It's an extremely difficult
matter to have it changed...
You know that.
Yes... You have to find a way
to break the bond between you,
just like with Makina.
I was thrown into
the whole thing...
before I had the slightest clue
about what was expected of me.
What's the matter...?
You came
to kill me, right?
I can't help it...
This is my first time.
What's wrong,
Shikabane killer?
So... how was that?
From now on,
this is what-...
Huh?
Hold on a second.
Try not to move.
Why would I try to move?
There! See?
See? I did okay. Right?
Your injuries are much
worse than mine...
I mean...
Don't worry. I told you
I died, right?
It was a bus accident.
You mean...
that was true?
Of course it is...
Even after I've taken all
that time to explain it...
You still have trouble
believing me, don't you?
Shikabane are corpses that,
because of intense
regrets or obsessions,
stay animate
even after death.
After that day
I became a Shikabane.
But the Kougan sect allowed
me to become a Shikabane
that hunts others
like me...
They made me what's
called a Shikabane Hime,
a killer of immortals.
One hundred and eight.
That's how many Shikabane I
have to kill to go to heaven.
And since I want to be
able to go to heaven
as soon as possible...
I chose the strongest
contracted monk.
Which means you naturally chose
the strongest warrior monk...
the Genpaku.
I never imagined that you'd be a
rookie who didn't know anything.
I guess not.
You're not going alone...
I have to be the
one to kill him.
But... you still aren't
used to fighting?
No, but I know how
it feels to die.
How it felt when my bones
pierced my organs...
when my body began to get cold
because of all the bleeding...
I can remember
every detail.
But... you're not
cut out for this.
I'm sorry I got
you involved.
This kind of life will
end up killing you.
What is this...
why aren't my...
legs moving?
Just couldn't stay
away, could you?
Do you really think
you can kill me?
What?
You're weak. You're just
an ordinary Shikabane...
I'll eat you.
I'll eat you!
I killed him...
My first...
My first one...
Die one more time!
When I chose to become
a Shikabane Hime,
I thought that I could
accomplish my goal quickly...
that I'd be able
to fight monsters
since I was
already dead...
But now...
faced with it again...
I'm scared.
What?!
Takamasa!
You son of a bitch!
Shikabane!
Over here!
Hey, hey, hey!
Take it easy, will ya...?
Not too hard...
This really hurts,
you know...
Of course, it does...
But it's gotta be
better than dying.
I didn't realize it
would be this painful...
but you've got a point...
I guess dying
would be worse.
What made you...
decide to help me?
I found my father's
old bow...
It makes me wonder if all
of this was the reason
for the archery and
Kendo lessons he...
made me take when
I was younger.
What...?
No, I was
referring to...
What else could
I have done...?
I couldn't just stand
there and watch you...
I couldn't let you die...
That's nuts... you know I'm
already dead, silly.
Yeah, well to me you still
look like just an ordinary girl.
Idiot...
Am I?
[Laughter]
Congrats on your
first victory...
Only one hundred
seven to go.
This was our first
victory together.
Hey, Takamasa!
You know that's
my hurt shoulder.
Look over there!
Hm?
Everyone, I'd like to
introduce Itsuki Yamagami...
She just transferred
to our school today.
Are you seeing this...?!
Okay, I've decided...
I'm TOTALLY gonna make
a move on this girl...
Oh, no, here she comes...
Every man for himself.
How are you today?
I'm Tomoharu Kishibe.
If you like, I'll fill
you in on this school...
The Kougan Sect creates
family registries for us
since there are times
when we'll need them...
like for example,
undercover investigations.
No. No, not that.
Why my school?
I heard that the bond becomes
stronger if I stay
at the contracted monk's side
as much as possible...
Is that a problem?
No, it's not going
to be a problem at all.
That's wonderful!
Now we can work
hard together!
Come on, treat me
to some ice cream!
Why would I do that?
At first, while it might've
felt a little overwhelming,
I learned that life between
a Shikabane Hime and her
newly contracted monk
is exciting...
But between Itsuki and me, the
normal everday side of things
-especially after
she moved in with me--
was even better.
We were just a pair of kids,
enjoying life to the fullest...
I think I know now...
Hm?
Why I became a Shikabane.
Itsuki...
When I was still alive
I wasn't doing much of anything
with my life.
The fun-loving high school
girl life that you see
in books and
on television...
never seemed
to show up for me...
no matter
how long I waited.
I think...
I wanted...
just to be able
to live more.
And also...
to love someone...
What's that?
Never mind!
I'm sorry!
Are you okay, Takamasa?
Yeah...
Hey... Remember
how I said the reason
I chose you as my
contracted monk was
so I could get into heaven
as quickly as possible?
Uh-huh.
Well now, I feel like I actually
want to stay in this world
as long as
I possibly can...
That's kinda
strange, isn't it?
It seems to me that
all you're really doing
is bragging about
your love life.
Wrong!
You're just inventing things
in that head of yours...
I don't know whatever wild
fantasies your imagination
is coming up with, but I can
tell you they didn't happen.
What do you mean?
Around that time, I went into
seclusion up on the mountain
with Master Umehara...
He told me exactly
the same thing
that I told
you earlier, Ouri.
Which is...
The girl before
you isn't human.
She's a Shikabane Hime.
Are you done training
for the day, too, Itsuki?
Don't do it.
Master, it's you...
What are you talking about?
Did I not make myself clear
before, Takamasa...?
You are on
a dangerous path.
Itsuki is a
Shikabane Hime.
You must stop acknowledging
her as though she were human.
But Master... Why is that?
Shikabane Hime are
aberrations...
Even if they look human, that
is not their true nature.
A contracted monk who
cannot understand
that will certainly die.
But Itsuki is just
an ordinary girl...
I mean, at least she's trying
to live as an ordinary girl.
Isn't that her
true nature?
Listen, Takamasa... There was
once another contracted monk
named Akasha Shishidou...
He also...
Seriously?!
You seriously haven't told
her your feelings yet?!
It's complicated.
I don't know how long
I can be with her, either,
so...
She'll have to go
to heaven some day.
Then what better reason
to cherish the time
the two of you
have together now?
Hey, I don't know the
details of your situation...
but if you don't know how
much time you've got...
you need to tell her
how you feel about her.
But the Master
also said...
Master...? C'mon, you're
just making excuses.
What do you mean excuses?
The truth is that you're
afraid of being turned down
when you tell her,
aren't you?
Are you stupid or what?
Wha... What?!
Ah, dude, give
me a break...
You mean to tell me that
you haven't noticed
how often that girl
gives you the eye?
Huh?
Ever since the day she
came to this school...
You're the only one she
wants anything to do with.
So much so that I,
the master of love,
have had no effect on her.
Tomoharu...
Ah... good!
I thought you guys
had already gone home.
See, there's
the eye, dude...
What?
What? What is it?
Well, I hope the two of
you have a great weekend!
Did you say you were going
out of town, Tomoharu?
Yeah, I'm going to my
parent's hometown...
Seriously, all
we're going to do
is visit all my ancestors'
old graves or something.
See ya.
That was the last
time I saw Tomoharu.
On his way to his
parent's hometown,
the car he and
his family were in
was hit by a minor
driving recklessly
and fell off a cliff.
Once they were found,
the bodies of all four family
members were unrecognizable.
Takamasa.
That's it!
Huh?
Shirae!
Inspector Shirae,
what happened?
What're you
asking him for...?
Didn't you just
see what happened?
Briefing us on the situation
is his responsibility!
Guardian Sougi...
[Coughing]
Our suspicions have
been confirmed...
It's the same Shikabane that
was identified four years ago
and went into hiding.
His ability to freely
manipulate car engines
using the curse
hasn't changed...
It's the Shikabane
of Tomoharu Kishibi.
Tomoharu... He's the one
you mentioned earlier...
He became a Shikabane
4 years ago.
First of all, the guys in the
car that caused his family
to get into an accident...
Were killed
one after another.
But it didn't end there.
Whenever he saw young
people behind the wheel,
he'd take control of their
car and steer it headlong
into a fatal collision -
one that echoed the crash
his family perished in.
But that was
4 years ago...
It's one after another
with you Kougan sect people...
You sure work hard.
But I have way too much energy
being that I've been asleep
for going on
four years now.
Huh?
Hey... Takamasa...
and if it isn't
little Itsuki...
Well, well.
Tomoharu...
The lovestruck contracted monk
and his Shikabane Hime...
This is quite the reunion,
wouldn't you say?
I gotta tell ya...
If I'd known back then
what I know now...
But thankfully I met someone who
gave me quite the education...
who told me about
the Kougan sect...
and about Shikabane Hime.
So, Itsuki... Since
you're a Shikabane, too...
that makes us the
same, doesn't it?
Tomoharu... Following
our philosophy...
I must kill you.
Do you think you
can this time?
What happened
to those scars?
The ones from
4 years ago...
This may be your last chance,
so don't screw it up!
What...
What is this?
What is he doing?
Takamasa...
Itsuki...
Tomoharu!
Stop this!
What... What happened
to me, Takamasa?
You died
in a car accident.
What are you
talking about, man?
That's crazy!
I was... in the car
with my parents
and my little sister
and we were all driving
to visit my
Grandma's house.
Then all of a sudden,
we saw a bright flash in
front of us on the road...
Wait... those idiots
drove right at us
and they were blocking
the entire road...
So Dad tried turning
the wheel and...
We were...
we were all killed...
by those idiots...
Stupid kids...!
They were driving
too damn fast!
None of that has anything
to do with these people!
They're not any different
than the others.
All they care about is how
fast they can drive...
And those bitches that like
to watch and cheer them on
are all the same.
It's more important
to them to show off
and try to make
themselves look cool...
no matter who else is on the
road It feels good to kill them!
Tomoharu, how could you...
Look... It's too late.
Takamasa!
What do you think
you're doing, Itsuki?
Takamasa,
give me the order!
The order? For what?
It was the same order
I had given to her
so many times before...
"Kill the Shikabane."
But I didn't
really understand...
Knowing that he was a
Shikabane, somewhere in my mind,
the reality of death
felt distant...
Takamasa!. Please...
give me the order!
Itsuki... I can't.
I won't... tell the girl that
I've fallen in love with...
To kill the only person that
I ever called my best friend!
Itsuki, please...
I just can't...
But...
I can't bring myself
to let you do that!
Takamasa...!
Why don't I just
kill the both of you?!
Watch out!
Itsuki!
Please don't look
at me, Takamasa...
I don't want you to
see me like this...
Itsuki?
You monster!
What the hell?!
Itsuki?
Help me!
Was it that I didn't want
Itsuki to kill Tomoharu?
Looking back at it now,
I'm sure that Takamasa
was simply incapable of seeing
me as Itsuki at the time.
In those moments,
her form...
My form...
Takamasa...
Takamasa!
Takamasa, I'm sorry!
It was all my doing...
That's not true...
The sins were mine
and mine alone.
I couldn't understand that
Shikabane Hime were aberrations.
I considered them
to be like humans.
It was nothing but a
punishment for my mistakes.
I can now say...
Itsuki,
kill Tomoharu.
Okay!
What's the matter?
Sir, look!
Tagami?!
[Music]
You know, contrary
to what you expect,
life as a human can
be most inconvenient...
Try as you might,
however you choose,
you can't escape them...
"Nature and Regrets."