[Music]
Ouri, it's you!
Makina!
Hey! Makina!
Where are you?
That injury...
it should've killed him.
No, you can't
take him on!
I know
I can do it.
How about this...?
Which Brother do you
like the most, Ouri?
You think a little
too much of yourself, kid...
To actually inflict
some harm on me...
a human like yourself would
have to use a surprise attack.
Ouri!
Makina,
don't do it!
It's disgraceful...
I know this is nothing
more than the illusion
of Brother's face,
but I can't help
the way I feel about it.
And like I said before,
no one else should have
to deal with this!
Ouri, listen...!
Don't just toss
that thing...!
Focus your attention
on the tip of the staff!
You're just sad
little humans
confined in your small,
weak bodies.
I almost feel
bad for you.
Not bad enough
to let you live.
Ouri...
That was a
Zadan technique...
It's a fighting style the
Kougon Sect's contracted
monks learn during
their training...
So when he beat
Ena earlier,
it wasn't because
he caught him off guard.
But how can Ouri do that when
he hasn't even completed
the full training?
A Zadan technique isn't the
power of the monk himself...
It's the act
of borrowing power
from the stars and the gods,
those who protect him.
Looks like this kid here is
receiving a lot of protection...
from a lot
of different places.
Oh, please...
Would you stop hiding
and come out to play...?
You want to be happy,
don't you?
Happy...? To be
killed by you?!
The greatest happiness is
to die happy, of course.
All should
understand this.
For can anything else
truly be called happiness?
So you think those like me
should have just stayed dead?!
Don't let him get
to you, Saki...
He's with
the Seven Stars
and knows how to
manipulate people's minds.
I guess all these guys
are just the puppets.
Ouri!
No puppet here, you brat...!
This one is the real me!
Seven Stars...!
I thought Ouri had killed you!
[Laughter]
I can't be killed...
That's precisely what the Seven
Stars are, you foolish thing.
Ena manipulates corpses
and transfers his soul
into each one of them.
You can consider
all of them his spare bodies.
Spares?!
He's right. Mine
is a free existence.
I'm not confined to a body
like the rest of you!
[Laughter]
Then I'm just gonna have
to kill all the bodies
that you're planning
on switching to.
That's a smart move, kid!
Th-they're crazy!
They're all out
of their minds...
Don't your hearts ache seeing
the faces of these people?
No!
Say what you want to because
you're out of spare bodies now!
Toya...! What are
you waiting for?!
I was only
waiting to see
how long you planned
on fooling around, Ena.
I have brought
a present for you.
Thank you so much, Toya.
Darn... I didn't
wanna use this body.
It just that I like
it so very much...
I'd hate for it
to get damaged.
Don't act...
innocent...
That body's just stolen from
another corpse someplace, right?
Your words are
so very hurtful to me...
I think I'll
punish you first.
Take... this!
Sadahiro!
That looked like
it was gonna be more than
just a punishment to me.
[Laughter]
In order to achieve
a more beautiful,
more perfect existence,
I myself created this body
through the gathering and
use of many, many corpses.
This body really
is the best.
You might not think much
of my curse's power now...
But I swear I won't
miss this time.
Let me take this...
You're my
contracted monk...
You call me Makina
and we work together.
Look at that.
Such a beautiful friendship
between a dead person
and a living one...
I'm telling you, you should
abandon everything too,
like I did.
You can evolve into
something more beautiful.
Something so much
stronger than this.
You think the dead
need to evolve?
Makina!
Your regrets are a useless
match for my curse...
What do you say
we test my theory.
Seven Stars!
Makina...
No, no, no!
That's a useless attack...
This high-speed spinning
will grind your fingers
until you have nothing
left but your palm.
I wonder
if you'll push
until it strips you all
the way down to your wrist.
I will say that kind of
destruction would be perfect
for recreating you and giving
you to Hokuto, though.
Are you okay, Ouri?
His Rune is being absorbed.
What?! She actually stopped
the spinning for a moment?!
How can that be?!
Are her fingers
regenerating faster
than they can
be scraped away?!
No Shikabane can
regenerate that fast...
It's as if she has an ability
to regenerate infinitely...
I get it!
I know what this is!
It's my curse!
This isn't
an ordinary curse.
My power comes from
two regrets, not just one!
Beautifully...
More beautifully...
The true beauty...
This isn't me.
It isn't me!
The real me is...
The real me is gone!
Stop it! Stop it!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You thought if you
abandoned your body
you could become
someone else.
This isn't me.
It's not even not.
And you think that this is a
beautiful, perfect existence?!
No... No... No...
I will never abandon
myself to anything...
not 'til the day I destroy
every last writhing one of you.
[Gun firing]
Makina? Ouri?
Good evening,
mademoiselle.
What does
death mean to you?
Go on...
It's the most beautiful
thing imaginable.
The greatest
happiness we can feel.
That's precisely correct.
It seems I've finally met
someone who shares my sentiment.
I see how beautiful
Makina Hoshimura is,
and I've
begun to realize
there's only
one reason for it:
she's dead...
Death is beautiful.
I adore it.
I don't want to live
this ordinary life.
I should be special.
Like Ouri and Makina.
They get to be
on the other side.
Why do I have to live this
ordinary, boring existence?
You don't. I'll give you
something wonderful.
Now...
become... happy.
You're capable
of anything now.
And at the peak of your
happiness, you'll die.
This is ecstasy...
[Laughter]
Don't push yourself.
You need to rest a while.
How are you feeling?
I think I'm all right...
I have to get used
to this kinda thing.
My name's Akira Tooka.
Are you my senior?
I think so. I've been with
this guy here for 3 years
working on everything
under the sun.
Sounds like you're a little
unhappy with that, Akira...
I guess you've gotten close
to your hundred and eight.
I hope you'll be making
it up to Heaven soon.
Ouri!
Makina?!
Are you out there?!
It's better if you didn't
tell anyone you saw us here.
And we won't tell anyone
about your curse, either.
We're after the
traitor monk right now,
so we better go...
Later!
If they're after Akasha...
then when it comes
to humans...
Can she kill them?
The Seven Stars are different
from the normal Shikabane
we're used
to dealing with.
They have a clear intention
behind their actions
and always work
in a group.
It is quite clear
that their purpose
is to harm
the Kougon Sect.
While they are
the Seven Stars...
You must remember that they
are nothing but Shikabane...
like all the others
you have faced.
Two stars out of seven
have fallen.
Now we are to set up
a defense perimeter
around this head temple
and wipe out
the remaining Stars.
Begin preparations.
This is an imperial ordinance
from his Grace Dai- Sojo.
Excuse me...!
Ouri!
Whoa! Ouri's
got some guts.
Blurting that out when he just
joined the sect... impressive.
I hope he's not scolded
in front of everyone.
I don't think
that their goal
is just to come
after the Kougon Sect.
It has to be something bigger,
but the question is what?
Restrain yourself,
Dai-Sozu Kagami...!
Remember you're only here due
to extraordinary circumstances.
But I've actually
crossed paths
with the Seven Stars
more than once...
and with that traitor monk
running around with them...
Restrain yourself!!
Dai-Sozu Kagami...
My apologies,
your Grace.
I am curious as to what you
perceive to be the true goal
behind the Seven Stars.
The Dai-Sojo is
talking to me...
You can't answer,
can you?
The Seven Stars
consider us their enemy.
It's as simple as that.
I don't have an answer.
Are you perhaps suggesting
that we should not fight them?
No. We will
destroy them...
as it is our wish.
Check him out...
"As it is our wish"...
I broke into
a cold sweat...
Thought I was
gonna pass out.
Did I do something wrong?
I mean after all I was
only voicing my opinion...
Are you brain dead?!
An imperial ordinance
is an order.
Once it's issued we
just have to obey it...
We're not allowed to pose
questions or defy the order.
You mean it's like this
was passed down to us
by God or something?
Exactly. The Dai-Sojo
is equal to God...
That's the way it is.
That's the way
it'll always be...
And don't forget he's also
the only person in the sect
who can carry out the code
to create Shikabane Hime
in a complete manner.
That's...
It's something
Keisei left behind.
Wouldn't you
like to keep it?
As a memento?
Oh, no. I don't think that's
what he would have wanted.
I think he would have
preferred you to keep it.
Which makes sense,
because if you're
to learn a Zadan technique,
you're going
to need a catalyst.
But I don't know...
Just take it, Ouri.
What?
She's right.
You put that robe on and who
knows, you might just end up
being a little less
of a burden to everyone.
She didn't mean that...!
I mean, come on, that's not what
you were saying right, Makina?
Oh, whatever...
What's going on?
No way, that's...
That's the Breast Goddess?!
It's amazing... I went
to see her earlier, too.
Yeah, well,
good for you...
Why are you sulking
around like a big baby...?
I just never realized that
she was this beautiful before.
That's not the Breast
Goddess, Sumitori.
What do you mean?
It's not the craziest
thing in the world
when a girl
comes back to school
after the holiday break
looking totally different.
I can't explain it.
She's different...
My Breast Goddess just
wasn't as full of confidence
as she is now...
I liked her because she was
fragile, like she always seemed
to be the slightest
bit troubled by things.
Damn... Where
the hell is Ouri?!
He should've been here!
Don't know. I never know
what that guy is up to.
I'm done.
What? What're you
talking about, baby?
We were just getting
warmed up here.
I've never done this kind
of thing with a boy before...
And I thought it would
make me feel happier...
This isn't good...
I have to become
happier and happier.
What are you?
Some kind of tease?
I want you to
become happy, too.
What?
This is ecstacy, Nozomi...
Thank you so mu-...
It's so wonderful...
Nozomi! What
happened to you?
Where have you been?
I feel unrelenting
happiness now.
Like any wish
I make will be granted.
Happiness?
Do you want me
to make you happy, too?
Is it your time?
Lock the door
behind you.
What...? Then it's
okay if I come inside?
'Course it is...
It's not like there're things
in here I don't want you to see.
So, I'll just come on in.
Is this the only kind
of stuff you eat?
The truth is it doesn't matter
if I eat or not since I'm dead.
But I get hungry.
From time to time.
Like anyone.
It's strange,
isn't it?
But I didn't realize that the
contracted monk has to pay
for all your stuff.
Providing for your Shikabane
Hime is part of your job.
Do you feel
like quitting now?
Of course not!
Are you serious
about all of this?
Accepting my curse
and contracting with me?
If I use my curse, your body
is going to get weakened,
and in the worst case...
The worst possible scenario
is that you could die.
I've made up my mind!
Uh...
I mean... Uh...
I... I've made
my decision.
I loved Keisei so very much,
and I love him even more now.
Uh...
Don't worry
about it...
Nozomi...
Uh...
What are you doing?
Say, Ouri...
Will you
kill me... please?
[Music]
I know you've known
it for a while.
It's such a simple thing
that it leaves no room
to misunderstand it...
But you are the
only one who can grant it...
her "Mundane Wish."