[Music]
'Kay, it's here.
Makina,
are you alright?
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm sorry for not being
able to protect Keisei.
Ever since that night,
I've wanted
to say that to you.
I am...
So sorry.
Please don't cry...
It wasn't your fault.
There's no need
to apologize.
Here. Dry your eyes...
Crying doesn't really
seem to suit you.
I'm not a fragile
little girl.
What are you doing here?
And what's with your clothes?
What the hell
were you thinking...?
Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
What do you mean...?
Takamasa was
helping me train
so I could get better
at this whole monk thing.
When I got word that
you might be in trouble,
I left as soon as
possible... to save you.
Keisei did everything he could
to keep you out of harm's way!
But here you are...
Sticking your nose where
it doesn't belong again!
I don't understand...
You and I are supposed
to work together!
We didn't have much of a choice
when we made this arrangement.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Keisei will always be
my contracted monk.
If you don't
let me help you...
You'll die.
I died a long time ago.
Tell me... Why did you
become a contracted monk?
What?
What's your reason
for fighting?
My reason...?
You know why...
It's because my
brother asked me to...
He asked you to?
You would put your
life on the line
just because someone
asked you to?
No... You're taking
it the wrong way...
I...
I did it for you, too.
Hey! What are
you doing here?!
How'd you
get in here...?
This isn't
the kind of place
where you can come
and go as you please.
Kurai...?
What happened to you?
You two... What did you
do to Kurai?
Let me explain...
We had to stop him...
Don't you move!
How on earth did he enter the
purification chamber so easily?
He's a Shikabane...
He is the brother
of the late Gon Sojo Tagami.
I am Honda, an Inspector.
What the hell
is he doing?
Open, my zadan technique...!
On-Jiri-Chei-Sowaka...
That crazy bastard!
He's summoning
more Shikabane!
Sadahiro!
What...?!
Lotus Flower!
So this is the backyard of
the Kougon Sect's head temple.
The air appears to
be tense somehow.
Yes, I sense it, too...
A purifier used
to exorcise defilement.
We mustn't stay here
for too long,
we're incapable
of fighting it off.
What do you mean, Isaka?
He means that we'll
be unable to move...
Pretty boy...
Isaka is correct...
Every one of you is at risk.
Nothing like this has
ever been attempted.
Maybe we're
being reckless.
Well, we'll just
have to leave
before things become
too dangerous for us.
I can see the mirror...
It's broken...
I want the mirror.
It seems that Hokuto
has already found her.
Zadan technique.
Get out of here!
Isaka!
Eyes of Asura!
They disappeared...?
We had'em!
They escaped
into a trench!
Stop it...! What are
you doing to her?
Purifying the defilement
of this Shikabane
is no longer an option.
That's not true!
Murdering one of our own
is simply... Unforgivable.
We have no choice
but to kill her.
He wasn't one of yours!
He was a Shikabane!
Monks within
the Kougon Sect
abandon petty regrets
and obsessions...
They become enlightened!
They never become Shikabane!
You're really gonna pretend like
this has never happened before?
Stay right there.
What is the meaning of this?
Please allow my fellow
disciple to come with us...
His Shikabane Hime as well.
The two of them are innocent.
Your fellow disciple?
Ouri Kagami has been
training with my master...
Over the past several
months if you must know.
His Grace Sojo Umehara?
I'm sure you're aware...
That the contract
between the two of them
is only a temporary one.
Temporary or not, Ouri does
have a contract with her.
What?
By the way, Makina...
Congratultions...
You just love to hear the sound
of your own voice, don't you?
Here...! Catch!
Unbelievable!
I'm shaking in my boots.
You know it wouldn't kill
you to say thanks, Makina.
I found her.
What is this?
Looks like a trench...
A space created
by a Shikabane.
Is there a way in?
This is the work of
a powerful Shikabane.
Whoever's responsible knew how
to infiltrate this sacred place.
Where are we?
What do we do now?
Don't panic!
Well, well.
I wasn't expecting
so many guests
for such a
small gathering...
But that's okay.
Akasha...
The traitor monk.
Before we get started, allow
me to introduce our hosts
for the evening.
These people are indeed
enemies of your pathetic world
and all who
dwell within it.
They are the Seven Stars!
It's been a long time...
Daughter of Hoshimura.
I wonder if you remember.
You begged and
pleaded in puddles
of your own blood that day,
wriggling on the
floor with what was left
of your arms and legs,
asking to be forgiven.
She doesn't remember.
Her fear has
made her forget.
Makina!
Where do you
think you're going...?
Just sit back
and enjoy the show.
What's the matter,
daughter of Hoshimura?
I thought you were
going to destroy us?
Every one of you...
Played a part in killing me.
And my family...
They're dead...
I'm dead.
Destroying every last
one of you is my goal...
And I will
accomplish it...!
I'll kill all of you!
Destroying the Seven Stars...?
This is your obsession?
You're so ridiculous.
There's no way
you can destroy us
with such a meager
and petty obsession.
Why can't she defeat you?
Say what you want...
But you came back to this
world because of your regrets!
You're just Shikabane!
That's where you're
wrong, my boy.
Our actions aren't
based on regrets.
Those in the Seven
Stars act this way...
Because it is our nature.
What...? The Seven Stars are
near the purification chamber?
Our sources have
confirmed it, yes.
Sojo Takamine...
I hope you understand why we
cannot permit you to leave.
The purification chamber
is a short distance
from the head temple.
It is our responsibility
to protect Dai-Sojo.
May I remind you that Makina
Hoshimura is in the chamber...
As are many
of our soldiers.
We can't simply
abandon them!
Flesh, what
are you doing...?
Explain yourself!
I'm so sorry!
I am! Umehara
threatened me!
He told me that if
I didn't help him
that he'd make me eat
a whole tree frog!
She's a liar! Don't listen
to a single word she says!
I'm not lying...!
Why are you throwing
me under the bus...?
You're the liar!
What can I say...?
I'm a man, Flesh.
That's just
how we're built.
Can't fight mother nature.
Umehara...
You are supposed to be on
assignment in the mountains.
I was... But it would seem
I'm needed elsewhere.
So... Should the two
of us pack our things
and head back
to camp...?
Or go greet
the Seven Stars?
Umehara!
There's something I'm
gonna need to borrow.
I promise I'll get it back
to you as soon as I can.
I need the tool
for exorcisms.
You can't...! Its too
important to our history,
his Grace Dai Sojo even
sealed it himself.
Now, now. No need
to get snippy.
Besides, I'm the only
one who can handle it.
It'll be fine.
Nature is a scream from
inside the heart...
It yearns to be set free.
It's a person's
true spirit.
True spirit?
Regrets are nothing more
than the subtle obsessions
that occur right before someone
exhales their last breath.
Nature is a feeling that has
been growing and festering
inside a person's soul from the
moment they entered this world.
This isn't something
they can just control...
It's a part of
who they are.
Every human suppresses it.
They live in denial
of their true nature.
But we, the Seven Stars,
released that nature.
We live according to it.
By accepting what lies
within our hearts
and not denying
who we are...
we're the true humans.
Witnessing this hollow
attempt at vengeance,
pitifully based on regret...
Makes me think we
were wrong about her.
I'm not gonna let
you kill Makina!
That poor little girl has been
dead for quite some time...
She's nothing more
than a Shikabane.
Even so, I will
protect her.
Do you have feelings
for that Shikabane...?
She's nothing more than a
carcass with guilt, right?
You're so quick to fight for
her, even in an unfair battle.
But there isn't
a reason for it.
I find this all incredibly
fascinating, young man.
Perhaps,
this is your nature?
In the depths of your heart
you feel it, don't you?
You could be a Shikabane
with this nature.
I'm sorry for not being
able to protect Keisei.
I can't thank you enough for all
that you've done for me, Makina.
Spending my days
fighting alongside
you means everything to me.
The impact we made is
worth all of this...
And more.
Please don't cry...
In my last moments,
I want to see you smile.
Smile for me... Makina.
No.
That's not it.
I...
I couldn't...
Keisei...
Keisei!
Well...
This is a twist.
Have you awoken...?
Daughter of Hoshimura?
Keisei...
My, you have so such strength
for such a puny regret.
Keisei.
I'll admit I'm impressed.
You murdered him!
You're the ones
who killed Keisei!
What incredible form...!
She's casting a
powerful curse.
I no longer do
this for me.
I don't carry these guns
for my family, either...
I carry them for Keisei!
I'm not like you!.
I never will be!
Die!
The mirror.
It's still broken...
She was able to knock down
a cursed Shikabane Hime
with a single blow.
Hokuto is such a mystery.
It's safe to say you don't
want to piss the girl off.
Not if you value your
existence, that is.
Unlike any other Shikabane,
she doesn't act on regrets,
obsession, or nature.
Her life came to
an end too abruptly,
and now, as a Shikabane...
Connecting with others, being
involved with other people...
In her eyes,
this is as important
as learning
the meaning of life.
However, her way of connecting
means killing those people.
She is the epitome
of death itself.
Show it to me.
This is exactly why she's
the symbol of the Seven Stars.
She's why... They exist.
Sorry to crash the party...
So this is what passes for a
strong trench these days, huh?
How could a half-witted mortal
break the barrier of my trench?
There's no need to resort
to name calling, Wrinkles.
Looks to me like this
game is over, Seven Stars.
Akasha!
Perfect timing.
Who is that?
Maybe a monk...?
But I don't know him.
He looks familiar.
It can't be...
Sadahiro!
What the hell...?
I hadn't planned on
an impromptu reunion.
Unfortunately...
Being in such close proximity
to the purification chamber...
Makes it near impossible for the
Seven Stars to use their power.
Not to mention...
The presence of the youngest
Genpaku of the Kougon Sect.
A descendant of one of the
Ten Great Holy Families.
The only living Sojo
capable of handling Acala,
the divine sword
of exorcism.
And, of course,... The man
who more than likely possesses
the strongest
zadan technique.
If we are to fight
against them...
We must fight their
Shikabane Hime as well.
The Seven Stars
must prepare themselves
to make difficult choices.
Makina Hoshimura...
From this day forward...
We, the Seven Stars will
view you as an enemy.
Our malevolent
and beloved enemy.
But I feel
I should tell you...
This outcome was our desire
from the very beginning.
The mere fact that
you stand before us...
Proves that your existence is
part of the Seven Stars plan.
Remember that.
Upon our next encounter,
we hope you'll realize
what that truly means.
Mark my words,
I will annihilate
every last one of you.
You took everything
I had away from me...
The least I can do
is return the favor.
I am Makina, a
Shikabane Hime...
And I will destroy you!
[Music]
Would you say you're
in love with her?
Are you aware of what lies
underneath her tough exterior?
Go ahead...
Don't dry yours eyes,
sit and cry for her...
She's your
"Beloved Aberration."