[Music]
You murdered him!
You're the ones
who killed Keisei!
I no longer
do this for me.
I don't carry these guns
for my family, either...
I carry them for Keisei!
I'm not like you!
I never will be!
Okay, you two...
Better go change into
your new training outfits.
I didn't think we'd get
dressed in the same place.
Not good...
Definitely not good.
She's taking off
her clothes
without giving it
a second thought.
Am I the only one that
has a problem with this?
Is everything okay, Ouri?
I'm fine.
I just figured
since our training is
about to get intense that...
I'd get myself super
psyched up, you know?
How optimistic.
What?
With everything
that's happened,
I thought you'd be sad.
I was...
I mean, I am sad.
When it happened...
I cried like a baby.
No matter what I did...
I couldn't stop. ...
It wasn't pretty.
My nose wouldn't
stop running.
You know, you might
wanna try crying more...
It could make you
feel better.
No matter
how much I cry...
It only makes me
feel worse.
Oh, wow... That was
painful to watch.
Who's there...?
Show yourself.
I'm Saki Amase.
But most people
just call me Saki.
My name is
Rika Aragami...
I'm a Gon-Sojo as well as
Saki's contracted monk.
Your brother and I trained
together under Sojo Takamine.
I guess you could say
we were classmates.
May I ask why you're here?
We're making sure you don't
try anything funny with Makina.
Keep those hands
to yourself.
Anything funny...?
What do you mean by that?
It's obvious what
I meant by that.
You said you have
feelings for her.
What? I never said
anything like that.
I'm just trying to protect
and care for her
the way Brother did.
That's all!
We heard everything from
outside the Shikabane's trench.
You were listening in?
You're one nosy kid,
you know that?
Kid?! Who do you
think you are?!
Why does the brother of Keisei
Tagami still have a contract
with the Hoshimura girl?
The Seven Stars have
made it abundantly clear.
We've become
targets, gentlemen.
We have to strengthen
our defenses.
The defiled ones
in question
not only entered the
purification chamber,
but the grounds surrounding
the head temple...
The fault lies
with your people.
As if that weren't
bad enough,
the Seven Stars escaped from
the contracted monks you sent.
Not shocking... Shikabane
Hime are just as defiled
as the ones they
have sworn to fight.
I say we must find a new way
to try to save the lives
of innocent civilians without
the use of Shikabane Hime!
That's enough!
We don't have time
for this discussion!
Explain to us what
happened to Umehara.
How could such a respected Sojo
be responsible for this blunder?
I permitted him.
Whether Makina Hoshimura
forms a strong bond
with her new contract
monk is irrelevant...
As is her ability to
return to the philosophy
of the Kougon Sect.
Umehara was ordered by
me to see it through.
If Makina returns
to the fold...
then Ouri Kagami...
Shall keep his
contract with her,
be accepted into
the Kougon Sect
and granted the title of
Dai-Sozu or a similar ranking.
But sir...! There is
no precedent for that!
Instead of relying
on Shikabane Hime,
we have to consider
our other options!
I find it hard to believe
that one little girl
can fight these Shikabane
all by herself!
His Grace Dai-Sojo has
given the ordinance.
From this point on...
We're going to focus on training
you in battle scenarios.
As far as your weapon; you
wanted a monk staff, right?
Yes... Just like the
one Brother used.
I hope you know
it won't matter
how much or
how hard you train.
You'll never defeat a Shikabane,
let alone the Seven Stars.
Destroying Shikabane
isn't your responsibility.
If you get hurt,
your Shikabane's life
is put in danger.
Think of yourself as a battery
for your Shikabane Hime.
If Umehara was really a
battery, he'd be an N,
one of the smallest
batteries on the market.
You shut your mouth?
How would you know
what size I am?
An N battery, really?!
My point: the job
of a contracted monk
is to not get killed.
Getting you to master
the basics of combat
is a good way to do that.
Yes, sir.
Makina, however...
Will be undergoing a
different type of training
before she's able
to join you.
What?
The bond with her previous
contracted monk...
Must be broken.
Looks like you'll
be the first one up...
Enjoy yourself.
All right!
Just don't forget;
the boy is mine.
Oh, you mean her
contracted monk?
I'd love to...
But even though he doesn't
particularly inspire me
to create a painting
or write a symphony...
I can't promise...
that I won't kill him.
Don't tell me that you're
really going to send Ena alone?
You have a problem
with me going alone?
If Makina Hoshimura is indeed
an enemy of the Seven Stars,
you should find a
way to defeat her.
Believe it or not,
our actions the other night
served their purpose...
But this time,
it will be different...
I will defeat Makina, using
a method I find suitable...
This isn't just a game for
you to act out your desires.
Seven Stars This
is just his nature.
Nature?
As I've said before...
Obsessions are
for lesser beings.
The Seven Stars are
more highly evolved.
Within the depths of the soul
there lies a hidden potential,
one that cannot
be controlled.
A person is defined by
it; it is their nature.
What humanity suppresses...
We embrace and are
thereby vastly superior.
Ena, for example, has an
undeniable yearning for beauty.
He is compelled to rescue
people from obscurity
by making their
deaths significant.
It is his nature
to create beauty.
Do you get it now?
We act because it is
the right thing to do...
Following our nature
is worth everything...
Even if it results
in our death.
Just stay out of our way.
Akasha... Do you
really believe
you'll be able to lure the
daughter of Hoshimura
and the others out?
I'm acquainted
with a Shikabane...
A useful fellow whom I
haven't sealed in my casket
for one reason; he
gets the job done.
He's the perfect bait for
those surrounding Hoshimura.
I understand...
If she comes out, she'll be
playing right into our hands.
But if she decides
to stay behind,
her friends won't be
there to protect her...
It's a win-win situation.
Hokuto... I've got
my eyes on you.
Don't underestimate
these arrows...
If one hits you,
it'll hurt!
You're Makina's current
contracted monk, aren't you?
Other bonds will be nothing
more than obstacles
when she exerts her
strength and energy.
There's no need
to worry, Ouri...
Breaking the bond doesn't
mean she'll forget
what she and your
brother shared.
It'll just be harder for her
to recollect certain things...
This will help her let go
of the past and move forward.
Makina feels there
isn't a reason
to break the bond
with Keisei,
so she'll try to keep
it no matter what.
That's the curse.
It's hard to look
at the bond
between Makina and
Brother that way.
Though you showed us how
tremendous your power can be...
That power is a curse.
I'm sure you know that a curse
can give you the ability
to turn regret or
obsession into strength.
But regardless
of the reason,
if a Shikabane Hime
is performing curses...
That tells us she's
only a step away
from reverting
into a Shikabane.
Not to mention that she
puts those around her,
including her contracted
monk in danger.
The cause of your
curse is obvious.
You have regrets toward your
previous contracted monk.
Breaking your bond to him is
the only way to purify the Rune
that rots within.
Understand?
Do you really think you
can do this, Makina?
I will defeat
the Seven Stars.
For as long as I can remember,
that's all I've wanted to do...
And I know Keisei
is counting on me.
Let's get this over with.
Come now. You know this
isn't what you really want.
Be honest.
You still miss him.
This isn't real...
It's just an illusion...
A hallucination brought
on by exhaustion.
If you give up your
ties with Keisei...
What will be left of him?
Turning away from
such a sacred bond...
Shouldn't that be
out of the question?
But I died and
became a Shikabane...
My family and I were murdered in
cold blood by the Seven Stars.
It's my duty
to destroy them.
And what of him?
Ever since Keisei was
murdered before your eyes...
No... Long before
his passing...
Having him by your side was the
reason you fought these battles.
He meant absolutely
everything to you.
You're right...
I cared for him...
And I couldn't protect him.
But I have to do this.
If I'm going to avenge him, I
don't have any other choice.
You're not going to
break the bond...
You know you won't.
I owe it to him...
Who do you think is responsible
for all of this...?
Look deep inside
yourself, Makina.
Me... It's me.
Makina?
Everything is exactly
how it should be.
You finished
breaking the bond?
Saki! Wait a minute!
Stop right there!
The Kougon Sect tells
us it's our duty
to kill as many Shikabane
as possible, right?
Saki!
Saki?
Sorry...
I couldn't do it.
Don't tell me it
wouldn't bother you.
What if you were to die and
I had to break my bond with you?
I don't think I have
what it takes to do that.
A traffic accident?
Yep... The truck just came
out of nowhere and bam...!
I died almost instantly or at
least, that's how I remember it.
But... Well, then...
How did you have time
to remember anything?
I asked myself that question
a lot in the beginning.
I was told that having regrets
or obsessing over something
turns a person
into a Shikabane.
But before I died, I was
just an ordinary teenager.
All I cared about was...
Candy and ice cream...
Nothing else
really mattered.
Now I know my reason for
coming back to this world.
Oh yeah?
I never got the chance to
do anything with my life.
You know, like go to college,
take a roadtrip with friends,
fall in love -
that kind of stuff.
To experience new,
exciting things...
To find something they
view as priceless.
These are things that
people feel they need to do
before they die...
And I never got
to do any of them.
So that's my regret.
An ordinary teenage girl who
was told to fight against things
that go bump
in the night.
I was so afraid.
I begged and pleaded
with the Kougon Sect
to give me a contract with
the strongest monk available.
You're Takamasa
Sougi, am I right?
What?
The heir to the
strongest warrior monk
with the Genpaku title?
Yeah... Do I know you?
May I see your hand?
Why did you bite me?!
Look at the blood!
Why would you do that?!
We are those
who have lost awareness
and we require your help
in finding salvation.
We... need those who are
familiar with the philosophy.
There... Now we
have a contract.
From this point on...
You are going to be
my contracted monk.
'Kay...
I may not be the strongest
Shikabane Hime out there,
but I will do everything in
my power to protect you...
Promise...
I'm sorry. But what exactly
are you talking about?
His father died without ever
telling him about this world...
He was just a
high school student
that had never
been in a fight.
That is before I came
into the picture anyway.
You must have
felt so stupid!
How funny!
Good job, Itsuki!
You really know
how to pick 'em!
I get the feeling
she's being sarcastic.
[Laughter]
Checking the restoration
levels of Shikabane Hime
is an important
duty of any Sojo...
Dirty job, but
someone's gotta do it!
When Rika said
that Makina was going to break
her bond with Brother...
I knew that it was going
to be difficult for her...
The two of them were
really close after all.
Honestly...
I know it sounds awful,
but I was relieved.
I know there isn't a chance
I could ever have a relationship
with her like the one
she and Brother had.
I've got some big shoes
to fill, that's for sure.
Breaking their bond
makes it easier...
For everyone...
I think things will
start to get better now.
Takamasa!
Have you told Itsuki that you're
madly in love with her yet?
Ouri...
It seems that you're forgetting
a very important thing.
You have to understand that the
girl standing in front of you
is a Shikabane Hime.
She's no longer
a human being...
She's merely an aberration that
exists only to kill Shikabane...
Nothing more... No matter
how much you think otherwise.
Aberration?
These are part
of the price I paid
when I couldn't
comprehend that fact.
And take my word for it,
I was not the only one
to pay that price...
Not by a long shot.
Shikabane Hime
are aberrations...
They became
powerful by dying.
But their power comes at the
expense of their humanity.
Almost doesn't seem
worth it in my opinion.
What is it that you want
from your Shikabane Hime...?
Is it power...?
Maybe love?
Unfortunately, you'll
never acquire both.
I'd consider myself lucky
if I was able to get one.
So you're saying if I want
to harness Makina's power...
You need to let go of whatever
is in your heart now...
Before it's too late.
Oh, gross!
What was that?
What's going on?
Itsuki and Flesh must have
caught Master sneaking
around the
ladies room again.
They'll think of something
to even the score, I'm sure.
I just hope they don't
cause any permanent damage.
What do you mean
by permanent?
He's hopeless...
Well, I better go get him.
Okay...
That was weird.
Perhaps you have more in
common with that poor girl
than you think...
Nothing would surprise
me at this point.
Why is it so wrong
for me to see Makina
as just a normal girl
and not a monster?
I wouldn't be so careless
in labeling people...
Maybe you're the monster.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Come back, please!
Ouri Kagami... There's
something you should know.
Makina?
I'll just say it...
You're not
my contracted monk.
What? Why?
You lack ability.
But if you don't have
a contracted monk...
You'll die or
become a Shikabane!
I have a contracted monk.
Keisei is still with me...
The curse he left me keeps
the two of us connected.
But it is for me
alone to endure
You don't...
I can help you!
You're nothing but
a burden to me...
And I'm a burden to you.
The only reason you
fight is because of me.
It's not necessary.
Stop it!
You're not getting
it, are you?
If something were to happen
and you got injuries
you couldn't recover from,
they wouldn't accept you
as a contracted monk.
No.
I see.
Then you leave
me no choice.
Zadan technique,
Golden Claw!
These strings are an extension
of my nervous system.
They can trace even the
subtlest of movements...
I can control my opponent's body
down to each individual muscle.
You're not getting
away this time!
How long do we have
to keep her like this?
I don't know.
But if she continues
harboring this curse...
Her days as a Shikabane
Hime are numbered.
This is the one
from four years ago.
It's been verified.
Are absolutely
sure about that?
Fine.
Takamasa?
After four long years...
Where are we going?!
We just got information
of Shikabane activity
in our district.
The two of you can handle it.
Makina needs me.
You saw it,
right...?
Makina Hoshimura's
aberration?
I told you...
I realized that my Shikabane
Hime is an aberration...
And accepted it.
Where we're going...
I'll be able to
prove it to you.
You should...
You need to see this.
Dammit!
What? The Seven Stars
aren't enough...?
Now this Shikabane?
Takamasa.
[Music]
The lips that once
whispered love...
Now scream...
"Don't look at me!
Stay back!"...
Over and over again.
Even so, you find it
difficult not to look at...
"Itsuki's Form."