I must admit
I'm curious,
do you know
what they truly are?
They fight only to
fulfill a contract.
If they succeed in
destroying 108 Shikabane...
they can make it
into heaven.
Into heaven?
Itsuki,
you're all right!
C'mon!
Itsuki, no...
You too?
She murders
her own kind.
I am Takamasa
Sougi, Genpaku...
I am a contracted monk.
Don't move.
Umehara's
favorite disciple
is the new Genpaku
if I'm not mistaken.
For generations,
those in the Sougi family
that have become Genpaku have
proven to be fierce warriors.
According to tradition, Takamine
belongs to the Shuhou faction.
However, Umehara doesn't
work for the Shuhou
or the Shujou faction.
So he was the one sent in
to investigate Keisei, huh?
If that's the case, we
can just leave everything else
up to Genpaku and
see what happens.
We're aware of the fact
that Ouri Kagami...
has appeared during several of
the last Shikabane encounters.
I don't get it.
What about
the traitor monk?
Akasha Shishidou has
been sighted in the area.
If Sho-Sojo Tagami has anything
to do with the traitor monk...
The actions of his brother
may mean something.
According to our
extensive research...
Akasha shared a room with
Sho-Sojo Tagami years ago.
Your research
is misleading.
Tagami wasn't his
only roommate.
I shared
that room as well.
I am aware of that.
I see then...
I gotta find Akasha now.
If Keisei and Ouri
are working with him...
I'll take care of
both of them as well.
Although there are nearly
100 Shikabane Hime...
Yours remains to be
the only one permitted
to terminate human beings
as well as Shikabane.
I'm counting on you.
Have things really
come down to this?
What are
you talking about?
As of right now,
Sho-Sojo Mee-bu might have to...
If he is to discover that they
have been in communications
with the traitor monk...
More than likely, he will
neutralize Sho-Sojo Tagami.
Everything... Is for the
survival of the Kougon Sect.
From what
I know about Ouri,
he doesn't seem like the type
to get mixed up with Akasha.
But you'll kill him,
won't you?
You ready?
Itsuki is a
Shikabane Hime?
More than one Shikabane
Hime can exist?
Well...
I think there are more of us
than you think there are,
does that make sense?
What's that
teacher doing here?
I guess you could say...
He's like an added bonus.
Or a babysitter!
He's a contracted monk.
You didn't think your big
brother was the only one?
How the hell do you
know my brother?
We have a history...
He was even there
on the day...
Don't try to
interfere in this...
I have to...
Did you just
pistol whip me?
I'm not the
one interfering!
What?
The rental car...
He used it to gather all
of those people together...
Forcing them to
kill one another.
And do you
wanna know why?
To produce Shikabane!
The two of us can
take this guy down...
There's nothing you can do,
so stay out of it!
Run, Ouri! Get the
hell out of here...!
Go!
Such a shame...
Things were just starting
to get a little interesting.
At least, now we know he
isn't working with you.
Finding a way to handle it is
a problem for the Kougon Sect.
I've heard of you...
The monk who betrayed
his calling...
attacked the head temple,
stole ritual scriptures...
And murdered his
own Shikabane Hime.
Stop,
I'm blushing...
Looks like my reputation
has proceeded me.
Allow me to
introduce myself...
Former head of
Gon-Sho-Sojos...
I am Akasha Shishidou.
I just have to know...
Why would you kill your
own Shikabane Hime?
And why on earth would you be
trying to create Shikabane?
Well... I would hope
you were smart enough
to figure it out
on your own.
Then again... Your brain
is probably just as dead
as the rest of your
walking corpse.
I may not be the hero of
this story, sweetheart.
But that doesn't
make me a Shikabane.
Can you, a simple
little Shikabane Hime,
really take a human life?
I find it hard
to believe
that the Kougon Sect
would allow such a thing.
She will do whatever
she needs to do
in order to bring you to
the head temple, Akasha.
Defiled.
You gonna cry?
How dare you touch me with
those cold, dead hands of yours.
What's that?
It's a shame to waste this
on someone like you...
But you must
learn a lesson...
For laying a hand on me.
Open...
My zadan technique!
No, a zadan
technique?
On-Jiri-Chei-Sowaka...
Itsuki!
Move away!
I can't!
Lotus Flower!
There's nothing you can do,
so stay out of it!
Stay out of it...
Heard that before.
If you really want to help,
don't get involved.
What the hell
am I doing here?
I can't see the
Shikabane's brain.
If you don't
wanna die, beat it!
That girl said
the same thing.
Itsuki?
You know her,
don't you...?
Because you're both
Shikabane Hime?
I've seen her
around before...
That's all you
need to know.
Why were you
with her?
You... Said if
I got involved
that it would end up
hurting my brother.
What did you
mean by that?
Not sure if you'd
noticed, Ouri...
But this really
isn't the best time...
Answer the question!
When someone has a duty
to protect a person...
They can exert an unusual
amount of strength...
Years ago...
A monk ended up dying
because he was
betrayed by someone
he was trying
to protect.
Are you saying that
Brother might die
if I keep
getting involved?
If you were
to step in,.
the scar inside Keisei's heart
would be larger than ever.
Do you understand...?
That's why I don't want you
to come closer to our side.
It's not for
Brother's sake...
It's for your own,
isn't it?
Killing 108 Shikabane,...
Gets you into heaven,
isn't that right?
You're right... That's
the contract I agreed to.
Do you care about
anything else...?
Or is earning
your wings it?
If you wanna die,
go right ahead and die...!
But don't take my
Brother with you!
I do care.
Makina!
It's gone!
Keisei...
Do it!
Brother!
What're you doing?!
I made a promise.
What do you
mean a promise...?
A promise that puts your life
on the line for some girl...?
And makes it okay for you
to chop her arm off?
Please tell me,
what kind of promise
could be worth
all of this?
She doesn't do
this for rewards...
Not even for Heaven.
From the moment she was
resurrected as a Shikabane...
She has
only two choices.
She can either violate
the world of the living,
acting on her regrets
as a Shikabane.
Or attempt
to keep her humanity
by being a Shikabane Hime
and kill all Shikabane.
The price tag on either
of them is too great!
True... but she lives
with her choice.
My choice...
my promise...
is to stay by her side.
Keisei...
There it is.
I trust everyone else
in the rental car
made it out all right?
There was one other person,
but I haven't seen her.
Now, you're sure he called
himself the traitor monk?
I'm sure... he knew
about you as well as me.
Akasha...
Who is that,
Keisei?
Wait, don't!
Just an ordinary Souma...
The Kougon Sect's
special elixir.
If it really is him...
But what about...
Doesn't it have a
strong side effect?
I'll be fine.
Brother...
Makina...
I understand why your promise
is so important now...
I'm sorry.
Brother...
All I need is for you to
promise me this one thing...
Promise me you won't die.
Do not seek death...
but do not
fear it either...
There cannot be
life without death.
It is inescapable.
I'm sorry, little brother...
I can't promise that.
Itsuki...
Genpaku...
When did you become
in charge of this district?
Senior Tagami...
I'm sorry, I was sent here.
I see... You're here
investigating Ouri and me.
Akasha...
Its been a long time,
Senior... Hasn't it?
Makina!
You can't do anything
with your wounds.
He's using
a zadan technique.
A zadan technique?
Just like
Shikabane Hime...
Zadan is a technique
that's meant
to symbolize
the Kougon Sect.
You make yourself head monk
within the ceremonial altar...
Open a scripture using
a holy instrument...
This causes a miracle with
the help of the stars...
and infinite power.
That's a miracle?
Five years ago...
Sadahiro and I were the
only ones with the ability
to perform the
zadan technique.
This is the first time you
or that vestigial Genpaku...
have seen such an
advanced zadan, isn't it?
They are...
Shikabane.
Yes... I gave
their lives purpose.
They were fortunate enough
to become Shikabane
after killing one another
in the rental car...
I trapped them
in my zadan.
Their regrets... He's using the
Shikabane like a damn battery!
How is this any different
from the Kougon Sect
using the power
of Shikabane Hime?
I don't allow my Shikabane to
keep their pathetic feelings...
They're used
simply for power.
Take it from me,
they suffer much less in
such an unenlightened state.
You're wrong!
You murdered those kids,
not once but twice.
Making them kill each
other off in cold blood
to create Shikabane.
And the second
they resurrected,
you used them to create
that forsaken zadan.
You always had a soft spot
for the young ones, Senior...
If you love your walking
corpse this much...
it's only a matter of time
before you love Shikabane, too.
Makina!
In order to open a zadan
of that level,...
he'd need a powerful
holy instrument.
I don't know if it's
a holy instrument...
But he put out
a dark-red box.
We're gonna have to cut
nap time short, princess.
Makina, were you able to
patch things up with Ouri?
You're hilarious...
Stop kidding around and help
me break this zadan technique!
Don't try
to order me around.
Your bullets are useless.
Guns aren't necessarily
used for shooting.
That's it.
Brother!
Senior!
Keisei!
If you don't have
the mediation...
Going after the mediation
was a wise decision.
As you can see, this casket
is no ordinary instrument.
It's the blood of 108 people
at the end of their lives.
Brother!
Even just one person's regrets
can have great power
when they transform
into Shikabane.
And he said 108 people.
Simply touching the box
would cause spiritual trauma.
Any average person
would have been knocked
immediately unconscious.
Come on, Senior...
You must have known that
this was bound to happen
because of your
love for her.
You would know better
than I about a love
for Shikabane Hime,
Akasha.
Is that why...?
You betrayed everyone
within the Kougon Sect?
Because you couldn't stand
to look your Shikabane Hime
in the eyes
for one more second?
Know this, Senior...
With everything
that I have done,
I never betrayed
the Kougon Sect.
They are the deceivers.
The Kougon Sect
betrayed me.
He couldn't
have moved!
Souma!
Idiot...! Do you realize
what you've done?
The blood inside
will flow out!
Resulting in the regrets
and obsessions of 108 people
to fall on us.
If you suffer
a spiritual trauma,
your body is going
to be greatly affected too.
What can I say?
It seemed like a
good idea...
Sorry.
My trauma
doesn't compare...
The pain and suffering will be
much worse for you, old friend.
What...? That was
no ordinary bullet...
It had a zadan technique!
Of course.
Do you have
to stand so close?
Not much choice
in the matter...
I need to be this close
in order to use my zadan
with your bullets.
Sadahiro.
This is far
from over, Senior.
My Shikabane will triumph in
annihilating the Kougon Sect...
Until next time.
Is he okay?
Keisei used Akasha's mediation
as some sort of shield,
he knew that he would
suffer spiritual trauma.
At least, now we know
he isn't in alliance
with the traitor monk.
Are you relieved?
Then... There's no problem
reinstating Keisei Tagami's
position as Guardian?
Yes.
And as for, Akasha...
Will he...
be okay?
Since Keisei
refuses to do so,
I'll make the promise
in his place.
I won't let Keisei die...
I will always protect
him, no matter what.
[Music]
Humans can understand each
other because they use words?
What a joke.
Humans always get confused
by their meanings.
They're controlled by
"The False Power of Words."