[Music]
Now then...
Time to destroy you!
Because...
I will live
as a human!
Don't think you can die,
without my permission.
Because...
Because
I need you, Ouri.
Ouri!
It's gonna crash!
Late-breaking
news this hour.
We have at least
two confirmed reports
of aircraft engine failure.
No word yet if there
are any survivors.
This just in, planes crashing
within minutes of one another.
We'll keep you
updated with details
as soon the story unfolds.
The area surrounding
Ikai Station
appears to have caved in,
resulting in the damage
of buildings nearby.
Due to the emissions
of natural gas,
access has been restricted
to the general public.
This was the Seven
Star's plan all along...
Could we have
foreseen this?
Where are the
Seven Stars now?
They appear
to have vanished...
We haven't the slightest
clue where they are.
I gave the retreat order
as soon as I received word
of the crashes.
Now is not
the time to argue.
Everything they've done over
these past few months,
even the death of Senior Tagami,
has been to accomplish this.
The Kougon Sect made us believe
they were just challenging us.
We've been too busy with wild
goose chases to think otherwise.
We couldn't have known.
They've tried to invade areas
around the head temple,
while still pursuing
our contracted monks.
And Shikabane have been
created at every turn.
How could we have known
that it was all to spread their
defilement throughout the city?
Given the nature of death, there
will be a large number of them.
Shikabane produced
in Ikai City could range
from the thousands
to the ten thousands.
The longer we sit here,
the bigger the number.
Wow... This is all starting
to sound like something out
of a really cheesy
horror movie!
[Laughter]
What...? You don't think
it's even a little funny?
Shame it's not like
an action movie,
I could be
the leading lady.
For crying out loud...
Would you give it a rest?
None of us are really in
the mood for jokes, Flesh.
Why?
Have you forgotten that our
whole reason for being here
is destroy 108 Shikabane?
If there are
swarms of Shikabane,
we'll take
every single one out.
Today could be the day every
one of us goes to heaven!
Is today the day
you wanna die...?
Flesh?
We can't just leave...
There has to be a way
for us to save Ikai City.
If each Shikabane Hime
were able to kill 108,
it still wouldn't be enough.
Are you concerned about
the Shikabane Hime?
Or worried of what
may happen to you...?
Like it or not, the contracts
they've made will run out.
Eradicate the Shikabane
threat within Ikai City.
Your Grace...
This would greatly
weaken our defenses here.
We, the Kougon Sect...
Exist to protect and maintain
order within society.
How many Shikabane
Hime are available?
Eleven, sir.
They, as well as their
monks, are moving out.
If anyone needs to replenish
their weapons, do it quickly...
Understand?
Where are we going?
Into the depths of Hell.
Wow... This is going to be so
much fun, I think I might vomit.
Anything from
Makina Hoshimura?
Makina's whereabouts
have been unknown
since we separated
in the underground.
We haven't heard
from Ouri either.
Don't worry, I think the two
of them will be all right.
If I know them at all, I bet
they've destroyed another member
of the Seven Stars
and are on their way.
I hope you're right.
I'll go on my own.
I doubt you'll be
enough to stop him.
But what if ...
something were to happen?
You and I both know
that Akasha's target
isn't the head temple.
We must tend to this
matter on our own.
No one else needs
to be made aware of this,
not even his
Grace Dai-Sojo.
Is that all
you're taking?
What do you expect
us to do...?
Umehara and the others cleaned
the place out for the most part.
And finding these wasn't
easy by any means.
Do what you must...
But work quickly...
Akasha is coming.
And don't forget...
Our success may very
well rely on you.
We won't allow anyone
near that place.
Contracted monks...
Or Shikabane Hime.
Do not disappoint me.
They're inside!
Are all of you
okay in there?
Ouri!
Hanagami...!
Don't scare
us like that!
Ouri...
Get somewhere safe.
Ouri!
I'll take care of everyone
until you come for us...
Hanagami!
Ouri...
Acts like Keisei now.
He sure does.
Maybe you should've
gone with them...
They might run into Shikabane
on their way out of town.
I think the Seven Stars
on are the move.
I know where
Hokuto is going.
She's heading to a
different location.
She's going to a place I'm all
too familiar with these days.
The purification chamber.
We should go.
But Shikabane are festering
throughout the city.
You know the others will have
no problem destroying them.
This isn't just
about you anymore.
I want revenge on
the Seven Stars...
Just as much as you do.
Your Grace...
The purification chamber...
Heals a defiled
Shikabane Hime.
We have always relied
on this place...
The land is drenched
in defilement.
But isn't the only
reason for this location.
Combining the power
of the Seven Stars
with a Zadan technique,
Akasha...?
This is bordering on
just plain pathetic!
Is that you,
old friend?
Let's end this.
You got it.
How impertinent.
I'm not the man
I was before.
I will show
you no mercy!
Senior Mibu...
Listen to me,
Sadahiro.
I have no desire
to quarrel with you...
My fight is with
the Kougon Sect.
Think about
what you witnessed.
Think about what happened to
my Shikabane Hime on that day...
The fate that awaited
my beloved Hibiki.
You walked right
into a trap.
We were told it was
only a few Shikabane...
But well over 100
ambushed your group.
My Shikabane Hime was the
strongest I'd ever seen.
Even though Hazama's
bugs kept eating her...
She kept fighting...
And fighting...
She fought her hardest...
Until she destroyed
more than 108 Shikabane.
And then she...
That's enough!
You know what
happened to her...
And so does your
Shikabane Hime!
We know all too well.
That's why we not only kill
Shikabane, but human beings.
I didn't have a choice.
I wandered down this path
because I've seen
how dark the world truly is.
But I'm no traitor!
Because not everyone
is like you, Akasha!
Whose Zadan technique
is stronger...?
Let's find out!
Hokuto!
You're producing
the water again?
Just ahead from here lies
the origin of the Kougon Sect.
Then that's where
I must go now...
I'm their enemy...
Remember?
Wait!
You know where
she's going!
What are you doing
here, Sadahiro?
What's wrong?
It's just...
Some of these people
could be survivors...
And I'm shooting anyone and
anything that I see moving.
I think we're
all doing that.
There were no survivors.
At least, that's what'll be
announced in the morning.
Oh, so big.
I think we're all
in trouble now!
If we get out of this,
I'm gonna slap you.
Well done, my dear...
I expect no less from
the Shikabane Hime
they call the strongest.
Seven Stars...!
Do your worst.
Scatter about your
defilement all you like.
Every one of us swore an oath
to protect the humans
and this world.
Getting the attention of you
and your Shikabane Hime
seems to have worked.
You wish to subdue
the Seven Stars?
The time has come to end
the pitiful lives you lead.
Are you
the reserve unit?
We'd gotten word that
you'd been kidnapped...
But that doesn't appear
to be the case... Good.
Get out of our way.
I can't allow you
to go past this point...
Whether you're
Shikabane Hime or human.
What do you mean
you can't allow us?
I just saw not only Akasha,
but members of the Seven Stars
enter the
purification chamber.
We will stop them...
After we stop
the two of you.
What have we done...?
Why are you stopping us?
Unlike you, we know
how to follow orders...
No one is allowed
to get beyond this point.
What's inside the
purification chamber...?
What are you trying
to hide from us?
Are you really
that stupid?
We wouldn't have to go
through all this trouble
if we could just tell you.
Stop it,
Makina!
Akira is a Shikabane Hime,
just like you are!
She's just an enemy.
C'mon - think this through.
You've seen my Zadan
technique in action;
you know what'll happen.
Get up...! Go back...!
This is far enough.
Not until you explain
why we need to leave.
That's the least
you could do...
What's inside the
purification chamber?
Listen to me
carefully, Ouri...
Shikabane aren't the only
ones we've had to kill.
At times we've had to
resort to killing people.
Occasionally people that
try to make the existence
of Shikabane public after they
learn of it themselves...
Or others that
attempt to hide them.
I'm not talking about a couple
of people here and there...
There are dozens,
maybe even hundreds!
There was a time that
we didn't have to do this.
But times change...
We do what is necessary
for the greater good.
The world is a better place
because of the sacrifices
we make everyday.
The secret the Kougon
Sect is trying to hide...
It's really
that important?
Trust us, you don't need to
concern yourself in this matter.
Don't talk to me like
you know what's best!
Don't pretend for a second
like you two are the only ones
that have been to hell.
This whole time...
All I've ever
known is hell.
And still...
My heart tells me
that hope is not lost...
Out of my way!
That's it!
Ouri...?
Was that your...?
Zadan?
I will... Protect
Makina at all costs!
She's meant
to protect you.
A Shikabane Hime is meant to
act as a shield for her monk.
Protecting her is
just a lost cause!
My brother did everything in his
power to protect me from harm.
Deep down, I know if it wasn't
for me, he'd still be alive.
I never had the chance to repay
him for everything he did.
This is why...
This is why I must do all
that I can to protect Makina.
It's the least I can do
and Brother would
have done the same.
Sadahiro!
I'm going...
And I'm sorry.
That hurt.
You didn't even try
to dodge that, did you?
Keisei...
Looks like it was a good thing
you took in the boy after all.
Akasha.
The reign of the Kougon
Sect is at an end.
The dead will know
what freedom is
and walk the
earth once again.
Shut your mouth,
you treacherous snake!
Quite an impressive
zadan, Gon Dai Sojo.
My technique is only
known by a select few...
It purifies the area...
And eliminates any
defilement within its radius.
My zadan would render any
other's completely powerless.
Leave and take
your pets with you!
Do you consider
me an enemy, monk?
I should warn you...
If you step into this space,
you'll turn to dust...!
Do you seek death?
I am death.
Hokuto!
It isn't killing her!
Shikabane Hime scripture?
None other than.
The last volume of the scripture
on Shikabane Hime Laws...
One of the most
important and holy
amongst the Kougon
Sect archives.
This one in particular
was once stolen
from the family
of Hoshimura.
And you were crazy enough
to put that on the body
of a Shikabane?
Indeed...
What could be better than
that when creating a shield?
No one has the power
to stop Hokuto now.
Hokuto...!
Use your new strength and break
the coffin in front of you!
Makina!
I felt this way when Keisei's
rune was taken from me.
Rika, where are you?
Why?
Takamasa...
My power...
It's gone.
Takamine...
Our bond...
It can't be.
Makina....
The tie that
binds you and I...
I can't feel it anymore.
[Music]
They say killing 108 Shikabane
buys you a ticket into heaven.
She believes
fighting for others
has all been
for a greater purpose.
"One hundred and Eight lies"
are about to be revealed.