[Music]
How can this be?
Akasha must
have failed...
That's the only
explanation for this.
Oh, he succeeded.
The bonds with our
Shikabane Hime were broken...
I don't doubt for a second
your plan worked.
I never thought
this could happen...
I didn't think it was possible
to preserve the connections
all of us created.
No one thought
it could be done.
For crying out loud...
I can't believe you guys.
At least, now we know how
you really feel about us.
It's been said that the
very first Shikabane Hime
was created by the founder
of the Kougon Sect...
Most believe
this to be true.
The existence of the first
works as a catalyst,
which connects all
Shikabane Hime to their monks.
Perhaps I was fooled
into believing this.
Deep in the pit
of my stomach...
I always felt a strong
presence connecting us.
Now I know it was
the first Shikabane Hime
giving Umehara and I her
strength and power...
However.
The first isn't the only
thing connecting us to you...
A moment shared with
Takamasa is what binds us.
I see... We thought
we bound you...
With the Kougon Sect's power,
we believed we were
creating the bond,
but you were
the ones binding us.
Precisely... In the battles
that we'd face,
we wanted you
to fight alongside us...
The Kougon Sect is only a
piece of the puzzle after all.
The contract can
easily be severed...
Our will... is what
keeps us connected.
Those responsible for the
existence of Shikabane Hime...
Have always been the
Shikabane Hime themselves?
Let them try
everything they can...
No one can
eliminate our will.
Will...? Call it what
you want, ladies.
It's nothing
more than regret.
Your regrets are inferior
to our beloved nature...
Your emotions make
you weak and pathetic.
[Firing]
Help me!
I can't.
Coward.
All I wanted...
All I wanted was to spread
happiness to the world.
Death is happiness...
Death is forever.
But all of you...
Already knew...
What happiness was.
Is this really happiness?
She might be
onto something...
I never knew what true love
was until after I was dead.
I guess you could
say happiness
wasn't something
I knew the meaning of until...
I became a
Shikabane Hime.
I thought I knew
what happiness was...
I was wrong.
Toya!
Impossible...
I haven't felt Hokuto's
presence in quite sometime.
Maybe I'm the only member
of the Seven Stars left.
I cannot die...!
I won't perish...!
I will make
it through this!
No one can violate
my nature...!
No one can
destroy me!
You really think you chose
your contracted monk?
I know I did...
That's why we have the ability
to reconnect our bond again.
As long as I,...
The Shikabane Hime, wish
for the bond to remain.
This is the true power
of Shikabane Hime.
Let's do this, Ouri!
I'm ready.
Makina!
You're my enemy...!
You're Akasha's enemy!
You have to get up,
Makina!
No, Ouri.
Come on, Makina.
Your curse is
rather something...
You have quite
the wonderful ability
to regenerate infinitely.
You can battle Hokuto
on equal footing.
However, the problem is that
it takes a large amount
of rune away from
your contracted monk.
He weakens with every
second that you fight...
And this time, no one
is going to save him.
Don't listen,
Makina... I'm fine.
You're my enemy...!
You're my enemy!
Haven't you
heard the news...?
Hokuto isn't a Shikabane,
she's death itself.
Death?
Her actions have
neither a regret
or a nature fueling them...
She is the evolution of
all primitive Shikabane.
She is the death that awaits
you and the rest of this world.
Humanity doesn't stand
a chance against Hokuto.
After all,
everyone dies.
You should know that
better than anyone.
This can't be it!
You're my enemy!.
You're Akasha's enemy!
Sadahiro...?
Akira?
Akira... I figured you'd
relish the day your bond
with me came to an end...
Now I know that you'd
be lost without me
as your contracted monk.
Try not to get
the wrong idea...
I'm only here because
I haven't killed enough.
I was murdered
by monsters like these
and I intend to kill as
many as I can... Period...
That's the reason
I was brought back.
We've accepted a heavy
responsibility...
Humans who know the true
fate of Shikabane Hime
must be silenced
at any cost...
This situation requires
a different approach.
What the hell...
are you aiming for?
Lotus Flower!
Hokuto, you're not
injured, are you?
What's wrong,
Akasha...?
You look like you've
just seen a ghost.
What are they...?
And what's inside them?
These are the tombs
of all the Shikabane Hime
that have destroyed 108...
You'd think this
was a graveyard.
They're forced to live out
eternity as Destroyer Shikabane.
I see... This is where
the journey ends...
There is no heaven
for a Shikabane Hime.
Any Shikabane Hime that has
destroyed 108 Shikabane...
Rests here...
Including yours, Akasha.
What's the matter?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Akasha!
Why can't I feel you...?
Why can't I feel your rune?
Including his...
Akasha's Shikabane Hime.
Now's your
chance...! Ouri!
Makina!
Right.
Zadan technique!
I don't understand...
Why?
I promised myself I would never
create another Shikabane Hime...
I know now that
I couldn't have saved her.
A Shikabane Hime is nothing
more than an abomination
with regrets and obsessions
from this world.
It's no surprise that
she couldn't go heaven.
Hibiki... She was the only
thing that mattered to me...
And I turned her
into a monster...
Because I believed
their lies.
I wanted revenge
against them
for what they
had done to my love.
And you helped me
to make that happen.
Unlike the others,
you exist without a nature.
I was wrong.
Shikabane aren't
defiled creatures.
They had no choice,
they were born this way.
My regret...?
I thought of Hibiki
as an awful defilement.
By making you
my Shikabane Hime...
I felt I could atone
for the chaos I created.
Hibiki.
I'm so sorry, Hokuto...
But I can
no longer do this.
Oh great... She reverted
back into a Shikabane...
We have to work quickly!
Okay!
I should have
known better...
It was my fault
for placing our trust
in the hands
of a pathetic human.
I'm sorry your experience
was so unpleasant.
I missed the bugs...
I don't see the child...
Will he really
be gone forever?
Yes... We won't be seeing
Akasha ever again...
Now come with me,
Hokuto.
I couldn't get
a clean shot.
Dammit!
Sadahiro.
They're gone...
Where'd they go?
The number of Shikabane
is rapidly decreasing.
There were
so many of them.
I'd never seen that
many Shikabane before...
The Seven Stars
definitely succeeded
in creating swarms
of Shikabane.
The Seven Stars are gone.
The remaining Shikabane
will lose their power
or die instantly...
Am I wrong
in assuming this?
Of course not, sir.
But that doesn't
eliminate the threat
they pose against
our Shikabane Hime.
You know as well as I do
that after this battle...
Many will have killed
more than 108 Shikabane...
Preparations must be made.
Haven't you heard?
They'll just go to heaven.
Sadahiro!
Gon Dai Sojo Shiou has
joined the spirit realm.
Before he passed on...
It was decided that Sadahiro
Mibu will be his successor.
I consider this an honor...
Things will change
from here on out...
I'll take responsibility in
dealing with the Shikabane Hime
who reach 108 ...
I know we can do better.
We must fulfill our
promise of heaven to them.
Sadahiro...
Tell us what happened...
And Akasha...?
Did he...?
None of you need to know
the details... It's finished.
It's that simple?
Akasha has been destroyed...
Shikabane Hime are
still at our disposal...
What else do you
need to know...?
It's finished.
Where's Makina?
She's gone missing...
Or at least, that's how
they're going to treat it.
Treat it?
You don't think she got
herself killed, do you?
There's no way Makina
could be dead, Flesh.
What about Ouri?
Same story.
Then she'll be okay.
As long as Ouri
is with Makina...
It doesn't matter where she
is, she'll be safe with him.
Am I right?
I don't know what I should
do or where to go anymore.
I know... But I think
you're done fighting.
Even if you kill
108 Shikabane,
you won't be able
to get into heaven.
There's no reason
for you to keep fighting...
Do you know what I mean?
If you continue
down this path...
There's a chance you'll
become a destroyer Shikabane.
I know that, Ouri...
It's just that...
I don't... I don't
have any place to go...
I mean what am I
supposed to do now?
Come with me...
I know a place.
Makina?
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Now hold on a second...
I was just taking
your hand to lead you,
we're going
this way... Come on.
I don't need you
to lead me anywhere.
This is where you
want me to live?
Yeah...
I think Riko and the kids will
be coming back pretty soon.
You know it
wouldn't be long...
Before they found
me living here.
I figured that...
But I'll try to have a talk
with someone in the Kougon Sect.
And who knows...
Maybe you'll
finally be able
to have some kind of
a normal life, Makina...
Given the chance...
I think the kids could
really warm up to you.
You won't have to
think about fighting...
You can just be like
a regular girl again.
Makina?
I can't... I've never been able
to step inside this gate before.
What...? But what
about you and Brother?
Keisei always wondered
why I couldn't.
I don't know why
I can't either...
I think it has something to do
with the children playing
and having fun...
I guess I thought...
This place
wouldn't accept me
because of my
defiled human form...
I shouldn't enter.
Wow, I...
I'm inside.
See?
Ouri...!
There you are!
Dude...! Where the hell have
you been hiding all this time?
Sorry... Are we ruining
an intimate moment?
What are you
talking about?
Nevermind... What are
you guys doing here?
We've been so
worried about you.
You disappeared on us after
that disturbance at school...
So many things have
happened since then.
Some airplanes
crashed in the city.
No one's saying anything,
but we've been seeing monsters
all over the freakin' place.
I wish someone would
tell us what's going on.
Uh, monsters...? Sounds like you
guys have been through a lot.
Ouri... And Makina, if
I'm not mistaken?
I don't mean to pry, but...
Do you guys know
about any of this...?
Are you connected somehow?
We were... But all of
that is in the past now...
I'll explain it
to you later.
You, uh... You haven't
seen Nozomi, have you?
Nozomi is the only
person we can't find.
Do you know
where she is...?
We thought... Maybe
she might be with you.
She was.
Makina?
Wait. Where are you going?
For a second,
I forgot everything.
You're talking about Nozomi,
aren't you...?
She wasn't the only one
to get caught in the crossfire.
You don't...
I mean, you shouldn't...
Please don't think what
happened to her was your fault.
That's not it.
You know as well as I do...
Nozomi Kasuga adored death.
An eternal death...
She wished to stay
beautiful forever.
She wanted to be a Shikabane
more than anything.
If I don't do something...
An eternal death
is what awaits me.
I don't want that...!
I want to live!
I didn't know
what it meant...
When I was alive,
I couldn't fathom it.
What it means
to be truly alive...
How to get the most of
what we already have.
I stood by Keisei's
for years...
For as long
as I can remember,
fighting was all
I knew how to do.
I finally
figured it out...
I understand what
it means to live.
And I know that
in order to live,
I have to keep on fighting.
Makina, I don't know if
you should be doing this...
I mean what about Hokuto?
Hokuto isn't really
death itself...
Not even close...
She's just another
Shikabane that I must fight.
Her memory is just a
little clouded right now...
It's my job to help her remember
why we do all of these things.
She'll know what
it means to live...
And what it really
means to die.
No one can escape from death
and I'm no exception...
I don't know about you,
but I choose to live
and die fighting.
Please... You can't.
Let me ask you this...
Do you wish for me to become
the person Nozomi Kasuga dreamt
of being someday?
Simply existing in this form
for all eternity...?
Not dead,
but not alive either?
My heart would...
Be the only thing
about me to die.
Is that the life you
wish for me to have?
I intend to keep
fighting death... I...
This is what it
means to be alive...
You know that I'm right.
Ouri...
I need you with me.
Did you forget...?
You're my contracted monk,
after all.
And I need you
to be there...
I want you
to see me fight.
You know where?
I can feel him...
Keisei is near.
Hazama...
He has Akasha's
catalyst with him.
It was created using
a part of Keisei's body.
The bond between
you and Brother...
It's still there,
isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Oh, don't be...
It doesn't seem to stop me
from being your contracted monk.
Besides...
He once told me that we're
not here for the dead.
A monk's duty is
to help lessen the pain
for those who the
dead leave behind.
I know I'm still
new at this...
But I can help you...
So please let me.
Monks aren't here
for the dead.
You're not dead.
That's why you
fight, isn't it?
To stay alive...
That's not something
a dead person does.
Makina!
Enemy...!
I've missed my enemy!
You have to remember...
Damn you!
Stop it, please...
You're going to kill her.
I'll help you remember...
All the pain, sorrow,
hatred, and anger!
You're human just like
all the rest of us!
I'll keep fighting...
To stay alive.
Am I alive...?
Right now...
I am...
I am!
You and I...
Are not dead...
We're alive!
[Music]