I'm leaving.
Hold on...
I'll take you.
You should probably take
that brother of yours home.
Oh, no.
I'm fine.
You're the one
who's hurt...
Why don't you let
him take you home?
I've already healed...
I am a Shikabane after all.
You two should
have a talk.
Should we follow--
She won't listen once
she's made up her mind.
Women like
that are trouble.
What are you
talking about?!
There's
nothing in here.
So...
Are you gonna tell
me everything?
Did I say you could
take my stuff?
Well I can tell you, but
it definitely won't be cheap.
1,000 for the bust alone;
2,000 more if you want
the waist and hips.
What?
After all,
it was a lot of work
checking her
measurements you know?
Who said I wanted to know
Makina's measurements?!
Who said
they were Makina's?
Well if they're Zenbu Nose's,
I really don't want to know!
Now tell me!
The reason
why we fight...?
Maybe you
should sit down.
Listen Ouri...
Have you ever thought about
what happens when someone dies?
Do you understand
what I'm asking?
There is meaning
in a persons death...
every death has the potential
to affect individuals,
society, or even
the world around us.
So you see, death is
by no means a bad thing.
Yeah but...
I don't see why-
Listen...!
There are those...
Who refuse to
accept the truth.
They can't realize their
death has any meaning.
So they cling
to their past life...
holding regrets and
obsessions toward this world.
Becoming monsters
called Shikabane.
But how can...
Something like
that exist?
There are numerous theories
as to the reason behind
the transformation...
But we still don't
have any answers.
The philosophy of salvation
has been passed down
through the Kougon Sect
since its founder...
It states that we are to
return all Shikabane to death
in order to keep
this world safe...
Do you
understand, Ouri?
Yes. This my job and
none of it concerns you...
Can you do me a favor
and stay out of trouble?
Hey, wait up!
So all of those times
you came home injured?
It wasn't because of
your motorcycle, was it?
Well...
Sometimes I did
actually fall...
Then how can I
not be concerned?
Don't sit there and tell
me I shouldn't worry!
What if something horrible
were to happen to you...
What if you died.
If that does happen...
Burn some incense for me.
If you're gone, what's gonna
happen to the Dai Rin House?!
What are we all
supposed to do?
Think about everyone
you'd leave behind
if you got
yourself killed.
I'm sorry, Ouri...
But quitting is out
of the question...
I became a contracted
monk for Makina's sake.
What?
You have to understand
I'm the only one she has.
I think this is it...
It looks like the car.
Sweet dude,
it's not beat up at all.
Wait a minute,
so whose car is this?
You don't need to worry
about it, just hop in.
Please...
It'll be okay.
The rumor's were true...
Keys are in the ignition.
I had heard about this rental
company from a friend...
They do all their business
under the table...
Renting out cars to people
without a license.
A rental company?
So... we're paying
for this?
According to the rumor
I'm supposed to leave
the money on the dash...
But I think we can all skip
that part, don't you?
I'm down, why don't we
just take the car and run?
Good idea, but apparently
there are consequences.
That's enough!
What are you doing?!
Nothing...
I'm not steering!
What the...
is this a joke?
Our Kun-chan is dead...
why?!
It's not like
you knew her.
I think she must have
been pushing herself
too hard yesterday
by trying to go on
with the live
performance.
Oh, she really loved her fans,
why did she have to die?!
A couple of friends
were saying
that she was
connected to Yakuza.
You shut your face
about Kun-Chan!
Hey Ouri...
why are you so quiet?
All right...
I know you deliver papers
in the morning but seriously.
Settle, today
I would like your help
in welcoming a new student
to our classroom.
Her name is Itsuki...
Yamagami.
Ouri she's an angel...!
A freakin' angel
is in our classroom!
I thought you were
in love with Kun Osaki?
Hey...
look over here.
Ouri!
Tell me...
how did you do it?
Hey there.
You're Ouri Kagami,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Sorry about earlier.
You remind me of a dog I used
to have a long time ago.
So I waved
on accident.
Oh... I see.
But... Maybe it was fate
that made me wave to you.
What do you say
we be friends?
Sure.
Why should you care...?
So what if she happens
to know Ouri?
It's just
unbelievable!
I find it hard to believe
that a girl would smile
at a guy like Ouri before...
She'd smile at me!
Listen dude...
It's nothing against Ouri,
I just think that
spunk is a commodity
that the girls in
our class tend to lack,
and when you
find a gal...
Ladies, there's enough
Ushi for everyone.
I guess
the word is out.
The new health teacher
must be starting today.
You think
he's good looking?
I guess
he must be.
And that ends
our demonstration.
There may not be much
I can teach you,
but I promise
to do my very best.
It was nice
to meet you all.
I don't understand...
Are you telling me that I will
no longer be the guardian?
That's not what
Sojo's saying.
You're taking it
the wrong way.
Look, the Kougon
Sect is well aware of
how I came
to take in Ouri.
That's not the... uh?
Now, it was my understanding
that your brother
was never to know of your
work as a contracted monk.
That was the condition
we agreed on, wasn't it?
It was.
We'll follow the head
temple's orders
as to how we deal
with Ouri Kagami...
Got that?
Until further notice, you are
to cease all duties as guardian.
[Disconnect tone]
Thank you very much, Sir.
Was it you,
Inspector Honda,
who went through all the
trouble of letting His Grace,
Gon Dai Sojo,
know about this incident?
Yes. I do believe that it was
well within my jurisdiction.
So tell me, do you really think
we can't trust this boy...?
Honestly.
I am suspicious
of everyone.
It's one of the more difficult
parts of being an Inspector...
No exceptions.
In my personal opinion there
are times when Keisei Tagami
treats his Shikabane Hime
as if she were human.
Well...
Makina is the only surviving
member of the Hoshimura Family.
Treating defiled corpses as
human is against our philosophy.
I see...
But it could become very
dangerous if a Shikabane
were to attack while
Keisei is still off duty.
I'll go there
if I'm needed...
I know the district isn't
too far from the head temple.
I don't think it's necessary
to send the strongest
of the Shikabane Hime,
do you?
It's taken care of...
I have already spoken to Genpaku
about picking up the slack.
Very well...
I believe that I've
heard of him...
Are you sure?
I am certain.
He is the youngest to become
a contracted monk in the history
of the Kougon Sect.
What do you think?
You know
as well as I,
contracted monks are to tell
no one about their job,
not even their family.
The less people who know
of the Shikabane's existence.
The better off this world
will be for it, Kamika.
I don't think that's
the only thing Honda's after.
I have to agree...
They seem to think Keisei
has some connection
to the traitor monk.
But I've already...
I've already
investigated it.
There are rumors about
an unlicensed rental car.
And I can't find
anyone who's rented it.
Well to be precise,
I can't find anyone
who's still alive
after renting it.
Trapped by a Shikabane...
But I've been ordered
not to work by the temple.
Isn't it our duty
to protect...?
To prevent even
a single human life
from falling victim
to this world?
You and I have made a
mistake by telling Ouri.
The head temple is
already suspicious
that he's somehow connected to
the recent Shikabane attacks.
Why?
Let it go, besides we have
plenty of time to relax now.
Going for a drive?
Yeah, I was asked out but...
It was so sudden
and I'm kinda scared.
You mean of the guy
who asked you out?
He said there's this rental
car company renting out to kids.
Could you come along...?
It would really mean a lot.
I would...
But I...
I gotta work tonight.
Please Ouri...
Later.
Why is it you...?
Why couldn't it be me?
I think I've heard of this
unlicensed car company
renting out to kids.
Rumor says...
Anyone who rents a car from
them, ends up disappearing
without a trace
of evidence.
Do you think
he'll show?
What man in his right mind
would turn down a girl like you?
No man except
for you, right?
Now that just
isn't true...
Remember to be careful.
Makina.
A shady rental company
where people disappear...?
Sounds like
Shikabane to me.
Brother told me...
I shouldn't get involved.
But Ouri...
You're already involved.
I finished taking out the trash,
so I'm gonna head out.
Oh good you came...
I was so afraid
you wouldn't.
Hey listen to me Itsuki...
Someone told me...
About this rental
company and it's cars.
They're involved in
some pretty shady stuff.
What are you doing here?!
I knew it.
You two know
each other...?
Great... Why don't we all
go out for a drive together?
Um, hey there,
Itsuki?
You do have...
A driver's license
don't you?
Can't say
that I do.
So what's up with that
guy who asked you out.
The truth is I lied...
I just really wanted to spend
some time getting to know you.
But if...
You have a girlfriend,
I guess it's a bad idea.
She thinks I'm
your girlfriend?
So you aren't then...?
That's good to know.
Yeah...
Go right on ahead.
I'm not gonna
put up a fight.
Very funny!
Why are you here?
I figured I'd
see you again...
As long as I kept
following strange events.
Thought you were told
to stay out of it?
I can't just
stay out of it.
Not as long as my
brother's in danger.
Don't you get it?
You're a liability.
Your presence here puts your
brother in more danger
than you fail
to realize...
If you really want to help,
don't get involved.
I hope you know he
became a contracted monk
for your sake
and not his own.
Hey, Itsuki,
watch out!
You're going a little fast,
don't you think? Slow down.
But... I'm not the one in
control of the wheel anymore.
What about the breaks?
It's not working.
One Passenger?
What in the world is this?
It wants us
to kill each other?
What're you
talking about?
That's what it wants,
isn't it?
We kill each other here.
It won't stop until there's
only one of us left,
that person lives.
We'll find
another way out.
No. We won't...
I don't want to die.
Regrets!
If people were forced
to kill each other...
They would most likely leave
this world with regret.
So a person who
dies in this car,
has a greater chance
of becoming a Shikabane.
Then... the car was made
to create Shikabane?
What are you saying...?
There's, no other way
out of this car.
Makina, wait!
That's not fair.
Humans tend to struggle more
when they don't wanna die...
Like it or not,
it's gonna happen...
Remember that!
Quite an impressive disguise,
you've been hiding behind...
but it's not them who will
be doing the killing tonight.
It'll be me.
Time to die,
Shikabane.
Makina!
You get out too!
Tell me does your friend
always look so angry
or is this just one
of those nights?
Do you see him too...?
What's the matter?
Ouri...
Stay away from him.
Now, now...
I don't appreciate having
my conversation interrupted.
Tell me
who you are.
Aren't we
the curious one...?
They call me
the traitor monk...
I turned my back
on the Kougon Sect...
My time
is now spent
destroying all the
pathetic little puppets
they've created to
protect themselves.
Do you mean...
The Shikabane Hime?
I must admit
I'm curious...
do you know what
they truly are?
They're the...
Good Shikabane.
They kill other
Shikabane for a humans sake...
And that makes them
the good Shikabane?
Let me enlighten you...
They fight only
to fulfill a contract.
If they succeed in
destroying 108 Shikabane...
they can make it
into heaven.
Into heaven?
Shikabane Hime are those
who became Shikabane
without ever wishing it
upon themselves.
They quite simply don't
know how to die...
And the Kougan
sect uses them
as if they were nothing
more... than puppets.
Itsuki,
you're all right!
So...
It was you who was trying to
make Shikabane this entire time?
I create Shikabane.
This is just the first
of many necessary steps
if I'm to
achieve my goal.
I don't give a damn
about your goal...
C'mon!!!
Itsuki, no...
You too?
You see now
don't you...?
They're given a false life
for making a contract
with the Kougon Sect,
agreeing to destroy
one-hundred and eight Shikabane
for there own entry to Heaven!
She murders her own kind.
I am Takamasa Sougi,
Genpaku.
I am a contracted monk...
Don't move!
[Music]
You start running...
With the belief that
something good lies ahead.
But don't fool
yourself...
You're about to find
a new kind of despair
"At the End of
the Dangerous Run."