[Music]
Emi, I think it's
time we headed back.
You're still
chickening out?
We're already here, so there's
nothing you can do about it.
Nozomi, stop dragging
behind, would you?
Ah, I'm sorry.
It happened about
two months ago...
A friend of mine from
middle school talked me
into going out
to this old building
that everyone believed
to be haunted...
And that's
when I met her.
Hey, Takatoo...
Yeah?
Is this place really haunted
or is it just an empty building?
This place is
haunted all right...
I have it on good authority
that 3 years ago,
a gang of bank robbers used
this place as a hideout.
But when the cops were
catching up with them,
one of the members freaked out,
thinking they were done for.
The fire spread
in an instant.
And they weren't the
only people here.
Some people were
burned to death.
Others died jumping
from the windows,
trying to escape
the blaze.
Not too long
after that,
a strange rumor
started going around
that some kids who went
to play in the scorched ruins
never came out.
And when some adults
went in to look for them,
they didn't
come out, either.
Everyone vanished.
Soon, companies started
turning down orders
to demolish
what was left.
After a while, some people
gave the building a name
they thought it deserved.
They call it "the
man-eating building."
[Screeming]
You guys have
to be careful.
I'm used to being
in this kind of environment,
but it can be
dangerous in here.
Okay.
Hey, man. I'm guessing
this is the room
where the bank robbers hid
and ended up biting the dust?
Yeah... You can
feel it, can't you?
Such incredible energy.
Really?
Yeah, really.
You should be leaving now.
This place is dangerous.
I'll just stick
with you...
Wait up!
No...
What's wrong?
I thought I saw
a dead body right there.
No you didn't...
They cleaned all
that out a long time ago.
Well, look at that...
It's just a dummy.
Must be some kind
of practical joke.
I'm not a spiritual guy,
but this has gotta be
disrespectful to the dead.
That looks like
real cash, man.
Who would joke
with real money?
It's fake.
Don't!
Put the money back and
step away from there!
Hey, you're that chick.
Give it back...
It's mine...
My money...
Give it back...
Give it back!
What're you doing?!
Get outta here!
Just keep running to
the end of the hallway!
It'll get you
outside...! Go!
The bastards
stole my money...
And I'm gonna
kill them...
Hold on to me!
We gotta hurry.
This is my money!
What happened...?!
Are you okay?
She's dead?
Oh, no!
She's dead!
I'm gonna kill you all.
You're not getting away!
And now you die
like the rest!
When someone dies with strong
regrets, they become Shikabane.
They're corpses
who curse living people
and set their sights
on killing them.
I've heard talk
that there are people
who want to get rid of us
using other Shikabane.
Which must be what you are!
One who tries
to kill immortals?!
Damn you...!
If I knew you weren't human,
I would've skipped
those other worthless kids
and killed
your ass first!
In that moment,
I was calmly amazed
that it wasn't fear
or surprise filling my heart.
I was captivated.
Held tight in the wake of beauty
left behind that fighting girl.
People have said from the
beginning of humanity
that death is something
of which to be frightened.
I've thought that perhaps
that's not entirely true.
Because death releases
people from this world.
And yes, her beauty
is the beauty of death.
The beauty of release.
Since that day,
I've wanted more than anything
to see her
just one more time.
I wonder why.
No matter
how hard I searched,
I could never
find a Shikabane.
More importantly,
I could never find her.
I can't believe it!
It's her!
I've told you
over and over again... .
Do not get
involved with us!
I know
what you've said...
But I have to know
where Minai was taken...
Why can't you
just tell me that?
Minai...?
Who's that?
Come on... You know
who I'm talking about!
Actually,
Ouri, I don't.
Did you kill her?!
I don't know anything because
we didn't do anything.
Keisei said it was resolved,
which is good enough for me.
It should be good
enough for you, too.
Don't lie to me...!
Where did she go?!
Give me
a straight answer!
Thanks...
I think
I remember him...
Hi there.
Are you a
friend of Ouri's?
Um... Well...
I guess you
could say that...
Bye!
What a weird girl.
I don't know, Ouri.
Maybe you'll know what
I'm talking about
when I tell you this.
But when I heard about the
senior dying in a strange way
and another stabbing
someone, I felt...
sorry...
For them.
Yo! What's with the
gloomy faces, losers?!
I wonder what's
gonna happen
to the Student Council's
assistants... Now?
You're the only member
of the student council.
But I let you guys
help me, don't I?!
For I, Mizuki Inuhiko,
manage the 10th grade
and you're positioned
beneath me; learning, growing.
But next year,
I'll be the president
and you will
all be my staff.
We'll carry out
glorious reformations!
We alone will craft a golden
era for Ikai High School...
Hey...! Pay attention
when I'm talking to you!
While it looks like you
two suckers are busy
riding the depression train,
I'm gonna show
you something today
that will instantly make all of
your problems a distant memory.
Okay...
That's just Kasuga.
So what...?
She's not that hot.
What do you
mean so what...?!
It should be obvious.
That woman is a Breast Goddess!
Breast Goddess?
See? I mean,
would you look at that!
There's nothing wrong with
focusing our infatuations
on hot models or TV stars
or anime voice actors
or even transfer students.
But I thought I'd go back
to when it all began for me.
The goddess who's
drawn my attention
since I started
high school.
And she's bigger than
that transfer student!
Isn't she hot?
Don't you feel better?
Aren't your
worries gone?
It's him.
So... have you
talked with Ouri
since everything
happened the other day?
No...
How about you?
Nope... He's completely avoided
any kind of contact with me.
I heard that the Inspector
took care of Minai.
But as far as Ouri
is concerned,
he thinks
we killed her.
Right. But if he stays
away because of this,
things will work out...
Don't you think?
They should.
I wonder what's gonna happen
between him and Makina.
He'll probably avoid
her the most...
He seems to think,
for whatever reason,
that Makina is his
brother's girlfriend.
Would he be close to
the truth on that?
No, not a chance...
although I don't know how
Makina feels about it.
She's a Shikabane Hime.
She knows.
Yeah, I guess...
Ouri...
What's wrong with you?!
Hello.
Ouri, I would like
to introduce you
to my lovely
breast goddess.
Breast, what?
I'm sorry to spring
this on you...
Don't worry about it.
What's going on?
When I asked Ushijima,
he said the two of you
were good friends,
so I thought...
We're friends...
I don't know how--
It doesn't matter. Just let
me get right to the point,
if you don't mind.
Of course.
I want you to give up on that
girl you've been chasing.
What girl do you mean?
You were waiting for her
in front of a temple.
She has long hair.
She's beautiful.
She's talking about that
Shikabane Hime, Makina.
Makina Hoshimura?
Really,
that's her name?
Makina?
Makina Hoshimura!
It's simply beautiful!
Yeah...
but I think it'd be better
if you stay away from her.
I don't understand. Why?
It's complicated...
Because...
Shikabane Hime attract
those who admire death.
I wonder if this woman is
also fascinated by death...
Just like you.
Uh... is something wrong?
It's nothing, sorry.
In the same way
you're drawn to death,
you're also drawn
to Shikabane Hime.
You can no longer
get out of it.
Shut up!
Uh...
Oh, no... I was just
trying to catch...
a... cat.
You pervert! There's not
a cat anywhere around us!
I swear there was a cat...
You don't know anything!
You're just chasing her around
like every other brainless man!
How dare you lie to me just to
fulfill your dirty fantasies!
I only said that because
I'm concerned about you.
I'm not some jerk.
I'm going to make sure
Makina never has to deal
with this kind
of crap from you!
No one else
can see me...
Because I am you...
Here, I'm finished.
If you can do this
kind of work...
your arm has
regenerated well.
Isn't there a better
way for you to test
if my arm's up to speed?
I want you to know that
if Ouri comes to see me,
I'll ask him to help.
But it looks like
he's pretty mad.
Who is Ouri anyway?
You said you found him
one day and took him in...
But it seems like the Inspectors
know a lot more than that...
So what kind
of child was he?
He was an ordinary kid.
You're wrong.
He's always been
a strange one.
I mean, when he knew
my heart wasn't beating,
it didn't faze him.
Almost like
he expected it.
And even with Minai.
He knew she was
a Shikabane Hime,
but he treated her as if
she was an regular girl.
I find it hard to believe
that there's an
ordinary kid anywhere
who could do all of that.
If I remember correctly...
he was about three
when he came here.
Such a sad
and useless child.
He didn't know how to put on
clothes, how to use tableware.
The kid didn't even know
how to use the toilet.
Nothing. Forget about any
emotional understanding.
But one day,
something in him changed.
He was different.
What do you mean
you adopted him?
Well, he was on the
riverside, crying.
I had to do something.
And bringing him
home was the answer?
Don't listen to him.
I think it's great...
He's your
friend now, right?
Ouri had never
shown any interest
towards other
kids up until then.
Or anything for
that matter.
And the very
first thing in this world
that caught his attention
was a small, helpless life.
You couldn't say he
was a good caretaker.
He was much too clumsy
and short-sighted.
But it seemed the kid was coming
back to life little by little.
The poor thing.
We'll hold a memorial
service for him.
Riko, would you mind
grabbing a set of work gloves
and some incense?
I'll get the shovel.
Ouri stared for
hours at that cat,
marveling at how it changed
from a life into an object.
Ouri...
Why did you bring him
to a place like this?
This is where I found him.
I know he'll start crying
again if he's here.
I know he will!
Ouri...
The best thing
we can do for the dead
is remember them
for who they were
and shed tears
for the loss.
A monk's obligation isn't to
put the dead on a pedestal...
but to help guide the tears
of those who are left behind.
So, Ouri...
It's okay...
You can cry now.
I think that was the first
time he ever experienced
a real emotion.
In everyday life, people
forget about death...
And when they're reminded
because someone close to them
died, they soon forget again...
But I think it's harder
for Ouri than it is for
everyone else out there...
For some reason he thinks
he shouldn't forget.
But why...?
It'll just make him suffer
more than he already does...
There's nothing
to gain there.
It's time...
I should be leaving now.
Where're you going?
I gotta show my face at the
head temple once in a while.
Ouri...
Have you already
forgotten?
About little ol' me...?
But you...
You're dead.
Ouri, what's
going on in here?
It's the cat...
I know you're sad,
but stop crying...
Go to sleep.
What's wrong?
I'm only visible to you...
Because I am you.
Have you forgotten
about me...?
About us...?
Not again...
I'm sorry... I think my
mind was kinda wandering.
Thinking about
that girl again?
You know--
Look, you left
her with us,
but she said
she had to leave.
I didn't use my best
judgement and I let her go.
I'm sorry.
You still don't know
where she is, do you?
I'll be fine. I gotta
clean this mess up now.
Excuse me...
Is your name Makina?
Depends on who's asking.
I'm Nozomi Kasuga, you saved
me from that man-eating monster.
I came by because wanted to say
thank you for saving my life--
For the good of you and
everything you care about...
you should forget about
that night and me.
But Makina, there's
no way I could.
Go home, kid.
I don't want to...
Ouri couldn't possibly
understand you
or what you are
the way I can.
He's no good for you and he
doesn't get any of this...
He doesn't understand
anything about you or death.
Death?
Death is forever
and it's something
only the chosen can
approach without fear...
Death is beautiful...
That's why I'm drawn
to you... I get it.
You get nothing.
Death is death.
It's as simple as that.
But...
You don't know
anything about Ouri.
You're not familiar
with death at all.
He is.
And with you, too?
Sorry about that.
I don't know
how it happened,
but she seems to have gotten
the wrong idea about me.
So what...? I thought you
were gonna stop coming here.
I only see him with
you some of the time...
Do they not allow
cats at your place?
What?
Wait, you can see him?
It's not so dark that I can't
see a cat in front of me...
And if you're here
to see Keisei,
he's at the
head temple.
Do you mind if
I ask you a question?
Is it about Minai?
Yeah... Whenever I try
to think about her...
I realize that I don't
really know that much.
Would you mind telling me a
couple of things about her?
What was she like?
All we can do for the
dead is remember them...
And cry for the loss
when they're gone.
Brother told me something
along those lines
when I was younger...
But with Minai...
I don't know enough about
her to remember who she was.
All I have
to drink is tea.
Huh?
Thank you.
[Music]
Stars shine in the sky while
people writhe and struggle
on the ground.
But in this backwater place
where the living and dead
have seemed
to switch places,
even "Stars on the Ground"
can begin to twinkle.