[Music]
[Panting]
Why are you just
sitting there, Minai?!
It's your job
to destroy the Shikabane!
As Deputy Guardian,
I demand you carry out your job
as Shikabane Hime!
If I allow a Shikabane Hime
in the process of regenerating
her body to assist us,
then Guardian Tagami
will have my hide.
Besides... all your actions
here are forbidden...
a Shikabane Hime cannot
destroy a Shikabane
without her contracted
monk present.
Minai...
There's no way you can hold
your own against that thing!
Don't do it!
If I can break
his concentration,
I can take him down before he
has a chance to use the curse.
And I'm not doing this
because I was ordered to.
Minai!
You're just a monster...
but I am justice...
Do you hear me...?
I am justice!
It's time to die!!
Mitsu... Yoshi?
Mitsuyoshi,
are you there?
I had no idea you knew Ouri,
but thank goodness you do.
I'm so relieved.
How are you?
You know I've been reading
your blog lately
and it got me
kinda worried.
You need to answer your phone
once in a while, mister.
At least for your friends.
Sho Men!
Sumitori...
Hello?
Mitsuyoshi,
can you hear me?
Are you practicing
kendo anymore?
You should.
You were good at it.
It's been too long, man,
why don't we get together and
check out the new Kendo Dojo?
Sumitori...
Are you even there?
Mitsuyoshi,
can you hear me?
Guess not.
Ouri?
Our--...
Sumi...
I'm sorry.
If you don't wanna feel
the way you're feeling...
you shouldn't get involved
in the first place.
Are you okay,
Minai?!
He acts like you two
are long lost friends.
Minai...
we're going back...!
Right now!
I'm gonna be fine...
And I think I'm done with
considering the wounds
on my body as punishment.
Punishment?
I'm not human...
I'm Shikabane Hime...
I know now
why I fight...
Even if it means that
I could get injured...
I promise that
I will do everything
I can to protect people.
I... I can do this...
I can take pride in myself
even though I'm not human.
Thanks for coming
all this way.
Don't even mention it...
I hope your wounds
are healing properly.
And also... if you need anything
at all, don't hesita-...
And if you didn't know it,
bending over and licking my feet
will heal
you up just fine.
Would you stop talking
like a streetwalker?!
If that's how
you want it,
then I'll keep all of your
true feelings to myself.
Those are certainly
not my true feelings!
Senior, what do you
think you're doing?!
Self healing...
I'm in pretty
bad shape, you know.
Go on, let the poor
guy lick your feet.
Thank you very much.
Would you stop that?!
It's disgusting and you're
really creeping me out!
Sorry for serving
what you brought,
but this is
all we have.
I knew you didn't
have anything here,
so I picked out
what I wanted to eat.
I reported the traitor monk's
case to old man Takamine.
It's his
decision now...
I'm assuming that you came
here for the other case today.
That's right...
And I wanted to talk to
you about your brother.
He's just been sticking his
nose where it doesn't belong.
He's your brother,
why don't you just have him play
'follow the leader' and
join you in the Kougon Sect
as another contracted monk?
It could be fun for you.
Minai could work with him after
she cuts her bond with Isaki.
No...
I won't do it...
I can't let him get
any closer to our side.
Nice idea...
But you're a contracted
monk attached to Makina...
Keeping him away will be hard
with your attention divided.
True. But I've
made up my mind.
I'm going to keep my
promise to Makina...
But what I won't do...
is allow Ouri any closer...
They're both important to me
and that's the best I can do.
Sure...
Mr. Cool Sunglasses
Indoors guy
has some feelings...!
More like, you screw up
again and you're toast...
At least that's
what you told me...
Right, Rika?
She's crazy! I didn't
say anything like that!
Ouri!
You never told me what happened
with you and Mitsuyoshi.
Oh, yeah...
But... it's...
a little hard to
explain right now.
Any word on how
he's doing?
Gotta run... I'll fill you
in the next time I see you!
I guess you will...
I just hope
Mitsuyoshi is okay.
I'm afraid I have
some bad news.
Because you accessed
that Shikabane blog
using your cell phone...
I'm going to have
to confiscate it
as evidence in a
Shikabane case file.
Isn't that an
inspector's job? .
I mean, why did you come all
the way here by yourself?
I thought it was
an urgent matter...
I also had some business
to attend to in the area.
I really don't mind
you taking my phone...
but I'm out of luck if I need
to call or text someone.
Don't worry. We'll
get you a new one.
I'll even pay for it.
If it's okay with you,
of course.
See you after school?
Hey, Ouri!
Can I help you,
Mr. Sougi?
I don't say this
as your teacher...
but as a colleague of
your brother, Keisei.
I probably don't need
to tell you this,
but Shikabane Hime are
not human in any way...
No matter how cute they may
seem, they're dead flesh.
You didn't have
to put it like that.
[Phone ringing]
Dammit, Minai,
where are you?
[Phone ringing]
I'm not like
those others!
[Phone ringing]
Ah...!
Stop!
It's you!
I remember you!
Let me go!
It's all yours now.
The new one works fine...
Thanks for coming here
to get me a new one.
Sure.
What about you?
Do you have a cell phone?
Of course...
I have to use it to keep in
touch with my contracted monk.
You think you could
give me your number?
It's just... Makina isn't
the easiest person to talk to,
especially when it comes
to my brother, you know?
I think that'd be great.
Do you want to put it
into your new phone?
Minai!
Minai...
What's wrong with you?
What is it?
Please tell me
you're okay.
I can't...
Can't be...
But I am...
So it's true.
Inspector Honda has just
arrived at the site.
He confirmed
that this afternoon
Shuuji Isaki has
passed this life.
He's joining the other holy
monks in the spirit realm.
The witnesses said
that he was arguing
with two young men around
this area earlier today...
Then he showed up
here stabbed to death.
There are bad
people everywhere.
No matter who asks,
we're classifying this death
as 'in the line of duty.'
Now bring in
the burial cloth.
Yes, sir.
So, where's
Isaki's puppet?
Puppet?
His Shikabane Hime.
She shouldn't have
been too far away.
Saki?
Itsuki's coming...
and I'm sure he'll be alone.
Alone?
We can't show anyone...
what the two of us
are about to do...
Contracted monks are tied
to their Shikabane Hime
through a bond
stronger than those
you know in the
physical world...
and a contracted monk's death
directly leads to the death
of his Shikabane Hime.
However,
if that doesn't happen
and she continues to live
on past the monk's death,
she becomes just
another Shikabane.
That's why...
on this day...
Shikabane Hime must
kill one of their own.
Makina!
No time like
the present...
A Shikabane Hime
is about to die.
Why?
Minai, slow down.
What's going on with you?!
Just tell me what's the matter.
You can talk to me!
Shut up!
Oh, Ouri...
I'm sorry...
Minai...
Don't worry about it...
It's okay.
No, it's not!
Stop...!
You might think
I'm nothing more than
an irritating 10 year old...
But... my contracted
monk is Rika Aragami,
a member of the
Great Holy Families!
Descendants of the ten
senior disciples...
are obligated to become
con-tracted monks
to Shikabane Hime.
No Shikabane Hime
can beat me!
Please, no...
You know it.
You felt it
when it happened.
Your contracted
monk is dead!
It's true... They said
it was an accident.
Well, Minai...
You followed up murdering
somebody by killing yourself.
You thought your job
as a Shikabane Hime
was a way of atoning
for your sins.
But it's over now!
How'd she stop it?!
Why are the Shikabane
Hime fighting each other?
Whenever a contracted monk dies,
the bond is severed...
Unless his
Shikabane Hime dies...
She becomes...
just another Shikabane.
I don't wanna die... please.
Are you stupid...?!
We're not alive.
We're already dead!
But he thanked me...
He thanked me!
So thank you.
I thought what I was
doing was just atonement.
But things are
different now.
I'm changed, and I understand
now that being a Shikabane Hime
wasn't punishment.
And I wasn't some
kind of monster!
I can save people...
I can help!
I've never felt
this way before.
But I finally figured out what
it is I'm supposed to do...
Shut... up!!
I can't do it.
We're getting
out of here!
No, Ouri...! Minai is
already a Shikabane!
There's nothing
you can do!
Come on!
Ouri, stop!
He's such a jackass!
Makina...
I mean the Shikabane Hime
are mostly just a shield
for contracted monks.
So they're usually dead
well before the monks croak.
Sounds like one hell
of a crappy life.
I suppose things like this
happen every once in a while.
But I gotta say,
I think it's the first time
I've heard of a monk
being killed by punks.
We don't have
to go, do we?
They're not our targets.
If we run into
them by accident,
in town or something,
we'll do what we have to do.
But honestly, I want
to stay out of this mess
as much as possible.
I couldn't agree
with you more.
Sorry, guys...
but I was wondering
if my friend could stay here
for a little while...
like until later tonight?
She won't bother you.
They're not the nicest
people in the world,
but I think
you'll be safe here.
Where's Minai?
I don't think so!
You've hid her,
now what...?
You gonna be her
decoy forever...?
What a hero.
I don't get it...
Why do you have
to kill her?
Because a Shikabane Hime
who lost her monk...
Is just a Shikabane.
Are you sure...?
Because she said she
wanted to help people.
You think that's her
acting righteous...?!
It's an obsession
driving the Shikabane.
If she wants
to help people...
She's already
exhibiting regret...
This is what a
Shikabane does, Ouri.
They obsess...
Like it or not, Minai
isn't someone worth saving.
Do you understand?
I just don't think
that's right.
There's no right or
wrong to any of this...
If she's obsessed
with anything...
she's no different
from a Shikabane.
Now where is she?
You should probably know
that Shikabane Hime
can sense
their own kind...
we'll find her
sooner or later...
So it's no use
hiding her.
Why does it
matter to you?!
What are you
fighting for?!
You don't have a reason,
do you...?!
I know...
But at least Minai does...
I didn't know that
you knew about us.
Just a little.
They're secret
and imperfect,
but the Kougon Sect
has a few ideas on this...
The chance of success
is small but we can try.
First thing we gotta do is
find a monk to replace Isaki.
And we have to do
that like now...
If you can sever the
bond you have with him...
And tie
as strong a bond
to whoever we find
to replace him...
we might be able to keep
you as a Shikabane Hime.
The big question is
"can you find this kind of
contracted monk in time?"...
One who already
has a certain level
of spiritual ties
to this plane...
Who already
has ties to you.
Ouri is Keisei's brother,
why not him...?
I mean I've never seen the kid
more worried about anything...
so he's already connecting
to you in the way you'd want.
No...!
He's just a kid!
He isn't even in
the Kougon Sect.
I know that, but I can skip
that whole process
if I mediate the contract
between them myself.
Thank you...
Thank you so very much.
Yo, Ouri.
Check this out.
It's just crazy, man!
What happened?
Someone said that a monk
was stabbed to death
in that parking lot
over there...
They also said the killers
are the same age as us.
Sumi thinks he might've
went to middle school
with a couple
of those guys.
A monk was
stabbed...
Oh, no...
Ouri!
Chill, man!
What's your
freaking deal?!
Cut it out!
Ouri?!
I am... the Shikabane Hime
of Shuuji Isaki.
Well done...
Did you sustain
any injuries?
Not at all.
Then I guess,
we can transfer her now.
Hold up... What about
the burial cloth?
The cloth is for monks above
the Gon-Sho-Sojo level
or those who died in
the line of duty...
So, of course,
we didn't bring one.
But she died in the
line of duty, right?
And for the sake
of the doctrine.
You actually brought
one with you?
Yes... Senior Tagami said
the same thing earlier,
so I thought I
should be prepared.
Alright...
She might've survived
if you'd have made Ouri
her contracted monk like
you said you would...
She didn't have to be loyal
to Isaki to the death.
[Phone ringing]
[Music]
Suddenly, you want
to die for no reason.
Time will stop forever.
Because youth is beauty.
And once you become an
adult, you're defiled.
"Set Your Heart Aflutter."