Wow.
I could get lost in here.
Leave it to Totsuki
to build a storage area
on this scale
right next to the main venue.
I mean, this place
is pretty insane.
They even have a wealth
of niche items as well.
Whoa.
Check it out, you two.
This place has a ton
of great veggies and stuff.
Good thing we're first!
This is hardly the time
to treat this like any normal
shopping trip, Soma.
Oh, my.
Um, the ingredients
I'm after --
Move it,
country bumpkin!
Ah! Ah!
I'm so sorry!
Hey, Mr. Aldini,
it's not polite
to glare at people like that.
Oh, my apologies,
but I can't be blamed
for taking this seriously.
It's not often one has the honor
of battling a skilled chef.
Your eyes are telling a
different story
than your lips,
freshman.
Eizan-yan,
go over there
and get that for me, will ya?
Why don't you just go
and get it yourself?
But I'm small, so it would be
hard for me.
Oh, and bring me
a cart, too.
I'm afraid I've got
my hands full
with little Bucchi
over here.
While I would say tossing
that stuffed toy in the cart
would free up your hands,
yes...
This is no stuffed toy.
This is Bucchi.
Plus, this full bully
makes Bucchi super heavy.
Yes, well, there are several
student IDs
stuffed inside
that thing.
Bucchi.
Yes, ma'am.
Thanks a bunch,
Eizan-yan.
Whoa. There are so many kinds
of just soft flour.
If you're going to make
a sponge cake
for the food battle,
I'd recommend,
the one on the far right.
Eh?
Oh, thank you
so much for that.
Oh, sure thing.
You're such
a cute underclassman, Megum-yan.
Uh...
The thing is, when Chef Momo
regards you as cute,
she's actually
looking down on you.
She only uses that way
of addressing people
for those she considers
inferior to herself.
Megumi: Just calm down.
You'll be fine.
You learned so much
while training on the Tsukikage
before coming
to Rebun Island.
You learned from
first rate chefs
like Joichiro and Dojima.
And also...
Hello there, dimwit.
Looks like
somehow you've managed
not to get tossed
out of Totsuki.
Chef...
Chef Kojiro!
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Urara: Now then, it's time
for the third bouts.
While our contestants are out
collecting their ingredients,
let's go over the cards
for this upcoming round.
The first card,
the number four seat
on the Ten,
sushi maestro Somei Saito
versus that son
of an eatery owner,
Soma Yukihira.
The theme ingredient is
butter!
Second card is the number seven
seat on the Ten,
the alchemist himself,
Etsuya Eizan,
versus Italian transplant
Takumi Aldini.
The theme ingredient
is beef!
♪♪
I had assumed you were
already headed back, Kojiro.
My flight doesn't take off
for a little while yet.
I'm just killing
some time.
That leaves us with
the third card --
number three seat
on the Ten,
patissier
Momo Akanegakubo
versus the low level student
who almost got expelled,
Megumi Tadokoro.
Theme ingredient --
apples!
That about sums it up.
I wonder what tactic
will Megumi use?
Wait!
Chef Kojiro!
Getting special training
from him?!
Yes. Chef Shinomiya became
her instructor
at the adamant request
of Chef Dojima.
Why such
a respected member?
For him to ask the
Legume Magician for help,
Chef Dojima must have
quite the vested interest.
I hope it works.
The training should play a role
in this food war.
We will,
most certainly.
[ Train whistle blows ]
Dojima: Up to this point,
the mock battles you fought
have strengthened
your sense of teamwork,
but make no mistake,
my friends,
your bouts
and the regimental food war
will test your individual skills
as well.
So, we will now
begin.
Personalized
training to elevate you.
To start, today, we'll pair
Joichiro with Soma Yukihira,
and myself with Takumi,
and Master Senzaemon
will observe Erina.
As for young Megumi...
Well, for starters,
why don't you go ahead
and show me
what you've already got,
cooking skill wise.
Make me something.
Hmm.
Um...so then,
you mean...
That's right.
I, Kojiro, am personally
going to build you up brick
by brick, Megumi Tadokoro.
Ah!
It's Mater Shinomiya.
She gets him
as her teacher?
The man who want
a Pluspol award?
But even still, she seems
a little bit off, doesn't she?
I've got
a good idea why.
Kojiro: Megumi Takahiro,
you're out.
She's remembering
training camp.
That's getting her
all nervous.
Hurry up
and make something.
Ah!
Yes, sir!
[ Whimpers ]
Ah!
Ee!
Oh, God. This isn't salt.
It's sugar.
Are you a novice again?!
You did better than this
at the damn training camp!
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry!
She's so nervous that
she's frozen.
Maybe him being here is having
the opposite effect this time.
That's
wishful thinking.
[ Groans ]
[ Whimpering ]
It's nice to see you have
a limit, Kojiro.
Come to have some sport,
have you, Chef Dojima?
[ Chuckles ] That was quite
unforeseen, though, I must say.
Huh? Likewise.
I would have never expected
such prompt willingness
from you to participate
in this training.
Have you in your own way felt
anxious about Totsuki's fate?
Not really.
I couldn't really care less
about the Azami administration.
What's their name?
Central, is it?
I have no plans to deal with
nor align myself
with anyone in that group.
I'm just acting on a whim.
Yes.
A whim.
I had a feeling I might be
the next to serve
as someone's guide.
In that moment,
the people who immediately
sprang to mind
were Soma Yukihira,
and yes, of course...
Megumi Tadokoro.
Huh? Gah!
Guts, damn it!
If you're a chef,
you better show some guts!
What the --
Don't tell me he's here
to get philosophical.
This isn't gonna
go well.
Quit relying on others,
you hillbilly trash!
Get your head
on straight!
Is this all the fight
you've got?!
[ Whimpers ]
[ Whimpering ]
No!
Show you can rise to the
challenge of my training!
Hit the ball
with all your frustration
and sweat and tears!
That's super awesome!
Now then,
aim for victory!
Yes, sir.
I won't lose.
I swear,
Coach Kojiro!
Hmm.
I won't get discouraged.
Please just give me
another chance, Coach!
Well, all right, then.
You'll make up
for lost time along the way.
I can do it, Coach!
I'll show you I can do it!
What the --
She call him "Coach"?
Megumi's
approach to vegetables
could be further refined
through Kojiro's help,
as he too has staked
his reputation
upon vegetable dishes.
If I were to give
them a title,
it would be the Legume Master
and Apprentice.
[ Ping pong ball hits ]
Megumi: I'm going to pour my all
into this bout.
Everything
I've learned from Coach Kojiro
so that we can all win.
Urara:
The competing chefs have all
returned from the storehouse.
That means cooking
is about to begin!
Okay.
Everyone, gather round.
Huh?
Hear me out. I want the dish
to have depth and sweetness,
but at the same time, I want it
to really hammer home
the butter flavors.
Okay. You'll need a lingering
aftertaste of something brisk
to help accomplish that.
Yes. Yuzu. No, apples would be
your best bet.
Yeah, I think I could back
you up on that.
Also, Takumi, I'd really
like your help with something
once you're done cooking.
They're planning
to work as a trio.
And they'll support
one another as team members.
This is harder than
Mimasaka supporting Kuga.
They're really going
to try doing this
for the first time
out there?
All:
Okay!
Perfect.
This was precisely the reason
for sending those three out
in a third bout.
After repeated
practice battles on the train,
this should bring out their
sharpened individual strengths
and let them work
in tandem.
Now, prove to me that
my command in this
is nothing short of flawless.
It kind of looks to me
like Erina has now come
to resemble you, Miss Alice.
What's the big idea,
Ryo?
Takumi is awesome!
It's perfectly julienned.
Yes, it is.
He learned that technique at the
restaurant from the Stagiaire.
Takumi: To best use the ginger,
the more slender
and uniform it is,
the more you can have it
permeate your dish.
Megumi:
Now to stir the eggs,
adding some delicately
sweet wasanbon sugar
to dissolve so the bone
doesn't rise.
Next up,
honey and mirin,
and then...
Megumi, here's some
cake flour for you.
I weighed it out
while I was rinsing the ginger.
Thank you!
Take this, too.
Sure!
Yo, Takumi!
They're laid out by size!
Give them a check!
Thanks.
I appreciate it so much.
Soma, almost there.
Just give me 30 seconds.
Nice. Thank you.
It's like watching pros,
who throughout
thick and thin
have developed
incredible synergy together.
One might say that
through cooperation like this,
even a short
time is enough
to accomplish what would be
impossible all alone.
Such nice teamwork.
The opposition just might
be putting the Ten
at a major disadvantage.
Come on, Soma!
Takumi! Megumi!
Do your best!
Tear 'em a new one!
Knock the Ten off their
frickin' pedestal!
Quick talking
so much horse crap,
you filthy
rebel dirtbag!
Your whole damn
pathetic crew there
is as good as
expelled from here!
You've got a mouth
on you.
You starting to lose your temper
more and more, huh?
Huh?
Ah.
That intense fragrance.
I think
it's coming from Momo's pot.
Huh...
What is this?
Now then, I expect both sides
to show us their best.
So please, if you would be
so kind, adorn your dishes
with
the beautiful flavor of apple.
Wait.
Just the smell was enough?
Even the sinister Urara
Kawashima has lost her spite.
Now she's the picture
of elegance
in both mind
and body.
Just what on Earth
could be going on in that pot?
Hmm.
[ Whimpers ]
This is it.
My finest sweetness.
Everyone is going to know
tastiness.
Isn't that great,
Bucchi-poo?
♪♪
Ah.
Such a vulgar, horrible,
uncouth based girl
I've been.
Going forward,
I'll be a new person
inside and out.
Good morning, my little birdie.
Would you mind too terribly
if I joined you now
with the sweetest of harmonies?
I feel like what I'm seeing
is not normal.
Is that girl
going to be all right?
Okay, then, Bucchi.
Time to finish.
Look at how fast
she's working.
And look at
her presentation.
[ Cheering ]
Okay, then,
all done.
Huh?
She's done already?
What is that thing?
What's going on?
A bouquet of roses?
Is that some sort
of prop or something?
No.
At first glance,
they're roses.
But if you look
closely at them...
Each of
those delicate flowers
is atop a perfect
tart crust.
The so-called roses --
they're actually made
from apples.
All: Whoa!
Not only is
it luxurious,
but such aroma!
I am already
entranced by it!
Both: Wa-hoo!
Oh, God!
The judges, too?!
They're reacting
to the scent alone!
Welcome to Momo's magical world
of wonder.
Please take your time
and enjoy.
Incredible!
Mmm!
Even as the sweet fragrance
blossoms,
the crispness of the apple
is a delight to the palate.
This scent is Damask rose!
Damask rose?
Really?
So, that's what
that thing is?
Yes. Damask rose.
This is one of
my most favorite flowers ever.
It just always smells
so beautiful.
They say it has the most refined
scent of all flowers.
It is called
the Queen of Roses.
Even Cleopatra adored
this flower.
She would even soak them
in her bath
to enjoy the fragrance.
You mean to tell me those apple
tarts smell
like freakin'
flowers, too?
They got to be
delicioso, bro!
So she's managed to impart
all of that aroma,
but no damage
from the boiling.
That's right.
If she condensed
that aroma through simmering,
it should have completely
wrecked the appearance
and texture
of the apple.
That's because I didn't
simmer it.
I simply infused
the rose's fragrance.
It might take a little more work
on the chef's part,
but first you gently rinse
the Damask rose petals
and then into the pot
they go.
After doing that, you can make
a sweet pink syrup out of them.
Thinly slice the apples
and give them a little soak
in the extract made
from the boiled apple peels,
then you add
the gorgeous rose syrup.
Let is sit
for 30 minutes or so.
Do that, and the apples will
turn a delicate rose red
and slowly take a wonderful
fragrance
for all to luxuriate in.
Just tossing everything
into a boil
would not be queeny
at all.
Being allowed a very slow
and graceful soak
better suits a rose
than a hot boil.
If I were to give this
splendid dish a name,
it would be
Apple Tart Fit For a Queen.
Also,
this basket is made of bread,
so you can eat it as well.
Huh?
Cute, isn't it?
Simply adorable.
[ Giggling ]
Reminds you of the autumn
leaves, doesn't it?
So then she utilized the apples
in order to make the sweets.
It is but
a subtle infusion,
and yet this requires
both a delicate hand
and a breadth
of expert techniques.
You need to discern
the optimal water temperature.
Without it, this sirup
is impossible.
Not a single ingredient
was lost.
As such, the natural sweetness
and the acidity of the apple
become the basis
for the tart.
And the luster
she achieved
by applying the liquid
with concentrated apple skins
was beyond reproach.
Her aesthetic
sense extends
even to
the lovely presentation.
It's as if she's from
some children's book.
Indeed, she is
truly an inhabitant
of some magical
fairy tale world.
She is a sorceress,
one who cast a spell
on nondescript ingredients
to create a princess
of deliciousness.
Every last person
who eats her sweets will...
All: Take up residence in
the world of dreams!
Simply sublime! With
this one dish,
she has thoroughly tinged
the color of our hearts!
Could any other
dish here
possibly best
this a brilliant masterpiece?
[ Both giggling ]
Megumi...
Sorry for the wait.
Please enjoy my dish.
But Chef Momo's dish
was so delicate and spectacular.
We'll need a dish
good enough
to make the judges forget all
about it.
Bring on the smackdown,
Megumi!
What's her dish?!
What is going on?!
All: Dorayaki?!
That's way too simple.
Still, that is like
Megumi.
When it comes
to presentation,
that thing's a dud!
But taste
is where it counts.
Let's base this thing
on taste.
Let us now
begin our deliberation.
The filling is a
white bean paste,
and there are bits of diced
apple mixed in as well.
Oh, the apple
envelops it all
with a lush and truly beautiful,
refreshing scent.
However, that apple tart remains
superior in appearance,
and if I must,
aroma as well.
Not so fast.
Japan's dorayaki has
been passed down for 800 years.
Some say its dual layers
were a direct influence
on the Western pancake
known to us today.
It is most culturally
intriguing.
I see. So, you like
that sort of history thing?
Now then.
Mm.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Gasps ]
Are you okay?
Love!
Oh!
Wha!
Hmm!
The silky smooth
batter infused
with honey, refined sugar,
and soy milk caresses
one's mouth
in soft whispers!
The mellow flavor of it spreads
across the tongue
like fireworks,
veritable explosions of light!
Then the faint
acidity of the apple
scatters and fades.
The flavor of it reverberates
in your brain
with the grace and power
of a super dreadnought,
challenging everything you've
ever known to be true and pure.
[ Indistinct clamoring ]
But the greatest secret
to this flavor
is the apple infused butter
you've brushed on the backs.
[ Grunts ]
And true to the name,
it includes grated apple
and lemon juice,
sugar for added sweetness,
and then melted butter
to bind them all together.
Adjusting the inherit
fruit profiles with butter
increases saltiness, acidity,
and depth of flavor.
Correct.
But to create this, you must
perfectly blend and emulsify
not just any ingredients,
but ones
with different qualities.
Put simply, you'd have to
combine oil and water.
Even from a pro,
keeping it from falling apart
while retaining
its smooth luster would be hard.
I'd imagine
it would require some form
of special technique.
Yes. I used
the monte au beurre method.
It's a French technique
with butter.
Kojiro:
The key to winning is to be
able to instantly glean
your ingredients'
true deliciousness,
and then to elevate
those flavors to a higher level,
what you need
is knowledge and skill.
What I am about to teach you
is one such skill --
monte au beurre.
I don't know
if you can master it
in the time we have left
before the food war,
though we will certainly
give it our best efforts.
Can you master this?
Aim for victory!
I can!
I know that I can do it!
Please teach me
the French method, Coach!
Hurry up, halfwit! It's already
started to separate!
Ah! Sorry, Coach!
Once your pot's
off the stove,
you stir it gently!
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey, the liquids
haven't boiled down yet!
Yes, sir!
Quit making me
repeat myself, numbskull.
Yes, sir!
[ Whimpering ]
All: Expelled.
Yep. Expelled.
Aim for victory.
Coach,
one more time, please!
Eh -- Sure.
Of course.
Out of all the students
I've taught so far,
you are truly
the biggest mess
I've ever come across.
A considerable mess.
Though, one thing
you're not is stupid.
My heart is stricken by waves
of ferocious deliciousness!
It's like they're representing
their fighting styles.
Megumi Tadokoro,
aim for victory.
Yes, Coach.
I will.
Megumi: Contestant and coach,
apple and butter.
This is what results when two
different things grab each other
by the scruff.
You got to drive
a hole through them
and strike!
Strike!
All: A fatal blow!
Two entities as one!
[ Laughs ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Indistinct muttering ]
[ Sighs ]
I really thought this might
end up being a heated battle,
but I concede my predictions
were hardly accurate at all,
so it seems.
But even
if that's the case,
the sweetness and sublime aroma
that Momo produced
is not lacking.
Indeed, it is
the very opposite of that.
Wha!
No, bro!
Please, Megumi!
Anne:
Those eyes.
They haven't yet given up.
Could there be
some other secret in her dish?
[ Gasps ]
This flavor.
What seems to be
the matter, Anne?
You'll understand
if you just keep eating.
What?
If we just
keep eating?
Love! Love!
Ah!
Oh!
So, Megum-yan, just what do you
think you've done here?
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
My tongue!
Mezzaluna.