[ Clapping ]
Your attention, please.
I have some news.
I hereby announce
a small change
to the judges panel
for this Food War.
Effective immediately,
I am acting as panel chairman.
You have, after all,
had more than your fill
of the Ten's offerings, yes?
You friggin kidding?!
What the hell
are you talking about?!
There is no way
the jackass ringleader
himself could be allowed to do
the damn judging!
Get out of here!
Do you think you can
get away with this?!
I'm sure he does think
he can do just that.
He's got some nerve
keeping a straight face
while talking
that kind of garbage.
Since returning
back to Japan,
I have yet to enjoy the cooking
of my beloved daughter,
because during the lunar feast,
there was an unwarranted
intrusion.
Hey, hey, Erina,
you got an open table?
Hey, old man,
I didn't mean to intrude.
I take it you were just about
to order some grub.
I've suddenly
lost my appetite.
Whoa, no way!
Someone intruded
on your big night?
Sure are some rude folks
out there.
What the heck, Chief?
You can't just come in
and change the rules in
the middle of the competition!
Quit trying to mess
everything up around here!
Please do not misunderstand
my reason.
Master Senzaemon has given
the approval for this change.
Isn't that right,
Master Senzaemon?
But grandfather!
This was decided
by both commissioners.
No one has the right
to overturn it.
Now, if you would,
please relinquish your seats.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Anne: This is an officially
sanctioned Food War.
As its appointed judges,
the responsibility lies with us.
Outside judgment is in violation
of WGO procedure.
You're indeed correct.
Now, please let me introduce
our esteemed guests.
Decora and Courage?!
What?
You know them?
Yes, they're both respected
officers within the WGO.
What the...?!
Are you telling me
Azami Nakiri's influence
extends all the way
to the WGO?!
Indeed,
and as members of the WGO,
it was the two of us who helped
Anne refine her palate.
And after much intense
training,
you were finally able
to become a top-tier official.
So proud.
No matter what the task,
you were just hopeless.
Not to mention you were also
so delightfully nerdy back
then.
Care to see a photo?
Those two braided twins
over there.
They look like separate
halves of the boorish creature
that you once were.
Stop, please!
Just stop already!
I'm not even
a part of this,
but somehow
I got burned.
I'm boorish?
In any case, we'll be
taking over from here.
You don't intend to challenge
the WGO's
founding principles,
do you?
Understood.
However,
as I am a tier-one official,
I shall be participating,
as well.
You at least must accept
that concession.
Azami: [ Scoffs ]
Fair enough.
Take your seat, Miss Anne.
My apologies.
Seems I wasn't able to
secure a seat for you.
Oh, not at all,
Mr. Azami.
I'd be just fine
sitting in your lap.
[ Both grunting ]
Now then,
let us resume the contest.
We three shall be your judges
for the remainder
of this Food War.
Aah!
This chaps my hide!
He totally took over
the judges table!
Boy, these regimental
Food Wars are great.
Talk about luck.
In what friggin' way?!
I mean,
we got the big man himself
to come down to
the battlefield.
We get to bludgeon him
with our dishes personally.
-Oh.
-Hmm.
Soma!
Things have taken
an unexpected turn,
but regardless, we move on.
Still up,
we have the first card of
Eishi Tsukasa
versus Satoshi Isshiki,
as well as the second card
of Rindo Kobayashi
versus Takumi Aldini!
Damn it, why'd you do that?
Pulling some stunt
that can screw up the contest.
You better believe
ol' Chef Rindo
is pissed off
with this bullcrap.
She's going for it.
It's like she's pouring
all of her anger
into the dish
she's preparing.
You better not lose,
Takumi!
You can do it,
brother!
Takumi:
True, Azami Nakiri's little
stunt caught me off guard,
but come on.
Why is she so irritated?
Wait, what?
What was that I sensed
just for a moment?
It was like some wild animal
baring its fangs.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't start dragging
your feet now, Takumi.
I'm going to have to
serve up my dish first.
We start with
Chef Rindo, huh?
Courage, fetch me the wine list,
if you would.
Sure, I'd be glad to.
[ Chuckles ]
Ol' Chef Rindo
is comin' at ya, you hear me?
[ Both gasp ]
Hmm?
My brother's
finished his dish, too.
Urara: Looks like both
contestants for this card
will be serving
at the same time.
Now everyone
at the judges table,
which includes the new faces,
will begin the tasting.
Remember, the theme ingredient
was spear squid.
The dish that my brother made
is known as calamari ripieni.
The sliced-up spear squid
is stuffed
before being roasted in the
oven
to make one juicy package.
It's a regional specialty that's
frequently eaten in
southern Italy
near the Mediterranean seashore.
That's the stuff!
Way to go!
What about
Chef Rindo's dish?
Shoji: I'm getting some real
prim and proper vibes.
Daigo: It looks kind of like
a cute cake or something.
Well, now this
is most wonderful.
Let us partake in
Takumi Aldini's dish first
before it gets cold.
[ Chuckles ]
Piping hot calamari.
It's like I'm about to get
burned by the umami flavor.
Mr. Azami,
if you'd like us to [blows]
cool it down,
then say the word.
Quit your yapping
and get to eating already!
That looks delish!
Reminds me of ikameshi.
They do look very similar,
but the stuffing inside the
squid of this dish is
different.
The most common filling
for this particular dish
is made from a mix of panko,
cheese, eggs, tomato, and so
on.
And because it's such
a simple dish,
the chef needs creativity
to help them determine
what to use in the filling.
[ Slurps ]
Oh!
It's so fresh,
it almost wriggles
in my mouth
as the rich flavor dances
upon my tongue!
Squid liver and anchovies
is what's behind this punch.
Precisely right.
I finely minced both of those
and then sautéed them
with olive oil,
red pepper, and garlic
to infuse a lavish aroma.
Then I added white wine
and let it all simmer slowly
to create the filling.
However, your genius idea
that gave a boost to the
flavor
is actually on the outside.
Yes, after I sautéed it, I added
some heavy cream to the liquid
that was left over, creating
a squid and anchovy sauce.
I randomly drizzled that over
the baked squid before serving.
The cream creates a contrast to
the tangy taste of the filling,
and it provides our tongues
with a variety
of ever-changing flavors.
By perfectly matching the squid
and the filling together,
I brought out the maximum flavor
of the spear squid itself.
That is my take
on calamari ripieni.
Now we shall use our bodies
to exemplify just how delicious
this dish truly is.
Bodies?!
Decora: Calamari is packed with
the umami flavor of seafood
until it's on the verge
of gushing all over.
It's like --
-This new winter lineup of
garments that glamorously wrap
themselves around our bodies.
Both: Calamari lingerie!
The supple and glossy skin
of the proud squid
is represented with white silk,
with thin silver fabric
that shines like the scales
of the anchovy.
Truly the height of
extravagance.
This semi-transparent
camisole
is colored red
in the image of the red pepper.
The embroidered lace
has a garlic-inspired pattern
accentuating
all the right places.
Perfect for the season.
He'll have his hands
all over you before you know it.
The stud of your dreams
won't be able to
take his eyes off of you.
-Wowee!
Delicious lingerie!
I mean cooking!
This makes zero sense.
My, my. As I fully expected,
it was quite the superb dish.
Even Chef Azami
is complementing it.
Way to go!
Now then, that's it
for the opening act.
Time for the real star
to take the stage.
Rindo Kobayashi's dish.
Ahh!
What is this?!
This is causa.
It's one of Peru's
most popular dishes,
a variety of seafood
and mashed potatoes
that are flattened into
a multi-layered dish
similar to pressed sushi.
You might even consider it an
eccentric take on potato salad.
First, the spear squid is
minced
and then mixed together
with egg whites and onions,
then seasoned with lemon
juice,
mayonnaise, and soy sauce
before getting fried,
completing the tender squid
burger at the core of this
dish.
One of the elements
in Peruvian cooking
is a paste made
from yellow chili pepper.
It's called aji amarillo,
and has given the potatoes
a yellow color.
And because she used Danshaku,
one of Hokkaido's
finest potatoes,
the richness of the squid
is more profound.
The biggest surprise
lies below the squid burger.
That layer is typically made up
of tuna as the main seafood.
However, it seems she made use
of a rather unconventional
ingredient instead.
Yep, it's pirarucu, the largest
freshwater fish in the world.
It's native
to the Amazon River basin.
There it is, the power
of the rare ingredient master.
What is pirarucu?
-Is it edible?
-Is it even legal to eat?
The white meat of this
large fish is light and soft,
making it quite luxurious.
If cooked properly,
it has a supple
and pleasant texture
similar to that of
a chicken tender.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm friends with a vendor
in Japan
who breeds them domestically,
and I've even been to the Amazon
to catch them myself,
That's downright awesome.
You have served up a dish
that is truly
befitting of you, Chef Rindo.
You have tamed
all of the savory flavors
in the great animal kingdom
and channeled them
into a gourmet dish
that is beyond compare.
Anne: Takumi Aldini's dish
truly was of high quality,
thanks to the balance
he struck between the flavors.
Decora: However, I can't believe
the tender pirarucu was
so effective in highlighting
the aroma of the squid.
Courage: I feel like my body
is being made
more elegant
just by eating it.
Yes! This is...
Anne: ...the absolute
perfect way to get into shape.
Decora:
Is your body too modest to fill
out a set of calamari lingerie?
Well, then this is for you.
By spending 15 minutes a day,
the pirarucu
will change your life
in just two weeks.
This is the miracle pirarucu
training course.
Even the shabbiest-looking girl
is about the ideal body.
Who are you
calling shabby?!
The judgment has been made.
I'm willing to hear objections.
I have no complaints.
Urara:
In a unanimous decision,
the winner of the second card
is Rindo Kobayashi!
Aaaaah!
We should have known
the second seed of the Ten
was just too powerful.
Even though they loved
Takumi's dish,
he still lost.
I can't believe this!
Damn it to hell!
You did good, brother.
♪♪
Rindo: Yo, Takumi.
I got to admit,
your dish was fantastic.
However, it looks like
in the end, ol' Chef Rindo
still comes out
on top of the mountain.
Yeah, I invested
literally everything
I had into
that single dish.
At this point in time,
you are undoubtedly better.
I hate to say it,
but that's the reality.
I'm glad you see it.
[ Chuckles ]
It's finally here,
the last card of the day.
It's Eishi Tsukasa
versus Satoshi Isshiki.
Come on.
I know he can do it.
But he's going up against
the first seed of the Ten,
Chef Eishi Tsukasa.
And the theme for this
is wild rabbit.
Rabbit meat?
You don't say?
I kind of remember using it
during French cooking class.
That's right.
And in fact,
rabbit meat is so
frequently used in French dishes
that preparing it
has been streamlined.
Which means that Chef Tsukasa
will know all about it.
I mean, he is a specialist
in French cuisine.
What about Isshiki and
his expertise in Japanese food?
There aren't many methods
that utilize animal meat
in traditional
Japanese cooking.
There are some regions
where people
have historically made venison
or boar meat part of their diet,
but our overall food
culture here
has shied away
from exotic stuff like that.
Hmm.
[ Slurps ]
[ Gags ]
In any case,
watching Soma drink tea
is killing the tension in here.
Oh, nice.
This is turning out perfectly.
It looks like he's preparing
a soup stock.
Even though he's going up
against the best of the Ten,
he seems to be having fun,
as usual.
He looks just the same
as he does
when we're cooking stuff up
at the dorms.
[ Satoshi humming ]
Nene: How can you enjoy cooking
in this situation so much?
You're not going to win this.
You know how strong
Chef Tsukasa is.
Maybe so.
But nobody can really know
until they try.
Besides, people who find joy
in what they do are invincible.
As you know, that's the motto
I live my life by.
Nene: It's unfair.
How? How is it
that Isshiki is so good
at everything he does?
No matter what it is,
he masters it so smoothly.
It's just not fair.
You're a cheater, Isshiki.
Must be nice
to be a genius.
Hmm?
I'll bet Isshiki will try using
a different type of cuisine
instead of Japanese!
-Oh, that's a good point!
He's a total pro at pretty much
any style of cooking
that's out there.
No doubt.
I'm sure he's got
tons of ideas
for dishes that work great
with rabbit.
[ Gasps ]
I'm going full on-Japanese.
This is my special
Isshiki chowder.
It brings out the best
in ingredients.
Wha...?
All: Japanese soup?!
You got to reconsider,
Chef Isshiki!
Please don't call
it Isshiki chowder!
Huh?
What got you in a tizzy?
A Japanese soup
with rabbit meat?
That sounds good to me.
It's not that simple!
Wild rabbit is a game meat
that has a very
profound stench!
Mm-hmm.
And despite that fact,
he chose to make
a Japanese dish
that's known for
being incredibly smooth.
It's true.
flavors much like these
would normally be considered
quite exquisite,
but can very quickly become
off-putting when it comes
to a traditional Japanese
soup like this.
Using wild game with a pungent
smell in this type of soup,
well, it's the most reckless
thing ever!
You've had to use
bear meat before, Soma.
You should know how hard
wild game is to prepare.
Oh, yeah,
that totally sucked.
I struggled with that one.
Okay, this is where
the real battle begins.
I cook the water out
of the rabbit giblets,
and now I'm adding them
to my kombu broth.
That will extract
all the wild umami flavor.
I'm going on the offensive
right till the end.
I can avoid making it
tart or bitter
and keep only umami flavor
by timing it right.
Wait for it.
Now's my chance.
My dish is complete.
Now, please,
allow yourself a taste.
The instant you take
the lid off
is the instant you can tell
the quality of Japanese soup.
The real test is
when the aroma wafts up.
How much of an impact
does it have?
♪♪
It's hare-raisingly soft!
What?!
Bro!
How is the stench of rabbit
not bringing it down?
It's authentic.
The aroma's so pure
it evokes peace of mind
like one feels when hugged
by their mother.
It's true the smell of rabbit
can be sharp and vicious,
but here it's merged with the
mellow aroma of the kombu broth.
All the typical harshness
has been taken away,
leaving only a pureness
that is more than suitable
for a traditional Japanese dish.
-We've been hop-nytized.
Nene: All it took was a whiff
to leave the WGO's bookmen
totally enraptured.
Soup stock
is the most intricate aspect
of Japanese cuisine,
and yet he found a way
to blend wild game
into its very essence.
Anne: The way the colors of each
ingredient are incorporated,
it's a magnificent work of art.
I'm being drawn
in just by looking at it.
A distinctive look
for chowder.
It's the work of genius.
Nene: I don't get it.
He was born in a line of
prestigious Japanese chefs
who value tradition
above all else.
So how can he break the mold
so much so easily?
I wish you didn't give me
such a scary look all the time.
You must really have a grudge
against me, huh?
-No, not at all.
-Oh, come on.
You've been like this
ever since we were kids.
Whenever you couldn't manage
to do what I did,
you'd start crying
right away.
I've never forgotten.
You're always the same,
making fun of me
because all I can do
is make dishes by the book.
Imagine how it feels
to watch
you and realize
how talentless I am.
Look, Nene, you should be
more proud of all your efforts.
You've spent
a lot of time learning.
Because the reality is
that without you,
I'm not even sure that I would
have continued being a chef.
-[ Gasps ]
-Okay, time to judge the taste.
[ Slurping ]
[ Both gasp ]
Amazing!
Finding a way to make
rabbit and kombu come together
in such a way
is an incredible feat.
But he even managed
to incorporate clam.
He used clam, bro!
Is it possible for anyone
to work shellfish and wild
game
into a Japanese broth?
By maintaining a nice balance
between both the clam
and the wild rabbit,
the resulting broth
is infused
with the saltiness
of the shellfish
and has a viscosity
that makes it more flavorful
than the typical
Japanese soup.
He created a broth
that opens
up a different way
of approaching
traditional Japanese soups.
Oh! So then he's created
a new standard.
Excellent work, Isshiki.
Well done.
Mm-hmm.
Surprise going from
smelling to tasting
is outstanding.
It's as if
he slowly tempts us
to the realm of
Japanese cuisine
by putting on
a captivating dance.
Plus, the way these ingredients
sit in the clear soup.
What are you
talking about, Isshiki?
How does you continuing
to be a chef
have anything to do with me?
I don't understand.
The real truth is that
you're my savior.
[ Gasps ]
You just haven't noticed it.
So, would you like
to hear my side now?
Isshiki: In Kyoto, there's
a famous Japanese restaurant
that has been around
since the Muromachi period.
I was born as the eldest son of
the family that owns it.
My training began the instant
I could understand
my surroundings.
Man: The first thing
you must learn
is those born
into the Isshiki family
aren't allowed to say the words,
"I can't."
Woman:
You will do just fine,
and I'm sure
you'll become a chef in no time.
I was never praised
for my accomplishments,
nor did I feel
any satisfaction.
My training dragged on
day in,
day out without giving me
any sort of excitement.
Back in that time of my life,
I hadn't had the experience
to understand what the purpose
of cooking even was.
But it was around then
that I met a certain
hardworking little girl.
We were training
at the same place.
As she learned
skill after skill,
I watched from the side
and saw the joy
and excitement in her face.
She was beautiful.
Seeing her lovely face
made me consider that,
for the first time,
maybe cooking can be something
for one to learn and enjoy,
that there's a certain charm
in learning such skills
so that people
appreciate your food.
And the name of the chef
who taught me
that important lesson was...
Nene Kinokuni.
I have nothing
but respect for you.
[ Gasps ]
So listen, Nene,
I want you to remember
how you felt
back in those days
when I found your face
so beautiful.
The ingredients inside.
Could it be there's something
packed within the mochi
that's in the middle?
Let's see.
[ Gasps ]
The crystal clear broth
is being colored by something!
This mild aroma.
It's miso!
The clear soup turned into
miso soup almost instantly.
All: What the...?!
Please let me explain.
The inside of that mochi
was packed with
minced rabbit
and green onions.
I slowly cooked them together
with some white miso paste.
The first sip leaves you
with the impression of
the clear broth,
but the rabbit
and miso gradually
spread their flavors
so you can enjoy
an evolving dish.
Please, try a taste
of the filled mochi
and give the soup
another sip.
♪♪
-Oh, my!
Anne: The white miso ties
the rich taste
of the rabbit meat
and the pure broth together!
Decora: It all blends into
absolute perfection!
As I recall, there's a phrase
to describe the movement
and change seen
in traditional arts.
Yes, this is it.
Jo-ha-kyu!
This is just like that.
Different types of beauty
that progress in stages
all in one bowl!
[ All cheering ]
This can only be described as
super-aggressive
Japanese cuisine!
Even Der Weisse Ritter der Tafel
would struggle
against this surging storm,
the ferocious attacks.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
One, two,
total domination!
[ Groaning ] One, two...