♪♪
Nene, if you keep following
Central like this,
do you really believe you'll be
able to enjoy cooking?
Isshiki, I...
Hey, uh...
[ Gasps ]
Yeah?
What, uh, can I do for you,
Chef Tsukasa?
Oh, nothing much.
Just wanted to say
that was an impressive dish.
You really are
quite amazing.
So, hey, if all goes well
and I end up being
the winner here today,
would you consider
joining Central
and serving
directly under me?
I'll make sure
you don't get expelled.
You have
an exceptional talent
when it comes to Japanese food,
Isshiki.
And I think you would make
an absolutely superb assistant.
A recruitment pitch
in the middle of a food war?
I can't believe
the nerve of this guy.
[ Chuckles ]
You never change, huh?
Always the same,
regardless the situation.
Just do me a favor
and think it over.
You have until they finish
judging my dish, okay?
Mm.
Now, then,
my dish is finished.
[ Footsteps echoing ]
Go ahead and please
help yourselves.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Urara: Satoshi Isshiki
of the Rebel Alliance
cooked up a very aggressive
Japanese soup for his dish.
Meanwhile,
from the Council of Ten,
Chef Eishi Tsukasa has made...
Anne:
Lièvre à la Royale,
a wild rabbit dish
fit for royalty.
It's said to be a top-class
French dish
once adored by King Louis.
As far as the royalty of France
is concerned,
when it comes to wild game,
this dish is the best
of the best.
Such an incredibly
profound fragrance.
The aroma alone says
that this is a premium dish.
I wonder how he incorporated
his own unique taste
into a traditional dish
such as this.
He sliced the useable meat
off the legs and neck
to form a ballotine
and then butterfly-cut
the rest of the rabbit meat
to wrap around it.
Then he sautéed the whole thing
perfectly,
keeping the meat juicy
while curbing the intense smell.
He made the sauce by boiling
a bone-and-meat broth
with red wine,
then adding foie gras,
chocolate, and rabbit blood.
This is superb,
with no flaws.
However,
the pure delectability
and the surprise I felt
with Mr. Isshiki's dish
makes it superior.
[ Cheering ]
Wait! It's not over!
There's more!
Huh?
What does that mean?
Something's got her
squirming.
There's something down
beneath the sauce!
Ah?
There's a strange layer to it
that's hidden under the sauce.
This is...
It's royale.
[ Screams ]
The flavor of porcini mushroom
is spreading
throughout my mouth!
The texture of it feels
so silky on my tongue
as it melts away.
Wait, I thought "royale" meant
it was a dish for royalty.
That's certainly
part of it.
But royale can also refer
to various fillings
that are chilled
so as to act as a firm custard.
It's like the French
version of chawanmushi.
It is fit for royalty,
with a Western twist.
That means this dish is playing
on both meanings of royale.
That's not the only thing
this dish was hiding from us.
There's also a fig and apple
puree with a chestnut confit.
The mildness of the royale
combined with the sweet
and sourness of the fruits
creates a refreshing
flavor profile.
This contrast downplays
the potent rabbit meat
and allows you to clean
your plate in no time at all.
It does it without killing
any of the impact.
How on Earth did he come up
with this dish?
Even if someone
had such an idea,
any normal chef
would never try it
because of
how complex it is.
Without a doubt,
this chef is a genius.
So much so,
he almost seems insane.
Okay, please paint something
that you really like, everyone.
Since we're doing
watercolor,
try combining different colors
to make your very own.
I did it!
It's such a pretty color.
Mm?
Oh!
[ Crying ]
Wah! Eishi stole the color
I just made!
Now, listen here, Eishi.
You can't do that.
Huh? But I thought
my painting
would come out
a whole lot better
if I were able to use
this color instead.
Tsukasa: I've had many
experiences just like that,
but that's just my life,
I guess.
It's the only way to make
my cooking feel truly
polished.
♪♪
[ Grunting ]
Tsukasa emerged the victor!
[ Cheers and applause ]
This sucks hard-core.
Insane.
Nobody can compete
with him.
I can't believe
Chef Isshiki lost.
Tsukasa: So, Isshiki,
did you think it over?
If you stick with the Rebels,
then you'll just get expelled.
Don't you think
that's a waste of your talent?
I don't.
I have to decline your offer.
Even if you strip me
and my fundoshi,
I'll never quit enjoying
cooking things my own way.
Isshiki: [ Sighs ]
I should have figured.
And Soma turned me down
once before, too.
I suppose I'm not cut out
to be the kind of guy
who has his own underlings.
Anyone with a brain
is smart enough
to refuse an invite
in that situation.
-Isshiki.
-Yeah?
Are you here
to console me?
[ Gasps ]
No, I'm not.
I just came
to remind you
that I said
you couldn't beat him.
You knew from the start.
Right, Isshiki?
This is the kind of person
that Chef Tsukasa is.
All he thinks about is how to
sharpen his own cooking
skills.
That's what makes him the best.
He's unbeatable.
Maybe.
Wait, what?
Well, then.
All I can do now is leave
the rest to these two.
Urara: That brings an end
to today's competition.
So we'll have
another war tomorrow.
We are now down to just
two chefs left in both teams.
If the teams end up
deadlocked in a tie
with one win apiece
in the fifth bout,
we will carry on
to a sixth.
-Nay!
-Hmm?
-[ Gasps ]
This very next bout
shall bring an end
to the regimental food war.
It will be the final bout!
-Grandfather, what?
-What's he mean?
How is it supposed to end
with the next match?
I'm changing how the match
will now be conducted.
The two members of both teams
will each prepare one dish,
but they'll be served
consecutively,
so teams are judged
over who makes the best course.
In other words, one shall
prepare the hors d'oeuvres
while the other member
of the team shall work
on making the main dish.
Two dishes
that go together?
To make a full course.
Really?
So that means the dishes
will be judged together.
Sweet!
This sounds like fun.
-Yeah.
-You are free to choose
whatever theme
ingredient you wish,
but in exchange, the task
you are assigned is
creating a multi-course meal
of true gourmet food.
Director Azami,
have you any objections?
None. Actually, I think
that it is a wonderful idea.
A cooking suite composed
by the duo of Tsukasa and Rindo.
I would love nothing more
than a fresh taste of it.
Besides, the current Council
of Ten perfectly embodies
what my vision
of an ideal chef is.
Although I don't feel
Erina is capable
of making true gourmet food.
[ Growling ]
I am merely stating
what I know to be true.
Erina: I wouldn't be
so confident.
I'm no longer
the person I used to be.
In fact, the dishes I make now
are beyond compare.
[ Azami chuckles lightly ]
All you see is a delinquent
daughter who ran away from home.
But that meek and obedient girl
you clearly have in mind
no longer exists.
Erina!
-Way to give it to him!
-[ Chuckles ]
At this young age,
it's perfectly natural
to become rebellious,
my dear.
As your father,
I accept that
and welcome you
to join us in Central.
But only after we've cleansed
you and removed all
impurities.
That is to be
your destined fate, Erina,
because you are the key
that is necessary
to guide all chefs
along their proper path.
Well, then, so be it.
See you on the morrow.
The victor shall forge
Totsuki's path to the future.
Put your best food forward,
you young and valiant chefs!
Woman:
Yeah, those two might stand
a real chance at this.
Woman #2: Soma and Erina have
both sharpened their skills
in the kitchen
to a new level.
They can definitely
produce a dish
that won't lose to the first
and second seats of the Ten.
All: Those two can do it!
Hey, Chef Rindo.
Huh?
Do you mind if I ask you
something real quick?
Huh?
Sure.
What is it, Takumi?
I apologize if I have
the wrong idea.
Really.
However, I could sense
something was off
during our battle earlier,
and I wanted to know.
So tell me, what exactly was it
that frightened you
during our battle
just now?
What?! I'm not scared,
you big old dummy!
I have no clue
what you're talking about.
I swear,
young punks like you
are just so full of themselves
these days!
Huh?
What's going on here?
Did you piss off Chef Rindo
or what?
Takumi:
Not intentionally.
Tomorrow is the day,
the end of the food war,
and all will be settled.
It makes me so nervous.
I'm not gonna be able
to sleep for a second night!
Tell us, is there anything
that the rest of us
can help you with?
Yeah, 'cause, I mean,
those two are fighting on behalf
of all of us who got kicked out.
Maybe we can help decide
what to make.
-No, no.
-Huh?
Everybody arguing
about what's best
is only going
to waste precious time.
But we can't just sit
on our butts doing nothing.
If you ask me, our role
is simply to have faith
and leave it all up
to little Soma For now.
Besides, a lack of sleep
is bad for your skin!
Get to bed if you want to stay
beautiful, girls.
[ Laughter ]
Girls: Alright.
Soma:
Let's go over it again.
First off -- a-wham! --
whip up a winning dish.
Then -- boom! --
we'll shove it in their faces!
So all you gotta do is stay cool
and cook up a good appetizer.
Why are you always so brainless
about everything?
You are going to sit right where
you are and listen to my lecture
and learn what an elegant
multi-course meal is!
[ Laughter ]
Wow. I've never seen a meeting
go this sideways before.
We really don't have time
for any of this nonsense.
Rindo:
Geez, it's freezing.
I'd say we've got
the perfect plan
for tomorrow's meal,
don't we?
Hey, you hear me?
Hmm?
Oh, sorry. I think it all
sounds really good.
Soma: Risotto-stuffed quail
with egg, Yukihira revised.
Limited edition mapo curry,
Yukihira revised.
Either of these dishes
could be called my specialty.
Erina:
Neither of them is esoteric
enough to be a main dish.
They didn't get selected as
main
dishes at Shino's, did they?
That's proof enough.
It's far too difficult to work
something like mapo noodles
into a coursed meal.
You haven't even been thought
to the overall balance
with these crazy dishes.
They're rejected!
Mmph!
See you later.
Make sure to rest up
for tomorrow, Tsukasa.
Same to you, Rindo.
Good night.
Hey, Rindo.
Oh! What's going on?
I'm sorry. In the end, I guess
I didn't have what it takes
to defeat you.
Megishima,
what are you going on about?
I can tell. I know who's been
struggling the most.
It's been you since the start,
hasn't it, Rindo?
Am I wrong?
I'm not saying this out
of personal preference,
but strategically, we both know
my abilities are far superior.
I should be the one
to make the main dish.
Huh?
It's never been made clear
which one of us is better!
I'm the 10th seat
on the Council
and you're just
a common student,
so it's obvious
that I'm better than you.
You gave up your seat on
the Council not that long ago.
That makes you
as common as me.
That doesn't
change anything.
[ Whimpering ]
How long are they gonna
keep this up?
Rindo: It used to be
a lot of fun, you know?
Innocently admiring the things
and places we couldn't reach.
We never gave
a single thought
to what would happen
after we actually made it.
♪♪
Swallows are totally
awesome, huh?
I can't believe
how high they can go.
But we've been watching them
for nearly 30 minutes now.
You're such a weird
little oddball, Rindo.
Yeah, well, not as much
as you are, Tsukasa.
You're always pressuring
the teachers during lectures,
giving them a hard time
while saying,
"I want to aim
for further perfection."
Wow, this dude is
kind of funny.
Yeah, well, that's me.
I have to try harder
than anyone else
if I want to survive
at Totsuki.
Okay, so, true.
And thanks to that,
you're sitting at the very top
of our class right now, Tsukasa.
I want to make dishes
more refined than anyone's,
and then I want to take
the first seat
on the Council of Ten.
Well, if you're taking
the first seat,
then I'm gonna take
the second seat.
Huh?
It'll be way more fun to aim for
the top if we do it together.
Uh, sure.
We're gonna go to Totsuki,
then it'll be
one-two domination!
Sounds good.
Rindo: And then
Tsukasa and I did just that.
We actually ended up
becoming the first
and second seats
on the Council of Ten.
Chef Tsukasa,
I thought you needed
to attend a gourmet banquet
with Chef Rindo today.
Yeah, but I've got an endless
amount of work to do.
That's not good.
Butchy and I will gladly
help you out with doing this.
I'll take care of
all the budget documents.
I'm really good
at crunching numbers.
Rindo: Tsukasa wasn't good
at a lot of things
outside of cooking,
but he kept doing his best
for the sake
of becoming a master chef.
This is
absolutely perfect!
They're incredible!
Delectable!
The first seat
is no joke!
Totsuki sure is
an impressive school.
Heavens, yes!
And I hear he's currently
the best student there.
[ Laughter ]
[ Tsukasa groans ]
Wait, what the heck is it
that's making me feel
so irritated?
Man: Welcome to Keiser Hotel's
exclusive gourmet banquet
for our grand platinum
members.
Today, we have a chef
from the famous Totsuki Academy.
He is the top student --
Eishi Tsukasa.
Please give him a hand!
Enjoy his cooking
to your heart's content!
Congratulations, Tsukasa.
You got invited to go overseas
to cook in a super fancy
restaurant.
-Most delectable.
-Simply amazing.
-I expect no less
from the first seat.
-Indeed.
[ Women oohing ]
Nice work!
You did awesome, Tsukasa.
Especially the main dish.
That sauce you chose to do
must have been a real challenge.
O-Oh, thanks for saying
that, Rindo.
Man: Dear me.
What a horrid banquet
that was.
It was so horrid, in fact,
that I found it amusing.
What the hell?
Who even are you?
Eishi Tsukasa,
the intense passion
you poured into your cooking
didn't reach any of those pigs
who were in attendance today,
now did it?
What?
And I know that main dish
you served
isn't one that you yourself
consider to be any good.
Isn't that right?
Is it still bothering you?
Who cares what some weird
skunk-headed jerk says, anyway?
Look, all the people there
loved that main dish of yours,
and I thought it was
totally unique, as well.
I'm not sure.
But lately,
whenever people I don't know
praise me for my cooking,
it really gets on my nerves.
I don't know why that is.
What?
But that man, he was
the only one thoughtful enough
to actually give me
any kind of real criticism.
Rindo: After that,
at some point
when Tsukasa was on his own,
he got approached.
Uh!
Say, you're the boy
I met in Vegas.
What a coincidence.
Coincidence?
It feels more like
you're following me around.
You should be happy
that we met again.
I think you've taken
an interest in me.
Am I wrong?
Suppose that Pablo Picasso
was still alive today.
Okay.
And imagine that he has just
unveiled a brand-new painting.
Would you be able to discern
whether or not
it was a genuine work
of genius?
That would be impossible.
I don't know very much
about painting or art.
I guess I'm impressed
by music sometimes
when they're able
to emphasize a single instrument
while also blending them
together.
Let's make this easier
by talking in terms of food.
You can deduce
a chef's ingenuity
from tasting their dish.
I'm sure you can agree.
But what about people
without any knowledge
or sense of cooking?
Doesn't matter how much
ingenuity you put into it
or what challenging
new methods you use.
Their reactions
will always be the same.
Just carrying the title
of the first seat
was enough to make those
self-proclaimed foodies
rave about your food.
Are you getting sick
of hearing from them?
All that energy you have should
be used for the sake of people
who truly understand
how incredible your skills
are.
For example,
people like me.
Then Tsukasa started
to search for and accept
more job offers
in America.
I only found out about it
after the fact,
but he had been meeting
with Azami Nakiri
every time he went.
What do you think it means
for a chef
to polish their skills?
Huh?
At a glance, the cooking
profession seems
like a vast wasteland,
but the truth
is the exact opposite.
There is a definite finish
line
for all chefs to reach.
As long as they know
the proper method,
anyone can reach
that goal,
and without
having to face any trouble.
I don't understand
how that would even work.
You must never heed any words
from the pigs of the world.
All you need to do is pay
attention to a single compass
with 100% accuracy
that knows how to get you there.
It's the only thing capable of
saving the chefs of the world.
And my daughter
happens to have it.
It is known as
the God Tongue.
The God Tongue?
Do you mean...
Someone you know well.
The 10th seat of the Council --
Erina Nakiri.
I'm her father.
Megishima: So, Azami Nakiri
must have already planned
his takeover
of Totsuki Academy
before he even got
so close to Tsukasa.
Rindo:
Hell if I know!
I don't really care
about all that stuff.
Then tell me,
why are you backing that guy?
Well, because...
Rindo: A new wave
is coming in to take over,
and the mere thought of
riding it makes my heart pound!
I thought that was
the best way to keep on
making tons of yummy stuff
alongside Tsukasa.
Now then, I have to hurry
and get some sleep
so I'm ready for tomorrow.
Good night, Megishima!
♪♪
Urara: The final bout
of the regimental food war!
The crowd and the judges
are all ready
to get this thing started.
What kind of heated battle
is awaiting us today?
Honestly, I'm really
looking forward to this!
Hey, Chef, how long
is that rose syrup you made
gonna have
that effect?
[ Urara giggling ]
Don't know, but I say
the longer the better,
because she's way cuter
like this.
If you would please have a look
over on the Council of Ten side,
we have Eishi Tsukasa
and Rindo Kobayashi
making their appearance.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Are you okay today,
Tsukasa?
I bet you're still feeling
some of the fatigue, aren't you?
No, oddly enough,
I'm feeling just about right.
Actually, I think that my senses
are extra sharp.
I might be
in top form today.
So, tell me, how are you two
going to split the workload?
Well, I'll be in charge
of the appetizer,
and Tsukasa is doing
the main dish.
There's no surprise that
he's in charge of the main
dish.
I wonder what Soma and Erina
decided.
Hey, Megumi,
how did things go last night?
[ All groaning ]
They're looking kind of
dead to me, but why?
What happened
at the strategy meeting?
Who's gonna make
the main dish?
Well...
Yeah, about that...
[ Grumbling ]
[ Groaning ]
Let's do this now,
Erina!
Fine!
Let's do it!
Together:
Throw down now!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Do it again now!
Shoot, shoot,
shoot, shoot!
[ Screaming ]
They have no sense
of teamwork at all!
-This is a disaster!
-Hm.
Shoot!
Gah! I'm doing
the appetizer?!
But I wanted to be the one
to deliver the final blow.
Hm!
This is for the best.
Urara: The two
on the Rebel Alliance side
seem to be chitchatting
about something.
But, come laugh or tears, this
is the end of everything!
The final bout begins!
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
The endowing pulse, pulse,
pulse, pulse!
Pulse, pulse, pulse!
[ Girls screaming ]