♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Announcer:
And now we're sure to see
even more action coming up here
in the second bout.
Cooking is steadily moving
forward for each of the cards.
Light it up!
[ Grunting ]
Wow, look at everyone go
out there.
They're really going
at full power.
As if.
Full power, huh?
There are other approaches
that are far more clever.
And who is the person who
lost to a first year, huh?
I am an altogether
different person now.
Look, Soma. I will crush you
and split you wide open.
How's Mimasaka doing?
He looks like
he's focused on something,
but I still can't
quite tell what it is.
He's gotta be using his perfect
trace technique, right?
Ah! You scared me.
What's your damage?!
Um...well, it's just that Chef
Kuga doesn't seem
to be using
green tea at all.
Yeah, he's right.
Meanwhile, look at
what Chef Tsukasa has.
He's got four
different kinds.
So he's going to use
all those in his dish?
The definition of green tea
is quite broad
and as such, there are
just as many applications.
Green tea is essentially
an unfermented tea.
It's dried immediately upon
harvesting to prevent oxidation.
There are many varieties --
Sencha, Gyokuro, Hojicha,
Kabusecha,
and that's just the tip
of the iceberg.
The flavor profiles are endless.
Still, that's the number-one
seed for you.
It's like he knows
how to speak to the ingredient.
Tsukasa:
Come out. Come out.
That's it.
Don't be afraid.
Come to me.
Sencha should be steeped
in hot water for 30 seconds,
drawing out [inaudible] and
giving it its bitterness.
Genmaicha, which lacks both
bitterness and umami,
should also be steeped
30 seconds in 95-degree water.
That will elevate its aroma.
The compounds in deep-steamed
Sencha, however,
are easily dissolved,
so it should be steeped
in 80-degree water.
Then there's Gyokuro --
2 minutes at 60 degrees
to allow its umami profile
to fully develop.
He's using an iron pot to boil
the water for the tea.
That will reduce
the harshness of the water,
giving it
a mellow flavor.
Splendid, isn't it?
These talented chefs
manipulating the ingredients,
bending them
to their very will.
And then there's
Eishi Tsukasa.
It's as if he's an attendant
that's pledged loyalty
to the sovereign
ingredient,
whose sword is keen
and swift.
What the heck?
It looks like it's just
a simple cheese grater,
but I don't think
I've ever come across one
that gigantic before.
Looks like a blade
that a knife would wield.
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
♪♪
His prep's done
in no time flat.
This guy has such
remarkable precision.
Girl: His treatment of the tea
is beyond perfect,
and that's just the beginning.
Oh, God. How can we even fight
against that?
You seem to have been
supremely focused on your wok
for quite a while now.
You doing okay there,
Kuga?
Limiting oneself
to a specific culinary field
might not be
the best choice.
Staying trapped inside
that bubble could prevent you
from reaching
new heights of flavor.
It's not that I don't admire
your zeal,
but at this rate,
without a broad palette,
I highly doubt
it's even possible
you could ever defeat me.
Mimasaka:
You sure about that?
Huh?
♪♪
As I recall,
the rules allow us
to help fellow team members
with their dishes.
That's the essence of
the regimental food war, right?
Much obliged, Mimasaka.
Chef Kuga has finally
brought out the green tea.
Mimasaka must have been
waiting this whole time
until it was finished.
Well, well,
isn't that something?
He's using his traceability
to help out an ally.
So then that's how Mimasaka
was able to get the timing
down just right.
Alright!
That was perfect, Mimasaka!
Yeah!
You better believe it,
girlfriend.
I wouldn't leave someone
hanging out like that.
Time for that pansy-ass
Tsukasa to go down.
Could you please cut that out?
Thanks a bunch, Mimasaka.
This is where Terunori Kuga's
dish kicks it into high gear.
What the heck is that?
He's using a wok?
He's lined it with tin foil
and added a grill.
He's come up with
a makeshift smoker.
It's a smoker?
That's right. Chef Kuga's plan
is to use the tea
as part of the smoking process.
That sounds just wonderful.
He's been over there
slow-cooking that pork shoulder
like that so as to get the
surface all nice and crispy.
Taking that stir-fried pork
and choosing to smoke it
rather than braise it
is an interesting idea indeed.
Smoking allows for a more direct
infusion of the tea's aroma,
passing it to the key
ingredient.
Eishi Tsukasa, however,
we'll be taking
an alternate approach
to the tea.
Oh, whoa.
So then you can even use
a wok just like a grill.
I'm gonna try that
next time.
So what was the deal with that
black liquid from earlier?
Kuga: Just you wait.
It's coming up next, Soma.
Along with the smoke,
I'll be using a sauce
that will knock him dead.
First a balsamic reduction.
Then after that, I'll be adding
black vinegar and sugar
and some powdered green tea.
And then finally,
the pièce de résistance,
this smoked soy sauce.
That's smoked soy sauce?
Yes, that is
exactly what it is.
And Mimasaka
has been over there
smoking it
this entire time.
When soy sauce is
smoked like that,
it becomes even more mellow
an altogether different depth
of lingering flavor.
It certainly
does smell delicious.
By infusing that smoky aroma
into the meat
as well as the sauce,
it creates a profile
that's more multilayered.
That's quite the innovation,
I will say.
And I would also say
excellent teamwork.
Ha ha. So it's like Chef Tsukasa
has to go up against
two amazing chefs
at the same time.
Hey, Kuga.
Yeah?
Weren't you the one going on
about taking on Tsukasa
one on one?
Shut up.
I may not look it,
but I'm a grown up, okay?
I mean, I'm not the one
who's splitting up
my personal pride first.
If you haven't noticed,
my one big role here
is to take you down
at all costs, Tsukasa.
I see. You'll abandon
your sense of self for the win.
It would seem you're not exactly
the same Chef Kuga anymore,
now, are you?
Is that so?
I'm afraid your days
of being unbeaten
are finally now
at an end.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
Still, has Subaru Mimasaka
been able to work
on his own dish
during this time?
He's had to devote
both time and attention
just to lending support,
yes?
Yeah. I guess you have
an excellent point there.
And it goes without saying he's
facing one serious opponent,
the current number-four seed
on the team,
a genius of our time
in the world of sushi,
none other than the Somei Saito.
-He's really a sushi chef?
He must suffer tuna
as the theme ingredient,
and he's facing
an actual sushi chef?
That's too unlucky.
He is one unlucky bastard,
even worse than Soma.
I'm not that unlucky.
Why would you even think that?
Also just take a look.
Check out Mimasaka.
That's the face of a guy
who's gonna pull something off.
Saito: You are sadly
a most unfortunate man.
No corners shall be given.
For when I stand before
the cutting board,
I pour my heart
and soul into my technique.
[ Roars ]
Did you see how fast
he sliced up that tuna?
Power and technique.
The skill of a high-ranking
member of the 10.
[ Yells ]
♪♪
And I'd say Mimasaka's
coming along
with his butchering
as well.
Hyoah!
♪♪
What the heck is going on?
There's no time lag at all.
He's perfectly copying
that super-speed technique.
Perfect trace. Flash!
Just like that burst
of strobe lighting
from the cameras,
I can instantly read
an opponent's thoughts
and movements and replicate
the entire procedure perfectly.
I understand.
This allows him to spend
absolutely zero effort
in planning
his own dish.
While his opponent was busy
considering exactly
what recipe to create,
Mimasaka
was supporting Kuga,
concentrating solely
on the smoked soy sauce instead.
It really was done
in a flash.
That's on a whole
different level
from the trace he's used so far.
So when the heck did
his copying ability
get this good, huh?
-Oh, wow.
-Well, well.
I'd say this is
quite encouraging.
I just knew you would
pull something off, Mimasaka.
And now they're going to see
just how strong we rebels are
as a team.
Now then,
this one is Saito.
He walks a culinary path
you could not imagine.
You can even mimic that
which has been learned
through the swift cut
of the blade.
Your skills
are impressive.
That is not
in question here.
The bushy warrior
may be noble,
but never with these little lips
uttered this one before I.
You do say that.
He does, huh?
You do.
Totally.
Yes, you do.
You, too?
[ Laughter ]
No matter.
Give me just one moment.
Hyah!
He butchered the rest
of it all at once.
Use this.
The blade you use
lacks sufficient quality.
It would surely
become damaged,
thus you should wield
[speaks Japanese]
my trusted blade.
It is a reflection
of my own bushido.
-Bushido?!
Oh, here we go yet again.
We're seeing Saito's tired
old habits as usual.
Habits?
No matter how trivial,
he's determined to see
all things
as bushido-esque.
What's bushido-esque?
It is an honor to wield.
With a blade such as this,
this one shall be able
to perform my tricks
to perfection.
Yeah!
Now the preparations
are complete.
It is time to begin things
in earnest.
Give it your all.
Of course.
The cuts will get a marinade
of a mixture of soy sauce,
sweet sake.
All that butter and sear
just one side of the cheek
to get that savory aroma.
What is this madness?
He's using completely
different methods
for each of the cuts.
What kind of sushi
is he making?
What is that?
It's straw.
-But why use that?
-[ Speaks indistinctly ]
Just light a fire and that
will be one kick-ass grill.
Mimasaka is like Chef Kuga
in this.
He is trying anything
and everything in order to win.
♪♪
Mimasaka:
To think using my image trace,
and all of them would wear me
out this much, but...
Next time, I won't lose.
That's what makes a true chef
after all.
Mimasaka: Takumi Aldini
and Soma Yukihira.
It's thanks to you two
that I'm still standing in front
of the cooking counter
and haven't given up.
I have to repay that debt.
This one here is Somei Saito.
One must not falter.
Alright! I'm Chef Rindo,
totally Chef Rindo!
For the sake of fine dining,
I shall devote all,
such is the cooking
of Eishi Tsukasa.
Yukihira, I'll crush
and split you open.
Come on, Poochie.
Have a talk with
your best pal, Momo.
You sure are a cutie poochie.
Meow, meow.
Just die.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
It's not like I'm here
doing this for you.
Just who are you calling cute,
you idiot?
Mimasaka: Deeper.
I have to take my trace
even deeper.
♪♪
Okay.
Now to arrange things.
♪♪
I apologize for the wait.
They've been at the same pace
the whole time,
but Chef Saito has finished
cooking first.
Such beautiful presentation,
various shades
of red all glistening
so vibrantly.
Pretty.
Look at that.
They're even tinier
than the temari sushi I made,
but this isn't
the fall selection.
Cute!
Saito: I present a 10-piece
course of mini ruby red tuna.
Please taste the perfection
for yourselves.
So this --
this is the ultimate sushi
prepared by the
preeminent expert?
It's said that in Kyoto,
there is sushi
that's tiny enough
for the apprentice geisha to eat
without ever disturbing
their makeup.
This dish is indeed
a distillation
of the Japanese
cuteness aesthetic.
They're kind of cute
with the tuna
all front
and center like that.
Yeah.
This one apologizes
for the wait.
-There's that perfect trace!
-Check it, bro.
Man: His sushi looks
completely identical.
Man #2: Wait. Look closely.
One is different.
Man #3: You're right.
Chef Saito didn't have
that gunkan Maki.
So that one must be
the Mimasaka original,
the point where the flavors
will differ.
-Wah!
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
Quit talking like
he's got an actual chance
against Chef Saito.
Got it?!
The skills
of a sushi chef are sublime.
It's a long and harsh road.
A single day wouldn't even
get your foot in the door.
There's no way some ridiculous
fool like you
can make amazing sushi
just by copying what you see.
Why not try it for yourself
and tell me?
Huh?!
Go on.
Have a taste.
[ Whimpers ]
Well, of course
I'll freaking eat it, loser!
-Whoa!
-Oh!
Mm.
[ Gasps ]
Such bliss!
Huh?
Wh-- what?
Oh. Oh.
[ Sighing ]
The flavors from each part
of the tuna
are perfectly,
flawlessly executed,
And the rice -- this is
no ordinary vinegared rice.
You're correct in that.
I cooked it
in red vinegar instead.
Red vinegar is made
from sake leaves
and fermented
over an extended time.
It's a product that takes
five to six years to mature.
So then, tell me
what you think.
Well done.
Sure enough,
because it is less sweet
and has a nice mellow flavor,
rice will become
light and fluffy
whenever it gets absorbed.
True. However,
elevating its flavor
while achieving harmony
with the ingredient
requires a nice,
delicate touch.
Mimasaka was somehow able
to make a copy of that
as perfectly as he did
everything else.
Damn it!
His amazing flavor is for sure
on the same level
as a high-ranking member
of the 10.
-Aah!
It's like he pairs
the cutting of a deadly snake
with a passion
that glows ruby red.
Aah! My body's so hot!
How it burns!
I've avoided all sorts of
reactions up until now,
but this...
No. No!
I can't take it!
I'm ruined!
I'm no longer fit to be a bride.
[ All cheering ]
Well, it's no use for you
trying to avoid it.
Is it, Miss Emcee?
As we know, sushi is best
when it's freshly made,
so I may as well eat --
-Now, hold it right there.
I, Chef Rindo, will be calling
the shots here.
♪♪
Now, then, I'd like you to have
some of this dish
before it gets cold.
What?
The meat is
totally buried
under the chili
peppers, dude!
I call this awesome dish
firecracker chicken style kamen.
I finished mine as well --
African ramen.
Chef Megishima's dish
doesn't look very red,
though.
Where are the peppers,
the themed ingredient?
Well, then, we'll just have
to try all four dishes together.
Wha-- Wait.
All of them at once?
But the flavors
will get all jumbly.
Are they even
allowed to do that?
Well, of course
we are.
Yes, for we are
the esteemed bookmen,
gatekeepers
of fine cuisine, the WGO.
Woman: And so we shall now
start our deliberations.
I think I will try some of this
delicious sushi first.
Mmm. Is this bright-red paste
the chili pepper element?
♪♪
-Oh!
Both: These ingredients are like
one fierce volley after another.
♪♪
-Oh!
-A direct hit.
-There it is.
-That's one gratifying reaction.
Oh, my goodness.
Neither of these sushi
are lacking at all,
but the one that nails it,
the noten sushi grilled
with straw and grass.
It's most excellent
and divine.
What is noten?
Even among tuna,
it's known as a top-class cut,
a pricey, rare piece
of meat called sunatoro.
Grilling it with straw gets rid
of the unpleasant raw odor,
leaving it with nothing
but a pure, rich aroma.
His trace was perfection.
So then it will be the gunkan
Maki that decides who wins.
Oh, Negitoro topped
with a savory meringue.
The aroma of the smoked
soy sauce is most effective.
Not only was he supporting
a teammate,
but he also arranged it
for his own needs.
It's not just smoky.
Oh, no.
The differing textures
of Negitoro and meringue
create more flavor.
Yes!
The ultimate gunkan sushi
combining Negitoro
with egg-topped rice.
[ All cheering ]
What about
Chef Megishima's ramen?
That is harissa.
It's a condiment
said to have originated
in North Africa.
The ingredients are
paprika powder,
caraway seeds,
lemon juice, garlic,
and a great deal
of chili peppers.
They are ground up and turned
into a paste
used for African dishes.
I remember my dad made harissa
at the dorm once.
He said it had something to do
with Africa.
The soup base
is a chicken muamba,
a well known
savory African chicken dish
stewed with nuts
and tomatoes.
It serves as the trigger
for the spicy harissa.
Hyuh!
Along with the slices
of braised pork,
he's added peanut butter,
which offsets some of the heat
from the harissa
that permeates the noodles
in the broth.
Yes! Yes!
My body cries out
from this deliciousness.
Such heat!
Aah!
The African ramen
was well received.
Alright! Yes!
We can do it!
Two top seats on the 10
have been shut down!
[ Laughs ]
And now we have the final
winning results
for the second
and third competitors.
Ha ha!
Well, you see that, you filthy,
moronic rebel bums.
You're no match at all
for the 10.
You're not even close.
[ Cheering ]
But how can that possibly be?
That arrangement
should have been perfection.
It was not the gunkan Maki
that led to your defeat,
but your protein scoring.
If so, then it was
all part of my perfect trace.
I couldn't have failed.
By scoring
the protein first,
it means the second you take
a bite, it melts in your mouth,
creating a wave
of delicious flavor.
Yes, your version was
quite splendid indeed,
but what I made
for the judges
was bite-sized
Kodama sushi.
It seems you understand
you made the common mistake
of applying too much scoring
on a piece of fish.
If you apply the knife
as you would with normal sushi,
the protein will melt
too quickly.
In order to prolong
that deliciousness,
you must learn
to control your scoring.
It seems you were unable
to trace
that extremely subtle difference
in my technique.
You mustn't blame yourself
with that mistake.
It is merely a difference
in our experiences
forged along the path
of sushi.
No. But what -- what about Chef
Megishima's African ramen?
What about all the high praise
you gave it?
True, his African ramen
was most spectacular,
but it can be said
Rindo Kobayashi's dish
has eclipsed even that.
By using the techniques
of firecracker chicken,
she was able to take
the mild flavor of the alligator
and give it
a whole new dimension.
-[ Trumpets ]
-[ Roars ]
♪♪
Ha ha.
Sorry, Megishima.
It looks like the difference
in skill level
has made me the winner.
I guess a battle is a battle.
I have no regrets.
Nothing to worry about.
We're still standing here.
How right you are, Soma.
Would you be so kind as
to assume the battle is over?
Terunori Kuga has still
more dishes to serve up!
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]