Anne: In the second card
of the third bout,
the winner is from
the rebel's side, Takumi Aldini.
Grazie!
[ Cheering ]
Sun Tzu said, "If you know
your enemy and yourself,
you need not fear the results
of a hundred battles."
Very well done,
Takumi.
a rival you may be,
but I applaud your tenacity.
That's my bro.
It's a hell of a victory.
That makes the total wins
even now -- 4 against 4.
The remaining card is
Chef Somei Saito
versus Soma Yukihira.
Their theme ingredient --
butter.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Soma!
We're counting on ya!
The theme ingredient
for this card is butter,
but what could they make
that actually showcases butter
as the theme ingredient?
You've got
a point there.
What actually
makes a butter dish?
You can't use it
as the main ingredient.
Maybe butter sautéed whitefish
or some scallops.
But could you say butter plays
a starring role in those?
What about
buttered potatoes?
That would be
way too simple.
I'm sure that Soma will think
of something special.
I mean, after all,
butter was used
in Miss Erina's Hokkaido
instructional class.
Oh, is that so?
What was the lecture,
Erina?
If you must know,
it was a thorough overview from
the European history of butter
to its chemical constituents.
You can now call Soma
a professor of butter.
[ Snoring ]
It's embarrassing to admit
he spent most of it asleep.
Well, let's just believe
he at least learned something.
In some cuisines,
such as French,
there are a few dishes
that don't use butter.
Not just France,
but northern countries as well.
There are any number of ways
it could be utilized.
That's right. I'm anxious to see
what sort of approach
Chef Saito
will take in this.
Huh?
Hyah!
Oranges?
He started squeezing
a whole bunch of oranges.
Perfect.
Ah. I see
what Saito's goal is.
Now we're even more curious
about the final product.
Meanwhile, what kind of dish is
Soma Yukihira up to over there?
What's this?
Mochi?
Yep.
Three cup mochi.
I sure was surprised
to see this
among the ingredients
in the warehouse.
I've got soy milk boiling
on the stove
in which I'll throw some thin
sliced mochi
and slowly stir
it 'til it's melted
and add some salt and pepper,
then my kinda sorta
white sauce is complete.
It's a nice technique we'd use
at home when we had leftovers.
This sounds like
an interesting concept.
Normally, white sauce is made
by melting butter with flour,
then adding milk while
continuing to heat and stir.
That method would more
fully accentuate the butter.
So, why is he using
mochi then?
The answer to that will become
clear during tasting,
and I can't wait
to get started.
Both contestants simultaneously
dropped the theme ingredient,
butter,
into their frying pan.
Oh, man!
I can't take it!
The smell
of that butter
is going to melt
your brain matter, brah!
It's like a butter
tsunami!
It looks like Soma Yukihira
is now pan frying chicken
with onions, shrimp,
as well as uncooked rice.
Meanwhile, Somei Saito has let
the garlic aromas
fully develop before adding
soy sauce, squid,
some delicious
squid liver.
He's taking that exquisite
tidal wave of aroma
and elevating it
even higher through
the rich flavor
of butter.
This is when the cooking
really begins.
We can't even afford to blink.
This duel is under way.
Wait.
If he's using that wooden cover,
he must be simmering
something.
As his opponent,
I can sense it.
This man has not yet
drawn his true blade.
Interesting. By all means,
young
chef, come at me by surprise.
Before I strike
you down first.
Huh?
Mm?
What are you
doing in here?
Well, I thought I'd get myself
some coffee in the kitchen.
What are you doing?
Well, isn't it obvious,
Nene?
Naturally, I couldn't resist
the pleasure of a morning bath
and massage.
So, where are Chef Tsukasa
and Chef Rindo?
They're both resting
in their rooms.
Still in hibernation,
huh?
And you? Are you not going
to the food war today?
I've already done everything
I possibly can. What about you?
What are you still doing
in the hotel?
Hard to show your face to the
public after losing?
Is that it?
You know you never had
a chance of winning, right?
Excuse me?
I just feel bad
for not one,
but two people who took on
a challenge only to be defeated.
[ Both growl ]
Well, say what you must,
but you're going to regret
taking on little Soma.
He's a first year
he's earned my respect.
I actually thought he was
just a piece of crap loser
back when we all
first met him.
Huh?
That first day he transferred,
in at the opening ceremony,
I was there helping out.
I saw the whole thing.
So, um,
my name's Soma Yukihira.
And, well, to be honest,
it's an honor
to attend this school
as a stepping stone
in my career.
Now, sure, my transfer
was kind of unexpected,
but I still don't plan on
losing to a bunch of wannabes
who've never stood in front
of a customer before.
I mean, come on,
am I right?
Anyway, since I'm here
and everything,
I might as well
take the top spot.
That sounds
like Soma, alright?
He might actually take
that top spot
at the regimental food war.
It's never gonna happen.
Even you are aware of that.
You know how strong
Chef Saito is.
Saito:
The time has come.
Yet, interestingly,
you choose not to draw first.
So, in that case,
I shall strike.
Well?
Do you think
you'll be able to meet
the sharpened blade
I have unsheathed before you?
The steam rising off that
salmon meuniere is impressive,
like a strong
blast of butter.
The pan fried squid liver has
an
exquisite fragrance,
garlic and soy sauce.
With some burst in your mouth
soy marinated salmon roe
added to it.
That's
an unbeatable lineup
of first rate
ingredients.
Chef Somei Saito has served up
a lavish
butter-cooked
seafood masterpiece!
Eh...
Hey, Yuki,
you're drooling.
It can't be
helped, now can it?
Finally,
Soma Yukihira.
It is time for us
to cross swords.
[ Dish clatters ]
The second you cut it,
it releases more steam.
My body is aflame
with anticipation.
Whoa!
The wave is coming!
Histoire: Riding the top
white cap of butter
comes this marvel
of seafood!
Carde: It's an onslaught
upon the tongue!
All: I can't stop myself
from eating!
The slow fried salmon.
The flour with a hint of sugar
reacts on a chemical level
with the butter,
producing an exquisite richness
to create the ultimate meuniere.
It's as if the saltiness
and delightful bitterness
of the squid liver
have completely incorporated
the flavor of the butter.
The soy marinated roe has been
paired with pomegranates
and tonburi caviar.
The butter has fused
these three ingredients
into a perfect blend.
And also, the secret
to his use of butter
not being too cloyingly rich
lies in that special
vinegared rice
of his,
an original vinegar made
using both orange
and lemon juice.
He put oranges
and lemons in it?
So that's what all those
oranges
and lemons were for.
When pairing
the fattiness of the seafood
with that of
the greasy butter,
it naturally becomes too rich
for one to consume.
Which is why, to avoid that
and create
a more pleasing
flavor to enjoy,
he instead went with using
the sharp tang of oranges.
French cuisines,
among some others,
have sauces that traditionally
pair butter with oranges.
Ikumi:
But to think of showcasing
the butter by pairing
it with vinegared rice!
It's what led him to this.
A dish showcasing
the buttery aroma.
You're not lying. That bastard
hit it out of the ballpark.
It's like a duel
between two fighting warriors.
And in this case,
he's drawn his blade
and poured the entirety
of his soul into it.
♪♪
It's amazing.
Too amazing.
Yet we still have
another dish to judge.
I don't care
if I get full on this alone.
I really hate
to admit it,
but that just seems like
it's pretty friggin' delicious
according to all
the judges.
He's managed to nail it
in one damn bowl.
I thought maybe Soma
would have at least
a slight advantage with this.
I would have never imagined
you could feature butter
in a seafood bowl.
Although, it has no business
being used in sushi like this.
My primary duty
is to the sushi,
which is precisely why
I was able to utilize butter.
People may think
the quality of sushi rests
solely
in the cut of the fish,
but that is not all
that big sushi so special.
The main ingredients
are supported by shadow players.
Salt and vinegar are added
for an exquisite balance,
bringing forth the true flavor
of the fish.
And it is true of all dishes.
It is the supporting ingredients
that allow the blade
that is the fish to shine
in the capacity that it's meant.
Put simply,
all secondary ingredients
are within my realm of
expertise,
all are striking.
And he's not just talking
a big game either.
It doesn't matter how delicious
a fish you have,
the ingredients you pair it
with can sink the whole dish
if you don't know
what you're doing.
Such an attachment
towards fish.
Just where does
it come from?
Chef Saito's place was small,
but beloved
by regular customers,
some of whom visited daily.
Hey Mom!
I finished deliveries!
Thanks for doing that.
Sorry for always having you
deliver.
Uh, kado, please.
Coming up.
Isshiki: He had much love
and respect for his mother.
She worked the counter
all alone, raising her son,
and even managing to get him
into Totsuki Academy.
Saito: I want to hurry up
and be a first rate sushi chef,
just like Mom.
Then we can run
the shop together.
Somei, listen up, your mom has
been accepted as an understudy
at Shigarami Sushi.
Wow.
That's an old famous shop.
That's awesome, Mom.
I'll have to close this place
up
for a little while, though,
but by the end of it,
I'll be able to make sushi
that's even more delicious
than before.
Isshiki:
However, what awaited his mother
was a traditional setting,
one of nothing but hardship
and prejudice,
a place with the old way
of thinking
that a woman didn't belong
behind the counter.
Not only was she not allowed
to handle the fish,
she couldn't even
touch the rice.
So she spent her days doing
menial tasks,
morning 'til night.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I'm sorry...my son.
Mother, please endure.
Please.
By my sword,
this one shall make his name
in the world
and provide for my household.
Mom, I will save
our shop.
Now, take a look at this.
That little punk-ass really
is working behind the counter.
Well, if it isn't
Shigarami Sushi.
You've got a lot of talk,
but that's about it.
Like your punk ass
could make worthy sushi.
Okay, then. Would you care
to try some?
[ Grunting ]
[ Bodies thudding ]
If you try to go
up against us,
I swear to you, you'll never
make it in the industry.
Prevailing in times of strife
is the hallmark of a warrior.
Nothing is greater
than defeating you.
Isshiki: That's how Chef Saito..
Hyah!
...set out on his own.
Huah!
Isshiki: And using that single
blade called fish...
Huah!
...has made his way this far.
Sure enough, this buttered
seafood bowl
perfectly encapsulates
his cooking style.
The seafood is the blade,
while the butter is the sheath
that guides it forward.
It's like the art of sword
drawing made into a dish.
When faced
with such an attack,
all who eat it...
All:
...must surely fall!
That's Chef Saito
for you guys.
He struck down the judges
with a single blow.
He just made 100%
perfect use of the butter.
Can Soma
even compete against this?
This could actually be bad.
What?
What did he say?
No, no. Hold on, what's going on
with you, Soma?
This could actually be bad.
Doesn't sound like you.
There are things only two
opponents facing each other
can understand.
You've already seen this,
yes?
Soma Yukihira?
The vision of your long sword
delivered with might
only to be shattered
to pieces.
Sure enough, your cooking's
pretty awesome looking, Chef.
So tell me,
why would an honorable person
like you side with Central?
It is the duty of a warrior
to be wield his blade
in defense of the weak,
and as you very well know,
there cannot be another victim
like your mother.
So, help me make sure
of that.
Being part of this revolution
is following the bushido way.
It is for the sake of protecting
those who are weak.
Oh, yeah? But if that's so,
the same goes for me.
A perfect world,
an ideal place.
It's for that
I'm using this dish
so I can take
your ass down.
All right, all right!
Sorry for the wait!
[ Gasp ]
Order up!
Yukihira style! Rich butter
pilaf inarizushi!
[ Gasps ]
He used that pot with the lid to
fry the tofu skins.
And he stuffed them
with a pilaf
instead of the typical
vinegared rice.
[ Stomachs growling ]
Oh...
It has
such incredible impact!
My stomach suddenly
feels empty.
It's so savory.
I feel like I could melt.
Normally, it's the contrast
between the sweet fried
outer layer
and the vinegared rice
that makes inarizushi.
Butter pilaf would be
too overpowering.
Simply emphasizing
the theme ingredient
would be
insufficient.
How then has he chosen
to answer this?
We shall see.
Ah!
With each bite, the taste of
butter infused tofu skin
floods my mouth
like a slippery invader.
The butter is seeping
into my very brain!
When paired with the plump
and juicy tofu skin,
the pilaf within comes across
as delicate and refined.
It's not overpowering
at all.
The ingredients burst forth
like a geyser of flavor.
All: This is such
a perfect combination!
I know, right?
The key was to do up the rice
without rinsing it first,
then before seasoning
the fried skin,
I rinsed it
to remove the oil.
But the most
important thing of all
was the kinda
sorta white sauce,
which I made with soy milk
and sliced mochi.
I see
what you did there.
A normal white sauce
using butter and flour
would have been way too heavy
and risk ruining the dish.
This has depth and creaminess,
but it's not oily.
That's what made
the uniquely light flavor
of this mochi based white sauce
so indispensable.
That I topped it
with some different cheeses
and baked it in the oven.
That's what makes it
so crispy.
Doing it like that also
emphasizes the saltiness
as well as
the smooth creaminess of it.
This dish pretty much takes
all the most delicious things
I could have
ever thought of
and then ramps
up the flavors to their max.
Some ingredients blend softly
into the richness of the butter,
and other ingredients
become even richer with it.
You can tell the great amount
of skill
that lies within these tiny,
scrumptious inarizushi.
The magical mochi white sauce
he brilliantly added
cuts the oiliness
and emphasizes each ingredient
so very, very much.
It's a swift slash, a counter
attack to Somei Saito's
heavy handed sword,
like endless blades striking
from all directions.
It's so
incredibly delicious
that I can't contain
my voice. Anne. Anne.
Anne! Anne! Anne!
Anne! Anne!
Both: Anne!
This was a duel
between two,
yet somehow I feel the sting
for more than just one blade.
Just what are you?
How did you gain such fast,
powerful strength?
Because I knew I was in trouble
going up against you.
This could actually be bad.
I knew I'd never be able
to beat you with the edge
of just one blade.
A mock food war?
What exactly do you mean,
Mimasaka?
As you all know, I have
performed by perfect trace
on all the members of the Ten.
Uh...
So, I'll battle you all
as if I were the person you will
face tomorrow
in a mock food war.
But will you be able
to handle that many?
Wouldn't that
take a toll?
Battling
as three different people?
I've already
lost my battle.
So, this is the extent
of what I can do for you.
Won't you please use me
as your punching bag?
Well then, when you
put it like that,
I guess I'll take
you up on it.
Let's get to training!
Takumi: Yeah!
Megumi:Okay!
So long
as you've got cash,
anything goes.
Morals? I've never heard of
such a thing.
How do they taste,
Aldini?
Megum-yan. Megum-yan.
Megum-yan-yan.
[ Grunts ]
No good.
Ah!
No matter what I try,
I just can't win with a blade
that's only this sharp.
What I need is...
That's it!
The saltiness of various cheeses
creates a brilliant balance.
So, that's it,
then.
Takumi put this cheese blend
together,
making sure it paired well
with the inarizushi.
Ah.
I understand now.
That's how
the flavors are so rich,
but not overpowering.
He used Megumi Tadokoro's
apple butter.
Its sweet,
invigorating flavor
toned down
the other elements.
Yes.
Good job, Soma.
This is indeed
a regimental food war.
[ Grunts ]
Hyah!
And yet, there were more
than three slashes.
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Tokumi special
killer cheese!
Akira style
fragrance burst!
Ryo shrimp
awesomeness!
Megumi's apple infused
butter!
He's not even
using blades anymore.
Yoshino family super delish
chicken stock!
There is a limit to how
flippant one can be.
[ Grunts ]
Ever have I honed my blade
for the sake of victory,
yet in order
to defeat me,
you have wielded not one,
but numerous sharpened blades.
You've mastered the bushido
way and are a true warrior.
Nah, I'm just
some upstart first year.
However, I've gone toe to toe
with a whole bunch of chefs.
Could be that I've learned
some stuff along the way,
and everything I've picked up
from other cooks
I'm sure will continue
to inspire me.
Soma:
And well, to be honest,
it's an honor
to attend this school
as a stepping stone
in my career.
Because I'm a first year
and the 92nd second class
here at Totsuki Academy.
And my name
is Soma Yukihira.
♪♪
That dish was not just the
result of specialized
training.
It's the culinary culmination,
everything he's learned
since the day he transferred
to Totsuki.
How very foolish
of me.
It was my mother's remorse
that drove me to think
that the weak must be protected.
This is why I became
so powerful,
But Soma Yukihira,
you do not classify
any chef as strong or weak.
In fact,
you have learned something
from all of their blades,
you have walked
the true path of bushido.
I concede.
It's unanimous.
-The winner is...
From the rebellion side,
Soma Yukihira.
[ Cheering ]
♪♪
[ Exhales sharply ]
You're welcome.
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
Remember to breathe.