Urara:
Uh, I-I don't believe it.
Soma Yukihira has defeated
Somei Saito,
the number four seat
on the Ten!
You did it!
You freakin' a third-year member
of the Ten, my man!
You're like the Hercules
of awesome takedowns!
[ Cheering ]
Yeah.
Congrats. Uh...
I honestly
can't believe it.
Yeah,
he actually pulled it off.
I knew you'd
do it!
Takumi: Megumi.
Huh?
We won this round
as a team.
There's no doubt about it.
Your efforts played a big part
in Soma's success,
and I'm pretty sure
he knows that.
[ Laughs ]
Why are you standing
all aloof, Takumi-poo?
You were amazing!
Ugh!
Congratulations,
big bro!
Both teams, please retire
to the waiting room,
and choose your members
for the upcoming bout.
Soma Yukihira,
Eishi Tsukasa's
fearsome.
I know.
Best of luck.
Thanks.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Now, choose one,
Soma.
A nice herbal medicine
to calm your heightened nerves
or one that is destined
to increase your focus?
Uh, no thanks.
I'm good.
Come on now. You could be
suffering from fatigue.
Are you sure you're not tired?
You want something to eat?
Nah, I'm totally fine.
Thanks, Meat-Meat.
Um, Miss Erina,
perhaps you'd care for some
hot herbal --
Hey!
Why are you being so dang mousy?
Just go up there
and talk to her already.
Aldini,
it would seem that you won.
You're looking
quite pale.
Mimasaka, I have
to give you credit.
It's thanks to what
I learned from you.
Hey, if you went all in
with observing your rivals,
you'd make
an excellent stalker.
You still ain't using your
clingy nature
to its full extent.
Who are you calling
clingy?
Isshiki: Well, the time's
almost upon us.
The fourth bout.
I would like
to compete in this one.
Erina, Takumi, Soma.
How about you?
I like to think it goes
without saying we're ready.
I'll be happy to take on
any one of them.
This next bout will be
decidedly
different than the others
have been, as all the remaining
members are sure to participate.
If we win the next
three battles,
we will have
wiped them all out.
this whole thing
will be over.
Maybe,
but we'll hardly be facing
pushovers out there.
Momo Akanegakubo,
Rindo Kobayashi,
and Eishi Tsukasa.
How do we challenged them?
How do we defeat them?
Hmm.
Can I say something?
What?
I must say, that
Soma Yukihira fellow
is rather heroic.
I can see why you lost to him
in a food war.
Makes a lot of sense.
Wipe that dumb
smirk off your face.
Well, I suppose the rest is up
to Momo and the others.
As much as
we're counting on her,
it's a shame she's always doing
crap like that.
You be quiet.
This is people
showing their love
for things
cute and adorable.
Hmm. I'm getting a lot of cute
comments today as well.
That's encouraging.
Still, it's not enough.
It's not really doing
it for me.
Kinokuni, go sew up
Bucchi's handsy-wansies.
Uh, o-okay.
I'm busy with looking at
pics and stuff, 'kay?
Soma Yukihira.
I can't believe he was able
to defeat Chef Saito.
Hey, where are
Tsukasa and Rindo?
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Laughs ]
She was so worn out yesterday,
she could barely stand,
but now she
is crazy hyper.
Look alive, suckers!
Chef Rindo's in the house now.
I had a super
good sleep,
and now I've got more energy
than ever before.
What do you make of ol'
Chef Rindo now, little Soma?
You are ramped up
about this.
Rindo has the strength
of a wild animal.
Oh, crap. He looks totally
back to normal, too.
That's bad.
Chef Momo's
here, too.
Ugh. Sure enough, I can't shake
this nasty feeling.
I'll just have to make
another cute dish
to make myself
feel better.
That sushi Som-yan made
really managed
to give me my strength back.
My dish is gonna eat
the competition alive.
Right, Bucchi?
Even if that competition
will be me?
Of course.
In this mood of mine,
I think I'd be even more savage
than I usually am.
I look forward to it,
Erin-yan.
You seem to be
in a testy mood today.
So, let me inform you
of the real reason
of your current mindset.
Huh?
Something about you seems
a bit different, Erin-yan.
Woman: Miss Erina!
Man: Look, it's Miss Erina!
Chef Momo
is the queen of cute
when it comes to
everything!
But Miss Erina is certainly
no slouch either.
She can be mean, but she's
so incredibly beautiful.
And that's why
they call her Ice Queen.
Erin Nakiri,
the daughter of Director Azami,
the great Senzaemon's
granddaughter.
They say she has
a God-like tongue
and is the very embodiment
of fine cuisine.
We're getting a dish
from the same family
as the Demon of the Kitchen.
It should be quite good.
I get to see her
and do a food war?
I don't believe it.
Urara: Alrighty, let's get the
fourth bout back underway.
The cards and
the theme ingredients
have already been decided.
The first card is Eishi Tsukasa
versus Satoshi Isshiki.
The theme ingredient --
wild rabbit.
Isshiki, huh?
This could be a tough battle.
[ Chuckles ] It's truly
an honor, Chef Tsukasa.
Hmm.
The second card is
Rindo Kobayashi
versus Takumi Aldini.
The same ingredient --
spear squid.
Yo, Takumi.
Don't go getting
all scared.
No way. My fighting spirit
burns white hot, Chef Rindo.
And then for
the third card,
we have Momo Akanegakubo
versus Erina Nakiri.
The theme ingredient --
brown sugar.
Brown sugar?
That's another
one suited more for candy.
Do your best,
Erina-poo!
Okay, Bucchi.
Let's make a great dish
and get rid of all this anger.
And we'll also take down
Erin-yan while we're at it.
Whoa!
What is all that?!
I'm trippin' on all those
super colorful batters
she got over there!
Interesting.
Let's see.
Strawberries,
matcha tea, cocoa, blueberries,
and black sesame.
It's like the fresh,
clean palate
for some vibrant painting.
With these beautiful,
delicious, edible colors,
it's time to start making
my painting.
She looks to be completing
one fancy illustration
after another.
How can she possibly
be so fast?
[ All gasp ]
She baked them all out
at once?
How good can
this pipsqueak be?
Now that they're done
and cutely decorated,
I'll put them in the oven
for three minutes,
and then after
I take them out,
by squeeze in this batter
that has the
delicious brown sugar.
It would seem to me that she's
making a form of cake roll.
The illustrated
confectionery popular in Japan?
If that's true,
that's surprisingly
unsophisticated,
considering the luxurious tart
she made.
Even the decorations
have to be cute. So cute.
She's using
the sucre tiré.
By tempering
the candied sugar,
keeping its flexibility,
you can stretch it out.
Of all
the candy making techniques,
this is the one that creates
the most sheen,
but it's extremely
hard to master.
And yet, she makes it
look so easy.
Her performance brings a wealth
of cuteness
to the entire cooking process.
Cuter. Cuter.
Carde:
Hold on a minute.
Histoire: Just how many
does she plan to make?
It's still not enough.
Right, Bucchi?
Momo's House of Sweets sure is
keepin a busy pace today.
Will Erina
be alright?
Well, let's just relax
and watch her do her thing.
I'm not sure
what she's up to,
but old Erina
sure seems fired up.
She's so careful
with the heat.
Whoa!
They came out gorgeous!
Look at those beauties.
She's made crispy tuiles
of brown sugar and black sesame.
And she has
two batters ready --
one with egg whites
and one with yolks.
Judging by all the ingredients
laid out,
it seems Erina's doing
a confectionery as well,
against the most skilled
patissier in Totsuki.
Yah!
It looks like it, huh?
Erina-poo is talented,
but isn't that
a bad move?!
No. The odds of winning are in
Miss Erina's favor.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Urara: Whoa!
It looks like
in the fourth bout,
the first tasting will be
courtesy
of the super cute Chef Momo!
All done, everyone.
All: Wha?
What the heck's that?
Ah!
It's so cute!
Totes adorbs!
Anne: It looks like the castle
from some dream kingdom!
[ Man laughs ]
[ All gasp ]
Ah.
I was wrong when I called it
unsophisticated.
There is nothing simple
about that creation at all!
However, no matter how great its
appearance, taste is everything.
Yes, that's true.
It all rests on how
the flavors dance on the tongue.
Momo: Love!
Mm! Oh!
Oh!
Oh! What is this
exquisite texture,
this
delightful sweetness?
When touched
with a fork,
it bounces back with
delicate fluffiness.
It is so remarkably
spongy!
Yet it melts in the mouth
like a soft, gentle rain
falling upon the tongue
and churgling its way
to utter bliss.
More than that, what is
this sweetness that permeates
to the very core?
The answer you're looking for
is this.
Both:
Soy sauce?!
I added cream, brown sugar,
vanilla essence,
and soy sauce,
then whipped it all up
and spread it on the cake
I just baked
and pulled out of the oven.
Then I rolled it up
and let it chill.
That makes the flavor
of the brown sugar
even cuter when one
bites into it.
So, put simply,
complementing the sweet elements
with a salty one
actually
emphasizes the sweetness.
It's an idea
much like salted caramel.
You used an original
soy sauce cream
to add flavor
to the mixture.
Brown sugar.
It contains sodium ion
and other minerals
not found in normal sugar,
giving it its unique flavor.
It is a mystery unto itself.
The unique flavor of the brown
sugar is the perfect match
for the richness
of soy sauce,
making it a match
made in heaven.
If you take a bite
with a piece of fruit in it,
then you'll enjoy
a different explosion
of flavor.
Of course, you can eat the candy
decorations, too.
So, if you put some little
pieces of it on your tongue
before you eat the cake,
it tastes
even more amazing.
I'm speechless!
With each bite,
it's as if I'm being led
into a world of dreams!
She's a master of cute.
This aroma encapsulates
an entire universe of sweets.
Indeed, paired with
the taste and looks,
the result
is a perfect castle.
She rules her own kingdom
with iron sweetness,
and this is a lovely volley
fired at all
who would dare enter!
Both:
There's no escaping it!
Somebody help me!
I cannot escape it!
Both: Anne!
Just how
will Erina Nakiri
breach this
impenetrable fortress?
[ Slurps ]
It doesn't just look perfect,
it tastes perfect, too.
How could she make something
on that level of perfection?
I traced that girl,
so I understand.
Her devotion
to cuteness
is so utterly absolute that she
has achieved perfect mastery
in the realm
of adorable.
Everyone,
I made a whole bunch of these.
Would anyone
like one?
[ Cheering ]
No pushing now.
Stand in line, okay?
It's like
a damn autograph session.
Apparently, she's some kind
of social media star.
Erina-poo?
What about Erina-poo?
She'll be okay.
She got just the right peaks
on her meringue
before pan frying.
Erina's dish
won't be too much longer now.
Good luck and all that stuff,
Erin-yan.
Do your best or whatever,
Woman: Huh? That's what
you want, Momo?
But it's not very cute.
Are you sure you want it?
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Now you want this?
This one, right?
Man: Momo just keeps predicting
the next big thing.
Woman #2: She's a prodigy,
a prodigy of cuteness!
Man #2:
Miss Momo, these are the new
products we have in mind!
Which of them
do you think are cute?
Woman #3: You like to design
for these children's clothes?
Man #4:
Or these new sweets?
This one. That one.
That one. This one.
Woman: What?!
Man: You're really going to
Totsuki Academy?
But we make toys!
Are you sure?
Woman #2: No, come to
our fashion company.
Man #2: You could be
a graphic designer.
Woman #3:
Please tell us, why did you
choose to become a patissier?
Well, because I believe
that I'm at
my ultimate cuteness
for delightful,
enjoyable sweets.
To this very day,
I've walked the path of what
I think is cute,
expressing both cuteness
and deliciousness
in all the dishes
that I've curated.
And yet...
So, let me inform you
of the real reason
of your current mindset.
Just what is it you think
you'll inform me of, Erin-yan?
Erina: My apologies
for the wait. Please enjoy.
This is
soufflé léger de grace.
Ah.
A souffle.
I made one of those before.
Fluffy.
She countered
her opponent's roll cake
with an actual
pancake instead.
That's just like Miss Erina
to tackle the problem head on.
It's perfect.
I mean, it looks stylish
and super pretty,
but visually,
that roll cake
is just way too powerful
for anything else to succeed.
[ Giggles ]
Hey, what's up?
Is something funny here?
[ Giggles ]
Not really.
Well, let's
have a taste then.
A dish from
the God Tongue.
The cake looks so light
and wonderfully fluffy.
The moment
the fork slices into it,
the expectation of it
melting upon the tongue
runs through
every nerve of the body.
She knows how to make a dish
such that just imagining it
on the tongue
can control the human heart.
Erina: Love.
What is this?!
This is no
normal pancake.
Between these
two cake layers is...
All:
Anko!
Huh? Anko?
Yes. That is
the star player of this dish.
I used refined adzuki beans,
then added some brown sugar.
Brown sugar
infused with bean paste.
[ Giggles ]
She used a pressure cooker
to get it done quickly
and without losing any flavor.
A brown sugar paste?
So, then,
this dish is just a --
It's a bit
of red bean anko
that's been sandwiched
in between two pancake layers.
You know it is
traditional dorayaki.
The finest adzuki beans
from Tokachi
make the flavors
speak in even lower volumes.
The brown sugar is a perfect
match for this dish.
There's no flavor disparity
in this at all.
That's Master Erina,
our Hokkaido expert.
She knows
her ingredients!
Whoa!
Take a look!
Even Urara's
sucked in.
No,
I mustn't do it.
I must stand firm
and act solely just as an MC.
Don't worry. There's no reason
to hold back.
Don't you want to know just how
delicious this dish really is?
I want it.
Please, Master Erina.
More.
Please instruct me.
Make me your filling.
Anne and Urara: Fold me into
these sumptuous layers!
Looks like she's
been sandwiched, too,
as Anne-ko filling.
I'm so jealous.
Uh, shameful.
Now, judges, what say you?
A moment, please.
There is one more person
that I would like
to taste
this creation of mine.
Will you do me a little favor,
Miss Queen of Cuteness?
Momo: I will admit that your
dish seems pretty decent
in terms of cuteness.
However, it's still only
a 9.5.
Why did you add anko
to make it like a dorayaki?
I would think that would
have dulled
that delicate flavor
and texture of the souffle.
You could have just added
brown sugar to the meringue
so as to make it
a souffle pancake
that then would have giving you
a 10 out of 10.
I can tell by looking
it's just sub par, the same
as Megumi Tadokoro's dish.
Is that truly the case?
I think
that if you have a taste,
the reason
for your foul mood,
I'm certain that it will become
clear to you.
Did you hear her, Bucchi?
What do you think?
Huh?
Give it a taste and see?
Yes. You're much too kind
for us, Bucchi.
Mm.
Hmm.
This cuteness --
avoiding it is impossible.
Whoa.
What the --
What is even happening?
Momo's gushing
over something she didn't make?
This -- This --
This beautiful depth of flavor.
You've added yogurt
as the secret ingredient.
That's exactly right.
I found by straining it,
the flavor
was concentrated enough
to become
a Greek style yogurt.
Removing the moisture
from the yogurt
emphasizes
the dairy aspect,
giving it a more subtle cheese
like depth of the flavor.
Then I added that
to the souffle batter,
which I made
with beaten egg whites.
So, then this --
this must have been
what made the presence
of the brown sugar
even more prominent
in the dish.
Wow!
It didn't look like she was
using any special tool, though.
I see. That's how she used
those coffee filters.
Yes. Not only are they easy,
they're made for filtration.
That very design made them the
perfect choice for this dish.
Thanks to the strained yogurt
as my secret ingredient,
I was finally able to reach
the level of exquisiteness
I wanted.
Something
with a stronger flavor
like ricotta or cream cheese
would have,
as Momo Akanegakubo
said,
been sub par.
She is a talent indeed.
Upon seeing such skill as this,
I can imagine nothing greater.
Truly, she's an epiphany
from the heavens,
one that transcends
the boundaries of convention.
Erina:
The flavor that was my goal
could only be reached
by transcending the norm.
If I had not seen Megumi's
inspired dorayaki,
I could never
have made this dish.
What?
That dish
was a soufflé
léger de grace.
So,
that's a light souffle
and "grace"
can translate to "blessing",
just like your name,
Megumi.
Huh?
Momo,
up until now,
your exceptional
cooking sense
has allowed you to always
put out some top-tier dishes.
And that's why you refused
to even acknowledge
that there are worlds beyond
that which you have no control,
where dishes sparkle
with a shine
you've never known.
Megumi
was willing to experiment
and fall short of a 10
because she was aiming
for a 12.
That's what irritated you.
How dare you,
you horrible girl!
You're acting all big and just
saying whatever you want, huh?
No wonder why everyone here
called you the Ice Queen,
Erin-yan!
Yes, that they do.
But I am no longer
a queen content with merely
sitting back in her throne
and ruling with no innovation.
That's right. The frustration
that you're experiencing,
it's something that I have
felt myself once before.
On that day, in my castle over
which I had full reign
and I have absolute authority,
he appeared.
There's no way
I'll acknowledge this dish.
The only cute things
hose those Momo thinks are
cute.
End of story.
I don't want
to acknowledge this.
I really don't want to.
Oh, no!
I'm gonna say it.
It's super cute!
You are most welcome.
Urara: The winner,
from the rebel alliance,
Erina Nakiri!
She did it! Miss Erina just beat
the number three seat
on the Ten.
All: Yeah!
Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai!
You got some nerve,
Erina.
Hmm?
You sneak. You totally stole
my catch phrase,
even though you changed it up
to try to make it
your own.
Now, look her! I was not
inspired by your phrase at
all!
You took a glance over at me,
though, didn't you?
And that was totally a sign
you were ripping me off.
But you won,
so I totally forgive you.
I don't need your
stupid forgiveness!
Erina!
Congratulations.
And also, um,
w-well, um...
thanks so much!
Thank you for my
name in --
Th-- Thank you
It's so nice of you.
Come on now.
It's nothing to cry about.
God, you're weird.
Any case, this is no time
to rest on our laurels.
There are still
two cards remaining.
Your attention, please.
I have some news.
I hereby announce a small change
to the judges panel
for this food war.
Effective immediately,
I am acting as panel chairman.
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
I look up to you!
Dummy!
Unfair, unfair,
unfair, unfair, unfair!