Urara:
The final bout begins!
The battle
will be fought
by means of a set menu
of two dishes.
Both teams will serve
an appetizer
followed by a main dish.
And the team
that comes out on top
will take over all seats on
the Council of Ten.
If the rebels win,
it's possible for them
to save the students who
were expelled
after the advancement exam.
Ugh.
I make it happen!
But they're going up against
the first and second seats.
Sure, Erina and Soma
are both awesome chefs,
but they're still
just first years.
How can they
defeat the top two?
It's not possible.
All right,
let's do this.
Tsukasa: [ Sighs ]
Hmm?
Once we win this thing, I'll be
drowning in council work again.
I was hoping to rely more
on Isshiki and Megishima.
Hey, cut that out
and put it together, Tsukasa!
Of course.
I'll do my best.
Once this competition
is finally finished,
there'll be no one left
to oppose Central.
I feel bad
so many others will be expelled.
But oh, well.
This too is for the sake
of honing one's talents.
Urara: That council team has
begun to cook!
[ Grunts ]
[ Cheering ]
The rest is yours.
Go for it.
Sure.
I see. So they can support each
other in this bout as well.
They make the perfect
combination.
By sad and frightening
comparison, our team is --
I ended up having
to do the appetizer,
but I won't let your dish
get the better of mine!
That's hardly the point now,
is it?
You should take
this more seriously!
They're still out there
bickering.
Can they really
handle this?
[ Chuckles ]
The outcome of this was
determined the moment it began.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Urara: Okay, let's take a look
at how each team is progressing.
As always, the rebel side
has no sense of cohesion.
What kind of dishes can a mood
like this even produce?
Meanwhile, the council team
are not
only supporting each other,
they seem to be
finishing up their dishes.
Will they make more powerful
and exciting dishes
that use big game
and rare ingredients?
Rindo:
[ Chuckles ]
I'm just about done over here.
How about you?
Oh, perfect timing,
as usual.
I'll be done about the same time
as they finish their appetizers.
All right.
Then I'm going to go
serve mine up!
The council is already putting
out their first dish!
So, that's the appetizer
Chef Rindo made?
I'm not so sure.
Is that really it?
It doesn't seem like
something she would try to make.
You can tell from
those beautiful layers
it's a mille-feuille.
[ Chuckles ]
I call this
mushroom mille-feuille,
with duxelles laced
inside of it.
[ Chuckles ]
The look is outstanding.
Now then, let's get straight
to the tasting.
Yes. Mm.
[ Giggles ]
Incredible!
The blend of different
mushrooms
brings a rush of flavor
that gently embraces the ultra
thin crust of the mille-feuille.
The main ingredient used for
this was shiitaki mushrooms.
She simmered them
in some olive oil,
creating a confit,
locking in the umami,
making it aromatic.
She took champignons
and shallots and sautéed them
a rich brown in butter,
then simmered them in stock.
Finally, she mixed in nuts
and heavy cream,
which she sandwiched
between the crusts.
But the real star of the flavor
is this tartness.
Mm.
What is this taste?
What manner of ingredients
did you use?
[ Chuckles ]
A little bit of ant.
[ All gasp ]
She is truly the master
of rare ingredients.
For real? Ants?
Has she gone buggy?
I wanted to get f-ant-cy.
Ants secrete
a substance called formic acid,
so I extracted some of that and
tossed it in with the duxelles.
I see then. Ingesting too much
formic acid is poisonous,
but used in small doses,
adds a great accent.
It has a nice sharp tang.
It's not overly sweet,
which helps make
this dish exceptional.
If combined with sweetness,
it can create a flavor profile
that has more depth and nuance
than even citrus fruits.
This is indeed the dish of a
first rate professional.
Older ants pump out
too much formic acid,
which would make
the taste harsh.
But younger agents
have a mellow sweetness,
which makes them just right.
Well, hell,
she's super good at this.
The second seat
really knows her stuff.
To think that she can use such
a bizarre ingredient so deftly.
Her appetizer is exquisite
and refined.
The appetizer.
Its role is to invigorate
the appetite,
filling the diner with the
excitement for what's to come.
Yes. I'm truly.
Even the butterflies that flit
about the culinary world
with cunning and power are
helpless before this parade
of decadent flavors,
overcome with
ant-icipation
as they are dragged helplessly
toward the main dish!
[ Gasps ]
Ah!
A perfect score.
Flawless.
A dish that cannot
be surpassed.
Hold up now.
It's too soon for you to start
feeling all satisfied,
'cause after all, the main dish
is still yet to be presented.
Let him have it, Tsukasa.
Not a problem.
I've put everything
I have into this.
It's a true gourmet feast,
my specialty!
A salt crust.
The dish is coated
with salt and egg whites,
then baked
'til it forms the hard crust
over the whole thing.
That way, the moisture
from all the ingredients
is locked inside,
allowing those flavors
to be concentrated.
Historians say
that long ago,
Toyotomi Hideyoshi
supplied his troops with salt
so that the sea bream
would last longer.
All: Uh...
[ All gasp ]
Whoa.
There's some kind of
lustrous red meat under there.
Mm.
He may be the enemy, but...
Just this once, I want
to stuff my face with his
meat.
That packs such a punch,
anyone would think that.
Yes. The Plate of White Armor
in Sauce Chevreuil.
"Chevreuil" means deer,
making venison the star
of this delicious dish.
Both:
So, venison?
Chef Tsukasa used venison
when we served as judges
for that impromptu food war
as well.
Back then,
Soma couldn't put up
a decent fight against it,
but now he's served up
something to outclass even
that.
I can't -- I can't
bring myself
to destroy
this masterpiece.
It'd be shameful.
Don't be a prude, Anne!
Give me a bite of that!
Nah --
[ Moans ]
Why don't you give it a taste,
Soma?
You can compare it to that
previous venison dish of mine.
How could something
be this delicious?
The taste flies off the tongue
and shoots right up
into my nostrils.
The flavor's gonna
rattle my brain.
There's a frickin' universe
of difference
between this dish
and his other one.
That appetizer was not meant
to simply guide the diner
along to the final course.
It took us to a place
where all chefs are free of
hardship and mediocrity,
a world of peace and beauty
we have struggled to find,
a culinary Eden.
Hey,
quit acting like you've won.
Soma and Erina are not going
to let that happen.
Yeah!
Damn straight, girl!
You tell 'em, Meat-Meat!
Huh?
Why are you two staring at me?
Hmm?
Oh, God!
What's going on?!
[ Whimpers ]
Out here,
it is manifested.
My power
of endowment.
Both:
Endowment?!
When I taste greatness,
the endowing pulse
within me discharges,
causing those around me to lose
all their clothing in one burst.
What is
he talking about?
I don't think
I understand this.
So, is he saying that the people
around him
were forced to get naked?
I remember
that happening once.
Whenever someone formally
receives the Nakiri surname,
they inherit
the power of endowment.
This includes marrying
into the family, of course.
So Uncle Azami was also
granted endowment abilities.
What is going on
in the Nakiri family?
You know,
these things happen.
No!
Well, now, can't say
I'm too impressed forcing a
girl
to disrobe
in the middle of a public venue.
It was not intentional.
It is simply indicative
of how delicious this was.
The fabled nakedness
of the great Nakiri family.
The fact that
the endowment ability
manifested
on such a great scale
proves that this dish is nothing
less than the genuine article.
Rindo Kobayashi put everything
into her appetizer
to highlight the main dish,
which allowed Eishi Tsukasa
to bring sheer brilliance
to his plate.
I can imagine no greater
response to this challenge.
They are the most powerful
forces on Totsuki's campus,
and the course that these two
have served up
is nothing less than
the ultimate in fine dining.
Now, the Totsuki side
has served their dish,
and it's in
the most exquisite of forms.
On the opposite side, the main
dish will be served up by Erina,
who has forgotten my teachings
and peppered it with impurities,
which can never be considered
fine dining,
thus there is no hope
that you will ever
win this battle.
When we fought before,
you didn't serve this dish,
did you?
And so, I'm led to believe
that you decided to take it
a little easy
on me back then.
Frankly,
it's kind of an insult, Chef.
Ah.
It wasn't intended as an insult.
Rather, I thought
there was no need
to put forth the effort
to make the dish.
But since now the emphasis
is true fine dining,
I simply went with the
greatest
option at my disposal,
and naturally, I chose
to use my specialty.
Then the gloves
are off now,
because I'm not here
to lose either.
I couldn't make this
at the time,
but this is
my specialty.
So, get ready!
I'm gonna whip it out,
right here and now.
Did Some just say
that he's going to
make a specialty
of his own?
But Soma's the one
making the appetizer.
What's it going to be?
Is it a specialty
appetizer?
If it's our dude
Soma we're talking about --
Don't tell me he's going
to make that!
Behold, my specialty
appetizer --
squid tentacles
drowned in peanut butter!
Both:
Peanut butter squid?
There's no way, right?
Wait, Takumi,
so how did the recipe meet-up
go with them last night?
Yeah. Did they come up
with some sort of strategy?
I swear,
this is going nowhere!
Let's just put aside who'll
be making the main dish.
Instead, we should use tonight
to hammer out
the overall
core structure.
You're fine
with that, right?
Soma: I'm telling you,
this is the kind of appeti--
Oh, come on!
I'm going outside to get myself
some fresh air for a minute.
Erina, come back!
[ Door closes ]
Ha!
She seems rather excitable.
If the two of us
can't work this damn thing out,
I say we just go with some
rock, paper, scissors.
You can't be serious.
And if you lose
rock, paper, scissors,
will you properly devote
yourself to the appetizer?
Ugh. True.
It could end up coming to that.
There's no "could
end up" about it.
Just what are you
talking about?
Oh, by the way,
Isshiki,
what was that key thing
we heard about?
Sounded important.
Because you are the key
that is necessary
to guide all chefs along their
proper path.
Ah.
Director Azami.
He wants
to make use of her God Tongue
to implement
his plan.
Erina's tongue
can determine what is
good and bad about a dish.
And because of that gift,
her decision can free chefs
from the burden
of menu creation.
That is Central's
ultimate ideal.
The key that lies at the heart
of their great revolution.
Oh, really?
They want to use the God Tongue.
That sounds kind of interesting,
actually.
Mm!
Soma didn't say much
at the time,
but does he have
some idea in mind?
Erina!
Hmm?
Here are some chicken livers.
Taste them for me?
Chicken livers.
What's he doing?
He should be cooking.
In the regimental,
it's okay for you to help
each other out with the cooking.
So, then it shouldn't
be a problem to leave
the tasting to her.
If you're out to use Erina
to help you,
I'll just have to use her
God Tongue a bit myself!
That's an evil face!
What are you thinking there,
Soma, my man?
He's totally gonna use
his own teammate!
Although,
it does make sense.
Not this. Rubbing homemade
mayonnaise into the livers
is indeed a good thing,
but the taste of it
doesn't spread
across the tongue well enough.
Got it.
How about now?
This is good.
Heh.
So, basically what he's doing
here is going back
and fine tuning the flavor
of each part.
Doing it this way,
he can take stock of what's
lacking and adjust accordingly,
getting those flavors
as fully realized as possible
so as to make the perfect dish
to bring down the council.
Clever.
Yes. This way,
he will probably be able
to make
one incredible appetizer.
But still, being told
how to adjust his flavor...
Yeah.
By the time it got this far,
Soma would have
pitched a fit.
Not now.
It looks like Soma has learned
Miss Erina's true power.
He's come
to finally trust her!
Give the spice mix
a little taste!
How's the sauce
flavor palates?
To his credit, he will now
listen to my instruction.
This should
at least be laudable.
And yet...
If you must
make the appetizer,
what do you think of doing
a paté de campagne?
Oh.
A paté de campagne.
What is that?
It's an appetizer that refers
to a country style paté.
We've had to make it
in class before.
You take ground meat,
then add liver paste, stir in
vegetables, and cook it up.
The sticky texture and rich
flavor increases
the diner's anticipation,
making it a staple appetizer.
So basically,
it's just like corned beef.
It's completely different.
Whatever.
Now, regardless, the first dish
should tie into the main one.
Please keep this in mind.
Now then, I will
teach you the recipe.
I showed him
how to prepare this.
So, why does he keep tweaking
its arrangement?
[ Soma laughs ]
Soma,
what are you doing?!
Heh.
All done now.
Who's hungry?
Huh?
Wait!
All:
Now hold on!
Your order is up.
How do you like
my super delish appetizer?
[ Laughs ]
This...
This is...
You say you consider
this an appetizer?
He's a caveman!
A slab of meat is what cavemen
eat in anime!
Never mind the look.
There's no way
that's anything
other than
the main entree!
Dude, Soma!
What the hell are you doing,
brah?!
Huh?
What's the matter?
I just did what Erina
asked me to do earlier.
I served them a paté
de campagne as a starter.
Soma.
Is so determined
to fire back at Chef Tsukasa
for that specialty that he's
gone completely off the rails
and has sabotaged
your chances of winning?
Why, Soma?
Soma Yukihira,
you fool.
Now, look here.
That is not an appetizer.
Why do you seek
to admonish him for this mess?
Excuse me.
What was that?
I, uh, just thought
that I, uh...
Still, I suppose
we may as well try some.
True enough,
the inside is a paté.
By wrapping shaved meat
around the exterior,
he's made it look like
a piece of solid bone-in flesh.
Mmm.
[ Gasps ]
The exterior is made out
of shaved marinated beef.
While it's rich
and flavorful,
it's those fruity,
meaty juices
that grab hold of
your consciousness.
Just beneath that,
there's some sliced bacon.
It's also placed there
so as to hold the paté firmly
in place.
From the first bite,
the impact of all the protein
races through your body.
For the base
of that delicious marinade,
I used a Korean barbecue sauce.
To the store-bought sauce,
I decided to add aromatics like
garlic and ginger,
and I added soy sauce and mirin
to balance out the flavors.
It forms the perfect base.
I kept going,
adding honey, some grated onion,
and a bit of orange juice
to the mix.
I had Erina taste test it,
making sure it was a good match
for the paté de campagne.
It's not just the exterior.
The paté nestled within
is exquisite as well.
The flavors are so rich,
but also so delicate.
It's the perfect match
for the mellower exterior meat,
creating
a firecracker of flavor.
Chicken livers
are first,
complemented
by breast meat and cream,
then diced green beans,
carrots,
and shimeji mushrooms
are folded in,
each playing their own role,
making it simply wonderful.
Confit, [Speaking foreign],
and [Speaking foreign],
the perfect method
was used for each ingredient,
drawing forth
a soft sweetness,
which elevates the dish
to a whole new level.
Mm.
[ Gasps ]
What?
The flavor just changed.
It's like from between
these was delicious meat,
a geyser
suddenly erupted.
What is this
savory aroma?
Though I have yet
to try a bite,
my body is
reacting to it.
Something is oozing out
from in between the meat.
That would be a slow simmered,
super rich,
jellied consomme sauce
I thought would be nice.
Just before serving, I injected
a whole bunch of that stuff
using a large
cooking syringe.
As you keep eating,
more will start to come out,
evolving the flavor.
A flavor bomb.
That's like out
of molecular gastronomy.
Where the hell did you learn
that, Soma?
Amazing.
It feels as if this dish has me
in its thrall,
even more so than it did before.
From the luxuriousness that hits
you with the first bite,
as you continue,
it's like you're buffeted
by wave after wave of ingenuity.
To think all of this
was incorporated
onto a single plate.
Such satisfaction.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, my clothes!
What's happening to us?!
Daigo and Shoji:
[ Laughing ]
The endowment
has struck!
So then, Azami Nakiri must think
this is delicious, too.
Azami: This approach
to the vegetables
call to mind
Kojiro Shinomiya,
the Legume Magician.
By realizing the taste
and sweetness of the vegetables,
their dignity is preserved,
yet their flavor enhanced.
Also, different flavors come out
at different times,
pulling the diner
right along with it.
Wow. Like that crazy dish
that Soma made
for the lunar feast.
That's correct.
I took my two revise
Yukihira dishes
and combined them.
The result
is this very dish.
That's why I borrowed
Erina's skills,
to properly blend
the two together,
working out any elements
that didn't match up
and keeping hold of
the ones she liked.
I call it Time Release: Uppity
Brat-Style Primitive Meat!
This is beyond revised.
This falls into
a new Yukihira category!
Normally, with complex
ingredients like these,
combining and balancing
so many would not be seen
as a possibility.
But thanks to the God Tongue's
instruction,
the result was this dish,
one truly worthy of being
called a specialty.
Its level is such that
it cannot be called inferior
to Tsukasa's Plate
of White Armor.
[ All gasp ]
Azami: However, that is only
as a single dish,
and as you have
just witnessed,
Tsukasa's dish received
a nice boost,
the result of being preceded
by Chef Rindo's starter.
By comparison,
you served a main-level dish
as an appetizer,
thus disrupting
the flow of the meal.
It was
an ill-advised decision.
[ Silverware clatters ]
No matter how close your dish
came to tasting of perfection,
this was a menu battle,
and as such, receives no points.
What an idiot. I know full well
what a short sighted
cretin he is, but is he really
that thoughtless?
Don't you have something up
your damn sleeve?
What are you doing?
Look, nothing we've done has
been teamwork at all, has it?
Listen, Erina,
I just -- I'm determined
for us to win
this frickin'
regimental food war.
Then why are you
doing this?!
'Cause there's no way
your dish is enough.
I had some of Chef Tsukasa's
dish earlier,
and it had
some crazy impact.
You let me try a few
of your candidates
for the main dish
yesterday,
and none of them
could top his.
But how can you
be certain?
Because none of those
could be called your specialty.
[ Gasps ]
If you want to beat him,
you have to put everything into
making a specialty
of specialties.
We have to put out a menu where
it's a battle at that level.
You can make something better
than I can, right?
So, prove it to me.
You need to go above and
beyond my dish, or we won't win.
This is really a food war
between you and me.
[ Gasps ]
So, bring it, Erina.
Pour everything
you possibly can into this.
It's time for
your specialty.
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
Idiot.
Moron.
Moron?