The victors are
the Rebel Alliance. Ugh.
You're welcome.
[ Cheering ]
We won!
We crushed
the Azami Administration!
Wha-ha!
Well, they actually
pulled it off.
Heh.
Not bad, I'd say.
[ Laughs ]
Brother! yay!
Soma!
Erina-poo!
That was, like,
super awesome!
Uh --
You've got some nerve
making me change
everything
at the last minute.
Erina, this hurts.
You're not off the hook
'cause we won.
Things like this need
to be planned ahead of time.
Come on. You had
10 minutes to work with.
That's plenty of time
for you, right?
Mm.
O-Of course.
I don't get it.
The two of them working
together makes no sense.
Though gifted
in their own unique ways,
Soma and Erina
continually butt heads.
How could they create
something so delicious?
Yes, well,
that is the question.
But if you ask me,
the answer is very simple.
Those two seem
to enjoy themselves
the most out of everyone
here in the stadium.
That's it?
We've lost the regimental,
haven't we?
Indeed. It seems we
and Central as a whole
have been
utterly defeated today.
♪♪
Father, thank you for
all you've taught me.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Hey, there,
Nakamura.
You've come to remind me
in person, have you?
Rest assured, then,
I will keep my promise.
I shall remove
myself from Totsuki.
Appreciated
and well-deserved.
You've always had your eye
on me, haven't you?
Ever since that time.
We're going to forge
all new horizons.
Right. I'll stick to you like
glue, no matter what.
Well, no matter
what you said,
I went around suffering
all by myself.
Gin, Nakamura,
catch you later. Sorry, guys.
I truly am sorry that
during that whole time,
I never got in touch,
though. I really am.
But here's the thing.
What Soma said was true.
I've been really happy.
And I'm still happy now,
as both a chef and a person.
So, yeah,
maybe you should lighten up.
[ Grunts ]
Don't fall to despair,
Nakamura.
I heard that when
you left Totsuki,
you were in a bad place
for a while.
Try not to
go back there.
Feel free to reach out to us
at any time.
At this point, I don't deserve
to be saved by anyone.
Don't talk such foolishness
like that, man.
At least
let's go grab a drink.
Perfect.
And I'll treat you to some of
my cooking while we're at it.
I have to say,
that sounds
like a marvelous idea.
Please pass
this along to Senzaemon.
"I'm hoping the chefs in
your age of kings
continue to reach
even greater heights."
Everything that I've done
was motivated by a goal
quite similar to Senzaemon's
I did all of this
just for her.
You mean the Rebel Alliance
has won and Central lost?
Damn it!
Are you frigging
kidding me?!
Ah? The Damask rose effects
have all worn off.
Are you serious?
Still, a win
is a win,
so take your victory
and get the hell out of here!
These damn rebels have taken
all the seats
on the Council of Ten!
Just a moment.
Before that.
[ Gasps ]
What are you doing?
Give me back my Bucchi,
Som-yan!
We must return
these student IDs
that we've retained.
Oh, so then
we can get our school IDs back.
So, then, does
that mean we're safe?
We're not
expelled anymore!
Right on!
That's so
very cruel.
My tore my little
Bucchi's back wide open,
like
some serial killer.
You're in no position
to talk,
given that you're always
ripping him to shreds.
Oh, just leave
her alone.
Huh?
This is kind of warped.
Uh, my school ID
is all messed up.
Mine is
a bit waterlogged
Because
Momo always has that thing.
She even takes it with her
into the bathtub.
That's why.
This thing
has a name -- Bucchi.
Uh, my apologies.
All: Uh...
It's not my fault,
you know.
Som-yan use Bucchi.
to store them.
Anyway, they can just issue
new ones for you all.
[ Laughs ]
All right.
Our work here is done.
The rest will be up to Soma
and
the others from now on.
True enough.
We're all counting
on you now, Soma,
and we won't forget about
Erina either.
Ha!
Chef Tsukasa,
we haven't had a real proper one
on one food war yet.
I want to throw down
with you for real.
Sure.
Anytime is fine.
Although, next time,
I don't
think that I'll lose to you.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Don't forget about
little ol' moi.
Rindo, right now,
what are
your feelings?
Huh?
Yeah, well...
...I think that I might be
the most excited I've ever
been.
Hmm.
Let's go, Tsukasa.
Huh?
Go where?
To Africa
or the South Pole
or even outer space.
Anywhere,
as long as it's place
where we can discover
more and more
delicious foods.
Ah. Yeah. There's no more
awful paperwork
left to do for the Ten.
We can go anywhere.
Well, peace out!
See ya, Soma Yukihira.
Yep.
Nene,
let's meet up at the school
and do some
cooking together.
You don't have to say
it all weird like that.
We're bound to run
into each other.
Although, why are you the only
one still standing
around half naked?
You crazy?
[ Laughs ]
Now, in accordance
with the original agreement,
the eight rebels
who participated here
in this year's
regimental food war
shall be given first priority
in joining the Council of Ten.
Yes. That's right.
We're the new seats
on the Ten.
That means you're guaranteed
a spot, Megumi!
Huh?
Is he for real?
I mean, that's believable. I'm
so happy, I can start crying!
Way to go!
This is awesome,
Takumi!
You're really
on the Ten!
[ Laughs ]
Congrats! Yay!
But who will be assigned
to which seat?
Most importantly,
the number one.
Well, of course,
it will have to be Miss Erina.
She did turn out that incredible
main dish during the final bout.
Mm.
I've gone along
with your selfish whims,
so this time you must listen
to one of mine.
So, Soma, you're taking
the number one seat.
Huh?
Wha?
But Miss Erina --
It was, to an extent,
thanks to you,
that I was able to produce
this dish in the first place.
Considering the person
who contributed the most
to this food war
and the one most suited
for the seat is Soma Yukihira.
I'd say
that's cool.
If it weren't for
the little Soma over there,
then things wouldn't have
turned out so rosy like this.
Of course,
he has my vote, too.
Yeah, my vote,
as well.
What the --
Soma?
[ Grunting ]
Now,
I hate to rush this,
but there is one thing the Ten
must decide upon immediately.
A new director of the school
must be selected.
What?
But Grandfather, you're
the director of the academy.
That position was unfortunately
taken from me
when your father
stripped me of it.
I would be losing face
were I to reclaim it.
However, there is
a silver lining.
So yeah, I'm retired now,
and the truth is,
I'd be glad
to have some me time, okay?
Grandfather.
So, who shall
that responsibility fall to?
I ask this of the new number
one seat of the Ten.
Well, if I must pick, it's got
to be this one here.
Uh...
Huh?!
For generations, the director
has been someone
from the Nakiri family.
Besides, it should be
an easy job
knowing how stuck up
and prissy you are.
And, uh,
besides all that,
your dish ran circles
around my own specialty.
Hate to say,
but you're still better than me.
So, unless you take
the director's spot,
I'm not taking
the number one seat.
Now you look here,
that's no reason for me
to have to be the new
director!
What if Uncle Soe were to do it
instead, Grandfather?
Soe: No, I'm in agreement
with the number one seat.
Huh?
Uncle Soe?
Why, hello there,
Erina.
Been quite a while,
hasn't it?
Oh, Father.
Glad you made it.
Of course.
Both: A pleasure
to see you, sir.
Mm?
My adorable little Alice.
Work has kept me away for
way too long,
but I finally
made it back.
Hello there, Soma Yukihira.
What's up?
Huh? Huh?
I, like you
and my father,
believe that Erina is perfect
for the position.
Her fresh vision makes
her magnificently suited
for the role
of academy director.
Please, Erina,
it's my wish to entrust
the future of Totsuki
to you.
Uh...
Mm.
[ Sighs ]
Alright, then.
I guess
I'll have to accept
the number one seat
as well/
But know this.
I won't feel like
I've taken the top spot
until I've taken you down
once and for all.
You're going to say it.
"Soma's food is awesome."
Just wait, 'cause that day
is gonna come.
[ Exhales sharply ]
So, then Soma
and Miss Erina...
[ Chuckles ] Looks like
they are both able
to succeed
in their own way.
It's simply incredible!
Absolutely incredible!
They did it!
You did it, too.
Megumi.
[ Both laugh ]
Hmm.
This makes Soma Yukihira
all the more
worth it to defeat.
I'd challenge the bastard
to a food war tomorrow.
Hmm.
Yeah. Me, too.
Boy: That transfer student,
Soma Yukihira
is now the number one seat?
Boy #2: What's gonna happen
to us now?
Don't tell me
we're gonna be expelled.
Boy #3: We betrayed the rebels
and talked down to them
as we sided
with the Azami Administration.
There's no way we could just
stay at school after that.
Huh?
What are you saying?
Nobody's getting expelled,
okay?
And listen up! On my word
is the current number one seat,
I'll accept a food war
challenge from anyone.
[ Cheers and applause ]
It's not like I outright beat
Chef Tsukasa or Rindo
in a one on one food war
or anything,
so I hold this seat
only temporarily.
If you battle me, you don't
have
to wager anything of your own.
Anyone who wants to
come after me, be my guest.
I got a ways to go, but I'd
like
you all to stick with me.
[ Laughter ]
Do it, Father.
Mm.
As departing director,
I make the following decree.
The director of
Totsuki Fine Dining Academy
shall be Erina Nakiri,
and the number one seat of
the Council of Ten
shall be Soma Yukihira.
[ Cheers and applause ]
I never thought he'd actually
make the number one seat
this quickly.
He's a hasty
little jackass.
Soma: We could go totally crazy
in this exciting
and endless wilderness.
So, let's butt heads.
Megumi: Dear Mother,
are you doing well?
It's been a few months now
since that regimental food war.
Our third year seniors
have all graduated
and are now exploring
their own paths.
Woman: Miss Momo,
we would definitely like you
to produce another mascot
character for us.
Not interested.
I'm going to focus entirely
on making the cutest of sweets
from here on out.
I want to make
the world sweeter,
more delicious, and more
and more cute.
Miss Momo!
Mm?
Please show us
your latest creation.
For my latest dessert,
I now bring you
Momo's Imperial
Majestic Pistachio Daifuku.
All: So adorable!
I'm terribly sorry. We won't
have a reservation available
until next spring.
Excuse me.
Uh, kada, please.
Understood.
I'll put all my heart
and soul into making it, sir.
Man: This is the killer ramen
from that Totsuki graduate, huh?
[ French accent ]
C'est si bon!
No doubt this is going to take
Paris by the storm!
Here you go.
[ Birds squawking ]
Oh, yes. Ah!
Hey, Tsukasa,
it's by you.
Don't you worry.
Leave it to me.
Man,
I really took a beating.
You may be an amazing cook
and everything,
but aside from that,
you've got a ways to go.
But don't you worry.
During our travels together,
I'm going to
whip you into shape.
Oh, yeah?
Be gentle with me, okay?
Look, it's a swallow.
Huh?
So, that's a swallow?"
So, uh, hey, Tsukasa,
those younger students,
do you think that
they're doing alright?
Hmm. Yeah.
Knowing them, I'm sure
they're doing just fine.
True that.
Both:
No doubt.
Megumi: Yep. Meanwhile, everyone
around here has moved on
to their next grade.
Come on!
Hurry up!
Ryoko, the next class
is gonna start soon!
Geez. Will you just wait up
a second, Yuki?
Meat-Meat, hey!
Hey.
So, you're studying
business management?
Wow!
That sounds tough!
I thought
it'd be good to study,
you know, the, uh, business end
of cooking as well.
Hey, where are you
headed off to, Shun?
Aren't you in the same class
as us, dude?
I'm gonna
have to skip it.
I've been challenged
to another food war.
This is your fifth time
in a row, right?
That's way awesome.
Uh, Chef Shun,
sir,
will you, uh, please
have a food war with me?
Sure, why not?
Both: Another one?!
I'd say Kyokuse
is in good hands.
Who are you?
Some newbie?
Huh?
This isn't
the freshman section, chump.
I was considering contacts.
Wait! You're Zengi!
Hey, everyone!
Let's give it our all
today as well!
All: Kyokuse!
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Wait, no, I don't actually
live at Kyokuse Dorm
with all you guys.
Not to worry. you're an honorary
member of Kyokuse, girl!
[ Laughs ]
Oh, dear.
Looks like you've
still got quite a ways to go.
After all, you're in the
presence of a noble third
year.
That was close.
This guy is really good.
The heck is going on
in the Yukihira era?
Akira!
Come on!
Do a food war with me,
you white-haired
bastard!
Fine by me.
But didn't
we fight yesterday?
Oh, quit acting like
you're so high and mighty
around me.
Right now,
we're 16 to 17,
which means
we don't know who's on top.
No, I get it.
Whatever.
You don't get anything.
Can you just
listen for once?
Ah!
So, this is where you've been
hanging, Ryo.
Come on, then.
Have another food war with me.
We're at 19 wins,
20 losses, and one draw.
We're just about to be
even right now.
We just battled two days ago,
didn't we?
Today I'm facing off
with Akira.
That will not do.
I'm going to have to come and
steal your seat first, Ryo,
Fine then. Why don't the three
of us do a food war together?
I swear, I'll take you two
on any time you want.
Hey, Chef Akira, can we please
go to the Shiomi seminar?
Yeah. We'll have a lecture once
I'm done with this food war.
Chef Kurokiba,
good luck!
You could
shut the hell up!
[ Laughter ]
Girl: Chef Alice,
you're so gorgeous.
[ Chuckles ]
Megumi: Soma's declaration that
he'll accept a food war
from anyone has changed
Totsuki Academy.
It's become a place where anyone
is free
to challenge anyone else.
For better or worse,
that is what our generation
has brought to Totsuki.
Yep, that was a close one.
What a match.
Hey, Nene?
As if. I had
nothing on you and you know it.
Hey, Chef Nene!
How can she be
so smokin' all the time?
I love you!
Just die.
All:
You're so hot!
We are doing this again.
So, get ready.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sizzling ]
I got the feeling someone was
in here training like a madman.
Of course it was you,
Mimasaka.
If you wanted, you could become
a member of the Ten.
But you seem to have put
that notion out of your head.
I'm nowhere close to being
in that league yet,
but sometime soon, I will
challenge you
and take that seat.
I can't just
rely on my trace.
No, I have to be able
to make my own perfect dishes.
There's no
understanding you.
I can't tell if you're hopeful
or just totally hopeless.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Urara: This Japanese cuisine
cooking combo
has received
a two-star rating from the WGO.
But it's the Aldini brothers
who take it!
With the sort of
coordination
then only brothers could have,
they've continued
to rack up the victories.
But still, are you alright
being this thin,
even though
it's not summer yet?
Well, every day
feels pretty hard,
but I'm doing really great
nonetheless, brother.
Both: Grazie!
Well, onto the next challenger!
The Aldini brothers,
their diligence is outstanding.
I hereby allow them to continue
to challenge Totsuki graduates.
Are we in agreement?
All: Ma'am.
The meeting is now adjourned.
I believe
that Miss Erina
has taking on the era
of a true leader of men,
hasn't she?
Hmm. She is indeed
a fitting successor.
Megumi: As the new director
of Totsuki Academy,
Erina Nakiri is always
charismatic
and runs a very tight ship.
These are
today's tastings.
I'd like you to look them over,
if you could, Miss.
Yes.
Thank you, Hisako.
Megumi:
Hisako continues, as always,
to give Erina
her tireless support.
But it seems like something
has changed
between the two of them.
Um, Hisako?
Yes? Is there something wrong,
Miss Erina?
Well, it's --
it's about the thing
you said
during the regimental food war.
The person I am now,
I'm Miss Erina's --
I'm her friend.
P-P-P-Please forget I said
something crude like that!
It was terribly impertinent
of me to call you a friend
without your saying so!
It wasn't impertinent
at all.
So, what do you think? Maybe
refer to me as the others do.
You know, that stupid nickname
they have for me? Erina-poo?
What? Impossible!
Absolutely no way!
Then just call me Erina,
like a friend.
Because we are
actually friends!
[ Heart beating ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Eh...eh...
E-Erina.
[ Gasps ]
Um, I think
"Miss Erina" is best for now.
Yes, I agree.
Otherwise, it's embarrassing
somehow.
Megumi: They seem to get
along quite well.
And as for me,
all sorts of things
have happened.
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
Merci!
After
the regimental food war,
I set out to do some around
the world traveling.
Serve!
I've been to and experienced
several different countries.
I got to know the various
flavors of many cultures,
and now I can use them
in my own dishes.
That experience has served me
well since coming back to Japan.
[ Sighs ]
Chef,
I'm off to set the tables.
Man: Thanks, Soma.
Appreciate it.
Hey, Soma.
Mm!
Oh!
[ Both gasp ]
Megumi: I ended up battling
a mysterious chef
at a certain hotel
after he got annoyed
at the lack of hospitality.
I've put my heart and soul
into making this dish.
I wish for you
to please enjoy.
Uh --
So, that's a --
All: A kid's lunch?!
Well, well.
[ All moaning ]
Megumi:
This is called gumbo.
It's a specialty from
the southern region of America.
I could tell you're from there,
'cause, you know,
just based on your accent
and the way you talk.
I bet when growing up,
you must have had
a lot of gumbo as a child.
So -- So, that's why it tastes
like Mama's cooking.
Oh.
You mustn't ever
be selfish, right?
No, no.
Man, this paperwork sure
has piled up.
Wherever you ended
up going,
I'm sure you were the picture
of hospitality.
[ Chuckles ]
It's thanks to my new
position on the Ten
that I'm able to visit
so many wonderful countries.
Oh, yeah? How about you have
a food war with me?
Fight for
the number one seat!
Ah! A f-food war
with you? Are you crazy? Ah!
God, I swear, you're constantly
challenging people to food wars
for any stupid reason.
Huh?
Of course I do.
I said I'd battle
anyone to a food war, right?
That may sound all well
and good to you,
but I have to clean up
your messes.
So, put yourself
in my position.
[ Chuckles ]
Come on.
It's not
a big deal, Erina.
It is a big deal!
And actually,
as a member of the Ten,
it's supposed
to be your job!
It's not meant to be work
for the director to do!
Fine, then!
How about this?!
If you want me to do my job,
then let's have a food war!
That's the problem!
Megumi: There are hurdles here
and there, of course,
but all of us at Totsuki
are enjoying our school lives
to the fullest.
Oh! As director, I have my own
duties to attend to!
Just do
whatever you want!
Sure.
Erina seems like
she has it pretty rough.
She looks a lot busier
since becoming a second year.
Yeah, I guess.
Although, she sure looks
a lot happier now
than back when she was
a snot-nosed first year.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. I'm off to kick ass
in some food wars!
Geez.
[ Laughs ]
♪♪
You can now enter.
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Gasps ]
You're welcome!
That's a no-no.
Ugh. I swear.