Hmm.
Yes, I see.
I'd say I've been blessed
with the or three.
It is what it is,
or so I've been told,
to something of that effect.
My family's got lots of cash and
I'm a really awesome cook.
Plus, don't forget, I'm totally
pretty boy cute, right?
I gotta say, I've kind of been
given it all, you know.
What's that you say?
They say I'm on the short side?
That means nothing.
Nothing at all!
Do you hear me over there?
It means nothing to me!
Anyway, I've got
other gorgeous stuff on my side
as I'm flying down the road,
a surefire victory in fame.
But then that day came.
As a first year, I was
challenging senior students
left and right,
winning battle after battle.
When suddenly out of the blue,
an epic defeat,
and all that pride
turned into dust.
But that wasn't even
the worst of my problems.
The truly worst part
is what came next.
It's been 10 days and you're
still down in the dumps, Kuga?
If you challenge
Eishi Tsukasa,
of course you won't be able
to claim victory,
you itty-bitty
pipsqueak.
It must be serious if Kuga
won't even react
to being called silly names.
You managed to draw a battle
against the number one seat.
Now, don't you think
that's something to be proud
of?
You're right!
I, the great
Terunori Kuga,
am the only underclassmen
to have challenged Eishi Tsukasa
since he became
a second year! [ Laughs ]
Why do you keep that kind of
talk to yourself, Isshiki?
That settles it.
I'm gonna go challenge him
to a revenge match
right now!
Wait.
Are you kidding?
Tsukasa.
Tsukasa:
Oh, Rindo.
I thought you were
in South America.
I told you that I would be
coming back today, right?
More importantly, it was
pretty cold for you to do that
while I wasn't around.
Huh? Do what?
Have a food war
with Kuga, duh.
Kuga.
Who exactly is that again?
Uh...uh...
What are you talking about,
Tsukasa?
You battled Kuga
in a food war.
Good grief.
Don't you remember anything?
Oh, yeah. He's the guy
who does Szechuan, right?
Kuga: Tsukasa. He wasn't even
trying when we fought.
I'm not just another
face in the crowd.
With this next battle,
you're going to learn about
Terunori Kuga the hard way.
Prepare yourself before
you eat this!
I just finished
my dish as well.
Soma: Here we go.
Let's see who takes it.
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
We're coming up on the end
of the second bout!
Will the Ten be bringing home
yet another easy
and flawless victory?
Check out that Eishi dude's
dish. What is that?
Did he make sherbet?
Nah, it's steaming.
So, that's a dish
from the number one seat.
My goodness. That thing
looks friggin' amazing.
Still, our side's dish
is hardly lacking in beauty.
Whoa. That pork shoulder
looks juicy and piping hot.
It appears to be a sweet
and sour pork
made with black vinegar.
Look at
his presentation.
It's as gorgeous as any high end
French or Italian dish
I've seen.
Terunori Kuga's
Szechuan cooking skills
seemed like they would be a bad
fit for this tea battle.
What kind of
flavor combination
has he come up with?
And now
for the taste test
Poor Megumi's
the most nervous person ever.
I totally understand
how she feels.
You can do it, man.
Come on, bring it.
Regarding Mr. Kuga's dish,
the idea to pan fry
and then smoke
the meat was interesting.
Kuga.
Who exactly is that again?
[ All chewing ]
All:
This is yumses!
Both:
Right on!
When you taste it,
it's as if the freshness
of the tea bathes
the whole visible spectrum
with the brightest of emerald.
The balsamic vinegar and Subaru
Mimasaka's smoked soy sauce
add to the black vinegar glaze!
The richness and acidity of it
binds to the umami of the pork,
eliminating the unpleasant
fatty aftertaste.
Histoire: The theme ingredient
of green tea is elevated
to the starting role.
He has truly broken
the boundaries
of sweet and sour pork.
Anne: That said,
here is the point
that deserves
the most attention.
It is not the methods of Chinese
cooking alone
that have brought forth
this flavor.
There is masterful usage
of French techniques as well.
Did she say French?
Yeah, yeah, I'll explain it all,
so listen up.
I kicked that black
vinegar braise up a notch
with sauce au vinaigre
balsamique.
It's a sauce used in
French cooking
in their back-end
notes of that as well.
Indeed so.
It says right here
that vinaigre balsamique
is a reduction
of glace de viande,
which is itself a reduction
of fond de veau
and balsamic vinegar.
It also says it combines
the brightness of acidity
with a rich,
deep flavor that could elevate
the sweet and sour pork
to its highest potential.
French cooking, huh?
That Kuga's something else.
Awesome!
Where'd he get the idea,
let alone the skill?
I thought his specialty
was Chinese cuisine.
When I lost to you, Tsukasa,
I spent this whole time
thinking
I have to change up my cooking.
It was a lot of work for me.
I had to break through the
wall
of Szechuan cuisine,
of Chinese cooking.
Today, I'll beat you,
Eishi Tsukasa.
You will no longer find
yourself
asking who Kuga is ever again!
You really have become a
different person in recent days.
It's quite
remarkable really.
But we third years
aren't so unskilled
that that amount of effort
would be enough to beat us.
But I'm sure
you already knew that.
Oh.
Mm.
[ Spoon clatters ]
The aroma alone is
affecting my senses.
Um...rather than the purée
on its own,
would you care to try it with
the accompanying sauce
this time?
In fact, I'd like you to try
all
four purées in your mouth
at the same time.
Please wait. I can't handle
any more stimulation.
But then you won't -- you
won't
fully appreciate the dish
in its completed
and final form.
You won't enjoy it
as I intended.
Just wait a second.
Mm.
So good!
I can't take it!
So refined,
yet such an
unbridled jolt.
Gentle enough to make you melt
while stirring up a maelstrom.
This is indeed
the true face of cooking.
All:
It's nothing but love.
[ Church bell tolls ]
What's happening?
Is it really
that good?
Full-bodied aroma.
It's the elevation
of the absolute best
the four types of tea
have to offer.
It's a soup gradation, purée
born of four types of tea.
Chickpeas, artichokes,
porcini,
and white asparagus.
He paired ingredients
that would be best fit
for each type of green tea,
then realized his purée
as panels.
The ingredients and he
complement each other
perfectly, transforming
into some sublime flavors.
Was he really able
to utilize
all four types of green tea
that perfectly?
Yeah, well, the secret
is in the sauce.
He used tea leaves
as a base
and added Champignon de Paris
to make a cappuccino sauce.
Charme: When eaten together,
the gradation of the purée
becomes even more profound.
Histoire:
The four types of tea,
each distinct
in their own right,
are effortlessly paired
with the respective
ingredient.
Hmm!
Haaah!
♪♪
In this battle,
the victor is Eishi Tsukasa.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Yo, bro,
we just lost.
Dude's too good.
This is Central at its most
absolute peak.
The number one seat
on the Ten.
He's a fierce competitor
for sure,
and yet there must be some way
we can defeat him.
Serves you right,
you damn fools!
You challenge
talent like these,
you're gonna get put down
like the dogs you are.
Sucks to me you,
losers!
I wouldn't be
so sure.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Urara: The Ten continues to
dominate this competition!
With both teams now equal --
5 against 5 --
it's time for today's regimental
food war to come to a close.
We'll resume
with the third bout,
which kicks off tomorrow
at 10:00 A.M.
Once again, these rebel pukes
are gonna get
what's coming to them!
We're bringing them
down, Tsukasa.
We are. You're
quite right, Rindo.
The way things are going,
how about we compete
against them again?
Let's you and me go
another round tomorrow, Tsukasa.
No. I don't think
that's a good idea.
That took way more out of me
than I ever would have imagined.
I think I would rather
sit out tomorrow.
The hell's
with you, Tsukasa?
Sound like some pathetic --
Oh.
Huh!
Chef Rindo,
are you all right?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
Yeah, you're right.
That Megishima's battle
was no picnic, either.
If I'm being honest,
it's got me a pretty worn out.
You're tougher than we are.
You're made of good stock,
Saito.
You're wrong.
This is not true.
It was a duel akin
to striking down my own shadow,
and it took much out of me
as well.
That perfect trace
is a thing to be feared.
That's right. This is what
you talked about before
the second bout,
isn't it, Erina?
If we let them roll over us and
hammer us with pure divine skill
that only Central knows
how to wield,
we will all lose
in the worst possible way.
But there is a chance.
If we chip away
at their physical strength,
their ability to concentrate,
then everything will change.
The chances of us delivering
that final blow
will increase dramatically.
These are the tactics
that the regimental food war
will afford us to use.
I say in no way have any of
these losses been in vain.
Instead,
this is what we wanted.
We will remain united in this.
Together we stand as one.
We can still do this.
We're not out of this yet,
you guys.
Unwavering conviction,
eyes focused on victory.
You're starting to show
your true colors as a leader.
I just want to curl up
in a ball!
I seriously
wanted to win!
Soma! I'm tired!
Back rub!
On it!
Now wipe off
my sweat.
On it!
I'm thirsty.
My mouth's dry. Tea me.
On it! This is the green tea
that Chef Tsukasa brewed.
[ Sighs ]
[ Slurps ]
You really have become a
different person in recent days.
It's quite remarkable,
really.
Well, I did get to see Tsukasa
looking rattled
and be a pretty big thorn
in his side.
I guess that's okay
for now.
Soma Yukihira, I probably won't
compete against anyone tomorrow
so I can come back
at my very best.
If you want to go up against
me,
you might have a better chance
if you sit tomorrow
out as well
so as to make sure you'll be
coming in nice and fresh.
Nah.
I plan on going out next.
I came here to win
as part of a team.
I've got an important
job to do,
follow in the footsteps
of Erina and Isshiki
and take the fight out
of the opposition
and stick 'em
where it hurts.
Ain't that right, guys?
Yeah.
Yes!
And so, with that said,
I'll make
an announcement here.
In the third bout,
it's going to be us three
first years who shake things up.
How you like that?
[ Chuckles ] I certainly hope
there are no hard feelings
between us if we take out
every single last one of you.
Right back at you,
Chef Rindo.
Speaking of which,
wouldn't it be easier
if we decided on the next card
right here
and now for
tomorrow's bout?
Yeah.
Mimasaka.
That was a tough break
for you.
♪♪
Geez. I couldn't sleep
at all last night
I know worrying
about it won't change anything,
but still,
I couldn't help it.
I wonder if Takumi-poo
is worried.
He hasn't said
a single thing in a while now.
He's fine. That's the same face
he makes in the kitchen
when he's concentrating.
Oh, so that's it.
You guys are twins.
How's Megumi?
Yeah.
It looks like she's working
through her anxiety.
[ Whimpering ]
Yes.
Use forceful strokes.
Concentrate writing
from your elbow
rather than
your wrist.
Actually,
I'd hazard to guess
she looks
completely nervous right now.
Agreed.
Ikumi: Meanwhile, somebody else
is not nervous enough.
Man. That hotel breakfast
was pretty delish, huh?
Hokkaido
is fantastic.
Why was I made to join
this card game as well?
You're sitting on a queen
of diamonds, aren't you, ma'am?
[ Laughs ]
I don't know what you mean.
Um, Miss Erina.
Is it really all right
for us to be doing this?
What?
Uh...
Well, it beats being so nervous
that we just seize up instead.
Hey, Alice, you don't have
to play that card yet, do you?
Just hang onto it!
What the heck, Erina?
Shut up!
Ikumi: The real truth is
Erina wants to join in.
How about you, Hisako?
Care to play cards?
Uh...no thank you. Having lost
during the advancement exam,
I am not worthy
of such pastime.
You're the only one still
feeling bad about that,
you know.
♪♪
[ Chuckles ]
Well, that's it for me.
Ugh.
Ah!
Okay, one more game,
Soma!
You don't have to wear
your bandana for everything.
Okay.
It's got to be about that time.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Chef Momo,
you came here alone?
Where are the others?
Somei-yan and Eizan-yan
are already waiting for us at
the venue.
Somei-yan
and Eiza-yan?
And what about
Tsukasa and Rindo?
They're both still resting up
in their rooms right now.
They're trying to recover
just a little bit longer.
Oh.
What about Chef Saito?
Is he all right?
I think so.
Well, he did a cold water
cleanse last night
and this morning,
which he said helped a lot
with his fatigue.
Cold water?
He did that in Hokkaido
in the middle of winter?
That sounds like it would
make him feel even worse.
He's gonna be just fine.
Don't worry, Takum-yan.
Takum-yan?
That's right.
It's your new nickname.
See, I like cute,
adorable things.
When it comes to food, the
cutest things of all are
sweets.
Don't you agree?
That's the very reason
I became a patissier.
That's why when I call someone
by name,
I want to call them
something cute.
Takum-yan, Isam-yan,
Mi-yan.
No.
Having "yan" at the end
of a name
sure is lovely, huh?
It's cute, right?
So in the case
of Kuga, I use "N"
to make "Kugan-yan".
That's much nicer
when it comes out the mouth.
And your name
is good, too.
"Soma" with an "M",
so I can call you
Som-yan.
That also makes it a little
easier for me to remember you.
Oh, but we've got a Son-yan.
Your names would be the same.
You'll have to be
Yuki-yan.
Yuki-yan?
So, uh, Chef Momo certainly
is quite talkative today,
isn't she?
She's the type
who is really shy
whenever
she meets someone,
but once she...finally warms
up to you,
she gets chatty.
Although,
the thing is, when Chef Momo
regards you as cute,
she's actually
looking down on you.
She only uses that way
of addressing people for those
she considers inferior
to herself.
Uh...
[ Sighs ]
I swear, Bucchi-Cutie,
you're so full
of student IDs
that you're all
heavy.
Heavy.
All:
Uh...
Oh, that's right.
You too, Megum-yan.
Good luck out there.
Uh...Thank you.
[ Grunts ]
Testing, testing.
Mic check.
Today, weather
calls for clear skies.
How did you do last night,
Eizan?
Did you sleep well,
my friend?
Our enemies are underclassman,
but strong.
Let us confront their challenge
in good spirits.
My spirits are good and
my will is forceful,
driven as they are
by impatience and bloodlust.
Do not worry about me and how
good I might have slept.
Eizan,
are you
that disgruntled by the match
decided upon yesterday?
Well, I had intended to crush
Soma Yukihira once and for all.
But this was the requested card
from yesterday,
and granting in this battle
is a classic form
of honored bushido,
is it not?
In any case, my opponent today
is going to feel my wrath.
Hey, Son-yan.
Yeah?
You better
make sure you win today.
You as well, Momo.
Hi, everyone!
Good morning!
I am just
full of energy today!
[ Giggles ]
Now then, it's time for the
first card of the third bout.
First, though he comes
from a simple eatery background
and hardly seems suited for
Totsuki,
it's a wretched little twerp
who has scored
several undeserved victories.
He will be facing the last bushi
warrior of these modern times,
the sushi chef who has
pledged allegiance to Central
and to destroy all rebels,
it's Somei Saito
versus Soma Yukihira.
Okay. The theme ingredient
for this card is...
Soma!
Huh?
Don't do like you did
in the first bout!
You'd better not draw
the other guy's specialty.
Oh, yeah.
That sucked.
Nah.
Urara:
It's butter!
It's butter?
Somei Saito,
the sushi expert,
will have to use
butter?
Looks like maybe
he picked a good one, huh?
I know. It's like
he's not as unlucky this time.
Well, butter,
is it?
In that case,
I'll present a seafood
rice bowl.
What? A seafood bowl
with butter?
How would that even work?
Huh. Coincidence?
I plan to make a dish using rice
as an ingredient, too.
I am, after all, just from
a simple eatery.
Urara: Next up,
the second card.
He was born and raised in Italy,
but is now in Japan.
Are those icy blue eyes
gazing at his own defeat?
Facing him is a man
obsessed
with both wealth
and fine dining,
the man who wielded
his authority
turning countless other chefs
into his subordinate.
It's Etsuya Eizan
versus Takumi Aldini.
And their theme
ingredient is...
beef!
Alright! That's
an easy ingredient to use
in Italian dishes,
Takumi.
Oh hell yeah!
Stick it to 'em!
Well, well, well.
Chef Etsuya Eizan.
I do believe I still owe you
for the fall selection.
Urara:
Finally, the third card.
She's a lover of candy
and traditional snacks,
the sweet professional,
Momo Akanegakubo.
And can you believe it?
Up until six months ago,
this next lowly student
was on the verge
of getting kicked out.
Throwing her hat in the ring now
is Megumi Tadokoro.
This card could be over
before it's even started.
The theme ingredient is
the king of the fruit world,
the apple!
Apples?
An ingredient
with many potential uses.
Normally, that'd be
a good pull, but --
She's going up against
the patissier of the Ten.
And it's the perfect ingredient
to make sweets.
If only the theme
could have been vegetables.
Then Megumi would have
been able to show off.
Momo: They said
we're doing apples,
so what should we make,
Bucchi?
A single, cute,
perfect little dish?
Something so cute the challenger
won't stand a chance?
I'm gonna cute the crap
out of this dish.
Okay, let's do this.
All right.
No surrender, you guys.
You okay,
huh, Megumi?
Somehow...
I'll give it my all,
right to the very end!
Erina:
Everyone.
Hmm?
Mm.
[ Gasps ]
Hmm.
[ Chuckles ]
Erina: Do your best.
All of you.
The third bout kicks off, and
the difference in their skills
could not be greater!
It's time to get this
cooking battle underway!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Soma Yukihira,
come at me
with everything you've got.
You know it.
You can count on it, dude.
I wonder if Yuki-yan
and the others understand
just how dangerous
this food war will be.
If we beat you
all here in today's battle,
only two rebels
shall remain standing.
The same goes for you,
as I recall.
If we take
all of you down,
that means just two of you
are left.
Talk all you like.
If you think this will go down
the same way, you're wrong.
Isshiki:
This could be the moment
that decides it all.
Will we be the ones
to put the other side in check,
or will they do it to us?
The answer lies in the dishes
Soma and the other first years
create.
Listen up, guys.
We may be first years,
but you better watch your backs.
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
[ Footsteps echoing ]
Coach!
I'm going to do my best!
Coach?