- ( Avatars yelling )
- ( grunts )
- ( all grunt )
- ( gasps )
- ( female Avatars shout )
- I'LL KEEP THEM
TIED UP HERE.
- YOU GUYS GO ON
AHEAD WITHOUT ME.
- ( gasps )
- ( siren blares )
- THEY MUST HAVE CHANGED
THE PASSWORD.
- HOW DID THEY KNOW?
- THESE PEOPLE
ARE YOUR FRIENDS.
HOW CAN YOU BETRAY THEM
SO EASILY?
- ( chuckles )
WHO NEEDS THEM
WHEN I HAVE YOU?
- ( grunts, gasps )
YOU SHOULD RUN
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
- I'LL LET GO.
- NO.
SOMEONE DRAINED ALL
THE SHAMPOO AND CONDITIONER.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THAT MEANS WE CAN'T HIDE
BEHIND THE BUBBLES NOW.
- IT'S TIME, MS. TOUDOU.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO ESCAPE.
- ( groans )
DAMN THAT PROBATIONARY STUDENT!
- ( all scream )
- NO WAY. SHE'S GOT THE WEIRD
BURN MARK ON HER BUTT.
- SHE MUST BE THE SCUMBAG
THAT WAS TRYING TO BLACKMAIL US.
- SO, AKIHISA DIDN'T SET UP
THE HIDDEN CAMERA AFTER ALL?
OH, THAT'S SUCH A RELIEF.
- I'M REALLY SORRY, AKI.
WE WERE WRONG.
- IT'S OKAY.  AS LONG AS YOU
FEEL BAD ABOUT IT.
- WELL, YOU WIN.
I'VE DECIDED TO LET YOU
SPY ON THE GIRLS ALL YOU WANT.
- All: YEAH!
PARADISE, HERE WE COME!
- ( gasps )
- Fukuhara: THE WHOLE THING
WAS JUST A DREAM.
THIS WOULD BE THE THIRD NIGHT
OF ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP.
- DAMN.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
WHY DID MS. TAKAHASHI
HAVE TO BUTT INTO OUR BUSINESS?
- SHE'S TOO STRONG.
IT'S CHEATING.
- HOW ARE YOU
GONNA HANDLE IT?
I MEAN, YOU'VE GOT
TO DO SOMETHING
IF YOU WANT TO GET OUT
FROM UNDER
THE BLACKMAILER'S CONTROL.
- I KNOW.
WE'RE NOT GIVING UP YET.
- YEAH, BUT TOMORROW IS
THE LAST NIGHT TO CATCH THEM.
- I'VE ALREADY GOT ANOTHER PLAN.
ALTHOUGH, I DON'T THINK
THE GUYS FROM D, E, AND F
ARE GONNA BE ENOUGH. WE'LL STILL
NEED A LOT MORE BACK-UP.
ARE YOU WITH ME, KOUTA?
- I'LL HANDLE THE PHOTOGRAPHY.
- AKIHISA, YOUR JOB'S TO LURE
THE GIRLS TO OUR ROOM.
- BUT WHY?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- IF WE CAN JUST GET
A COUPLE OF PICTURES OF THEM,
THEN WE CAN USE THOSE
PICTURES AS BAIT
TO REQUEST HELP FROM
THE OTHER CLASSES.
- YEAH, I GET IT.
WE'LL CONVINCE THE OTHER GUYS
TO HELP US BY APPEALING
TO THEIR ANIMAL DESIRES
WITH THE PICTURES.
- AND HERE IS A YUKATA
FOR YOUR PICTURE.
- NO, WE'RE TAKING
PICTURES OF THE GIRLS.
- I'LL SEND HIMEJI
AND MINAMI A TEXT MESSAGE.
"I'VE GOT SOMETHING
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
CAN YOU COME TO MY ROOM
ASAP?"  AND SEND.
- ( phone beeps )
- HIMEJI NEVER
LEAVES ME WAITING.
- "I'LL LEAVE IN
A FEW MINUTES.
I'VE JUST GOT TO PACK UP A FEW
SNACKS FOR US FIRST, 'KAY?"
- OH, COOL.
MINAMI REPLIED TOO.
- "YEAH, I GUESS I CAN.
BUT WHY THIS LATE?
CAN'T IT WAIT
TILL TOMORROW?"
- SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S
PLAYING IT SAFE.
HOW SHOULD I RESPOND?
- ( phone beeps )
- HUH, ANOTHER ONE?
AND IT'S FROM SUGAWA.
- "HEY, I WAS WONDERING,
WHY ARE YOU GUYS SO DESPERATE
TO SPY ON THE NAKED GIRLS?"
- REALLY?
OH, COME ON.
THAT QUESTION PRACTICALLY
ANSWERS ITSELF.
"YOU KNOW WHY.
IT MAY BE DESPERATE,
BUT THE HEART WANTS
WHAT THE HEART WANTS."
HMM?  HMM?
AAH!
CALM DOWN, AKIHISA, BUDDY.
LET'S PLAY THIS BACK
STEP BY STEP.
AAH!
- HEY, IS SOMETHING WRONG,
AKIHISA?
( grunts )
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
YOU LOOK KIND OF DOWN.
- COULD YOU MAYBE
GO BACK IN TIME
AND NOT BREAK MY PHONE?
- QUIT WORRYING.
I GOT IT.
I'LL HAVE THIS THING
FIXED UP IN NO TIME.
- LET ME BORROW YOUR CELL.
NOW, DAMN IT!
- SURE, MAN.
- I NEED TO EXPLAIN
THAT TEXT TO MINAMI.
YOUR CONTACTS ARE EMPTY.
YOU KNOW YOU'VE ONLY GOT
SHOUKO'S CONTACT INFO IN HERE?
- WHAT?!  DAMN IT.
I'VE GOTTA FIND A NEW PLACE
TO HIDE MY PHONE.
I WISH SHE WOULD
STOP DOING THAT.
- YEAH,
THAT'S KIND OF MESSED UP.
YOU DON'T HAPPEN TO KNOW
MINAMI'S NUMBER, DO YOU?
- OH YEAH, SURE.  THE SAME WAY
YOU KNOW SHOUKO'S NUMBER.
- WELL, I GUESS IT WAS
WORTH ASKING.
- HOLD ON.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SEND?
AAH!
YOU JUST TOOK A GIANT DUMP
ON MY LIFE, YOU MORON!
- NOW YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL.
AND YOU CAUSED THAT
FEELING, YOU JERK!
- SHUT THE HELL UP!
- ( boys gasp )
YES, SIR.
- THIS IS BAD.
I'VE GOTTA FIX IT.
I NEED YOUR CELL
TO CALL SHOUKO.
- I DROPPED MINE IN THE TOILET
AND CAN'T AFFORD A NEW ONE.
- YOU KNOW THE GOVERNMENT
CAN TRACK YOU WITH THOSE THINGS.
- IT'S OVER.
MY LIFE IS COMPLETELY OVER.
- ( knocks on door )
- IT'S OPEN.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, YOU GUYS?
- HEY, HIMEJI.
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
BUT HOW DID YOU MAKE IT?
DIDN'T IRON MAN
TRY TO STOP YOU?
- I GAVE HIM A COUPLE OF SNACKS
AND HE LET ME THROUGH.
- MAY FLIGHTS OF ANGELS
SING HIM TO HIS REST.
- WELL, I'M HERE, AKIHISA.
WHAT DID YOU WANT TO
TALK TO ME ABOUT?
- Akihisa: OH, YEAH.
I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT THAT UP.
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- Fukuhara:
WITH THE PICTURES TAKEN
AND THEIR GOAL COMPLETED,
THE NIGHT COULDN'T GET
ANY BETTER.
HOWEVER...
- HEY, AKI.  AKI.
YOU ASLEEP?
HEY.  WAKE UP, JERKWAD.
- HMM?
- I CAME TO YOUR ROOM
LIKE YOU SAID.
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA.
NOW GO AND WAKE UP.
- ( bones crack )
- ( screams )
- SHH!
SHUT UP, AKI.
YOU'RE BEING TOO LOUD.
-  ( muffled screams )
( groans )
- WELL, DON'T JUST
GO BACK TO SLEEP!
- MINAMI, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
( gasps ) I THINK I MIGHT
KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT.
ONE, I SENT MINAMI
A WEIRD-ASS TEXT.
- ( groans )
- TWO, KNOWING HER,
SHE'S PROBABLY PISSED OFF.
THREE, SHE'S LOOMING OVER
MY SLEEPING BODY.
FOUR, HER BODY'S A WEAPON.
- AAH!
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
JUST PLEASE TRY TO MAKE IT
QUICK AND PAINLESS, OKAY.
- TO BE HONEST, I'M NOT
SURE I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THAT'S SUPPOSED TO MEAN.
- WHAT?
YOU MEAN I'M SAFE?
- I DON'T GET YOU.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT WAS EASY
FOR ME TO COME OVER HERE,
YOU KNOW.
- ( gasps )
- SO THEN... I...
I WANT YOU TO
TELL ME IN PERSON,
NOT BY TEXT,
BEFORE I LET THIS THING
GO ANY FURTHER.
- THAT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE
TO COME UP WITH MY FINAL WORDS.
( gasps )
I COULD USE
SOME HELP RIGHT NOW.
HIDEYOSHI LOOKS TOO CUTE
TO WAKE UP.
KOUTA'S WRAPPED UP
TAKING PICTURES, OF COURSE.
YUUJI'S BEING TIED UP
AND MOLESTED BY SHOUKO.
-  ( muffled scream )
- DAMN IT.
DON'T MY FRIENDS REALIZE
I NEED THEM?
- ( muffled screams )
- I'VE COME TO RESCUE YOU,
MY DARLING LOVE.
AAH!
- THERE'S SOMETHING BEHIND YOU!
- MIHARU, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
- I CREPT INTO YOUR BED
TO SURPRISE YOU
ONLY TO FIND THAT
IT WAS EMPTY.
AND WHERE ELSE
COULD YOU HAVE GONE?
- WE TALKED ABOUT THIS
YESTERDAY,
YOU LITTLE LUNATIC!
- HUH?
YOU TRIED THIS YESTERDAY TOO?
- COME ON, BABY.
LET'S GO TO OUR ROOM
AND COIL OUR
NAKED BODIES TOGETHER.
DON'T GO THINKING
YOU'LL BE GETTING
ANY SLEEP TONIGHT THOUGH.
NOW FOLLOW ME.  COME ON.
- ( screams )
- I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU
TRY TO RESIST ME.
- GET COMFORTABLE.
YOU'RE NOT SLEEPING EITHER.
- ( gasps )
- WHY IS EVERYBODY SCREAMING?
- SHUT UP, GUYS.
KEEP IT DOWN.
IF YOU ALL GET ANY LOUDER,
THEN--
- Nishimura: HEY!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE HELL IS
ALL THIS RUCKUS?
- MAN, WE ARE IN
DEEP CRAP HERE.
- HE'S GONNA KILL US WHEN HE
SEES FOUR HALF-NAKED GIRLS
IN OUR ROOM.
- THERE'S ONLY THREE,
OR AM I MISSING ONE?
- YUUJI AND I ARE GONNA
TRY TO DISTRACT HIM.
YOU GIRLS MAKE A RUN FOR IT
WHILE WE DO.
LET'S GO.
- YEAH.
- ( panting, squeals )
- I HOPE YOU'RE PREPARED
FOR YOUR DESTRUCTION, YOSHII.
- ( grunts )
I TRY NOT TO THINK ABOUT THAT.
- THEN PREPARE TO
GET PREPARED!
- HE'S ON OUR ASS.
OUR ONLY HOPE IS TO HIDE
SOMEPLACE HE CAN'T GO.
- AND WHERE IS THAT?
- THE GIRL'S ROOM.
- I GET YOU.
IRON MAN CAN'T GO INTO
THE GIRL'S ROOM
'CAUSE HE'S A GUY
AND HE'LL GET FIRED.
BUT IF I GO IN THERE WEARING
NOTHING BUT MY UNDERWEAR,
THEN I'LL MOST LIKELY
GET SENT TO PRISON.
- LET'S RISK IT.
- NO FREAKING WAY.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA ACT LIKE
SUCH A GIRL ABOUT IT,
PUT THIS ON AND SHUT UP.
- THANK YOU.
-  ( screams )
- OKAY, THERE IT IS.
WE'RE ALMOST IN THE CLEAR.
- HOLD ON.
I'D BE BETTER OFF GOING IN THERE
BUCK NAKED THAN WEARING THIS.
- YOU MAKE AN EXCELLENT POINT,
BUDDY.
GOOD LUCK.
- GET BACK HERE.
- LOOK, I'D RATHER
NOT GET BUSTED
WITH A CROSS-DRESSER, OKAY?
- THEN I GUESS YOU'D BETTERd
GIVE ME YOUR YUKATA.
- GET OFF ME, YOU FREAK.
- DO IT.
NOW!  TAKE IT OFF.
- STOP!
- GIVE IT TO ME, JERKFACE.
- HELP.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?
I KNOW YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE
MUCH LUCK WITH THE LADIES,
BUT SAVE THIS KIND OF THING FOR
THE PRIVACY OF YOUR OWN ROOM.
- Both: THIS ISN'T WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE, WE SWEAR.
- Fukuhara: A PERFECT INCIDENT
FOR SUCH A HOT NIGHT.
WHOO-HOO.
- ( yawns )
SO SLEEPY.
- YOU GUYS SURE YOU'RE
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT TODAY?
'CAUSE WE'VE STILL
GOT A LOT OF
TESTS AHEAD OF US
TO RECOVER OUR SCORES.
- WE'VE GOT COUNSELING WITH IRON
MAN FOR THREE DAYS IN A ROW.
- YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,
IT DID LOOK PRETTY BAD.
- AT LEAST SOMETHING GOOD
CAME OUT OF IT.
- WHOA!
YOU ARE FREAKING AMAZING, DUDE.
- OKAY, GUYS.
IT'S TIME.
LET'S GO FIND SOME
RECRUITS TO HELP US.
- Fukuhara: THE FOURTH DAY
OF ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP,
A DAY DESTINED TO GO
DOWN IN HISTORY
AS THE FINAL SHOWDOWN.
- I'VE GATHERED SOME
USEFUL DATA FROM THE LAST TIME.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
VIDEO SURVEILLANCE
FROM THE UNITS
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
- THOSE WERE THE CLASS 'C'
GIRLS, RIGHT?
THIS WAS THEIR SCIENCE
AND HUMANITIES SCRIMMAGE.
- THE TROUBLE HERE,
THE TEACHERS' AVATARS
ARE FIGHTING ALONGSIDE THEM.
THERE'S NO WAY TO
GET PAST THAT.
- WHOA!  THERE GOES
TAKENAKA'S TOUPEE.
- NOW WATCH THIS CLOSELY.
- THE TEACHER FIELD
JUST VANISHED.
- IF THE FIELDS OF TEACHERS
FROM DIFFERENT SUBJECTS COLLIDE,
THEY CANCEL EACH OTHER OUT.
- I SEE.
I GUESS IT MUST CAUSE
TOO MUCH TECHNICAL
INTERFERENCE.
- THIS IS OUR LAST CHANCE.
THEY'LL DO EVERYTHING THEY CAN
TO CREATE AN UNBREAKABLE
LINE OF DEFENSE.
WHILE AVOIDING THE INTERFERENCE,
THEY'RE GOING TO STAGGER
THEIR MAIN FORCES
BY THE LEVEL OF THEIR STRENGTH.
THIS IS THEIR
EXPECTED FORMATION.
- OUR ROOM IS HERE
ON THE THIRD FLOOR,
WHILE OUR GOAL LIES
DEEP IN THE BASEMENT.
- MS. TAKAHASHI,
MR. OOSHIMA, AND IRON MAN
WILL PROBABLY BE
DEFENDING THE BASEMENT,
WHILE ON THE OFFENSIVE FRONT,
WE'VE GOT THE GUYS
FROM D, E, AND F.
- AND THE REST, FINGERS CROSSED
ON THE GUYS FROM A, B, AND C.
- IT'S GONNA BE A ROUGH FIGHT,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- YOU GUYS CAN LET ME HANDLE
LITTLE MISS TAKAHASHI.
KOUTA, WE'LL LEAVE OOSHIMA,
THE GYM TEACHER,
FOR YOU TO HANDLE.
BEST OF LUCK.
- ( grunts )
- AND AKIHISA,
YOU'LL TAKE IRON MAN.
- WHY ME?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE HERE
THAT HAS A PHYSICALLY ENHANCED
AVATAR THAT CAN BRING HIM DOWN.
- OKAY.
- IF YOU DO THIS,
WE'RE GONNA WATCH YOUR BACK
AT ALL COSTS.
AND I GUARANTEE YOU, WE WILL
GET YOU TO IRON MAN UNSCATHED.
AND WE'LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO SACRIFICE OURSELVES.
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO MAKE CERTAIN THAT
NO ONE EVEN TOUCHES YOU
BEFORE YOU'RE ABLE TO REACH HIM.
- YOU MEAN IT?
- WILL YOU PLEASE
DO THIS FOR US, AKIHISA?
- FINE.
- ( alarm rings, stops )
- IT'S TIME TO LAUNCH
THE MISSION, GENTLEMEN.
- RIGHT.
SO LET'S DO IT.
ARE YOU GUYS
FIRED UP OR WHAT?
- All: YEAH.
- THIS IS OUR ONLY CHANCE.
- HUDDLE UP.
- WE ACCEPT NOTHING LESS
THAN TOTAL VICTORY,
AND NOTHING WILL STOP US
FROM ACHIEVING IT.
- All: YEAH.
- I DON'T CARE IF IT'S
GIRLS OR TEACHERS IN THERE.
OUR EYES WILL FEAST UPON
A WET AND BUBBLY SKIN BUFFET.
ON THE FOURTH NIGHT OF
ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP,
WE SHALL OVERCOME!
LET'S GO.
- ( Avatars grunting )
- THEY'RE HERE.
THE FOUR PERVY MASTERMINDS.
- THEY WON'T GET PAST US.
- Both:
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- ( Avatars shout )
- SUMMON!
- ( grunts )
- DON'T KID YOURSELF,
CLASS F.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HIT THE BOOKS BEFORE YOU TALK.
- ( grunts )
- ( both scream )
- NO TIME TO WASTE
ON THE SMALL FRIES.
- THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
NOW GIVE IT UP, YUUJI.
- ( panting )
- AAH!
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- IT'S HIRAGA FROM CLASS D!
THEY SHOWED!
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE'LL HOLD THEM BACK.
KEEP MOVING.
- ( Avatars shout )
- THANKS A LOT, COMRADE.
WE'LL SEE YOU IN VALHALLA.
- ( moans )
- THERE'S SO MUCH DEDICATION.
- THAT'S 'CAUSE OUR
HEARTS ARE UNITED
BEHIND ONE PURPOSE.
- BUT OUR REAL BATTLE
STARTS HERE.
- WE'RE SCREWED IF WE DON'T
HAVE ANY BACKUP THOUGH.
- YOU BOYS NEVER LEARN!
- ( Avatars grunt )
- I'M SORRY, MR. FUSE.
THIS ISN'T PERSONAL.
- NO, NOT YOU TOO.
TELL ME WHY.
- IT'S KUROSAKI
FROM CLASS C!
- KOUTA'S PICTURES HAD
A PROFOUND EFFECT ON ME.
IN FACT, I'VE NEVER
CARED SO MUCH ABOUT ANYTHING
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
AND I PROMISE TO FIGHT
UNTIL THE BITTER END
TO SEE SUCH BEAUTY
WITH MY OWN EYES.
- ( boys grunt )
- WE COULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
THIS FAR WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
YOU GUYS WATCH OUR BACKS,
AND WE'LL DO OUR BEST
TO CLEAR THE PATH.
- THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME
A REASON TO DREAM AGAIN!
MEN OF CLASS C, LET'S GIVE THEM
EVERY BIT OF THE SUPPORT
THEY NEED.
THE GLORIOUS PATH TO VICTORY
LIES STRAIGHT AHEAD.
- ( Class C boys cheer )
- ( panting )
- IT'S STARTING TO LOOK LIKE
WE'VE GOT BACKUP
FROM EVERY GUY
IN EVERY CLASS.
- TOO BAD CLASS A IS STILL
KIND OF A WILD CARD.
- WE ALREADY KNOW THOSE PICTURES
WON'T WORK WITH KUBO.
- HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
DON'T TELL ME HE HAS
A BETTER COLLECTION
OF PICTURES THAN THOSE.
- ( all sigh )
- WELL, WELL, WELL,
IT TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
- LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT
CLASS B TOO.
- HIYAH!
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( Avatars groan )
- YUUJI,
IT IS TIME TO GIVE UP.
- SHOUKO.
- HIMEJI.
- WE'RE NOT LETTING YOU
GET PAST THIS POINT, AKIHISA.
- THAT'S IT.
WE'RE FINISHED.
WE CAN'T DEFEAT THEM.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- NEMOTO.
- WE SHOULDN'T HAVE EVEN TRIED.
IT'S A LOST CAUSE.
- AND IS IT EVEN WORTH IT
IF HIMEJI AND SHOUKO
AREN'T THERE ANYWAY?
- OF COURSE IT'S WORTH IT, GUYS.
SURE, THEY MAY NOT BE
TAKING A BATH,
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE OTHER NAKED GIRLS?
- YEAH, WHAT ABOUT THEM?
- EACH AND EVERY NAKED GIRL IN
THIS WORLD IS WORTH SPYING ON.
NOW GET UP!
GET UP FOR BOOBIES!
- LOOK, AKIHISA,
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN
WIN AT THIS POINT,
SO WHY ARE YOU SO INSANELY
DETERMINED TO FINISH THIS?
EVEN IF YOU MANAGE
TO GET THE PICTURES BACK,
IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE
YOUR REPUTATION.
- IT ISN'T THAT, HIDEYOSHI.
I ADMIT,
THAT WAS THE ONLY THING
I REALLY CARED ABOUT AT FIRST.
CAPTURING THE REAL CULPRIT
AND CLEARING MY NAME OF
ANY GUILT IN THE PROCESS.
BUT AS WE PASSED
THROUGH THIS BATTLE
AND WITNESSED GOOD MEN
SACRIFICING THEMSELVES,
WELL, I CAME TO
REALIZE SOMETHING.
- AND WHAT WAS THAT?
- EVEN THOUGH IT'S CONSIDERED
THE WRONG THING TO DO,
I'M NOT GONNA LIE
ABOUT MY FEELINGS.
SO I HAVE TO BE HONEST,
AND THE TRUTH IS, THE ONLY
REASON THAT I'M DOING THIS
IS I WANT TO SEE
THE GIRLS NAKED!
- ( chuckles ) YOUR STUPIDITY
IS SOMEHOW ADMIRABLE.
- ARE YOU REALLY SAYING
THAT YOU WOULD RATHER
PEEK ON MINAMI IN THE BATH
INSTEAD OF SPYING ON ME?
THAT'S THE LAST STRAW, AKI.
NO MORE.
YOUR PEEKING DAYS
ARE OFFICIALLY OVER!
- GO AHEAD AND LET
SOCIETY JUDGE ME FOR IT.
I DON'T CARE!
I HAVE TO STAY TRUE
TO THE FEELINGS IN MY HEART!
- I COULDN'T AGREE MORE,
AKIHISA.
- HEY, WHO SAID THAT?
- ( gasps )
- I'M SORRY IT
TOOK US SO LONG,
BUT NOW THAT I'VE
HEARD HOW YOU FEEL,
I KNOW THAT I'VE MADE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
- HEY, KUBO.
YOU MADE IT.
- I WAS A LITTLE
HESITANT AT FIRST,
BUT I AM NOW A TRUE
BELIEVER IN YOUR CAUSE.
THE GUYS OF CLASS A
STAND 24 STRONG,
AND FROM NOW ON,
YOU HAVE OUR COMPLETE
AND UNDYING ASSISTANCE.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
GIVE HIM THE COVER HE NEEDS.
- Class A Boys: YEAH!
- THANK YOU, KUBO.
I OWE YOU ONE.
- I'M THE ONE WHO SHOULD
BE THANKING YOU.
YOU WERE RIGHT
EARLIER ON.
I CAN'T LIE ABOUT
MY FEELINGS EITHER.
AND WHILE SOCIETY MAY
LOOK DOWN UPON ME,
THE HEART WANTS
WHAT THE HEART WANTS!
- THIS IS BETWEEN
ME AND AKIHISA.
NOW BUTT OUT!
- SUMMON!
- AAH!
- I'VE MADE A PERSONAL VOW
TO PROTECT AKIHISA,
AND I WON'T LET YOU
STAND IN HIS WAY.
- ( Avatars grunting )
- COME ON, YOU GUYS.
LET'S MOVE OUT!
- I'M SURPRISED.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU MANAGED
TO TALK CLASS A
INTO HELPING YOU,
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER,
DOES IT?
THIS IS THE END OF THE LINE
FOR ALL OF YOU.
SUMMON!
- NO WAY.
WE'RE WALKING RIGHT THROUGH.!
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- UH--
- GO!
YOU CAN DO IT!
- ( panting )
- SUMMON!
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
- NOTHING'S GONNA STOP HIM NOW.
- WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I WAS STARTING TO THINK
YOU WEREN'T GONNA BE
ABLE TO MAKE IT, KOUTA.
- THEY WERE EXPECTING YOU.
- THERE'S NO CHANGE
IN OUR GAME PLAN.
KEEP GOING, AKI.
- I CAN'T.
- SURE, GO.
- ( gasps )
- I'LL LET YOU PASS,
BUT ONLY IF KOUTA
STAYS AND FACES ME.
- OH, FINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
GOOD LUCK NOT DYING,
MY BROTHER.
- I AM BEYOND DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, KID.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU HONESTLY THINK
A STUDENT CAN
BEAT A TEACHER.
- WHO SAYS?
- WHAT?
- WHO SAYS THAT
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
FOR A STUDENT TO
DEFEAT A TEACHER?!
- VERY WELL.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
- All: SUMMON!
- ( grunts )
- 774?!
NOBODY'S EVER
SCORED THAT HIGH.
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- HAVING FAITH RENDERS
ANYTHING POSSIBLE.
- BUT HOW?  AND WHEN DID YOU
GAIN THAT MUCH STRENGTH?
- OUR TIME IS RUNNING OUT.
SO COME AT ME TOGETHER
IF YOU'RE GONNA ATTACK.
- ( both grunt )
- ( grunts )
AAH!
- I'M KIND OF SHOCKED
YOU ACTUALLY EXPECTED ME
TO MAKE IT THIS FAR.
- I MAKE A POINT
OF NEVER UNDERESTIMATING
MY OPPONENT.
AND WHILE YOU'RE AN IDIOT,
YOUR TENACITY IS
EXTRAORDINARY.
- I APPRECIATE THAT.
LET MET TAKE
THIS CHANCE TO THANK YOU!
AND BY THE WAY,
YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD TOO.
- AAH!
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- DON'T PATRONIZE ME, YOU TWERP.
- AAH!
- ( screams )
( grunts )
- DON'T PISS ME OFF, KID.
I'M A LOT STRONGER
THAN THIS.
- PROVE IT.
GO ON AND GET UPSET.
LET'S DO THIS FOR REAL.
- YA!
- ( grunts )
YOU KNOW...
YOU'RE GONNA GET SUSPENDED
IF YOU WALK THROUGH THAT DOOR.
- I'M NOT TOO
WORRIED ABOUT IT.
THERE ARE WAY TOO MANY
OF US TO CATCH.
YOU WON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO TO SUSPEND.
- REALLY?  YOU CAN'T
HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT.
- ( gasps )
- DON'T DROP YOUR GUARD!
( grunts )
- NO!
- IF THERE'S THAT MANY OF YOU,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
KICK YOUR ASSES
AND TAKE OUR TIME
IDENTIFYING YOU!
- ( both gasp )
- AAH!
- ( both grunting )
- AND NOW WE'RE DONE.
SO GIVE UP.
- WHAT CAN I DO?
I'VE GOT TO BEAT THIS GUY.
- YOU SIMPLY LACK THE FOCUS TO
EXECUTE SUCH A COMPLICATED PLAN.
- I TRIED SO HARD,
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SIMPLY LACK--
THAT'S IT!
YEAH.  FOCUS.
IF I NARROW THE AIM,
IF I FIGHT ALONGSIDE MY AVATAR,
WE CAN CONCENTRATE OUR ATTACKS
TO A SINGLE SPOT ON YOUR BODY.
WE'LL FOCUS OUR ATTACKS
ON YOUR BALLS!
- WHAT?!  THAT IS
A GENUINELY DISTURBING IDEA
FOR YOU TO EVEN THINK OF.
- PASS OUT AND SAVE YOURSELF
A LITTLE PAIN!
- AAH!
- KISS YOUR BALLS GOOD-BYE!
- ( gasps )
- I'M JUST MESSING WITH YOU.
- ( bones crack )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- SUCKER.
( gasps )
- AH!
- ( gasps )
- I REFUSE TO LET YOU
DEFLOWER MY LOVE.
- MIHARU?
- CALL IT QUITS,
OR OTHERWISE I'LL SPREAD THIS
PICTURE AROUND LIKE THE PLAGUE
AND YOU WILL NEVER
EVER BE POPULAR.
- YOU'VE GOT MY PICTURE?
I'M GONNA GO OUT ON A LIMB HERE.
DO YOU HAVE A BURN MARK
ON YOUR BUTT?
- HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
- SO YOU'VE BEEN THE ONE
BLACKMAILING ME THIS WHOLE TIME?
WHICH MEANS THAT
THE HIDDEN CAMERA
IN THE LOCKER ROOM IS YOURS.
- GOOD JOB FIGURING IT OUT,
BUT NOW I HAVE TO KILL YOU.
WAY TO GO, SMART GUY.
- YOU DID IT, MAN.
VERY NICE.
- AWESOME.  YOU GUYS ALL
MADE IT OUT ALIVE.
- OF COURSE.
- IF WE STORM THE BATHING ROOM
WITH THIS MANY PEOPLE,
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA BE ABLE
TO CATCH ALL OF US.
- EXACTLY.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY CAN
PUNISH US
IF WE ALL RUSH IN TOGETHER.
LET'S GO.
- All: YEAH!
- Fukuhara: A DIFFICULT
AND PAINFUL BATTLE
FROM WHICH THEY
ARISE VICTORIOUS.
WITH NO ONE LEFT TO
STAND IN THEIR WAY,
THE MEN MARCH FORWARD
WITH PRIDE IN THEIR HEARTS.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU BOYS
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- Boys: ( gasping )
IT WAS ALL FOR NOTHING?!
- Fukuhara:
"ALL YEAR TWO MALE STUDENTS
IN FUMIZUKI ACADEMY,
A TOTAL OF 149,
ARE TO BE SUSPENDED
FROM SCHOOL FOR A WEEK."
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: BAKA AND TEST.
- Mizuki: AKIHISA!
- HEY.  LONG TIME, NO SEE,
HIMEJI.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
- I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
I'M REALLY SORRY.
- WHAT, BUT WHY?
- I FEEL SO TERRIBLE FOR
TREATING YOU LIKE A PEEPING TOM
ON THE FIRST DAY OF
ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- WELL, TO BE FAIR,
ALL YOU DID WAS CALL IT
BEFORE IT HAPPENED,
SO NO BIG DEAL.
- AKI!
- HEY, MINAMI.
WHAT'S UP?
- Fukuhara: QUESTION EIGHT.
WHAT WERE YOUR ASPIRATIONS
WHEN YOU ENTERED THE ACADEMY?
- Akihisa: I BELIEVED
THAT I WAS SPECIAL,
AND THAT ONE DAY OTHERS WOULD
REALIZE MY TRUE TALENTS.
- Fukuhara: GET REAL, KID.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME,
ME, JAPAN, AND UNKNOWN WORDS!
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.