- THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
YOU HAVE TO DRESS UP
LIKE A GIRL IF I WIN.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'RE PRETTY FUNNY SOMETIMES.
- WHAT'LL BE FUNNIER
IS WHEN I WIN
AND YOU'RE DRESSED UP
LIKE A GIRL.
- OH, YOU.
SUCH A KIDDER.
- I'M NOT KIDDING.
I REALLY WANT YOU
TO DO THIS FOR ME, AKI.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
Akihisa: HOW DO I ALWAYS END UP
IN THESE SITUATIONS?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: IT ALL BEGAN EXACTLY
ONE HOUR AND 15 SECONDS AGO.
- HEY, YUUJI,
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY "DOUBT IT"?
- WOW, YOU'RE A BRAVE ONE TODAY.
- SERIOUSLY.  EVEN AFTER
YOU LOST THE OTHER DAY
AND HAD TO BUY
ALL OF US BURGERS?
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- I COULD GO FOR THAT.
- ( scoffs )
PLEASE.
I'M GETTING MY
REVENGE ON TODAY.
- WHAT REVENGE?
JUST GIVE ME YOUR WALLET.
THAT WAY, I CAN BUY
WHATEVER I WANT FOR LUNCH.
- DREAM ON.
SO, SAME RULES
AS BEFORE, RIGHT?
- Fukuhara: AND NOW,
CLASS F'S RULES
FOR THE GAME ENTITLED
"I DOUBT IT."
EACH PLAYER PLAYS
A CARD FACE DOWN.
- Akihisa: ACE.
- Fukuhara: THEY CALL OUT
THE CARD THEY PLAYED.
THE OTHER PLAYERS DECIDE
IF THEY ARE TELLING THE TRUTH.
IF SOMEONE THINKS THEY'RE LYING,
THEY SHOW THIS BY SAYING--
- Yuuji: DOUBT IT.
- Fukuhara: IF THE PERSON
WHO PLAYED THE CARD WAS LYING,
THEY MUST COLLECT ALL THE CARDS
PREVIOUSLY PLAYED.
IF THEY WERE TELLING THE TRUTH,
THE PERSON WHO CALLED
"DOUBT IT"
HAS TO COLLECT THE CARDS.
THIS CONTINUES UNTIL
ALL THE CARDS ARE PLAYED.
- Akihisa: DOUBT IT.
( groans )
- Fukuhara: USUALLY,
THE FIRST PERSON TO
GET RID OF ALL THEIR CARDS
WINS THE GAME.
- Kouta: DOUBT IT.
- All: THERE'S ALSO AN EXTRA
CLASS F SPECIAL RULE.
- Fukuhara:
I'M GETTING TO IT.
CLASS F HAS A SPECIAL RULE.
THE WINNER IS DETERMINED WHEN
A PLAYER IS LEFT WITH TWO CARDS.
- Akihisa: IT HELPS THE GAME
MOVE A LOT FASTER.
- Hideyoshi:
THE KEY IS TO MAKE SURE YOU GO
AS CLOSE TO LAST
AS POSSIBLE.
- NORMALLY, THE GAME STARTS
AT THE LOWEST NUMBER POSSIBLE,
BUT CLASS F PLAYERS
START WHEREVER THEY WANT.
- THINK HARD, DUDE. YOU COULD
BE DIGGING YOUR OWN GRAVE.
- Kouta: MM-HMM.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M UP FIRST.
EVERYONE READY?
ACE.
- THAT MEANS I'M NEXT,
RIGHT?  TWO.
- THREE.
- OH, CRAP.
IT'S MY TURN.  FOUR--
- All: DOUBT IT.
- WHAT?!
I DIDN'T EVEN GET TO
FINISH SAYING THE NUMBER.
- IT WAS OBVIOUS
YOU WERE LYING.
- THE "OH, CRAP"
KIND OF GAVE YOU AWAY.
- PLUS YOU'RE NO GOOD
AT CARD GAMES.
- ( sighs )
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
I'M A MASTER AT
PLAYING CARDS.
I LOST THAT HAND ON PURPOSE.
IT'S CALLED STRATEGY.
( gasps ) EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF YOU WAS LYING.
THAT SUCKS!
- Fukuhara: TICK-TOCK.
- OKAY, THIS IS IT.
NO MORE SCREWING AROUND.
IT'S GO TIME.
- THREE.
- FOUR.
- ( chuckles )
ANOTHER FOUR ALREADY,
AKIHISA?
I DOUBT IT.
- IDIOT.  WHY DON'T YOU
SUCK ON THAT!
- NO WAY.  DID YOU JUST
HOLD ONTO THE FOUR
FROM THE LAST ROUND
OR SOMETHING?
- SO IT WAS A SET UP THEN?
- NOT BAD.
- ( chuckles )
NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW
THAT I JUST DIDN'T REALIZE
I HAD A FOUR THE FIRST TIME.
- Fukuhara: TICK-TOCK.
- ( sighs )
FINALLY DOWN TO SIX CARDS.
HIDEYOSHI'S ONLY
GOT FOUR LEFT.
SO IT'S BETWEEN
HIM AND ME, I GUESS.
WHAT ARE THOSE TWO PLANNING?
- OH, GOOD.
I HAVE A SIX.
KOUTA, YOU'RE UP.
HAVE YOU GOT A SEVEN?
- SEVEN.
- ( stammers )
I MEANT TO SAY I DOUBT THAT.
- NICE MOVE.  HE'S TRYING
TO MAKE US PARANOID
SO WE'LL SAY DOUBT IT
WITHOUT THINKING.
OKAY, I-- HUH?
- HI, GUYS.  WHAT KIND OF
GAME ARE YOU PLAYING OVER THERE?
- OH, HEY, HIMEJI. WHAT ARE
YOU STILL DOING HERE?
- ONE OF MY TEACHERS
NEEDED HELP AFTER CLASS,
SO I STAYED.
I'M GLAD I DID TOO,
BECAUSE HE GAVE ME
THIS AS A REWARD.
THEY LOOK REALLY YUMMY.
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO
TRY SOME?
- IT DOES LOOK GOOD,
BUT WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF "I DOUBT IT."
HOW ABOUT AFTERWARDS?
WE'RE EACH BETTING THAT--
( gasps )
I SHOULDN'T SAY BETTING.
IT SOUNDS LIKE GAMBLING.
- HMM.
- MM.
- DID I SAY BETTING?
I DIDN'T MEAN BETTING.
I JUST MEANT THAT THE LOSER
GETS A PENALTY, THAT'S ALL.
- OH, A PENALTY?
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- OH, YOU KNOW.
- EVERY TIME YOU LOSE,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE
SOMETHING OFF.
- ( gasps )
LIKE CLOTHES?
- YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
- NO, AKIHISA.
PLEASE.
- ( squeals )
WHY?!  YOU GUYS
ARE SUCH PERVERTS.
- HOW ARE WE PERVERTS?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE
SEEING ANYTHING FORBIDDEN.
WE'RE ALL GUYS HERE.
- All: DOUBT IT.
- WHOA!  WHY ARE YOU
GIVING ME ALL THOSE CARDS?
I DIDN'T EVEN CALL ANYTHING.
- EVEN IF IT IS
JUST YOU GUYS,
IT'S STILL INAPPROPRIATE.
WHY DON'T WE HAVE
A CHOCOLATE PICNIC AND CHAT?
( gulps )
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
AMD STUFF.
- OKAY, FINE.  WE WILL.
BUT AFTER THIS GAME,
ALL RIGHT?
I'LL KICK THEIR TAILS
AS QUICK AS I CAN.
- UM, HIMEJI, YOU OKAY?
- RIGHT.
SO THIS IS AN EIGHT.
- NINE.
- THIS IS 10.
- JACK.
- QUEEN OF HEARTS.
- I DOUBT IT, HIDEYOSHI.
- ( sighs )
I GUESS THAT MEANS
YOU HAVE ALL THE QUEENS,
DON'T YOU?
OH WELL.
HEY, WE'RE ALL GUYS,
SO THIS ISN'T
A BIG DEAL RIGHT?
- ( both gasp )
- HERE IT GOES.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU CHICKENING OUT?
- ( giggles )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SILLY, YOU CAN'T FALL ASLEEP
AT SCHOOL,
GOOBER-PILE-FACE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
SNOOZERS ARE LOSERS.
GUESS I'M PLAYING FOR
HIDEYOSHI NOW,
SO WATCH OUT.
- THAT MIGHT NOT BE GOOD.
I MEAN, YOU WOULD
HAVE TO TAKE YOUR--
- I HAVE NO CHOICE.
YOU'VE GOT A MAN OVERBOARD.
- HE WON'T BE
OVERBOARD FOR LONG.
IT'S JUST TEMPORARY.
- HE'S A VERY VERY VERY
SLEEPY BOY.
- THE BOTTLE.  LOOK.
( grunts )
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- IT LOOKS LIKE KOUTA'S
FEELING A LITTLE SLEEPY TOO.
- Akihisa: WHAT THE HECK
IS HAPPENING?
IT SEEMS LIKE SOMETHING IS
SERIOUSLY WRONG WITH HIMEJI.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THOUGH.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S
POSSESSED OR SOMETHING.
WAIT, COULD IT BE?
HOLY CRAP.
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
HIDEYOSHI TRIED TO
TAKE HIS CLOTHES OFF
IN FRONT OF YOU, AKIHISA.
I DON'T KNOW WHY HE'D
DO A THING LIKE THAT.
- Akihisa: THIS IS INSANE.
IT'S THOSE CHOCOLATES.
SHE'S DRUNK OFF
WHATEVER'S IN THEM.
- WHY ARE YOU MAKING
A SHARK FACE, AKIHISA?
- I'M JUST UPSET
BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH PLAYERS ANYMORE.
LOOKS LIKE THE GAME'S OVER NOW.
- NO.
WE DON'T HAVE TO STOP
PLAYING THE GAME AT ALL.
WE STILL HAVE FOUR PLAYERS,
AND THAT'S ENOUGH, RIGHT?
- NO, WE DON'T.
- YES, WE DO.
- SHOUKO?!
WHEN THE "H'" DID YOU GET HERE?
- IF YOUR CLOTHES ARE TO BE
FORCEFULLY STRIPPED OFF OF YOU,
AS YOUR FIANCEE,
I SHOULD BE THERE.
- I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY
YOU CAN GET MORE WRONG INTO
ONE SENTENCE.
- I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE PLAY
BOYS TEAM VERSUS GIRLS?
- I LIKE THAT.
WE CAN FINISH
A LOT QUICKER THAT WAY TOO.
- UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CAN'T HELP IT, DUDE.
LET'S JUST GET THIS
OVER WITH QUICKLY AND BOUNCE.
- YEAH, BUT WE CAN'T
LET THEM TAKE THEIR CLOTHES OFF.
THAT'S WRONG.
- WE WON'T.
- THEY'RE GONNA START
FEELING UNCOMFORTABLE,
AND WANT TO STOP PLAYING.
- I GET YOU.
LET'S DO THIS THING.
- ( both groan )
- YOU CAN'T JUST
TAKE OFF A SOCK, AKI.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
- YUUJI, I EXPECTED
MORE OUT OF YOU.
- LET'S STOP PLAYING.
YOU WIN.
- OH MY GOSH, ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE JUST STARTED.
- YEAH, BUT SHOUKO'S
REALLY TIRED, RIGHT?
- DOUBLE UP.
- LOOK...
YOU DON'T WANT US TO GET NAKED
IN FRONT OF YOU GUYS, RIGHT?
- IT'S OKAY.  YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES.
YOU CAN PUT THIS ON INSTEAD.
- OH, NO.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
I JUST WENT BLIND.
- ( giggles )
- TOO BAD YOU DIDN'T
LISTEN TO ME WHEN I SAID
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
PLAYING THIS GAME.
NOW YOU HAVE TO PLAY
BY MY RULES.
- Akihisa:
THE EMERGENCY DUDE CODE.
- Both: HMM.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
LET'S GET BACK
TO THE GAME.
OH, LOOK WHAT I DID.
ALL RIGHT, GO.
OH, MAN!
- YOU DON'T THINK WE'D
FALL FOR THAT,
DO YOU, TRICKSY BOYS?
NOW PLAY NICE.
- YUUJI, I KNOW YOU
BETTER THAN THAT.
YOU NEVER MAKE STUPID MISTAKES
WHEN PLAYING CARD GAMES.
- ( gasps )
- SO NAUGHTY.
YOU JUST DON'T LIKE TO
PLAY BY THE RULES, DO YOU?
- THIS IS VERY BAD BEHAVIOR.
- Fukuhara: TICK-TOCK.
- SEVEN.
- Akihisa: IT WON'T BE
MUCH LONGER NOW.
I CAN'T GET THIS WRONG,
OR I'LL BE SCREWED.
HUH?
( gasps )
IS THAT KUBO?
NO WAY.  THANKS, KUBO,
FOR HOOKING A BROTHER UP.
YOU'RE THE BOMB.
I GOTTA MAKE THIS SOUND
LIKE I THOUGHT OF IT MYSELF.
IT MUST HAVE REAL
EMOTION IN IT,
LIKE GREAT POETRY.
YOU SAY IT'S A SEVEN,
BUT I DOUBT IT!
- SORRY, SWEETIE.
IT'S DEFINITELY A SEVEN.
- DAMN IT, KUBO!
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY!
I SUCK.
- ( sighs )
- DO YOU MIND EXPLAINING TO ME
WHAT THE CRAP IS
WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY IN THE HELL WOULD YOU
TRUST KUBO WITH OUR NAKEDNESS?
- 'CAUSE I'M AN IDIOT.
- Fukuhara: TICK-TOCK.
- ( Akihisa groans )
- I'M STARTING TO HAVE
MIXED FEELINGS ABOUT WHETHER
WE SHOULD BE DOING THIS.
- I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'RE FRIENDS, HIMEJI.
WE SHOULDN'T PLAY AGAINST
EACH OTHER LIKE THIS.
WE SHOULD JUST STOP
RIGHT HERE WITH NO PENALTIES.
- ( sighs )
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW,
YOU'LL BE AN INTERNET SENSATION
AND YOU'LL BE
SURROUNDED BY GIRLS.
- FIRST OF ALL,
I NEVER SAID I'D CROSS-DRESS.
AND SECOND, I NEVER SAID
YOU COULD TAKE PICTURES
AND PUT THEM ON THE WEB.
- YUUJI.
IF IT GETS TO BE TOO MUCH,
YOU CAN CLOSE YOUR EYES
WHILE I TAKE YOUR PICTURE.
- WE ARE NOT GONNA LOSE.
I WON'T LET IT HAPPEN!
- THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE I
SHOULD TELL YOU.
- GREAT. AND WHAT
MIGHT THAT BE?
- IF I END UP HAVING TO TAKE MY
CLOTHES OFF FOR WHATEVER REASON,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THE GAME IS OVER.
WE'RE GONNA KEEP PLAYING
TILL THE END.
- NO WAY.
- SHE DOESN'T MEAN THAT.
- IT'S A GOOD THING I PICKED
OUT SUCH CUTE UNDERWEAR TODAY.
- OH, COME ON NOW!
- WHY DO THEY WANT TO TAKE
THEIR CLOTHES OFF?
- Fukuhara: INDEED.
- WELL, I KNOW YOU'RE ABOUT
TO SAY YOU'RE PLAYING A KING,
SO I'M GONNA GO AHEAD
AND SAY "I DOUBT IT" NOW.
- ( whimpers )
FOUR.
- FIVE.
- AND SIX.
- UH, I DOUBT IT?
- ( both screaming )
HURRY IT UP, DUDE!
THEY'RE GAINING ON US.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE
NAKED ON THE INTERNET!
- SLOW DOWN.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU ABOUT--
- SORRY. PLEASE HELP US!
- WE'LL TAKE A REMEDIAL CLASS.
- HOLD ON.
WHY IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
DRESSED LIKE THAT?
- DO YOU THINK WE COULD
TALK ABOUT THIS SOME OTHER TIME?
- HOLY CRAP, IT'S THEM.
WE GOTTA GO.
- ( both scream )
- AKI, WHERE ARE
YOU GOING, SILLY?
YOU FORGOT TO PUT ON
YOUR NEW CLOTHES.
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
- ( scoffs )
THEY'RE BEING CHASED
BY GIRLS WITH SCHOOL UNIFORMS,
AND I DON'T EVEN CARE
TO KNOW WHY.
- Kouta: BAKA AND TEST!
- All: WHAT?
AN AVATAR SYSTEM TEST RUN?
- OH, GOOD.
YOU CAN READ.
YES, I WOULD LIKE
YOUR HELP WITH THIS.
- WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
WE COULD HELP WITH THAT?
- I DON'T THINK IT,
I KNOW IT.
IF SOMETHING GOES WRONG,
I KNOW YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
DEAL WITH THE HIGHER
SCORING AVATARS.
- OH, YEAH.  YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I ALMOST FORGOT
ALL ABOUT THAT LITTLE INCIDENT.
- TRUST ME, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
I ENJOY BRINGING UP.
BUT NOW WE CAN MOVE FORWARD.
ONE OTHER THING
I MUST INSIST ON,
KEEP CLASS A AND HIMEJI
OUT OF THIS.
- WAIT, THAT'S ME.
BUT I WANTED TO HELP TOO.
- TOO BAD.
- AW, THAT SUCKS.
WELL, WE'LL MISS YOU.
- I DO APPRECIATE
YOUR COOPERATION
IN THIS MATTER.
I'LL GO AHEAD AND
COUNT YOU ALL IN.
- WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
THAT'S GONNA BE A PAIN.
WHY DO WE HAVE TO
DO THIS AGAIN?
I MEAN,
PROBATIONARY STUDENTS ALREADY
HAVE SO MANY CHORES TO DO.
THERE MIGHT NOT BE
ENOUGH TIME.
- HOWEVER, THERE'S PLENTY OF
TIME TO RUN AROUND THE HALLWAYS
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR,
IS THAT CORRECT?
- I'M SO SORRY.
- I'M NOT COMPLETELY HEARTLESS.
I SUPPOSE IT WOULD BE FAIR
TO COMPENSATE YOU IN SOME WAY.
A COUPLE OF LUNCH TICKETS
OR A COUPON BOOK SHOULD
BE ENOUGH, YES?
- All: SWEET!
- ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
I'LL CREATE A MOCK FIELD
OUT OF THE SCHOOL BUILDING
FOR YOU TO PRACTICE ON.
FIRST UP WILL BE...
KOUTA TSUCHIYA, KINOSHITA,
THEN SHIMADA.
YOSHII, OF COURSE,
AND SAKAMOTO
NOW DO NOT LET ME DOWN.
- Yuuji: WAIT JUST A SECOND.
I'VE GOT HIGH SCORES.
HOW COME I'M BEING
PUNISHED WITH THESE LOSERS?
- YOU ASK ME THAT AS THOUGH
YOU BELIEVE I HONESTLY CARE.
- HEY!
THIS IS SO STUPID.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- CAN YOU STOP WHINING?
IT'S NOT HELPING US
GET THIS DONE ANY FASTER.
NOW COME ON.
WE JUST HAVE TO SUMMON THEM,
THAT RIGHT?
- THAT'S THE IMPRESSION I GOT.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- BRING IT.
- All: SUMMON.
- ( giggles )
THAT'S WEIRD.
I GUESS WE'RE STILL
IN OUR UNIFORMS
SINCE THIS IS JUST
A TEST RUN.
- BUT WE DON'T
HAVE ANY WEAPONS.
- WE'RE SO CUTE.
- THIS REMINDS ME OF
WHEN WE WERE IN FIRST YEAR.
OH, NO.
- ( all gasping )
- ( Avatars giggling )
- THEY SEEM REALLY HAPPY.
- HAGASAURUS SAID THE NEW UPDATE
WAS FOR USABILITY
IMPROVEMENTS, RIGHT?
- I NEED ADVICE.
SOMETHING REALLY STRANGE
HAPPENED THIS MORNING,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- HUH?  WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT WERE YOU
JUST TALKING ABOUT?
- UH, ARE YOU TALKING TO ME?
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
- OUR NEIGHBOR TOLD ME
HE'S IN LOVE WITH ME,
WHICH IS COURAGEOUS, BUT ALSO
KIND OF WEIRD, YOU KNOW?
- ( gasps )
- WHOA!
YOU MEAN A GUY
OUTSIDE OUR SCHOOL
ADMITTED HE HAD A CRUSH
ON YOU? THAT'S GREAT.
DOES THAT HAPPEN
TO YOU A LOT?
- OF COURSE NOT.
I'M A GUY, REMEMBER?
WHY WOULD THAT HAPPEN TO ME?
- IT'S THE THIRD
TIME THIS MONTH.
- ( all murmur )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE FINALLY ADMITTED IT.
- NO, THAT WAS THE MINI DOUCHE.
HIDEYOSHI DOESN'T LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT THAT STUFF.
- IT'S TRUE. HE'S VERY SECRETIVE
WHEN IT COMES TO HIS LOVE LIFE.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T HAVE ANY SECRETS.
- HOORAY!
SHE SAID SHE BELIEVED ME.
I'M A GOOD ACTOR!
( giggles )
WHY BE QUIET?
I'M SO HAPPY.
- ( chuckles )
AH!
I HAVE A QUESTION.
GOT A SEC?
- MAYBE.
- DO YOU WANT TO TALK DIRTY?
I'M ALL ABOUT IT.
- ( laughs )
NOT THAT I'M OPPOSED TO
THAT KIND OF THING AT ALL,
BUT THIS HAPPENS TO BE ABOUT
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
- SORRY, I'M ONLY INTERESTED
IN WHAT'S UNDER YOUR SKIRT.
- ( laughs )
HE DOESN'T MESS AROUND, DOES HE?
AT LEAST HE'S FUNNY.
- PLEASE STOP IT.
- WHAT'S UNDER YOUR SKIRT?
WHAT'S UNDER YOUR SKIRT?
THIS IS AVATAR ABUSE,
YOU KNOW.
- ( laughs )
YOU GOTTA LOVE HIS HONESTY.
I THINK I MIGHT WANT
TO PLAY WITH HIM A LITTLE.
- ( both sigh )
- SO YOU WANT TO SEE
WHAT'S UNDER MY SKIRT,
DO YOU?
- NO, NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
- UNDER YOUR SKIRT
LIES THE DOORWAY
TO ALL MY HOPES AND DREAMS.
I WANT TO SEE ALL
YOU HAVE TO OFFER.
THERE'S NO SKIRT
I DON'T WANT TO EXPLORE.
I DON'T CARE IF THEY'RE
LONG AND STRAIGHT,
TIGHT, MINI, FLARED,
PLEATED,
THEY'RE ALL EXCEPTIONAL.
DON'T TRY TO TRICK ME
WITH THOSE CULOTTES THOUGH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THOSE THINGS ARE,
BUT THEY ARE NOT SKIRTS.
- PLEASE DON'T LISTEN
TO THIS GUY.
- HMM.
- YAY!
- THEY'RE SAYING WHAT THEIR
SUMMONERS ARE THINKING.
- ( giggles )
- WHOA.
I ACTUALLY TOUCHED
HER AVATAR WITH MY HANDS.
- THIS IS GONNA GET
WAY CRAZY.
- ALL RIGHT.
HAND THAT LITTLE BRAT OVER.
- MM!  NO!
I'M STAYING RIGHT HERE
WITH AKI.
- SO NOT ONLY DO THEY TALK,
THEY'RE ALLOWED TO
DISOBEY US?
- THEY'RE LIKE REAL LIVE
STICKY CHILDREN WITH OPINIONS.
- THAT'S IT.
THEY'RE LIKE KIDS.
- PICK ME UP, PICK ME UP.
- NO TOUCHING!
LET GO OF HIM RIGHT NOW.
- NO!
- HEY, PLEASE DON'T
WORRY ABOUT.
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT, I'M USED
TO THIS SORT OF THING.
IT'S TOTALLY FINE.
- HUH? YOU'RE USED TO WHAT?
- WELL, KIDS REALLY LIKE ME
FOR SOME REASON.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE THEY FEEL
LIKE THEY CAN RELATE TO YOU.
- OH, WHATEVER, YUUJI.
- PAY ATTENTION TO ME NOW.
- RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
- KNOW WHAT?
WHEN I'M A LITTLE
MEAN TO YOU,
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE...
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU--
- ( screams )
WHAT FIELD DID
YOU HATCH FROM?
ARE YOU TRYING TO RUIN ME?
- AKI, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU OKAY? SAY SOMETHING.
- YOU'RE NOT EVEN
LISTENING TO ME.
- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S A GOOD THING
I DON'T HAVE ANY SECRETS.
'CAUSE THAT LITTLE BRAT--
- SO YESTERDAY,
THIS GIRL FROM FIRST YEAR
TOLD ME SHE'S IN LOVE WITH ME.
- ( Minami screams )
- ( straining )
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU, AKI?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO USE
HER TO DIG INTO MY STUFF?
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- WHAT?
SHE'S THE ONE WHO'S
PUTTING IT ALL OUT THERE.
- OH, DON'T YOU
BLAME THIS ON HER.
WHY DON'T YOU SUMMON
YOUR BABY BEAST,
AND WE'LL SEE
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
- AAH!
THERE'S NO WAY I'M BRINGING
THAT LOOSE CANNON OUT.
I HAVE TO AVOID IT.
- SO THEY SAY
WHATEVER WE'RE THINKING?
- HUH? WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I'M SORRY.
- ( gasps )
NOTHING, I WAS JUST MUMBLING.
HEY, CAN YOU READ THIS
FOR ME BY ANY CHANCE?
- UH, SURE.
"KAKU-SA-MON-DAI,"
I THINK.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU READ IT PERFECTLY.
- HMM?
- NO! WHY'S HE HERE?
MOTHER OF CRAP!
- I'M SORRY, AKIHISA.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN CURIOUS ABOUT,
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
THIS WOULD DO IT.
- NICE WORK, MIZUKI.
SO SPIT IT ALL OUT.
WHO DO YOU LIKE?
IS IT SOMEONE IN THIS ROOM?
- I NEED A DISTRACTION.
SOMEONE DISTRACT ME!
- HMM.
- NO WAY.
- Both: OH, MAN.
NOW I CAN'T USE THAT IDIOT.
- Both Yuujis:
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S AN IDIOT!
- Both Akis:
WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
- ( chuckles )
OKAY, CALM DOWN.
- ALMOST.
I'M SO CLOSE.
- ( all gasp )
- I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU'VE NOTICED,
BUT I USUALLY WEAR
LEGGINGS UNDER MY SKIRT.
BUT THAT'S NOT THE CASE TODAY.
- ( chuckles )
LIKE WE EVEN CARE.
- FOR THE LOVE OF MICE,
FLIP IT UP!
- THIS ISN'T GONNA END WELL,
IS IT?
- SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
I'M FROSTY.
- LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'LL DO IT.
- WHY DOES HE WANT TO
RUIN MY ENTIRE LIFE?
- AKI, COME HERE!
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- ME TOO.
I HAVE A QUESTION I WANT TO ASK.
- HEY, YUUJI...
- Fukuhara:
WE'LL BE BACK IN JUST A MOMENT.
- ( both murmur )
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR HAVING
A BRAIN FULL OF SMUTTINESS.
- I HOPE YOU BOTH HAVE
LEARNED A FEW THINGS.
- I DON'T WEAR LEGGINGS WITH
MY SKIRTS EITHER, YOU KNOW.
- OH, MAN.  WHAT A RIOT.
THAT WAS HILARIOUS.
- All: OW OW OW OW.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
- PROBABLY THE WORST THING
YOU'VE EVER DONE.
- ( chuckles )
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I OVERSLEPT THIS MORNING,
SO I WAS RUNNING LATE.
LEFT THE HOUSE
WITHOUT A BRA.
- Both: PLEASE STOP,
WE CAN'T TAKE IT!
- Both Avatars:
YOU'RE NOT WEARING A BRA?!
- ( both groan )
- YUUJI.
- NO, IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
I'M A GUY.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
- COME HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET ME GO.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
- YOU HAPPY?
- AND WHY WOULD I BE HAPPY?
THIS MEANS NOTHING.
- ( cheering )
- I AM NOT HAPPY!
- YOU COULD HAVE FOOLED ME.
I'D SAY YOU'RE IN LOVE.
- YOU'RE THE COOLEST GUY
I KNOW.
I'M SO JEALOUS
I CAN'T SEE STRAIGHT.
- BUT THAT'S OKAY.
'CAUSE LOOK WHAT I GOT, RIGHT?
- Fukuhara:
WE WILL RETURN IN A MOMENT.
- I'M NOT SAYING IT'S BAD...
- MM-HMM.
- BUT THE TIMING
HAS TO BE RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T JUMP INTO
THAT SORT OF THING.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- YES, MA'AM.
- IT TAKES TIME.  YOU HAVE TO
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER FIRST.
AND YOU SHOULD BE IN LOVE.
- LIKE US!
- AKI LOVES ME.
- ( gasps )
- ( sighs )
- AKIHISA?
- ( both gasp )
- YO, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I KNOW THIS SEEMS
COMPLETELY RANDOM,
BUT I STILL WANT TO KNOW.
IS THERE ANYONE YOU LIKE?
- Both:
WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
- I'M SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT IN THE MOOD
TO TALK ABOUT WHO YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN
AFTER EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED SO FAR TODAY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- LET ME JUST TRY ASKING
A DIFFERENT WAY.
- ( gasps )
NOT AGAIN.
I WON'T LET HER TRICK ME.
( chuckles )
- IS THERE ANYONE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU LIKE MORE THAN OTHERS?
- YEAH, SURE.  I MEAN,
SAMON IN CLASS G'S PRETTY COOL.
- WAIT, HOLD ON!
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE NAMED SAMON.
( gasps )
- NOW WHAT WERE WE
TALKING ABOUT?
WHO IN THE SCHOOL WE LIKE?
- THIS ISN'T FAIR.
YOU TRICKED ME.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
HIMEJI?
YOU TRYING TO SAY
YOU HAVE SECRETS
YOU DON'T WANT ANYONE
TO KNOW ABOUT?
- NO.  IT'S TOTALLY OKAY.
I DON'T HAVE ANY SECRETS.
- BUT IF I'M BEING HONEST,
WHEN WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
HAVING NAUGHTY THOUGHTS EARLIER,
WELL...
I STARTED TO FEEL FUNNY
AND HAVE STRANGE THOUGHTS TOO.
- NO!
- ( footsteps approach )
- SO HOW'S IT GOING IN HERE?
( gasps )
- NO!
- SIT STILL.
STAY HERE.  STOP IT!
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
- WHAT HAVE THEY DONE?
LOOK AT THEM.
WHY CAN'T THIS SORT OF THING
EVER HAPPEN TO SOMEBODY ELSE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( door opens )
- HI THERE.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- MY NAME'S NAKABAYASHI.
I'M THE REP FOR CLASS E AND I.
I WANTED TO EXPRESS
SOMETHING TO YOU
THAT I'VE BEEN HOLDING IN
FOR A LONG TIME.
WELL, I GUESS I HAVEN'T BEEN
HOLDING IT IN FOR THAT LONG.
BUT STILL,
I'M NOT GOOD AT THIS,
SO BEAR WITH ME PLEASE?
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
THAT I TELL YOU SOME--
WELL, SOME UNPROFESSED WORDS.
- TELL ME SOME
UNPROFESSED WORDS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( both gasp )
- I LIKE YOU AND I REALLY WANT
YOU TO GO OUT WITH ME.
- WHAT IS IT THAT MAKES
AKIHISA SO DEVILISHLY CHARMING
AND IRRESISTIBLE?
HIS WALK,
HIS WORDS, HIS THOUGHTS?
EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM
IS PERFECTION!
- Fukuhara: GOODNESS.
- NAKABAYASHI?
- YES, KUBO?
- I'M SORRY.
- I CAN'T THINK OF A MORE
HUMILIATING WAY
TO BE REJECTED!
- Fukuhara:
QUESTION NUMBER FIVE.
WHAT DO YOU PAY
IF YOU'VE BURNED A LOVED ONE?
- Kouta: WHAT?
UM, I HAVE NO IDEA.
- Fukuhara:
ALIMONY VERA.
- Akihisa: NEXT EPISODE...
ME, PEEKING, AND TRAINING CAMP!
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.