- ( violin music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- ( Minami speaking
in German accent )
I'M GOING TO JAPAN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Minami: IT WAS A
YEAR AGO TODAY,
DURING THE
ORIENTATION CEREMONY.
I'D JUST MOVED TO JAPAN
FROM GERMANY,
SO I WASN'T VERY FAMILIAR
WITH THE LANGUAGE YET.
- NICE TO MEET YOU, AND I HOPE
YOU HAVE A GOOD YEAR.
- "IF I WANT TO FIT IN HERE,
I HAVE TO MAKE A GOOD
FIRST IMPRESSION.
I CAN'T GO UP THERE
AND EMBARRASS MYSELF.
NO GETTING NERVOUS
OR FIDGETY
AND MAKING EVERYONE THINK
I'M CRAZY."
THOSE WERE THE SORTS OF THINGS
GOING THROUGH MY HEAD
AS I WAITED MY TURN TO INTRODUCE
MYSELF TO THE CLASS.
- Fukuhara: NEXT WE HAVE
MINAMI SHIMADA.
- HELLO EVERYONE, MY NAME
IS MINAMI SHIMADA.
IT'S SO NICE TO
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH.
- ( students murmuring )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID I DO SOMETHING
STRANGE ALREADY?
- I'VE BEEN TOLD MISS SHIMADA IS
A RETURNEE STUDENT FROM GERMANY.
I IMAGINE IT'LL BE DIFFICULT
FOR HER TO ADJUST FOR A WHILE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS IN
JAPAN SHE'S STILL NOT USED TO,
SO DO YOUR BEST
TO HELP HER OUT.
I KNOW IT SEEMS DIFFICULT,
BUT TAKE IT SLOW.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO USE
CHINESE KANJI,
START WITH ONE CHARACTER
AT A TIME.
- CHINESE?
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU
SO MUCH.
EMBARRASSING.
WHY DIDN'T THEY JUST TELL ME I
WAS WRITING IT WRONG
INSTEAD OF STARING?
- Minami: MY DAD HAD TOLD ME
EVERYONE IN JAPAN WOULD BE NICE,
AND THAT I'D BE ABLE TO
MAKE FRIENDS SUPER EASY.
BUT THAT ONE CLASS PROVED HIM
WRONG IN THIRTY SECONDS.
I FELT LIKE CRAP.
- HEY, MY NAME'S YUUJI SAKAMOTO.
REALLY GLAD TO BE HERE.
- THAT'S THE ONE EVERYONE CALLED
"THE DEMON" AT HIS OLD SCHOOL,
AND I CAN SEE WHY.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S TOO LATE
TO SWITCH CLASSES?
- ( German accent ) HAVE I COME
TO A SCHOOL OF DELINQUENTS?
NO, NO, NO.
FATHER SAID
JAPAN IS VERY SAFE,
SO I AM SURE HE IS NOT AS
SCARY AS HE LOOKS.
- I'M HIDEYOSHI KINOSHITA.
IT'S NICE TO MEET ALL OF YOU.
- OH MY.  IS THIS GIRL
REALLY WEARING A BOY'S UNIFORM?
MAYBE SHE'S ONE OF THOSE GIRLS
WHO ISN'T INTO WEARING SKIRTS.
AND THAT IS OKAY.
IT'S NOT WEIRD AT ALL.
DAD SAID THERE IS NOTHING
STRANGE OR SCARY ABOUT JAPAN,
AND HE IS RIGHT.
- I'M KOUTA TSUCHIYA,
AND I TAKE PIC--
PICNIC LUNCHES.
I'M VERY GOOD AT STALKI--
UH, NOT GOOD AT ANYTHING.
- PLEASE WAIT, THERE IS
SOMETHING YOU DROPPED.
- FORGET WHAT YOU SAW
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
- OKAY, THAT WAS NOT CREEPY.
HE USES THAT CAMERA
TO RECORD THE CLASSES.
NOTHING STRANGE.
JUST LIKE FATHER SAID.
- AND NOW STRAIGHT FROM
NAGATSUI JUNIOR HIGH,
THE ONE AND ONLY,
AKIHISA YOSHII!
( laughs )
- THAT KID IS STRANGE.
THEY'RE ALL FREAKS!
FATHER LIED TO ME!
- ( students chattering )
- YOU'RE A RETURNEE STUDENT?
THAT'S SO COOL.
- HEY, WHEN DID YOU GET BACK
TO JAPAN?
- WERE YOU BORN IN GERMANY?
- Minami: LIKE THEY'D NEVER
SEEN A RETURNEE STUDENT.
EITHER THEY WERE
HONESTLY INTERESTED
OR TOTALLY FREAKED OUT.
- ARE YOU, LIKE,
REALLY GOOD AT GERMAN?
- ARE YOU GONNA JOIN A CLUB
AT THIS SCHOOL?
- DID YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND
ON THE OTHER SIDE?!
- ( German accent )
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND THEM.
THEY'RE ALL TALKING SO FAST,
I CAN BARELY PICK
UP A FEW WORDS.
I DON'T REMEMBER IF IT'S
"PLEASE SLOW DOWN"
OR "PLEASE BE QUIET."
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT CATS ARE?
- WHAT DO PEOPLE EAT OVER THERE?
- WHAT SIZE BRA DO YOU WEAR?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DID THAT GIRL SAY
THIS MORNING
THAT MADE THOSE GUYS BACK UP?
IT WAS JUST ONE PHRASE.
OH, YAH.
I REMEMBER NOW.
DA...
- All: DA?
- DAMN STUPID PIGS.
SHUT YOUR FAT TRAPS.
- All: UH...
- UH?
- Minami: NEEDLESS TO SAY,
THAT DID NOT MAKE A
GOOD FIRST IMPRESSION.
- ( students chattering )
- I ASKED DAD ABOUT IT LATER.
TURNS OUT IT'S NOT
THE NICEST THING TO SAY
TO PEOPLE YOU WANT
TO LIKE YOU.
AFTER THAT,
THEY WERE SCARED.
NONE OF THEM EVEN WANTED TO
COME CLOSE TO ME.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR ONE PERSON.
- EXCUSE ME.
SHIMADA, RIGHT?
- OH, HI!
- ( squeaking )
- ( sighs )
- WHAT?!  WHAT'D I DO?!
- ( German accent ) DO YOU ALL
THE TIME WEAR THOSE TO SCHOOL?
- YOU MEAN THE SAILOR SUIT?
NO, I OVERSLEPT.
AND I DIDN'T HAVE
ANYMORE TIME.
I JUST GRABBED SOMETHING
AND RAN OUT.
- SO BEING IN A HURRY
MADE IT OKAY
TO DRESS UP
IN A SAILOR COSTUME?
IF THIS IS HOW
JAPANESE STUDENTS THINK,
I'LL NEVER FIGURE
THIS PLACE OUT.
- HEY, ARE YOU GONNA MOVE?
OR ARE YOU JUST GONNA KEEP
BLOCKING THE EXIT
AND RAMBLING ON LIKE AN IDIOT?
- THERE IS NO NEED TO BE RUDE,
BUDDY!
SHIMADA'S JUST NOT USED TO
LIVING IN JAPAN YET, OKAY?
THAT DOESN'T MAKE HER AN IDIOT.
- OH, SHUT UP!
I WAS TALKING TO YOU, STUPID.
- OH, YEAH?  WELL, WHAT'S
SO STUPID ABOUT ME?!
- EVERYTHING!  AND WHOSE
DRESS ARE YOU WEARING?
- IT'S A SHIRT,
AND YOU SHOULDN'T JUDGE PEOPLE
BY WHO THEY ARE
OR WHAT THEY'RE WEARING!
- HOW ELSE AM I GONNA
JUDGE THEM?
YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE,
DUDE.
- WHATEVER!
YOU'RE STUPID TOO.
I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES!
THIS MORNING!
THAT REALLY PRETTY GIRL
TRIED TO TALK TO YOU
AND YOU JUST IGNORED HER
LIKE A TURD.
- THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
AND WHY WERE YOU STARING
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOU
FROM THE VERY FIRST TIME
I SAW YOUR STUPID ASS.
- I COULD SAY THE SAME TO YOU!
WHAT KIND OF DILL WEED CALLS
SOMEONE THEY JUST MET AN IDIOT?
ONLY A LUNATIC, THAT'S WHO!
- OH, NO WAY!
SAILOR SISSY BOY IS
CALLING ME CRAZY?
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE THAT
CIRCUS MONKEY BACK HIS OUTFIT?
- I'M GOING TO GOOD-BYE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- Minami: I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
EVERYTHING THEY WERE SAYING,
BUT I GOT THE IDEA I SHOULD
PROBABLY GO AHEAD
AND AVOID THEM.
I WAS TRYING TO GET BACK TO
A NORMAL SCHOOL LIFE,
NOT CREATE MORE DRAMA
FOR MYSELF.
THINGS WERE GREAT IN GERMANY.
BUT HAZUKI, MY LITTLE SISTER?
SHE NEEDED ME.
SHE'S WHY I CAME BACK
TO JAPAN WITH DAD
WHEN HE GOT HIS JOB TRANSFER.
STILL, I WASN'T SURE
I DID THE RIGHT THING.
- ( German accent )
SO THE GIRLS' ROOM IS BLUE
AND THE BOYS' IS PINK HERE,
IS IT?
YES, THAT COULD HAVE BEEN
VERY AWKWARD.
- ( boys screaming )
- WHAT THE HELL?!
WHY ARE THERE GIRLS IN HERE?!
- Hideyoshi: WHERE?
I AM NOT A GIRL!
- COME RIGHT HERE,
KINOSHITA!
- NO!
I HAVE TO PEE REALLY BAD!
- ( both pant )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID I HAVE TO LEAVE?
- ( shouts in German )
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WHY ARE YOU SO MAD?
I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS,
BUT I'M NOT THE ONE WHO WALKED
INTO THE WRONG RESTROOM.
SHIMADA, WAIT!
- ( German accent )
I KNOW IT'S JUST THE FIRST DAY,
BUT EVERYTHING ABOUT JAPAN
IS FREAKING ME OUT.
I'M SURE IT'LL START TO MAKE
SENSE EVENTUALLY.
I JUST HAVE TO BE PATIENT
AND PUT UP WITH A BIT
OF CRAZINESS UNTIL THEN.
AT LEAST I GET TO SPEND
SOME MORE TIME WITH MY FAMILY.
- JUST A LITTLE HIGHER--
AAH!
- YES.
JAPAN DEFINITELY
FREAKS ME OUT.
- ( violin music playing )
- Minami: THERE WERE
ONLY STRANGE PEOPLE, EVER.
- ( inaudible )
( German accent )
FRIENDS.
- ( dog barking )
- Minami:
BAKA AND TEST!
CLASSES WERE IN FULL
SWING AFTER ABOUT A WEEK.
I WAS OVERWHELMED WITH HOW
QUICKLY IT WAS MOVING.
MODERN JAPANESE CLASS WAS HARDER
THAN ANY OTHER CLASS I HAD.
EVERYONE WAS FLUENT,
AND I COULD BARELY FOLLOW ALONG.
WHEN THE TIME CAME TO
READ CLASSICS,
IT WAS PRETTY MUCH GIBBERISH.
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN HOW ABOUT YOSHII?
IN THIS CASE, CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT THE CONJUGATION OF THE
WORD "HA-BERRY" IS?
- YES.
IT'S "HANNARI," SIR.
- NOW WHY WOULD YOU GIVE ME
A WORD IN THE KYOTO DIALECT
WHEN I ASKED YOU
FOR THE CONJUGATION
OF A CLASSIC JAPANESE WORD?
IT'S SO IRRELEVANT
THAT IT'S ACTUALLY REFRESHING.
- HUH?
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
- ( laughter )
- ( chuckles )
HUH?
- THAT'S ALL.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE FAMILIAR WITH
EVERYTHING WE DID TODAY
BEFORE OUR NEXT CLASS.
- ( German accent )
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
- Minami: I MAY HAVE
BEEN FREED FROM THE JAWS
OF THE MOST BORING
CLASS EVER, BUT...
- HEY! WAIT UP, SHIMADA!
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED NOW?
- WHERE AM I GO?
- UM, YEAH, RIGHT.
- WHAT IS IT TO SAY
"TO GO HOME"?
- DID YOU SAY, "WHAT A SEA"?
- TO.  GO.  HOME!
- ( distorted ) OH, "HOME."
THAT MAKES MORE SENSE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SAYING SOMETHING
ABOUT "THE SEA" FOR A SEC.
I'M SORRY.  IT'S HARD
TO UNDERSTAND YOU SOMETIMES.
GUESS THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR BEING CULTURED
AND STUDYING ABROAD, HUH?
YOU'RE LIKE A FOREIGNER NOW,
YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT THAT?
- Minami: GETTING USED TO A
LANGUAGE AGAIN IS HARD ENOUGH
WHEN PEOPLE SPEAK IT
AT LIGHTNING SPEED...
BUT I WAS SO STRESSED OUT
THAT I COULDN'T CONCENTRATE.
MY HEAD WAS POUNDING
AND MY BRAIN COULDN'T EVEN
PROCESS WHAT I WAS HEARING.
- BELIEVE ME, I WISH
I COULD DITCH THIS PLACE TOO.
I'M DYING OF BOREDOM HERE.
BUT WE STILL GOTTA GO BACK
TO HOMEROOM AFTER THIS.
- HUH?
- I GUESS YOU COULD SHORTEN IT
AND CALL IT HOME IF YOU WANTED.
THEN IT WOULD BE
TRUE FOR EVERYONE.
HOW WEIRD WOULD IT BE
IF WE ALL SAID
WE WERE GOING HOME...
- WHAT IS HE SMILING ABOUT?
IS IT REALLY THAT FUNNY THAT
I CAN'T SPEAK MY OWN LANGUAGE
VERY WELL?
- ( speaks French badly )
- HUH?
- UH...
( speaks French badly )
- WHAT?
"TUNA SOMETHING,
SOMETHING MONAMIE"?
WHY IS HE TALKING ABOUT FISH?
HE'S JUST SPOUTING OFF
GIBBERISH.
AND ON TOP OF THAT, HE'S NOT
EVEN SAYING MY NAME RIGHT.
- ( speaks French badly )
- PLEASE STOP!
I DO NOT KNOW!
- UH--
- ( crying )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THIS IS SO HARD.
WHY DOESN'T ANYONE
UNDERSTAND ME?
IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M NOT TRYING.
WHAT IF--
WHAT IF THEY ALL HATE ME NOW?
( inaudible )
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
COME BACK HERE.
I WON'T TO GO HOME.
( crying )
- Minami:
NOTHING HAD CHANGED.
I STILL COULDN'T FOLLOW ALONG
IN CLASS.
I REALLY WANTED
SOMEONE TO TALK TO,
BUT THAT'S HARD TO DO WHEN
NO ONE KNOWS WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
IT WAS KIND OF A NIGHTMARE.
IT'S TRUE WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT FIRST IMPRESSIONS
LASTING FOREVER.
I PROVED THAT THE DAY
I SHOWED THEM
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO WRITE
MY OWN NAME.
- ( German accent )
WAIT.
I'M SURE I NEVER
CORRECTED THIS ONE MYSELF.
BUT WHO...
- SO CHECK IT OUT.
THE GUYS FROM AKEBONO JUNIOR
HIGH WANT TO PLAY BASKETBALL
FOR GRUB FROM
THE SCHOOL STORE.  YOU IN?
- HECK YEAH, I'M IN!
I HAVE, LIKE,
NOTHING FOR A FOOD BUDGET.
- I'M IN TOO.
- WOULD YOU MIND
IF I JOINED YOU GUYS?
PLAYING SOME BALL
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
WHEN DID THEY BECOME SO CLOSE?
- Hideyoshi: UH, I DON'T KNOW.
- Akihisa: I GOT THIS.
( speaks French badly )
AM I SAYING IT RIGHT?
- WHAT IS WITH HIM?
WHY DOES HE KEEP TALKING TO ME
IN GIBBERISH?
NOW HE IS JUST
MAKING FUN OF ME.
THE LEAST HE COULD DO IS
GET MY NAME RIGHT.
MINAMI, NOT MONAMI, JERK.
IF YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHO I AM,
WHY TRY SO HARD TO UPSET ME?
- ( speaks French badly )
TU NE VOUDRAIS--
- ( speaks German )
- YOU WANT TO SHAVE FUR
OFF A BEAST?
- I SAY...
- WHAT A "SHE-MAN" YOU ARE?
AS IN-- WAIT.
YOU'RE SAYING
YOU'RE A DUDE?!
OH, THAT'S COOL, I GUESS.
- THIS BOY IS
THE BIGGEST IDIOT ON EARTH!
- THERE WAS SOMETHING IN THERE
ABOUT YOU BEING A SHITTY GUY.
GUESS YOU PISSED HER OFF, MAN.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.  YOU THOUGHT A GIRL
WAS ACTUALLY TELLING YOU
SHE WAS A GUY,
AND DIDN'T EVEN QUESTION IT?
THAT'S HARSH, BRO.
- I AM SO SORRY, SHIMADA!
I DIDN'T MEAN IT,
AND IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE FACT THAT YOUR CHEST
IS FREAKISHLY FLAT
OR THAT MY ELBOWS ARE
BEING TORN OUT OF THEIR SOCKETS!
- I MAY NOT UNDERSTAND
EVERYTHING THEY'RE SAYING,
BUT I'M CERTAIN
I HEARD "FLAT-CHESTED."
WHAT DID I EVER DO TO HIM?
YOU ARE A VERY BIG SHIT MAN!
I HATE THIS.
I HATE IT HERE.
I WISH I NEVER MOVED.
- HEY, SHIMADA.
JUST WANTED TO SAY I DON'T
KNOW THAT IDIOT VERY WELL,
BUT I THINK
HE MIGHT BE ALL RIGHT.
AND I ALSO THINK
THAT YOU MIGHT BE FREAKING OUT
A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
- ME?  WHY?
- I KNOW HE ACTS WEIRD
WHEN HE TALKS TO YOU,
BUT WHAT HE'S SAYING IS NICE.
- SO THAT'S THE WORD
FOR "IDIOT."
THAT'LL BE USEFUL AROUND HERE.
( speaks French )
I CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
HE'S PROBABLY TRYING TO
CONFUSE ME SO I'LL LOOK STUPID.
AS SOON AS I FIND IT,
I'LL SAY SOMETHING
JUST AS RUDE BACK.
- ( inaudible )
- "TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS.
TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS..."
WHERE IS IT?
UGH, THIS IS MAKING
MY BRAIN HURT.
WHY CAN'T I FIND IT?
EVEN IF HE'S USING SLANG,
SOMETHING SHOULD'VE POPPED UP.
AND DOES HE REALLY NOT KNOW
MY NAME BY NOW
OR IS HE CALLING ME "MONAMI"
JUST TO BE ANNOYING?
WAIT A MINUTE.
- ( violin music playing )
- ( gasps )
HERE IT IS.
FRANCE.
"TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS
DEVENIR MON AMIE."
SO IT ISN'T IN JAPANESE.
I BET HE WAS TRYING TO LOOK UP
SOMETHING IN GERMAN,
BUT FOUND IT IN FRENCH
ON ACCIDENT.
WOW.
HE REALLY IS AN IDIOT.
- Minami:
AFTER I FIGURED THAT PART OUT,
I COULDN'T FIND
A FRENCH-GERMAN DICTIONARY
ANYWHERE IN THE LIBRARY.
I HAD TO TRANSLATE THE WHOLE
THING INTO ENGLISH FIRST
AND THEN BACK INTO GERMAN.
I HAD NO IDEA IF
I WAS SPELLING IT RIGHT
OR EVEN PRONOUNCING IT
WELL ENOUGH TO GUESS.
- ( German accent )
THERE.
"TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS"
IS SECOND PERSON.
IT SHOULD MEAN "COULD YOU."
"DEVENIR" IS "BECOME."
HE WAS SAYING "MON AMIE,"
NOT "MINAMI."
AND "MON AMIE"
MEANS "MY FRIEND."
SO IF I PUT IT ALL TOGETHER,
IT MEANS...
"COULD YOU BECOME MY FRIEND?"
- TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS
DEVENIR MON AMIE?
TU NE VOUDRAIS PAS
DEVENIR MON AMIE.
- HE HAD TO GO THROUGH ALL THIS
TO BE ABLE TO SAY IT.
HE LEARNED THE WRONG LANGUAGE
FROM A COUNTRY
HE'S NEVER BEEN TO.
HE DOESN'T EVEN
WORK THAT HARD
FOR THE CLASSES IN
HIS OWN LANGUAGE.
HE'S NOT THAT SMART...
BUT HE TRIED.
HE TRIED SO HARD.
COULD YOU BECOME MY--
MY FRIEND?!
OH, THAT IS SUCH A NICE WORDS!
I COULD.
GOOD MORNING, YOSHII!
HOW ARE YOU?
- UH, MORNING, SHIMADA.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
WHOA.  HI.
WHAT'S UP, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I WISH TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
- UH, 'KAY?
- WHAT A SHIT--
- WHAT'D I DO NOW?
I'M SO SORRY.
DID I DO SOMETHING
TO UPSET YOU AGAIN?
- NO, I AM NOT MAD!
HOW DO YOU SAY...
"YOU WERE NOT A SHIT PERSON."
YOU SEE...
I WAS.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara:
QUESTION NUMBER NINE:
WHAT DO YOU CALL THE ACTIONS
BY GROUPS THAT REACH OUT
TO POLITICIANS
IN ORDER TO INFLUENCE POLICIES?
- Minami: FLIRTING?
- WHO'S YOUR DADDY?
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME:
ME, ROMANCE
AND NEGOTIATION SKILLS.
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.