- Akihisa: ON A NIGHT
ILLUMINATED BY COUNTLESS STARS
AND A FLEETING CRESCENT MOON,
I WAS BEING PRESSURED BY
THE SUSPICIOUSLY SUPPORTIVE
GIRLS IN MY CLASS.
- AKI, CAN WE DO IT?
- AKIHISA, PLEASE.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE, CAN WE DO IT?
- I'M SORRY, I CAN'T.
- BUT WHY?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- YOU MEAN, YOU DON'T WANT TO?
- IT'S NOT THAT.
I JUST CAN'T.
- WELL, THEN IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU REALLY WANT,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO DO IT
WITH KOUTA INSTEAD.
- OKAY?  AKI?
- OKAY.  I'M COOL WITH THAT.
- AWESOME!  KOUTA, DID YOU
HEAR WHAT AKI JUST TOLD US?
YOU GET ONE MORE.
- AAH!
- Fukuhara:
THIS IS CALLED ISHI-DAKI.
IT'S A FORM OF TORTURE
USED IN THE EDO ERA.
- ( boys groaning, screaming )
- AFFAIRS WILL NOT
BE PERMITTED.
- NOW IT'S YOUR TURN
FOR MORE, AKIHISA.
- Akihisa:
NO!
- ( dog barking )
- Fukuhara: WOW, THE GIRLS
ARE KINDA BALLSY TONIGHT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara:
EARLIER THAT MORNING...
THINGS GOT A BIT STRANGE.
IT WAS THE DAY BEFORE
THEIR ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP.
AKIHISA RECEIVED
AN ANONYMOUS LETTER.
WITHIN IT WAS A MESSAGE--
A MESSAGE THAT WOULD BLOW
OUR LITTLE ANTI-HERO'S MIND.
- ( Akihisa's voice )
"DEAR AKIHISA,
I KNOW YOUR SECRET"?
WHY WOULD SOMEONE DO THIS TO ME?
- WHAT'S WRONG, AKIHISA?
YOU SEEM KINDA BUMMED OUT
THIS MORNING.
- HUH?  WHAT?!
NO, NOTHING'S WRONG.
- WHY ARE YOU ACTING WEIRD
THIS TIME?
AND WHAT'S BEHIND YOUR BACK?
- MY BACK?  WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- OKAY.  YOU MUST BE
HIDING A LOVE LETTER.
YEAH?
- WHY WOULD YOU EVER
SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
YOU KNOW HOW THESE GUYS GET.
- BESIDES THAT, WHO WOULD
GIVE YOU A LOVE LETTER?
TALK ABOUT RIDICULOUS.
- TALK ABOUT YOUR FACE!
PEOPLE SEND ME LETTERS.
TAKE TODAY--
- NEXT TIME YOU'RE DEAD.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
MISS MINAMI.
- NOW WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TELLING THE TRUTH FOR ONCE?
- ALL RIGHT! I WAS HIDING
A LETTER FROM YOU.  IT WAS BL--
WAIT, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TELL PEOPLE
WHEN YOU'RE GETTING BLACKMAILED.
THE BAD GUYS ALWAYS SAY
NOT TO ON TV.
- "BLA--" WHAT?
- WHAT "BLA--" WHAT?
- Fukuhara:
WHEN HUMANS ARE IN STRESS MODE,
THEIR SYNAPSES FIRE RANDOMLY,
CAUSING A SCATTERED
THOUGHT PATTERN.
THIS IS CALLED
A KALEIDOSCOPE OF MEMORIES.
- YES!  UH, BLACK COMPETITIVE
SWIMWEAR SOCIETY INVITATION
WAS WHAT I WAS HIDING.
- WHAT?
- Fukuhara: AKIHISA HAD
WATCHED A DOCUMENTARY CALLED,
"COMPETITIVE SWIMMER: 24-HOUR
CLOSE-UP" THE NIGHT BEFORE.
- OKAY, SO ARE YOU GONNA GO?
- MAYBE!  YES.  I DON'T KNOW...
I THINK THEY'RE COOL.
- ( sighs ) JEEZ.
- OH, CRAP. I'M GETTING CLOSE TO
THAT POINT OF NO RETURN THING.
- WHAT DO YOU FIND SO COOL
ABOUT COMPETITIVE SWIMMERS?
- HUH?  UH...
THINK, AKI.
WHAT MAKES THEM COOL?
I LIKE WHAT THEY WEAR.
PERFECT!  NOW I SOUND
LIKE A TOTAL WEIRDO!
- MINAMI, EVERYTHING
HE JUST SAID WAS A LIE.
- WHAT? THAT STUPID STORY
SOUNDED SO REAL,
I ALMOST BELIEVED HIM.
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME
THE TRUTH THIS TIME,
YOU'RE GONNA PAY.
SPIT IT OUT, JERKY!
- OKAY.  I MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN
A BLACKMAIL NOTE THIS MORNING.
- AH!  WELL, THAT'S A RELIEF.
- WHAT DOES THIS
"MIGHT BE A BLACKMAIL NOTE" SAY?
- OH.  "STOP TRYING TO GET
CLOSER TO THE GIRLS
WHO ARE ALWAYS AROUND YOU
OR ELSE."  THAT'S ALL.
- WHOA.  IF YOU ASK ME,
IT SOUNDS LIKE
THE BLACKMAILER
IS JEALOUS OF YOU.
- AND IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
THERE ARE ONLY TWO GIRLS
IN THIS CLASS.
HIMEJI AND HIDEYOSHI.
WHOEVER IT IS MUST NOT
LIKE ONE OF THEM.
- YOU DO REALIZE SHE
MOST LIKELY JUST LEFT
TO GO GET A METAL BAT, RIGHT?
- WHY?!  I THOUGHT THAT WAS
A GOOD GUESS.
- HOLD ON JUST A SECOND.
WHAT ARE YOU BEING
BLACKMAILED WITH ANYWAY?
- UH, I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
"IF YOU REFUSE
TO HEED MY WARNING,
I'LL RELEASE THESE PICTURES."
COOL, THERE'S PICTURES!
- HEY, THOSE ARE FROM THE LAST
SCHOOL FESTIVAL, AREN'T THEY?
- BUT WHO TOOK THESE?
SURELY THEY WON'T HAVE
ANYTHING CRAZIER THAN THIS.
IT'S TRUNKS, SO IT'S OKAY.
JUST TRUNKS!
- EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT
OVER THERE?
- YEAH, THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
THAT BAD IN THESE PICTURES.
I THINK.
NO!
DON'T LOOK AT IT!
I'M HIDEOUS!
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO ASHAMED!
- DUDE, YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
- IT CAN.
THAT KIND OF POWER
IS DANGEROUS.
WHAT EVIL VILLAIN
IS DOING THIS TO ME?
- YOU'RE JUST BEING DRAMATIC.
EVERYONE WEARS
A FRENCH MAID COSTUME
AT LEAST ONCE IN THEIR LIFE.
- GOOD MORNING, YOU GUYS.
LOVELY DAY, HUH?
HOW IS IT GOING?
- YOU KNOW,
SAME OL', SAME OL'.
- PERFECT TIMING.
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW
THOSE PICTURES TO HIMEJI,
SO SHE CAN PROVE
THEY'RE NOT WORTH
FREAKING OUT ABOUT.
- SHOW ME WHAT PICTURES?
- OKAY, WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU SAW A PICTURE OF AKI
DRESSED UP IN A MAID COSTUME?
- WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
I WOULD PROBABLY BUY A SCANNER.
- HUH?
- THAT WAY, I WOULD BE ABLE
TO DOWNLOAD THE IMAGE.
AND THEN SHARE AKIHISA'S CHARM
WITH THE WORLD WIDE WEB.
- DON'T JUMP, MAN!
IT'S NOT WORTH IT!
- LET GO OF ME! I HAVE
NO REASON TO LIVE ANYMORE.
- COME BACK INSIDE. LET'S GO
GET SOME ADVICE FROM KOUTA.
- OF COURSE!  THAT IS
AN AWESOME PLAN, HIDEYOSHI.
I WOULD EXPECT NOTHING LESS
FROM MY WIFE.
- I THINK YOU MEAN HUSBAND?
- I THINK THEY'RE BOTH WRONG
IN SO VERY MANY WAYS.
- ( laughing )
- Aki: OH, CRAP.
THERE YOU ARE.
I HAVE A QUESTION
FOR YOU, KOUTA.
- YEAH, WELL,
GET IN LINE, BUDDY.
I WAS HERE FIRST.
- YOU NEED ADVICE TOO?
- APPARENTLY, YUUJI
HAS A WEDDING SOON.
- YEAH, WE ALL KNOW ABOUT THAT.
WHAT'S HE GONNA DO?
I HAVE BIGGER PROBLEMS.
PEOPLE ARE ABOUT TO THINK
I'M A SICKO FREAK WHO ENJOYS
DRESSING UP LIKE A GIRL!
- SO WHAT?!  PEOPLE ALREADY KNOW
YOU'RE A SICKO FREAK.
- SHUT UP AND GO BACK
TO YOUR WIFE.
GETTING MARRIED
HAS MADE YOU SUCK!
- LIKE THE WORDS OF A PERVERT
ARE GONNA HURT ME?
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK TO WEARING
YOUR BIG SISTER'S CLOTHES?
- ( both growling )
( crying )
- YOU GUYS ARE SO SENSITIVE.
YOU JUST CAN'T TAKE TRASH TALK.
- SO BACK TO ME... I MANAGED
TO GET THIS AWAY FROM SHOUKO.
IF I WIN THE TOURNAMENT,
I'M GONNA PROPOSE TO YOU.
I LOVE YOU, SHOUKO!
- HUH?
- Fukuhara: THESE ARE THE
WORDS AKIHISA AND HIDEYOSHI
FABRICATED AT THE FUMIZUKI
ACADEMY SCHOOL FESTIVAL.
- ( laughs nervously )
THAT SHOUKO CRACKS ME UP.
WHO WOULD HAVE FIGURED SHE'D
WANT THOSE WORDS RECORDED?
- I WOULD!
SHE'S GONNA PLAY IT FOR HER DAD
AS PROOF OF OUR ENGAGEMENT.
- OH.
- SHE COULDN'T DO THIS HERSELF.
SHE'S AN IDIOT WHEN IT COMES
TO TECHNICAL STUFF.
WHICH MEANS THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOMEONE ELSE BEHIND THIS.
- WHAT DID YOU
WANNA TALK ABOUT, AKI?
- I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER WAY
TO SAY THIS.
AN UNDERWEAR PICTURE OF ME
IN A MAID'S COSTUME
IS ABOUT TO HIT THE INTERNET
BIG TIME!
- HMM?  HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
- WELL, IT'S KINDA LIKE THIS.
BLAH BLAH BLAH.
BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH.
- YEAH YEAH YEAH.
SO WHERE'S THE PICTURE?
- OH, YEAH, IT'S RIGHT HERE.
- NO!
- NO WHAT?!
- ( sighs )
THE ANGLE IN THAT PIC
IS BETTER THAN THE ONE I TOOK.
- AAH!
THERE'S A TRAITOR IN OUR MIDST.
- OH, STOP FREAKING OUT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GIVING 'EM
AWAY FOR FREE.
- SO WHAT?!
YOU MAKE MONEY OFF OF ME?
- I SEE.  IT APPEARS THAT
AKI'S IN THE SAME BOAT I AM.
- YES, YOU'RE BOTH VICTIMS
OF BLACKMAIL, WIRETAPPING,
AND SURVEILLANCE PHOTOS.
- KOUTA?
I'D LIKE FOR YOU TO INVESTIGATE.
AS A REWARD, I'LL BRING
SOME DIRTY MAGAZINES
THAT YOU CAN BORROW.
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- AND I'LL LET YOU HAVE
HALF OF MY NAUGHTY TREASURE
COLLECTION.
- THIS IS EXTREMELY
NOT A PROBLEM.
- ( bell tolls )
- SO THAT'S ABOUT
WHAT YOU CAN EXPECT
FROM ACADEMIC TRAINING CAMP.
- COOL!
WE GET TO GO TO THE UZUKI
HIGHLANDS THIS YEAR.
- WOW, THAT'S KINDA SWANKY
FOR CAMP.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT IT!
- AND FOR THE LAST TIME,
THERE ARE DIFFERENT
MEETING PLACES PER CLASS,
SO DON'T SCREW IT UP.
- CLASS "A" IS PROBABLY
GONNA GO BY A LIMOUSINE BUS
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- TOTALLY.
AND CLASS "F" WILL GET STUCK
WITH A MICRO-BUS.
- SPARE SEATS ARE STANDING UP.
NO, PROBABLY IN THE TRUNK
OR IN A BIKE RACK.
- CLASS "F" HAS THE DISTINCTION
OF MEETING UP AT THE CAMPSITE.
- WHAT?!  WE DON'T EVEN
GET TRANSPORTATION?!
- Fukuhara:
LIFE JUST ISN'T FAIR.
- NUH-UH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I SWEAR!
ARE WE THERE YET?
( snoring )
- I'M BORED.
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU READING,
MINAMI?
- JUST A PERSONALITY QUIZ.
- OOH, THAT SOUNDS WAY BETTER
THAN DOING NOTHING!
ASK ME SOME QUESTIONS.
- OH, WHY NOT?  LET'S SEE...
"AMONG FRIENDS
OF THE OPPOSITE SEX,
WHO DO ASSOCIATE WITH
THE FOLLOWING COLORS?
NUMBER ONE: GREEN;
NUMBER TWO: ORANGE;
NUMBER THREE: BLUE."
- WITH GREEN ORANGE
AND BLUE, OKAY.
UH, WELL,
ORANGE IS HIDEYOSHI,
BLUE IS HIMEJI.
GREEN CAN BE MINAMI.
- COULD YOU PLEASE EXPLAIN
WHY EXACTLY YOU ASSIGNED
GREEN TO ME
AND BLUE TO MIZUKI?
- UH.  IF I TELL HER
IT'S BECAUSE
I SAW HER WEARING
GREEN PANTIES BEFORE,
I'M GUESSING
SHE'S GONNA GET MAD.
- I'M NOT GONNA GET MAD.
SO YOU CAN TELL THE TRUTH.
- BECAUSE I SAW YOU WEARING
GREEN PANTIES BEFORE.
- HEY, YUUJI, CAN YOU OPEN
THE WINDOW, PLEASE?
- SURE THING.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE YOU GONNA THROW ME
OUT OF THE WINDOW?
- LET'S SEE.
GREEN IS YOUR FRIEND,
ORANGE IS YOUR ENERGY SOURCE
AND BLUE--
- EXCUSE ME!
THAT'S MY BOOK.
- HEY, AKI,
SHE WAS ASKING ABOUT FRIENDS
OF THE OPPOSITE SEX, RIGHT?
WHO WAS ORANGE AGAIN?
- ORANGE WAS YOU.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY
BECAUSE I'M KINDA FLATTERED.
- WOW, I WANNA KNOW TOO.
WHAT'S IT SUPPOSED TO MEAN
WHEN SOMEONE ASSOCIATES YOU
WITH THE COLOR BLUE?
- ( groans )
QUESTION TWO!
- LOOKS LIKE THAT'S
YOUR ANSWER, HIMEJI.
- BETWEEN THE NUMERALS
ONE AND TEN,
STATE THE FIRST TWO NUMBERS
YOU THINK OF,
AND TELL ME IN THE SPECIFIC
ORDER YOU THOUGHT OF THEM.
- HMM, FIVE AND SIX, I GUESS.
- I'M GOING WITH TWO AND SEVEN.
- I THINK IT'S ONE AND FOUR
FOR ME.
- I SUPPOSE I'LL SAY
THREE AND NINE.
- "THE FIRST NUMBER YOU STATED
MOST LIKELY INDICATES
THE WAY YOU NORMALLY PRESENT
YOURSELF TO OTHER PEOPLE."
- YUUJI'S FIVE MEANS
HE'S COOL AND CYNICAL.
- HIDEYOSHI'S TWO MEANS
CALM AND COMMON SENSE.
- AKI'S ONE MEANS
HE SHOULD DIE.
- MIZUKI'S THREE MEANS
SHE'S GENTLE AND CAREFUL.
- WAIT.  DID YOU JUST SAY
MINE MEANS I NEED TO DIE?
- "THE SECOND NUMBER YOU STATED
MOST LIKELY REPRESENTS
YOUR TRUE SELF THAT
YOU DON'T NORMALLY REVEAL
TO OTHER PEOPLE."
YUUJI'S SIX MEANS
FAIRNESS AND KINDNESS.
HIDEYOSHI'S SEVEN MEANS
STRONG, FEMININE CHARMS.
AKI'S FOUR MEANS
HE SHOULD DIE TRAGICALLY.
MIZUKI'S NINE MEANS
A STRONG WILL.
- WAIT.  NOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO DIE TRAGICALLY?
- ( groaning )
- HEY, KOUTA'S WAKING UP.
- FINALLY.
GOOD MORNING, SUNSHINE.
- MY STOMACH IS EATING ITSELF.
- OH, YEAH,
I'M KINDA HUNGRY TOO.
- SOUNDS LIKE
IT'S LUNCHTIME, BABY.
- UM, ACTUALLY, YOU GUYS
ARE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO TRY SOME OF MY LUNCH.
I MADE IT ALL BY MYSELF.
- Boys: I'M GOOD!
- SORRY.
I MADE MY LUNCH TOO.
AND I DON'T WANT IT
TO GO TO WASTE.
- YEAH, I DID THE EXACT SAME
THING THAT YUUJI JUST SAID.
- ME TOO.  WEIRD.
- NO WORRIES,
THOUGH, HIMEJI.
I'M SURE AKI'S
JUST DYING TO TRY SOME.
- YOU'D THINK,
BUT I BROUGHT MYSELF A SANDWICH.
- ( gobbles )
I'M SO SORRY, MAN.
MY HAND TOTALLY SLIPPED.
- ( laughs nervously )
BE CAREFUL THERE, YUUJI.
MY HAND CAN SLIP TOO!
- FOR YOUR SAKE THEN,
I'LL JUST KEEP
HOLDING IT LIKE THIS,
SO THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
- ( both growling )
- JEEZ, WHY ARE YOU GUYS
ACTING SO WEIRD?
SERIOUSLY.
AKI, YOU WANNA TRY THESE?
- YES!  THEY LOOK SUPER YUMMY!
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
HAVE AS MANY AS YOU WANT.
- YES, MINAMI,
YOU'RE THE BEST!
- OH, YEAH, AKI...
I SHOULD MENTION
SOMETHING FIRST.
I'M NOT SURE WHICH,
BUT A FEW OF THOSE...
ARE LOADED WITH HOT MUSTARD.
- AAH!  ARE YOU
A FRICKIN' IDIOT?!
MY MOUTH FEELS LIKE
IT'S ON FIRE.
- AKIHISA, THIS MIGHT BE
THE BEST THING FOR YOU.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
- GOOD POINT.
I MIGHT BE OKAY SINCE MY TASTE
BUDS WERE JUST DESTROYED.
- HAVE SOME OF MINE.
COME ON,
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
- HECK YEAH.
GREAT, THANK YOU.
- Yuuji:
CHARGE TO 300-- CLEAR!
- ( electricity zapping )
- ( beeping )
- ( Aki murmuring )
HEY, WHERE ARE WE?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- YOU ALMOST DIED--
AS IN, YOU STARTED
REPENTING SINS FROM
A FORMER LIFE ALMOST DIED.
- SERIOUSLY?
- YEAH, BUT YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
WHILE YOU WERE HOVERING
BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH,
WE FINALLY MADE IT TO
TRAINING CAMP.
- THIS IS OUR ROOM.
THEY ASSIGNED IT
TO ALL FOUR OF US.
- ALL RIGHT, NOW THAT
YOU'RE AWAKE,
IT'S TIME TO GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY BUSINESS?
- OPERATION: FIND THE CULPRIT,
A.K.A.,
PHOTOGRAPHER/WIRETAPPER.
- I'VE ALREADY MANAGED
TO DIG UP SOME INTEL.
- WOW, THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
- I FOUND REMNANTS OF DEVICES.
I BELIEVE THEY WERE USED
BY THE PERPETRATOR.
BASED ON THEIR M.O. AND
THE KIND OF EQUIPMENT THEY USED
IN THEIR SURVEILLANCE,
MY CONCLUSION IS THAT
BOTH HEINOUS CRIMES WERE
COMMITTED BY THE SAME PERSON.
- AWESOME.
SO, WHO DID IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- YEAH, I GUESS NOT.
IT'D BE KINDA HARD
TO FIGURE OUT THAT FAST.
- ALL I'VE DISCOVERED
IS THAT THE CULPRIT
IS A FEMALE STUDENT
WHO HAS A BURN
ON HER BUTT.
- WHAT THE CRAP
DID YOU INVESTIGATE?
- I SET UP A SMALL CAMERA
ON THE SCHOOL GROUNDS.
THEN ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS WATCH.
- HEY, LOOK.
- THIS IS FROM INSIDE
THE GIRLS' LOCKER ROOM.
- WHY'S IT CENSORED?
- IF YOU WANNA SEE,
YOU GOTTA PAY.
- WE'RE FRIENDS, AREN'T WE?
- WAIT A FREAKIN' MINUTE.
IT'S SHOUKO.
WHO IS SHE MESSAGING
ON HER PHONE?
- I'M NOT SURE.
LET'S BLOW IT UP.
- Hideyoshi:
HERE WE GO.
IT'S AN ORDER FORM.
"I'D LIKE TO HAVE ANOTHER ONE
OF YUUJI'S MARRIAGE PROPOSALS."
SHE SENT IT.
- ( grumbles )
STUPID SHOUKO!
- ( cellphone rings )
- LOOK, SHE'S ALREADY
GOT A REPLY.
"THANK YOU.
I'LL GIVE YOU A DISCOUNT
SINCE THIS IS
YOUR SECOND ORDER.
TRAINING CAMP STARTS TOMORROW,
SO I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU
NEXT MONDAY."
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
I WAS SAVED BY TRAINING CAMP?
- CHECK IT OUT.
THERE'S OTHER ONES TOO.
CRAP.
- DUDE, YOU'RE IN THERE!
- I SHOULD HAVE JUMPED OUT THAT
WINDOW WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE!
- SO, I GUESS WE CAN CONFIRM
IT'S THE SAME CULPRIT
FOR REAL NOW.
- I THINK YOU'LL WANT
TO SEE THIS.
- Yuuji:
SHE'S WRITING BACK.
- "ALL YOUR PICTURES ARE
WONDERFUL,
BUT IT'LL BE A PROBLEM
IF THEY FIND OUT."
- ( cellphone rings )
- HOW CAN ANYONE
TYPE THAT FAST?!
- "DON'T TELL ANYONE,
BUT MY MOM TOTALLY FOUND OUT
WHAT I WAS DOING THE OTHER DAY
AND GOT ALL BENT OUT OF SHAPE.
WHAT KIND OF MOM
USES MOXIBUSTION
AS A CLEANSING AND BURNS
HER DAUGHTER'S BUTT?
SHE SAID IT WAS AN ACCIDENT,
BUT I KNOW THE TRUTH."
- AND THAT'S ALL THAT
I'VE GOT SO FAR.
- INTERESTING.
WE CAN ASSUME BY DAUGHTER,
THE CULPRIT MUST BE A GIRL
OR HIDEYOSHI.
- ( Hideyoshi sighs )
- SO WE'RE LOOKING FOR A CHICK
WITH A BURNT BOOTY.
- WE CAN'T JUST FLIP UP
ALL THE GIRLS' SKIRTS.
- EVEN IF WE HAD
AN INFRARED CAMERA,
WE WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO MAKE OUT A BURN MARK.
- I KNOW!
IT'S ALMOST BATH TIME,
SO WE CAN JUST
HAVE HIDEYOSHI GO LOOK.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
I COULD GO LOOK.
I DON'T TAKE BATHS WITH GIRLS.
I'M A GUY.
- AKIHISA, READ
THE TRAINING CAMP GUIDEBOOK.
- HMM.
"THE BATHING TIMES FOR EACH
CLASS ARE AS FOLLOWS"...
AAH!
THEY'VE GIVEN HIDEYOSHI
A PRIVATE BATH TIME!
- WHY DO THEY ALWAYS DO THAT?
- DON'T MOVE, IDIOTS!
ALL OF YOU, PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD
AND LIE FACEDOWN
ON THE GROUND.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WE SAID PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD
AND LIE FACEDOWN ON
THE GROUND!
- COME WITH ME.
WE DON'T HATE YOU.
- HEY!
- WHAT ARE YOU CHICKS
SO PISSED ABOUT?
- DON'T ACT ALL INNOCENT.
WE KNOW YOU'RE THE CULPRITS!
- I'M SORRY, WHAT?
- RECOGNIZE THIS?!
WE FOUND YOUR SECRET CAMERA
HIDDEN IN THE GIRLS'
CHANGING ROOM.
- SOMEONE PUT A HIDDEN CAMERA
IN THERE?
WHO WOULD DO SUCH A THING?!
- YOU THREE WOULD DO
SUCH A THING.
YOU'RE THE CREEPIEST CREEPS
IN THE SCHOOL.
- NOT TRUE!  PEEKING
AND SETTING UP HIDDEN CAMERAS?
THEY WOULDN'T DARE!
'KAY, THEY MIGHT DARE.
- Both: WHAT?!
- SAY YOU DIDN'T DO IT, AKIHISA!
YOU WOULD NEVER EVER DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, WOULD YOU?
- THEY'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG,
DON'T THEY, AKI?
DON'T WORRY,
WE BELIEVE IN YOU.
- IF YOU BELIEVE IN ME...
THEN WHY DO YOU HAVE TORTURE
EQUIPMENT WITH YOU?
- HOW CAN YOU BE SO MEAN,
AKIHISA?
OF ALL THE TIMES
YOU COULD HAVE PEEKED ON ME,
YOU HAD TO GO AND DO IT
RIGHT AFTER I HAD A HUGE MEAL?
I-- I WAS BLOATED.
I'M NORMALLY WAY SKINNIER!
- THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE UPSET ABOUT?!
- YEAH, AND FOR THE RECORD,
MY TA-TAS ARE NORMALLY BIGGER
THAN THEY ARE TODAY.
- LYING DOESN'T HELP ANYTHING,
MINAMI.
- ( groans )
LADIES, ATTACK THEM AT WILL!
- ( girls grunting )
- I TAKE IT BACK.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT, I SWEAR!
MY SPLEEN.
HEY!
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE!
OOH-HOO.
- BAD... BOY.
- ( groaning )
- OH, NO!
IT'S TOO LATE.
GUYS!
WE'RE ALL DEAD!
- IT'S TIME, AKIHISA.
- WE'RE GOING TO
TEACH YOU A LESSON.
- ( screams )
- WELL, THAT WASN'T THE NICEST
OF ACCUSATIONS, WAS IT?
I STILL CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHY THEY TREATED ME
LIKE A VICTIM, THOUGH.
- THEY OVERREACTED TO
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
WE HADN'T EVEN
PEEKED ON THEM YET.
- THEIR CAMERA WASN'T
ONE OF MINE, BY THE WAY.
- SHE CRUSHED THAT THING
WITH HER BARE HAND.
- IF THEY'RE GONNA BE
LIKE THAT, THEN WHO CARES?
- YOUR WORDS DON'T MAKE SENSE.
- THEY'VE ALREADY MADE
US DO THE TIME,
SO WE MIGHT AS WELL
COMMIT THE CRIME.
- YOU DON'T MEAN--
- HELL YEAH!
I'M GONNA PEEK ON THE GIRLS
TAKING BATHS FOR REAL.
- YUUJI, IF YOU WANNA SEE
SHOUKO NAKED,
I'M SURE ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS ASK HER.
- THAT'S NOT
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
WOULD YOU SHUT UP?
I DON'T WANNA SEE HER NAKED.
- THIS ISN'T ABOUT SHOUKO.
IT'S ABOUT FINDING
THE BOOTY BURN MARK CULPRIT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AT FIRST I THOUGHT PEEKING ON
THEM WAS CROSSING THE LINE,
BUT IF THEY'RE GONNA
BE LIKE THAT,
THEN I SAY SCREW THE LINE!
I'M GONNA LOOK AT
EVERY GIRL'S BUTT UNTIL
I FIND ONE WITH A BURN ON IT!
- I RECOGNIZE THAT CAMERA
AND MICROPHONE.
THEY'RE THE SAME ONES
USED BY THE BLACKMAILER.
- GET OUTTA TOWN!
- SO THE BURNT BUTT GIRL WHO'S
BLACKMAILING YUUJI AND ME
IS THE SAME PERSON
WHO WAS PEEKING ON THE
GIRLS' CHANGING ROOM
EVEN THOUGH THEY
THOUGHT IT WAS US.
- THERE'S NO REASON TO HESITATE.
SHE SET US UP.
- OKAY, I'M REALLY CONFUSED.
- THEIR BATHING TIME
IS IN 30 MINUTES.
THEY'RE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THAT DOOR.
- WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
LET'S GET IN THERE, BOYS!
- ( all shouting )
- STOP IMMEDIATELY!
NOW COME ON, YOU KNOW
YOU CAN'T GO IN THERE, GUYS.
- ISN'T THAT
THE CHEMISTRY TEACHER?
- WHO CARES?
JUST KNOCK HIM DOWN.
- I'D REALLY RATHER YOU DIDN'T.
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR!
SUMMON!
- NO WAY!
- AH, TERRIFIC, THIS IS NEW.
- Fukuhara: LIKE PROBATIONARY
STUDENTS' AVATARS,
THE TEACHERS' AVATARS
ARE ALSO CAPABLE
OF PHYSICAL INTERFERENCE.
- WHATEVER, DUDE.
WE'RE GONNA CRUSH YOU RIGHT
ALONG WITH YOUR AVATAR.
- I'LL JUST KEEP RUNNING.
- NO, WAIT.
BEFORE YOU GO,
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME WHAT
YOUR CHEMISTRY SCORE WAS.
- IF I HAD JUST ONE MORE POINT
ON MY TEST,
JUST ONE MORE POINT...
- YEAH, WHAT WOULD IT BE?
- IT'D BE A TWO.
- GOOD TO KNOW.
KEEP RUNNING.
- IT'LL BE HARD TO WIN
IF YOU HAVE TO FIGHT HIM ALONE.
I'LL STAY AND HELP YOU OUT.
- YOU'RE THE MAN, HIDEYOSHI.
- Both: SUMMON!
- ( Avatars grunting )
- WELL, KOUTA, MY MAN,
LOOKS LIKE IT'S UP TO US--
HEY, HE'S ALREADY GONE!
- I DON'T THINK SO, KID.
- WELL, IF IT ISN'T
MR. OOSHIMA,
HEALTH AND P.E. TEACHER.
- GIVE IT UP ALREADY, TSUCHIYA.
- NO, YOU GIVE IT UP.
THIS ISN'T NORMAL PEEKING.
- SO WHAT IS IT?
- HEALTH AND P.E.
PRACTICAL TRAINING.
- SUMMON!
KEEP GOING, AKI.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE.
- GOOD LUCK, KOUTA.
NOW IT'S ALL UP TO ME!
I'LL MAKE IT.
FOR THE GUYS!
( gasps )
NO...
IT'S IRON MAN.
- PATHETIC.
ARE YOU BOYS EVER GONNA LEARN
HOW TO STAY OUT OF TROUBLE?
- PROBABLY NOT. BUT I DON'T
HAVE TIME TO TALK ABOUT IT!
SUMMON!
- ( grunting )
- WAIT, YOU DIDN'T SUMMON
YOUR AVATAR, MR. NISHIMURA.
- IT'S A LONG STORY, BUT I
DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE A SCORE.
- WELL, ISN'T THAT FANCY.
ALL RIGHTY THEN...
GET READY!
DIE, IRON MAN!
- ( grunts )
- WHAT?!
- YOSHII, I SHOULD REVOKE
YOUR SUMMONING PRIVILEGES,
BUT I WON'T.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY?
- MAYBE.
- I LIKE THAT YOU'RE
A PROBATIONARY STUDENT.
'CAUSE AS LONG AS
IT'S JUST AN AVATAR,
I DON'T HAVE TO FEEL BAD
ABOUT DOING THIS.
CLENCH YOUR TEETH, KIDDO!
- ( Avatar screams )
- ( both scream )
- PRESUMPTUOUS IDIOTS
TAKE A REMEDIAL CLASS.
THAT'S YOU THREE, BY THE WAY.
- ( all groaning )
- THUS THE FIRST DAY OF
TRAINING CAMP COMES TO AN END.
AKIHISA AND HIS FRIENDS
HAVE YET TO BE CLEARED
OF THE ACCUSATIONS
AGAINST THEM.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT? WILL THE
EVER FIND THE BLACKMAILER?
( flatly )
BUM BUM BUM.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuuji:
BAKA AND TEST!
- I'M SO RELAXED.
I'M LIKE A PUDDLE.
- YEAH, I ALWAYS FEEL LIKE THAT
AFTER A LONG BATH.
- ( beeps )
- Fukuhara:
QUESTION SIX--
"HISTORY REPEATS ITSELF."
PROVIDE AN EXAMPLE
OF THIS ADAGE.
- Hideyoshi:
REINCARNATION?
- YOU GONNA BE IN CLASS "F"
IN YOUR NEXT LIFE TOO?
- Akihisa: NEXT EPISODE: ME,
PEEKING AND GUYS' FRIENDSHIP!
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.