- ( yawning )
HIDEYOSHI, I'VE GOT REMEDIAL--
HUH?
- UH.
- HMM...
- YOU OKAY?
UH, WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- IT'S JUST THAT...
THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT
ABOUT YOU TODAY.
- WHAT?  THERE IS?
WEIRD.
I MEAN, I'M...
EXACTLY THE SAME AS ALWAYS.
I'M THE SAME HEIGHT,
AREN'T I?
AND I'VE GOT THE SAME FACE.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM,
DUDE, MAN, BRO?
- I'M NOT SURE WHY,
BUT YOU DON'T SEEM AS GIRLISH
AND CUTE AS USUAL.
- AAH!
( growls )
- HMM?
- ( giggles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SO, TELL ME,
MS. TAKAHASHI.
TELL ME YOU'VE GOT
SOME PROGRESS TO REPORT.
- WELL, PRINCIPAL,
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT
YUUKO KINOSHITA FROM CLASS "A"?
SHE'S ONE OF OUR
BRIGHTEST STUDENTS
AND QUITE OUTGOING.
- GO ON.
- HER TWIN BROTHER HIDEYOSHI
MANAGES THE LOCAL OPERA
FROM TIME TO TIME,
EVEN THOUGH HE'S A CLASS "F"
STUDENT.
SO IT'S PROBABLY SAFE
TO ASSUME
THAT YUUKO IS
A TALENTED SINGER AS WELL.
- GOOD.  IT'S NICE TO KNOW
THAT WE HAVE AT LEAST
ONE GENUINELY MULTI-TALENTED
STUDENT AT THIS SCHOOL.
- INDEED. YOU COULD PRETTY
MUCH CREATE A CHECKLIST
FOR THE MODEL STUDENT
PATTERNED AFTER HER--
OUTGOING, COURTEOUS,
INTELLIGENT, GOOD-LOOKING,
TALENTED.
- ( sighs )
LIFE WOULD BE POINTLESS
WITHOUT HOT BOYS.
ESPECIALLY THE SCENE
WHERE YUUICHI PINS SHINJI
TO THE GROUND.
WAIT!
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS NOW!
- I'M HOME.
WHAT'S UP, SIS?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
OR ARE YOU JUST
FINALLY SICK OF
YOUR FAVORITE GAY BOOK?
- ( growls )
WE'VE GOT LIKE THE SAME
GENETIC STRUCTURE, RIGHT?
SO HOW COME YOU CAN DO THINGS
THAT I CAN'T?
- WHAT THE CRAP
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- TODAY IN CLASS,
MS. TAKAHASHI PICKED ME
OF ALL PEOPLE
TO PERFORM THE SCHOOL SONG
IN A NEW PROMOTIONAL VIDEO
FOR THE ACADEMY.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU'RE LIKE THE MOST
TONE-DEAF PERSON
I'VE EVER MET
IN MY LIFE!
AND YOU HAVE NO SENSE
OF RHYTHM AT ALL.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU? IT'S
LIKE YOU WANNA GET PUNCHED.
- IF YOU'RE SO WORRIED
ABOUT IT,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TELL THEM NO?
- ABSOLUTELY NOT!
I HAVE TO PROTECT MY IMAGE
AS AN HONOR STUDENT
WHO ROCKS AT EVERYTHING.
- THAT'S A PRETTY HARDCORE CASE
OF VANITY.
- ( cheers, applause )
- DON'T ACT LIKE IT
DOESN'T RUN IN THE FAMILY.
YOU JUST ACT OUT YOUR ROLES
ON THE STAGE.
WHILE I SPEND EVERY DAY
OF MY LIFE
ACTING OUT THE ROLE
OF A PERFECT STUDENT.
- HMM.  WELL,
WHEN YOU SAY IT LIKE THAT,
I GUESS WE AREN'T REALLY
ALL THAT DIFFERENT.
- OF COURSE WE AREN'T.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SAYING IT OUT LOUD,
BUT THE TWO OF US ARE...
IDENTICAL!
- UH...
- ( grunting )
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SIS?
- I'M THINKING.
YOU'RE GOOD
AT IMPRESSIONS, CORRECT?
- IF YOU'RE REFERRING TO
MY SKILLS AS A THESPIAN,
THEN-- WAIT A MINUTE!
- COME ON, BROTHER.
DON'T YOU WANT TO HELP YOUR
SISTER OUT OF A BAD SITUATION?
AS A FAVOR?
- A FAVOR?!
HOW IS IT A FAVOR
IF YOU'RE THREATENING MY LIFE?!
I CANNOT BELIEVE I LET YOU TALK
ME INTO DOING THIS, YUUKO.
- I'M GOING TO
YOUR IDIOT CLASS FOR YOU,
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM,
GIRLY MAN?
- FOR ONE, WHAT IF THE PEOPLE IN
MY CLASS FIGURE IT OUT?
- WHO CARES IF THEY DO?
- UM, ME?
COME ON, IT'S BAD ENOUGH
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL IS ALREADY
CONVINCED I'M A GIRL.
- THEN IT SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE THEY'LL THINK
EVERYTHING
IS PERFECTLY NORMAL.
HERE.
PIN THIS ON YOUR SHIRT.
- WHY, WHAT IS THAT THING?
- IT'S JUST A HIDDEN MICROPHONE.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
I CAN KEEP TABS
ON HOW EVERYTHING IS GOING.
- SERIOUSLY?
WHERE DID YOU EVEN GET
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
- FROM SOMEONE IN YOUR CLASS.
- HELLO, NEW PICTURES.
- THIS DISASTER OF A ROOM
IS THE EQUIVALENT
OF A SINKING SHIP.
- ( crashes )
- ( grunts )
- SUGAWA'S TRYING TO RUN!
- HE VIOLATED OUR CONTRACT BY
APPROACHING A FEMALE!
HE'S A TRAITOR!
- CAPTURE THE TRAITOR!
- OH--
- ( laughter )
- ( murmurs )
- OH, HIDEYOSHI.
I HEARD WE'RE
DOING WORKSHEETS TODAY.
- AH, YOU DON'T SAY.
- YOU HEAR ABOUT
THE JACKASS MOVE SUGAWA MADE?
- URGENT REPORT!
WE'VE GOT BREAKING NEWS!
WE HAVE NEW INFO ON THE GIRL
SUGAWA APPROACHED!
SHE'S NOT INTERESTED IN HIM!
IN FACT, ALL SHE WOULD SAY TO
HIM IS "TELL ME ABOUT AKI"!
I REPEAT: SHE ONLY WANTED TO
TALK ABOUT AKI!
- LATER!
- GRAB HIM!
- ( clamoring )
- THE FEMALE WAS INTERESTED
IN AKI!
- ( sighs )
IT'S LIKE A PLAGUE OF IDIOTS.
OH, YEAH.
THAT REMINDS ME,
I BETTER CHECK IN.
- ( static )
- THANKS, YUUKO.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- WHO IS THAT?  KUBO?
- IT'S JUST GOOD TO KNOW
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
- Hideyoshi: AWW, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO THANK ME.
- NOT THE ONLY ONE?
WHAT ARE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
- WELL, I NEVER IMAGINED
I'D FIND A CLASSMATE
WHO SHARED
THE SAME FEELINGS.
AND I'M KINDA SURPRISED
IT'S YOU.
HAVE YOU ALWAYS BEEN INTERESTED
IN HOMOSEXUALITY?
- ( gasps )
( pants )
- UH, HIDEYOSHI.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- SIS, COME WITH ME!
YOU AND I NEED TO TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- WHAT?!  HEY, SIS--
I MEAN, HIDEYOSHI!
- SO, HIDEYOSHI...
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TELLING ME EXACTLY WHAT
YOU AND KUBO WERE
TALKING ABOUT BACK THERE?
- IT WAS JUST
CASUAL SMALL TALK.
- HA!  SMALL TALK
THAT MADE ME SOUND
LIKE AN AFICIONADO
OF ALL THINGS GAY!
- WELL, YEAH.
YOU READ ALL THOSE BOOKS--
- WHAT?!
HOW STUPID ARE YOU?!
THAT IS TOTALLY NOT
THE SAME THING!
WHAT YOU TOLD KUBO IN THERE
MAKES IT SOUND LIKE
I'VE GOT THE HOTS
FOR OTHER GIRLS, YOU IDIOT.
- NO, I SWEAR THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
- AND I SWEAR, IF YOU CAUSE ONE
MORE MISUNDERSTANDING...
- OKAY!
MESSAGE RECEIVED!
- MESSAGE RECEIVED, HUH?
WE'LL SEE.
- Shouko:
YUUKO, MAY WE SPEAK?
- Hideyoshi:
SURE, WHAT'S UP?
- SHOUKO?
ALL RIGHT, HIDEYOSHI.
YOUR LIFE IS ON THE LINE HERE.
- Shouko: YOUR SKIRT--
IT'S FLIPPED UP IN BACK.
- WHAT?  THAT MORON!
- THANKS FOR TELLING ME, SHOUKO.
IT'S COOL, NOT A BIG DEAL.
- BUT... YOUR SKIRT.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- IT IS?
- I'VE ACTUALLY GOT
SOMETHING ON
BENEATH IT TODAY,
SO IT'S ALL GOOD.
- WE NEED TO TALK, SIS!
'KAY...
NOW WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
- THAT CAME OUT ALL WRONG.
WHAT I WAS TRYING TO EXPLAIN
TO HER IS IT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I'M WEARING LEGGINGS.
- IS THAT SO?!
WELL, YOU MADE IT
OUT TO SOUND LIKE
I DON'T NORMALLY
WEAR PANTIES!
- WELL, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT,
SO CALM DOWN.
- THAT'S NO EXCUSE!
DON'T SAY DUMB THINGS
AND FIX YOUR SKIRT!
- I'LL TRY.
IT'S JUST THAT YOUR SKIRT IS
A LITTLE TOO BIG ON ME
AROUND THE WAIST.
OKAY!  NO MORE MALFUNCTIONS
AND I WON'T SAY ANYTHING DUMB.
- LAST CHANCE.
- UM, HI, YUUKO.
- WHO'S THIS GUY?
- MY NAME IS KOUJI YOKOMIZO.
- KOUJI YOKOMIZO?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
- I-- I LOVE YOU!
WILL YOU PLEASE
GO OUT WITH ME?!
- HE LOVES ME?!
WHAT DO I DO?
I MEAN, I'M FLATTERED,
BUT STILL--
- Hideyoshi:
THANK YOU, KOUJI.
BUT YOU'RE JUST NOT MY TYPE.
- GOOD JOB!
NICELY HANDLED.
- I'M NOT?
CAN I ASK WHAT YOUR TYPE
IS THEN?
- WELL, IF I HAD TO SAY,
I, UH...
- WHAT?
I WHAT?
- I GUESS,
IN TERMS OF ATTRACTION,
I'M FOND OF
VERY YOUNG BOYS.
- OH MY GOD!
I DON'T LIKE OTHER GIRLS!
I WEAR PANTIES EVERY DAY
AND I'M DEFINITELY
NOT A PEDOPHILE!
- HOW THE HELL
AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT
WITH THE TYPES OF
BOOKS YOU READ?
- THOSE ARE WORKS OF FICTION,
YOU MORON!
AND THE THINGS THAT I CHOOSE
TO READ AT HOME
ARE MEANT TO
STAY INSIDE OUR HOME!
- I GOT IT.  I PROMISE.
I'LL ACT EXACTLY LIKE YOU DO
FROM NOW ON.
- ( sighs )
- AH, HIDEYOSHI.
- OH, UH, HEY, AKIHISA.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE HIDING
SOMEWHERE FROM THOSE PEOPLE?
- NOPE.
THOSE GUYS FOUND OUT
THAT KOUJI
CONFESSED HIS LOVE
TO YOUR SISTER EARLIER,
SO THEY'RE TRYING
TO CAPTURE HIM NOW.
- OH, I SEE.
POOR KOUJI.
I THINK HE'S ACTUALLY HAVING
A WORSE DAY THAN I AM.
- THAT DUMBASS NEVER LEARNS,
DOES HE?
- HUH?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'D ACTUALLY TRY TO GET
YOUR SISTER TO GO OUT WITH HIM
JUST BECAUSE YOU
TURNED HIM DOWN.
( laughing )
- I TAKE BACK MY SYMPATHY.
- OH, ON THE SUBJECT
OF YOUR SISTER...
- HUH?
- ( jazz tune playing )
- YUUKO'S PRETTY INCREDIBLE,
ISN'T SHE?
- WHAT?
WHERE'S THIS COMING FROM?
- WELL, LOOK AT HER.
SHE'S SO CUTE.
AND SHE'S REALLY SMART TOO.
NOT TO MENTION
A STELLAR ATHLETE.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF HER.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- YEAH, AND ON TOP OF THAT,
SHE'S PRETTY NO MATTER
WHAT SHE'S DOING.
- SHE'S PRETTY?
HUH.
- TALK ABOUT A MAJOR WASTE.
- ( gasps slightly )
- WORD IS SHE'S FREAKY-DEAKY.
I HEARD SHE'S A GIANT LESBO
AND SHE NEVER WEARS ANY PANTIES.
- WHY WOULD YOU BELIEVE THAT?!
- WHAT THE--?!
WHAT'S WRONG?!
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE,
BUT I SWEAR I CAN
FAINTLY FEEL THE SHAPE
OF SOME BREASTS RIGHT NOW!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY FAINTLY?!
THERE ARE DEFINITELY
BREASTS THERE!
- AAH!
- SO, FOR SOME STRANGE REASON,
THERE'S A RUMOR GOING AROUND
THAT MY BREASTS ARE DEFINITELY
BEGINNING TO DEVELOP.
- WELL, THAT'S FUNNY.
BECAUSE THERE'S A RUMOR
GOING AROUND
THAT I'M INTO GIRLS,
YET ATTRACTED TO LITTLE BOYS,
AND THAT I WANDER AROUND
WITHOUT WEARING UNDERWEAR.
- IT SEEMS A LITTLE UNFAIR.
I MEAN, THEY'RE NEVER GONNA
STOP TREATING ME
LIKE A GIRL NOW, ARE THEY?
- YEAH, BUT THEY ALREADY
TREAT YOU LIKE THAT.
THEY'LL TREAT ME LIKE
A TRIPLE-THREAT PERVERT.
- THIS NEVER WOULD'VE HAPPENED
IF YOU DIDN'T MAKE ME SWITCH
PLACES WITH YOU!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST KEEP
YOUR STUPID MOUTH SHUT?!
- ( both sigh )
- I GUESS WE JUST HAVE TO
LIVE WITH IT.
- EXACTLY.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN GETTING UPSET.
- Both: THERE ARE A MILLION
OTHER RUMORS AT OUR SCHOOL
TO DISTRACT PEOPLE, ANYWAY.
- Hideyoshi:
BAKA AND TEST.
- Fukuhara:
ONE YEAR IN THE PAST.
- EVERYBODY FREEZE!
- ( gasps )
- PUT ALL OF YOUR BAGS
ON THE DESKS AND OPEN 'EM UP
SO I CAN SEE INSIDE!
RESISTANCE IS FUTILE!
SAKAMOTO, WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO HIDE IN YOUR POCKET?
- CRAP!
- I'LL BE CONFISCATING THIS.
- OH, COME ON!
THIS IS SO NOT FAIR!
- YOSHII!
CHANGE INTO YOUR GYM CLOTHES,
SO I CAN SEARCH YOUR CIVVIES.
- NO WAY!  THAT IS SOME
HARDCORE SUSPICION, MISTER!
I MEAN, COME ON.
CAN'T YOU EVEN TRY TO TRUST US?!
- OH, HEY, AKIHISA.
YOU DROPPED YOUR GAME CONSOLE.
- OH!  HEY, THANKS, YUUJI.
I AM NOT HIDING ANYTHING
AND I RESENT THIS INTERROGATION!
- YOU JUST SAVED ME A STEP, KID.
- Student:
SUMMONING MY AVATAR!  SUMMON!
- TODAY IS A FULL DAY OF AVATAR
TRAINING FOR YEAR ONE STUDENTS.
- OH, MAN, WE'VE HAD NOTHING
BUT BAD LUCK LATELY.
- CRAP.
I JUST BOUGHT THAT MP3 PLAYER.
- RIGHT?  HE CONFISCATED
MY PROPS AND COSTUMES TOO.
- YEAH, YOU GOT OFF EASY.
HE TOOK MY CELLPHONE, GAME
CONSOLE, VIDEO GAMES...
- WHAT IS THE POINT OF EVEN
BRINGING ALL OF THAT STUFF
WITH YOU TO SCHOOL?
- HEY, LOOKS LIKE IT'S
HIMEJI'S TURN NEXT.
- DUDE, ARE YOU PASSING UP
THE CHANCE
TO TAKE A PICTURE OF HER?
- MY CAMERA GOT CONFISCATED.
- AW, MAN, THAT SUCKS.
IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH TO GET
ANOTHER PICTURE OF HER
IN HER GYM CLOTHES
SINCE SHE'S IN
A DIFFERENT CLASS.
- I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR!
SUMMON!
- ( grunts )
- HOW COULD ANYONE NOT LIKE
A GIRL THAT CUTE?
AND THAT SMART?
- DON'T YOU KNOW HER
OR SOMETHING?
COULD HAVE SWORN
YOU TOLD ME THAT ONE TIME.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE AND I WERE IN THE SAME
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL CLASS
TOGETHER WAY BACK WHEN.
BUT WE HAVEN'T TALKED AT ALL
SINCE THEN.
- NEXT!
AKIHISA YOSHII!
- 'KAY.
- YOSHII WILL BE FIGHTING
SHIMADA!
SNAP OUT OF IT!
- OH!  YES, SIR!
AKI?
- YOU WERE IN KIND OF
A DAZE THERE.
YOU OKAY, SHIMADA?
YOU EATEN ANYTHING TODAY?
- HMM.  I DON'T NEED TO
STUFF MY FACE LIKE YOU.
- I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT FIGHTING
ME BECAUSE YOU WOUND UP
WITH A CRAPPY AVATAR,
DIDN'T YOU?
- I'M ACTUALLY GLAD
IT'S YOU I'M FIGHTING.
- HUH?
- KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE I'M PRETTY SURE
BEATING YOU UP
IS GONNA FEEL AWESOME.
- WAIT!  OUR AVATARS
ARE SUPPOSED BEAT EACH OTHER UP.
NOT US!
- THAT'S TRUE.
THE TWO OF US AREN'T GOING TO
BEAT EACH OTHER UP.
- ( exhales )
THANK YOU.
- AAH!
- GOOD TO HEAR.
- IT'S JUST ME.
NOT THE TWO OF US.
I'LL BE DOING
THE BEATING UP.
- ( whimpers )
- ( clears throat )
SHIMADA.
- SEE?  THERE!
IT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
- JUST THIS ONCE.
- SURE!
- FOR REAL?!
- ( giggles )
- ( chattering )
- ( sighs )
THIS IS SHAPING UP
TO BE THE WORST
SCHOOL YEAR IN HISTORY.
HUH?
WHOA!  IT'S HIMEJI.
- ( door closes )
- ALL RIGHT...
TIME TO ACT LIKE A MAN
AND TALK TO HER.
( groans )
AAH!  IT'S JUST TOO
SICKENINGLY CUTE!
I CAN'T TAKE IT!
RETREAT!
- PLEASE, I'M BEGGING YOU!
- HUH?
- I NEED THAT BEAR
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
PLEASE HELP ME.
- I WISH I COULD, BUT...
- EXCUSE ME.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM HERE?
- WELL, THIS YOUNG LADY
IS PRETTY DESPERATE FOR ME
TO SELL HER THAT STUFFED TOY
IN THE WINDOW DISPLAY.
BUT SHE DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY FOR IT.
- ( whimpering )
- SO, WHY'S IT SO IMPORTANT
FOR YOU TO HAVE THAT ONE?
- BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
MY OLDER SISTER
TO KEEP ON BEING SO SAD.
- YOUR OLDER SISTER?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAVE TO GET IT FOR HER.
SHE TOLD ME ONE TIME THAT
SHE REALLY WANTED IT, SO...
- OH, I SEE.
YOU WERE THINKING IT MIGHT
CHEER HER UP
IF YOU GIVE HER A PRESENT, HUH?
- MM-HMM.
I KNOW SHE'S BEEN HAVING
A TOUGH TIME AT SCHOOL
SINCE WE JUST MOVED HERE.
BUT SHE-- SHE STILL DOES
ALL THE CHORES.
- HUH?
- SHE DOES ALL THE CLEANING
AND THE LAUNDRY AND SHE ALWAYS
MAKES TIME TO PLAY WITH ME.
( cries )
- OH, NO, PLEASE STOP CRYING!
MAYBE I COULD DO SOMETHING
TO HELP YOU.
- HUH?  YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- MM-HMM.
- THAT'S SO NICE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
- UM, SIR, HOW MUCH IS
THE STUFFED TOY THAT SHE WANTS?
- 25,000 YEN.
- AAH!
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY DID WANNA HELP.
BUT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- AAH!
WAIT!  I FORGOT.
I'VE ALREADY GOT
10,000 YEN.
- IF I ADD MY ENTIRE FORTUNE
OF 1,000 YEN
TO HER 10,000 YEN,
WE'VE ONLY GOT 11,000.
WHICH MEANS WE'D STILL
HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO COME UP WITH
THE OTHER HALF OF THE 25,000.
- YOU'RE NOT GOOD WITH MATH,
ARE YOU?
- IN THAT CASE, YOU COULD
CUT THE TOY IN TWO PIECES.
AND THEN SELL US
ONE HALF OF IT.
- I'M GETTING A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT THE STATE OF EDUCATION
THESE DAYS.
- YOU'RE A LITTLE STUPID, HUH?
- WELL, THAT SHOULD GIVE US
ENOUGH TIME TO COME UP
WITH THE REST.
- BUT THEN,
WHAT HAPPENS IF WE DON'T?
- IT COULD BE TOUGH.
THAT IS A LOT OF MONEY
TO GATHER.
( gasps )
THAT'S ABOUT THE TOTAL WORTH
OF EVERYTHING THAT GOT
CONFISCATED FROM ME.
PERFECT!
- DID YOU HAVE AN IDEA?
- TELL YOU WHAT,
MEET ME IN THIS PARK
AT THE SAME TIME TOMORROW.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
- MEET HERE TOMORROW.
- MM-HMM.
- OKAY, I'LL BE HERE!
- AWESOME.
- ( giggles )
- Yuuji: YOU WANNA TAKE BACK
ALL OF OUR STUFF?
- YEAH.  BUT I'M GONNA NEED
YOU GUYS TO HELP ME PULL IT OFF.
- WE'VE GOTTA GET A HOLD OF
THE KEY
TO IRON MAN'S LOCKER
IF WE'RE GONNA DO IT.
- BUT HE KEEPS THAT KEY
IN HIS JACKET POCKET.
- SO NOT A PROBLEM.
ALL WE'VE GOTTA DO IS DOUSE HIM
WITH A BIG OL' BUCKET OF WATER.
WE WAIT FOR HIM TO CHANGE HIS
CLOTHES, RIGHT?
AND THEN WE JUST
TAKE IT FROM HIS POCKET.
YOU CAN DO IT, AKIHISA.
JUST DON'T GET KILLED.
- ME?!
- TARGET APPROACHING!
- DON'T SCREW UP!
- GOOD LUCK!
- I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE GONNA HELP ME!
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
AAH!
MY FOOT SLIPPED!
ON ACCIDENT!
NO WAY!
YOU'RE NOT DODGING THIS ONE!
- ( groaning )
- ( sighs )
( chuckles )
WELL...
I'M SORRY.
I TRIPPED-- AAH!
- YOU SURE THAT'S THE STORY
YOU'RE STICKING WITH?
- ( whimpering )
I HAD A HELL OF A TIME,
BUT I GOT THE KEY.
- NICE.
LET'S OPEN THIS BAD BOY
AND GET OUR STUFF BACK
WHILE WE CAN.
- JACKPOT!
- OKAY, NOW MOVE OUT
BEFORE WE GET CAUGHT.
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
HUH?  OLD BOOKS?
NO REASON TO WASTE THEM.
MAN, THAT WAS PRETTY CLOSE.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN
A FEW THOUSAND YEN SHORT
IF I HADN'T SOLD
THOSE OLD BOOKS.
- HEY!
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
- SORRY I'M LATE.
- OH, THAT'S OKAY.
- WAIT, YOU GOT ONE?
- UH-HUH.
A REALLY NICE
HIGH SCHOOL GIRL SHOWED UP
AND GAVE IT TO ME
BEFORE YOU GOT HERE.
- A HIGH SCHOOL GIRL,
THAT'S FUNNY.
- YEAH!
SHE TOLD ME TO GIVE THE TOY
TO MY SISTER, BUT...
SHE ALSO TOLD ME THAT I COULD
KEEP IT FOR MYSELF
IF YOU BROUGHT THE BIG ONE
FOR HER INSTEAD.
WE'D BOTH HAVE ONE!
- UH, WELL, I GUESS THAT
MEANS THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
- IT IS?  REALLY?
- YEP.  AND THEN...
THIS ONE IS FOR YOUR SISTER.
- ( gasps )
YOU DID IT!
- I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT, AND THIS
WILL CHEER HER UP FOR YOU.
- UM, CAN YOU, UH--
CAN YOU SQUAT
DOWN FOR A SECOND?
- HUH?
YOU MEAN LIKE THIS?
- THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
- ( chuckles )
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU MAY BE STUPID, BUT I LIKE
YOU 'CAUSE YOU'RE SO NICE.
AND I'VE MADE UP MY MIND--
AS SOON AS I GET OLD ENOUGH,
I'M GONNA MARRY YOU!
- UH--
( chuckles nervously )
- LISTEN CLOSELY.
THERE WAS AN INCIDENT YESTERDAY.
SOMEONE STOLE ALL OF
THE CONFISCATED MATERIAL
AND MY OWN PERSONAL BOOKS
OUT OF MY LOCKER.
THIS INDIVIDUAL WAS SO
SHAMELESS AND COCKY
THAT HE OPENLY PRESENTED
HIS STUDENT I.D.
WHEN HE PAWNED OFF MY OLD BOOKS
AND HIS VIDEO GAMES.
YOSHII, WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THAT?
- YEAH, THAT IS A COCKY MOVE.
- INDEED IT IS.
- ( both laughing )
- YOSHII, PREPARE YOURSELF
FOR DOOM!
- I'M SORRY!
I HAD A GOOD REASON!
- YOU HAVE FINALLY EARNED
THE TITLE
THIS INSTITUTION
RESERVES FOR TRUE IDIOTS.
AKIHISA YOSHII...
FROM NOW ON, YOU ARE
A PROBATIONARY STUDENT!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HERE, BIG SIS!  FOR YOU!
- WHAT?  HOW DID YOU--
- HOPEFULLY THIS'LL BE ENOUGH
TO CHEER YOU UP SOME.
- THANK YOU, HAZUKI.
THIS CHEERS ME UP A LOT.
- IT'S TOUGH MOVING
TO A NEW PLACE,
BUT THINGS
DON'T HAVE TO BE BAD.
- YEAH, WE PICKED UP
THE LANGUAGE QUICKLY.
BESIDES...
- BESIDES?
- ...I'M KIND OF INTERESTED
IN SOMEONE.
THERE'S A BOY
THAT I THINK I LIKE.
- WHAT?!
TELL ME ABOUT HIM!
- ( giggles )
WELL, WE'RE IN
THE SAME CLASS TOGETHER.
AND HE'S PROBABLY ONE OF
THE STUPIDEST PEOPLE I'VE MET.
( giggles )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION FOUR:
WHEN YOU ADD ALL OF THE NUMBERS
OF THE 52 PLAYING CARDS
IN A DECK, WHAT'S THE TOTAL?
- Akihisa: ONE PLUS TWO PLUS
THREE PLUS, UM...
- GOOD LUCK WITH THAT ONE.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME:
ME, TRUE COLORS
AND A MAN'S DIGNITY!
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.