- OKAY, THIS IS WEIRD.
WHERE AM I?
"THE RIVER STYX"?
THAT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE FUN.
- COME ON, AKIHISA.
COME TO OUR SIDE OF THE RIVER.
- IT'S NICER THAN IT LOOKS.
I PROMISE.
- EVERYTHING IS
BETTER OVER HERE.
- TRUST ME, THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO BE SCARED, MAN.
THIS SIDE JUST TAKES
A LITTLE GETTING USED TO.
NO BIG DEAL.
- YUUJI?
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU DOING OVER THERE?
- I'M HERE BECAUSE I'M HERE.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU
TO BE SCARED, I PROMISE.
COME ON OVER.  DON'T BE AFRAID.
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
- ( screams )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( shivers )
- HEY, WHERE ARE WE?
- I DON'T REMEMBER EXACTLY.
BUT I FEEL LIKE WE WENT
THROUGH HELL TO GET HERE.
- YOU HAD TO KNOW
THE GIRLS WOULD FIND OUT
WHAT YOU WERE UP TO.
I MEAN, IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU GUYS ARE LUCKY
TO BE BREATHING.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE SHOULD BE
GONERS FOR SURE.
- Fukuhara: AKIHISA AND YUUJI
MADE A CONTEST
OUT OF HITTING ON
CHICKS YESTERDAY.
THE GIRLS FOUND OUT AND
PUNISHED THEM SOMEWHAT SEVERELY.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
SOMEONE PUNISHED
AS GRUESOMELY AS YOU WERE.
I CAN HARDLY BEAR
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
IT WAS JUST SO
HORRIBLY SADISTIC.
- YEAH, I'M GLAD
I CAN'T REMEMBER IT.
- ME TOO, ALTHOUGH I GUESS
WE DESERVED WHATEVER IT WAS.
WE WERE BEING JERKS.
- I'M JUST SAYING,
THE NEXT TIME
YOU'RE WITH GIRLS,
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY AVOID
FLIRTING WITH OTHER GIRLS.
- YOU KNOW, NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT,
WE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN OFF
A LITTLE EASY.
- I DON'T KNOW
IF I'D EXACTLY CALL
A NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE
"GETTING OFF EASY."
- NO, I WOULDN'T EITHER,
BUT I THINK I GET
WHERE AKI'S COMING FROM.
THERE MIGHT BE MORE
PUNISHMENT TO COME.
- SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD DO? RUN?
- Minami: SOMEONE SAY "RUN"?
- WE'RE TOO LATE.
- Girls: TA DA!
- HEY, GIRLS.  YOU LOOK NICE,
BUT WHY ARE YOU WEARING YUKATA?
- BECAUSE THEY'RE HOLDING
A FESTIVAL IN TOWN, SILLY.
- SO, AKIHISA,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- UM, THEY'RE GOOD.
YOU GUYS LOOK SO NICE.
- REALLY? THIS IS KINDA
MY FIRST TIME WEARING ONE.
- OH, YEAH, YOU
GREW UP IN GERMANY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I KEEP FORGETTING THAT.
- WHAT? WILL YOU QUIT STARING?
- ( gasps ) OH.
I WAS JUST ZONING OUT.
- OR MAYBE
YOU JUST COULDN'T
KEEP YOUR EYES OFF HER.
MINAMI SURE DOES
LOOK PRETTY, DOESN'T SHE?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- KIMONOS ARE SUPER GREAT
BECAUSE THEY MAKE YOU LOOK GOOD
EVEN IF YOU'VE
GOT SMALL BOOBS.
- I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- OH, WELL, THEN I SUPPOSE
I BETTER SHOW YOU, HUH?
PAY ATTENTION.
( kisses )
UH-OH.
- HMM? ( screams )
- YOU SEE WHAT I MEAN?
HE LOST IT WAY FASTER
THAN USUAL.
- ( gasps )
- LISTEN, KOUTA,
YOU'RE GONNA BE JUST FINE.
STAY WITH ME NOW.
- ( groans )
I KNOW.  IT LOOKS
A LOT WORSE THAN IT IS.
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- YUUJI.
HOW DO YOU LIKE MY YUKATA?
TELL THE TRUTH.
- IT'S FINE AND I ALWAYS
TELL THE TRUTH, DON'T I?
- THANK YOU.
IN THAT CASE THEN,
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GET MARRIED?
- NO FREAKING WAY.
- ALL RIGHT, THAN WOULD YOU
RATHER MOVE FORWARD
BY GETTING ENGAGED FIRST?
- NOT EVEN A LITTLE.
- THEN LET ME ASK YOU THIS.
- NO MEANS NO.
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO KEEP BREATHING?
- YEAH, OKAY FINE!
YOU LOOK GREAT, SHOUKO.
VERY PRETTY.
- THAT'S SO SWEET
OF YOU TO SAY, YUUJI.
- LIKE YOU GAVE ME A CHOICE.
- MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO KEEP MY MAN.
- THIS IS WEIRD. I THOUGHT
THEY WERE ALL MAD AT US.
I DON'T TRUST THIS,
LIKE NOT AT ALL.
- OKAY, EVERYONE.
ARE WE ALL SET?
IT'S TIME FOR US TO HEAD
OVER TO THE FESTIVAL NOW.
- AKIRA'S RIGHT.
LET'S GO GUYS.
HURRY UP, WE DON'T WANT
TO BE LATE, DO WE?
- I'M SO EXCITED RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS ONLY THE SECOND JAPANESE
FESTIVAL I'VE BEEN TO.
- I DON'T WANT
TO MISS ANY OF IT.
- GET A MOVE ON, BOYS.
- Both: YEAH, OKAY.
- WOW, EVERYTHING
IS SO SPARKLY.
- I KNOW, FOR REAL.
I LOVE IT.
- YUMMY, SOMEONE HAS
DONER KABOBS HERE.
- THEY LOOK GOOD TOO.
- WELL, WE SHOULD TRY THEM.
IF THEY LOOK GOOD,
WHY NOT, RIGHT?
- ( screams )
- YUP, MORE PUNISHMENT.
I WANT YOU TO GO
BUY SOME FOR ME.
- ( screams )
- WHY DID I HAVE
TO AGREE WITH HER?
- I'M GOING TO ASSUME
YOU WANT SOME TOO.
I DON'T MIND PAYING FOR THEM.
- IT'S FINE.
I WON'T ARGUE WITH YOU.
HOLD ON.  ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU'RE GONNA BUY THEM?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
DID YOU WANT TO PAY INSTEAD?
- NO, NO, AS YOU WERE.
I WONDER.
MAYBE SHE REALLY
DID FORGIVE ME.
- HERE IT IS.
I GOT US ONE ORDER TO SPLIT
IF THAT'S OKAY.
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS HERE
I WANT TO TRY.
SO I DIDN'T WANT
TO FILL UP TOO SOON.
- YEAH, GOOD PLAN.
I'M TOTALLY COOL WITH THAT.
SO HOW DOES IT TASTE?
- OH, I CAN'T EAT AND WALK.
I'M NOT SURE YET.
I GUESS THEY DON'T
USE LAMB IN JAPAN,
BUT IT'S STILL PRETTY YUMMY.
YOU TRY.
YOU MIGHT ACTUALLY LIKE IT
BETTER THIS WAY.
- OH WOW, THIS IS REALLY GOOD.
- OH, AKI, YOUR FACE.
YOU'VE GOT SOME SAUCE ON IT.
- THANKS, THAT WAS NICE
AND AWKWARD.
- AKIHISA, I JUST BOUGHT
SOME OCTOPUS DUMPLINGS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY SOME?
- WELL, YEAH, OF COURSE I WOULD.
THANKS, HIMEJI.
ONE DUMPLING PLEASE.
- HERE YOU GO.
SAY AAH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED ONE.
DOES IT NOT LOOK GOOD?
- IT LOOKS FINE.
IT'S NOT THAT.
- WELL, THEN.  AAH.
- AAH.
MHMM, YUM.
THE PANCAKE PART
IS HOT AND CREAMY
AND THE OCTOPUS
IS NICE AND CHEWY.
( gasps )
NO WAIT, AKIRA!
PLEASE! I KNOW
THAT SOUNDED SEXUAL,
BUT IT WASN'T AT ALL.
I SWEAR.
- "THE OCTOPUS IS CHEWY,"
THAT'S SEXUAL?
- IT'S NOT?
- ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY
YOU DIDN'T LIKE IT?
- NO.
- WHAT'D YOU SCREW UP, AKI,
THIS TIME?
QUIT FREAKING OUT.
IT'S JUST A FESTIVAL.
YOU CAN BE SUCH
A BABY SOMETIMES.
- WHO'S FREAKING OUT?
YOU'RE THE ONE
SHELLING OUT
AT EVERY BOOTH.
- HEY, YOU DON'T KNOW.
THESE COULD HAVE BEEN
TOTALLY FREE, GOD.
- THIS IS ONLY YOUR
SECOND FESTIVAL HERE.
IT'S OKAY IF YOU COULDN'T
HELP YOURSELF.
- THANK YOU.  COTTON CANDY
IS LIKE WAY DELICIOUS.
DO YOU WANT TO TRY SOME, AKI?
- WHAT?
SURE, I LOVE THAT STUFF.
- YEAH, YOU DO.
SAY AHH.
- AAH.
- IT'S GOOD, AM I RIGHT?
- YEAH, IT'S GOOD.
THANKS, MINAMI.
- OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
- YUUJI, WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME OF MY NOODLES?
- YEAH, SURE. I GUESS I'LL
HAVE SOME IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- I HAVE OKONOMIYAKI TOO.
- THANKS, THAT'S
VERY NICE OF YOU.
- WOULD YOU LIKE SOME SODA?
- YES, MUCH APPRECIATED.
- NICE, YUUJI LOOKS LIKE
HE GOT OFF THE HOOK TOO.
I MEAN, THIS IS A FESTIVAL.
WHY WOULD THEY WANT
TO BE PISSED THE WHOLE TIME?
TODAY ROCKS!
- AKIHISA,
THEY HAVE BABY CHICKENS
IN DIFFERENT COLORS OVER THERE.
THERE'S LIKE GREEN ONES,
AND BLUE ONES, AND EVERYTHING.
- YEAH, THEY JUST HIRE SOMEONE
TO PAINT THE BABIES.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IT'S BECAUSE OF THEIR BREED
OR SOMETHING NATURAL LIKE THAT.
- ( laughs )
YOU TWO ARE LIKE
BEYOND STUPID.
KOUTA, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT ALL THIS?
- ( screeches )
- ( evil chuckle )
I'LL COLOR YOU
HOWEVER I LIKE!
- WELL, PAINTING MAKES
A SICK KIND OF SENSE.
- SO TELL ME, AKI, ARE YOU
HAVING A GOOD TIME YET?
- YUP.
- AND, YUUJI, ARE
YOU HAVING FUN?
- YUP, SURE AM.
- HEY, LOOK, AKIHISA.
IT TURNS OUT THE FESTIVAL
IS THROWING A SPECIAL EVENT
LATER ON TODAY.
- "ENTER TO WIN
OUR FIRST EVER SUMMER
MISS YUKATA BEAUTY PAGEANT."
NICE.
- BEAUTY PAGEANT?
- WE SHOULD TOTALLY
GO WATCH THAT.
- MY CAMERA AND I
ARE UP FOR IT.
- ALL RIGHTY THEN.
HOW ABOUT WE ALL GO.
- BETTER YET,
WHY DON'T WE HAVE EVERYONE
JUST COMPETE IN THE THING.
WELL, I MEAN, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO OBVIOUSLY.
BUT I JUST THOUGHT
IT'D BE A NICE MEMORY
OF THE DAY AND STUFF.
THAT'S ALL.
- GREAT IDEA.
- WHAT? REALLY?
- YES, OF COURSE, WE SHOULD
ALL DO THIS TOGETHER.
- SOMETHING WE ARE SURE
TO NEVER FORGET.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S
COMPETE IN THE PAGEANT.
LET'S HAVE
EVERYONE HERE COMPETE.
- Both: RUN!
- ( screams )
- WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO
IN SUCH A HURRY? YOU SCARED?
- WE'RE GOING TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE BEAUTY PAGEANT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, YUUJI?
- WHAT? DON'T TAKE
THIS PERSONALLY,
BUT YOU GUYS AREN'T
MAKING ANY SENSE LIKE AT ALL.
- FOR REAL.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- HITTING ON GIRLS EARLIER.
- SURELY YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE
WE WERE FINISHED
WITH YOU BOYS YET.
- YOU SHOULD KNOW BY NOW
THAT WE WOULD MAKE YOU PAY
SEVERELY FOR WHAT YOU DID.
- ( laughs )
HEY, BOYS, DON'T WORRY.
I TOTALLY BROUGHT
MY MAKEUP KIT WITH ME TONIGHT.
- ( both gasp )
- NO WAY!
I'M SUPER TALL.
I'D NEVER PASS AS A WOMAN.
I THINK MAKING AKIHISA
DRESS UP AS A CHICK
IS PUNISHMENT ENOUGH
FOR BOTH OF US.
- WHAT?! DON'T YOU USE ME
TO TRY TO GET OUT THIS.
IF ANYONE'S DRESSING UP,
IT'S YOU.
- PLEASE STOP FIGHTING.
NEITHER ONE OF YOU
IS GOING TO WIN.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD
FOLLOW KOUTA'S LEAD.
HE'S TAKING HIS
CROSS-DRESSING LIKE A MAN.
- ( sighs )
- I THINK THIS IS WHAT THEY MEAN
BY "CRUEL AND UNUSUAL."
- I'M SORRY.  I HAVE SUCH
A FLARE FOR THE DRAMATIC.
I PROBABLY OVERDID IT
WITH THE MAKEUP,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- I JUST WISH HE WEREN'T
SO EXCITED ABOUT DOING IT.
- I DON'T LIKE THIS AT ALL.
WHERE'D THEY COME UP
WITH KOUMI? I HATE IT.
- OH PLEASE.  WHAT ARE
YOU COMPLAINING ABOUT?
ON TOP OF LOOKING LIKE
A TOTAL FREAK,
I'M SUPPOSED TO ACT
LIKE A DAMN FOREIGNER.
- WELL, THE ONLY WAY
ANYONE WOULD EVER BELIEVE
SOMEONE AS BIG AS YOU WAS
A CHICK IS IF YOU TELL THEM
YOU'RE AN INTERNATIONAL ATHLETE.
- EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU
LOOKS JUST ADORABLE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.  ONE OF YOU
COULD TOTALLY WIN THIS.
- I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW HAPPY IT MAKES ME
TO SEE MY LITTLE BROTHER GROW UP
TO BE SUCH A PRETTY GIRL.
- I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW NOT HAPPY
IT MAKES ME
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
- YOU NEED TO WORK ON
YOUR SEX APPEAL, YUUJI.
- I DO NOT.
I'M SEXY AS HELL.
- HEY, I HAVE A QUESTION.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
WHY DO I HAVE TO
COMPETE IN THE PAGEANT?
- Fukuhara: BECAUSE THAT'S
THE PLOT IN THIS EPISODE.
ROLL WITH IT.
- Mizuki: BAKA AND TEST.
- Announcer: AND NOW,
IT'S TIME TO START
OUR FIRST EVER SUMMER
MISS YUKATA BEAUTY CONTEST.
- ( cheers )
- AS A COMMENTATOR,
WE HAVE MR. OBATA,
WHO'S WEARING
HIS YUKATA TODAY.
HE IS ALSO OUR
SPONSOR AND JUDGE.
- I AM EXCITED TO BE,
BUT I'M EVEN MORE EXCITED
TO SEE ALL THE PRETTY LADIES.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- STOP STRESSING.  NO ONE
WILL FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
- YUUJI, IF YOU BELIEVE
IN YOURSELF, YOU CAN WIN.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
- I'LL RECORD THE WHOLE THING.
THIS TIME YOU'RE
THE ONE ON CAMERA.
- I HATE YOU.
- Aki: DUDE, WHAT ARE
WE GONNA DO?
- Yuuji: WE MAKE SURE
WE LOSE THIS THING FAST.
THEN WE ROLL.
- I GOT IT!
WHY DON'T WE JUST
TELL THEM WE'RE GUYS?
- WE CAN'T DO THAT.
- YEAH, LIKE ABSOLUTELY CAN'T.
WHAT IF SOMEONE WE KNOW,
LIKE SOMEONE FROM SCHOOL
IS IN THE AUDIENCE?
- THINK ABOUT IT
FOR JUST A SECOND.
IMAGINE OUR CLASS
FOUND OUT WE WERE
DRESSED UP LIKE CHICKS.
AND NOT ONLY WERE WE DOLLED UP
FROM HEAD TO TOE,
BUT WE WERE SO CONFIDENT
IN OUR HOTNESS
WE ACTUALLY ENTERED
A CONTEST TO PROVE IT.
- NO, THAT'S SOCIAL SUICIDE!
I FINALLY GOT POPULAR!
I CAN'T GO BACK
TO BEING A NOBODY.
- YOU'RE IDEA OF
POPULAR AND MINE
ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
- FOCUS!
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
WE'RE GONNA
GET OUT OF THIS
MASSIVE BALL OF SUCK.
WE CAN'T ALLOW OURSELVES
TO MAKE IT PAST THE FIRST ROUND.
AND NO ONE CAN FIND OUT
WE'RE GUYS.
OUR TIME HAS COME.
THIS IS OUR BATTLE FOR MANHOOD.
- FIRST UP TONIGHT, WE HAVE
LOVELY CONTESTANT NUMBER ONE.
PLEASE TAKE THE STAGE.
- ( cheers )
- OKAY, WHAT DO I DO NOW?
- WELL, SWEETIE, WANT
TO TELL US YOUR NAME?
- I'LL JUST LOOK AT THE FLOOR
AND BE AS QUIET AS I CAN.
( high-pitch )
UM, HELLO.
MY NAME IS AKIKO YOSHII.
- PERFECT.  NOW IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU MIGHT BE
A LITTLE BIT SHY, MISS AKIKO.
- SHYNESS USUALLY MEANS
A GIRL IS PURE AND INNOCENT.
I'M GOING TO GIVE
HER A HIGH SCORE.
- WHY?
- DO YOU HAVE ANY
SPECIAL TALENTS?
- I CAN'T LIE ABOUT THIS.
WHAT IF THEY START ASKING ME
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE TALENT?
( high pitch )
I GUESS I'D HAVE TO SAY COOKING.
I'M GOOD AT PAELLA AND
SPAGHETTI CARBONARA TOO.
- SO DO YOU MOSTLY
COOK AT HOME?
- UH-HUH, I COOK ALMOST
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- A LOOKER AND A COOKER.
DON'T SEE THAT MUCH
THESE DAYS.
NOW TELL US, DO YOU
HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
- NO! NO BOYFRIEND!
- ( cheers )
- WELL, THAT IS GOOD NEWS
FOR ALL THE GUYS
IN THE AUDIENCE.
MR. OBATA, WHAT'S
YOUR OPINION ON THAT?
- IF YOU GIVE ME YOUR PHONE
NUMBER AND LET ME CALL YOU,
I PROMISE TO GIVE YOU MONEY
TO SPEND ON WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- SO YOU KNOW, I'D LIKE
TO PUNCH HIM FOR SAYING THAT,
BUT HE IS OUR SPONSOR.
NOW, MISS AKIKO,
WHAT DO YOU LIKE MOST
ABOUT THE YUKATA YOU'RE
WEARING FOR US TODAY?
- LIKE ABOUT IT?
WELL, IT'S VERY MODEST.
SO IT HIDES MY BODY.
- INTERESTING.
SO THEN, MR. OBATA,
HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT HER MANNER
OF WEARING YUKATA?
- YES, I DO.  I WANT TO KNOW
IF SHE'S WEARING ANY UNDERWEAR.
- UNDERWEAR? LIKE PANTIES?
( high pitch ) NO FREAKIN' WAY!
I DON'T WEAR THAT STUFF!
- ( cheering )
- THANK YOU FOR ANSWERING THAT
WILDLY INAPPROPRIATE QUESTION.
YOU CAN LEAVE THE STAGE NOW.
- NICE SCORE, MAN.
THEY LIKE YOU.
- I HATE YOU.
- PLEASE TELL US YOUR NAME.
- YEAH, OKAY.
I AM KOUMI TSUCHIYA.
- AND DID YOU COME HERE
TO SWIM TODAY?
- I DID.
- GREAT, NEXT QUESTION.
DO YOU OFTEN WEAR YUKATA?
- I DON'T.
- DID YOU COME HERE ALONE
OR ARE YOU HERE WITH FRIENDS?
- WITH FRIENDS.
- SO ARE THEY CHEERING YOU ON
IN THE AUDIENCE?
- NO, THEY'RE NOT.
- HMM.
OKAY, BESIDES YUKATA, WHAT ARE
YOUR FAVORITE KINDS OF CLOTHING?
- SILK CHINESE DRESSES, KIMONOS,
AN OUTFIT FOR RACECAR GIRLS,
CHEERLEADERS, NURSES,
FLIGHT ATTENDANTS,
WAITRESSES AT OLD-SCHOOL DINERS,
AND POLICE WOMEN.
ALSO, ANY KIND OF LEOTARD,
CHICK POWER SUITS,
AND SCHOOL GIRL UNIFORM,
SHRINE MAIDEN OUTFITS,
MAID UNIFORMS,
AND TENNIS OUTFITS.
UH, I MEAN, NOTHING MUCH.
- ( cheering )
- WELL, THAT WAS UNEXPECTED.
APPARENTLY THE SHORT-ANSWER
SWEETHEART
ENJOYS COSTUMES ALMOST AS MUCH
AS THE AUDIENCE ENJOYS HER.
- NO, FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
- ( cheers )
- PLEASE CALM DOWN.
- THIS IS QUITE A REACTION.
THIS CUTIE'S DEFINITELY
MAKING IT TO THE FINALS.
- PLEASE STOP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CHEER FOR ME.
- ( cheers )
- ( sighs )
- YOUR PLAN BACKFIRE
ON YOU, KOUMI?
- I HATE YOU AND
I HATE THIS PLACE.
- ( with accent )
I'M HONG XIONG LI.
IT IS SO NICE TO MEET YOU ALL.
- WE MIGHT HAVE A REAL-LIFE
AMAZONIAN WOMAN ON OUR HANDS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MR. OBATA?
- I LOVE THE TALL ONES.
I'M ENTRANCED.
SOME MIGHT CALL IT A FETISH,
BUT IT'S SIMPLY A RESPECT
FOR STRONG WOMEN.
- WHAT?!
- SHE HAS THE HIGHEST SCORE
OF ALL OF OUR
CONTESTANTS SO FAR.
NOW THEN, DO YOU HAVE ANY--
WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- WE'LL BE MARRIED IN THE SPRING
AND SPEND OUR HONEYMOON
IN CAMBODIA.
- WE'RE FROM DIFFERENT CULTURES.
OUR FAMILIES WOULD
NEVER APPROVE.
- THE FORBIDDEN ASPECT
OF OUR LOVE
ONLY MAKES IT STRONGER.
DO YOU NOT AGREE, DEAR?
- WHAT LOVE? WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU'LL FEEL THE SAME WAY I DO
SOMEDAY.  JUST HAVE FAITH.
- ( normal ) THE ONLY THING
I HAVE FAITH IN
IS THAT I'M ABOUT
TO KICK YOUR ASS.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE AFRAID, DARLING!
WE CAN START OFF AS FRIENDS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU'LL WANT FOR NOTHING!
- ENOUGH!
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
YOU ASKED FOR IT!
- ASKED FOR IT?
I'M PRACTICALLY BEGGING FOR IT.
YOU COULD DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT?
- AFFAIRS WILL
NOT BE PERMITTED.
- SHOUKO, NO!
WHAT ABOUT ANY OF THIS
IS AN AFFAIR?!
( cries )
- I THINK I'M GONNA
NEED THERAPY NOW.
- ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOU COULD SAY WE HAD
AN UNFORGETTABLE SUMMER.
- YEAH, EXCEPT
I WANT TO FORGET IT.
- IT WAS PROBABLY FOR THE BEST
THE CONTEST GOT CANCELLED.
- I DON'T THINK THAT
CREEPY SPONSOR GUY
WOULD AGREE WITH YOU.
- HUH, MAYBE WE WENT
A TEENSY BIT OVERBOARD.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK? SHOULD
WE LET THEM OFF THE HOOK NOW?
- PERHAPS.
I'M NOT OPPOSED TO IT.
- THEY ALL LOOK PRETTY SORRY
IF YOU ASK ME.
WHY DON'T WE
MAKE AN EXCEPTION
AND FORGIVE THEM
THIS TIME, OKAY?
- ( sighing )
- YOU KNOW, I WONDER WHO WOULD
HAVE WON THE PAGEANT
IF IT DIDN'T GET ALL EXPLODED.
DON'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.  HIDEYOSHI SEEMS
THE MOST APPROPRIATE CHOICE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.  WHY AM I
THE MOST APPROPRIATE CHOICE?
I'M A GUY TOO.
AND YOU HAD THE HIGHEST SCORE.
- MY HEART DID A LITTLE
FLUTTER-THING WHEN I SAW
KOUTA DRESSED UP
LIKE A GIRL.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, AKIRA?
- IT WAS FUN.
I MEAN, I'M USED TO AKI
WEARING GIRL'S CLOTHES,
BUT IT WAS STILL NICE
TO SEE THE OTHER TWO
EMBRACE THEIR
CROSS-DRESSING SELVES.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, CRAZY?!
I DON'T EVER
WEAR CHICK CLOTHING!
- OH, DON'T BE RIDICULOUS,
AKI, MY DARLING.
YOU WORE A SKIRT AGAIN
LAST NIGHT.
I SWEAR YOU HAVE
THE WORST MEMORY.
OF COURSE, YOU WERE
ASLEEP AT THE TIME.
- YOU'RE MY SISTER!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME
WHILE I WAS SLEEPING?!
- AKI, CALM DOWN.
I AM HALFWAY LYING
ABOUT THIS.
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN, YOU SCHIZO?!
TELL THE TRUTH.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME?!
- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
I COULDN'T GET IT UP
PAST YOUR KNEES.
- SO YOU LEFT IT HALFWAY ON?!
- IF YOU'D RATHER, WE CAN SAY
IT WAS HALFWAY OFF INSTEAD.
- ( cries )
- Yuuji: OKAY, GUYS.
THE FOOD'S READY.
- All: YEAH, I'M STARVING.
- THIS LOOKS SO DELICIOUS.
- SERIOUSLY, SAKAMOTO
IS REALLY GOOD AT GRILLING.
- MY FUTURE HUSBAND,
I'M SO PROUD.
- I WANTED TO COOK TOO, BUT
AKIHISA WOULDN'T LET ME HELP.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WAS GONNA
ACCIDENTLY KILL SOMEONE
WITH A KITCHEN KNIFE.
- THAT WASN'T WHAT
WE WERE AFRAID OF, HIMEJI.
THE PROBLEM WAS
YOU COULD STILL HAVE KILLED US
WITHOUT EVEN TOUCHING A KNIFE.
- IF SHE COOKS, WE'RE DEAD.
- MY TONGUE JUST CURLED
BACK IN MY THROAT.
- THE WOMAN CANNOT BE
ALLOWED NEAR A KITCHEN.
- I HAVE AN IDEA.  WHY DON'T
WE HAVE A COOKING COMPETITION
BETWEEN ALL THE GIRLS.
AND THE GUYS CAN JUDGE IT.
- Boys: THAT'S
THE WORST IDEA EVER.
- OOH, I LIKE IT,
BUT COOKING'S SO SUBJECTIVE.
HOW DO WE DECIDE
WHO THE WINNER IS?
- IF THEY'RE GOING
FOR A K.O,
I'D KNOW WHO'D WIN.
- ( groans )
- GOOD GRIEF.
WE SURE DID STUFF OUR FACES,
DIDN'T WE?
- WE DID, YEAH.
CALL ME CRAZY, THOUGH.
I'M STILL HUNGRY.
- TOO BAD.
THERE'S NO FOOD
LEFT TO COOK.
- SURE THERE IS, MAN.
IT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
- ALL I SEE IS UGLY.
- IT'S CALLED THE OCEAN,
YOU NIMROD.
FRESH CLAMS ARE TOTALLY OUT OF
THIS WORLD WHEN THEY'RE GRILLED.
- OH YEAH.
- Mizuki: YOU KNOW,
NOW THAT I THINK OF IT...
- ( gasps )
- I BAKED SOME
MADELEINES AT HOME.
SO WE COULD EAT
THOSE IF YOU WANTED.
- COME ON, YUUJI.
LET'S GO FIND US SOME CLAMS.
- YEAH, CLAMS!
CLAMS ARE GOOD.
WE SHOULD FIND SOME.
WE SHOULD GET SO MANY
THAT WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO EAT THEM ALL.
- HEY, SO WOULD YOU LIKE
TO JOIN ME ON THE BEACH, KOUTA?
WE CAN HELP THEM.
- YES, I LOVE CLAMS.
- WEIRD, I WONDER
WHAT THAT WAS ALL ABOUT.
- THERE'S NO TELLING.
- THEY'RE GUYS.
SO WHAT'S THE STORY
WITH THOSE MADELEINES?
- OH, YEAH, WELL,
I DID BAKE A DOZEN OF THEM.
BUT I FORGOT THAT
I FORGOT TO BRING THEM.
THEY'RE STILL SITTING AT HOME.
- BUMMER,
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD
TO SOMETHING SWEET.
- Hideyoshi: WE CAN DO
THIS, GUYS. WE HAVE TO.
- I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Minami: LOOK AT THEM.  THEY'RE
SLEEPING LIKE LITTLE BABIES.
- WELL, CONSIDERING
WHO THEY ARE,
THAT SEEMS FAIRLY APPROPRIATE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WHO KNEW THEY COULD
LOOK SO INNOCENT, THOUGH?
- I KNOW, THEY LOOK SO ADORABLE.
- THEY MUST BE TIRED
AFTER LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS CRAZY.  I'M GLAD EVERYONE
HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME, THOUGH.
- YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD?
THEY FELL ASLEEP
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY.
- THEY WERE
STUMBLING AROUND
BEFORE THEY COULD
EVEN GET IN THE CAR.
- WHEN THEY WERE
EATING BREAKFAST,
THEY HAD LOTS OF ENERGY,
BUT, LIKE
THE NEXT SECOND,
THEY WERE ALL FALLING OVER.
- THEY WERE JUST REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT EATING, I GUESS.
- YEAH, SERIOUSLY,
BUT THAT DIDN'T MEAN
THEY HAD TO EAT
ALL OF OUR FOOD TOO.
- IT KIND OF SUCKS
WE DON'T GET
TO CHAT WITH THEM
ON THE WAY BACK.
- I AGREE.
- ( groans )
- THEY FELL ASLEEP SO FAST,
I DIDN'T GET THE CHANCE TO ASK
HOW THEY LIKED BREAKFAST.
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
I WAS THE ONE WHO MADE IT.
- Boys: COME ON OVER
TO THIS SIDE.
IT'S NICER THAN IT LOOKS.
YES, THERE'S NO
NEED TO BE SCARED.
IT JUST TAKES
A LITTLE GETTING USED TO.
- Fukuhara: QUESTION THREE:
"WHAT ARE YOU NOT SUPPOSED
TO BRING TO SCHOOL?"
- Aki: SNACKS?  BUT I DON'T
THINK BANANAS SHOULD COUNT.
- THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE BANANAS.
GET IT? "BANANAS."
- NEXT EPISODE, "ME, THAT GIRL,
AND A STUFFED TOY."
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.