- MINAMI, I--
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- UH, I'M...
SORRY ABOUT EARLIER.
- WHATEVER.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE MAKING OUT
WITH MIZUKI OR SOMETHING?
- UH, NO.
WE SHOULD BE THINKING
OF ANOTHER STRATEGY.
I MEAN, IF WE LOSE
AGAINST CLASS B,
HIMEJI MIGHT HAVE TO
CHANGE SCHOOLS.
THEN WE'D BE STUCK
TRYING TO REPLACE HER.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY, JERK?!
- ( gasps )
- WHY IS IT ALWAYS ABOUT
MIZUKI WITH YOU?
WHY DOES SHE GET TO BE
THE ONLY ONE WHO MATTERS?
- SHE'S NOT.
- WELL, YOU COULD
HAVE FOOLED ME.
WHY DON'T YOU CARE
ABOUT MY FEELINGS?
YOU TREAT ME LIKE I'M A GUY.
- WHAT?
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT, I SWEAR.
- IF THEY TRY TO MAKE HER MOVE,
I'LL TALK TO MIZUKI'S PARENTS
AND YOU CAN BE
TOGETHER FOREVER.
- MINAMI--
- JUST STAY OUT OF MY
LIFE, ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T EVER WANT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: AND NOW TO
RECAP THE LAST EPISODE.
WHOO-HOO.
NEMOTO KYOUJI,
THE CLASS B REP
WAS PLANNING TO DECLARE
WAR ON CLASS F.
HE FIGURED THEIR
FIGHTING POWER WAS LOW
SINCE THEY JUST FINISHED
THEIR SUSPENSION.
AKIHISA AND FRIENDS
THEN DECIDED TO PROVOKE CLASS D,
HOPING THEY WOULD
DECLARE WAR FIRST.
FIGHTING CLASS D
WOULD GIVE THEM TIME
TO TAKE THEIR RECOVERY TEST
AND REBUILD THEIR STRENGTH.
THEY FIGURED CLASS B
WOULD BE LESS LIKELY TO STRIKE
IF CLASS F HAD A LITTLE MORE
FUEL IN THEIR TANK, SO TO SPEAK.
- Yuuji: TO GET D'S ATTENTION,
WE DECIDED AKIHISA AND MINAMI
SHOULD PRETEND
TO BE DATING.
THAT WOULD REALLY
PISS OFF MIHARU
AND IT WOULD BE ON.
BUT NOW THAT WHOLE PLAN IS SHOT,
SO HERE WE ARE.
- ( chuckles )
- MAN, YOU'RE SUCH A TROLL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SCREWED THIS UP.
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?
HOW DOES ANY OF THAT
DRAMATIC CRAP HELP
WHAT WE'RE TRYING
TO DO, MAN?
- SORRY.
- I DEFINITELY THINK
MORE ACTING LESSONS
WERE REQUIRED HERE.
I THOUGHT SHIMADA AND HIMEJI
WERE VERY BELIEVABLE THOUGH.
- OH, WOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- WHY DON'T YOU CARE
ABOUT MY FEELINGS?
YOU TREAT ME
LIKE I'M A GUY.
- HEY, KOUTA.
WHAT ARE THINGS LOOKING LIKE
OVER THERE IN CLASS B?
- THEY'RE CURRENTLY ABOUT
70% RECOVERED,
AND IT ACTUALLY LOOKS LIKE
SOME OF THEM ARE ALREADY
GETTING READY FOR
THE NEXT WAR.
- THEN THEY'RE MOVING
FASTER THAN I THOUGHT.
- THAT'S KIND OF SCARY.
THEY'RE REALLY ON A MISSION.
- WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO STALL THEM.
SO GET READY, KOUTA.
I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO
START A RUMOR IN CLASS B.
- HIT ME WITH IT.
- TELL THEM CLASS D
IS PREPPING FOR AN ST WAR,
AND CLASS B IS THEIR TARGET.
- WORD.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S GONNA WORK?
- THE ONLY THING NEMOTO
REALLY CARES ABOUT
IS GETTING BACK ON TOP.
THE DUDE WANTS TO WIN,
PERIOD.
HE'LL TRY TO AVOID
FIGHTING A SERIES OF WARS
TO KEEP HIS CLASS
FROM GETTING EXHAUSTED.
IF HE FINDS OUT CLASS D
IS AFTER THEM HARDCORE,
HE'LL LAY OFF OF US
FOR AWHILE.
- MAKES SENSE.
IT'S NOT LIKE
CLASS F'S EQUIPMENT IS
A PRIZE FOR ANYONE.
- SO HIDEYOSHI, YOU'RE UP.
IT'S NOW YOUR DROP TO DRAW
MIHARU SHIMIZU OUT OF CLASS D.
YOU'LL BE THE ONE
TO HANG ON MINAMI
AND MAKE LEZZI-TRON
WANT TO ATTACK US.
- ( grunts )
- AS SOON AS THEY STRIKE,
WE'RE HOME FREE.
SO BRUSH UP, BRO.
- BUT WHY DO I
HAVE TO DO IT?
- THANKS FOR GIVING ME
THE OPPORTUNITY TO GO OVER
HOW AKIHISA RUINED
OUR ENTIRE LIVES AGAIN
AND HOW WE CAN'T USE HIM OR
HIMEJI FOR THIS TASK ANYMORE.
- OH, YEAH.  I'M ON IT.
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
- WHO, ME?
- YES, YOU.
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
I COULD GO FOR A SANDWICH.
- THAT IS NEVER
GOOD NEWS, MY FRIEND.
YOU ARE THE CORNERSTONE
OF THIS OPERATION,
AND WE NEED TO FILL YOU UP
WITH SOMETHING GOOD
SO YOU'LL BE
READY TO FIGHT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, HIMEJI?
- WHAT?
YEA, I MEAN...
IF HE'S HUNGRY,
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO FOCUS
ON GETTING THE JOB DONE.
- ( groans )
- SO THAT'S ON YOU THEN.
FIND SOMETHING TO
STUFF HIS FACE WITH.
- I FORGOT.
I HAD LUNCH ALREADY,
AND I'M PRETTY STUFFED.
I COULDN'T SWALLOW
ANOTHER MOUTHFUL.
- IS THAT THE LUNCH
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, HUH?
- IT'S DELICIOUS.
- AAH!
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT TO ME?
- YOU WERE ASKING FOR IT, MAN.
SO, HIMEJI, YOU THINK YOU COULD
MAKE SOMETHING FOR AKIHISA?
- SURE, I'D BE DELIGHTED TO.
- HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
- FEED YOU. NOW WHAT DO
YOU FEEL LIKE EATING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
( gasps )
IF I PICK SOMETHING HEALTHY,
I JUST MIGHT SURVIVE.
- WE DON'T HAVE ALL DAY,
YOU KNOW.
- OKAY, THERE HAVE TO BE
AS FEW INGREDIENTS AS POSSIBLE
SO THERE'S LESS CHANCE
SHE'LL POISON ME.
I CHOOSE BOILED EGGS.
- SOUNDS PERFECT.
AKIHISA WOULD LIKE YOU
TO MAKE HIM SOME JELLO.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S IN THAT.
WHAT IF IT SLOWS ME DOWN?
- WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
YOU EAT DURING THE OPERATION.
- ( grunts )
- MAKE SURE TO PUT IT
IN ALUMINUM POUCHES
SO HE CAN CARRY THEM WITH HIM.
- I WON'T EVEN BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT COLOR IT IS IN THERE.
- I'LL DO IT.
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN!
- WAIT!  CAN YOU AT LEAST
TELL ME WHAT KIND YOU'RE MAKING,
SO I'LL HAVE SOME IDEA?
- YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO KNOCK IT OFF.
LOOK, CALM DOWN. NOBODY'S
REALLY GONNA MAKE YOU EAT THAT.
- HUH?
- I NEEDED HER TO HELP US
MAKE SOME MORE WEAPONS,
THAT'S ALL.
( chuckles )
- OH.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- BECAUSE NOW SHE'S
GONNA TRY TO FEED IT TO YOU,
AND THAT'S GONNA BE
FREAKING HYSTERICAL.
- YOU'RE A COLD-HEARTED SNAKE.
- ( giggles )
FIRST THING ON THE LIST
IS TO GET THE GELATIN
AND SUGAR NICE AND READY.
- NOT BAD.
SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE KNOWS
WHAT SHE'S DOING.
- OH, THAT'S GOOD.
- NOW TO MIX THE COCOA POWDER
IN WITH THE CORN POTAGE
LIKE CHOCOLATE COVERED POPCORN.
- WHOA.  WHERE DID SHE
GET THAT RECIPE FROM?
- SHH, SHUT UP.
SHE'LL HEAR YOU.
- WILL IT BE THE ORANGE
OR THE SCALLION?
THEY'RE BOTH SO GOOD,
I CAN'T DECIDE.
- SERIOUSLY? YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
TO THINK ABOUT THAT ONE.
- KNOCK IT OFF, YO.
SHE'S TRYING TO PICK
INGREDIENTS THAT ARE
THE MOST NUTRITIOUS,
YOU UNGRATEFUL TURD.
- SCALLIONS ARE MUCH HEALTHIER,
ESPECIALLY WITH NATTO.
- MAKE IT STOP.
- WAIT A MINUTE, I THINK I
REMEMBER READING SOMETHING
ABOUT NATTO THAT SAYS IT'S NOT
AS GOOD FOR OUR BLOOD FLOW
AS WE ONCE THOUGHT.
- SAFE.
- BUT IT'S STILL AN
EXCELLENT SOURCE OF PROTEIN.
- ( groans )
- THERE WE GO.
AND I JUST REMEMBERED
IT'S BLUE FISH SKIN
THAT IMPROVES BLOOD FLOW.
( giggles )
- IT'S A DOUBLE PLAY.
- THAT'S A FISH.
WHY IS SHE PUTTING A
FISH IN JELLO? THAT'S GROSS.
- SHE KNOWS HOW HARD
IT IS FOR YOU TO BE
SUCH AN IDIOT, SO SHE'S TRYING
TO FEED YOUR BRAIN.
IT'S SWEET, REALLY.
- HE'LL LOVE THIS.
OH MY GOSH,
THIS ISN'T GOING TO TASTE GOOD.
- I KNEW YOU'D
COME THROUGH, HIMEJI.
- EVERYONE KNOWS YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO ADD MUSTARD TO NATTO.
- THAT'S NOT GOING TO FIX IT!
- AND MAYBE A LITTLE
GINGER FOR THE FISH.
- YOU'RE JUST
MAKING IT WORSE.
- WHAT OTHER SECRET
INGREDIENTS CAN I ADD?
- SECRETS DO NOT
MAKE GOOD FOOD.
- I KNOW!
I BET SOME HOT SAUCE
WILL MAKE IT EXCITING.
- LET'S GO.
- ( crying )
- YOU HEAR ANYMORE,
YOU WON'T EAT IT.
- I DIDN'T GET TO SEE
HOW HOT THE HOT SAUCE WAS.
WHAT IF I CAN'T TAKE IT?
I'M AFRAID OF HEAT.
- Fukuhara:
NOT THAT IT REALLY MATTERS.
- I HOPE YOU GUYS LIKE IT.
I MADE A MESS OF
THE HOME EC ROOM.
I'M GONNA GO
CLEAN IT UP.
- WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH THESE?
- WELL, I THINK NEMOTO
IS SENDING A MESSENGER
OVER TO CLASS D.
HIS MISSION WILL BE
TO FIND OUT
IF THEY'RE ACTUALLY
STARTING A WAR LIKE WE SAID.
- OH, GREAT.
NOW WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
AS SOON AS HE GETS THERE,
HE'LL SEE
WE MADE THE WHOLE THING UP.
- VERY SIMPLE.
WE HAVE TO ASSASSINATE
THE MESSENGER.
- ( gasping )
- WE MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
SOMEONE FROM CLASS D DID IT,
LIKE A DECLARATION OF WAR
BEFORE THE FIGHTING STARTS.
- WHEN HE FINDS OUT
ONE OF HIS MEN IS DOWN,
HE WON'T QUESTION WHO DID IT.
- I DON'T KNOW. IT SOUNDS CRUEL.
- BATTLES ARE CRUEL,
MY FRIEND.
KOUTA, IT'S TIME
TO GET MOVING.
- INDEED, IT IS.
- WHAT THE HECK'S THAT?
- ( students gasp )
- ( grunts )
WHO'S THAT?
( gagging )
- REST IN PIECE.
- ( gasping )
MOMMY.
- MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
- PERFECTION AS USUAL.
- THAT WAS SERIOUSLY IMPRESSIVE.
- SOME ARE JUST
BORN WITH IT.
THAT WAS A NICE
LITTLE WARM-UP THOUGH.
- HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO DO THAT
WITHOUT ANYONE NOTICING?
- Kouta: YOU'RE ASKING
TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
- WHAT'S IMPORTANT HERE
IS THAT NOW NEMOTO SEES THIS
AS A WARNING CASUALTY
FROM CLASS D.
- GOOD.
NOW WE HAVE TIME TO PREPARE.
- YEP.  SO HOW HAVE
NEGOTIATIONS BEEN GOING?
- WE AGREED TO MEET IN ONE OF
THE EMPTY CLASSROOMS.
MINAMI SAID SHE WOULD
BE THERE AS WELL.
- AND THAT'S WHERE
THE MAGIC HAPPENS.
WE'VE GOT THIS THING
IN THE BAG.
- HOW DO WE KNOW FOR SURE
THOSE GUYS ARE GONNA
RESPOND TO THAT?
- OH, I'VE GOT IT
ALL WORKED OUT.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
- THERE IS STILL ONE THING
THAT KIND OF WORRIES ME.
- WHAT IS IT?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- I SAW NEMOTO EARLIER.
HE WAS TALKING VERY INTENSELY
TO SOMEONE IN CLASS A.
- CLASS A, HUH?
THAT'S VERY STRANGE.
I WONDER WHAT IT WAS ABOUT.
- THERE YOU ARE.
- ( gasps ) SHOUKO.
WHAT-- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
WHY ARE YOU STILL AT SCHOOL?
- WHY WOULDN'T I
BE AT SCHOOL?
- I'M SO SORRY.
I JUST HEARD THAT
YOUR MOM COLLAPSED TODAY.
- NO WAY.
ARE YOU POSITIVE IT WAS MY MOM?
YOU'RE MAKING THAT UP. THE
WOMAN'S NEVER EVEN HAD A COLD.
- SHE NEEDS YOU.
LET'S GO CHECK ON HER.
I CAN'T GO ANYWHERE RIGHT NOW.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF
SOMETHING VERY IMPORTANT.
- THIS IS YOUR MOTHER
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- SHE'S FINE. I'LL CHECK
ON HER WHEN I GET DONE.
- YOU'RE DONE NOW.
- LET ME GO.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- SOMETHING'S FISHY HERE,
AND IT'S NOT FISH.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IS HE OKAY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHY WOULDN'T YUUJI BE
THE FIRST ONE THEY CONTACTED
ABOUT HIS MOTHER?
- MAYBE BECAUSE
THEY COULDN'T REACH HIM?
HE SAID HE HAD TO TAKE
HIS PHONE IN FOR REPAIRS.
- THEN THEY COULD HAVE
JUST USED THE P.A. SYSTEM.
- SO THAT MEANS THAT NEMOTO
WAS PROBABLY TALKING TO
SOMEONE IN CLASS A
ABOUT ALL THIS.
- HE KNEW YUUJI
WOULD GO WITH SHOUKO.
- THAT EVIL SON OF A--
- THIS SUCKS.
IF I UNDERSTOOD RIGHT,
OUR NEXT STEP IN THE OPERATION
WAS TO PISS OFF MIHARU
SO SHE'D ATTACK YUUJI.
- NEVER HEARD
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS?
- NOT A PEEP.
- WHAT IS NEMOTO
TRYING TO DO?
DO YOU THINK HE MAY HAVE
FIGURED OUT OUR STRATEGY?
- NO, BUT HE'S PROBABLY TRYING
TO BUY SOME TIME AS WELL.
- I BET HE'S TRYING
TO KEEP US AT BAY
UNTIL HE FIGURES OUT EXACTLY
WHAT CLASS D IS PLANNING.
- WELL PLAYED, NEMOTO.
- BETTER LATE THAN NEVER,
RIGHT?
- MINAMI, HI.
- ( scoffs )
I ONLY CAME HERE
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU CAN'T
DO THIS WITHOUT ME, OKAY?
- SO WHAT'S OUR
PLAN OF ACTION NOW?
- YEAH, I GUESS
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
YUUJI ISN'T HERE,
SO WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO HANDLE THIS
ON OUR OWN.
- Miharu: BAKA AND TEST!
- SWEET SUGAR DUMPLING!
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
HUG ME!
- NO!
LET GO, MIHARU.
YOU'RE CHOKING ME.
- OH, LAMBKIN,
YOUR SWEET BREASTICLES
REMIND ME OF THE OCEAN.
SO SMOOTH AND PERFECT!
- MAYBE YOU'RE
THINKING OF THE HORIZON
WHICH IS FLAT
AND LEADS TO NOWHERE.
- YOU'RE STILL TOUCHING ME.
I SAID GET OFF.
- YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT
I THINK OF YOU EVERY MINUTE
360 DAYS A YEAR.
- SO YOU MUST TAKE
THE HOLIDAYS OFF,
GOOD FOR YOU.
- ENOUGH OF THAT.
MINAMI IS AKIHISA'S GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT THEY HAVE IS LIKE
BEAUTIFUL AND STUFF.
I WON'T LET YOU
COME BETWEEN THEM.
- WAY TO GO.
JUST AS WE PLANNED.
- WHAT SORT OF INSANITY
ARE YOU SPITTING AT ME?
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT MY GUMDROP PRINCESS
WANTS ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THAT MOLDY MUFFIN WRAP?
LOOK AT THAT FACE. IS THAT A
FACE THAT LOVES TROLL BOYS?
WHAT MAKES AN
APE FART LIKE YOU
THINK YOU'RE WORTHY OF
THE GINGERSNAP GODDESS?
- NO.  YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT EXACTLY A STUD.
I'M PRETTY SCRAWNY,
AND I'M NOT SMART, BUT--
- I DON'T CARE.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
THIS GOES WAY BEYOND
LOOKS OR SKILLS,
YOU SHALLOW ASS.
THIS IS MUCH MORE COMPLICATED.
- ( gasps )
- I'VE HAD MY EYE ON YOU
FOR A LONG TIME NOW,
AND THE WAY YOU TREAT PEOPLE
YOU SUPPOSEDLY CARE ABOUT
IS DISGUSTING.
MY PRINCESS IS IN
THE SAME CLASS AS
BOTH YOU AND HIMEJI,
BUT FOR SOME REASON
YOU TREAT THEM BOTH
VERY DIFFERENTLY.
YOU ARE AS SWEET
AS CANDIED APPLES
WHEN IT COMES TO HIMEJI. TREAT
HER LIKE SHE'S THE PRINCESS.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO MY LOVE,
NOT ONLY ARE YOU RUDE
AND INCONSIDERATE,
BUT IT'S LIKE YOU FORGET
SHE'S A GIRL ALTOGETHER.
ARE YOU THAT STUPID?
DO YOU NOT SEE THE CHARM
AND DELICACY THAT OOZES
FROM HER EVERY PORE?
WHAT KIND OF PIG-BRAINED IDIOT
TREATS SOMEONE LIKE HER
AS JUST ONE OF THE GUYS?
THIS IS NOT JUST AN ASSESSMENT
OF YOUR MISERABLE LOOKS
OR YOUR EMBARRASSING
SUGGESTION OF ACADEMIC SKILLS.
YOU MAKE ME SICK.
THIS IS ABOUT A BLACK SOUL
WHO WOULD THROW THE HEART OF
A PERFECT ANGEL IN THE TRASH
JUST TO PURSUE SOMEONE
AS AVERAGE AS HIMEJI.
IT'S PATHETIC. YOU
THINK MINAMI'S A GUY?
MAN, YOU REALLY MUST BE
DUMBER THAN YOU LOOK, AKIHISA.
- ( crying )
- ( gasping )
- MINAMI!
- WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU CATCH UP TO HER?
YOU GONNA WRESTLE WITH HER
AND CALL HER NAMES
UNTIL YOU BOTH LAUGH
AND THEN SPIT SHAKE ON IT?
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU GO REMIND
HER WHY SHE SHOULD HATE YOU.
- I'LL GO TALK TO HER.
MIHARU'S RIGHT.
WE DON'T WANT TO MAKE THINGS
ANY WORSE RIGHT NOW.
- UH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE,
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE
I'M NOT NEEDED.
- DID YOU REALLY COME TO SHOVE
YOUR SORRY EXCUSE FOR LOVE
IN MY FACE?
'CAUSE I'LL TELL
YOU RIGHT NOW,
YOU ARE NOT WORTHY TO
COMPETE WITH ME
FOR ANYONE'S HEART.
YOU NEED TO PROVE SOMETHING,
OBVIOUSLY.
BUT LOVE IS NOT ABOUT WHO WANTS
TO FIGHT FOR WHAT YOU HAVE,
AND EVEN IF IT WAS,
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO GETS
HOW HARD YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
FOR SOMEONE LIKE HER.
SO I'VE ALREADY WON.
- MIHARU, WAIT.
- I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
MORE I WANT TO SAY TO YOU.
- NO, YOU'VE SAID IT ALL.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
- WE, THE SECOND YEAR
STUDENTS OF CLASS D
HEREBY DECLARE WAR
ON CLASS F!
- All: WHAT?!
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
- I THOUGHT YOU GUYS SAID
IT DIDN'T GO AS PLANNED.
- WE WEREN'T EXPECTING A WAR.
NOW WHAT?
- IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH FIGHTING
WITH THIS LOW LEVEL OF STRENGTH.
- DON'T WORRY.
IT'S PART OF OUR PLAN.
- YUUJI.
- JUST AS WE THOUGHT,
IT WAS A BUNCH OF
STRATEGIC B.S.
MY MOM'S FINE
AND HEALTHY AS A DONKEY.
- YOU MEAN HORSE,
BUT THAT'S AWESOME.
- WAY TO STEP IT UP,
AKI, MY MAN.
- IT DIDN'T GO EXACTLY
AS WE PLANNED,
BUT YOU STILL MANAGED
TO HIT THE TARGET
AND UNLEASH THE CHICK BEAST.
- NOW WE'RE AT WAR.
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'LL
BE ABLE TO FIGHT THEM ALL.
- IT'S TRUE.
WE'LL NEVER SURVIVE
IN AN ALL OUT BATTLE.
WHICH MEANS...
WE'LL HAVE TO FIGHT
REPRESENTATIVES ONE-ON-ONE.
- I HAVE TO SAY, I'M IMPRESSED
YOU DIDN'T RUN AWAY.
- MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
- BELIEVE ME,
THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO
IS BATTLE MY LOVE SQUIRREL,
BUT IF IT MEANS A CHANCE
AT MAKING JERK JERKY
OUT OF THIS PIG,
IT'S WORTH IT.
- I GUESS WE'LL
SEE ABOUT THAT.
OKAY, IT'S ALL YOU
FROM HERE ON OUT, BUDDY.
MAKE ME PROUD, SON.
- I AM ALL OVER THIS ONE.
- YOU'RE GONNA PAY
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY, DORK.
MAY WE HAVE PERMISSION?
- I APPROVE!
- I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS.
- READY AND...
- Both: SUMMON!
- BEFORE WE BEGIN, I HAVE A
QUESTION I WANT TO ASK YOU.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- WHAT YOU SAID EARLIER.
DID YOU MAKE ALL THAT UP
JUST SO YOU COULD START
THIS WAR WITH CLASS D?
RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- BEFORE WE LEFT,
I SAW HER TEAR UP.
I KNEW IT WAS BECAUSE
THE THINGS I SAID TOUCHED HER.
I UNDERSTOOD HER PAIN.
PAIN YOU CAUSED HER!
SHE SHOULD NEVER EVEN HAVE
TO KNOW THOSE FEELINGS EXIST!
- HOW ARE YOU ALLOWED
TO BE IN HER PRESENCE?
YOU SHOULD BE
CHAINED AND LOCKED UP.
YOU COULDN'T BE TRUSTED TO
HOLD A CONVERSATION WITH HER
WITHOUT MANIPULATING AND
THEN DISMISSING HER FEELINGS.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
YOU LIED TO HER.
YOU USED HER.
YOU ONLY PRETENDED
TO BE HER FRIEND
SO THAT YOU COULD
KEEP HER AROUND FOR BATTLES!
YOU DON'T GIVE
A CRAP ABOUT HER!
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- YOU'RE WRONG.
I WAS TELLING THE TRUTH!
- ( screams )
- I'M NOT THE SMARTEST
GUY IN THE WORLD,
BUT I KNOW THERE ARE SOME
THINGS YOU NEVER JOKE ABOUT.
EVER.
I WAS TELLING THE TRUTH!
- WHY SHOULD I BELIEVE
A WORD YOU SAY?
- THEY WEREN'T JUST WORDS.
WHAT I SAID WAS
EXACTLY HOW I FEEL!
- ( screams )
( grunts )
- I'M NOT FALLING FOR IT
A SECOND TIME.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT THE CRAP?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU CAN GO NOW.
WE'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE ON OUT.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
THIS IS FOUL PLAY.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
- YOU CAN CALL IT
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THIS ISN'T SOME KIND OF GAME.
THIS IS WAR.
IT'S WAR!
- NO!
- GO GET 'EM, BOYS.
- ( moans, shouts )
- STOP IT!  TRAITORS!
OW!
( whimpering )
WHY?!  WHY ARE THEY
ATTACKING ME?
( yelping )
THIS IS THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EVER FELT.
IT'S LIKE A MILLION SHARP BLADES
SHOOTING IN AND OUT OF MY BODY.
- MIHARU.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK? I'M
PRETTY SURE THAT KIND OF PAIN
WILL LAST AWHILE.
I KNOW HE DESERVES
MUCH MORE THAN THIS,
BUT IS IT POSSIBLE THAT YOU
CAN FORGIVE HIM FOR NOW?
- MAYBE FOR NOW.
THIS ISN'T SOMETHING I'M GOING
TO GET OVER VERY QUICKLY.
- ( shouts )
- PROMISE ME THIS PUNK-ASAURUS
WILL BE CONFINED TO
THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM,
AND I'LL GRANT
THE CEASE-FIRE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
WAS THIS PART OF YOUR PLAN,
DOUCHER?
- OF COURSE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I KNEW THERE WAS NO WAY
WE COULD WIN AGAINST CLASS D
IN OUR CURRENT STATE.
SO I JUST FIGURED
NEGOTIATING A CEASE-FIRE
WAS THE BEST THING TO DO.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU STILL HURT
MY LOVE KITTEN,
AND THAT PART HASN'T CHANGED.
- ( groans )
AND I'M SO SORRY FOR THAT,
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY-- GAH!
- I'M ONLY LETTING YOU
OFF THE HOOK THIS EASILY
BECAUSE I BELIEVE SOME OF THE
THINGS YOU TOLD ME WERE TRUE.
- AAH!
- ( screams )
- SO JUST IMAGINE WHAT YOU'D
BE GETTING IF YOU HAD LIED.
- AND THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A SWEET DEAL.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S HEAD BACK.
GOOD JOB.
- All: YEAH!
- ( stammers )
( whimpers )
HUH?
AHH.
- IT'S SO GREAT
TO HAVE YOU BACK.
- Fukuhara: WITH THAT,
THE WAR WAS FINALLY OVER.
- WHAT'S THE SCOOP, KOUTA?
- IT LOOKS LIKE NEMOTO
AND CLASS B FINALLY GAVE UP.
- YEP.
JUST AS WE PREDICTED.
- GOOD.
I STILL CAN'T SEE
WHAT THEY WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN OUT OF IT ANYWAY.
- OH, YEAH. I PICKED THIS
THING UP LIKE YOU ASKED.
- WHAT ARE YOU
USING THAT FOR?
- Miharu: DID YOU REALLY
COME TO SHOVE YOUR SORRY
- WHAT?
- EXCUSE FOR LOVE IN MY FACE?
- NO, PLEASE TELL ME YOU DIDN'T.
- I MAY OR MAY NOT
HAVE RECORDED THAT
ENTIRE CONFERENCE.
- NO, WHAT IS IT REALLY?
IS IT SOME KIND OF NEAT NEW
AUDIOBOOK YOU FOUND?
- KEEP SQUEEZING.  HE'S STILL
GOT ENOUGH AIR TO TALK.
- STOP SQUIRMING LIKE THAT.
- LET ME GO!
- I GOT YOU NOW.
AND SORRY, I AM NOT
LETTING YOU GO.
- TURN IT OFF!
- YOU'RE BEING TOO LOUD.
I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
- Miharu: I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
MORE I WANT TO SAY TO YOU.
- ( muffled shouts )
THINGS AREN'T ALWAYS
EXACTLY THE WAY THEY SEEM.
- YEAH, I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
REALLY DATING MY BUTTERCUP.
THAT WAS PAINFULLY OBVIOUS.
- 'KAY.
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
UHH...
I PROMISE YOU,
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO RECOGNIZES
HOW AMAZING MINAMI IS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE STILL TRYING!
DO YOU NOT GET THAT I SAW YOU
SAY AWFUL THINGS TO HER?
I SAW YOU TREAT HER
LIKE A GUY,
AND I SAW HER CRYING
BECAUSE OF IT.
- OKAY, LISTEN.
I DON'T TREAT HER LIKE
A PRINCESS, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I'M PROBABLY ACTING
THE SAME WAY AROUND HER
AS I WOULD MY GUY FRIENDS
WITH THE WAY I JOKE AND STUFF.
BUT THAT'S BECAUSE...
- BECAUSE WHY?
BE CAREFUL.
- BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE TO.
MINAMI IS SOMEONE I CAN
JUST BE MYSELF AROUND.
I DON'T HAVE TO PUT ON
AN ACT FOR HER.
I LOVE HANGING OUT WITH HER
BECAUSE WE JUST GET
EACH OTHER'S WEIRDNESS.
YOU CAN'T KID AROUND
WITH MOST GIRLS LIKE THAT.
AND IT'S THE DUDE PART
THAT MAKES HER SO HOT.
( gasps )
- WHOA.
YOU JUST SAID SHE WAS HOT.
- YEAH, I HEARD IT TOO,
AND I DON'T DISAGREE, BUT I'M
SURPRISED YOU SAID IT OUT LOUD.
- ME TOO.  SO ROMANTIC.
- WHY?  WHY IS THIS
HAPPENING TO ME?
WHY DID THEY OUT OF ALL PEOPLE
HAVE TO HEAR IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT WAS
JUST SO SWEET AND BEAUTIFUL.
- YOU SAID THE DUDE PARTS
MADE HER HOT.
MY HEART IS BEATING SO FAST.
- YOU CAN BE YOURSELF
AROUND HER.
- Akihisa:
SOMEONE KILL ME, PLEASE.
THIS SUCKS.
- NO, DON'T STRETCH MY ARMS.
( giggles )
SIS!  OH MY GOSH,
YOU'RE HERE.
I MISSED YOU!
- HI.
I MISSED YOU TOO.
- OH, NO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOUR FACE LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN CRYING.
- I JUST--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- OH, NO, TEARS!
DID SOMEBODY CALL YOU
A NAME AT SCHOOL?  TELL ME.
- IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST--
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- THE WORST THING THAT
COULD HAVE POSSIBLY HAPPENED.
I'VE FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE,
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF HE LOVES ME BACK.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sighs )
I HATE TODAY SO MUCH.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO APOLOGIZE
TO MINAMI FOR WHAT I SAID?
- HEY.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU TODAY?
YOU LOOK LIKE CRAP, AKI.
- ( gasps )
MINAMI...
- THAT'S MY NAME.
- YEAH.  UH... IT IS.
I'M SORRY ABOUT YESTERDAY.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT,
SO YOU JUST TOLD ON YOURSELF.
WHAT LIES ARE YOU SPREADING?
- NOTHING!
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
- GOOD.  BECAUSE NEXT TIME
YOU PULL A STUNT LIKE THAT,
I'M NOT LETTING YOU OFF
WITHOUT A PUNCH.
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
YOU IDIOT.
- Fukuhara:
QUESTION NUMBER 11.
WHAT DO YOU CALL SOMEONE
YOU WERE CLOSE TO
WHEN YOU WERE SMALL?
- Yuuji:
A CHILDHOOD FR-- ( gagging )
- Shouko: A FIANCEE.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME, YUUJI,
SHOUKO, AND CHILDHOOD MEMORIES.
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.