- I WONDER...
WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
WHEN DID EVERYTHING CHANGE?
- IF I COULD DO IT
ALL OVER AGAIN,
IF I WAS ONLY
GIVEN THE CHANCE.
- Shouko: EVER SINCE THE MOMENT
I SAW HIS SHOULDERS TREMBLING.
THAT DAY, THAT PLACE.
- I WANT TO SET HER FREE.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE
HELD CAPTIVE BY THIS ANYMORE.
- NO, HE'S WRONG.
BECAUSE I KNOW THERE'S
MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
IN THE END,
I FOUND SOMETHING
MORE IMPORTANT.
- Both: I REMEMBER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- DID YOU HEAR THERE'S A WHIZ
KID IN MINAZUKI ELEMENTARY?
THAT RUMOR SNAKED ITS WAY
THROUGH THE SCHOOL
SEVERAL YEARS AGO.
THE WHIZ KID IN QUESTION
WAS INDEED SOMEWHAT SMARTER
THAN THE OTHER STUDENTS.
ON TOP OF THAT,
HE WAS UNUSUALLY FOCUSED
AND A DILIGENT HARD WORKER.
ALL THE ADULTS
SANG HIS PRAISES
AND HAD UNDERSTANDABLY
HIGH HOPES FOR HIM.
THEN ONE DAY...
- YOU ARE AMAZING, YUUJI.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE TEACHER KEPT
BRAGGING ABOUT YOUR SCORES
ON THE PREP TEST.
SHE CALLED YOU A BOY WONDER.
- YOU SAY THAT LIKE
I SHOULD CARE OR SOMETHING.
- DIDN'T YOU GET
EVEN BETTER SCORES
THAN THE KIDS FROM
JUNIOR HIGH?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- SEE, THAT'S AMAZING.
THOSE SIXTH GRADERS
WHO TOOK THE TEST WITH YOU
WERE NOT HAPPY
ABOUT IT EITHER.
- I MADE A MISTAKE
ON THE SOCIAL SCIENCE TEST.
OTHERWISE I WOULD HAVE
BEEN NUMBER ONE.
- Yuuji: BACK THEN, I ALWAYS
WANTED TO BE THE BEST.
I NEEDED IT.
- Young Shouko: I HEARD
YOU'RE GOING TO GET ADMITTED
TO THE BEST
JUNIOR HIGH AROUND
ON A RECOMMENDATION ALONE.
- YEAH, EASY ENOUGH FOR ME.
THOUGH, MOST OTHER KIDS
WON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- Yuuji: UNFORTUNATELY,
I HAD AN EGO
THAT WAS COMPLETELY INTERTWINED
WITH A SUPERIORITY COMPLEX.
- WILL YOU PLEASE
KEEP WORKING, SHOUKO?
I WANT TO FINISH THIS
SO I CAN GO HOME.
- ( sighs )
BUT I WAS HOPING
WE COULD STAY HERE
AND TALK FOR AWHILE.
- I WANT TO GO HOME.
- BUT I WANT TO TALK.
- I DON'T.
- YES.
- I SAID NO.
- NO!
- YOU WANT TO KNOW SOMETHING?
I THINK MY BOOBS ARE
GETTING BIGGER AND BIGGER
EVERY DAY.
- ( grunts )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
YUUJI?
- SERIOUSLY? WHERE IN THE
HELL DID THAT COME FROM?
- YOU WERE ATTEMPTING
TO IGNORE ME,
SO I DECIDED TO
BRING UP SOMETHING
A BOY WOULD FIND
INTERESTING.
- NICE TRY,
BUT I STILL DON'T CARE.
- Yuuji: THAT MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN ENTIRELY TRUE.
- WILL YOU PLEASE JUST
GET BACK TO WORK?
- I DON'T MIND WORKING.
BUT I WANT TO TALK
WITH YOU TOO.
- DON'T YOU EVER
TALK TO YOUR FRIENDS?
- YES.  THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO NOW.
- YEAH, LUCKY ME.
- Yuuji:
SHOUKO DIDN'T QUITE FIT IN
WITH THE REST OF THE SCHOOL.
SHE CAME FROM
A WELL-KNOWN FAMILY,
WAS AT THE TOP OF HER CLASS,
HAD INCREDIBLE
ATHLETIC TALENT,
AND OF COURSE,
WAS BEAUTIFUL.
SHE WAS THE LUCKY ONE,
AND EVERYONE
RESENTED HER FOR IT.
- GOOD MORNING.
MY NAME IS SHOUKO.
- ( kids murmuring )
- HMM.
- DUDE, YOU SHOULD
GO TALK TO HER.
- WHY? YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WANTS TO, YOU BUTT HEAD.
- YEAH. I THINK YOU WANT HER TO
BE YOUR VERY FIRST GIRLFRIEND.
- NO I DON'T.
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS THAT KIRISHIMA GIRL
TRYING TO ACT TOO CUTE?
- HER FAMILY'S RICH.
I BET SHE'S A SPOILED PRINCESS.
- SHE'S NOT EASY TO TALK TO,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- Students: I KNOW, RIGHT?
- Yuuji: WITH THE WAY ALL
THOSE KIDS BEHAVED TOWARDS HER,
IT'S NO WONDER SHOUKO
ENDED UP GETTING ATTACHED TO ME.
AFTER ALL,
I TREATED EVERYONE THE SAME,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- SO IT'S ALREADY
BEEN TWO YEARS
SINCE YOU TRANSFERRED
TO THIS SCHOOL, HASN'T IT?
- YEAH.  I HAVE MORE FRIENDS
NOW THAN I DID BACK THEN.
I DON'T HAVE A WHOLE LOT,
BUT SCHOOL'S MORE FUN
THAN IT USED TO BE.
- WAIT.  YOU THINK
SCHOOL IS FUN?
- WELL, WHEN I'M AT HOME,
NO ONE PLAYS WITH ME
OR EVEN TALKS TO ME
FOR THE MOST PART.
AND THE HOUSE IS SO BIG,
I GET LONELY.
SO, YEAH.
SCHOOL IS FUN IN COMPARISON.
- JEEZ.
CRY ME A RIVER.
I WISH I COULD FEEL
LONELY AND SAD
IN A BIG HOUSE LIKE THAT.
- YOU CAN COME HANG OUT
AT MY HOUSE IF YOU WANT TO.
- I DON'T. IT'S LIKE 100
TIMES MORE FUN READING
THAN HANGING OUT WITH YOU.
- Shouko: THAT WAS MEAN.
- JUST BEING HONEST.
- Shouko: STICK IN THE MUD.
- SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT TO SAY.
- Shouko: PIG-HEADED.
- KEEP IT UP.
- OH, YUUJI?
- HMM?
- I THINK YOU MIGHT HAVE
A LITTLE CRUSH ON ME.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT, YOU'RE TOO
NERVOUS TO HANG OUT AT MY HOME.
- WHY DO YOU WANT ME
TO GO TO YOUR HOUSE
SO BADLY
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- WELL...
- WELL, WHAT?
SPIT IT OUT.
- MY GRANDFATHER
TALKS ABOUT SENDING ME
TO AN ALL-GIRLS'
ACADEMY A LOT.
- ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT
FAMOUS RICHY SCHOOL FOR CHICKS?
ARE YOU GONNA
CHANGE SCHOOLS AGAIN?
- PROBABLY.
HE SEEMS TO THINK
I GET PICKED ON
MORE THAN MOST KIDS
AT SCHOOL DO.
- SO YOU WANT TO SHOW OFF
YOUR FRIENDS TO YOUR FAMILY
SO THEY WON'T THINK
YOU'RE LONELY AND MISERABLE?
- I DON'T--
I DON'T WANT TO
CHANGE SCHOOLS.
I ACTUALLY HAVE MADE SOME
FRIENDS BESIDES YOU,
SO YOU KNOW.
- THEN TAKE THOSE WEIRDOES
TO YOUR HOUSE.
- WE'RE NOT CLOSE ENOUGH
FOR THAT YET.
- OH.
WELL, EITHER WAY, THAT'S GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
- Yuuji: I TREATED EVERYONE
THE SAME NO MATTER WHAT.
I WAS EQUALLY UNINTERESTED
IN ALL OF THEM.
AT LEAST,
THAT'S WHAT I TOLD MYSELF.
- THAT WAS MEAN, YUUJI.
- NO, IT WASN'T.
- WAS TOO.
- WAS NOT.
- YUUJI.
- HMM.
- IN OUR ENTIRE CLASS,
I'VE GOT THE BIGGEST
OF THE BOOBIES.
- ( Young Yuuji grunts )
SHOUKO!
- Yuuji: EVEN SO,
THE ATTENTION I GAVE
SEEMED TO BE ENOUGH
FOR A GIRL WHO HAPPENED
TO BE VERY LONELY.
- WHAT'S UP, SAKAMOTO?
- ( sighs )
- ( boys panting )
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING, FREAK?
- WE GOT SOMETHING
WE WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
AND THIS IS WHY I WANTED
TO HEAD HOME EARLIER.
- WHAT?
CAN'T HEAR YOU, TURD.
- TURD, REALLY?
WHAT DO YOU ALL WANT?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO WASTE ON A BUNCH OF LOSERS.
- SHUT UP! TRY AND HAVE A LITTLE
RESPECT FOR YOUR ELDERS.
- SURE ARE A SMART ASS
FOR A FIFTH GRADE BABY.
- ( sighs )
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS
SINCE I BEAT YOUR SCORES
ON THAT TEST, HAVEN'T YOU?
DON'T YOU HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO,
LIKE FRIENDS
TO HANG OUT WITH?
OR MAYBE YOU GUYS
ARE TOO PATHETIC
TO HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
- ( boys gasp )
- UH, NO.  YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO DOESN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
- DON'T THINK YOU'RE
BETTER THAN US,
JUST 'CAUSE YOU GOT
A FEW GOOD TEST SCORES.
- WE'RE IN THE SIXTH GRADE,
KID.
WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
- WATCH MY MOUTH?
ARE YOU GUYS STUPID
OR WHAT?
THE ONLY REASON PEOPLE
CENSOR WHAT THEY SAY
IS TO BE RESPECTFUL.
AND WHY THE HELL WOULD I
EVER WANT TO RESPECT
A GROUP OF IDIOTS LIKE YOU?
- YOU CAN'T SAY THAT.
WE'RE OLDER THAN YOU.
- TRUE. YEAH, YOU'RE A
WHOLE YEAR OLDER THAN ME,
HOWEVER, I'M THE ONE
WHO DID BETTER ON THAT TEST.
YOU GUYS ARE HILARIOUS.
YOU SHOULD SHOW A LITTLE MORE
RESPECT TO ME.
- ( grunts )
- SAY THAT AGAIN,
I DARE YOU.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IF SOMETHING HAPPENS TO ME,
THE TEACHERS WILL
DEFINITELY FIND OUT.
I MEAN, I AM THE BOY WONDER,
AFTER ALL.
GET LOST.
- ( kids groan )
- ALSO, I DON'T EVER
WANT TO SEE YOU JERKS AGAIN.
- THAT KIDS LIKE
TOTALLY PISSES ME OFF.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
TEACH HIM A LESSON,
- SPECIFICALLY?
- WELL, IF WE CAN'T TOUCH HIM,
WE CAN AT LEAST MESS WITH
HIS LOCKER OR SOMETHING.
- YEAH, THEN HE CAN'T
RAT US OUT.
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
LET'S TEACH THAT
LITTLE PUNK SOME MANNERS.
- ( kids chuckle )
- I'M HOME.
- OH, YAY.
MY BABY BOY IS BACK.
YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE TODAY,
AREN'T YOU?
- YEAH, I HAD TO FINISH UP
SOME CLASS REP STUFF AT SCHOOL.
- OH, WELL, I GUESS THAT
DOES MAKE THE MOST SENSE,
BUT FOR SOME REASON
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SPENDING
A LITTLE QUALITY TIME WITH
YOUR LOVELY FRIEND, SHOUKO.
- WHY THE CRAP WOULD I WANT
TO HANG OUT WITH SHOUKO?
DON'T BE STUPID.
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU
TWO WERE FRIENDS.
- YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
- YOU SHOULD BE.
THAT GIRL IS GOING TO BE
INCREDIBLY GORGEOUS
WHEN SHE GETS
A LITTLE OLDER.
ALTHOUGH BY THAT TIME,
IT MIGHT BE TOO LATE
AND ALL YOU'LL BE LEFT WITH
IS REGRET.
ACCEPT IT, SHE'LL BE
AS CUTE AS ME SOME DAY.
- LET IT GO, MOM. BESIDES,
YOU'RE NOT THAT PRETTY ANYWAY.
- YUUJI, THAT'S MEAN.
- I'LL BE LATE AGAIN TOMORROW.
- OH?  MORE WORK FOR
YOUR CLASS AGAIN?
- NO. I HAVE A LITTLE
SOMETHING
I NEED TO TEACH
SOME SIXTH GRADERS.
- SIXTH GRADERS?
- LONG STORY.
- OHH.
- WHAT'S WITH THE APRON?
PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE
NOT MAKING DINNER?
- ( chuckles )
I'M MAKING MEAT AND POTATO STEW.
IT'S YOUR FAVORITE.
I'VE BEEN PEELING
THE SWEET POTATOES--
- MOM, YOU CAN'T PUT
SWEET POTATOES IN A STEW!
- BUT WHY NOT? I THOUGHT
THEY WERE BETTER FOR YOU
THAN REGULAR POTATOES.
AND THEY DON'T
GET AS SOFT EITHER.
- THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO GET SOFT,
AND I DON'T CARE
IF THEY'RE BETTER
FOR ME OR NOT.
( sighs ) AT LEAST IT
MIGHT BE EDIBLE THIS TIME.
- OH. I FORGOT TO BUY
MEAT AT THE STORE,
SO I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
WE'RE HAVING MEATLESS
MEAT AND POTATO STEW.
- ARE YOU SAYING
WE'RE JUST HAVING
STEAMED SWEET POTATOES?
- Yuuji:
SINCE THEY COULDN'T BEAT ME UP,
I KNEW THEY'D TRY TO
DO SOMETHING TO MY STUFF.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY I PROVOKED
THEM IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- ( chuckles )
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
I GRABBED THE THINGS I DON'T
WANT THEM TO MESS WITH
FROM MY LOCKER AND
KEPT THEM WITH ME.
- Yuuji:
I THOUGHT I'D KILL TIME
UNTIL THE SIXTH GRADERS
MADE THEIR MOVE.
ONCE THEY STARTED IN
ON MY LOCKER,
I PLANNED ON GOING
TO GET A TEACHER.
- OKAY.
IN THE MEANTIME,
I'LL START READING ANOTHER BOOK.
- Yuuji: AT THAT TIME,
I BELIEVED I WAS A HERO.
MOSTLY BECAUSE I ALSO BELIEVED
I WAS BETTER THAN EVERYONE ELSE.
- WEIRD.
WHERE'S SHOUKO BEEN ALL DAY?
SHE HASN'T FOLLOWED ME
AROUND LIKE SHE USUALLY DOES.
Young Yuuji:
BAKA AND TEST.
- Shouko: BACK THEN,
I SPENT AS MUCH TIME
AS YUUJI WOULD LET ME
FOLLOWING HIM AROUND.
I DIDN'T EVEN CARE
THAT HE WASN'T ALWAYS
VERY NICE TO ME.
HE TREATED ME JUST LIKE
HE TREATED EVERYONE ELSE,
AND I LIKED THAT.
- ( gasps )
I WONDER IF
YUUJI IS STILL HERE.
HMM?
- Shouko: I ENJOYED
BEING AROUND HIM.
I SIMPLY COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
- DAMN IT.
NOT HERE EITHER.
- THAT GUY'S SUCH A PUNK.
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SOMEBODY ELSE DECIDED
THEY WANTED TO
HIDE HIS SHOES TOO,
SO THEY JUST BEAT US
TO THE PUNCH.
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
THAT NERD DOESN'T HAVE
A LOT OF FRIENDS.
HE GETS PICKED ON
ALL THE TIME.
- THERE'S PLENTY OF
OTHER STUFF WE CAN MESS WITH.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS
THINK WE SHOULD WRITE?
- HOW ABOUT "I LIKE TO
CHEAT ON ALL MY TESTS"?
SOUND GOOD?
- Both: HELL YEAH!
- STOP THAT NOW!
- ( boys gasp )
- THOSE ARE--
THEY'RE NOT YOURS.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- UM, WELL...
IT'S JUST THAT
THOSE ARE YUUJI'S.
AND YOU SHOULDN'T BE
MESSING WITH THEM.
- WHAT?!
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
YUUJI IS MY FRIEND.
- IF YUUJI FINDS OUT
WHAT I'M DOING,
HE'S GOING TO BE
SO MAD AT ME.
SO I THOUGHT...
NONETHELESS.
- YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
STOP!
- I DIDN'T THINK
HE HAD ANY FRIENDS.
- I KNOW.
AND SHE'S A GIRL.
- COME ON, GUYS.
WHO CARES ABOUT HER?
LET'S JUST DO WHAT
WE CAME HERE TO DO.
- GOOD POINT.
- THIS IS GONNA BE AWESOME.
- STOP IT!
- HEY, LET GO OF ME.
- I THOUGHT YUUJI
WOULD GET MAD.
AND I WAS AFRAID
HE'D TELL THOSE BOYS
I WASN'T REALLY HIS FRIEND.
- ( grunts )
- PLEASE STOP IT!
- ENOUGH ALREADY!
GO AWAY.
- ( gasps )
- SHE'S CRAZY.
- FOR REAL. WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?
- STOP!
- YOU'RE ASKING FOR
IT, YOU KNOW THAT?
- BUT I DIDN'T CARE
WHAT THEY SAID.
- LET GO!
- ( straining )
- NO! ( gasps )
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( gasps )
- AAH.  LOOK AT WHAT
YOU DID TO MY NEW SHIRT,
YOU STUPID BRAT.
NOW I'M PISSED.
- PLEASE DON'T. I'M SORRY.
- IT'S TOO LATE FOR SORRY.
- ( gasps )
- WELL, I WONDER IF THEY'VE
FALLEN INTO MY TRAP YET.
ALL RIGHT,
THEY'RE DOING IT.
- ( boys chattering )
- NOT FUNNY!
- ( gasps )
THE HELL'S GOING ON?
WHY'S SHOUKO IN THERE?
DON'T TELL ME.
- IT WAS OBVIOUS WHY
SHOUKO HAD BEEN DRAGGED INTO IT.
EITHER WAY, SHE NEEDED
SOMEONE TO HELP HER OUT.
- I HAVE TO SAVE HER.
- YES.  LIKE THE HERO
THAT I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE.
PLUS THOSE GUYS WERE
ALL PRACTICALLY IDIOTS.
IT WAS ME THAT WAS THE OVERLY
INTELLIGENT SPECIAL ONE.
NOT TO MENTION, WE WERE
IN COMPLETELY DIFFERENT LEAGUES,
SO WHY HESITATE?
- I'LL BE FINE.
DON'T BE SCARED.
GUYS LIKE THEM...
THEY'RE NO BIG DEAL.
- DON'T KID YOURSELF, BUDDY.
THERE ARE THREE OF THEM.
- HEY, I KNOW.
I'LL GO GET A TEACHER.
BUT WHAT ABOUT SHOUKO?
- THE TEACHER'S GONNA
TELL HER PARENTS,
AND THEN THEY'LL
THINK THEIR LITTLE GIRL
GETS PICKED ON ALL THE TIME.
- THEY'LL MAKE SHOUKO
CHANGE SCHOOLS FOR SURE.
( grunts ) WHATEVER. WHAT
ELSE AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT HAS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH ME ANYWAY.
- WHAT ELSE CAN YOU DO?
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
YOU CAN DO, YUUJI.
- ( grunts )
MAN, THIS SUCKS!
I JUST WANTED
TO MAKE THEM PAY
FOR BEING SO MEAN TO ME!
- OKAY, THEN PRETEND
YOU DIDN'T SEE THIS
AND WALK AWAY.
- YOU KNOW THERE'S
NO WAY I CAN DO THAT.
- NO MATTER WHAT
CHOICE YOU MAKE,
YOU'RE GONNA GET HURT.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
YOU'LL BE THE ONE WHO PAYS.
THAT BEING SAID, YOU'VE GOTTA
DO WHAT YOU'VE GOTTA DO.
- WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THREE SIXTH GRADERS HERE.
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
NO WAY I CAN BEAT THOSE GUYS.
- HOW DO YOU THINK
SHOUKO FEELS ABOUT IT?
- YEAH, BUT STILL...
- I KNOW. GETTING BEAT UP
IS PRETTY SCARY, ISN'T IT?
- OF COURSE, DUH!
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE A HERO.
- BUT A TRUE HERO WOULDN'T
EXACTLY HESITATE, RIGHT?
EVEN IF HE WAS TOTALLY
SURE HE WAS GONNA LOSE.
YEAH, HE'D DO IT.
- SHUT UP!
THAT STUFF ONLY HAPPENS
IN THE MOVIES, ASS!
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
BEEN ACTING BETTER THAN
THOSE GUYS IN THE FIRST PLACE,
RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH, BUT THEIR SCORES--
- IT'S NOT EASY BEING SMART,
IS IT?
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
BUT QUIT MAKING
ASININE EXCUSES
AND TRYING TO FIND
A WAY OUT OF THIS.
- SO WHAT, ARE YOU TELLING ME
IT'S BETTER TO BE AN IDIOT?
- ( chuckles )
I GUESS SO.
AN IDIOT WHO'D JUMP IN THERE
TO SAVE HER WITHOUT EVEN
STOPPING TO THINK?
YEAH, HE'D BE A HELL OF
A LOT COOLER THAN YOU ARE.
- I DON'T GET IT.
I DON'T GET WHY ALL THIS
IS HAPPENING TO ME.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING,
SO WHY AM I THE ONE
WHO HAS TO SUFFER?
THIS ISN'T MY FAULT AT ALL.
IF ANYONE'S TO BLAME,
IT'S THOSE GUYS FOR BEING
INSECURE JERKS,
AND SHOUKO FOR BUTTING IN.
IT'S THEIR FAULT.
SO WHY IS THIS
HAPPENING TO ME?!
( exhales )
WHAT'S MORE...
SHOUKO SHOULD BE SCREAMING
FOR HELP RIGHT NOW.
ALL SHE HAS TO DO IS ASK.
SAY IT, SHOUKO.
JUST SAY "SOMEBODY HELP ME"
ALREADY,
AND THEN EVEN IF
THE TEACHERS FIND OUT
AND HER PARENTS MAKE HER
CHANGE SCHOOLS,
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF HER,
NOT ME.
IT'S STILL NOT MY FAULT.
YEAH.  THAT WORKS.
COME ON, SHOUKO.
- Young Shouko: STOP.
- SAY IT.  ASK FOR HELP.
CHANGING SCHOOLS IS BETTER
THAN BEING PICKED ON, RIGHT?
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
JUST SAY THE WORDS.
ASK FOR HELP.
SAY IT.  SAY IT.
SAY IT!
- I WON'T.
I WON'T SAY IT.
THEY'LL MAKE ME
CHANGE SCHOOLS AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
WHY?
HEY, YOU GUYS ARE
A BUNCH OF JERKS!
- ( boys gasp )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU'RE HERE.
- DON'T YOU ASSHOLES REALIZE
HOW CRAZY PATHETIC YOU ALL ARE?
WHAT KIND OF GUY
BEATS UP ON A GIRL?
- SAKAMOTO?
- LOOK WHO DECIDED TO SHOW UP.
- COME ON,
LET'S GO HOME, SHOUKO.
- WAIT.  SORRY, BRO.
NOT SO FAST.
YOU TWO AREN'T
GOING ANYWHERE.
- ( sighs )
- YUUJI.
- SHOUKO IS GOING HOME.
- BUT--
- NOW.
- ( gasps )
I'LL GO GET A TEACHER.
- NO, DON'T BE AN IDIOT.
JUST GO HOME.
I DON'T WANT YOU HERE
GETTING IN MY WAY.
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
YEAH, OKAY THEN.
I'M GONNA GO HOME.
- ( shouting )
- Yuuji:
THAT WAS THE DAY I REALIZED
HOW IMMATURE
I REALLY WAS.
I'D NEVER FELT SO MISERABLE,
PITIFUL, AND EMBARRASSED.
- ( boys grunting )
- Shouko: AFTER SEEING YUUJI'S
SHOULDERS TREMBLING LIKE THAT,
I WAS SO MAD AT MYSELF
FOR NOT BEING ABLE TO HELP.
- Yuuji: I CREATED A REASON FOR
SHOUKO TO GET THE WRONG IDEA.
IT WAS ALL A MISTAKE.
IT WAS MY RESPONSIBILITY
AND I HAVE TO MAKE UP FOR IT.
- ( shouts )
- IT WASN'T.
YOU'RE WRONG, YUUJI.
THERE'S MORE TO OUR STORY.
YOU JUST NEVER KNEW.
- WELL, LOOK WHO'S BACK HOME.
HEY THERE.
I GOT A CALL FROM
THE SCHOOL EARLIER.
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
- I'M FINE.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
- OH, NO, HONEY.
OBVIOUSLY THAT IS NOT TRUE.
THEY TOLD ME THAT
YOU GOT INTO A FIGHT TODAY.
- WHAT CAN I SAY? A COUPLE
OF GUYS PISSED ME OFF.
- YUUJI, ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT?
- YEAH, THAT'S ALL.
THEY PISSED ME OFF,
SO I PUNCHED THEM.
WILL YOU PLEASE
GET OFF MY BACK ALREADY?
- THEY MADE YOU MAD,
RIGHT.
- I'M SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT.
HE WAS ONLY
TRYING TO PROTECT ME.
I'M SORRY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU'VE ALREADY
TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED,
AND I PROMISE YOU, EVERYTHING
IS GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
- HOW CAN IT BE? HE'S GONNA
BE KNOWN AS A BAD KID.
AND HE WON'T GET THAT
RECOMMENDATION
FOR JUNIOR HIGH NOW.
- ( chuckles )
I DON'T CARE ABOUT ALL THAT.
OH, SHOUKO, LISTEN.
YUUJI FOUND OUT
THERE'S MORE TO HIM
THAN JUST BEING A SMART KID.
WITHOUT YOU, HE NEVER COULD
HAVE REALIZED THAT.
SO I'M ACTUALLY
VERY GRATEFUL.
- ( gasps )
HMM.
- ( chuckles )
- MRS. SAKAMOTO?
- WHAT IS IT, SHOUKO?
I'M ALL EARS.
- UM, WHEN I GROW UP...
WELL, I'M GOING
TO MARRY YUUJI.
- ARE YOU POSITIVE?
IT IS A BIG DECISION.
- I PROMISE I'LL
MAKE HIM HAPPY.
- ( chuckles )
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE TRUTH, DEAR,
THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING
HE SHOULD SAY TO YOU.
- ( sighs )
I WON'T DISAGREE.
- WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO MAKE SURE HE SAYS
THE VERY SAME LINE
TO YOU ONE DAY.
- REALLY?
- YES, REALLY.
NOW THAT IS OF COURSE
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
STOP LIKING HIM
SO MUCH BY THEN, 'KAY?
- OH, I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
I WILL LIKE YUUJI FOREVER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 12,
WHAT DO YOU CALL IT WHEN
A MYSTERIOUS GROUP
STAKES CLAIM
TO A SPECIFIC PLACE
FOR NO REASON?
- DUDES WHO ARE POPULAR WITH
CHICKS ARE OUR SWORN ENEMIES.
- Fukuhara: I'M TALKING
ABOUT YOU, BY THE WAY.
- Akihisa: NEXT EPISODE,
IDIOTS, CLOWNERY, AND REQUIEM.
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.