[NAEGI] We're here in
the courtroom again.
As much as I'd hoped
it was a one-time thing,
we've had another murder.
[NAEGI] And now it's on
us to find the killer,
or we'll be the next to die!
I hope we can pull this off...
[MONOKUMA] Well then, my sweet
and tender hooligans,
why don't we kick things off
by talking about
the murder weapon?
According to the
Monokuma Files,
the victim was struck in the
head with a blunt object,
leading to what was most
likely an immediate demise.
Yes, but what could it've been?
Hey, I bet it was
a metal pipe!
No, that wasn't the weapon!
Duh, right! What
was I thinking?!
There weren't any pipes
at the scene of the crime,
so I don't think it was that.
The circumference of the injury
matched the weight at the
end of a small dumbbell.
Wait! You checked out
her crunched-in head?!
Ahhh! I bet
there were brains!
Given the bloodstains
we found on the carpet,
I think it's safe to assume the
crime was committed right there,
in the girls' locker room.
Thus, it's high time
to name the culprit.
Would you care to
rack your brains,
or shall I just
tell you who it is?
You know who did it?!
[TOGAMI] Obviously...
Chihiro Fujisaki's killer is...
Genocider Sho!
Wait a minute. That serial
killer who was in the news?
Whatever, brah!
But wouldn't that have to
mean that raving lunatic
is one of us?!
That's crazy-talk!
[NAEGI] It's not as
crazy as you think.
Togami and I found a dossier
on the killer in the library.
[TOGAMI] It called attention to
recurring motifs throughout
all of Genocider Sho's murders:
Two rituals, or calling
cards, in particular...
First, Sho always leaves a
message written in blood.
[YAMADA] Yes, "Funbag fever,"
if I'm not mistaken.
"Blood bath fever," y'mean?
The second motif is important,
as it's never been disseminated
to the public at large.
Without fail, every one
of Sho's victims
has been found crucified.
Thus, having found her
in such a unique state,
it's only natural to assume
that Fujisaki was slain
by the selfsame villain.
To wit...
we have an incredibly violent
serial killer within our ranks?
Indeed.
And she goes by the name...
Touko Fukawa!
Wha-?! I--! Uh...!
Hey, wait just a second!
Fukawa freaks out
at the sight of blood,
and whoever's been killing
those folks is not squeamish!
I think it would be fair to say
she's a "Sho", and a "no-Sho."
Word-play, seriously?
Our lives are at stake!
[NAEGI] "Fukawa's a Sho,
and a no-Sho"...?
What's Togami getting at?
[NAEGI] Yeah!
That's gotta be it!
They mentioned it in that
file from the library!
Listen to this:
They think Sho's suffering from
"dissociative
identity disorder."
I trust that will suffice?
[FUKAWA whimpers]
You...
You promised that would be
our little secret, Togami!
[TOGAMI] Be a good girl,
why don't you,
and let the lady in
question tell us the rest.
[FUKAWA screams]
[ALL gasp]
[FUKAWA (SHO)]
Guess that's my cue to tag in,
ain't it, bitches?!
[ALL scream]
Well, ain't that a kick
in the baby-maker!
You figured out
who I am! Behold!
The Super High School-Level
Serial Killer...
Genocider Sho!
Touko Fukawa's just the
craptastic name I was born with!
Wh-What on earth's
gotten into you?!
[FUKAWA (SHO) cackles]
Not enough these days,
if ya know what I mean!
Why? You volunteering?!
This new persona
we're seeing is...
nothing like Fukawa.
And so, we have
found our killer.
Fujisaki was slain
by Genocider Sho.
She had clear motive.
[OHGAMI] What would that be?
Fukawa did not want
anyone to discover
her bloodthirsty alter ego--
It was her secret...
A secret worth killing for.
Not a bad theory...
And kinda clever for a dude!
Too bad it's totally
wrong, blondie!
I'm actually innocent
for a change!
[OHGAMI] Why should we
believe a serial killer?
[ASAHINA] Ohgami's right!
I'm not about to take some
serial killer's word for it!
We've established it
could've been her.
But are we certain
she's our only suspect?
Face it. Sho has a very
specific modus operandi,
and it matches
this death to a tee.
[NAEGI gasps]
It's close,
but not quite!
Then how does it differ?
Toldja I didn't
do it this time!
Suck it, Sherlock!
[TOGAMI gasps]
Buy this bastard
a clue, huh?
I take pride in what I do,
which means I'm a
stickler for the details!
[NAEGI] She's right!
What about the killing blow?
All of Sho's other victims
had been stabbed to death.
Not a single one was bludgeoned.
[TOGAMI] Huh...
Why go with blunt force
trauma when I can just
grab some skizzers and
paint the town red?
[NAEGI] And the crucifixion
didn't match Sho's M.O., either.
Fujisaki was tied to the rack
with an extension cord, right?
But Sho's never tied her
victims up with anything.
She pins them up with those
scissors she loves so much.
Give the kid a cigar!
I use scissors on my trophies,
so I can stick 'em
right to the wall!
Don't want 'em crumpled in a
heap when the cops find 'em.
How considerate...
What's the one thing all my
victims have had in common?!
[NAEGI gasps]
One thing they've
all had in common...
I forgot!
Genocider Sho doesn't
kill women! Only men!
Damn, this kid is on fire!
Yup! I only cut up the
guys who get me going
in the "southern hemisphere,"
if ya catch my drift!
Oh! I mentioned my naughty bits!
How terribly, horribly
unladylike of me!
We're gathered here in
the pursuit of justice.
Your twisted kinks aren't
germane to the issue at hand.
Ah, shut your hole,
ass-face!
[TOGAMI gasps]
Ass-face...?
[FUKAWA (SHO)]
I stick to my style,
even if it means I gotta
blow my damn cover!
♪ Dun dun duuuuuun! ♪
[YAMADA] Where the hell'd
those come from?!
I got more of 'em on me,
if anyone wants to
go treasure-huntin'!
Give it a rest! Crucifixion's
your bag, scissors or otherwise!
It said so in the
cops' secret file!
Wasn't that why we thought
it was the real Genocider Sho,
and not some copycat?
Hold up a second...
There is one other person
who knew that detail...
Togami.
[ALL gasp]
[NAEGI] When we looked at that
file together in the library,
didn't you say:
[TOGAMI] I assure you,
these are genuine.
They match the copies
in my study at home.
[NAEGI] Frankly...
I wouldn't be surprised
if you knew Sho's methods
before we even got here.
S-So we're locked in here
with a serial killer
and a copycat?!
You were privy to
Fukawa's secret,
and hoped to pin your crime
to her other persona.
What have you to say
for yourself?!
Answer us!
I say, where's
your evidence?
You're not off
the hook just yet.
The extension cord used
to crucify Fujisaki
was not unknown to me.
I noticed its
presence in the library,
where you spent a fair amount
of time prior to the murder.
[TOGAMI] That's your proof?
So I killed Fujisaki in
the girls' locker room,
and then strung her up so
as to emulate the victims
of a known murderer,
throwing suspicion elsewhere
and covering my tracks.
Does that sum it up?
[NAEGI] We've got
him on the ropes,
so why is he so calm?
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] Wait!
Was the crime really committed
in the girls' locker room?
[OHGAMI] Huh...
After I was done with
my workout last night,
I spilled my protein
coffee on this rug,
but now there's no sign
of the stain that it left.
[NAEGI] Huh?
[NAEGI] I gotta wonder...
What if the killer switched the
contents of the locker rooms
to throw us off the trail?
[YAMADA]
Great Caesar's ghost!
[OHGAMI] So...
Togami swapped out
the rooms, then?
[NAEGI] There was a
swimsuit model poster
in the girls' locker room...
And a poster of some
boy-band over on our side.
[HAGAKURE] Man, it's backwards!
[NAEGI] You're right...
Which means...
Fujisaki wasn't killed in the
girls' locker room,
but in our locker room!
It's the only way it works!
What do you mean?!
[HAGAKURE] Wait...
So how did that chick get into
our locker room
in the first place?
Quite simple, actually.
Our Fujisaki...
was a boy.
[TOGAMI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[KIRIGIRI] I found out
when I checked the body.
[MONOKUMA] Righty-o!
Little Miss Fujisaki...
was a dude in a dress!
So, he was
cross-dressing, huh?
Oh, that's so hot...
I wish I HAD killed him.
[HAGAKURE] Yeah, but...
that doesn't really change
the fact that Togami did it.
[NAEGI] Actually,
I think it does.
What prompted the
change of heart?
Because...
when we found out a second ago
that Fujisaki was a guy,
you were as surprised
as all the rest of us.
But the real killer
already knew.
Therefore, you
can't be our culprit!
Hah. I guess that works.
Your evidence is purely
circumstantial,
but it clears my name.
As theories go, it'll do.
It's exactly as Naegi claims!
I'm not the guilty party!
[gasping]
That said, I found her
in the locker room
and did tamper with
the state of the body.
You smug bastard!
You get off on this, huh?!
I was testing your
powers of deduction
and unnerving the killer
with this late revelation.
[ISHIMARU] You...
you're still lying to us!
You're well within your
rights not to believe me.
But don't forget what happens
if you convict in error.
If you wish to see tomorrow,
help me find the killer.
--Squirrelly son of a--!
--So be it...
Let's speak of the case further.
Excellent!
Our little guessing game's
found its second wind.
[CELESTIA] Tell me something...
How, pray tell, was the culprit
able to enter both locker rooms
without being
shot to pieces?
Easily. I found
the digital notebooks
of the deceased
students in the foyer.
Huh? What are you getting at?
[CELESTIA] If I'm
not mistaken,
it means either gender
could use them
and gain access to both rooms.
[KIRIGIRI] No... Kuwata's
digital notebook was broken.
It's useless.
[ASAHINA] So in other words,
the killer has to be a guy?
[CELESTIA] Yes, but isn't using
another student's device
in direct violation
of the school rules?
[TOGAMI] The rule in question
prohibits the lending
of our digital notebooks.
It says nothing
about taking them.
[MONOKUMA] Yup!
Trust Fund called it!
So all we really know about
Fujisaki's killer right now
is that he's of the
male persuasion?
[NAEGI] What am I not seeing?
There's gotta be
something, right?
Celestia, didn't you say...
that you saw Fujisaki
on the night he died?
Indeed...
He was headed somewhere
and had a long-sleeve jersey
stuffed into a duffel bag.
Alas, we found no such
shirt at the crime scene.
The killer must have
disposed of it earlier on.
But did he leave behind
any clues as to its fate?
[OHGAMI] If I
remember correctly,
we have a lot of jerseys
at our disposal.
[ASAHINA] Yeah, and a bunch
of different colors, right?
[YAMADA chuckles]
I don't even have a jersey.
They don't fit me right.
Yeah! Mine's white!
Looks pretty bitchin'.
You said Fujisaki was on
his way to meet with someone,
didn't you?
So, what if they
picked out their
jerseys together?
Yes! That's it!
Fujisaki's jersey must
match that of his killer!
You're saying,
whoever killed him
has to have a matching
blue jersey, huh?
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
[NAEGI gasps]
[OHWADA] Well, looks like
I'm off the hook, at least.
I grabbed me a black one.
Shoulda kept your
mouth shut!
What the hell, bro?
You trying to start somethin'?
Looks like Naegi
caught it, also.
Ohwada, you just
made a fatal blunder.
Mm-hmm...
The jersey...
We talked about
him having one, but...
we never said it was blue.
[OHWADA gasps]
Think about it, man:
Celestia never even
mentioned the color.
What're you
gettin' at, bro?!
[KIRIGIRI] It seems you've
dug your own grave, Ohwada.
I didn't dig nothing!
You poor sap,
I'm afraid you did.
The logic of your
feint was very sound.
You gave him just enough
rope to hang himself.
So to speak.
No, you're wrong!
My friend Mondo would
never stoop to homicide!
[ISHIMARU] Tell them
how wrong they are!
This is all a mistake!
It has to be!
I don't know how you guessed
that the shirt was blue,
but that doesn't mean
you murdered Fujisaki!
It's not true!
He's innocent! Why are you
all trying to frame him?!
[NAEGI] We have to be sure.
Let's look at the case again,
starting from the beginning.
This will prove whether
our verdict is right or wrong!
[NAEGI] It was nighttime...
Fujisaki left the storage
room, duffel bag in tow.
There was a blue jersey
inside that bag.
Fujisaki headed off for
the boys' locker room.
But how was her digital notebook
able to get her inside?
Turns out...
Fujisaki was actually a boy.
Someone was in the locker
room, waiting for him.
Whoever Fujisaki met up with
is the very person
who killed him.
He grabbed whatever was handy,
in this case a dumbbell,
and attacked.
Once the deed was done,
he needed to confuse us,
so he flip-flopped the contents
of the two locker rooms.
To get into the
girls' locker room,
he just needed to grab Maizono's
or Enoshima's notebook,
which were in the foyer.
That's how the killer managed
to swap out the two rooms.
I get it about right...
Mondo Ohwada?!
You're a clever guy, Naegi.
You got me...
Yeah, I did it.
[gasping]
[ISHIMARU] Mondo...
What are you saying...?
[OHWADA] Hey, Monokuma...
enough dickin' around...
Just let them cast
their damn votes already.
[MONOKUMA] With pleasure!
[ISHIMARU] No, wait!
Please, don't do this!
[MONOKUMA] Gimme a
break-- He confessed!
All right, twerps,
you know the drill!
Place your vote
--and save your necks!
--[ISHIMARU] Please, noooo!
[machine whistles]
[MONOKUMA] Votes are in!
Shock-eroo!
Ohwada in the locker room
with a dumbbell!
Eat'cher heart out,
Colonel Mustard!
Believe it or not, my ragtag
bunch of character tropes,
the vote wasn't unanimous!
Ishimaru, voting yourself
guilty was noble, but stupid.
Good thing the others
had their act together,
or you'd all be boned.
[ISHIMARU] I don't believe it...
I refuse to believe he's...
a killer...
Sorry, bro...
Why?! Why are you apologizing?!
Why did you murder him, Mondo?!
Why?! Tell me!
Make me understand!
Why'd you do something
so horrible?!
[MONOKUMA] Poor guy...
Must be something too
traumatic to talk about.
Guess I'll have to
spill the beans for him!
A long time ago, in a
galaxy far, far away,
there lived a boy
named Chihiro Fujisaki.
Pretty much from day one,
Fujisaki was way too
girly for his own good.
I mean, look at those eyes!
Bro-ay was seriously moe!
After years of being told
he was the girliest girl
who ever girled,
Fujisaki had had enough
of everyone's crap.
Rather than punch everyone
in the mouth, though,
he dealt with the constant
oppression in another way.
A gentler way.
A way that involved tucking!
He decided to live life as
a girl, ladies and gents!
Sure, he kinda sucked at
being a boy, but man alive,
did he ever knock it outta
the park at being a chick!
He enjoyed his new life,
but the truth was a secret
he couldn't afford
to ever let loose.
If word got out, the
teasing from you schmucks
was bound to be ten times worse
than anything he'd ever
gotten back in the day.
I figured he'd grow a pair
and kill one of you.
Instead, he had the gall to use
the threat of exposure
as a catalyst for positive
self-improvement!
What a let-down, am I right?!
[FUJISAKI] Now's the time...
I can't hide anymore...
For better or for worse,
I need to get stronger
and be the real me!
[MONOKUMA] Our hero decided he'd
start hitting the iron
with testosterone-fueled gusto.
But the question remained:
Whoever to choose
as his man-mentor?
Hmmm...
Yeah, me.
Fujisaki trusted me enough
to tell me the truth.
[MONOKUMA] Bikers are rather
known for that
"my word is my bond" spiel.
And on top of that, Ohwada
here is a manly specimen,
once you get past the
blundered bouffant.
He was a goal for Fujisaki
to strive towards.
I feel like I'm on a roll here
with all this juicy exposition.
Let's traipse down
Memory Lane some more.
This time, we'll check out
Ohwada's big bad secret,
y'know, the one he max-repped
Fujisaki to keep hidden?
Check it out!
He killed his own brother!
[ALL gasp]
[OHWADA whimpers]
[OHWADA] My big bro
was like a god to me.
He created the best damn
biker gang in all of Japan.
So, of course I joined up.
My bro was top dog,
and I was his number two.
When it came time for him to
hang up his colors,
I was supposed to take
his place as the boss.
But I wasn't him, y'know?
Not even close...
I felt like such a failure
next to him, such a... fake!
On the night of his
retirement party,
I challenged him
to a street-race.
I was so
desperate to win
that I started pulling some
really reckless shit.
And that's when--!
[horn honking,
tires squealing]
[crashing]
[OHWADA screams]
[OHWADA] He died that night,
saving my stupid ass...
[OHWADA'S BROTHER] Don't let
the gang go to hell, Mondo...
We worked too hard...
Promise me... as a man...
[OHWADA] I'm such a weakling!
I'm pathetic! I couldn't
man up to my own failings!
[OHWADA sobs]
[OHWADA] But Fujisaki...
[FUJISAKI] I wanna change!
It's time for me
to become a man!
[OHWADA] This little dude
with so much to lose...
he had the balls to face
his fears and beat 'em!
I was jealous
of him, all right?
I was so... friggin' jealous!
'Cause he was stronger!
[OHWADA] You little...
bastard...
So, you wanna be a man?
Step right up...
It's your lucky day, for real...
I'm the strongest guy
here by a country mile,
and if anyone says otherwise,
I'll beat 'em to a bloody pulp!
I'm stronger than you!
And I'm stronger
than Big Bro!
[OHWADA yells,
blow hits]
[OHWADA]
I crushed his head in...
because he was brave...
I killed someone who
came to me for help,
someone who looked up to me!
He was more man
than I've ever been!
[KIRIGIRI] And then,
after you killed Fujisaki,
you broke his digital
notebook to hide his secret.
Isn't that so?
The other notebook
I found in the foyer,
the one that I assumed
belonged to Kuwata
was yours, I guess.
You took it into the sauna,
hoping the heat and
steam would ruin it.
You probably did the
same thing to Fujisaki's.
That would explain
why we weren't able
to track his notebook down.
You broke it before
disposing of it.
[OHWADA sobs]
[ISHIMARU sobs]
[NAEGI whimpers]
[sobbing]
[MONOKUMA] Boo-hoo-hoo.
As much as I love watching men
weep like damsels in distress,
it's Punishment Time!
[ISHIMARU gasps]
[MONOKUMA] Don't look at
me like I'm singling out
Pompadour Jr. here!
This punishment is
meant for all humanity!
Despair is your birthright!
And what does that mean?
[MONOKUMA] Huh? What's it mean?
It's gibberish, okay?!
It was the first damn
thing that came to mind!
What? You think I'm
goin' for a Pulitzer?!
Hmph.
I am going to survive this...
That's all the rest
of you need to know.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA]
You're a hoot, Richie Rich!
I like the cut of your jib!
Just so that we're crystal
clear on this, Monokuma,
The moment I'm
declared the winner,
I'm going to find a way
to end you, little demon!
I swear on my good name!
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Warning!
Bad-ass alert!
Look at you, with your
sweeping proclamations!
Aw, the bit part
thinks he's people!
That's so cute!
[TOGAMI] Who're you
calling a bit part?!
[MONOKUMA] Now, then...
it's time for you-know-what!
No! Not yet!
[MONOKUMA] I've prepped a li'l
special somethin'-somethin'
for our Super
High School-Level Biker.
Spoiler: I think
he's gonna dig it!
Whaddya say, Ohwada?!
Gimme five, Bro-seph!
Get ready for hell on wheels!
Don't do this! Take me instead!
[MONOKUMA] Well, let's
send him off with a bang!
Punishment Time, ahoy!
I'm begging you not
to kill my friend!
I hope you'll
forgive me, Big Bro.
I promised you man-to-man,
but I let you down...
[ISHIMARU screams]
[MONOKUMA] Try not to mourn your
lost pal too deeply, Ishimaru.
I'm sure his soul's gone
on to a "butter" place.
[ISHIMARU sobs]
[NAEGI] People's lives
are worth nothing to him.
Less than nothing!
[ASAHINA whimpers]
[NAEGI] I dunno how much of this
I can take-- I really don't.
And now listening to Ishimaru's
heart-wrenching screams,
I realize how
powerless we all are.
[ISHIMARU wails]
[MONOKUMA] Not gonna lie,
I think we've got a
good pace going on here.
You feel me?
Yeah, we're hitting our
milestones, so that's a relief.
That Maizono girl had gumption,
trying to pull off
that first murder
before the group got all bogged
down by ethics and junk.
Too bad she's worm-food!
The only thing
that bums me out
is I went to all that
effort to plant a spy
amongst the giblets,
and you haven't had to
lift a bloody finger yet!
[MONOKUMA] What? You
have a question for me?
Fire away!
So long as it's not my bust
size, I'll tell ya anything!
Huh? Who's the 16th
student at Hope's Peak?
Sorry!
That's classified, too!
[MONOKUMA laughs]