[ENOSHIMA] Fraternal
twins, invariably at odds...
One rough-hewn,
military minded...
The other, cunning.
Cunning and compulsively
attractive...
Guess which one I was!
[ENOSHIMA cackles]
Two sides of the same coin!
Twisted sisters united
in their commitment
to darkness and despair!
[TOGAMI] Ikusaba
and Enoshima...
were twins?!
But if you were sisters,
why wouldn't...
I mean...
Don't siblings usually
share a last name, or...?
Come on! We've already
covered this!
The bait-and-switch name-game
is a common device!
Sorry you can't get
your head around it!
But that would mean
you killed...
Oh god...
You murdered your own sister?!
My reasons for doing so
run deeper than the ocean!
Heh! Nah!
I was just bored!
[ENOSHIMA cackles]
[ENOSHIMA]
I do apologize.
I haven't addressed another
real human being for so long.
One quickly falls out
of practice, it seems.
Might have a li'l something
to do with why I'm sick
of my own company! Bleh!
What's the ol' chestnut
about too many cooks?!
I was right...
It's her!
[ENOSHIMA] For the plan to run
like a well-oiled machine,
we needed one of us
behind the scenes;
a sort of stage manager
if you like.
Someone to puppeteer Monokuma
and keep watch over you.
The proverbial "mastermind."
As such,
according to my exhausting
preliminary analysis,
Ikusaba, to put it mildly,
would've been
outrageously miscast.
She was the weaker-minded
of the two.
Case in point: consider
the breed of person
who jumps at the chance
to latch themselves
onto a rag-tag mercenary group.
Oh, yes. The choice was
clear, it had to be me.
So we agreed she would
remain a student
while I moved things along
insidiously from the wings.
Ah. Alas I ran into
a bit of hiccup.
Namely Ikusaba's Super High
School-Level Soldier status.
Call it a problem
of 3-D rendering.
Despairingly Smelly.
Despairingly Filthy.
Despairingly Gross.
One needn't resort to
statistical wizardry to conclude
her kind wouldn't mix
well with the others.
By the same token,
it'd be a crying shame
to let a Super High School-Level
Fashion Diva such as moi
languish in obscurity.
I see...
So you switched places.
[ENOSHIMA] Yes. Quite right.
Although, I hadn't allowed
for how unlike we were,
how distinct.
Not by a mile.
It was not easy...
She tended to behave like
a supporting character.
which was a challenge.
See, when such a
regrettable personality
dovetails with such
an unpleasant appearance,
the audience expects that
character to die early on.
And, who am I to sabotage
our market share?
You killed her off...
to please your viewership?!
[ENOSHIMA] Well, there
was a bit more to it.
Suffice it to say,
the vulgar wretch had
worn out her welcome.
[NAEGI gasps]
[ENOSHIMA] Sometimes
you just plan stuff out
and you can totally
see where it's going
in the long run y'know?!
I was all like "meh,"
Mukuro's no fun anymore,
and what's the point if I
can't make an example
outta peeps who bore me?!
Of course...
So, her death was a betrayal.
One could tell from the look in
her eyes when she was impaled.
What she must've gone through...
She had imagined the two of
you were in this together.
But clearly, your sister didn't
foresee her untimely exit.
[ENOSHIMA giggles]
Pieced that
together, didja?!
It was her own dumb fault.
Mukuro couldn't act her way
out of a wet paper bag
with both ends ripped open.
[NAEGI] You murdered
your own sister;
are you hearing yourself?!
How the hell are you not
bothered by what you've done?!
Oh, wow!
Someone doesn't pay
close attention.
This place is meant
to celebrate despair,
not honor silly
ol' family ties!
When you stop n'
think about it,
from the moment we pop
into this big stupid world
crying and wailing,
the one thing life has
to offer us wholesale,
is death and tears
So what that
boils down to is,
"murder" is just a comforting
euphemism for what
we're already guaranteed
to have to deal with!
News flash, Lamb Chop:
we all face oblivion someday!
What's it matter
how we get there?!
Enough. We don't need it
spelled out for us, thanks.
I'm less interested
in sibling rivalry
than I am the function
of this place.
I can't make the pieces fit.
I know it has something to do
with our memories being wiped,
but I can't tell
you what exactly.
Yeah, well...
When you consider
the alternative,
amnesia's actually a
blessing in disguise...
[HAGAKURE] Um... I'm not
real sure I agree with that!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA) laughs]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
I know what'll ignite those
wayward gray cells, campers!
Feast your eyes on this!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
You all kept clamoring
for the The Outside World...
Well, as saying goes,
be careful what you wish for!
[ALL gasp]
[ENOSHIMA] So, sad...
I think the phrase is...
Post-apocalyptic hellscape...
My brain refuses to
wrap itself around this!
Oh no...
We have to try and remember
how things got this way...
Or else there's only
one way this is gonna end!
Wait, that's it!
Wha-What did I say this time?!
Ours are shot, but what
about her memories?
Am I supposed to know
what you're babbling about?
Ugh! Come on, bring her out!
Let us talk to Sho!
Huh?!
Think about it!
You share the same body!
Maybe her memory
survived the wipe!
[FUKAWA (SHO)] At least we have
a full disclosure policy...
It's the best way
to be schizoid.
What the crap!
Get on with it already!
She freaks me out, okay?!
Ugh!
You know what, screw
you guys; leave me alone!
Damn it. Get a hold of
yourself, we need her.
[FUKAWA sneezes]
♪ Bada-boooom! ♪
Sorry for the delay.
I'm all yours!
This is vitally important,
so no straying from
the point, understand?
I want you to look
at the video feed
and tell me whether the
footage brings anything to mind.
[FUKAWA (SHO)] Video feed...?
Whoa, who's that?!
Oh... Hi, I'm the mastermind...
Ah. Nice to mee'cha.
Thanks... Feeling's mutual...
Focus, damn you!
The footage, if you please!
[KIRIGIRI] Well? Ring any bells?
Yeah, okay; fine...
It's true. I've seen it all.
You remember what
it was like?!
Oh-ho! Do I ever!
Seriously?! You knew
what it was like out there
and you didn't
say anything?!
I sorta keep to a strict
"don't-ask-don't-tell policy".
Keeps me outta undue trouble.
Oh yeah, sure!
I got no issue buying that line!
[TOGAMI] Moving on!
What's this have to do with us?
Sweetheart, please calm down...
You know what did this, surely.
[TOGAMI] I want
to hear you say it.
[FUKAWA (SHO)] The Worstest,
Most Despair-Inducing Event
in the History of Mankind.
Nature's fury vented itself
on humanity with impunity.
We're talkin' the most horrific,
blood-spattered end-of-times
madness ever.
The world that remained
turned into what you see here.
Almost overnight.
Heh. The end.
"The end"?!
The hell's that
supposed to mean?!
Case you haven't noticed,
you haven't explained a thing!
'Ey, just tellin' ya
what I know, hippy.
You want answers?
Miss Raincloud over there saw
the whole shebang in real time;
give her the third degree.
Enough! This is ridiculous!
[ENOSHIMA] Ridiculous?
We have an embarrassment
of ridiculous.
Tragi-comedy after tragi-comedy;
just pick a sacred cow.
Your bread and butter, the
Togami Corporation, for example.
What are you getting at?
Predictable. He can't
stand not to know.
Mention his beloved empire
and he takes the bait
like an obese secretary
to a slice of tiramisu.
C'mon don't be
such a silly goose!
What I'm getting at here is
what happened to your people.
Well done, plebeians!
Bravo! You are correct!
Wait. Correct about what?
We didn't say anything.
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
This just in...
Every last one of
Togami's constituents
are now tripping
the light fantastic!
Film at eleven!
Nonsense! I will
not be taken in!
[ENOSHIMA] The deaths
of your family members
and their business
associates are confirmed.
The glorious
Togami Empire is no more.
That is a vicious lie!
The very name Togami
is the alpha and omega!
Ha! Well the omega
happened a year ago, buddy!
Your homies are
ash and bone now.
What...?
No! Whaddya mean a year ago?!
That doesn't make
any sense even for you!
We've only been at Hope's
Peak for a few weeks...
A month, maybe...
Granted, our memories
have been erased,
but I remember the world
being in pretty okay shape
before I walked
through these doors.
If it'd had been the hellscape
you say it was, we'd have known!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA) laughs]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] You sure
about that? Time is relative...
Surely you don't mean...
You're lying to us!
We're not stupid; we only
set foot in this place
for the first time
a few weeks ago!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA laughs]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
Ya think so, Speedo?
Oh my...
Those two years must've really
gotten away from you, huh?
[NAEGI gasps]
[ENOSHIMA] I'm afraid
that's the last hint
I'll drop for now.
The answer's right
in front of you.
Well? Come solve the mystery!
You know the truth!
Expose this institution's
dread secret!
That's not true.
As Naegi says, it's only
been a matter of weeks.
It quite simply
is not possible...
unless, of course...
the memory wipe goes back
even further than we thought!
[NAEGI] Two whole years
of our lives. Gone.
Oh, man...
We've been here for two years!
So then, wait...
These pictures aren't fakes;
they're completely legit, huh?
[KIRIGIRI] Which means...
The people we thought
were perfect strangers
were in reality
our friends.
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA) laughs]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] Bingo!
Kinda takes killin'
each other off to
a whole new level of damn.
[ENOSHIMA] And to think...
our first couple
semesters here together
were so full of peace...
So full of hope...
So full of boring!
Ah, youth.
What a dweadful way to spend
the first part o' your life!
Oh, well.
Thankfully the situation
wasn't long-lived.
Hope only took a year
to dissipate, you see.
Just as you were developing
a sense of equilibrium,
the infamous "Incident" gate
crashed everyone's party.
In a twinkling, the
Halcyon days were over.
Hope's Peak High School was
hardly immune to the fallout.
Ninety-nine percent of the
student body perished.
Horribly.
Way to go, guys...
Everyone else kicked it,
but you survived...
That makes you the
last living members
of your graduating class...
Not that that will happen...
Listen up 'kay?!
'Cause here's where it
gets super interesting!
And I hate saying the
same thing twice,
so it's real important
you follow along!
Hope's Peak became a shelter
for those of you lucky enough
not to die like animals!
Isn't that just, like, awesome?!
Yup! A big, bad shelter
for the students lucky
enough not to die!
Oop!
Said that.
But.
Who turned it into
a shelter, you ask?
Who inadvertently condemned you
all to eke out your lives here?
Anyone care to guess?
Don't be shy now. Anyone at all?
It was the guy who
previously ran this place.
The principal.
He only wanted to protect us.
He didn't know
it'd turn into this.
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
Yeah, oops! His bad!
Y'know what they say:
the road to hell is paved
with good intentions!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA) laughs]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
Almost makes me feel sorry
for the poor, oblivious bastard.
Almost.
He couldn't have known that
despair had already infiltrated
his precious institution
in the form of two sisters.
Or that the concepts of
shelter and prison would bleed
into one another until
all distinction was lost
in a mushroom cloud
of mayhem and death!
That reminds me.
The ones responsible
for decorating
the windows and
doors in iron?
No one less distinguished
than yourselves.
In your paranoia, you
lot sealed off everything.
You mean-- No!
We locked ourselves in?!
This whole damn time we've
been trying to bust out
of a prison we made?!
Nice job throwin'
a hissy fit
over your own
handiwork, by the way!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] Once this
place was on proper lockdown,
Mukuro an' me thought:
on with the show!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA) laughs]
Our "School Life
of Mutual Killing"
was gonna be the
biggest television smash
the world had ever seen!
[ENOSHIMA] We knew what we
had from the very start...
Even before we
infiltrated Hope's Peak,
everything pointed to the
plan going flawlessly...
Humanity possesses such
an appetite for despair
and wretchedness that only a
scheme this fiendish,
broadcast for all to see,
could conceivably sate it!
[ALL gasp]
[ASAHINA] So you kept us
alive... You kept us alive
so you could get your
rocks off watching us die!
I don't get it...
Why go this far?!
[ENOSHIMA] The outside world,
I'm sorry to say,
still touts a handful of
people ridiculous enough
to hold out for a better life.
I've taken it upon myself
to disabuse them
of what hope they have left.
To give them,
as it were, perspective.
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] I like to
think of myself as an educator.
You're pirating us!
That's your game!
You hijacked the airwaves!
[ENOSHIMA] Indeed.
Well played, sir.
How else to peddle your
plight as a rallying call
to the merry holdouts
of the world
before I dash their
dreams to fragments?
Just picture the
broken bastards
starin' wide-eyed as y'all
massacre each other!
[HIGAKURE gasps]
Oh dear, look at you!
The truth is a
bitter pill, is it not?
How does it feel?
To solve the puzzle,
to unravel the mystery,
and have only despair
as your reward?
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
You meant for this to happen.
Your whole plan hinged
on us uncovering the truth.
[NAEGI gasps]
[ENOSHIMA]
Clever shrew. Naturally.
Would not you coming to terms
with the reality of your
situation be consistent
with my desire to showcase
utter misery at its finest?
[KIRIGIRI growls]
That is all kinds
of messed up.
[FUKAWA (SHO) cackles]
And I thought
I was tasteless!
Who's number one?
[ENOSHIMA] Beg pardon?
[KIRIGIRI] I don't buy that two
teenage girls orchestrated
all this on their own.
I'm sorry, but the
tactical genius required
argues against it.
Who are you working for?
A crime syndicate? A family?
[ENOSHIMA] Multiple
choice, is it?
None of the above, I'm afraid.
The Prime Mover you're
after is far more...
abstract.
[ENOSHIMA] Despair
spreads like a viral outbreak,
that is to say: geometrically.
No one is immune.
We get it, thanks...
You're a philosopher.
All hail depression and
negativity, yadda-yadda-yadda.
Look, if we all agree you've
hit the nail on the head,
can you let us go?!
Ha! Oh dear!
Am I to receive that
as a plea for more life?
I don't believe I've seen a
human being sink so low!
My, how extraordinary!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
Y'see, while no one's
immune to despair,
I'm immune to beggin'!
I do what I do 'cause
of what'cha call
a "deep-seeded
inner complex".
No rhyme or reason to it,
I'm just ridin' the wave.
Try to bargain with
a fractured psyche
and you get ten counter
arguments for every
reasonable assertion
you manage to squeeze in.
That's crazy for ya.
I got no clear motive,
you got no argument!
Zero-sum game!
Stop. I don't wanna hear it...
Y'keep talkin', but
you don't say squat...
We're s'posed to
swallow this B.S.
without a shred of evidence?!
I hope that's not your way
of calling me a liar.
Like you're one
to talk about hope!
Truth is, I don't
care if you're lying.
I just don't wanna lose to you.
And I won't!
We owe it to the
ones who've died!
[ENOSHIMA] Ah.
A pragmatist now, are we?
Is that how you stay positive?
Well, I'd love
nothing more
than to debate the finer
points of ontology,
but it appears
we're out of time.
"Outta time" how?
We can't
jibber-jabber all day!
Gotta step up to
the plate and vote!
Oh!
And since this
is the last round,
there's been a rule change!
I mean, it'd be
super lame to stick
with the same-old,
same-old, don't you think?
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
So here's the deal:
you li'l sugar gliders'll
represent Hope,
and I'll represent Despair.
The vote works as it always
does: someone's gettin' KO'd.
If even one of you
votes Hope down...
[gasping, screaming]
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] I win, and
the rest of you crash and burn
together as one big
happy, dead family.
Hold on, even if it's just one?
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] I know
what you're thinkin', and relax.
I will abstain.
Don't wanna stack the deck.
Still! That is way uncool!
The odds are totally
on your side!
No guys, we got this!
No one's gonna vote
to be executed...
Just think...
Really, the odds
are in our favor!
Yeah, good point.
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
Oh, but lemme paint an even
clearer picture for you
as to what'll happen if I win,
'cause it's a doozy.
You'll die...
of old age!
Here under the roof
of Hope's Peak,
biding time 'til you fade out
in a whimper of senility.
[ALL gasp]
So basically...
we would all be prisoners here
for the rest of our lives.
Hell, don't knock it;
'least we'd still have lives.
If we start thinking
like that, it's all over!
I see what you're doing...
And I am not gonna be
taken in, do you hear me?!
[ENOSHIMA] Whoa dere,
Sea Biscuit!
You just gave mama an idea!
We can't take a chance
this'll end without a death!
Our viewers would
so never forgive us
for pullin' the rug
out like that!
Here's the new deal:
If Hope gets voted down...
one of you takes the fall.
Brilliant!
Now let's see, eeny,
meeny, miney...
Naegi!
Seriously?!
It's only fair; I hate
your guts the most.
Next time, maybe don't be
such a jerk to your captor.
Oh, yes!
Case you're having trouble
followin' me, kiddos,
sacrifice him and the rest of
us live happily ever after.
[ALL whimper]
[NAEGI] Me...?
Sacrificed?
That's the idea!
Simple!
Sell the whiney kid
up the river Styx
and the rest of us make
it to our twilight years!
You can't...
No, you wouldn't!
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)] D'aaaaw...
What's the matter, Naegi?
Having a hard time
believing your pals
will take the high road?
No! Screw you! That's not it!
[NAEGI gasps]
Guys, what's the matter?
[FUKAWA (SHO) growls]
[NAEGI whimpers]
Kiri, back me up...
[NAEGI] Anyone...?
Wow...
If you could see
yourselves now...
The lines despair is
cutting into those faces...
Oh, that's right,
I almost forgot;
the outside world
is barely habitable.
[ALL gasp]
[ENOSHIMA] What keeps us safe
here is the air purifier
purring away in the physics lab.
I'm isometrically
linked to it,
so if I die that's
all she wrote.
Vote me down and
you'll be scrabbling
for someplace else to call home.
Hope's Peak will be
out of commission.
The purifier will seize up
and you'll be forced to leave.
I have mentioned the outside
world is a nightmare
of contamination
and death, right?
Ha-ha!
How does it feel
knowing if even one
of your bosom buddies
sides with Despair
you'll be dead in a
matter of seconds?!
Is it awesome?!
[NAEGI] Tch. Nice try.
Huh?
[NAEGI] Come on...
Like hell we're gonna
give in to you!
Wha--?
[ALL gasp]
We won't be brought
down that easily!
It takes a lot more than stupid
head games to make us cave!
Who cares what the
outside world is like?!
That's not where hope is!
Hell no.
Hope is a state of mind!
Well, okey-dokey then...
I'm sure we all appreciate
the locker room talk.
Now, before we nod off,
what do ya say we
get this over with?
Time for
the final vote!
Here it is, folks!
The grand finale!
Today, hope perishes!
And Naegi with it!
If the outside world
is contaminated...
If despair spreads
like a disease...
Hope can work
the same way...
I can be Patient Zero.
Vote for despair and
you'll live, sure.
But you won't truly be alive!
Yeah, but...
Naegi...
I'm shaking in my
boots right about now...
Plus I'm gettin' a new vibe...
Says we oughta just stay put.
[NAEGI] You've gotta
pull yourself together!
C'mon, man, you wanted
out of here the most!
You can't always rely
on your psychic vibes!
[HAGAKURE gasps]
Man up!
Either y'wanna stay in
this place or ya don't.
Now you just crumble
and set up house
like the mastermind wants?!
Hell no!
That's a sham and you know it!
You're right...
The hell was I even thinkin'?
There's a door needs opening...
And I swear on my life
I'm gonna open it if
it's the last thing I do!
[HAGAKURE] Forget "vibes."
I wanna live...
Hear me?!
I want out so bad
I can taste it!
[NAEGI] Asahina...
Don't you think the people
who didn't make it
deserve better from us?
Think about it...
We're moving on because
they didn't get the chance.
[ASAHINA gasps]
[ASAHINA] What would Sakura say?
If she were here right now,
what would she do?
Well, she wouldn't give in...
For damn sure.
We can't let them down.
They need us.
We owe it to them!
We carry the burden
of hope they can't!
[ASAHINA "What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger."
That's what Sakura would say.
Or maybe...
"When the going gets tough,
the tough kick ass."
Oh yeah, for sure...
Definitely that last one!
Thank you, Sakura.
My mind is made up!
From now on, I'll say
it in her place!
[NAEGI] Togami...
What would your
family have done?
Even if the world had gone
to hell in a hand basket,
wouldn't they have fought back?
This is an opportunity...
Ground floor!
We can rebuild!
Your family may
be penniless,
but you can't afford to give up!
Look, you're alive!
Meaning there's a
chance to start over!
Long as you choose life,
their legacy thrives!
Get off your ass!
Go out and re-stake
your family's claim!
Well played, sir..
But just so we're clear,
I need no encouragement from
the rank and file like you.
Welcome back.
[TOGAMI] Frankly
I'm offended.
You truly think me susceptible
to the wiles of a lunatic?
I've made a promise,
and to men of breeding,
our word is our bond.
I vowed to kill the mastermind,
and indeed I shall.
That's...
So...
Hot...
That cinches it for me
my gallant darling!
Where you go, I go!
That's the spirit!
Before ya go
thinkin' I'm all noble:
I could go either way...
As long as it's the fun way!
[FUKAWA (SHO) laughs]
And besides, wherever
my sweet Togami goes,
I will follow like a lamb!
[ENOSHIMA] What about you,
Miss Marple?
Does the smartest gal in the
room have a death wish, too?
Is the thought of all that
trouble daddy went through
enough to keep
you in the game?
Or are you gonna drink
Naegi's "unkool-aid?"
[NAEGI] Don't listen to her!
Kiri, please...
I know how important your
father was to you; believe me...
This is what he wanted.
You say that...
But how could we really
know what he wanted?
I certainly don't
have that luxury...
I never knew the man.
[NAEGI] Read between
the lines...
He had a vision...
He had hope for us all...
He wanted us to have a future!
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
[NAEGI] If hope
really has left us...
Then in his name we have to do
whatever it takes
to get it back!
That we do...
You're right...
My father did it all for us...
For tomorrow...
He sacrificed everything...
And decidedly not to have
his charges bend like reeds
under a current of misery!
Knew I could
count on you!
Thanks for the
reality check, Naegi.
I may not have ever
really known the man,
but somehow or other
I feel close to him.
Although, I suppose knowing
and understanding
are not the same thing.
[KIRIGIRI] Speaking of which...
You may look at yourself
as a lightning rod...
But I don't believe that's
a reflection of reality.
I think you fill an
entirely different role.
You stay positive for us.
Even when your luck
is at its lowest ebb,
when all seems lost...
You fight for hope.
When the rest of us would
give in, you persist.
Lady Luck doesn't snub you.
She depends on you.
Looks like that's
all she wrote.
So much for Despair.
Hope wins out!
Intense...
Way to go, Naegi.
Spoutin' off...
Rallyin' the troops...
Starin' me down...
Screw a bunch o' that!
You and your sparkly
rainbows go to hell!
Doesn't matter where
it comes from now...
[ENOSHIMA]
You are an imbecile.
And maybe it's flat-out
presumptuous of me
to represent hope...
Boy cooties! Eeew!
But...
I won't let you
drive us to despair!
You will bow
down before me!
Ha! Never!
Whatever happens...
I will hope to the bitter end!
Who you tryin' to scare?!
My chin'll stay up!
Death awaits you all.
[NAEGI] Whatever
curveball I'm thrown...
[ENOSHIMA (MONOKUMA)]
How we despises it, Precious!
[NAEGI]
Whatever's waiting outside...
I'm leaving!
Well, I'd say the jig is up...
Pity...
You nearly succeeded.
Time to lock in our
votes and finish this!
Let's make it happen, guys!
[FUKAWA (SHO) laughs]
Bring it to its knees...
end the ceaseless tribunals...
the murder, the suspicion...
Stop this, and move on.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shup up!
Shut uuuup...!
The more you f-flap your gums,
the more I wanna end you!
Despair for tomorrow!
Despair at the thought
of the unknown!
Despair that your memories
are made of glass!
[NAEGI] Sorry.
Despair only wins if we let it!
[ENOSHIMA] What's happening?!
[ENOSHIMA]
How are you doing that?!
Well, damn.
That... was balls.
Junko Enoshima.
I'd say you're defeated.
I am?
Seriously?
After all that work?
Huh.
Whaddya know?
Wow.
[HAGAKURE] She's...
taking it awful well.
[TOGAMI] Tell us, madam:
how does it feel to be
hoisted by your own petard?
All that ingenious plotting
and this is what it comes to.
[ENOSHIMA] There's...
No greater feeling
in the world!
[ALL gasp]
This is some
weapons-grade despair!
I mean, you gotta think of all
the planning I put into this.
Infiltrating this school
was no cakewalk.
For crap's sake, I murdered
my own twin sister!
This is great!
No-no, "great's"
too pedestrian...
Havin' the whole house of cards
come crashing down on me
at the eleventh hour?
This is the bottom
of the freakin' barrel!
You li'l optimism monkeys
couldn't begin to understand
the surge of endorphins
rushing through me!
Wait...
You're actually happy you lost?
What'd you expect?
Let's move on to
punishment, 'kay?
That's not what this is about!
The whole point of us winning
was so no one would
have to die anymore!
Shut up with that
"Give Peace a Chance" drivel
Don't you dare take
this away from me!
I've wanted to buy
the farm since before
the idea of mortality
even dawned on you!
When hope leaves a
bad taste in your mouth,
the only thing worth
looking forward to
is the spectacular final agony
of giving life a big,
fat "kiss my ass!"
[NAEGI gasps]
[ENOSHIMA laughs]
This is my time now...
Come on, baby...
Big money, no whammies.
Give it to me...
Make me suffer...
I've been a bad, bad girl...
Oh well, kind of
a shame, though.
Given the chance,
I would have bathed the whole
world in this glorious feeling.
Boo-hoo. Guess we can't
have everything, can we?
But at least I can
go out with style!
[ENOSHIMA cackles]
[NAEGI] And like that...
the last classroom trial
came to an end.
Hope's Peak was finished.
We were free.
Free to face the
outside world.
The hard part was over...
Or so we thought.
[KIRIGIRI] All right...
I suppose we have
to do this eventually.
[FUKAWA (SHO) sneezes]
[FUKAWA] Huh...? Uh...
What the...? Oh...
Weren't we just like, facing off
against the mastermind?
It's okay. We won actually.
So... we... can leave
this nightmare?
Mm-hmm! Of course,
there's no telling what's
waiting for us out there.
Well...
Look at it like this:
There are more possibilities
out there than there are here.
Sure, there'll be
despair, but hey...
Buck up!
Hope's waitin' patiently, too.
And if it's not, hell,
we'll bring our own.
Not a bad way of
putting it...
putting it at all.
Thank you for
showing us the way.
Mm-hmm!
First thing I'm gonna do is
find a donut shop and binge!
After that, life can hit
me with whatever it wants!
That's your big plan
for out there?
Donuts?
Yeah, I can
make my own!
That'd be awesome!
Unless there's no flour...
Then I'll jus' start
plantin' wheat!
Let's go. We're not
getting any younger.
And I gotta say, Naegi,
with you leading the charge,
I'm excited about our prospects.
For the first time in a long
time, the sky's the limit.
Thank you, Kiri.
[NAEGI] With me leading
the charge, huh?
That's a good one...
No pressure...
Not sure what'll we do...
But...
I have feeling it'll be big.
[NAEGI] All right...
Let's do this.
I can't say I'll miss
this place much.
But it does feel
kinda strange to leave.
Before we go,
I just wanna say
congratulations.
It's kind of our graduation
ceremony, isn't it?
[NAEGI] Hope never dies...
Not if we refuse to let it.
However scared you are...
You gotta push forward...
Always.
Yes, it takes courage...
But remember...
Courage isn't about
not being scared.
[NAEGI] It's about
being scared...
and finding the
strength to continue.
In the end...
hope opens doors...
Hope opens doors, and we...
walk through them.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Interesting...
You thought that was it?
[MONOKUMA cackles]
[MONOKUMA] Bet all o' you
thought I was a puppet,
didn't ya?! Honest mistake...
Lots of people do...
But ohhh...
I am so much more than that!
I'm your damn Principal!
[MONOMI] Don't be late for
your first day of school,
boys and girls!