[NAEGI] This is the
elite private academy
known as Hope's
Peak High School.
And, yes, the name is ironic.
More of a cruel joke, actually.
Because this is a
high school of despair.
There's only one way
to graduate here.
Kill one of your classmates,
without getting caught.
[MONOKUMA] Attention students!
Please be advised:
As per the notices posted
on your respective doors,
while all dorm rooms
are equipped with
fully-functioning showers,
the water will be
shut off at curfew.
No exceptions.
So if I wanna take a shower
at night, I'm outta luck?
[MONOKUMA] Additionally,
bear in mind only the showers
located in the girls' rooms
have locks installed.
Oh!
And you'll find I've left a
small token of welcome
for each and every one of you.
I encourage you to let
your imaginations run wild!
[NAEGI] Yeah, right.
I'd rather not if
it's all the same.
[NAEGI sighs]
[NAEGI] Might as well clean
up while there's time.
Really?
Ugh.
Son of a--! Aw c'mon!
I thought the guys'
showers didn't lock.
[MONOKUMA] Bingo!
Give that man a prize!
[NAEGI screams]
Where did you come from?!
[MONOKUMA] On the subject of
locks, some friendly advice:
I wouldn't leave my bedroom door
unsecured if I were you.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
[MONOKUMA] Ooh,
you're in a fix, Naegi!
Yeah, apologies for the
wonky doorknob there.
I'll put in a work-order
first chance I get.
Embarrassing, I know.
[NAEGI gasps]
[MONOKUMA] Meantime,
the trick is to lift and
turn simultaneously.
Takes a li'l left-brain
right-brain coordination, but...
Oh, hey, there we go.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Seriously, though...
What are the odds of you
gettin' the one bathroom door
that plays hard to get?
Hilarious!
[NAEGI] No big deal.
[MONOKUMA] But you're supposed
to lead a charmed life, right?
Frankly, kiddo,
Dame Fortune just doesn't
seem all that into you.
[NAEGI growls]
[MONOKUMA] Well,
that's it for me.
A thankless job,
but at the end of the day,
it's all about the kids.
And remember what I said:
lock this door.
Better safe than sorry!
[NAEGI sighs]
Yeah. Not that into me, huh?
Guess if she was I wouldn't've
wound up in this place.
[doorbell rings]
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] Yeah?
[MAIZONO] Um, hi...
It's me...
[NAEGI] Maizono?
Mind if I come in?
So, um..
It's getting kinda late.
Something happen?
I have a bad feeling
about my room...
[NAEGI gasps]
[MAIZONO] While I was
getting ready for bed,
my doorknob started to rattle.
Softly.
Somebody wanted in and they were
trying to be stealthy about it.
Well, it might've
been Monokuma.
When I flung the door open.
There was no one in the hallway.
He must've moved quickly.
Though it could've
been one of them.
The others...
Look, we don't
have to go there.
I just... I'm just
kinda freaked out.
Hey, it's fine, don't worry.
We all agreed not to leave
our rooms after dark, right?
[MAIZONO] Yeah, but, it wasn't
a hard and fast rule.
Sure we all promised,
but what if someone lied?
Sorta paranoid,
but here's an idea.
You could stay in
my room tonight.
I mean, you know,
if you'll feel any safer.
[MAIZONO] Huh?
[NAEGI] The rules don't say who
has to be in which room,
only that it's smart
to be in one after curfew.
So, there you go. Loophole.
Problem solved.
But, you might--
W-Wouldn't it be kind of awkward
with us both in one bed?
Whoa!
Th-That's not what
I meant! I, uh...
I mean, you said you
were freaked out, so,
--I wanted to give you options.
--[MAIZONO] That's not it.
I know you didn't have
anything pervy on the brain.
You're not that kind of guy.
I trust you, believe me.
I just wonder whether it
might be easier for us
to swap rooms for the night.
[NAEGI] Swap rooms?
Yeah, sure.
Like I said, all about
giving you options.
Whatever makes you feel safer.
But...
It doesn't weird you out to have
a guy sleeping in your bed?
[MAIZONO giggles]
Like I said,
I trust you. It'll be fine.
Well, okay...
We're good, then.
Just be warned,
my shower door has
a mind of its own.
I'm sure I'll
figure it out.
[school bells chime]
[MONOKUMA] Evenin' Rugrats!
Announcement time! At the tone
--the time was exactly 10pm.
--[NAEGI] Whatever you do,
don't open the door.
--Promise me.
--[MAIZONO] You got it.
That door's staying locked
even if I know it's you
on the other side.
Would sorta defeat the purpose
of swapping rooms
otherwise, right?
[MONOKUMA] ...best hustle
your butt outta there!
Sweet dreams,
my little cherubs!
Flights of angels,
blah blah blah.
[NAEGI] Wow, so this
is Maizono's room.
Seems like they're all
more or less identical.
[NAEGI sighs]
Don't be nervous.
Nothing to worry about.
Remember, you're only doing
this to keep Maizono safe.
[school bells chime]
[MONOKUMA] Rise n' shine,
chickadees!
7am and all is well!
So let's see some hustle!
Alons-y!
Carpe diem!
Excelsior!
Oh, that's right.
Maizono and I switched rooms
last night, didn't we?
[NAEGI] We all agreed to
eat breakfast together
every morning.
Kinda like a roll call
to settle our nerves.
[ASAHINA] Ah! Hey, Naegi!
[ISHIMARU] Hello. A
very fine morning to you.
[NAEGI] Hi, guys.
[NAEGI] The first ones
there, without fail,
were the ones you'd classify as
the rule-abiding "good kids."
Ladies.
[NAEGI] Followed by the crowd
whose sense of time
is a bit more flexible.
[ENOSHIMA] Sorry I'm late...
[NAEGI] Most kids our age fall
into the second category,
I think.
Excuse me for gawking.
What's the haps?
Well, you look so different.
In person, that is.
Forgive me.
[ENOSHIMA laughs]
Yeah, they sorta gussy me up
for the magazine shoots.
Heh. That's the magic
of touchin' up for you.
Hmm. You don't say.
Aww, c'mon, how different
can I really look?
You're gonna hurt my feelings.
[NAEGI] Last but not least are
the ones who come in pretty much
whenever they feel like it.
You might say they march--
if you can call it that--
to the beat of their own drum.
[HAGAKURE] Yeah see,
but that's the thing.
I didn't oversleep.
I got lost.
I'm tellin' ya.
This place is like
a freakin' labyrinth.
[ISHIMARU] This still
isn't everyone, though.
Hey, yeah.
Where're Togami and Maizono?
Well, okay, here's one of 'em.
[OHWADA] Dude, Maizono
behind you or what?
I'm starving.
[TOGAMI] Do I look
like her keeper?
I came here directly from
my room, thank you very much.
Little out of character
for her to be late,
she's usually here 'fore I am.
Uh-oh, think
maybe she's sick?
[HAGAKURE] Somethin'
wrong, brah?
'scuse me.
I should prob'ly
go check on her!
Maizono!
[NAEGI gasps]
What the heck?
It should be locked!
[NAEGI] Please tell me this
isn't what I think it is...
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI screams]
[BOTH gasp]
What the...?
Where am I?
[FUJISAKI] The gym.
[ASAHINA] Sorry.
We carried you here after
we found you passed out.
Well, Ohgami did the
heavy lifting, actually.
So what I saw... was real?
[NAEGI gasps]
How's Maizono?!
I'm afraid
she's deceased.
Homicide.
[ISHIMARU] Where are you going?!
[NAEGI] Where do you
think I'm going?!
I can't just leave
her there, can I?!
Naegi! We need you
--to get a hold of yourse--
--Let go! I hafta--!
Waste of time,
my friend.
I can assure you the girl
is well and truly departed.
[NAEGI] Then why are
we all standing around
with our thumbs up our butts?
Someone's been murdered!
We can't just treat this
like it's any other day!
Understand, Naegi, it isn't as
though we chose to stand around.
So then what the
hell's goin' on?
Ugh. It was the damn bear.
The "principal." He ordered
us to meet in the gym.
Somethin' bout a "pep rally".
Believe me, man, we are
all against the idea.
"How on earth can you be so
disrespectful," we said.
But then--
[KIRIGIRI] Because they took
my suggestion and complied.
It's best if we just do
as the bear says for now.
[NAEGI] Kirigiri...
We're his prisoners,
plain and simple.
Nothing good can come of
us defying him on impulse.
Unless we want more causalities,
we have to play by his rules.
He killed her...
She was vulnerable
and he killed her...
I know it!
[MONOKUMA] BAAAH!
As if little ol' me would
do something like that!
Scouts honor! It wasn't me!
You monster!
[MONOKUMA] Use your head,
Mr. Jumps-To-Conclusions.
Why would I do something that
goes against the whole point
of this fine institution?
You're supposed to do
the killing, not me.
Rules are rules.
You shoulda seen me at
the zoo when folks ignored
the "do not feed
the bears" sign!
[FUJISAKI] But then,
who else? I mean, 'cause...
[MONOKUMA] Like we don't know.
Wake up and smell
the formaldehyde!
The killer is one of you!
[ALL gasp]
[MONOKUMA] Ugh. Really?
THAT pulled the rug out
from under all of you?
I thought you were supposed
to be "gifted" students!
It's obvious!
One of you sent poor Maizono
to the sweet hereafter
so you could breathe
free air again.
And that's okay!
It's what you're s'posed to do!
[FUJISAKI] This is horrible.
[ASAHINA] He's lying!
Of course he's lying!
[MONOKUMA] Sorry, Charlie!
I'm tellin' the truth.
It was definitely one of you.
And right now, someone standing
here knows that all too well.
Is he telling the truth?
I demand whoever did it
come forward immediately!
Huh. Sure, that'll
work like a charm.
Do you ever listen to yourself?
Look, whoever it is,
I won't judge.
I-It wasn't me, I swear!
Nuh-uh! I know you're
not lookin' at me!
Silence, all of you.
Right, then.
Let us assume the perpetrator
is in fact one of us.
By your own rules, shouldn't
they have "graduated" by now?
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Well aren't we a
Glass-Half-Full kind of guy?
I like your reckless optimism!
Having said that, though, the
main attraction's still to come.
What's that mean?
[MONOKUMA] Listen up, me droogs!
Freedom isn't straightforward;
there are a few
"supplemental" rules.
[CELESTIA] Ah, the article
in our digital notebooks
which states "Whoever kills
a classmate may graduate,
but he or she must not get
caught by the other students"?
[MONOKUMA] Exactamundo!
Someone studied!
Murder alone won't
cut the mustard;
the killer has to
get away with it.
In other words, to go free we
must commit the perfect crime.
[MONOKUMA] After each homicide,
you'll have time to investigate
before convening to debate
the guilt or innocence
of those who remain.
We call these debates--
Wait for it-- "Trials"!
You... can't be
serious about this.
[MONOKUMA] The trial
format is loosely modeled
on parliamentary procedure;
fierce back and forth
being the order of the day.
If the guilty party
is correctly identified,
they will be summarily punished,
and the rest of you allowed
to carry on under normal
school conditions.
Accuse someone wrongly, however,
and the defendant goes free
while the rest
of you are punished.
So point the finger
at your own peril!
There you have it!
High stakes trial by jury!
Beautiful system, really.
Uh, sir...
These punishments...
What do they consist of?
[MONOKUMA] Ah, I suppose
another name for them
would be "executions."
But surely you...
You don't mean that?
[MONOKUMA] Oh-ho!
I mean exactly that, sweetheart!
We're talkin' electrocution.
Gas chamber.
Death by hurricane, which,
yes, we CAN make happen.
[ALL gasp]
Wait. I want to be
sure I understand.
Decide incorrectly
and the jury gets killed?
[MONOKUMA] Let no one say
you aren't the smartest chimp
in the tree.
Oh, and way to imply you're
not the culprit in this case,
by the by. Well done.
[ISHIMARU growls]
[MONOKUMA] You all get to play
judge, jury and executioner
quite possibly of yourselves,
so proceed with caution!
Nuh-uh.
You're a nut-job and I refuse
to be part of this crap!
[MONOKUMA] Beg pardon?
You heard me,
you psycho hair ball.
Far as I'm concerned, the
whole trial thing can get bent!
[MONOKUMA] Aw, but why?
Is that even a question?!
I'm not playing juror if it
means risking my damn life
and that's that!
[MONOKUMA] Oh, be reasonable!
Don't even try to talk to me
about being reasonable,
you sadistic freakazoid.
I'm out of the game.
[MONOKUMA] Ooh-hoo-hoo!
The presence of evil before me
is so overpowering,
whatever shall I do?
I shan't succumb!
Perish the thought!
No, ma'am. I'm
stronger than that!
When Monokuma fights,
he fights to the last breath.
I will not be defeated!
I'll nip this budding rebellion
and reign victorious over--
I'm sorry.
You were tryin'
to say something?
[MONOKUMA] Big mistake...
Huh?
[MONOKUMA] Man-handling
the principal in any way,
shape or form is
strictly forbidden.
The rules, remember?
I know I warned you
about breakin' 'em.
--Activating summoning magic!
--[sirens buzzing]
--Save me, Gungnir Spears!
[slashing noises]
Okay...
Not gonna lie, kinda weird...
It's, uh, I dunno really...
Blood...
[gasping, screaming]
[FUJISAKI] Oh no... Oh no!
That is seriously
messed up.
[MONOKUMA] Honestly, I'd wanted
to avoid messy situations
like that as much
as humanly possible.
But, when an example's
begging to be made,
you can't let a
bad attitude slide.
Let's hope the gravity
of your situation
is beginning
to sink in.
High stakes are high.
[MONOKUMA] Best of luck
playing junior detectives!
The trial will be
gettin' under way soon,
so put on those thinkin' caps
and start a-case crackin'!
This is insanity...
What do we do?
If that was an example...
[TOGAMI] At the very least
we can rule out Enoshima
as a suspect in Maizono's death.
I propose that we move forward
with the investigation.
Not to sound unduly harsh,
but mourning for lives lost
can only hamper chances
of saving our own.
Sorry, but that is harsh.
The girl was warned;
not least of all by me.
Those who cannot adapt
are quickly swept away
on the tide of their
own obsolescence.
In short, good riddance.
That is a terrible
thing to say!
Our personal feelings
on the matter
are neither here nor there.
The situation we've
been tasked with
is to unmask the culprit or die.
Aw, crap. Heads up, guys!
We got sent some new pages!
Jackhole. Who gives a damn?
[ISHIMARU]
"The Monokuma Files", huh?
[YAMADA] Whoa.
It gives a complete run-down
of Maizono's cause-of-death.
Ah, this could prove useful.
Apparently the room she was
found in wasn't her own.
But, quite tellingly,
it was Naegi's.
[gasping]
Shoulda known!
You greased the
poor girl, didn't ya?
Hold on just a minute.
It's not what it looks like!
I think you'd better explain.
[NAEGI] She came to me wanting
to switch rooms for the night
and I said okay. She was
scared; she needed my help.
Oh, sure. We'll
believe that line.
[LEON] Stinks if you ask me...
Oh, come on.
You guys really think I did it?
[TOGAMI] Naegi, put yourself in
our shoes, what would you think?
I'm sorry, but if
you're innocent,
the burden of proof is on you.
--Guys, listen--
--Everyone. Come.
Let's get this over with.
Togami, wait!
Pray that it goes well.
It's as good a place
to start as any.
Ishimaru!
[NAEGI] I'm not a murderer.
But only two people
besides me know that.
One of 'em is the killer,
and the other one's dead.
I gotta do something
before it's too late!
[NAEGI]
"Victim is one Sayaka Maizono.
Time of death,
approximately 1:30am.
Her body was found
in the dormitory wing,
specifically in the private room
of classmate Makoto Naegi.
Death occurred in the
aforementioned
classmate's shower.
Cause of death: a stab
wound to the stomach
from a large
butcher's knife.
Other injuries: deep lacerations
to, and broken bones in,
the right wrist.
Indicating the victim struggled
against her attacker."
[NAEGI] What is that?
"One-one-zero-three-seven"?
[KIRIGIRI] If this is supposed
to be Naegi's room,
why is Maizono's
nameplate on the door?
[NAEGI] I agreed to
switch rooms with her.
Does that make me
responsible for her death?
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] Wait...
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me.
[MONOKUMA] Teen idol
Sayaka Maizono
seen here in her element--
singing like an angel--
was the toast of her generation!
[MONOKUMA] Sadly, for
reasons still unclear,
her chart-topping girl
band dissolved
right as they hit their stride.
These velvety-voiced beauties
neither basked in the limelight,
nor so much as warbled a note
in the shower, ever again.
Meaning, of course, that even if
she breaks free of Hope's Peak,
poor Maizono is essentially all
dressed up with no place to go.
Here's a puzzler for you:
Why on earth would this
phenomenally successful
vocal group disband?
Oh no. He is a monster.
Is there nothing he won't do
to make sure we play
his psychotic game?
How far is his reach that he can
bring down a chart-topping band?
[school bells chimes]
[MONOKUMA] All right, kiddos.
Your principal's bored
out of his gourd,
so whadaya say we get
this show on the road?
Time for the highly
anticipated trial phase!
Kindly march your butts
over to the red door
located on the first
floor at the end of the
academics wing and
mosey on through.
[ISHIMARU] Nice one. Don't
you know how to tell time?
We've been waiting,
I'll have you know.
Hah. I suppose you
can hardly blame him.
Right?
He knows it's only a matter
of time before he's executed.
We haven't proved
anything yet.
I'll remind you the
man's owed a fair trial.
Whatever, man.
Look at him,
he's totally guilty.
[NAEGI] I don't stand a chance.
They all think I did it.
Maizono's the only one
who'd know I'm innocent.
She and whoever
actually killed her.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Is everybody in?
Hop aboard and be conveyed,
as if by magic,
to the student courtroom.
Otherwise known as the
Moment of Truth Room,
for all of you.
[NAEGI whimpers]
[KIRIGIRI] Nervous?
You have two options here:
Bring Maizono's killer to light.
Or, collectively, suffer
the fate rightfully theirs.
The choice is up to you.
[NAEGI] And so, as they say,
the curtain rises on a life
and death performance.
Do we outwit one of
our own, or do we die?
Do we risk it all to
save our own skins,
or drag the whole group down?
Do we trust each other,
or do we destroy each other?
Our lives are on the line.
[NAEGI] Time for
the first Class Trial!