[NAEGI "School Life of Mutual
Killing."
Reality TV's latest smash.
Starring yours truly.
[NAEGI] Who's behind
this, and why?
And for the record, let
me just say how bunk it is
that we have hold another stupid
trial when none of us knows
what the hell is going on.
[NAEGI] Kirigiri's
okay at least.
Meaning the latest victim is
more than likely Student X,
a.k.a. Mukuro Ikusaba.
[NAEGI] The trick
now of course,
is exposing the
murderer of someone
we know absolutely
nothing about...
Wish us luck.
[NAEGI] Kirigiri...
Where were you this whole time?
The second floor dormitory.
The key I showed you
was a skeleton key
that opens any door on campus.
The details will
have to wait.
At the moment I'm hyper-focused
on getting out of
this trial alive.
The odds are against me.
I apologize in advance for
anything I might say or do.
[MONOKUMA] Okey-doke.
Who wants to put their
foot in their mouth first?
Without a doubt, the
murderer is Kirigiri!
[NAEGI gasps]
[gasping]
Can you prove it?!
[TOGAMI] Point one: the body
was discovered at 9 A.M.
[FUKAWA] I can vouch for that.
I'm the one who found it.
I'd gone to the garden to find a
mattock for Master Togami,
and hello corpse.
[TOGAMI] This
establishes a timeline
because we know the body
wasn't there at 10 o'clock
the previous night.
[HAGAKURE] Seems legit.
That's when you and I
checked out the gardens last.
[KIRIGIRI] Then the
murder occurred sometime
between ten o'clock
last night
and nine o'clock
this morning, correct?
[TOGAMI] Yes. Point two:
parting ways with Hagakure
shortly after 10 P.M.,
I wandered into the gym,
where I happened upon
an inanimate Monokuma.
Within moments I'd summoned
Hagakure, Fukawa and Asahina,
and the four of us
spent the entire window
attempting to
reverse engineer him.
Meaning everyone
present has an alibi.
Everyone, that is, except
you, Kyoko Kirigiri.
Just for clarification, I
notice no mention of Naegi
in that scenario.
[NAEGI gasps]
Hmph.
The sprinkler system
exonerates the boy.
You see, the garden is watered
at approximately 7:30 A.M.
The body, however,
was not wet.
Ergo, we may conclude
it was placed there
after the sprinklers shut off.
This gives Naegi
an ironclad alibi,
as he was with us
in the gym by then,
poring over the
inert Monokuma.
It also further
restricts the timeline
to between 7:30 and 9 A.M.
[KIRIGIRI] There's an
inconsistency in your account,
I'm afraid: The
body was in fact wet.
[TOGAMI] Ah. Yes, that.
Only the top half however,
and then only after
we'd discovered it.
The body burst
into flames.
All of us, including Naegi,
doused it in an effort to
preserve the evidence.
Before this, the carcass was,
except for the blood, bone dry.
Oh my! Wet on top,
and dry on bottom!
Internet Rule 34,
don't fail me now!
[KIRIGIRI] Ah...
So in other words, the sprinkler
system had nothing to do
with the body being wet.
Still...
That being said,
this doesn't restrict us
to between 7:30 and 9 A.M.
What are you getting at?
[KIRIGIRI] Suppose the murderer
covered his or her victim
with a vinyl tarp.
A clever misdirection.
It also reopens our timeline
to between 10 last night,
after you and
Hagakure parted ways,
and 9 A.M., when
the body was found.
In fact, we needn't suppose.
I'm certain this is
what the killer did.
My own investigation
uncovered such a tarp
in the garden shed.
Meaning...
Naegi's alibi isn't so ironclad.
[NAEGI] Wait...
Does...
Does she think I'm
the one who did it?!
[MONOKUMA] Woo-hoo, doggie!
Look at lavender locks go!
When it's balls to the wall,
she don't screw around, huh?
Lack of alibi isn't
the only factor.
The choice of weapon used
to kill this Mukuro Ikusaba
points incontrovertibly
at you as well.
Wait, I'm not
following you;
it was just a knife, right?
Any of us could've used that.
The knife was a red herring...
A mere decoy.
Think back to the blood.
Had the stab wound
been what did her in,
surely we'd have seen some
on the ground around her.
The murderer spattered the
lab coat prior to the deed
and dressed the body
to misdirect us.
I noted one of the chickens
missing from the coop.
Doubtless the blood was provided
care of an unfortunate fowl.
Dudes, check it out!
The Monokuma Files say
the body "showed signs of
blunt force trauma to
the back of the head,
consistent with a metal
pipe or cud-gel",
whatever that's
supposed to be...
There you have it: in the
garden with a lead pipe!
Kindly stop trying
to think, please.
I've already discovered
the weapon myself.
[NAEGI gasps]
It was in fact a quiver
of duralumin arrows
I found in a dojo locker.
[HAGAKURE] What? Gimme a break!
Arrows are for piercing,
not blunt force trauma!
[TOGAMI] Au contraire.
Taped together, they'd be ideal.
And it so happens, the
quiver of arrows in question
were held together
with a length
of blood-spattered
masking tape.
The easy explanation?
Kyoko Kirigiri is the killer!
[NAEGI gasps]
[KIRIGIRI] Well played...
There's just one problem:
I've never been to the dojo.
[TOGAMI] Ah, yes.
Naturally you'd claim as much
in your position, however.
Evidence refuting that claim
was found in your room.
Specifically the
dojo locker's key.
I'm being framed...
you have to see that...
Nix the charade!
You've been painted
into a corner! Confess!
[KIRIGIRI] I think not.
You of everyone here should know
better than to pin this on me.
Hm?
Your room key.
I demand you relinquish it.
[KIRIGIRI] It stands
to reason, does it not?
Without the key, I don't
have access to my room.
Period.
[NAEGI] Wait. That isn't true...
She just contradicted herself...
She's lying...
I'm sure of it...
The key I showed you
was a skeleton key
that opens any door on campus.
[NAEGI] She did have
access to her room.
She all but told me outright.
Why lie?
What is she hiding?
Oh, Kiri...
[TOGAMI] I don't imagine you
care to offer us a theory
as to how Naegi
came to find the key
to the dojo locker in your room?
A reasonably vital question
to satisfy, I think.
This is ridiculous.
Can't you see?
Execute me and the school
remains a mystery.
I'm sorry...
I cannot allow that to happen.
What is she...?
[KIRIGIRI] It's
risky... I know...
But if it means exposing
this place for what it is,
so be it.
[NAEGI] She must have her
reasons for holding out on us.
She's worked too hard...
To hell with it, I trust her!
Kiri's not a
cold-blooded killer!
[TOGAMI] Really!
So you do nothing
in your defense
but stare dejectedly
at the floor!
[MONOKUMA] Ugh.
What a friggin' snooze fest;
get the lead out, people!
Kirigiri's the
clear choice, yeah?
So carpe diem!
Cast your votes and send Jessica
Fletcher Junior to her doom!
[NAEGI] Hold on!
[MONOKUMA] Yeah...?
I can't exactly put
my finger on it...
but this trial seems off.
[MONOKUMA] Really?
[NAEGI] It's just...
Doesn't it feel weird
to anyone else
that we're forced to have one
when we don't even know
for sure who the victim was?
I mean, come on...
We oughta have more
time to investigate.
[HAGAKURE] Um, hello: the
victim was that Ikusaba chick.
Yeah, but we're just
assuming that, aren't we?
We don't really know.
There ya go bringin'
logic into this.
You see?
And yet here we are, expected to
make an instant decision...
What the hell, guys?
Monokuma!
You're trying to pull one
over on us, aren't you?
[MONOKUMA] Moi?
O-ho!
Methinks the screechy kid
doth protest too much!
You know what they say:
the guiltier, the chattier.
[NAEGI gasps]
[MONOKUMA] All right!
Enough fartin' around!
Time's officially up!
Debate and
deliberation are over.
Feel free to shut your traps.
In fact, please do.
But...
we're not done yet...
We still need to--
[MONOKUMA] Calling all votes!
You know how this works
by now, troopers!
Let your fingers do the talkin'!
No! Wait--
[KIRIGIRI] It's my
understanding Naegi was the one
to find the locker key, yes?
Mightn't he have planted it to
deflect suspicion from himself?
Wha...
W-What are you saying...?
[KIRIGIRI] If I can't enter
my room as I please...
I'm afraid that's the only
plausible explanation.
Then... oh dear!
That means he's the murderer!
[NAEGI] That isn't true...!
[MONOKUMA] Less talkie,
more votie!
[NAEGI] Damn it, it wasn't me!
[NAEGI] This...
This isn't happening...
This whole trial...
This whole trial is a setup!
Are you people out
of your minds?!
We didn't have enough
time to decide!
It's a sham!
We're being played!
[MONOKUMA] Button, button;
who's got the button?
Oh, yeah. I do!
Punishment time!
[MONOKUMA] What the...?
Excuse me?!
Wha...
What was that?
What in the hell was that?!
Did you... see
what I just saw?
I, uh... I think so, yeah.
Damn it all, I knew
Naegi wasn't guilty!
[MONOKUMA] I've been hacked...
Son of a mother,
I've been hacked!
Digi-Fujisaki planted a virus
when it infiltrated the network!
He's made a mockery
of this fine institution!
Suppose things don't
always go according to plan.
[MONOKUMA] Huh...
Maybe they don't.
Then again maybe starving
to death in a basement
piled with rotting garbage
is precisely the punishment
I had in mind for
the snot nose punk!
[MONOKUMA cackles]
[NAEGI] Where am I?
Man that was close...
Alter Ego saved me...
Well, best not to waste
a new lease on life!
[NAEGI] Now how do
I get out of here?
[NAEGI sniffs]
Ew. No thanks.
[NAEGI] Even the
water's gone bad...
If you think I'm just
gonna sit on my ass
waitin' to die, you
are sorely mistaken!
[NAEGI] Gotta...
conserve my energy.
[crashing]
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] What... the hell...?
[KIRIGIRI grunts]
[KIRIGIRI] Yeah, don't
help me or anything.
Kiri! How'd you get here?
[KIRIGIRI] You're faring
better than anticipated.
[NAEGI] Um, what're you doing?
Call it a rescue mission.
One I thought would
be fairly obvious.
[NAEGI] You've, uh...
You got a thing on your head.
You need to eat.
We'll talk after.
You're a life saver!
And just like that,
he's back at full throttle.
Well, I don't know
about all that, but...
I guess bein' rescued does
kinda put a spring in my step.
I owed it you.
It's the least I could do after
throwing you under the bus
to further my own agenda.
[NAEGI] No worries.
It's not like you're the one
who got us into this nightmare.
None of this is your fault.
[KIRIGIRI] Listen...
There's something you need
to know about Ikusaba.
She was murdered in
someone else's place.
Yours.
Whaddya mean?!
[KIRIGIRI] Don't you remember?
The guy with the
mask and the knife.
That...
wasn't a dream
the other night?
Holy crap, you actually
saved my life!
Naegi...
The mastermind originally
intended to frame me
for your murder...
I was getting too
close to the truth.
Of course.
But since he didn't
kill me for some reason...
...he used a different body
to achieve the same ends.
I've been a thorn in his side...
He's been chomping at
the bit for an excuse
to get me out of the way before
I undermine the whole system.
You singled yourself out...
Defending me and questioning the
circumstances of the trial
forced the mastermind's hand:
you had to go, too.
Hence the sudden
change of plans.
Why he rushed everyone to a
decision at the last minute.
[KIRIGIRI] Indeed...
He's falling back
on cheap tricks
because we've got
him on the run.
We're on the verge of bringing
down this house of cards.
For now, though...
I suggest we focus on
getting out of here.
I agree...
Trouble is we're locked in.
Are we now?
[NAEGI screams]
Watch your step.
If you fall, I won't
be able to catch you
and it's a long way down.
[NAEGI] Thanks.
[KIRIGIRI] My, uh...
My memories are coming back.
Piecemeal...
but enough to give me a decent
working conception of my past.
[NAEGI] Yeah?
Apparently, there's a
term for my skill set.
In this school's
particular jargon
I'm called a "Super High
School-Level Detective."
"Detective"... seems obvious
now that you say it...
[KIRIGIRI] Hence, the
mastermind sees me as a threat:
I'm uniquely
qualified to expose him.
It's why he brainwashed
me erasing my past life.
Yeah, makes sense.
I mean anyone who spends more
than ten minutes with you
can see you've got
sleuthing in your blood.
Thank you...
I pinned my hopes on recruitment
officers noticing that too.
I busted my tail to get here.
Dad left when I was little.
I had this ridiculous fantasy
of reuniting with him...
Figured if my application
crossed his desk,
he'd simply have
to deal with me.
Wait a sec, your
father's the principal!
[KIRIGIRI] Yes.
[NAEGI] Is that the reason you
don't buy into the principal
and the mastermind
bein' the same guy?
[NAEGI grunts]
[NAEGI] The incinerator!
We made it!
[KIRIGIRI] Finally.
So, now what're
we s'posed to do?
We have a talk
with Monokuma.
[MONOKUMA] For realsies?!
Why is he alive?!
Do executions mean nothing?!
You saved him, didn't you?
I knew this would happen!
Sorry, is that
against the rules?
[MONOKUMA] I should
say so, young lady!
Once the turkey's trussed,
there's no putting
'im back in the yard!
A death sentence
is a death sentence!
No interference
will be tolerated!
Back to the Death Chamber
with you, Naegi!
[KIRIGIRI] Huh...
Whatever floats your boat.
What?!
Except that...
Well, not that I'd know, but...
won't your viewers feel cheated?
[MONOKUMA] Beg pardon?
[KIRIGIRI] Consider the nature
of your programming...
You're catering to a
jaded audience as it is.
I imagine they want to see
you beat us fair and square.
Keep pulling a bait-and-switch
every time things look rough
for your higher-ups,
and the ratings are bound
to eventually plummet.
Sorry... Dirty tricks
will never persuade
your viewership
that hope is dead.
[MONOKUMA] Oh dear...
[KIRIGIRI] I have
a proposal for you.
Reopen the case
of Mukuro Ikusaba.
Let us hold a re-trial.
No tricks.
No manipulating the outcome.
[MONOKUMA hyucks]
Consider it the final
battle, if you like...
Hope against Despair.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[KIRIGIRI] Come now...
There's no denying your
audience would eat it up.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Fascinating.
"Beary" fascinating...
R-Really?
[MONOKUMA] I have to admit,
it would be a great
change of pace.
Ah, what the hell!
Challenge accepted!
With the caveat that we
give your grand finale
a li'l more kick. Can't
just go with the whole
"and the murderer is"
routine, eh?
No, no!
An epic showdown of these
proportions
calls for some high
stakes razzle dazzle!
What did you have in mind?
[MONOKUMA] Disentangle the
secrets of this fine institution
and I'll concede defeat...
You and your surviving
cohorts walk free.
[NAEGI gasps]
And the catch?
[MONOKUMA] Fail to solve
the mystery, however...
[KIRIGIRI] ...and every last one
of us gets executed, naturally.
[MONOKUMA] They don't call you a
Super High School-Level
Detective for nothin'!
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] This'll
be spectacular!
Hope doesn't stand a snowball's
chance in Hades against Despair
once you rug rats
know the truth!
Don't count your chickens
before they're hatched...
We may have a few
surprises in store.
The despair you keep prattling
about might just be yours.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[HAGAKURE] Bogus...
We know damn-well
Naegi's not a murderer.
But still we convicted him.
Which doesn't
make sense,
'cause according to the
rules we should all be dead.
[TOGAMI] I think it's safe to
assume the rules have changed.
To what, Heaven only knows.
[gasping]
Dude...
You gotta be kidding me...
Look, guys...
It's okay. Really.
We condemned you to death.
[HAGAKURE] Ugh!
You had to put it like that!
Like I don't already
feel like a tool!
We were manipulated.
[NAEGI] The mastermind wants
us at each others throats;
he wants to rob us of hope.
And I'll be damned
if I let him win!
I like the sound of that!
Nice!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
[TOGAMI] Cryin' out loud...
[HAGAKURE] Brah,
ya smell kinda ripe...
[ASAHINA] What's
wrong with you? Be nice!
[KIRIGIRI] Look sharp.
We have one final
trial on the docket.
[gasping]
[TOGAMI] What are you
talking about?
Why only one?
Listen: If we get to the bottom
of what this school's about,
we all go free...
No clue how we're
gonna pull it off, but...
Who cares?
workin' together's gotta
improve our chances, right?
Yeah!
[MONOKUMA] ♪ Bing-bong
bing-bonnnnng! ♪
[MONOKUMA]
Attention student body.
"School Life of Mutual Killing"
is now entering
what we'll call the "True
Answer Arc." No holds barred.
All or nothin'.
To get you sniffing
in the right direction,
here's a pointed li'l puzzler:
Why was the number
of students inducted alive
into this facility
capped at sixteen?
Is there some
special significance
tied to that figure?
No worries if you
draw a blank...
I'm sure the sweet
hereafter is a ball.
[NAEGI] Screw that noise!
We're gettin' outta here!