[NAEGI] Heck yeah.
Prime real estate much?
Place is smack dab
in the heart of Tokyo.
Hope's Peak High School...
Solid core curriculum.
Sports.
Liberal arts.
Like a prep school
for overachievers.
They cherry-pick the best of the
best from districts all over.
'Cause it's government funded,
we're talkin' crazy perks.
[NAEGI] Not gonna lie, though.
A kid like me cutting it here?
I wasn't so sure...
[NAEGI] Lady Luck
got me enrolled.
Who knew if she'd be
in it for the long haul?
I got this...
[NAEGI] Well, that's
what I thought, anyway.
That first step onto my
new campus, my new life,
should have filled me with hope.
[NAEGI grunts]
[NAEGI] What... the heck?
[NAEGI] Darkness...
Complete and total.
Life as I knew it was over.
[NAEGI] Took me a li'l bit
to put it all together.
In fact, at this point,
I was still clueless.
Luck, as it turns out,
had nothing to do
with my enrollment.
Not the good kind, anyway.
Nope.
The core curriculum
here was despair.
[NAEGI] A classroom...?
How did I...?
Security camera?
Iron plates?!
[NAEGI grunts]
[NAEGI] C'mon...
Ow!
The heck's with the place?
[NAEGI] Seriously?
[NAEGI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[murmuring]
[BOY 1 growls]
Uhh, excuse me?
Ah, cool! This'll
make fifteen of us.
For what?
Cannot predict now.
So!
This everyone?
Maybe now we'll
get some answers.
A-ha!
[NAEGI gasps]
Truant!
Instructions said
eight o'clock sharp!
You have no excuse
for your tardiness!
Yeah.
Could you just not?
Who gives a flying flip
about being on time?
None of us even know
why we're here.
Question...
Did you happen to wake up
in a classroom by yourself?
I did.
No idea how I got there.
That's what I thought...
That's exactly what
happened to us.
[GIRL 1]
Sudden unconsciousness.
Only to converge in
the gym upon awakening.
Fabulously peculiar.
[BOY 1] Yeah, that's the word.
[growls]
Reminds me of the digs
we had back in Juvie.
[BOY 2] Yeah, 'cept this time...
We got kidnapped.
Hey, maybe they'll
auction off our organs.
Hah!
Think positive!
It's a motivational program!
This is supposed to be
a special school, right?
It's difficult to say.
I suggest that first
we assess our situation.
Uh, okay.
[NAEGI] Oh man...
So these are them, huh?
The elite freshman class
of Hope's Peak High...
[squeals]
I knew it!
He's undressing me
with his eyes!
[NAEGI] Huh?!
[FUKAWA growls]
Bet he thinks
I'm a troll...
[BOY 3] He's certainly
not "all that".
[FUKAWA gasps]
Why not take a picture?
Uh, sorry! I--
I mean what else
could it be, right?
Yes?
Help you?
Uh... No!
I'm good!
[NAEGI laughs]
[NAEGI sighs]
[GIRL 2] Excuse me.
The name's Naegi, isn't it?
We went to the
same middle school?
[NAEGI] Maizono?
What a relief.
There's someone here I know!
Wait...
You, uh, I mean you,
actually remember me?
[MAIZONO giggles]
Well of course
I do, silly!
After all, we did go to the
same school for three years.
Oh, believe me, I know!
It's just, you were
so popular, and...
and I was more or less
the exact opposite of that.
[MAIZONO gasps]
I knew it, I came off
as a total snob!
[MAIZONO sobs]
[MAIZONO] Can you
ever forgive me?
[NAEGI] No! Hold up.
That came out wrong.
--I uh...
--[MAIZONO giggles]
Just teasing!
Fine. I take that back.
[MAIZONO giggles]
[NAEGI laughs]
[TOGAMI] If you two
are quite done flirting.
We can move on to
weightier matters.
Such as?
Ugh.
Such as our current quandary.
Someone has collected us
here for a reason.
Argh!
We're all essentially prisoners!
[ENOSHIMA] You'd think
the least they could do
is give me back my cell phone.
It's, like, totally barbaric.
[ALL gasp]
My phone is
missing as well.
Does this mean they've
been confiscated?
Yeah, no,
there's no way.
They'll give our stuff back
to us after orientation,
I'm sure of it.
In fact, it's already
been foretold!
Dude, please.
A crystal ball?
I'm dead-on thirty
percent of the time!
Isn't that impressive?
[HAGAKURE growls]
[mic screeching]
[VOICE] Testing. Mic test.
Mic test. One-two.
Everybody hear me
okay on this thing?
Ahem.
Hiya, kiddos!
Time ta roll out
the welcome wagon!
Not literally, of course.
Not even sure what that'd mean
literally, but you get it.
See? We're not prisoners.
This is just how they do
things here at Hope's Peak.
Well, you're half right.
[NAEGI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
What the heck?
[BEAR] I know what you're
all thinking, and no,
I am not a high-tech
Build-a-Bear reject.
I am the principal of this
illustrious institution.
Monokuma!
Pleased ta meetcha!
[YAMADA screams]
I had a nightmare
just like this once!
[MONOKUMA] Young man, some
respect if you please!
Monokuma.
Your Principal.
[NAEGI] This is weird.
[MONOKUMA] Yes, yes.
Like nothing you've ever
seen before. Uncanny.
Unsettling, even.
Yadda-yadda...
Moving right along.
Now all of you
stand at attention.
Give Principal your
snappiest "Good morning!"
Good morning,
Principal, sir!
Please! Don't encourage it!
[MONOKUMA] Eh. That'll
have to do, I suppose.
Anyway, welcome,
bright young things
to your new living quarters!
Now, before you get all uppity,
rest assured it's
for your own good.
Mustn't let the outside world
dull that dazzling inner spark;
we gots ta keep that
freshness sealed in!
[BOTH] Uhh.
Hold on, we--
I don't think so!
[MONOKUMA] So now you're
wondering how long
you'll be guests of our program.
Approximately...
the rest of your lives.
[ALL gasp]
[MONOKUMA] Oh, yeah!
By new living quarters, I mean
permanent living quarters.
You-You can't
be serious.
We'll be here... forever?
Aw, don't fret.
We have an astronomical budget.
Your needs will be
satisfied in perpetuity.
That's not the issue!
What if we have families?
No. Just no.
Excuse me.
So the iron plates in our rooms.
Those are to shut us in?
[MONOKUMA] Bingo, you're
here for keepsies!
Kick and scream all you want.
No one outside can hear ya'.
[CELESTIA] Forgive me
if I suggest this
to be less than ideal.
But to spend the rest
of our natural lives
confined in a
place like this?
[MONOKUMA coughs]
[MONOKUMA] Natural lives?
Oh, that's rich.
Actually, for those who wish
to leave, there is a loophole.
Enlighten us.
[MONOKUMA] Good,
ol' fashioned murder.
Yes!
The student who kills a
classmate and gets away with it
will be permitted to walk
out of here scot-free.
Pummel!
Shiv!
Bludgeon!
Mutilate!
Immolate!
Extirpate!
Asphyxiate!
Know magic?
Conjurate!
[MONOKUMA chuckles]
[MONOKUMA] Know what you kids
and this salmon have in common?
Neither of you has the
faintest notion how tingly
the thought of watching you all
slaughter each other makes me.
The best of the best,
the crème de la crème,
forced into a gore-soaked
free-for-all!
Is there anything hotter?
[MONOKUMA sighs]
You're crazy!
But why?
What could possibly be
the point in making us kill?
Yeah, what they said!
If you think we're on board
with this bull-crap,
you're out of your mind!
[MONOKUMA] Bull-crap?
Where do you get off talking
like that to your principal?
Love it or hate it,
sweetie pies, from here on out
this school is your
entire world.
Dems the breaks!
Look on the bright side!
I'm letting you get away
with murder... for reals!
So stop whining
and start plotting!
[OHWADA] You want murder,
Teddy Two-Tone?
Take this shit any further and
you'll be victim number one!
[MONOKUMA] Is that a threat?
You gonna impale me
on that pompadour?
Bitch! No.
What I'm gonna do
is tear you apart
'til there's nothin' left but
whatever's makin' you jabber.
[MONOKUMA] School
rules expressly state
"no harm must
come to the principal
under any circumstances!"
[siren buzzes]
Uh, guys.
What's that noise?
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
Oh no! Toss him!
Huh?!
Trust me, just do it!
[OHWADA grunts]
[siren buzzes faster]
[ALL gasp]
This is real, isn't it?!
It coulda blown my face off.
So the teddy bear's kaput?
[MONOKUMA] Not a teddy bear!
Monokuma!
♪ Tada! ♪
[ALL gasp]
You-You son of a--!
[MONOKUMA] Consider that a
verbal warning, young man.
Get smart with me again,
any of you.
And let's just say 'round here
we forego written warnings
in favor of instant
corporal punishment.
This now concludes
the introductory portion
of your orientation,
boys and girls.
Here's to you all
enjoying a fun, fulfilling,
if not exactly long, life of
scholastic enrichment here
at Hope's Peak High!
[ALL murmuring]
So if I understand
this correctly...
To make it out of this
place, we're to kill?
[ISHIMARU growls]
This is absolutely bogus.
No... It's a joke....
[TOGAMI] Hah. A joke
it may very well be.
That doesn't alleviate my
concern as to whether one of you
takes it at face value.
[NAEGI] So began our lives
as students of Hope's
Peak High School.
If you can call it a life.
'Cause this place was far from a
hallowed hall of learning
where overachievers are
stoked to hit the books.
The name was one hundred
percent ironic.
♪ Dangan Ronpa ♪
Well, give it a shot.
[OHGAMI growls]
It appears my strength
is insufficient.
[NAEGI gasps]
'Kay, not gonna lie.
I'm kinda diggin'
the digital notebook.
Nothing.
[OHWADA] Same here!
Got jack.
Bah!
Don't lose heart, friends!
If we persevere, the way out
is bound to present itself!
I'm with Cap'n Pep Talk!
Better to stay positive
than spin our wheels.
I agree.
Yeah, fine.
Leave no stone unchucked, right?
I prefer to search alone.
[ALL gasp]
Think that's smart?
I do, yes.
Considering one or more of you
might already be planning
my untimely demise.
Oh, come on.
Only a fool would deny it.
Whoa there, pal!
You can't just do
whatever you want!
Hmph.
Out of my way, narwhal.
Ooh, your paranoia's
'bout to be right-on.
[NAEGI] Hold up, guys!
The last thing we
wanna do is fight!
Say what?!
The hell d'you think
you are, punk?!
You wanna lecture me?
Gimme a lesson on teamwork?!
No, I--!
Shut up!
[NAEGI] Where am I...?
Maizono!
Hey, welcome back.
Wait, are we, still...?
'Fraid so.
This is your room.
[MAIZONO] Everybody gets
their own, apparently.
I got Ohgami and the others
to carry you in here.
Hope you don't mind.
No. No.
Are they...?
They've been tearing the school
apart for the past couple hours.
I stayed to--
I mean, I was worried
about you and all...
That's really sweet.
Wow. Thank you, I guess.
[NAEGI] Back when
life was normal,
Maizono used to be a big deal.
Big enough that you
wouldn't think she'd bother
remembering a nobody like me.
Oh, don't be like that.
Was-Was that out loud?!
No. I can read your mind.
Huh?!
[MAIZONO giggles]
Teasing again!
Girl's intuition.
[NAEGI laughs]
[NAEGI] Sorta the
same thing, isn't it...?
Look, I'm really
glad you're here.
Be a lot worse if
I didn't know anyone.
Y-Yeah.
[NAEGI] Here we go...
[MAIZONO] How you
feeling? Better?
[NAEGI] You bet!
'Sides, I'm not about to be
the only one lying down
while everyone else is
busting their humps
lookin' for an escape.
Yeah! You've got a good point.
Guess that cinches it, then.
If you're joining the search,
you'll need a Gal Friday.
Huh?
Someone who's got
your back, silly boy!
C'mon, it'll be great!
We'll be like detectives!
Uh...
Oh! Oh, hey! There's
the man of the hour!
You okay?
[NAEGI] Sure am! Never better.
So, Let's chalk the
whole thing up to stress.
Uh, yeah,
no worries Ohwada.
I mean, we're all on edge.
Tempers flare up sometimes.
I doubt any of us would kill
in front of witnesses.
That is to say, under present
circumstances
"safety in numbers"
would seem to hold true.
Right, listen up!
I hereby call to order the first
Hope's Peak High School
Reconnaissance Committee
Briefing on Academy Affairs.
Let's review the
present state of our intel.
And remember,
all cards on the table!
[OHWADA] I kicked at the
stupid door for an hour.
Nothing.
Didn't leave so much as a dent.
Thing's hard as iron.
[CELESTIA] It is iron,
so that makes sense.
[OHGAMI] At the end
of the main corridor,
we found a stairwell
leading to an upper floor.
[ASAHINA] But the
security gate was down
and we couldn't get it to budge.
I see...
It is interesting that
certain areas of the facility
are evidently out of
bounds for the time being.
[YAMADA] The dorm rooms
are actually quite nice.
Firm beds, good lighting,
stylish decor.
Except for the iron plates and
surveillance cameras,
I'd give 'em five stars.
[FUJISAKI] I searched
the kitchen.
They've got enough food packed
in the fridge to feed an army.
Safe to say we won't go hungry.
[YAMADA] Surely there's not
enough to feed fifteen people
for the rest of their lives?
[FUJISAKI] No, there is.
The fridge gets
restocked every day
according to how much
we've eaten the day prior.
See, Monokuma told me so.
Wha--? You saw 'im?
He popped up out of
nowhere while I was looking
around the kitchen,
then disappeared
before I could
see where he went.
[ISHIMARU] Ahem.
Anything else
to report?
[FUKAWA "Report."
We're still in the dark
about who's behind all this,
and we're still trapped.
This investigation
was a waste of time!
No...
Some useful information was
gleaned from our joint effort.
We now know the
boundaries of our confinement
And that we'll be
here for a while.
[FUKAWA screams]
Stop! I'm having a
nervous breakdown!
Monokuma's made that
perfectly clear.
From where else should the
incentive come for us to kill?
That's not something
to joke about!
Oh, man! What are we gonna do?
Adapt, I suppose.
What?
These aren't such
bad arrangements.
So we just suck it up?
Get used to being prisoners?
In the game of survival,
neither the strongest nor
smartest have the advantage.
But rather those most
willing and able to adapt.
The most pliable.
[ALL exhale]
With that chestnut in mind,
I would like to offer everyone,
if I may, a modest suggestion.
Yeah? And what would that be?
You will note in the
rules a designated curfew.
Observe.
Why not make an addendum to
these so-called "night hours"?
Like what, exactly?
At night we all
stay in our rooms.
Simple as that.
What?
What would even be the point?
Think about it, my dears.
Given this predicament,
the dark hours
will be especially hard
on our nerves as it is.
The tiniest sound will persuade
us of foulness afoot.
Now.
Needless to say,
this restriction
must be
self-imposed.
Its only means of enforcement
will be peer pressure.
[NAEGI] The next day we picked
up where the search left off.
And the day after that...
But, as you've probably figured,
we didn't make a lot of headway.
[LEON growls]
Damn it!
I'm tellin' ya, no matter how
many times I look,
I come up with squat.
[HAGAKURE] Same here.
[ALL groan]
We're stuck.
We're never getting out of here.
No one's coming to help us.
Aw, chin up, Fujisaki!
Someone on the outside's bound
to start missin' us soon.
Yes! Of course!
You think so?
Huh?
Well, we've been gone long
enough to raise the alarm.
We're talkin' three days!
The police are bound to be
closing the net on this place!
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[MONOKUMA] Dear, oh dear.
You're not hedging your
bets on law enforcement?
You know,
it's quite simple.
If you want out of here,
all I gotta see is
a little initiative.
[FUKAWA whimpers]
[MONOKUMA] Hyuck.
Well, I've gotta hand
it to you Generation Z-er's,
you've got balls when it comes
to dealing with authority.
Frankly though, that
attitude only goes so far.
You're borin' me to tears.
If you think you can
trick us into killing someone,
you're crazier than I thought!
[MONOKUMA] Eureka!
That's the problem!
Granted, my setup's perfect:
the right atmosphere,
a good balance of
tension and intrigue,
the perfect amount of pressure,
but not the vital ingredient
to bring it all together!
What are you gettin'
at, buddy bear?
[MONOKUMA] Motivation, son!
All students report to the
Multimedia Room at once
for a brief,
informative presentation
on just what I mean.
Multimedia Room?
Oh, my.
Where in the world do I start?
We're just so unbelievably
proud of you, Naegi darling!
You'll do great!
It's a pretty big deal,
buckaroo. Ha, ha!
Just, uh...
You know, don't work too hard.
Have fun out
there little bro!
I am totally jealous
of your luck!
[NAEGI gasps]
[ALL gasping]
This is insane...
I have to get out of here...
I have to get out of here now!
[MAIZONO whimpers]
No!
I can't do this.
I have... I have to get out
of here before it's too late!
What did you see?
[MAIZONO] Why...?
Why did this happen?
I didn't deserve this.
A kid shouldn't have
to make this choice!
Maizono...
[MONOKUMA laughs]
Yeah, who are you, really?
And what are you
getting out of this?
Is this all some kind
of sick game to you?
[MONOKUMA] Yes, what am I
getting out of this?
Very good question.
My payoff... is your despair.
[MAIZONO] Nooo!
[NAEGI] Maizono, wait!
[MAIZONO yelps]
Let go!
We're in this together
like detectives, remember?
[MAIZONO] Stop it!
We can do this!
If we work together,
we'll get out!
No one's coming!
We're all going to die!
I'm not gonna let
that happen, I swear!
Whatever it takes,
you hear me?
I promise you!
[MAIZONO wails]
[MAIZONO sobs]
--[MONOKUMA fake sobs]
--[MAIZONO sobs]
[MONOKUMA laughs]