[NAEGI] And just like that,
Maizono was gone.
Almost like she'd never
been here to begin with.
[NAEGI] Damn that
little two-tone psycho!
Thanks to his sadistic rules,
we can't even mourn her death.
Anyone's death...
I keep pinching myself...
but I never wake up.
[MONOKUMA] Every time you
sad-sacks survive a death-match
with Lady Justice,
you get a shiny presie.
It's a whole new world!
Don't you dare close your eyes!
As much as I'd love to split you
open from chins to cha-chas,
it's my principal-y duty to
stimulate that oatmeal
you call brains...
Happy hunting, chill'uns!
And don't say I never
gave you nothin'.
[HAGAKURE]
"Whole new world"?
Dude. It's a stairwell.
[NAEGI] Looks like he
gave us the second floor.
[KIRIGIRI] Our data's
been updated, as well.
In that case...
Guess we'd better head up
there and check it out.
[ASAHINA] Turn that frown
upside down, Naegi!
We'll get outta here if we
work together. I'm sure of it!
[TOGAMI] Please, spare us
your blandishments, woman!
One of our compatriots
butchered another...
Once that line has been crossed,
further villainy is assured.
[FUKAWA] That dead girl really
screwed us all over,
didn't she...?
[ASAHINA] O-okay...
Look, if we want to save
ourselves, we need to team up
and figure out who's
actually pulling th--
[TOGAMI] Quiet, you!
Lest we all drown
in your naiveté.
[YAMADA] Care to explain that?
[CELESTIA] What he's
trying to say is...
whoever kidnapped us has a lot
more clout at their disposal
than we assumed at first...
He's out of our league.
[OHGAMI] What're we supposed
to do, then? Give up?
[TOGAMI] The bear has been
very frank with us.
To graduate, one need only
deceive his classmates.
And given my classmates,
there's nothing to it.
[FUJISAKI] But...
it's deceiving them
about murder...
I don't wanna kill anyone!
I can't!
[YAMADA] Hmm... read it...
read it... hated it...
[TOGAMI sighs]
It won't even turn on.
Cut-rate piece of junk.
Not that I believed we
could Google our way out
of this mess, but it
did cross my mind.
Well... any luck?
Uh?
[NAEGI]
"Hope's Peak High School...
Principal."
[BOTH gasp]
According to the envelope,
it's a note from
the principal.
What do we got...?
Huh?!
Going by what I see here, this
isn't even a school anymore.
"School operations
will resume...
once the issues have been
resolved." What's that about?
Apparently, this place stopped
being a legitimate school
before we ever set
foot on campus.
[NAEGI] I don't know
how it was for you,
but it looked plenty
legit when I showed up.
Apparently, the author
of our misfortune claimed it
once it was deserted,
and then he set the stage
for this twisted little play.
[TOGAMI] Look at this...
Sensationalist trash
of the lowest order.
But in here, it serves
as a textbook.
Yeah, don't remind me.
[TOGAMI] It's not often that
life grants you reason
to feel such
delicious frisson.
The least we can do
is enjoy ourselves.
What the hell...?
[OHWADA] That little piss-ant's
treating it like a game!
You're in danger too, y'know!
It is a game,
you philistine.
[CELESTIA] A zero-sum
game, correct?
Whatever you win,
you take from another.
Vying for spots at a good
school, promotions at work...
And in this scenario...
the prize is life itself,
but only for one of us.
[ALL gasp]
Yeah, thanks for that...
Honestly, the thought that you
might not survive this game
has never once crossed
your mind, has it?
No, and why would it?
[CELESTIA giggles]
I would expect no less from the
heir to an elite conglomerate
like the Togami Corporation.
The world must look
different to you.
For a Super High School Level
heir such as you,
challenges simply exist
as accolades to be won.
Even with your life on
the line, you don't waver.
So you do understand me.
Shall I spell it out for
the rest of you plebeians?
You had better try
your damndest to win!
Nothing bores me more
than a bunch of quitters.
[FUJISAKI] No... I can't...
Hmm?
This is just wrong...
Why are you talking
about it so calmly?
It's horrible!
Friends aren't supposed
to kill each other!
We are not friends.
We are strangers, death-locked
in a fight for survival.
But... that's so... ruthless--
You voted Kuwata guilty
right along with the rest of us.
[FUJISAKI gasps]
Well, it's a good thing he got
what was coming to him, y'know?
Woulda been our necks with the
"cut here" lines on 'em instead.
Yeah! They're right!
Assuming you don't get off
on that kind of thing,
don't go blaming yourself!
Listen to him, Fujisaki!
Even Kuwata isn't
totally at fault!
Whoever took us...
this is on their heads!
[MONOKUMA] Right on!
You pass that buck!
You're telling me Leon played
hide-the-cutlery with Maizono,
and it's not his fault?
Oh, I get it:
she was gonna kill him if he
didn't beat her to the punch.
Bye-bye free will?
Whatever helps you
sleep at night, darlings.
[ALL gasp]
[HAGAKURE] Man,
that bear is a dick.
[FUJISAKI sobs]
[OHWADA] Stop that...
You're just givin'
him what he wants.
[TOGAMI] Hmph.
Taken up coddling
the weakest link, eh?
That's it! I'm feeding
this dude his teeth!
[ISHIMARU] Just calm down!
[OHWADA] Like hell!
[ASAHINA] Hey! You need
to chill out, Ohwada!
[OHWADA growls]
As enthralling as it is
to watch you beat your chest
like a caged monkey,
I'm sick of this sham.
[OHWADA] Runnin'
like a bitch, huh?
[FUKAWA]
Maybe Togami is right...
I can't trust anyone!
[ASAHINA] Really? Now is when
you finally decide to lose it?!
No one gives a damn
whether I'm alive or dead...
You could find me torn
to pieces and you'd say...
"Well, at least it
wasn't meee...!"
Fukawa. Nobody wants you dead.
Just calm d--
Liar! It's in your
eyes! All of you!
[FUKAWA squeals]
Man... There's crazy,
and then there's that chick.
[ALL exhale]
Soooo... Anyway...
Since more areas
have been unlocked,
how about we go check out
the pool situation?
Bet a quick dip
will do us some good.
[OHGAMI] Hmm...
Good idea.
What are we waiting for?
[ASAHINA] You, too.
It'll make you feel better.
Oh! I, uh...
[ASAHINA] All right.
Locker room, twelve o'clock.
Dang. I guess we'll have
to take a rain-check.
[MONOKUMA] Au contraire!
All you gotta do to
open that pesky door
is press your handy-dandy
digital notebook
up to the lock.
Ta-da! Problem solved!
Just 'cause I want y'all
to slaughter each other
doesn't mean anything goes.
So! No boys in the
girls' locker room,
and no girls in the
boys' locker room.
Capiche?
What if a girl held the door
open and a boy snuck in?
or what if they held their
door open for one of us?
[MONOKUMA] I think
Mr. Gatling Gun
will find the "holes"
in their logic?
Get it?! Roll tape!
[ASAHINA] Time out!
Anyone you shoot with
that thing is dead meat!
[FUJISAKI] I think...
that's the idea...
What happens if we borrow
a notebook from a boy
and try to use it?
[MONOKUMA] Hmm...
I never even thought of that!
Incoming rule change!
"Lending your digital
notebook to another student
is strictly prohibited."
Good thing you said something,
or you could've totally
gamed the system!
And that would have
been unbearable!
Toodle-loo, kids!
Yeah, you guys,
I don't really feel like
hitting the pool now.
He probably filled it
with piranhas, anyway...
[NAEGI] Huh. dark in here.
Fukawa, hey.
[TOGAMI] Please, could
you be any more obvious?
The sight of you repulses me.
[TOGAMI sniffs]
But I can smell you from here.
Take a shower.
[FUKAWA gasps]
Don't make me repeat myself.
Just do as I tell you.
Your stench is an insult.
What?!
Oh... okay...
[NAEGI] Fukawa, wait!
Look, I wouldn't take all that
stuff to heart, you know?
[FUKAWA]
I can't believe him...
Togami is such...
He's such a...!
He's such an absolute
dreamboat, isn't he?!
Huh?!
He took the time to
tell me to clean myself!
Well? What do you
think of us, Naegi?
[NAEGI] Hold on... Us who?
[FUKAWA] Me and Togami, duh!
Aren't we the perfect couple?!
Heh... Maybe you think our
love is one-sided, but...
you're wrong!
Oh, Togami! I'm yours forever!
Oookay, then.
[FUKAWA giggles]
They sure broke the mold
when they made that one.
[ISHIMARU] Ah, Naegi, perfect!
Your timing is impeccable!
What's going on?!
We need a ref,
and you're the first to show up,
so you get the job...
Goody-Goody-Two-Shoes here
keeps shooting his mouth off.
Thinks I lack self-control
or some crap!
Well, of course you lack it!
If you had self-control,
you wouldn't answer every
challenge with your fists!
Yeah?! Says the guy who
yells all the damn time?!
I got more self-control
than you, a-hole!
That'll be the day!
You talk a big game,
Poindexter!
Let's see if you got
the balls to back it up!
Hey! Lemme go!
So... you guys?
It's been like 40 minutes.
You still okay in there?
You're lookin' pretty
pink there, Pollyanna!
How's that self-control
treating ya?!
This is my regular
complexion!
You're sweating
like a stuck pig!
[ISHIMARU laughs]
This level of heat
is child's play!
Let me know when it
actually warms up!
Why don't we
call it a tie?
--[ISHIMARU] The hell with that!
--[OHWADA] The hell with that!
Don'tcha think we'd be
better off in our rooms?
It is after ten.
[ISHIMARU] Winning this duel is
the only thing that matters!
[OHWADA] Too bad for you, then!
I've faced more heat
than the devil's nutsack!
Naegi, we got this!
You can go!
All right. Be careful, guys!
[laughter]
Huh...?
[OHWADA] Aw, man!
You're such a kidder!
Maybe you just have a great
sense of humor, friend-o!
Hey, Naegi! How's it hangin'?
Yeah, thanks for helping
out with our little duel!
They're friends now?
Who knows? But I
think it's hella creepy,
whether they're
faking it or not.
[BOTH laugh]
As if a girl could ever
understand the bond
forged between two men!
Ours is a friendship
tempered in flame itself!
[OHWADA] Dude, I love it
when you get all poetic!
So? Which one of you
left the sauna first?
That's water under
the bridge, little man!
Put our duel out
of your mind.
Kame-hame-forget about it!
You're over nine thousand!
[BOTH laugh]
[NAEGI chuckles]
[glass shatters]
Huh?
The milk tea was not to
your liking, I assume?
Serving me this swill was
a culinary slap in the face.
[YAMADA whimpers]
Henceforth, my royal milk tea
will be simmered in milk,
and not just
slopped into a cup.
That's a lot of work--
Go make it again,
you corpulent bootlicker!
Yes! At once! Your bootlicker
is on the case, milady!
I'm so glad we
had this talk.
[ALl gasp]
[NAEGI chuckles]
[intercom chimes]
[MONOKUMA 'Sup? How about
you expendable little spitfires
do Principal Monokuma a solid
and head on over
to the gym, yeah?
We're gonna have
ourselves have a pep rally.
Come on, meat-sacks!
Show me some hustle!
[MONOKUMA] I'll give it
to ya straight.
'Cause I've still got
a lot of drinking to do.
I look out at you kids,
and y'know what I see?
A buncha teenagers
who aren't dead!
Major bummer.
That's why I'm gonna light a
fire under your tuchuses
to get things movin'...
Maybe a real one...
Don't tempt me.
With that in mind,
today's theme is:
"Embarrassing Memories"
or, "The Past Secrets
You Want Kept Secret"!
YOLO!
Aaah! How'd you know?!
If the others found out--!
[MONOKUMA]
Skeletons aren't my forte,
being a stuffed bear and all,
but every human has
at least one of 'em
swinging around
in their closet all secret-like.
[NAEGI] "Naegi wet the
bed until the fifth grade"?
Aw, jeez...
I mean...
it'd suck if they
found out, but...
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Time's
a-wastin', giblets!
If I don't get a corpse outta
one of you in 24 hours,
your skeletons will all
be front-page news!
And trust me, we've got
some real doozies in here!
Well, smell ya later!
Yeah, so, no one's gonna
go on a killing spree
to keep their secret
a secret, are they?
[NAEGI]
Is there something so bad
to make it worth killing for?
I wouldn't have believed
it back before this place,
but now I just don't know.
[NAEGI] Assuming
the worst of people
isn't going to help anything.
[NAEGI] Yeah...
Suck it up, Naegi.
We'll all be fine.
[MONOKUMA]
Top o' the morning, all!
Hyuck-hyuck-hyuck-hyuck!
While you were busy
drooling into your pillows,
one of your classmates
dished out a little homicide!
I wonder who bit
the big one...?
Who're we missing?
Too soon to say yet, brah.
But yet again...
one of us has turned
into a killer.
But do you really
believe that?
Who'd kill someone
over a dumb secret?
[TOGAMI] Dumb to you perhaps.
But not all secrets
are created equal.
Let's look for clues.
Naegi...
You're with me.
Huh...?
The locker room.
A prime setting for
the taking of a life.
Huh? Yeah, if
you say so, Togami.
Wait!
Guys can't go in there!
Open sesame.
[MONOKUMA] I've lifted the
restrictions on these rooms
while you investigate.
There's plenty of time
to shoot you later.
[TOGAMI gasps]
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI screams]
No! It's Fujisaki!
[TOGAMI] Written in blood...
"Blood bath fever," huh?
Interesting...
There's something
primal about the scene.
Most definitely.
[ISHIMARU]
Hey, guys, what's--
[ISHIMARU screams]
[MONOKUMA] We're three
for three, sports fans!
And you know
what that means!
A li'l free time to collect
your thoughts, and...
Boomshakalaka!
Trial!
What...? I don't...
[TOGAMI] It's part of
the ritual here.
Oh, right.
When he made the
announcement for Maizono,
you were still asleep. I forgot.
Once three people find a corpse,
the clock starts ticking.
[TOGAMI] Ishimaru!
Go round up the rest of us!
[ISHIMARU] Uh yeah, on it!
Another killer
on the loose...
And the game is officially
afoot once again.
[NAEGI] The others joined us
in the locker room
in what seemed
like record time.
We stared at the body;
fear and anger
clouding our faces.
One of us was looking
at their own handiwork.
But who...?
[FUKAWA] B-b-b-b-blood...!
[NAEGI]
"Victim is Chihiro Fujisaki."
"Time of death: Roughly 2 a.m."
"The corpse was found in
the 2nd floor girls' locker room
in the classroom area."
"The fatal injury was a blow
to the head by a blunt object."
"Death occurred instantly."
That dumbbell over
there is the weapon.
It's gotta be.
And I think they
killed her right here.
[KIRIGI gasps]
[KIRIGIRI] That's not rope.
It's an extension cord.
[NAEGI] Extension cord, huh?
Wasn't there one in the library?
[KIRIGIRI] Yes... I do seem
to remember seeing it there.
[NAEGI] Hey...
You don't see her digital
notebook anywhere, do you?
It's gotta be around...
[HAGAKURE] Hey, look!
Another dying message!
[ASAHINA]
Slow your roll, Hardy Boy.
[OHGAMI] Huh...
After I was done with
my workout last night,
I spilled my protein
coffee on this rug,
but now there's no sign
of the stain that it left.
[NAEGI] How does a
coffee stain disappear?
Wait...
that pin-up seems like
kind of an odd choice...
[NAEGI] So, what
do we have in ours?
[NAEGI] A poster
from some boy-band?
I don't get it.
I last saw Fujisaki
back in the storage area.
She had a jersey in a duffel
bag, and she was in a rush.
Maybe she
rendezvoused with someone.
If they met up here,
then where's her bag?
This is the work
of Genocider Sho.
Wait... How do I
know that name...?
Y'mean that serial killer
who popped up recently?
Curious yet? I'll allow you
to aid my investigation.
Uh?
Follow me.
[NAEGI] Hey, you know,
I just thought of something.
The Genocider Sho murders have
been a pretty big deal lately.
So, maybe we're
dealing with a copycat?
Sorry.
How can you be so sure?
Easily. Now hold your
tongue and listen.
[NAEGI] Whoa.
Confidential police files?
[TOGAMI] Normally, this
information is not released
to the public.
What the heck are they
even doing here?!
How do we know this
stuff is for real?
[TOGAMI] Your skepticism is
healthy, but I assure you,
these are genuine.
They match the copies
in my study at home.
Look, I get
that you're rich,
but they don't just
hand that info out.
[TOGAMI] That's one
of your weaknesses.
If something doesn't match
your ideals, you disregard it.
Here's the dossier
on Genocider Sho.
[NAEGI gasps]
[TOGAMI] He always writes
"Blood bath fever" in blood
at the murder scene,
the victims are always male,
and scissors are
always the weapon.
[TOGAMI] Based on his profile,
Sho might suffer from
dissociative identity disorder--
what we used to call
"multiple personalities."
Also, every one of his victims
thus far has been crucified,
although that detail is only
known to a select few officers.
You really... think that...
Genocider Sho is
in here with us?!
[ASAHINA] Thank goodness
I found you two!
Fukawa's gone off
the deep end!
[ASAHINA] She's been acting off
ever since we found the body.
Now she's locked in her room,
but yelled through the door that
she wants to talk to Togami.
[doorbell rings]
[ASAHINA] You doing
all right in there?
I brought Togami!
[FUKAWA] He's really here...?
I'm so sorry, Togami...
I couldn't keep my promise...
I thought I could,
but it was just too hard!
[FUKAWA] But... y'know?!
I'm okay! I've got
it under control!
I'm calling the shots again!
Listen up:
Genocider Sho is not gonna
add me to her body-count!
--[doorbell ringing]
--Fukawa, wait! Open the door!
--[NAEGI] What...
--None of that made any sense!
--What is going on here...?
--Try again without the crazy?
--[intercom chimes]
--Okay? Fukawa?!
[MONOKUMA] I know the idea's
that I give you toddlers
a chance to figure
out whodunit,
but this is like
watching paint dry!
Enough shufflin' your feet!
It's time to Trial!