Yasu... hi... ro...
[ASAHINA gasps]
[MONOKUMA]
♪ Ba-ba-ba-buuuum! ♪
Double corpse alert, chickadees!
Stop me if you've heard this
one: investigation, then, trial!
Oh. Great. The damn bear.
As if he weren't taxing enough,
he has to suck all the
fun out of this round.
Thanks for the buzz kill!
I believe we'd all appreciate
it if the pair of you
could rein in your
callousness just a smidge.
I'm in no mood to be delicate.
I've wasted enough mental energy
on this farce as it is.
"Yasuhiro"... Odd final words...
No. It's... quite telling;
that's Hagakure's first name.
[TOGAMI] Very well,
I'll sum up.
Hagakure dons a ridiculous
costume, attacks you,
then kills these two before
playing hide-and-seek
with their remains for
reasons best known to himself.
Case closed.
Let's get him.
What about the other one?
Kirigiri is
still missing, right?
No, just... don't go there!
I'm sorry, Naegi...
But we must at least
consider the possibility
she was his accomplice.
A rather fruitless venture
to involve herself in.
Only the actual killer
is eligible to graduate.
Unless she herself
struck these fellows down...
...the girl gets a
great big ol' goose egg!
Granted this has
all the benchmarks
of an open and shut case.
However...
I still think a thorough
investigation is called for.
[NAEGI] Yeah, sure...
You guys search for clues;
I'll try to find the others.
Where could they've gone?
It's not like this
place is that big.
[KIRIGIRI] Naegi.
[NAEGI] Kiri, jeez!
Where have you been?!
I was--
Bring everyone
to the pool.
[NAEGI gasps]
[TOGAMI] Well? We're all
waiting for an explanation.
Out with it! This is
no time to play coy!
Why are we here?!
[KIRIGIRI] This.
[ALL gasp]
[NAEGI] Justice Robo?!
[HAGAKURE] It is
officially not my day.
[HAGAKURE grunts]
Yamada's dying words
were in reference
to this one's given name.
So why'd he shut
himself in a locker?
[crashing,
HAGAKURE yells]
[HAGAKURE] Little help, please?
Next time choose a costume
that bends at the waist.
Word to the wise:
form equals function.
[NAEGI] There's a
clasp on the back.
Not so rough!
--Man, it pinches like a mother.
--Someone prefers their cosplay
rather form-fitting.
How did you get into this?
Cardinal rule of cosplay:
make sure you can
still go to the can!
Hold on, you don't think
I made this piece of crap?!
I swear on my life it wasn't me!
Some joker slipped a
note under my door,
told me to meet 'em after
hours in the game room.
I show up like a moron...
And bam! Lights out!
Easy!
When I woke up, I'd been
crammed into this thing.
[TOGAMI] Very interesting.
Show us the note.
Yeah, no problem.
Think I stuck it my pocket...
Um...?!
If you want us to take
your story seriously,
I suggest you find it.
[ASAHINA] Oh, whatever!
Stop playing us!
Just admit you're
the culprit already!
Excuse me?
The hell are you
talking about?!
However he got there, it's a
good thing we found him alive.
First rate detective work, Kiri.
What were you on the outside?
--An amateur sleuth?
--[ASAHINA yells]
[HAGAKURE] Girl, chill!
[NAEGI] Kiri, hold up!
I need to talk to you!
No offense, but where
were you this whole time?
When we split up,
it's like you just vanished.
Working a separate
investigation.
What is that
supposed to mean?
[KIRIGIRI] Look,
don't worry about it.
[NAEGI] I just want to--
It's nothing, all right?
Leave it.
I need to see the bodies
while they're still fresh.
There's something you
definitely don't think
you're gonna hear when you
wake up in the morning.
Wounds indicate death from
blunt force trauma to the head.
Evidence suggests
both were killed
with the same type of weapon.
So far, that's all
the info we've got.
[KIRIGIRI] Both murders occurred
back to back, the second victim
expiring in full view
of witnesses, correct?
[NAEGI] Yeah.
[KIRIGIRI] Very well.
That doesn't give us much,
but it's a start.
Let's hope the bodies
themselves have more to add.
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
[NAEGI] Managed to scrounge
up a handful of possible clues.
Not that they make much sense.
The thing that puzzles me most
was Yamada saying Hagakure's
first name as he died.
Could things really
be that simple?
[MONOKUMA] All right,
let's get the ball rollin'.
Someone's grubby li'l paws
were itchin' for some easy cash.
Bad enough to make 'em
murder not one,
but two of your classmates.
Who was it?
--Like that's a big mystery.
--[MONOKUMA laughs]
Ohhh...?
Not only does he
lack a credible alibi
for murder and/or
body snatching,
he was caught in flagrante
wearing the
cosplay in question.
That's you, Yasuhiro Hagakure.
I'm tellin' ya
it wasn't me!
Oh, give it a rest...
Yamada said your name
with his last breath!
Son of a-- So what?!
I was in La-La Land the
whole time, remember?
Shut your
lie-hole, murderer!
Dude! Like you're one to judge!
Order, please...
Much though it
pains me to say so,
further evidence
has been uncovered.
Highly, suggestive items
were found in your room.
Together, these parts
and blueprints
speak for themselves.
The soothsayer is without
a doubt our murderer.
No, that's incorrect!
It can't be established
beyond a reasonable doubt
that he wrote those
blueprints himself.
You have something to share?
Matter of fact, yes I do.
This is the note Hagakure
wrote me earlier today.
Look closely,
compare the handwriting.
They don't match up.
[CELESTIA] He likely changed
styles to cover his tracks.
[HAGAKURE] My writing's
barely legible as it is!
[NAEGI] Something else...
After killing Ishimaru, the
murderer almost certainly
used the flatbed cart
to move his body.
We can deduce as much
from the blood on its wheels.
But the Justice Robo costume
doesn't bend at the waist,
meaning Hagakure couldn't
have operated the cart
while wearing it.
[TOGAMI] I see...
So, Hagakure was indeed subdued
and stuffed into the outfit
as he maintains,
ergo not our culprit.
[HAGAKURE]
Naegi! Bro! Thanks!
--I owe you big time!
--Kid's a regular Sam Spade!
Hold on a sec...
What about the pic Celestia has
of Justice Robo
attacking Yamada?
[OHGAMI] Exactly.
Hagakure couldn't very well have
accomplished that unconscious.
You both raise a fine point.
With photographic evidence,
he's still our only
plausible suspect.
Wait! Don't shrug him off!
Yes, we're jumping
the proverbial gun here.
It behooves us to weigh all
possibilities carefully.
Too much is still in question.
[CELESTIA sighs]
If Hagakure's innocent,
we've but one other choice.
The only person
who lacks an alibi
for the time of the murders.
And I'm afraid
that's you, Kirigiri.
You must be the perpetrator.
[NAEGI gasps]
[KIRIGIRI] A fair assumption...
But ask yourself whether,
even with a flatbed cart,
a girl of my size would be
capable of moving Yamada.
Well, a gal the size
of an ogre would be!
Yeah, but the ogre
was on the second floor
at the time, wasn't she?
Only one person could
have managed it.
Consider the possibility that
Yamada simply moved himself.
[ALL gasp]
[KIRIGIRI] As in: he walked up
the stairs of his own volition.
[OHGAMI] But that
would mean he...
would've been alive
the entire time!
[CELESTIA] No...
I'm afraid that doesn't
make a lick of sense.
[KIRIGIRI] What precisely
contradicts my theory?
The timing of the corpse
announcement, for one.
It was played at exactly
the moment Yamada's body
was found the first time
in the nurse's office.
[KIRIGIRI] Correct me if I'm
wrong, but weren't Yamada
and Ishimaru found within
moments of each other?
So Monokuma cut corners
by making an announcement
that covered both discoveries.
[MONOKUMA] I do not
cut corners, young lady.
One, count 'em, one
announcement per corpse,
according to protocol.
[CELESTIA] Fine...
Discounting their obvious
change of position,
nothing on either body
indicated movement.
Nor is Yamada a
good enough actor
to have played possum
so convincingly.
You're leaving something out!
By all means, what
detail have I missed?
[NAEGI] When we first
found Yamada's body,
his glasses were
dripping with blood.
It's an image that's
stayed with me.
But when he turned up later
in the art supply room,
his glasses were clean.
He must've wiped them off
to see where he was going.
That's the only explanation.
[ASAHINA] Where'd the blood come
from in the first place, then?
It's simple.
There's an emergency stash
in the nurse's office,
presumably for transfusions.
He'd have certainly had access.
Sounds like Tubby McFatass
got kinda overzealous
applying the Realism
Rouge. Ha! What a rube.
[CELESTIA] And no one saw him
while he was on the move?
[OHGAMI] Now that
I consider it...
While tracking down the bodies,
Asahina and I noticed the
art supply room was locked.
That door can only be
locked from the inside,
so somebody had to be in there.
All else being as you say,
it must have been Yamada.
He had probably
just moved Ishimaru.
That's so creepy.
Indeed, and as it happens
I have hard evidence
to back up
Ohgami's assumption.
This scrap of paper was
found in Ishimaru's hand.
The rest however,
was stuffed into Yamada's...
...unmentionables.
--What were you doing in there?!
--You went trouser fishing?!
Yes, yes. Whatever.
Thankfully I didn't
have to dig very deep.
[HAGAKURE] Ah! That's
just like the one I got
telling me to go
to the game room!
Almost. But not quite.
Because this cryptic
note led Ishimaru
to an untimely demise.
Knowing it'd be used as
evidence against him,
Yamada hid it where he
assumed no one would find it.
[FUKAWA (SHO)]
In his tighty-whities!
Wait. The hammers, though.
If we go by the order,
Celestia and Yamada got konked,
then Yamada got killed,
followed by Ishimaru, right?
[NAEGI] I'm starting to think
the murderer numbered
the hammers to mislead us.
We now know Yamada
wasn't actually killed
until after Ishimaru.
So the numbers don't really have
anything to do with the order
in which they were used.
Sure! That makes sense.
All right. Then which
hammer had the honor
of dealing the fatal
blow to Yamada?
The one hanging on the wall.
It looked like somebody
had washed it.
I'm bettin' that's
our final weapon.
Call it "Justice Hammer Five."
Clearly, Yamada wasn't just an
unfortunate victim in all this.
He moved Ishimaru's body,
so at the very least
he was an accomplice.
But accomplices don't
graduate, do they?
No.
I think the real murderer
conned Yamada into helping
and then double-crossed him.
[MONOKUMA] Okay!
Time's up, jurors!
Justice be damned, the
fat lady's in full voice!
Who's da doity double dealer
what persuaded our favorite
basement dweller to help
moidah the ex-hall monitor?
only to moicilessly
ice the blubber-butt
once he'd outlived
his usefulness?
[ASAHINA] Dang it,
this was so straightforward
when we came in here. How're we
supposed to figure it out now?
Yep. Sucks when you
got nothin' else to go on!
Come, now; the murderer
must've slipped up somewhere.
We're dealing with a
formidable strategist.
Something tells me
they dotted every "I."
Then maybe it's not Hagakure.
So let's not forget
she without an alibi.
So, what? Our gooses're cooked?
It's just game over
for all of us?
All but one of us,
if we're wrong.
[NAEGI] I've gotta think...
There has to be something.
Go back...
Look at every detail...
Consider every angle...
Remember.
[CELESTIA] We're going to die...
Picked off one-by-one
'til there's...
'til there's no one...
Exactly like they were.
Wait, Celestia.
You said something
in the nurse's office
earlier this afternoon
when we found Yamada's body.
Can you please repeat it?
Well, let me think...
What was it?
I believe something like "we'll
be picked off one-by-one?
Exactly like they were,"
if my memory serves.
Is that what you meant?
Yeah, that's what
I thought you said.
You were in a panic, I know.
We all were.
No one could blame you for
talking out of your head
like that. But "they?"
At that point you shouldn't
have known Ishimaru was dead.
[CELESTIA] Speaking of
things said in a panic,
Try to think clearly,
Naegi darling.
What about this photo?
Easy...
It's not a snapshot of
Yamada being attacked
by Justice Robo at all.
[CELESTIA] No?
[NAEGI] Look close...
It's of him carrying
an unconscious Hagakure.
[CELESTIA giggles]
Whatever did I do to
make you want to paint me
as the villain in all this?
Because even for a
feeble-minded jackass,
you couldn't be more
sorely mistaken!
Celestia, what's
gotten into you?!
No... You're the only answer
that ties up all the loose ends.
Are you as deaf
as you are thick?
Yamada invoked the
killer's friggin' name
as he drew his final breath!
Why must you make it
so difficult?
Dammit!
Yasuhiro Hagakure
is the murderer!
I'm sorry...
And you almost pulled off
the perfect crime...
Shut up! You know nothing!
Y'hear me? Nothing!
The only thing we
don't really know is...
your real name!
How dare you accuse me
of sharing a ludicrous name
like "Yasuhiro"
with that troll?!
I should throttle you!
Fine, let's say I'm wrong!
All you gotta do is
tell us who you are.
Gladly!
But I expect you to give me
your full, undivided attention!
My real name is
Celestia Ludenberg!
Unless you got proof otherwise,
you can crawl back into
the reeking cesspool
from whence you came!
[NAEGI] I got plenty of proof.
[CELESTIA gasps]
Our digital notebooks are
programmed to display
our full names when
we power them on.
I'd like to see yours.
[NAEGI] The jig is up...
And you've lost.
[CELESTIA giggles]
"You've lost."
Dear, oh dear.
That string of words
takes me back.
Haven't heard them in a while.
Roll the dice...
And like that, it's over.
Is that a confession?
You admit to killing them both?
Honesty; refreshing
for a change.
What purpose would it
serve to be a sore loser?
The house does always
have the advantage.
[CELESTIA] Monokuma, sir...
May we get this over
with? Please...
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] You got it, babe!
Jurors! Lock in your votes!
[machine whistles]
[MONOKUMA] Right again!
Congratulations!
The sinister strategist behind
this dubious double homicide
is none other than
Celestia Ludenberg,
a.k.a. Taeko Yasuhiro!
"Yasuhiro," I was right.
[CELESTIA] If only the
disgusting tub of lard
would've kept
his piehole shut.
A damn shame.
Mark my words,
this is the last time
I'll put my faith
in another human being.
[KIRIGIRI] I see.
So you stole Alter Ego from the
locker room to spur him on?
Oh, yes! Worked like a charm!
A simple matter, when you
know which buttons to push.
I'm sorry...
I took this in Ishimaru's room.
[YAMADA screams]
I knew he had it in him!
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it!
Mmm, but I thought Alter Ego
was programmed to shriek
if either of us came
within five feet?
Forgive me...
I was extorted into
pilfering it on his behalf.
Wha--?!
No, that's not true...
The fact is he raised a hand
to me and I surrendered.
The filthy barbarian!
On top of coming between me and
the reason for my existence,
he dared manhandle a lady?!
By the flaming moons of hell
I will be his apocalypse!
We'll do it together.
Give him everything he deserves.
[YAMADA gasps]
[OHGAMI] What manner of
woman does that to a man?
And after playing dead
for you, what, pray tell,
did Yamada think was
next on his to-do list?
Stammer something to the effect
of his having barely escaped
with his life,
or what have you...
If pressed for details,
he could always feign amnesia.
Ha-ha! And Fatass actually
went along with it?!
[CELESTIA] As far
as he was concerned,
the plan was for
me to kill one of you
while he was being
interrogated...
I'd have a distraction;
he'd have an alibi.
He followed along like a loyal
puppy 'til the bitter end,
believing I'd hatched a plan
by which we'd both graduate.
Love leaves one vulnerable
to all sorts of
foolishness I suppose.
So your back wasn't against
the wall when you killed him;
you were planning to
do it from the beginning!
I was desperate...
The plan is scarcely coherent
unless the one who plays dead
winds up dead in fact later on;
or then what's the point?
Desperate; you out
of everyone here?
No joke! What about
living in harmony
and making the best of things
and all that noise?
That was bullshit!
You idiots don't know the
first thing about desperate!
I'd have mowed down all of you
to get out of this
Roman Holiday!
You see...
The grandest of dreams
was within my reach.
A fairy-tale castle.
One fit for an empress...
Where I could recline in
palatial comfort:
be waited on hand and foot
for the rest of my life.
It's what I deserve!
And the things
I stooped to;
everything but the shirt off my
back was gambled away
trying to make that
dream a reality...
Then Monokuma unveils
his mountain of cash
and all I could
think was "jackpot!"
So close I could
almost taste it.
Such a tragedy...
Why must dreams tease
us so mercilessly?
How can you be so
calm about all this?
For crap's sake,
you're about to be executed!
Aren't you terrified?!
[CELESTIA giggles]
Oh, I imagine deep down I'm
absolutely paralyzed with fear,
but there again,
you have my talent...
I'm so good at
deceiving everyone else,
deceiving myself
is child's play.
In a previous life
I'm sure I had to have
been Marie Antoinette.
So you're, uh...
familiar with execution.
Best of luck.
Though I know it's
hollow coming from me.
[CELESTIA] Maybe dreams
aren't so merciless...
But no...
Now is a cruel time
for epiphanies.
Farewell, everyone. Heh.
In another life,
perhaps we'll meet again.
[KIRIGIRI] She hid it
right under our noses.
[NAEGI] I'm just glad it's okay.
[KIRIGIRI]
That's one problem solved.
So, um...
When you were off by yourself,
what were you investigating?
[KIRIGIRI] I told you
not to worry about it.
[NAEGI] Yeah, well,
for your information,
I was worried about you!
Like I was sayin'...
You practically vanished.
[KIRIGIRI] I get it.
It's okay. Frankly in your shoes
I'd think I was the mole, too.
You're perfectly right
to be suspicious.
[NAEGI] What?
But I'm not! I...
I'd follow you into battle
I trust you so much!
[KIRIGIRI] Not a very
wise thing to say.
[NAEGI] So what?!
We're friends aren't we?
I trust you...
I'm just hoping you'll
return the favor.
Trust, huh...?
Very well, then.
Perhaps it's not unwise to see
where this will lead us...
Listen to me carefully.
When off on my own,
I came across a room.
Specifically the boy's restroom
on the second floor.
No cameras.
No monitors.
Look for the storage closet.
And check the back wall.
Holy crap she was right.
[NAEGI] "You must not
leave this place."
[NAEGI groans]
[NAEGI] What...?
It can't be...
Tell me I'm dreaming...
It's all gone?!
[blows landing]
[NAEGI] Whatever's happening...
Please...
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] What the hell?!
What's going on?!