[OHGAMI roars]
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] What's with
the sudden attitude?
Are you forgetting
I call the shots here?
We had ourselves a deal, chica!
I've made my decision...
This is over...
I'm sick of it...
And I'm sick of you...
That's why you're going down.
[MONOKUMA] Fair enough...
"Bear" in mind though,
if anything happens to me,
my hostages get
turned into skirt steak.
[OHGAMI growls]
[NAEGI] Wait... hostages...?
And what does he mean deal?
Does this mean...
Ohgami is the mole?!
[NAEGI] Three trials
into our "education,"
Monokuma unlocked the
school's fourth floor.
So, like always,
we scoped it out.
Jeez, would it have
killed Togami and Fukawa
to join us while we
look around up here?
Is there a problem, Naegi?
No! Heh. Everything's
just fine!
[NAEGI] The new floor
included the teachers' lounge,
and the chemistry lab...
[ASAHINA] Check it out!
Prodolumen X!
It's like god-tier protein!
Not over here...
Y'see this bottle?
It's a lethal poison.
[NAEGI] ...along
with the music room...
[NAEGI] ...the computer lab...
Wonder why it's locked?
[NAEGI] ...and the
principal's office.
[NAEGI] It's locked, too.
[KIRIGIRI] Naegi.
[NAEGI] Kiri, hey!
Do you have a moment?
I trust you found...
what I told you about?
[NAEGI] Uh... Yeah...
Thing is, soon as I
started to look around,
someone knocked me out.
By the time I woke up,
they had taken everything.
Damn...
[NAEGI] Oh, right...
I almost forgot...
I found this
really weird note.
How about we save that
topic for another time?
Huh?
[KIRIGIRI] Tell me the truth...
Are you... keeping
secrets from me?
Uh, why do you ask?
[NAEGI] Yeah, it looks
like Ohgami's a mole...
But...
I can't spread that around
'til I know for sure...
I'm sorry. I am.
You're the one who said we
should pool our knowledge!
What happened to doing
this as friends, Naegi?
[KIRIGIRI] Forget it...
Sorry...
[HAGAKURE sighs]
That floor gave us
a whole lotta nothin'.
[KIRIGIRI] Patience.
There may still be some leads
in the principal's office.
Or perhaps lurking
in the computer lab.
If only we could get in.
Hey yo, Hercu-Lady!
You wanna do us a solid
and break down
those doors, maybe?
[MONOKUMA]
Nice try, Brat Brigade!
So that's the plan?
Bust into my
sanctum sanctorum?!
Kids these days are
so gosh-darn violent!
Not to harsh your mellow by
movin' the goalposts, but...
[digital notebooks chime]
[NAEGI] He just tacked
on a new rule for us.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA]
I know I'll sleep easier!
Ta-ta!
He sure added that one
in a hurry, didn't he?
I mean, one of those rooms
must be hiding something
or why would he even bother?
Wait! Of course!
We're not dead in the
water yet, you guys!
We're not?
We've still got a
friend in cyberspace!
[ALTER EGO]
You came to see me! Great!
I just bypassed the
File Security Protocol!
Bitchin'! Nice goin'!
Well...
it seems as though the
school was in the process
of enacting a certain
plan when it shut down.
[ALTER EGO] It involved
the isolation of students
within the Hope's Peak
High School campus
who are then never allowed
off school grounds.
That's not even the most
shocking aspect of the plan.
In some cases,
they'd be forced to live out
their entire lives here.
Wait...
That sounds like...
[OHGAMI] ...the very thing
we're being subjected to.
[ALTER EGO] And this wasn't
some idea dictated to them
from outside...
The school itself
came up with it.
But to what end?
[ALTER EGO]
The plan was created
because of something that
happened one year ago:
The most
despair-inducing incident
in the history of mankind.
"The most
despair-inducing incident
in the history of mankind?"
Because of what happened...
Hope's Peak High was forced
to shut its doors forever.
The isolation plan
was put into effect.
The architect of the plan
was none other than...
the principal.
[ALL gasp]
I've learned...
that he's a man in
his late thirties...
And the odds of him still
being on-campus are rather high.
So he's the brains
behind the bear!
We gotta track this guy down!
I'll find the principal...
I have to be the one.
And then...
I'll make him answer for this...
I swear it!
[NAEGI] What was that...?
[ALTER EGO]
Oh, one more thing!
While looking
through the new data,
I discovered an image file.
[ALL gasp]
[TOGAMI] More impossible photos?
[ASAHINA] S'gotta mean
something, but what?
[MONOKUMA] Testing,
testing... one, two, three...
Hey, kiddos! How 'bout you hoss
your freight over to the gym!
What's he want this time?
I guess... we might
as well do as he says.
[MONOKUMA] Spring in
your steps and all that!
[MONOKUMA] Ow! So hot,
I can't hold it!
[HAGAKURE] Party foul.
[MONOKUMA] I have
something sad to tell you!
And no, it's not
about the squid...
One of you's working for me.
What?!
So there's a mole?!
No one listens to me...
Keeping tabs on us all
would require a henchman.
Who?! Who's the traitor?!
Please, you've gotta tell us!
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] How can I resist
when she asks so nicely?
My lackey isssss...
[MONOKUMA] Sakura Ohgami!
Whoa! The Amazon?!
I don't believe it...
Hey! Don't say that!
You know it can't be true!
Tell 'em, Sakura.
[ASAHINA gasps]
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Spoiler bomb:
I'm telling the truth for once!
And delicate orchid that she is,
I don't think Ohgami's goin'
down without a fight!
[MONOKUMA laughs]
Sakura...
Why...?
Keeping it from you...
was the hardest part.
[HAGAKURE gasps]
Holy crap! You really are
working for the bear!
You've been
lying from the start!
Hey! Just give it a rest!
I mean...
I'm sure she only did it
'cause he forced her to!
She's right!
I saw the two of 'em earlier...
Ohgami was attacking Monokuma,
and not pulling any punches.
But then he mentioned
something about hostages,
and she stood down.
You witnessed all of that?
Ohgami only obeyed
because hostages
were being threatened.
But she's back on our side, so--
[TOGAMI] Oh, give it a rest.
Do you believe this nonsense
that tumbles out of your mouth?
Hey...
If you've really
switched allegiances,
then tell me something:
The name of our jailor.
Alas...
I was never entrusted
with that detail.
Tch. Well isn't
that convenient?
All right...
To what end did your master
plan your little charade?
[OHGAMI] If we ever
reached the point
where no murders
were occurring...
either at first or later on...
I was to kill someone.
[gasping]
There you have it.
She's been waiting
this whole time
for an opportune
moment in which to pounce.
Dammit, she isn't like that!
Wait!
Enough of this...
There is no need for you
to be at odds over me.
The time has come...
to reap what I've sown.
Asahina, dear...
I am so very sorry.
Why didn't you...?
There were so many times
when I nearly broke down
and told you the truth.
But I couldn't...
I was afraid...
Afraid that you, my only
friend here, would despise me.
But I wouldn't've...!
[OHGAMI] I don't
deserve forgiveness.
But I will make this up
to you-- even if it kills me.
Huh? Even if it kills you...?
[TOGAMI] Empty words
from a treacherous brute
better off avoided.
We don't know what she might do.
You're not helping
things, Togami!
[HAGAKURE] Hold up!
I think blondie's
got a good point!
She...
She admitted she was his lackey!
[ASAHINA] What the hell?
Do you really not know
Sakura any better than that?!
[TOGAMI] We don't know
the first thing about her
and neither do you.
You were as shocked by
this as the rest of us.
Yeah... I was...
If she goes all "Hulk smash!"
on the dude in charge,
I'll trust her again!
[ASAHINA] Shut up!
What if something
horrible happened to her?!
[TOGAMI] Feh.
If it did...
so what?
It's one less person
in the enemy's ranks.
Let her die.
[ASAHINA growls]
[blow lands]
[gasping]
[ASAHINA] Bastard...
How dare you...?
Shut'cher mouth...
or I'll kill you myself!
[TOGAMI laughs]
Temper, temper...
Look...
if you want me dead...
do your worst...
Are you going to
slap me to death?
Maybe I will.
You deserve it!
You...
You filthy cow!
Shut your whore mouth!
Nobody threatens
my beloved Togami!
[KIRIGIRI] Enough, all of you!
[gasping]
[KIRIGIRI] When we fight
amongst ourselves,
we're just playing
right into their hands.
Whatever.
I'm outta here.
[TOGAMI] Hmph.
Togami...
Am I correct in saying you don't
place much value in emotions?
You are correct, yes.
I'm warning you...
They do carry weight.
And you disregard them
at your own peril.
You'll forgive me if I'm
not quaking in my boots.
--[school bells chime]
--[MONOKUMA] Hey, it's 10
and the night hours
are about to begin!
Good night, sleep tight,
do your bestest to
live through the night!
[NAEGI sighs]
[HAGAKURE screams]
[NAEGI gasps]
[FUKAWA (SHO) cackles]
What's going on here?
Uh! They started to
argue, and then...
out came the crazier one!
How nice of you
to join us, Naegi!
Now tell Tits McGee
here to take a powder.
'Cause if she doesn't...
I'm liable to snip
those sweater-puppies
clean off her torso, and
that'll just be the foreplay!
[FUKAWA (SHO) laughs]
[NAEGI] Asahina!
Let's getcha to
the nurse's office.
Hagakure!
Help me out!
[HAGAKURE] Huh?! Uh... sure...!
[ASAHINA growls]
Y'lucked out.
It's just a scratch.
Yeah... Thank you.
[HAGAKURE laughs]
If I didn't shoot under
that table and yell,
you'd be dead meat!
Guess I saved the day!
Gee. There was a coward
around when I needed one.
My hero.
[NAEGI] Asahina...
[HAGAKURE] Your grateful
face needs improvement.
Tell me one thing:
Why were you fighting?
[ASAHINA] C'mon,
I'm sure you can guess.
It was about Sakura.
Sho was saying...
such despicable things...
Things about my best friend!
Asahina!
Are you all right?!
Who-- Who did that to you?!
Tell me!
Nah. It's really not a big deal.
What're ya looking at me for?!
That crazy chick's
the one who cut her!
The psycho killer
living in Fukawa's head!
[OHGAMI growls]
To think Asahina...
was hurt because of my
treacherous deeds...
This degree of villainy...
is unacceptaaaaaable!
[HAGAKURE screams]
[HAGAKURE] Innocent bystander!
Innocent bystander!
[OHGAMI growls]
No longer!
I will not allow
this to continuuue!
[NAEGI] Just calm down! Ohgami!
[ASAHINA] Sakura!
[KIRIGIRI] Is there a problem?
[NAEGI] Kiri! Help us!
We have to hold her back!
[OHGAMI] That won't
be necessary.
I'm not going to hurt her.
I'll tell her to just
leave Asahina out of this.
No, wait! Come back!
[KIRIGIRI sighs]
So, uh...
are you still angry?
Take that as a yes...
'Cause, um...
I've earned it...
I'm not.
That thing you were
keeping from me...
it was the truth
about Ohgami, wasn't it?
You didn't want to drop that
bombshell on us without proof,
so you waited.
I see your logic.
But your discretion
is still insulting.
[NAEGI] Huh?
At heart, doesn't
it just go to show
you're not entirely
sure I can be trusted?
I...
guess it does...
Sorry...
[KIRIGIRI] No need...
Water under the
bridge at this point.
Besides...
There's a chance I might've...
"overreacted" a bit.
Well, yes.
Enough about that. I'm here
because Fujisaki's avatar
would like a word with us.
You came to
visit me, great!
Can't imagine he'd
ask us down here
unless it was something big.
[ALTER EGO] Well...
I'd like you to take
this laptop somewhere
that I can interface with
the school's network.
'Cause I...
I don't want
anybody else to die!
That's why I'm going to
help you get out of here.
[NAEGI gasps]
But I can't...
Not while I'm stuck on
this puny hard drive.
Without network access,
I can't help you at all!
[NAEGI] Huh... Seems risky...
I'm aware of the
dangers involved.
Even so...
I want to do my part!
I'll be fine!
Whenever I think of how brave
you've been, I feel brave, too!
I guess that's a silly
thing for an AI to say,
but I really do mean it!
It's 'cause of you!
So be it.
Let's get him hooked up
to the school's network.
But... what if he...?
I want to honor
the choice he's made.
Yeah, you're right...
If we're smart about this...
and get lucky...
maybe our foe won't
even notice him.
That hidden chamber
beyond the bathroom
has no surveillance
cameras in it.
And I remember there being
a network access port.
However...
we have no clue how close of
an eye he's been keeping
on the system.
That said...
it's still a gamble
worth taking.
Yeah it is...
And I'd like to be the one to
take him to the room,
if that's okay.
[ALTER EGO] Are we there yet?
Let's get ya plugged in.
[ALTER EGO] Yup!
Everything looks good.
[ALTER EGO] You can
leave the rest to me!
I'll be sure to track
down some useful clues!
Just cross your fingers
and hang tight!
So you...
think of me as a friend?
That means a lot!
Thank you!
[MONOKUMA] RIP, Super High
School-Level Grappler (lol)!
A Locked-Room Murder (lol)!
I don't know if you
guys realized this,
but parentheses are
freakin' amaze-balls!
No matter what horrible thing
you put out there,
so long as you slap a
parenthetical "lol"
afterwards, it's all gravy!
Back on topic!
We got seven students
still alive and kickin'.
Think it's gonna stay there?
Or are we heading
down to six?
[NAEGI] Everyone's handling
this differently...
[NAEGI] All I can do
is believe in them.
And hope they do
the right thing.
[KIRIGIRI] Naegi...!
[NAEGI] Did something happen?
[ASAHINA] It...
it's Sakura, she...
[NAEGI] What's she doing?!
[NAEGI] It's no good!
[NAEGI grunts]
Ohgami! Open the door!
I tried that...
Why doesn't she answer?
Oh, man...
Either the door has been
locked from the inside,
or something in there
is actively preventing
the knob from turning.
[ASAHINA] We have
to get in there!
Do something!
[NAEGI] Ohgami!
[NAEGI gasps]
[MONOKUMA] And behind door
number one-- that's right,
a big beefy dead chick!
Scramble around
awhile for clues,
and then we'll get down
to the judge-mo-fyin'!
Not again...
Sadly... this was inevitable.
[ASAHINA] Of course...
They killed Sakura...
Of course they killed her.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get the others now...
[NAEGI] Asahina...
[ASAHINA] I'm fine...
Couldn't be better...
[KIRIGIRI] I see two separate
instances of head trauma.
[KIRIGIRI] Seems to
have vomited blood.
[KIRIGIRI] Powder spilled
on the top of her trainers.
That's pretty
amazing... seriously.
Still freaks me out to
look at a body up close.
All I can figure is...
I must've worked with
corpses sometime before.
Huh?
Nothing.
Just thinking out loud.
Sorry.
The sole door to the crime scene
was barred from within.
It seems we have a locked-room
murder on our hands.
A "locked-room" murder?
[NAEGI] That door was
definitely jammed shut.
So how did the
killer escape
after they
barricaded the room?
[HAGAKURE] Dude!
What if... she's fakin'...?!
We-hell... Ain't
this a kick in the dick?
She's dead; you heard the
corpse announcement, didn't you?
[ASAHINA] Togami...
Hagakure...
Fukawa...
I know one of you
bastards did this...
One of you killed Sakura Ohgami!
Wait a sec...
How do you know?
She told me herself...
she asked for the three of them
to come and meet her here!
[NAEGI] Is that true?
[ASAHINA] Those three...
were the last people
to see her alive!
Whoever killed her,
I'm gonna make you pay!
[MONOKUMA laughs]