[NAEGI]
Hope's Peak High School...
A hell on earth where the
only way to graduate
is murder.
[NAEGI] As long as you don't
get caught, you go free.
[NAEGI] And now
Maizono's dead...
Butchered.
The prime suspect is me...
Thing is, I'm innocent.
She would tell you herself:
I couldn't hurt a fly.
[NAEGI] Here we go...
Good luck, everybody.
[NAEGI] We're gonna need it.
Holy crap...
Swank for a courtroom.
[MONOKUMA] Goodie gumdrop!
Took your time, I see.
[MONOKUMA] Be honest, now:
you were expecting something
considerably less tasteful.
Screwed up either way,
if you ask me.
Before we start...
[ALL] Huh?
I have a question
relevant to our task.
Why the portraits?
[MONOKUMA] Why not?
Just 'cause they're dead,
I'd hate for them to
miss the proceedings.
[CELESTIA] And the extra
podium belongs to whom?
Counting our departed
classmates, we number fifteen.
Why sixteen places?
[MONOKUMA] You're readin'
too much into it, darlin'.
The extra podium just means
this courtroom is tricked out
for a maximum of sixteen jurors.
Speaking of which:
that's all the time we've
got for pleasantries.
Ladies and germs,
time to get judicial!
This is jacked up...
Nobody here really thinks
one of us killed her?
Hmph.
[MONOKUMA] They'd
be correct, m'boy!
No room for doubt, I'm afraid.
Right. Everybody
close your eyes!
If you're the murderer
raise your hand!
Yeah, that'll float
like an old lady's fart.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] Enough chit chat...
Commence debating
for your lives!
[NAEGI] I've got to
stay focused...
Unless I can convince them I
didn't do it,
we're all done for.
So, uh...
How does debating work?
Knowing where to start's
half the battle.
Well, I suggest we begin by
considering the murder weapon
itself, see where
that takes us.
We can be sure it was
the weapon because of
where it was found...
Sticking out of the
victim's mid-section
is not generally
where a knife is kept!
[OHWADA] Congratulations.
You're good.
[NAEGI] Don't blow him off;
it's important.
[OHWADA] What?
Just stop and think
about it for a sec.
The knife had to come
from the kitchen.
So does...
that mean anyone who was in the
kitchen last night is a suspect?
He's just tryin' to
get us to split hairs.
He's the killer, remember?
[ASAHINA] Wait, you know what?
I think I can prove Naegi
isn't the one who took it!
[gasping]
I would know, 'cause
Sakura and me
spent most of the day yesterday
hangin' out in the cafeteria.
[CELESTIA] I'm sorry...
Sakura is who, exactly?
No offense.
None taken.
[OHGAMI] We were
there until late...
Enjoying a lovely evening
tea, as it happens.
[ASAHINA] I was on edge...
Sakura was sweet enough
to keep me company
and try and calm my nerves.
[FUKAWA] Phugh, well...!
What if you both did it?
If you teamed up...
you'd just have to keep
your stories straight.
[MONOKUMA] Oh, please note:
if two or more people team up
to commit murder,
only the actual killer
is eligible for graduation.
No exceptions.
Yes. It's clearly
stated in the rules.
I see...
In other words, no one
stands to gain anything
from opting to team up.
[FUKAWA] Yeah, fine...
Then stop beating
around the bush
and tell us who took
the knife already!
Swim-hussy!
You take that back!
[OHGAMI] As Asahina said,
we were there for some time...
We know who took the knife
because we witnessed
its removal.
[TOGAMI] Why did you
not mention this sooner?
I guess...
'Cause it's... rude to
speak ill of the dead.
Wait, what?
[ASAHINA] It was Maizono...
I don't know why,
but it was definitely her.
But that doesn't
make sense...
Why would she take the knife?
[OHGAMI] I'm afraid
there can be no doubt.
How does royal
milk tea sound?
You're nice enough to stay
here; I should go all out.
[door opens]
Oh. Hi...
Just thought I'd get
myself something to drink.
[ASAHINA] At the time, it didn't
strike me as weird or anything.
[OHGAMI] Nor I.
[ISHIMARU] I see...
So the victim
procured the weapon
that would then end her life!
[MAIZONO] Good night.
Sweet dreams.
--Yes. Good night.
--Huh? Sure! Same to you.
[OHGAMI] Hm...?
Of course. Yeah...
She must've wanted it
to protect herself!
That being the case...
The very thing she thought to
fend off her attacker with
proved her undoing...
Simple, tragic irony
at its finest.
Yeah, no kidding.
All the same, Naegi...
You're still rather far
from clearing your name
in this bloody business.
[FUKAWA] Ah-ha! See?!
There's murder written
all over his face!
Damn it, I told you
it wasn't me!
Ooh! En garde, everyone!
He's attempting to steer
the debate in his favor!
What a skilled
manipulator you are!
[NAEGI] C'mon; why aren't
you getting it?!
If you pin this on me,
we all get executed!
[KIRIGIRI] Careful.
I'm of the opinion
it's still too early
to point the finger at Naegi.
[ALL gasp]
[KIRIGIRI] There's evidence
we're not considering.
[NAEGI gasps]
You believe me...?
[OHGAMI] What "evidence?"
I submit to you all the
state of the crime scene.
Did the culprit appear to
have easy access to the shower?
I think not.
[CELESTIA] What
are you driving at?
[NAEGI] The doorknob to
my shower was thrashed.
I saw it.
[YAMADA] In point of fact,
it did look like it'd
seen better days.
So?! What is that
supposed to prove
except he broke it
to get at his prey?!
Animal!
[KIRIGIRI] That one
small detail convinces me
that Naegi couldn't have
been the murderer.
What're you, nuts?
He needed in: Boom...
He broke it; end of story...
He didn't have any choice 'cause
she locked the door on him.
I can prove you wrong!
The shower doors don't
lock in the boys' rooms...
Only the girls' showers do.
Yeah? And how do you know that?
[NAEGI]
Monokuma said so himself.
Our showers don't have
locks installed...
Go on sir, tell them!
[MONOKUMA] Huh? Yeah,
sure. Whatever.
But, then why'd the killer
have to go to the trouble
of breaking the doorknob
to get at Maizono?
[NAEGI] Because my door's wonky.
There's a trick to opening it.
[FUJISAKI gasps]
They didn't know...
figured the door was locked...
For all intents and purposes,
to them it was a girl's room...
They'd have thought the only
option was to bust the doorknob.
[KIRIGIRI] If Naegi were the
murderer, he'd've been aware
the door doesn't lock and,
knowing the trick to opening it,
simply walked in.
[FUKAWA] Makes sense...
I suppose. Ugh.
[murmuring]
Whoa, thank you.
Don't get too
comfortable...
We're not done yet.
[CELESTIA] Let us assume the
murderer is someone else...
Where would they get the
idea the door was locked?
Were they not aware that
the two had switched rooms?
And why be there if they didn't?
That's the point...
From the evidence, I think
we can safely assume
the killer believed he or she
was actually in Maizono's room.
[FUJISAKI] Let me
get this straight...
You're saying the culprit was
in the dark about the room swap?
[FUKAWA] Please... We were
all in the dark about it!
This ain't exactly narrowing
our list of suspects!
So? Then we put it
to a majority vote...
That could work... Yeah.
I mean... we are in
a bit of a pinch, right?
Either we put someone
on the chopping block
or we all get the axe.
No need to throw our hands
in the air, Yasuhiro...
The devil is in the details...
I urge you all to focus.
[ASAHINA] Now that
I think about it...
If Maizono was freaked out
like Naegi says,
how'd the killer get into
the room to begin with?
She wouldn't have let 'em in.
[FUJISAKI] Was the lock picked?
[ISHIMARU] Not possible.
The tumblers are all
reinforced electronically.
Heh-heh!
Prepare yourselves
for an ingenious bit of
sleuthing, friends!
Contrary to the assumption
we've been laboring under,
I put it to you
that Maizono indeed
let the killer in herself!
C'mon, man.
[YAMADA] Hmm...?
We've been over this; she was
too scared to open the door.
Ah... You certainly have the
right to your opinion, but...
Logic!
I'd agree with you,
except we'd both be wrong!
I know what I saw.
When she came to me...
she was practically in tears.
[NAEGI] Whatever you do,
don't open the door.
Promise me.
[MAIZONO] You got it.
That door's staying locked
even if I know it's you
on the other side.
Would sorta defeat the purpose
of swapping rooms
otherwise, right?
[NAEGI] I don't know about you,
but I have a pretty hard time
believing she'd
answer the door
after saying
something like that.
[KIRIGIRI]
Perhaps that was the idea...
Her terror could
have been a ruse.
[ALL gasp]
[NAEGI] No...
She wouldn't lie to me!
Maizono and I were friends!
Yes, I will grant you,
it is an unpleasant
possibility to consider...
But, I'm afraid, necessary.
[MAIZONO] "There's something I
want to talk about in private.
Please come to my room. Make
sure to check the nameplate
so you don't go to the
wrong room by mistake.
Sayaka Maizono"
What's that s'posed to be...?
The impression of a
letter she wrote.
I found it on the
notepad in your room...
I'm sorry.
Are you trying to say
it was you who wrote this?
No... It wasn't.
Of course not...
I thought as much.
As you can see, the
signature is quite legible.
[NAEGI] I don't get it.
Why would she...?
[KIRIGIRI] I think
she wrote this letter
with the intent of luring
someone to their death.
[NAEGI gasps]
[YAMADA] Someone would
have to be dead inside
to overlook a personal
invitation from a teen idol
of Maizono's caliber...
That is...
unless they were already
perfectly satisfied
with those of the 2-D variety.
Yes, but...
The note clearly says
to come to her room...
So there we have
it then, don't we?
She wasn't in her room.
[FUJISAKI] Right.
Whoever it was would've gone to
where Naegi was by mistake.
[KIRIGIRI] Ah... but they
wouldn't have, you see.
Maizono was clever.
[CELESTIA] Really? How so?
[KIRIGIRI] After she
and Naegi switched rooms,
she slipped out and
swapped their nameplates.
My notebook missed
this detail entirely.
[FUJISAKI] Then she was luring
someone into Naegi's room...
[TOGAMI] Well,
if memory serves...
I believe the phrase
tossed out a little earlier
was "luring someone
to their death."
Yes... Seems so...
And it's the only logical
conclusion left...
Of course, that points the
finger away from Naegi.
Finally...
Fine. Whatever...
So who killed her?
Isn't it obvious?
Whoever she invited to my room
turned the tables on her...
Got to her first.
[gasping]
We're actually going
with this idea
that she swapped rooms with
Naegi to try and off someone?
[TOGAMI] Far from
the worst of gambits...
Once the deed was done,
she'd have an out...
She had but to switch
the nameplates back
to pin it on you.
She'd never do tha--!
[TOGAMI] Oh please... Wake up!
What could she have possibly
been up to if not that?
Her fatal misstep, of course,
was inadvertently giving
her prospective victim the
opportunity to fight back.
They got the first strike
in with that katana!
[CELESTIA] No. That was
used in self-defense.
[TOGAMI] Yes, the damage to
the sheath implies as much...
Had things gone
according to plan...
Maizono would be
standing here now,
pointing the finger at Naegi.
I trusted her...
Why would she...
[CELESTIA] Why wouldn't she?
It was an ironclad
way out of here
was it not?
If we omit the fact that it
was a spectacular failure, yes.
Poor fool.
Don't talk about
her like that!
Oh, I'm sorry. You have
a reason to defend her?
No! But still--!
[KIRIGIRI] Calm down.
This isn't the time
to argue. Focus.
Yes, quite right.
The murderer is still at large,
and time is short.
Let's get to it, then.
It's one of us.
[HAGAKURE] Well, duh! But
how the hell do we pick?!
Ugh! We're all goners! I know
it! I'm too young to die!
It's not fair!
[NAEGI] I gotta think!
If we don't figure out
who killed her,
it's the end for all of us!
There's got to be something
we've missed...
[LEON] Well... Guess that's
pretty much it for us...
Damn... If only there
was more to go on, right?
We're outta clues.
That's where you're wrong!
The hell am I missin' then?
Something pretty big, actually.
She left us a message...
Not the one on the notepad.
Wha... What are you drivin' at?
She left a dying message.
One scrawled in blood
on the wall behind her.
[HAGAKURE] That's right!
What did it say?
[ASAHINA] You mean that
random string of numbers?
Hey, you're supposed to
be some kinda crazy genius
with numbers, ain'tcha?
The one's she left behind mean
anything special or what?
I tried every decryption
trick in the book...
but whatever they're supposed
to mean, it's not code I know.
I'm sorry...
[NAEGI] Break it down...
When things took a turn,
Maizono ran for the shower
but the killer
forced his way in...
Did he already have the knife?
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI] That's it! I've got it!
[ALL gasp]
The message wasn't
a string of numbers!
She wrote out her killer's name!
[ALL gasp]
[NAEGI] If you flip those marks
around a hundred-eighty degrees,
there you have it,
plain as day...
L-E-O-N.
Whad'ya know...
That's your name, isn't it?
Leon Kuwata.
[LEON gasps]
So, Leon, if you got
anything to say...
Now's the time.
[LEON whimpers]
[OHGAMI] Disappointing, Leon.
[LEON] Gimme a break!
You're not seriously listening
to this lying little punk!
[KIRIGIRI] Maizono
identified her murderer
from beyond the grave...
A name written as
her life ebbed away.
Scrawled that way 'cause
of the angle of her head...
Poor girl probably didn't have
the energy left to hoist herself
around the right direction.
[LEON] Maybe someone's
trying to frame me!
You think of that?
Everything you've got
is circumstantial!
Let's assume you're
not the perpetrator.
Care to explain why you
tried to destroy evidence?
[LEON gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Somebody explain!
Yeah, of course!
She means those
charred pieces of shirt
and glass ball fragments we
found in the garbage room!
[YAMADA] Right! I'd
forgotten all about those!
[HAGAKURE] Y'know,
come to think of it,
I haven't seen my
crystal ball in a while...
Think that's what
happened to it?
Well, Naegi...
Seems you and I are of
the same opinion...
Puzzle it out yet?
[NAEGI] Here's what
I believe happened...
Maizono's killer was
in over his head...
He hadn't planned on
killing anyone that night;
the evidence had to
be dealt with fast...
Unfortunately, the garbage
room was on lock down.
This is where Hagakure's
missing glass ball comes in.
Activating the incinerator
from the other side
of the gate would be near
impossible for almost anyone.
But our culprit had mad skills.
Specifically, Super High School
Level Baseball Player skills.
All finished, our perp
figured he could chill,
walk back to his room like
nothing had happened...
That, as it turns out,
was his big mistake...
A scrap of the burning
bloodstained shirt sleeve
fell out... Gotcha.
Hard evidence...
He thought he'd improvised
the perfect crime,
when in fact he'd left a trail
leading us right to him.
Deny if you want,
that's how it went.
You stand accused.
Now'd be the time to object.
[LEON] Object? Hah. Yeah...
Let me think about that.
You're damn right I object!
This is all a buncha BS!
Oh-ho ho ho, hell to the no!
Think I'm takin' the wrap?!
You're the only one here
with the athletic chops
to throw Hagakure's
glass ball far enough
and hard enough to
hit the incinerator switch
and you know it!
[LEON] Yeah! Nice
try, but screw you!
What about Yamada?!
He's on trash detail!
He could've unlocked the gate!
Which is exactly why he wouldn't
have needed to use the ball;
he would've just used his
access key and walked off
without any of us having a clue.
Ha-ha! Yeah, big man, tryin'
to trick me into fessin' up!
Well, like I said,
it's all circumstantial!
Maybe. But there's still one
vital piece of evidence
that points directly at you.
What, you gonna make
somethin' up now?!
The bathroom... The doorknob...
The screws were removed.
Who gives a flyin' rat's ass?!
[NAEGI] How exactly do
you think the murderer
removed those screws, huh?
[LEON] Whatever you're
drivin' at, jerkwad,
you are barking up
the wrong tree!
[NAEGI] Well if what I'm
driving at is on the money...
There'll be proof
in your toolkit.
How 'bout you give us a look?
[LEON] Never-never-never-never
never-never-never-never!
This is a sham!
I'm warning you, dude!
Back off!
[NAEGI] You're guilty,
Leon Kuwata!
I demand you show us
what's inside your toolkit!
Come on. What's the big deal?
What have you got to hide?
Bear in mind, if it's been
used, prepare to explain...
In minute detail and 'til every
last one of us is satisfied.
And under the circumstances...
Not knowing is not
going to be acceptable.
[LEON stutters]
Predictable... He has nothing
to say in his defense.
I'm sorry, man.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA] I'd say you kids have
hashed this one out nicely...
Major kudos! Let's
move on to Voting Time!
Kindly lock in your votes
by pressing the switches
there in front of you.
Who's the guilty so-and-so? Feel
good about your final choice?
And the award goes to...
[drum roll]
[machine whistles]
[MONOKUMA] Correct!
Well done, peeps!
Sayaka Maizono's
murderer was indeed...
Leon Kuwata!
I...
[ASAHINA] Oh wow...
You dumbass! What the
hell got into you?!
[LEON] I didn't want to...
She was...
I mean, she was tryin'
to kill me, right?
I just...
I didn't know what
else to do, okay?
What if she'd gone after you?!
You'd all'a done the
same thing in my shoes!
[LEON sobs]
[MONOKUMA] Right,
so there you have it!
Excellent job dispensing tough
justice; and I mean that...
Moving on now to
the punishment phase!
No! I didn't have a choice!
The crazy skank was gonna kill
me, what was I s'posed to do?!
Come on, guys...
I acted in self-defense!
Special circumstances!
I-I'm not really a murderer!
[MONOKUMA] Yes, yes.
I'm sure we're all
relieved to hear that.
But rules are rules;
too bad, so sad.
No, wait! It's not right!
[MONOKUMA] "Right"?! Right don't
enter into it, sweetheart.
You killed and got caught.
Which means you die.
[LEON] Nuh... no...! No!
Get me out of this place!
[MONOKUMA] For all-star
athlete Leon Kuwata,
whose talents behind the plate
certainly held more promise
than his career as
a lady killer,
I've come up with a very
special method of execution...
Play ball!
Nooooo!
[MONOKUMA] Ha-ha!
Now that's what I call extreme!
I feel the adrenaline coursing
through me like lightning!
[whimpering]
[FUKAWA] What is going on here?
Someone wake me up, pleeease!
[FUJISAKI] I-I... I just...
I can't take this.
[MONOKUMA] Now, now. It's not
so bad, once you get used to it.
Abandon all hope of seeing
the light of day again,
and you'll be fine. Promise...
'Course, now that I hear myself
say it out loud,
it does sound pretty cruel...
[MONOKUMA] There, there, Naegi.
It's all right. I know.
[NAEGI] Know what?
What are you talking about?
[MONOKUMA] Don't be like that.
Maizono sold you up the river.
You're hurtin', it's fine.
[NAEGI] Screw you!
You did this...
It was all your fault
from beginning to end!
Don't, Naegi... Don't lose it...
Think about this; you will never
avenge her
if you get killed too.
Damn it!
[NAEGI] Damn it all...
[doorbell rings]
[KIRIGIRI] I know now's
probably not the best time,
but I need to talk with you.
[NAEGI] It's about her,
isn't it? Maizono...
[KIRIGIRI] Yeah.
I'll be frank.
It may be undeniable
that Maizono meant to
frame you for murder...
The facts paint too
clear a picture...
That said...
What do you imagine
her dying thoughts were?
[NAEGI] How the hell
should I know?
Naegi, I'm serious...
You knew her well
enough to speculate...
Personally, I believe
her last thoughts
were of how to save you.
I think we can surmise that's
what she wanted in the end.
[NAEGI gasps]
[KIRIGIRI] Why else leave
the message, correct?
She certainly didn't have to.
Yeah, nice try...
I wish I could believe that,
but all she really wanted
was to make sure Leon
paid for killing her.
[KIRIGIRI] I beg to differ.
In fact...
She never meant to hurt you.
She wasn't a killer.
Nor was she comfortable
with deceiving you.
Sadly, she hesitated when
she ought to have been bold
and wound up dead...
Rather a high price to pay.
[NAEGI] So... Why are
you telling me this?
Because I think
you're strong...
You can push through
this intact.
Resilience is a rare quality
in people; I sense it in you.
[KIRIGIRI] Of course,
there's always the chance
I'm reading too
much into things.
But for your sake,
I hope I'm not.
Y'expect me to just "push
through" the death of a friend?
If that's what you're talking
about, then I'm not your guy.
[NAEGI] When someone I care
about dies, I don't move on.
I carry it with me...
Forever...
It's who I am...
Maizono and Kuwata's deaths...
I'm not sweepin'
'em under the rug.
I'm not the type
who just forgets.
If I get out of here,
I'll still be haunted by 'em!
I'll always look back!
How noble...
A difficult path, but noble...
Still, though...
I have hope.
So... While I'm here, and
it may be silly to ask...
What precisely keyed you in to
the fact that I'd popped by
to speak with you about Maizono?
[NAEGI] Oh, I can
read your mind.
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
[NAEGI] Kidding...
Intuition.