[AIKA]
Kimito? You're in there, right?
I'm coming in!
[gasps]
Well. What's up?
You asked me here.
So, uh. You wanted to
talk to me in private?
Yeah... It's best if
it's just you and me.
[gasps]
Oh... Is that why you
lied to the other girls?
And why you told them
you were busy today
and that all club
activities were cancelled?
Yes.
[gasps]
[AIKA gasps]
[KIMITO]
What are you so nervous about?
Hey. You shut up!
I can't help it, okay?
[KIMITO]
We're good friends.
You don't have to
be nervous around me.
[gasps]
[AIKA]
What do you mean?
[KIMITO]
I mean exactly what I said.
Now. Come and sit over here.
[gasps]
Whoa. What the heck is that?
[KIMITO]
A present.
[gasps]
No way!
[KIMITO] Hey, I'm being
generous here!
[AIKA gasps] I didn't
mean that to sound bad.
But why?
It made me think
of you. That's all.
[gasps]
[KIMITO]
Open it.
[AIKA] It's a yellow tux
with a red bowtie?
Uh...
[KIMITO] Well, it's like
you're always telling me...
I wanna be popular,
and you're not doing anything
to help me out! You jerk!
[KIMITO]
True?
[AIKA]
Mm-hm.
[KIMITO] And you know what?
You're totally right.
That's why I'm
stepping up my game.
[AIKA]
Huh?
[KIMITO] That suit is
your super-secret weapon
to becoming the most
popular girl ever!
Super-secret weapon?
[KIMITO]
Damn right!
If you put on that outfit and
perform the song "Gets,"
everyone will worship
the ground you walk on!
[gasps]
[AIKA]
Kimito?
Huh?
I've kinda heard "Gets"
mentioned before.
What the heck is it anyway?
[KIMITO]
H-Hmm...
It's a Commoner greeting
that's catching fire.
Only the coolest peeps
get down with "Gets!"
Sounds fishy.
Why should I believe you?
You've tricked me too
many times in the past!
[KIMITO]
I have?
[AIKA]
Duh!
[KIMITO] Okay, maybe I've
pulled your leg once or twice
but this time I'm dead serious!
If you don't believe me,
see for yourself. Here.
[gasps]
[AIKA]
Who is that guy?
The bad ass in the
suit is Dandy Sakano.
He's the founding
father of 'Gets.'
And now that his dance
is sweeping the nation,
He's become a
full-blown celebrity.
It's the truth. He's wearing
a bright yellow suit.
And he's doing a dance!
[KIMITO]
Check this!
[gasps]
[AIKA] There are 388,000
hits for Dandy Sakano?
[KIMITO 388,000 hits means
there are 388,000 pages
written about Dandy,
which means this guy
is a big freakin' deal!
I didn't even know someone
could be that popular!
This is insane!
[KIMITO]
Now watch what happens
when you search for
the keyword "Gets."
781,000 hits for "Gets?"
Amazing! So amazing!
Looks like "Gets" is catching on
with a crazy diverse audience!
You're absolutely right,
everyone is calling "Gets"
the next one hit wond--
I mean, the biggest handshake
greeting to hit the world
since the fist-bump!
It's that hot?
Yup.
And guess which comedian gave
birth to this magical move?
That's right, Dandy
Sakano himself.
Wait! What in the
heck is a comedian?
Huh?
[KIMITO] Someone whose job
is to make people happy!
That sounds totally cool!
[KIMITO] Okay. I've told you
everything you need to know.
You know what you
have to do now, right?
[AIKA] Yeah! I have to
put this thing on, pronto!
[giggles]
You're awesome.
You're crushing it!
In fact, I think I'm gonna
call you Dandy Aika!
Wait, Dandy Aika? That's like
the coolest name ever!
[gasps, giggles]
Gets--
That it?
[KIMITO]
Hm... No good.
You have to spread
your legs a bit more.
[AIKA gasps]
Oh yeah, good call.
[KIMITO] Also. Get low,
and crouch for me.
Right!
Gets... Gets... Gets!
That's good! You're totally
nailing it right now!
[AIKA] Okay, let's
go show the others!
Next, the advanced form!
First. "Gets". Then you spin
around and land like this!
Gets! Spin around...
Then... I land like this!
[KIMITO]
Yes, but faster!
Gets! Spin around!
[KIMITO]
Faster!
Gets! Spin!
Good job! That's a
little move they call
The "Gets-and-turn Delight!"
This is so cool!
Now, put on a
hardcore smug face,
lift your left hand and
right knee like this.
And you strut on
outta there, backwards.
Come on, Aika,
it's your turn!
Show me how you make an exit!
[AIKA]
Like this?
Don't speak!
[AIKA grunts]
That was perfect!
You are Dandy Aika!
All right! I really
did it! Yeah!
--I totally rule!
--[KIMITO] Mission accomplished.
Now I guess there's only
one thing left to do.
Tell Aika the truth and get
beaten to a bloody pulp again.
I'm gonna show
everyone my new moves
and they'll love me forever!
No, Aika, don't go!
Hey! Wait!
[KIMITO gasps, yells]
[grunts]
[KIMITO]
What is this?
Wait. I know exactly
what this is.
But these things don't just
run around on their own.
Anyone but Kujo.
[KUJO]
What are your intentions?
[KIMITO]
No...
Screw it. If I'm gonna
lose my balls anyway,
I might as well get
a good clean look
while I still have the
faculties to enjoy it.
And what a look it is.
To think that such a cold,
sharp person could be so warm
and smooth, and unmoving.
Shouldn't she be, like,
prepping for the operation?
And where the hell has she
been keeping the scissors
if not here? Oh no!
they're already out!
[KIMITO yelps, gasps]
Uh! I did not mean
to touch you there!
It is not so much
"where" I was violated.
But rather "by whom" I was
violated that most concerns me.
As you know,
this is of the utmost
psychological significance.
You've graced me with a
peek into your fetid psyche.
Thank you so much, Kimito.
[KIMITO]
Wait! Just hear me out!
[KUJO] I shall admit
myself for counseling now.
[KIMITO]
I'm sorry!
Oh yeah. I have to find Aika!
[gasps] Am I to understand
you gave the item that arrived
this very morning to Miss Aika?
Why would you
do such a thing?
[KIMITO] Hm? It's something for
the Commoner Club, is all.
[KUJO]
I know what you're doing.
[KIMITO]
Uh...
Every waking moment,
your libido consumes you.
Driving you to commit
petty heterosexual acts.
Such behaviors are often
seen in the fumbling efforts
of grade school boys trying to
get in with the girls they like.
[KIMITO]
How would you know?
Don't be coy with me.
What? I would never!
I love muscles!
So that encounter did nothing
for you, you're sure.
[grunts]
You bet I am.
Muscles are the only
thing that get me goin'!
[KUJO] Is that right?
What a relief to hear.
[sobs]
[gasps]
[AIKA hums]
Goodness me! What are
you wearing Aika?
This?
It's a "none-of-your-
businness outfit." Bye!
[gaps]
Hold on! Not so fast!
Why would this be
none of my business?
I've never seen a person run
that fast in my life! Weird!
Weird? What's "weird" is that
ridiculous suit you're wearing!
[AIKA grunts]
Please. My outfit's not weird,
it's the coolest ever!
But, it's so yellow!
I'm dressed up like
a famous Commoner
who wrote an awesome
song called--
[scoffs, inhales]
Gets!
Well, that's... Quite odd.
t's not odd, ya weirdo!
It's the most popular greeting
to hit the Commoner world
since the freakin' fist-bump.
Cool, huh? A comedian named
Dandy Sakano created it,
and this is what he wears
in all his viral videos.
And you learned about
all this from Kimito?
[AIKA] Yep. And not only that,
he bought me this outfit too!
Isn't that thoughtful.
[sobs]
So? How do I look? Pretty great?
Yes, indeed. The yellow
color is vibrant.
And the fact that you're
wearing a man's tuxedo
gives it an additional
comedic flair.
To think that you
would receive
such an incredible
gift from Kimito.
I'll admit, I am
quite envious, Aika.
Uh. Well. Since you
like it so much,
I could ask him to get you one.
[REIKO]
You would do that?
Sure.
[REIKO]
Thank you very much!
No problem at all.
[REIKO]
That gesture you made.
I assumed, apparently wrongly,
that this was something
you invented entirely.
[AIKA] No way! "Gets" is
a global, internet sensation.
Over seven hundred thousand
people have watched--
Seven hundred thousand?!
Goodness me!
Well. I'll try. Here I go.
Gets!
So very wrong.
[DANDY SAKANO]
Gets!
[REIKO]
So? Like this?
[AIKA] Yeah. But,
move your hands just a bit.
[REIKO gasps]
This?
[AIKA]
Mm-hm.
Kay. Now follow my lead!
Right!
--Gets!
[sighs]
This is how the Commoners
greet each other?
What can I say?
It feels so liberating!
I know!
We cannot keep
this to ourselves.
Let's share the gift of this
wonderful Commoner greeting
with the rest of the
students here at Seikain!
Awesome idea!
[KIMITO]
Hey! Aika!
Geez. Where the heck did she go?
Huh?
[FEMALE STUDENTS chatter]
[KIMITO]
There you are!
[gasps]
It's Kimito!
Huh?
Oh, I hope he
likes our suits!
Yeah!
Uh...
What perfect timing. We just
finished teaching the others
how to do the world
famous dance, "Gets!"
Everybody learned it!
So now all of us can be
popular in the Commoner world!
[gasps]
Everyone! Let us all
demonstrate for Kimito
the fruits of our
strenuous labor at once!
[FEMALE STUDENTS cheer]
[Yay!
Wonderful idea!
All right, here we go!
[AIKA]
One, two, three.
[ALL]
Gets!
[KIMITO]
Hattori, how ya doin'?
Hey, long time no talk!
You know I'm stuck at an
all girls' school, right?
Well, yeah, obviously, I thought
I had it made at first.
But then I realized something,
something I never
thought possible.
[REIKO gasps]
I don't like girls.
Guys are just better,
in so many ways.
[gasps]
[KIMITO]
I can't be myself around girls,
ya know what I mean?
There're just so many
urges I can't act on.
Plus. I miss the way guys smell.
You know, like when we're
wrestling or playing sports.
And we take our shirts off
and show our muscles.
[REIKO gasps]
[KIMITO] I miss you, man.
I wanna come home.
No. No!
This can't be happening!
What do you mean,
"Kimito wants to go home?"
[REIKO] I overheard him talking,
and he said when he's around
girls he can't
be his true self.
He said he misses
being around other men!
Hold on. Does that mean
he misses muscles, too?
Indeed. I heard him say
something to that effect.
Does this mean that
he's going away?
[ALL gasp]
Not if we can help it, no.
Let us brainstorm.
We will stop this.
[KAREN]
But, what can we possibly do?
[gasps]
I have a plan!
Kimito misses men,
so we should become men!
[KAREN]
Uh?
[REIKO]
Whatever do you mean?
It's so simple. We butch
ourselves up a bit.
And we fill the hole guys
have left in his life!
I see it now.
To satisfy his craving
for male company,
we must become
masculine ourselves.
Perfect. To keep Kimito
from leaving us,
we must do whatever it takes.
Even if that means
abandoning our femininity!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Then again...
I will admit. I've no earthly
idea where to begin.
[AIKA]
Uh...
That's tough. Let's see.
Well we, uh-- We...
We could act like Kimito.
Well played! After all,
Kagurazaka is the only
male figure with whom
we are all familiar.
[HAKUA]
Um?
And it's like they say,
"Imitation is the sincerest
form of flattery!"
Hey! Good call! Yep.
That's exactly what they say!
[laughs]
But how do we imitate him? Hm.
I'm totally drawing
a blank on that one.
Same here.
Now that you mention it,
this is quite difficult.
[KAREN]
Watch me.
I know a sure fire way
to imitate Kagurazaka.
[KAREN]
Like this!
Uh. Was that it?
It's quite subtle, but the key
is where you choose to look.
He never stares
straight into your eyes.
His gaze is always lowered!
That is so true!
Yes, that's right!
Kimito almost never looks
me directly in the eyes
when we are conversing.
We should try it!
Right!
[laughs]
[ALL]
Huh?
[laughing continues]
I've got it! I thought of
a way to imitate Kimito!
I love muscles!
Wow!
Excellent work!
That was classic Kimito!
I will attempt it
as well! Here goes!
I love muscles!
I love muscles?
[ALL] We love muscles! We love
muscles! We love muscles!
We love muscles! We love
You got me mad now!
Hold on!
[REIKO gasps]
Technically, he borrowed
that one from the internet.
[REIKO gasps]
You're right. Pardon me.
[ALL gasp]
You got me mad now.
[thumping]
You got me mad now!
[gasps]
[ALL] You got me mad now!
You got me mad now!
[AIKA] He. Loves this.
So, so much.
But, I do get the feeling
something is not quite right.
What are you talking about,
this is fun!
[REIKO] Yes, it is.
But that's beside the point.
I don't know what it is,
but I sense something
critical is missing.
Wait a sec!
[KAREN gasps]
Do you know what
we're lacking?
Yes, I do!
The men in those videos
were strong, oily and muscular.
Meanwhile, we're just a bunch
of adolescent little girls!
Excellent point!
A critical difference, indeed!
[AIKA]
Kimito loves muscles.
If we wanna keep him here,
then we gotta buff up fast!
That's an excellent idea.
Let's come up with a sound
muscle strategy right away!
[KIRYU]
Thank you for waiting.
[ALL gasp]
This is certainly realistic.
[HAKUA]
Big muscles.
Indeed. I'm sorry there's
only one of them.
Welp! I'll wear it then!
Ah! That's not fair, Aika.
Just because the muscle shirt
was your idea, does not mean you
are entitled to put it on first!
[KAREN]
Back off!
[REIKO]
We may be men,
but that doesn't mean
we have to be brutes!
[ALL shouting]
[panting]
We only have one choice left.
Play rock, paper, scissors.
Yeah. Good call!
[ALL]
One. Two. Three!
Oh yeah!!
[ALL grunting]
Looks like the suit's all mine!
Check it out!
I am ripped!
[AIKA]
Uh...
So wrong.
You look like a sad young
girl with a steroid addiction.
I am a girl,
what do you expect?
Hair's long.
Yes. True.
You should cut your hair so it
looks the same as Kimito's.
[KAREN] No. We have
to give Kimito
the ultimate male experience.
Which means this...
Wait. You mean Samurai hair?
[KAREN]
Yes. Exactly.
Put this on and he will
never miss men again.
The Samurai is the pinnacle
of Japanese masculinity.
[REIKO gasps] That leaves
the issue of clothing.
We cannot have you
wearing a short skirt.
I guess you got
a point there.
[REIKO]
When it comes to manliness,
nothing in the world
delivers like a proper,
refined gentleman.
[KAREN]
So, give her a walking stick.
[HAKUA]
And a moustache.
[KAREN sighs]
That should do it!
Oh! You do look quite manly!
[AIKA] It's too hard to move
in this. I'm taking it off!
What else? Is there something
we're missing perhaps?
[gasps]
[KIMITO] Plus, I miss
the way guys smell.
You know, like when we're
wrestling or playing sports.
And we take our shirts
off and show our muscles.
[REIKO]
I know what it is!
[KAREN]
Uh?
I specifically remember
hearing him say
he misses the way guys smell.
[BOTH]
The way guys smell?
I never even thought
about an odor.
But what exudes a
gentlemanly scent?
I'm lost. I have no idea.
Raw meat.
[BOTH gasp]
Now that you mention it,
raw meat is pretty manly.
Yes but, how does one
acquire the scent of meat?
Yakiniku seasoning.
[KAREN]
That is, how can I say it?
An awfully meaty aroma,
isn't it?
[REIKO] It does leave a hint
of masculinity on the nose.
[AIKA]
That's an understatement.
If we dab some of this on,
we'll smell manlier than
a sweaty jockstrap!
[stomach growls]
Come, Aika.
I'll put it on for you so
you smell like a real man.
The sauce should be applied in
the same region as perfume, yes?
[AIKA]
Mm! Then slather me up!
[KAREN]
We should put some on, too.
[REIKO]
Of course. Get ready, everyone!
Come on, Hattori.
Call me back!
[knocking]
Huh?
We're coming in, dude!
[KIMITO]
Okay?
Yo, Kimito!
Kagurazaka! It's a nice
day out! Let's have a duel.
Greetings, my lady.
Hey! I am not a lady!
Not that that's offensive.
Why do all of you smell
like Yakiniku sauce?
[ALL]
Uh...
What's going on here?
Why are you acting weird?
We dressed up like this cause
you said you were gonna leave!
[gasps]
What do you mean, leave?
[AIKA] Well. You're homesick and
you hate going to school here,
so you're leaving, right?
[KIMITO]
What?
It's what you said. And then you
said you couldn't be yourself
because there were
too many girls here.
Yeah, and that's
why I-- Uh, I mean.
That's why we decided to
butch things up a little!
This should tide you over.
[sighs]
You look ridiculous.
Hey!
But Kimito!
Look, We did this for you!
Yeah. Thanks for the thought.
[ALL gasp]
You don't have to
worry about me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm definitely
staying at Seikain.
[GIRLS sigh]
[KAREN] I am so glad I
can still kill you one day!
[REIKO]
We're just glad you're staying.
You got me mad now!
[KIMITO] Seriously, you don't
have to do that! I'm staying.
It's over!
[HAKUA]
"Gets."
I can tell you've
been to the gym.
How can you tell?
[HAKUA]
Locks are released.
You stay away from Reiko,
Filthy Commoner!
[HOKO] Your marriage talks
have officially concluded!
You can't leave, what will
I do without you here?
[REIKO] From now on, if it's
all right, please call me Rei.