[AIKA]
Hey, Kimito!
How do Commoners
get their fortunes told?
Our phones.
We use fortune telling apps
and websites, too.
You're totally blowing
my mind right now!
Okay, show me!
Yeah. Sure.
[MOON (ERI)]
You don't need the cosmos.
You've got me!
Hey, that sounds
like your friend.
Yup. This was
one of her first jobs.
Cool.
Get ready, because
here comes your fortune!
Sweet Aika...
The walls around your
brain are too thin
to keep in your thoughts!
That's why you're so blunt!
You blurt out your thoughts
'cause there's nothing
to stop them!
It's the reason you
keep people at arm's length!
Wow! That's so me!
This is incredible!
All I did was
put in my birthday,
and she summed up my
personality perfectly!
All in the blink of an eye!
This is the greatest
invention of all time!
Look. It has your lucky
color written down as well.
Let me see!
Well?
What is that?
The app says green
is my lucky color!
So if I cover myself with it,
then, for the rest of my life,
I'll always have good luck!
Brilliant plan.
But you missed a spot.
Your face.
[AIKA]
Good call.
If I want this to work,
I have to really commit.
[AIKA] Hey, wait.
What about my palms?
Shouldn't I do something
to green them up a bit?
Do it, Aika.
Go green all the way!
[AIKA] How do I look?
Great, or super great?
[KIMITO]
Mega great!
And while you're holding
those edamame beans,
you should dance around and
shout for all the world to hear.
"Beans, beans!"
[AIKA]
Wait, why?
It's a Commoner
dance we always do
the day before spring starts.
It'll bring you good luck.
[AIKA]
For real?
My dad would scatter
soybeans on Spring's Eve.
Do Commoners do that, too?
Yeah. But we also do the dance,
and even though
it's not Spring's Eve,
I think you should try it.
You've gone this far.
Might as well take it
to the next level.
Make me proud.
[AIKA] But shouldn't I
be using soybeans for this?
[KIMITO] Edamame beans
are baby soybeans.
[AIKA]
I didn't know that!
Break it down, Aika. Let loose!
Bust a move and get
yourself some good luck!
[AIKA]
Beans, beans! Beans, beans!
[KIMITO]
Attaway, Aika!
[AIKA]
Beans, beans!
[KIMITO]
Do your thing!
[AIKA]
Yeah!
[KIMITO]
Take it from the top!
[AIKA]
Right! Beans, beans!
Beans, beans! Beans, beans!
Yeah!
[REIKO]
This is certainly... peculiar.
Get ready, because
here comes your fortune!
Kind Reiko...
You live for the
daily contact you have
with the many friends
who surround you.
Because of your excellent powers
of observation and analysis,
you will find success
in doing management work.
You are relentless in
your pursuit of romance.
Oh my!
For a digitized gypsy,
she's quite accurate!
Totes! It's like she
can see inside our souls!
That it is.
Why don't we let
Hakua try it next?
Darling Hakua...
You're like a
walking contradiction.
So hard to pin down.
Depending on the day,
you're either fully invested
or fiercely apathetic.
You have a scholar's mind,
and an artist's temperament.
She's got you there!
Commoner fortune
telling is beyond belief!
What a lovely civilization!
[KIMITO chuckles]
It's surprising how
accurate this thing is.
I mean, it pretty much
described you perfectly.
[KAREN]
So pointless!
What could some
fortune telling app
possibly know about me?
I simply will not allow
myself to be caught up
in such childish,
inane frivolities!
Well, if that's really true,
then you won't mind
if I go next.
You're an idiot!
You obviously want to try it.
[KAREN] Only to see
what it knows of my skill!
Go ahead.
If this machine
is truly accurate,
then it will laud
my noble way of life,
and my unparalleled
ability to wield a sword
in the throes of combat.
Pretty sure you're wrong there.
[phone chiming]
Mighty Karen...
You are extremely lonely.
And your melancholy makes you
act in an aggressive way.
You're a scatterbrained
worrywart who lives your life
in a constant state of panic,
anxiety and distress.
When it comes to romance,
you are passive at best
and completely inept at worst.
This must be some
kind of terrible mistake!
[KIMITO]
Really? Sounds dead on to me.
[KAREN]
Let me see that!
I only got such
an absurd result
because you were
the one holding it.
Let's see if things
aren't a little different
this time around!
[KAREN] Test your romantic
compatibility with friends?
As members of the Commoner Club,
it is our mandate
to explore this.
I, for one, firmly believe that
we should learn all we can
from this app.
As do I.
A valid point.
[HAKUA]
Yeah.
I'm glad you agree.
Now then,
let's make full use of
this vaunted
fortune telling apparatus.
Sadly, it only
tells compatibility
between the opposite sexes.
Since Kimito is the only boy,
we'll need to have it evaluate
our compatibility with him.
Normally, more choices
would be ideal.
But as it stands,
he's our only option.
Yeah. Too bad.
We'll just have to make do.
Yes, painful though it may be.
[KIMITO] I've never seen them
agree like this before.
Well, I guess this is
today's club activity.
Should go fine, as long
as it's all in good fun.
Let's get started, then.
Care to go first, Kimito?
Sure. I'm glad to.
But don't you think
everyone's acting weird?
[REIKO]
Weird?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Well, how about we
start things off with you?
Is something wrong?
[REIKO]
Oh, no!
That just wouldn't be fair.
[AIKA gasps]
Let's go alphabetically!
[AIKA, KIMITO]
So then... A for Aika.
[AIKA]
Sure, I guess.
What's this?
What?
That's cool.
It gives us a numerical score.
[AIKA]
How many points did I get?
Uh... Well...
[KIMITO gasps]
[KIMITO]
Uh... Oh boy.
Spit it out!
[REIKO] Hurry up
and tell us the number!
[KAREN]
Quit stalling!
Uh...
Hakua, did you mean to
punch me in the shin, or...?
Yes.
Okay. Right.
Me and Aika's
compatibility score is--
You got 80 points!
This may take you by surprise,
but the truth is
the two of you would make
quite an extraordinary couple!
A strong romance
is often built upon
the foundation of friendship,
and that is certainly
the case here!
[AIKA]
All right!
[AIKA squealing]
[AIKA giggling, cheering]
So earlier, I got
excited 'cause I thought
my lucky green body suit
was paying off!
But then I realized luck's
got nothin' to do with it
'cause some things
are just meant to be!
And clearly that's
the case with me and Kimito.
Not that I'm into him,
but hey, destiny's spoken.
[REIKO]
I'd like to go next, please.
And I realize that might
appear to be out of order.
But in all reality,
I should've been first anyway,
considering my last name
starts with an A.
Uh huh.
Aww, isn't it sweet how
bad Reiko wants to go next?
Sure hope she gets
what she wants.
However, against a
score as high as mine,
I don't think she has much
of a chance of winning out!
And just in case you all forgot,
my score was 80!
Good luck, Reiko!
[AIKA laughs]
Please tell me
our results, and quickly.
I'm dying to know!
90 points! That's amazing!
You two are perfectly suited
for the bonds of matrimony!
Together, your life
as a married couple
would be long, joyous
and incredibly fruitful.
Oh my! 90 points indeed!
And she says we're highly
suited for marriage as well!
This is the greatest day
of my entire life!
You're wrong! No!
This has to be a mistake!
Aww... Come now, Aika.
We should be glad that we both
received favorable results.
For my part, I am quite pleased
with my score of 90.
And what was your
score again, Aika?
I don't remember.
Wasn't it lower?
How 'bout you, Hakua? Wanna try?
[KIMITO]
I didn't wanna leave her out,
but this could definitely
get a little awkward.
Here goes.
50 points.
Kimito and Hakua, it seems
the chemistry between you
is neither good nor bad.
Because Hakua hardly ever speaks
and is not much
of a communicator,
you two will have
to work extremely hard
even to understand one another.
[KIMITO] Not sure what
I was hopin' for with that.
All right,
time for damage control.
Oh well, it's just
a silly game, right?
Who wants some tea?
[KIMITO]
Hakua?
Okay, then.
I know what always
makes me feel better
when I'm feeling sad.
Delicious goodies!
Awesome idea!
I'll go get 'em real quick!
[door opens, closes]
[KIMITO] Honestly,
I don't think she's that upset.
Whelp, that leaves
the two of us.
I can't very well be the
only one who doesn't try it.
[KIMITO] Hey. If you don't
want to, it's no big deal.
But I can tell by the look
on your face, you secretly do.
[KAREN] You know nothing
about what I want, you fiend!
Yeah. Right.
Uh oh!
If you two were together,
poor Kimito would die!
Die?!
[KAREN growls]
Damn you!
[KIMITO] Why are you
trying to carve me up?
I didn't do anything!
Well, I'm not surprised.
I don't need a
fortuneteller to tell me
that we're romantically
incompatible.
You disgust me.
It's obvious!
Would you please
stop stabbing my carpet
with your katana?
Uh... Oh. Hey.
It looks like I messed up
your information.
[KAREN]
What?
[KIMITO]
I put in the wrong birthday.
Let me fix it.
A hundred points!
That's a perfect score!
Karen and Kimito,
what you have is fate.
There is simply no other way
to express your love!
As ultimate partners,
you will bond on a deep level,
both spiritually
and emotionally.
Karen, you should
start aggressively
pressing your attack
as early as tomorrow!
Play up your special skills and
charge him as hard as you can!
A... perfect score?
[KIMITO] Relax.
Don't take it so seriously.
It's just a game.
I'll say!
Clearly it's not
to be relied upon!
[AIKA] You can't put
your faith in that crap!
[REIKO]
Crap, indeed!
[KIMITO] You were both raving
about how accurate it was
like five seconds ago!
[AIKA]
Gimme that!
"No matter what, he will
slowly slip away from you."
Well, if that's not a
big old load of horse crap,
then I don't know what is!
"The two of you have a
strong karmic connection
from a past life."
That sounds lovely. Perhaps it's
not so bad after all.
"Aika sure does have
a whole lot of friends!"
That's wrong!
Wow!
There are so many fortuneteller
websites out there!
[AIKA]
No kidding!
[REIKO]
I'll find the perfect one!
[AIKA]
Not before me, Blondie!
Look here, I found another app
and this one says Kimito and I
are meant to be, so that's that!
I also asked about you,
and it says that your
connection with Kimito is
"all in your dumb little head!"
That is simply not possible!
This clearly says that
"Kimito and Reiko
are a match made in heaven
and they will live
happily ever after!"
Your compatibility says,
"Aika is verifiably insane
and Kimito could
never love her."
You lose, crazy.
If anybody here
is insane, it's you!
How dare you
insult me like that, Aika?
[KIMITO] Well...
So much for "all in good fun."
[arguing continues]
That's quite enough, ladies!
Both of you stop
this argument at once.
It's disgraceful
for us to compete
over which of our
fortunes is correct.
Especially when it's crystal
clear that my fortune
is the only one that
contains any validity.
[AIKA, REIKO]
Like hell it does!
You think I'm
gonna take anything
that some hussy in a sailor
outfit says seriously?
Hey...
Uh... You okay?
My blood sugar's low.
Ah... Well...
Should I make ya something?
[HAKUA]
Potato cakes.
Cool. That sounds good to me.
I just hope I have potatoes.
Pancakes would
be all right, too.
[KIMITO]
Sounds great.
D'you wanna be my sous-chef?
[KUJO]
Are you awake, Kimito?
[KIMITO]
Uh... Yeah.
You have no idea
how badly I wish
you'd never woken up.
[KIMITO]
What am I?
Caught in a freakin' time loop?
Listen.
There's something I've been
meanin' to ask you, actually.
How come you always
watch me sleep?
Every morning when
I wake up, there you are.
Is somethin' the matter?
Is there a rule that says
I'm forced to answer you
or am I permitted to
abstain from doing so?
[KIMITO] If you don't want
to answer me, then don't.
As I've said before,
unfortunately,
I am the maid assigned
to care for you.
And as such, the horrific chore
of waking you up every
single morning falls to me.
If I had my way,
you would stay asleep forever.
But because of my sworn duty,
I have no choice.
I've considered smothering you.
But that would be too merciful.
I'm almost positive I
counted four insults there.
You can count?
[KIMITO]
That makes five!
[KUJO] I find waking you
quite burdensome,
so I allow myself to enjoy
your final moments of sleep.
[KIMITO] Huh...
That was weirdly phrased.
The worst part is
I have to watch you drool.
[KIMITO]
I would say of all the things
that could happen in my sleep,
my drooling should be
the least of your concerns!
Are you having
impure thoughts?
[KIMITO]
What?!
And why are those
scissors so big?!
My point is you don't
have to wake me up anymore.
My smart phone has an alarm,
I'll just use that.
[KUJO]
Is that so?
In that case, I shall destroy
your evil smart phone!
What for?!
Excessive mechanization
is the bane of the worker!
[KIMITO] If you break that,
I'll lose all my contacts!
Since you insist
on forcing my hand,
I'm afraid that you leave me
with no other alternative.
Instead of waking you up gently,
I'll put on skates
and perform a triple axel
on your so-called "manhood."
[KIMITO] That seems a
little extreme doesn't it?
Then, am I to assume we
will continue the same way
we have up to now?
Umm... Yeah, let's.
[KUJO]
I'll excuse myself.
Please get dressed immediately.
[door opens, closes]
The heck was that?
[MALE VOICE 8A]
"Ah! My shoulder!"
[MEN grunting]
[MALE VOICE 8A]
"You got me mad now!"
[KIMITO laughs]
I've never watched one of
these muscle-men videos before.
"You got me mad now!"
[MEN grunting]
What's wrong?
[MOON (ERI)] Karen, you should
start aggressively pressing
your attack
as early as tomorrow.
Play up your special skills and
charge him as hard as you can!
[KAREN]
Karen style sword art!
Resolution!
The hallway!
That's for walking!
[KAREN]
Kagurazaka!
Karen?
My skill with
a sword is special!
Yeah?
Yeah it is.
Do you like it?
Uh... Well, I--
[KAREN] You think
it's amazing, don't you?
Yeah. For sure.
Almost supernatural!
Good. I'm glad you agree!
[KIMITO] She's always
been good with a sword.
Why's she braggin' about it now?
[KAREN]
What's this?
Oh no, how awful.
It appears that the sleeve of
your jacket's been cut through.
Yeah, I wonder
how that happened.
[KAREN]
Have no fear.
I can mend that
sleeve in no time.
[KIMITO]
What?
I don't have any
stitching equipment on hand.
But everything we need's
in my room.
I can take care of you there.
Take care of me?
[KAREN]
Welcome to my humble abode.
[KIMITO]
Wow. Kinda... spartan.
Of course it is.
Those who walk
the path of the samurai
have no need for
pointless decorations.
"Fortitude and Simplicity."
Please sit down.
I'll serve tea.
Cool. Thanks.
[KAREN]
Drink.
[KIMITO]
Right. Sure thing.
[KAREN]
What's wrong, Kagurazaka?
Uh... Nothing.
[KAREN]
Well, then.
I shall fetch my tailoring gear.
[KIMITO gasps]
[KAREN]
Let's see. It's here somewhere.
[KIMITO] She has a doll house
filled with bunny people.
Um... Is something
amiss, or...?
[KIMITO]
Huh?
[KAREN] I can feel your gaze
piercing into my back.
No. Pretty sure
you're imagining things.
Oh. All right.
He certainly is an odd one.
[KIMITO]
You're the odd one, bunny girl!
[KAREN]
Oh! I almost forgot.
Kagurazaka.
Turn your back, please.
[KIMITO]
How come?
Just do it!
[zipper zips]
[KIMITO]
That sound...
Is she seriously doing
what I think she's doing?
[zipper zips]
[KAREN]
You may turn around now.
See? The clothes.
Yep. Clothes.
[KIMITO] Okay, so clearly I
shouldn't be staring like this
because I'm pretending
to be a "sexual deviant"
or whatever the hell,
but come on,
how am I not supposed
to look at something
as wonderful as this?
Suddenly I picture her
on a trampoline.
A big, springy one
covered in baby oil.
Yeah, so we can bounce
up and down...
As I've told you before,
I think you look nice.
Hey! Don't get the wrong idea!
They're comfortable
and I enjoy wearing them.
Still, they look great on you.
For real, you look fantastic.
Well, in that case, I'll
continue to wear them sometimes.
But by no means will
I do so for your sake!
Of course, I know that.
You don't know anything!
[KIMITO]
Right!
This is nice.
I don't know how to put it.
She's surprisingly, uh...
Uh... Why are you
staring at me like that?
[KIMITO]
Oh...
I was just thinking how
you'll make somebody
a happy husband one day.
Why would you say something
like that, you fool?!
Wait...
Unless you're suggesting
that perhaps you and I might--
I'm not ready for this!
[KIMITO]
Please calm down!
You're gonna tear my jacket!
[KAREN]
All done.
Great job.
Even when I look
at it really close,
I still can't tell
it was ripped.
Indeed.
Next to swordplay,
this is my best skill!
Well, I'm really impressed.
Seriously, my mom doesn't even
know how to sew like this.
Oh. It is early,
but if you wanted me to meet
your parents, I'd be willing.
[KIMITO]
Huh?
It appears that your
undershirt is cut as well.
Yeah, you're right.
Then I'll have
to sew that, too.
Take off your shirt,
please. Quickly.
What? No, that's okay.
Just do it!
[KIMITO] If I give you my shirt,
I'll be half-naked.
[KAREN gasps]
That's part of my master plan!
[KIMITO yelling]
You're not hurt, are you?
No...
Good.
[KAREN]
You have peculiar limbs.
[KIMITO]
Do I?
They're not like
any girl's I've seen.
But I don't get it.
They aren't all that much
larger than mine, so...
So then how is it that
you're able to overpower me
with such ease?
It really is
pointless, isn't it?
I always wanted
to be a swordsman.
From the start of my youth,
all I did was train to fight.
Maybe I was wasting my time.
I am a girl, after all.
Why try?
[KIMITO]
Don't say that.
Kagurazaka?
You've worked your butt
off and it shows, Karen.
So what if you're a girl.
You can do anything you want.
Not to mention, you're one
of the strongest people
I've ever seen!
I'm always impressed
by your work ethic
and your dedication
to your craft.
Seeing someone
train as hard as you?
And never give up?
That's a beautiful thing.
You're serious, right?
You aren't gonna start laughing.
You really...
think I'm beautiful.
Ready or not!
[REIKO]
It appears to be empty.
But I'm not crazy.
You heard 'em say they saw him
going into Karen's room,
too, right?
[REIKO] Yes, but where
on earth did they go?
[AIKA]
Beats me.
Okay, look.
There's no reason to hide,
we're not doing anything wrong.
[KIMITO yelps]
Don't move or
they'll hear us in here!
I don't know how
you can say that
in our current position!
Hey! I told you not to move!
[KIMITO yells]
No... Stop. Not there!
[KAREN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
--[AIKA] Kimito!
--[REIKO] Oh, Kimito!
What is this?
What were you two
doing in there?
[music playing, MEN grunting]
Oh, boy.
I... I was just...
Telling Karen's fortune!
[AIKA]
Huh...
[KIMITO]
Huh?
Is that all? Oh!
In that case,
you'd better finish up!
[MALE VOICE 8B]
"Tap out! Now!"
Stop stalling and
tell her fortune already!
Go on!
"You got me mad now."
What's takin' so long?
[KIMITO growling]
[KIMITO]
"You got me mad now!"
[AIKA] The heck do you mean,
"I got you mad now?"
Tell the fortune!
[KIMITO]
"You got me mad now!"
The secret ingredient.
A little love.
You nasty pervert!
I'm nervous! I've never been
a maidservant before!
Do it right now or else!
You sound like
a dying wildebeest!
[HAKUA]
Will you gather sand too?
Sugar and some love!