[HOKO]
Reiko.
Uh, yes, ma'am?
Your marriage talks have
officially concluded.
[gasps]
If you abandon me and the
rest of the Commoner Club,
I don't know what I'll do!
[REIKO]
I want to stay at Seikain.
I wanna stay there with
Hakua, and with Karen.
And most of all, I want
to stay with you, Aika.
I'm so scared. Please,
I've no idea what to do.
[AIKA] Don't worry.
We'll think of something.
One way or another, we
will get you out of this.
[KIMITO]
It's all right.
This is a job for a Commoner.
We're out of the woods
now, for the most part.
Hey. Why'd you turn to us?
I'm a member of
the Arisugawa family.
I can't very well be seen
to be against the engagement.
My sister's fate rests
entirely in your hands.
So, is this what a
real city looks like?
It resembles
Shominland remarkably.
[KIMITO]
You've got that backwards.
What's the matter?
[MASAOMI]
See for yourself.
[KIMITO]
That's a lot of security.
[AIKA]
Lemme see, lemme see!
This is bad.
Somebody talked to my mother,
which means we have
a leak on the inside.
[AIKA]
Whoa! They have wooden swords!
What do we do now?
Here's the deal.
You charge in there
and create a diversion.
While the guards are distracted,
I'll slip past them and
make my way inside the house.
No way! I'm not
chargin' in there!
[KAREN]
Aika's right.
Those men are wielding swords.
And from the looks of it,
they're quite handy with them.
It's time. My time.
The moment I've been waiting
for my whole life is here.
I will fight these swordsmen and
put my training to the test!
We have to get to Reiko.
And I'm guessing
the only way to do it
is through that front gate.
Yeah. That's right.
Karen, wait.
No. I'm done waiting.
This is my chance!
My name is Karen Jinyo!
I challenge all of you to a
fight to the death by sword.
Karen style sword art!
Resolution!
[GUARDS yell]
Oh no. Where're my compatriots?
That Kimito never was much
for sticking to the plan.
Regardless, today is the day
I show the world my quality.
Behold my new technique!
Karen style sword art!
Single Stretch!
And we're in!
Wow! That was some straight
up superhero stuff!
We better go while we still can!
Oh no! We're surrounded!
Looks like it's
the end of the line.
There's too many, Kimito,
we don't stand a chance!
[KAREN] Continue the
mission. I'll handle them.
Right! My sister thanks you!
[KIMITO]
Be careful!
Karen style sword art.
Whirlwind Number 58.
Overabundance!
[TAKEMIYA]
Not so fast, Master Masaomi.
Please, let us by!
You know I can't do that.
I recognize this must
be very hard on you.
But Master Masaomi, it's
time to let your sister go!
I will not!
What're you doing?
Takemiya!
[TAKEMIYA]
I see your resolve is strong.
But it's not strong enough.
[MASAOMI] Don't worry,
guys, I'll handle him!
You go on ahead without me!
[yelling]
Quickly!
Reiko's up the stairs
and to the right.
[KIMITO]
Good work, Hakua.
[AIKA]
Hold on, Kimito!
Slow down a bit!
I think I'm gonna puke!
How can you say that
at a time like this?
[AIKA]
Because I'm gonna puke!
First we had to deal with
guards. And now robots?
[AIKA]
I can handle this one.
[KIMITO]
Handle it how?
[yelling]
Where'd you learn
to throw like that?
[AIKA chuckles]
Pretty impressive
don't'cha think?
[HAKUA]
Keep moving!
[KIMITO]
Right!
[AIKA gasps]
[AIKA]
Hey! Wait for me!
[bang]
The hell is this?
[KIMITO]
Oh, crap!
[HAKUA] Come on! The
control room's right here!
[KIMITO]
Good job, Hakua!
Look out!
[AIKA]
Are you okay?
We're good.
Thanks a lot.
It's closing too quickly!
We aren't gonna make it!
I love muscles.
Hakua, you're almost there!
Hot damn, it worked!
Kimito, what're you standing
around like that for?
We gotta move!
My bad!
[KIMITO]
Hakua, is this the right way?
[HAKUA]
Yeah. Just past this room.
[AIKA]
This way?
Is that what I think it is?
Hakua, how do we
stop this thing?
[AIKA yelps]
Watch out!
[ALL gasp]
[KAREN]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Is everybody all right?
Karen! Where did you
get that outfit?
There's a room in this mansion.
It's flow of time is different
from the outside world's.
That sounds cool.
Uh! Be careful!
[KAREN]
Watch and learn, Kagurazaka!
This is not Resolution.
Nor Overabundance,
nor Single Stretch!
This is the Karen sword
art final technique!
I call it: Rising
Impact Infinity!
[KIMITO] Your anime attack
names make no sense!
[KAREN yelling]
[AIKA]
She did it! It stopped moving!
[KAREN] Never mind about me.
Continue the fight.
Kagurazaka?
[KIMITO]
Thanks, Karen!
You can just keep
the jacket, 'kay?
[MASAOMI]
Takemiya!
[TAKEMIYA]
Damn you, Masaomi!
You have gotten much
stronger, my boy.
I'm not a little boy anymore,
old timer, I'm a man!
[BOTH yelling]
I hacked these two.
Thanks, you're the best!
[HAKUA]
Good luck.
[KIMITO yelps]
[KIMITO]
Oh boy.
Kimito. You came.
[HOKO]
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Reiko's
friend from school.
So nice to see you again.
I assume you've come here
because you're concerned
for my daughter.
But as you can
see, we're busy.
So, I'm going to have to ask
you to leave right away.
Goodbye, sir. We
appreciate you stopping by.
Uh, Ma'am?
Yes?
I have something to say.
The thing is-- Ah!
I am against this marriage!
Fly you fool.
Is that so?
And so is your daughter!
My daughter is happy
to do her duty.
Isn't that right, love?
Tell your friend.
She is nervous.
But as a daughter of
the Arisugawa dynasty,
she knows exactly how
important this engagement is
to our family legacy.
This isn't what Reiko
wants and you know it!
She's only going along with
it because she's afraid!
It makes no difference
what the child wants.
[KIMITO gasps]
Family comes first.
Even before true love.
Reiko is fully aware that
this is a step she must take.
And that to marry into a great
family is a noble calling.
Her desires notwithstanding,
this is her sole
purpose in life.
I know this is confusing.
I wouldn't expect a mere
Commoner to understand.
[KIMITO]
You're right.
I've been at Seikain for
a little over a month,
and I still don't
understand your world.
Not even a bit.
Everything is different,
from the clothes you wear
to the food you eat.
I did my best to explain what
life is like for regular people,
but it doesn't get
through. Not really.
Honestly, I'm not sure we'll
ever understand each other.
But, even so.
All these girls...
...the members of
the Commoner Club...
...they are my best friends!
It's true.
So what if we do things
a little differently?
So what if we come
from different places?
We have had so much fun.
But now you're taking that away!
You're tearing us apart!
Stop! Please!
[REIKO gasps]
He feels this strongly?
That's quite a story.
But Reiko's made her decision.
She's accepted her fate.
What a giant load of crap!
Aika.
[gasps]
When I got to Seikain, I just
wanted people to like me.
And all I cared about
was being popular.
But now I realize just
how shallow that was.
I mean. Who cares how
many friends you have?
Life's not about
getting everyone
to think you're awesome.
It's about finding the
people you click with.
I learned that from Kimito.
From Karen. From Hakua.
But most of all, from Reiko!
I know it's not our place
to barge into your house
and tell you what to do
with your own daughter,
even so... we're here!
Because Reiko deserves to be
around the people she loves!
Please don't force
her to marry him!
We don't want to
lose our friend!
Please, ma'am!
[AIKA, HAKUA, KAREN]
It's time for our
guests to leave now.
[GUARD A]
Come with me.
[AIKA] Let go! Kimito,
do something! Please!
[KIMITO]
What can I do?
[REIKO]
Mother.
I am sorry. But I'm
leaving home for good.
Reiko.
I appreciate your
sentiment, my darling,
but do you even realize
what you're saying?
Of course, I do!
[HOKO]
So sure of yourself.
I only ask because
I worry that perhaps
you've forgotten
the way things work.
Only young ladies from
prestigious families
are given the honor
of attending Seikain.
If you walk away from
your family name, my dear,
they won't so much as
let you in the front door.
So if you want to
run away from home,
by all means, suit yourself.
But you'll have nowhere to go.
And you'll find yourself
wandering the streets.
[growls]
No, you won't!
Come and live with me!
[gasps]
To hell with family prestige!
It's the Commoner world!
Those old rules and
traditions are dead now!
You wouldn't get
to stay at Seikain,
and I can't offer the
lifestyle you're used to,
but, you know...
Wow. This is wonderful!
[KIMITO] I'll have to
convince my parents,
but it'll work out.
I swear that I'll do everything
in my power to make you happy.
[REIKO]
Yes.
My answer is yes then!
In sickness and in health,
I shall be yours!
Yeah, whatever.
My dearest parents,
thank you for everything.
I would be nowhere
without your help.
[clears throat]
[KONOE FATHER]
Having heard the news
of Reiko's strong inclinations,
my son was
understandably surprised.
So he's returned to Stanford
and has decided to officially
withdraw the engagement.
That is that.
No hard feelings,
but from our perspective,
the matter is concluded.
Well, dear, I don't
know what to say.
[laughing]
Reiko.
As far as I'm concerned,
you may marry whom you like.
[gasps]
Do you mean it?
Thank you very much, Mother!
[HOKO]
Mr. Kagurazaka?
Uh. Ma'am?
Be good to her. Look after
her and cherish her forever.
[REIKO] I do not have
the words to tell you
how much this means to me!
Hold on. Forever?
That's correct.
Marriage is forever.
[ALL]
Uh?
You did just propose to my
lovely daughter, did you not?
Uh...
Come and live with me!
You won't be able to
go to school anymore,
and I can't offer the
lifestyle you're used to,
but, you know...
I'll have to convince my
parents, but it'll work out.
I swear.
I'll do everything I can
to make you happy.
[KIMITO] I did just finish
proposing to her daughter!
Although you're both a
bit on the young side.
It's never too early to start
planning your life together.
[REIKO]
Agreed!
[REIKO] At long last I get
to meet Kimito's parents!
[KIMITO]
Just one thing...
Yes, of course.
What is it, child?
[KIMITO]
Well. You see--
I do hope you're not
getting cold feet already.
Because that would
be a terrible shame.
Especially after all
the wonderful things
you've just said.
Is something wrong?
Wait! Why would you
let Reiko do this?
What do you mean, sir?
I am broke as a joke!
I'm a loser!
You seem confused.
Let me explain.
I've come to despise you in
the deepest part of my soul.
That is why I would
very much like you
to become my son-in-law.
Wait, that's not
how hate works.
You should avoid me.
No. That simply wouldn't do.
I'd love for you to
be a part of my life
so that I can torment you
with everything I can muster.
[squeals]
I do look forward
to it very much.
Welcome to the family, son.
[KIMITO] I don't want
her to be my mommy!
[AIKA]
Hold on a second, lady!
Objection!
We invoke our three fifths
majority in the Commoner Club
to veto this marriage!
That's right!
It's perfectly obvious that this
isn't what Kagurazaka wants!
Yeah!
But the matter is decided.
No, it's not!
You have got some nerve!
How dare you dodge
my sucker punch!
What am I supposed to do,
just stand there
and let you kill me?
I'm not gonna let you have her!
That's why I'm taking
you out, pervert!
[yelping]
[MASAOMI] Reiko's my
little sister, not yours!
I never said she was,
you big weirdo!
[growls]
Time to die!
[KIMITO]
Reiko! Can't you stop him?
[REIKO]
"One hundred Fun Wedding Ideas."
I didn't know that
Commoner's had such
wonderfully
engrossing literature!
You have no cause to be
reading that, ya hear?
We should confiscate it.
[REIKO]
Ah!
Give that back or else!
Really? After everything I did
to stop you from leaving?
Obviously, I will come
visit you whenever I can!
I don't really care if I ever
see your treacherous face again.
[KIMITO] Your brother's
a friggin' psycho!
[TAKEMIYA] Masaomi,
please! Stop this at once!
[MASAOMI]
Takemiya!
[KIMITO screams]
[KIMITO]
I'm sorry.
What I said was
profoundly misleading.
There's no need for that.
Oblige me and lift up
your head, please.
It was my fault for
jumping to conclusions.
Both my mother and I could
not be any more embarrassed.
Do not feel bad at all.
[KIMITO] That's really nice,
but obviously, I do.
You mean a lot to me, Reiko.
I never meant to hurt you.
You're supposed to call
me "Rei"' now, remember?
Oh. I forgot.
I'm so sorry, Rei.
I led you down the
wrong path back there.
It's my fault, do you hear me?
Yeah. Sure.
[door opens]
[AIKA]
All right, you two,
what're you doing
in here by yourselves?
What? There's
nothing wrong with it.
[AIKA] Uh, yeah there is,
it's Club time!
Though this meeting
is beneath the dignity
of a master Samurai,
I shall attend it.
That's right. I forgot.
I wanted to ask you about
something you said to me
back at my estate.
If I had run away from home,
were you actually going
to let me live with you?
Of course.
Maybe I will run away then.
[AIKA]
What?!
Seriously, after everything
we just went through?
Well, I'm afraid it's none
of your business, Aika!
Of course it's my
business, you freak!
Or did you forget
we saved your butt?
If I were you, I would cease
this line of conversation!
--And if I were you...
--Hakua!
[KAREN] Come back here,
you pointless little nugget!
[KIMITO]
Stop undressing right now!
[KAREN]
Stay still, you whipper-snapper!
[KIMITO]
Stop perving! Stop!
Bad!
You stupid jerk.
Where in the world
are you, Kimito?!
[PRESIDENT] Well, no matter
which way you look at it,
the damage is already done.
But how are we going
to deal with him?
I've an idea.
His tongue was the culprit, so
why don't we have it removed.
Oh, my. Perhaps
that is a bit harsh.
Please believe me,
I really am sorry!
Well, you know how
these things always go.
I suppose we'll have
to suffer through it
a little while longer.
[FEMALE STUDENT A, B] So, do you
ladies wanna give it a shot?
[FEMALE STUDENT C, D, E]
Totally!
[ALL]
Have a Gets Day!
[ALL chuckling]
This fad will die out.
I've no doubt the
forces of nature
want this wretched thing
gone as much as I do.
[sighs]
Yes, but when things
catch on here,
they have a tendency to linger.
How long are we talkin'?
I don't know.
Maybe about five years.
[KIMITO]
Five years?
Let's just hope and pray 'gets'
doesn't make it that long.
[KIMITO]
"Dear Mom and Dad.
How's the hot spring?
I've done something terrible.
I made 'gets' happen."
[ALL]
Gets!