[YAMADA]
Hey!
Good morning everyone,
this is Misaki Yamada coming
at you live from the studio!
I'm here today
with up-and-coming
teen idol and voice actress,
the one and only Eri Hanae.
Hello there.
Thanks for having me on!
[YAMADA] This is the third time
we've had you on the show!
In my opinion,
that pretty much makes
you an honorary host!
Well in that case.
I'd like our listeners to pick
me out a custom greeting!
Send them in
right away, folks!
Nothing would make me happier!
[ERI]
Damn it!
Stupid DJ!
She didn't talk about my voice,
aka "The Money-Maker."
She didn't even comment on
how freaking adorable I am,
even though everyone knows it!
I hate her!
How annoying!
How aggravating!
I don't think I've ever
been this pissed off
in my entire life!
[KIMITO]
Dear Eri. I'm doing fine.
I've managed to make
a few friends here,
so don't worry about me. Kimito.
[ERI] I'm not worried
about you, moron!
What the crap?
[KIMITO]
You came by to see me?
First, put some clothes on.
[stomach growls]
Not much variety here.
What sounds good to you?
Fried potatoes, steamed
potatoes, or potato cakes?
Potato cakes?
[KIMITO] Well, they're a lot
like rice cakes, I guess.
You make the dough
out of mashed potatoes,
then fry them in a pan.
They're pretty tasty.
I want that.
I don't mind cooking,
but are you sure you want me to?
I doubt these babies
are on your meal plan.
[HAKUA] As long as you're
the one who prepares it,
I'll eat anything.
[KIMITO]
Right.
Well then, I'll make sure
it tastes delicious.
[HAKUA]
Kimito?
Yeah?
I would like to help.
[KIMITO] You can ball up
the dough if you want.
[KIMITO] Hang on! Not until
you wash your hands!
[KIMITO]
I have an idea.
Whaddaya think? Cute, huh?
Yes, it is cute.
[KIMITO]
Okay!
She is one weird girl.
[KIMITO]
Aw man!
Wait! Why did you only
leave the apron on?
Why not your freaking panties?
Jeez!
[KIMITO]
Yeah, I don't think weird
is a strong enough word
to describe her.
[KIMITO]
All right! You ready to eat?
Is it good?
Very.
Yeah. It's not bad.
Not bad.
Here is the question:
What is always closed when
something passes through it,
but always open
when nothing does?
Oh. A riddle. Cool.
It says right down here
that the answer
is a train crossing.
That does make sense.
Don't I get a chance
to guess the answer?
Guess the answer?
What do you mean?
Well, you've played
riddle games before,
haven't you?
Like in kindergarten or
grade school or whatever?
I don't remember very
much from kindergarten.
You have to remember
something, right?
What did you do for fun?
I proved several
ergodic hypotheses.
Huh?
I created an autonomous robot.
And I drew quite a few
circuit schematics.
Oh. Gotcha.
Well in that case this
should be pretty easy.
Here's a good one.
A father frog obviously
croaks "erbit-erbit."
A mother frog clearly
croaks "ribbit-ribbit."
So then...
How does their baby frog croak?
"Erbit?" "Ribbit?"
If the vocal sac expands fully.
Depending on the
frog's species...
One twenty four point five!
[KIMITO]
Where'd she get that?
The correct answer is,
"it doesn't croak,
because it's a tadpole"!
[KIMITO laughing]
Not sure why,
but I thought you'd
be way better at these.
Ask me another one.
'Kay.
When a car drives
around a curve,
what's the one thing
it is guaranteed to lose?
Gasoline?
Gas might burn,
but it's not lost.
Parts?
That would be scary.
People?
I would hope not.
All right,
I'm just gonna tell you--
Not yet!
[HAKUA gasps]
[KIMITO]
Ya figure it out?
[HAKUA] Is it worn-down
tire molecules?
[KIMITO]
Yeah...
But those come off when the
car's going straight, too.
[HAKUA]
Huh?!
[KIMITO] The word you're
lookin' for is "speed."
[KIMITO laughs]
Yeah, ya might be
overthinking your answers a bit.
Give me another!
[KIMITO]
Sorry. I'm all out.
--[HAKUA] One more! One more!
--[KIMITO laughing]
[KIMITO] Go on, Hakua.
Sakimori's waiting.
I wanna stay with Kimito.
[KIMITO]
Don't worry.
You can come by
again tomorrow.
[KIMITO]
Is that a... plushy?
Uhh...
[KIMITO gasps]
[KIMITO]
Huh?
What was that all about?
[REIKO] Kimito and Hakua
seem to be getting along.
They spend quite
a bit of time together.
[KAREN] Why don't you say
what you really mean?
What those two
are doing is criminal!
Aika, you know Kimito
as well as anyone,
what are your thoughts
on the matter?
Oh yeah, those two
are totally out-of-bounds!
It's always bothered me,
but lately,
it's getting
borderline freakish!
If I so much as open
my mouth to talk to Kimito,
she gets all weird
and clingy with him
and he falls
right into her trap.
[KAREN] I wish she would
cling to me instead.
[AIKA] Sometimes, when we're
playing video games together,
Hakua decides Kimito's not
paying enough attention to her.
So naturally she starts
takin' all her clothes off,
like some deranged psychopath!
[KAREN] Well, we can't
force her to wear clothes!
I'm tellin' you,
she does it on purpose!
Oh, you don't
have to tell me that!
She only eats cookies
if he feeds them to her.
When he puts them on a plate,
she refuses to so much
as acknowledge them!
I don't know what else to say.
Except this, of course:
It depresses me to
the very core of my being!
He sucks!
Yes he does!
[BOTH]
Hm?
I feel envy.
I want to kill him.
No. Killing him will not do.
There's no question,
he's the one to blame here.
When he feeds her, he's like
a kid in a candy store.
He's loving every minute of it,
big ole jerk wad that he is!
He's acting like her manservant.
It's disgusting.
Well in that case...
Perhaps I should strip like her.
[AIKA]
Huh?
It was nothing!
Nothing at all, I swear!
The answer is simple.
We must tear sweet Hakua
from his clutches.
If we don't
intervene and fast,
this situation will turn
from bad to worse,
and I will not allow that.
The perv must be stopped!
I agree!
We can't just sit back
and let it go on like this.
You are exactly right, Aika.
We must do everything in our
collective power to stop them!
[REIKO]
But first...
We must discuss the matter
thoroughly with Hakua.
[REIKO]
This is peculiar.
She should be here by now.
Kimito is out running
an errand at the moment.
Unfortunately, he will
not be back for a while.
[REIKO]
Please! Don't leave!
He's gone, but you
can hang with us.
Oh yes.
It can be very fun with just
us girls, don't you agree?
We would very much like to spend
some time with you, Hakua.
Come, come. Take a seat.
Oh! I know what to do!
I will make us some tea!
[AIKA]
Sounds good!
[KAREN]
Yes, indeed!
Well? Is something
the matter, Hakua?
Please. Do have some.
What's her problem?
My tea is perfect, as are
the tasty treats I prepared.
Maybe she doesn't like
the way that it smells?
No, it's something else.
What could it possibly be?
[KAREN]
Hakua only eats
when someone feeds her
by hand, remember?
Eat the treat!
[AIKA] I don't think
that's gonna work.
You leave me
with no other choice!
Hi, I'm Kimito.
I like muscle men
and girls who look like
they're in grade school
'cause I'm a perv!
Oh hey, look.
A cookie in my hand.
Wanna eat it?
[KAREN]
She despises me!
[stomach growling]
[REIKO]
I'm confused.
What do we do, Aika?
How the heck
am I supposed to know?
Kiryu? Kiryu?
[KIRYU]
Yes, Miss Reiko.
I'm here.
Thank goodness.
Look at this, Hakua.
I brought you some sushi,
it's on your scheduled menu.
[REIKO]
I guess it's true.
If it's not part of her menu,
then she refuses to eat it.
[AIKA]
She's a weird one.
But now that
we got her eating,
I think we should have our talk!
[REIKO]
Yes. I concur.
[AIKA]
Say, Hakua!
[ALL gasp]
[AIKA]
Whoa! Stop that!
Hakua, please, you must
not undress yourself right now!
[KAREN]
Gah! She's so adorable!
Pointless! It's so pointless!
How can she be so cute?
Can you not? You freak.
What's wrong, Aika?
[AIKA]
Are you okay?
Don't just lie there!
Get her panties back on!
Stop it with
the strip routine!
[KAREN]
Pointless! Pointless!
[AIKA]
Karen, shut up!
[AIKA panting]
[REIKO]
This is quite tiresome.
Does Kimito go
through this every day?
[AIKA sighs]
He doesn't have to.
She's a heck of a lot
easier to handle
when he's the one
taking care of her.
Oh, dear.
So you're suggesting Hakua
has closed her heart off
to us completely?
Maybe.
[knocking]
Pardon, ladies.
Miss Hakua, I've come
to take you back home.
[REIKO]
Hakua. Wake up.
Your maid is here to get you.
I can handle things
from here. Thanks!
Gather up your things, please.
Oh! I see Kimito
is not here today.
How odd.
No, just my other friends.
[SAKIMORI]
All right. Off we go.
[HAKUA]
As I'm sure you all know,
a father frog obviously
croaks "erbit-erbit."
And given that,
a mother frog must clearly
croak "ribbit-ribbit." Right?
But if that's true,
how does a baby frog croak?
I adore a good riddle.
The father frog goes "erbit."
And the mother frog
goes "ribbit."
Then the baby frog goes...
The baby frog goes...
She's so cute! It's pointless!
What? That's a trick question.
A baby frog's a tadpole,
so it doesn't croak at all.
Well... Hello. Uh...
Long time no--
You jerk.
I don't even know you anymore.
You leave your girlfriend
all alone for over a month?
I suppose you must've
been very busy.
[KIMITO]
Yeah. Sorry. My bad.
[MARIKA (ERI)]
Moron.
I was terribly
worried about you.
I was starting to think
you didn't like me anymore.
[KIMITO] Would I feel less
creepy playing this game
if it wasn't voiced by Eri?
Probably not.
[MARIKA (ERI)]
How do you feel about me?
Tell the truth.
Well, I...
Uh... I love you?
What?
I'm sorry, I didn't hear you.
Could you say it again? Please?
[KIMITO] What kind of
mind game is she playing here?
I love you.
Hey, Kimito, how's it go--
[KIMITO squeaks]
I hope you're not doing
what I think you're doing.
[AIKA]
'Kay...
Let me make sure I
understand you correctly.
Your girlfriend's a character
in a hand-held video game.
[KIMITO]
Yeah?
I should tell him
how creepy that is.
But if I don't choose
my words carefully,
I'll hurt his feelings.
[KIMITO]
Thinkin' out loud again, are ya?
[AIKA gasps]
Just so we're clear,
I'm not playing this
because I want to.
Eri, one of my
friends from home,
is the lead voice actress.
Wait, what?
When you play video games,
the characters talk
and stuff, right?
She does the voices.
Cool! I wanna hear
what she sounds like!
Sure thing, knock yourself out.
I'm Marika.
Nice to meet you!
[AIKA]
Uh--Oh!
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Aika Tenkubashi.
So, you're good
friends with Kimito, are you?
Uh, yeah?
I mean, I guess
you could say that.
[MARIKA (ERI) chuckles]
No need to be nervous.
Oh. Right.
Well, if I'm being honest,
I'm a little bit
nervous myself.
That makes us twinsies.
[AIKA chuckling]
[KIMITO] You know
she's not real, right?
[P.A. VOICE 5A]
Mr. Kimito Kagurazaka.
Please come to the president's
office immediately.
[KIMITO]
What the heck?
I'll be back in a bit.
I like spending
time with you, Aika.
You seem like a
really awesome person.
You too!
You're super awesome!
Glad you agree.
I know we just met, but I
think we can be best friends!
Yes! Same here!
I'll love you
till death do us part!
Would you mind saying that
one more time please?
I'll love you
till death do us part!
Hello, Kimito,
how are you today?
[AIKA giggling]
Aika? What are you doing here?
Huh? Oh. Nothin' much.
Just makin' a new bestie.
Oh. Neat.
Look. If it's Kimito
you want, he's not here.
Hakua and Karen aren't either,
and I'm busy.
So don't let the door
hit your butt on the way out.
[REIKO] His room feels
far more spacious
with just the two of us inside.
Isn't your room spacious too?
There's a book I'd
like to borrow, that is all.
[AIKA sighs]
[AIKA] Doesn't look like
the silent treatment's
gonna work on this girl.
Maybe if I pretend
to have an infectious di--
I have a question.
Huh. Good for you.
I'm curious about these books.
Why do all the covers
feature girls?
[AIKA]
Well, if ya look closely,
you'll see that the girls
on the manga's covers
are also its main characters.
[REIKO]
Yes, that's true,
but all the other series
are the exact same way.
These novels are directed
at gentlemen, are they not?
Don't you find it strange?
Maybe I would if I cared.
Just borrow a book
and read it in your room.
Later, I'll tell Kimito
you stole it.
First I'd like to
ask you something else.
Why are you reading in his room?
Also, I find it unsavory
that you're on his bed.
Certainly there are more
appropriate places to read.
Mind your own business.
[REIKO gasps]
My goodness! Aika!
I can see your underpants!
[AIKA]
Pervert!
If anybody here
is a pervert, it's you!
You are far too relaxed in
Kimito's residence, young lady!
I'm goin' back to my room.
Are ya happy now, jerk?
Yes, extremely happy.
Now, when he returns,
the two of us will finally get
to spend some time by ourselves.
Ooh, which one is that?
Hey get away!
[REIKO] Once again, a book
with girls on the cover flap.
It appears to me that nearly all
of Kimito's books are like this.
Why is that?
[AIKA]
Uh... 'Cause he's a pervert?
How dare you!
Kimito is a gentlemen!
Why, surely you don't believe
him to be anything less?
[AIKA] Maybe he's
a perverted gentleman.
Well... One thing seems clear.
Even though he's purported
to be homosexual,
Kimito is obviously
interested in women.
[REIKO giggles]
What shall I do?
[AIKA] The heck do you mean,
"what shall I do?"
[REIKO] I must admit,
I have truly come to adore
one of the characters who
appears in this story.
She speaks and acts
in an unusual way.
But I simply love
her earnest demeanor.
And how hard she works
so as not to let the
recipients of her good will
feel indebted to her.
[AIKA] Meh. I prefer
the main character.
[REIKO]
Huh? Who do you mean?
[AIKA]
The main one! Her!
[REIKO]
Oh. Is that who you meant?
Forgive me, but she did not
leave much of an impression.
[AIKA]
How could she not?
She's a frickin' angel!
I mean look! She has wings!
I'm gonna go find
some comfort food.
What do you suppose that is?
Uh, you gonna
follow me everywhere, or?
It appears to be
some kind of juice.
This must be the type
of thing a Commoner drinks.
Well, it's mine now!
That is not fair, Aika.
I would like to drink
some of the juice as well!
What's your problem?
I'm the one who found it!
It's mine by right!
Look, Blondie.
I'm not a stingy girl.
But you're the last person
I'd share this drink with!
If that's how it must be.
What?
There's only one bottle,
so it doesn't appear that
sharing's a viable option.
Hey. Wait a sec.
Fine. Grab some cups.
Go ahead.
I'm gonna let you have some.
Because it's the
right thing to do.
[AIKA]
You're a weirdo.
Why are you so giddy
all of a sudden?
Oh. Well, I suppose
I'm a bit excited, is all.
It's not every day
I get the opportunity
to drink the Commoner juice.
Oh, yeah?
Let's give it a try then.
[AIKA]
Bottoms up!
[REIKO] Aika, I drink this
to your health!
[AIKA]
What is this crap?!
[BOTH coughing]
[REIKO] That bubbling
was absolutely horrendous!
[AIKA]
Aww, man...
Why the heck did you
spit it all over me?
So gross!
[REIKO]
You did the same!
[AIKA]
Ugh! This is just hopeless!
[REIKO]
Wait!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm gonna get
all sticky if I don't take
these nasty clothes off.
Why are you staring
at me like that?
No reason.
[REIKO] You can't just heap
your clothes on the floor!
[AIKA]
It's fine!
No ma'am, it is not.
As a student of Seikain, I
cannot abide this lack of form.
We have standards.
[AIKA]
Leave me alone!
Give them here!
[BOTH yell]
[REIKO]
Aika, can you hear me?
Aika, please.
You have to wake up!
Are you all right? Speak to me!
[muffled screaming]
I was so worried about you!
My apologies, Aika.
I do hope you will forgive me.
It was an accident, I swear.
Whatever, just get your
filthy jug-a-lugs outta my face!
What? Jug-a-lugs?
Are you making disparaging
comments about my breasts?
[AIKA] Oh, should I
have called them udders?
[REIKO] If I were you,
I'd take that back!
[AIKA]
No way!
Just get off of me, already!
They're filthy, you say?
Tell me, what exactly do you
find filthy about these?
I wash them with soap
nearly twice a day!
[AIKA screams]
--[AIKA] Get 'em outta my face!
--[REIKO] No! I shall not!
[REIKO] I shall not budge
till you take it back!
Apologize!
[KIMITO]
Uh...
Sorry to interrupt!
No, wait,
you've got the wrong idea!
Kimito!
This isn't what it looks like!
[ERI]
Damn it, Kimito.
Where did you go?
And what are you up to?
You see, this is "self" service.
I just want the toy.
One large chocolate
cream Foamuccino, please!
Meet me outside!
I will order first!
[SAKIMORI]
What are you doing, Hakua?
[AIKA screaming]
[KUJO]
It's called "Shominland."