[STUDENTS chattering]
[KUJO]
Ladies, please.
I ask that you all remain calm.
[KUJO]
As of this moment,
the specimen you see
before you will be
Seikain Girls' School's
"Shomin Sample."
Mr. Kimito Kagurazaka.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KUJO] Do any of you have
questions for the Commoner?
[STUDENTS]
Me! Me!
[chattering continues]
[school bell rings]
Wake up, Kimito!
Hey! Buy me tea?
Right now?
[ERI]
Why not?
You're about to go to
the store anyway, right?
Fine. Do you want your usual?
[ERI]
Yes, please!
You're a total lifesaver!
[KIMITO]
Yeah, yeah.
[MUSCLE SQUAD panting]
[KIMITO yells]
[MUSCLE SQUAD chuckling]
[KIMITO] Uh... Oh boy.
Is this weird?
Yep. This is weird.
[MUSCLE SQUAD C]
Yo!
[MUSCLE SQUAD D]
Boy!
[KIMITO yells]
Watch where
you're touching me!
[KUJO]
Mr. Kagurazaka.
Thank you very much for coming.
I didn't wish
to create a big scene,
so I chose this method.
[KIMITO] Well, I'd say
you failed, then!
Who the heck are you, anyway?
And where the heck am I?
Is this normally the way
you greet a stranger?
How very rude.
You are a Commoner
through and through.
I will explain the particulars
at a later time.
But for now come with me.
You may call me Kujo.
Please forgive me for not
introducing myself sooner.
I'm charmed to
make your acquaintance.
[KUJO]
This is a unique school
that teaches highborn
girls to be ladies,
raising them in tradition of
classical Japanese culture.
We value secrecy above all else,
and go to great lengths
to keep our existence
hidden from the world.
Welcome to
Seikain Girls' School.
An all girls' school.
Huh, right on.
You'll be receiving
your education here now.
[KIMITO]
Huh?
[KUJO] Formal arrangements
have already been made.
[KIMITO]
Huh?!
[KUJO] We have received
express permission
from your parents, as well.
Wait, I don't understand.
You kidnapped me from school.
At least tell me why!
[KUJO]
Follow me, please.
We have much to do.
[KIMITO]
Oh, yeah, sure!
[KUJO] You might say
this school exists
to be the academy of
modern female aristocracy.
Naturally, boys
are strictly prohibited.
Everyone on this
campus is a female.
Students, staff
and teachers alike.
And there has been
no exception to this rule.
However...
In recent years a certain
issue has complicated this.
What do you mean by "issue"?
I'm the President.
And a high school kid at heart!
Greetings!
And to you.
Continue, Madam President.
First of all,
it looks like Miss Miyuki
was a little rough on you,
and I know that she's
very sorry for that.
Right?
Tell him how
sorry you are, please.
[KUJO]
I do hope you'll forgive me.
[clicks tongue]
Did you just click
your tongue at me?
So...
Tell me more about this
"issue" you're having.
[KUJO] After the girls
graduate from here,
though they may live among
the upper echelons of society,
once outside,
they cannot avoid contact
with the normal world.
As such, students
are generally quite shocked
by the vast differences
between school life
and life outside these walls.
[KUJO]
Many fall hard.
Some even start
playing online games.
[KIMITO]
Hold on a second.
That's the "issue"
you were yakkin' about?
[PRESIDENT]
In these difficult times,
the consensus among
school leadership
is that we need to
inoculate our students
so they are better prepared
for life after school.
But it's a fine line.
We must prepare them, yes.
But not at the expense of
our long-standing tradition
of refined excellence.
And so...
That brings us to you.
You were selected as this
school's "Shomin Sample."
[KIMITO]
Okay. That's weird.
Incorrect.
It's not weird at all.
By inviting in a simple
Commoner like yourself,
and by having you live here
among your betters,
our students will
be more acclimated
to life after graduation.
[PRESIDENT]
Yes!
And with a boy, we kill
two birds with one stone!
[KUJO]
A lack of proper inoculation
against the opposite sex
has also been a problem
for our students.
[PRESIDENT] Oh, that's
one way of putting it!
But you're going to fix
all of that, I'm sure.
[KIMITO growls]
[KIMITO]
Now wait just a minute!
I hear what you're saying,
but I still don't get
why you picked me!
[KUJO]
Kimito Kagurazaka.
Prefectural High School
District 1.
Average student.
[KIMITO yelps]
[KUJO] Grades, looks,
height, brains, and weight.
Average.
[KIMITO yelps]
[KUJO] Well-known for
your caring nature,
you received the nickname
Sebastian in middle school.
You are average.
And that's just how we want you.
"Middle of the pack,"
as you Commoners say.
I was kinda hoping
you were gonna say
you picked me 'cause
of how awesome I am.
You do have one
extraordinary quality.
A rare quality
that we did not find
in any of the other
dozens of candidates
under our consideration.
[KIMITO]
My good looks?
[KUJO]
Afraid not.
I mean your attraction to males!
[KIMITO]
Wha--?
[KUJO] Or, more specifically,
a muscle fetish,
by which you are only aroused
by macho, muscular body types.
That makes you a--
[KIMITO]
Slow down!
What's wrong?
[KIMITO]
I don't have a muscle fetish!
Oh, but I'm afraid you do.
You typically have
no contact with girls.
According to our research,
you choose to spend all of
your time around boys instead.
[KIMITO]
They're my friends!
[KUJO] If there was any doubt,
the clincher was testimony
from your sole
female friend, Eri.
Damn that girl.
Anyway, you're dead wrong.
I like the ladies, okay?
[PRESIDENT]
This is a problem.
[KUJO] Agreed, this is an
extremely serious situation.
[KIMITO]
What's the matter?
If you are truly not a
muscle-loving gay boy,
then in order
to keep our secret,
you must live out
your days in a remote place
you won't find on any map.
And if you stay here,
so as to preserve the
chastity of our students,
we will have to
remove your genitals.
I'm sorry, but there's
just no other way.
[KIMITO growls]
[KIMITO]
I love... muscles!
[PRESIDENT]
That's terrific news!
[KUJO] You have a surprisingly
delicate side, don't you?
That's certainly a relief.
From this moment forward,
this is the classroom you'll
want to report to every morning.
Remember, these
young ladies have had
almost no contact with boys,
so be careful not to
overstimulate them, okay?
[KIMITO]
Okay.
I'll let you two take it
from here, Miss Miyuki.
As you wish,
Madam President.
[REIKO]
My name is Reiko.
I'm the committee chairperson
of the first years,
and as such,
I am at your service.
Should you need anything at all,
please do let us know.
On behalf of all of the
first years, welcome.
We're thrilled
to have you among us.
We look forward to four
productive years of study.
Hi.
I'm Kimito, and uh,
and I'm just a regular dude.
[STUDENTS]
Oh... my...
[MAYA] I cannot believe
he really said that!
[MIZUHO] I thought it was
just an old wives tale,
but it appears
Commoner men really do
refer to themselves as "dudes."
[REIKO clears throat]
Ladies, please.
[cell phone rings]
[KAE]
What is that?
[MAYA] Do you hear
that strange sound?
Ladies.
Stay calm, it's under control.
That's mine!
How rude.
But... What is it?
This is called
a cellular phone.
Or sometimes a smart phone,
depending on the model.
So strange.
So square. So dainty, too.
[KUJO]
As you can see,
it's a small telephone one can
carry around in one's pocket.
Such tools are widely used
amongst Commoners
like Kimito here.
[STUDENTS]
That is very neat!
I am beyond shocked!
Imagine something
so small and thin
being used as a telephone!
[chattering]
Pardon me.
But would it be all right
if I held it in my hand?
But of course.
Thank you, that's very kind.
Oh my! It's so dainty!
Imagine regularly using a
contraption as amazing as this!
It's wonderful.
Commoners truly are marvelous!
[REIKO]
Ladies.
That tiny telephone
is Kimito's property.
We must return it
to him at once.
[KAE] But how would one
do such a thing?
[MIZUHO] My heart feels like it
might leap out of my chest
just thinking of it!
I'll do the honor
on our behalf.
Perfect idea, Reiko!
There's no need
for us to fret now.
My dearest, sir.
Thank you for allowing
us to gaze upon
your tremendous device.
[REIKO gasps]
Oh! Heavens,
what am I thinking?
Please forgive me for
my mistake, kind sir.
I will write you a
thank you note immediately!
Kiryu!
Ma'am. I'm here.
My thanks.
That is the inimitable Reiko!
So considerate and refined.
[KIMITO]
Thank you very much.
[REIKO gasps]
[KIMITO]
Are you all right?
[STUDENTS]
Reiko, no!
It's Aika!
[KIMITO]
Wh-Whoa! Whoa!
Hey! What's your problem?
[AIKA]
You there!
Kiss me. Now!
Right now, Commoner!
C'mon then! Pucker up!
[KIMITO]
Wh-Whoa! Hold on. Why?
Duh! If you kiss a Commoner,
then all your wishes
will come true!
Now stop squirming
and give me a smooch
right here on the kisser!
[KIMITO] Your wishes
aren't gonna come true
just cause you kiss me!
You're wrong!
I know because
I was at a tea party
and I heard one of the
upperclassmen talk about it!
Look. Girl.
Who are you gonna believe,
some upperclassman who's never
been outside these walls, or me?
[AIKA whining]
Well... Whatever, man.
It's not like I believed her
anyway, you big loser!
Uh-huh.
Stupid jerk!
Please. You're the
one who's dumb
for thinkin' kissing
my lips is the same
as rubbing a magic lamp!
I don't believe that!
What's next?
You'll tell me rolling around
and barking like a dog
grants wishes too?
[AIKA]
Is that one true?
Bark!
[KIMITO]
She's kidding, right?
[AIKA]
Bark!
[KIMITO]
She's gotta be.
[AIKA]
Am I doing it right?
I wanna make sure
my wishes come true!
[KIMITO]
Nope. She's not.
[AIKA]
Bark!
[REIKO]
There you are!
I am terribly sorry,
my dearest sir.
Your sudden departure
deeply concerned us.
We couldn't help
but search for you.
The way Aika
yanked you away
was troublesome,
to say the least.
Yes, we were
quite taken aback.
Anyway...
Not to pry, but what have
you two been doing out here?
Oh. Well, uh...
Are you all right, Aika?
Don't go!
Dear.
It appears Aika
has run away again.
What's up with her?
[REIKO]
She's a mystery.
For some reason,
she refuses to talk to anyone.
Poor thing.
We don't know why,
but I suspect it's a shortcoming
on the part of all of us.
[KUJO] Mr. Kagurazaka,
this is the dormitory
where you shall reside
during your time here.
And, for your comfort
and consideration,
we have prepared a
special room for you.
We hope you find it suitable.
[KIMITO]
A special room?
[KUJO]
Yes.
We have spared no
expense in assuring
your accommodations will
be to your satisfaction.
Should you meet any issues,
I trust you will let us know.
[KIMITO]
Wow. Thanks a lot.
[KUJO]
My pleasure.
Well, here we are.
[KUJO] We had your
things brought here
from the Kagurazaka home.
We've reproduced your room
to near perfection.
I hope you are pleased.
Yup, this is
my room, all right.
[KUJO] After factoring in
freight costs,
construction expenses,
and other miscellaneous items
needed to maintain our secret...
This project cost us
one hundred million yen.
Wait... For real?
Who would've thought
that making something so cheap
could be so expensive?
But in the end, your comfort
is our number one priority.
[KIMITO]
This is insane.
Whoa!
[KUJO] If you truly are not
a muscle-loving gay boy--
[KIMITO yelling]
Please forgive me,
thigh collection.
I'm sorry!
What do you mean
thigh collection?
Are you referring to the
pictures of girls' thighs
you just tore down?
Wait, what? No!
So...
Am I to infer that your
muscle fetish is a lie?
[KIMITO]
Ooh! Gimme!
I love muscles!
Strange.
Oh... One more thing.
As of today,
I'm your personal maid.
Which means, whatever you need,
I'll see to it and make sure
it's done to your liking.
Well, that seems weird.
It's not weird.
At this school, students are
assigned a female maid
who looks after
their every need.
[KIMITO]
So then...
You have to do whatever I say?
[KUJO]
No.
Just because I'm assigned to you
doesn't mean I'll
do anything for you,
other than the
basic requirements.
[KIMITO]
Well, that's a bummer.
[KUJO]
Be ready.
In a few hours' time,
you'll participate in
an orientation meeting.
Till then,
I suggest you stay here
and try to get some rest.
You tricked me, Commoner!
I spun around 58 times
and barked all afternoon and
not a single wish came true!
[KIMITO] You'd think it
wouldn't take you 58 tries
to realize it wasn't happening!
[AIKA]
You shut your face!
It's not nice to trick
strangers, you know?
[KIMITO] You're the one who
jumped to the wrong conclusion.
I never thought you'd actually
do something so dumb
in the first place.
[AIKA]
Whoa... Your room.
I've never seen any
of this stuff before.
[KIMITO]
It's just regular old stuff.
[AIKA] This could be
my wish coming to life!
[KIMITO]
Uhh...
If I can learn to be common,
then everything I've ever
wanted in my wildest dreams
will come true!
I'd be the most popular
girl in the whole school
and everyone would love me!
[AIKA mumbling]
You're kidding me...
That's why you spun around and
barked like a dog 58 times?
Yeah.
That's right. So what?
It's fine to want that.
But you need to make friends,
not act like a big lunatic.
[KIMITO] Just be yourself
and treat people well,
and your wish'll come true.
Just being myself
won't get me anywhere.
You don't understand.
You're a Commoner.
[KIMITO]
Well, maybe I don't.
But...
[KIMITO] If you can
interact with others
the way you do with me
then I don't think you're
gonna have a problem at all.
You think so?
Yeah. That's my opinion.
The thing is...
I'm really bad when it comes
to not telling the truth.
It's a fault of mine.
I just blurt out
whatever's in my head.
Around here, that's
an unforgiveable sin.
Also, I'm really
scared of being disliked.
So that's why...
[KIMITO]
I see.
That's why you distance
yourself from them.
From your classmates.
It's hard.
Because I do wanna
be friends with people.
Being alone all
the time really sucks.
I want someone to talk to.
High school's supposed be fun.
But here I am, all by myself,
with no friends
to keep me company.
[AIKA]
It's pathetic, but in class,
I pretend to be asleep
most of the time.
And I'm always the
last one out the door
so I don't have to walk
with a big group.
But I hate it.
I'm tired of it!
[AIKA] I don't know why
I'm telling you all this.
You're just a
Commoner, after all.
[KIMITO]
Here. You wanna play?
What is it?
It's just a game.
Whoa. Neat.
Yeah.
You flip the switch and then
you're off to the races.
[AIKA gasps]
Pretty cool, right?
It's so awesome!
Crap, I responded
honestly without thinking first!
It's humiliating to behave like
that in front of a Commoner!
I have to find a way
to change the subject!
But the damage is already done!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Spills right out, huh?
There's a lesson in everything.
Hey!
What's up?
I want you to teach me
to be a Commoner!
[KIMITO]
Uh...
You're an expert.
Look. Uh...
No offense, but everything
in here is common.
Like this game!
Right now, Commoners are
all the rage at our school.
People are crazy about 'em!
So if I can pick up a little
bit of Commoner culture,
then you know what?
[giggles]
Everybody'll be crazy
about me, too!
I'll be the most
popular and beloved girl
in the whole school!
What say you?
There's no way I can make my
dream come true without you,
so what do you say?
Once I've become a master
of all things common,
I'll have so many new friends
I'll have to beat my
classmates off with a stick!
Hey, wait!
I know!
With you as my witness,
I hereby declare the creation
of the Commoner Club!
Uh... The what?
We just formed
a brand new club!
Which means we're
the founding members!
This is so much fun!
Wow!
Aren't you so
excited about this?
I've never formed
a real club before!
[AIKA]
Hey! You don't mind, right?
Well, I guess not.
[AIKA]
All right!
[laughing]
Commence Commoner Club
activities right now!
Definitely the first
thing I have to do
is master this crazy,
awesome game!
[KUJO] Do any of you have
questions for the Commoner?
[STUDENTS]
Me! Me!
All right.
Miss Yasuda has the floor.
I'm curious to know if you've
ever ridden a train before.
Yes. Yes, I have.
[STUDENTS gasping]
So... Good sir,
does this mean
that you paid money
and then subsequently
obtained a ticket
in exchange for your purchase?
Uh, no.
I don't really buy tickets.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KIMITO]
You see...
This is called a passcard, and
for the sake of convenience,
you can fill it up
with money in advance
using cash or a credit card.
It's actually a
pretty great invention.
So you just touch it
to the ticket gate
and it automatically debits.
[STUDENT 1B]
That was fascinating.
But I didn't understand
a word of what he said.
[STUDENT 1C]
Compared to us,
the Commoners have a much more
complicated civilization.
[STUDENT 1D]
I feel inspired!
I never dreamed
I'd have the opportunity
to speak to a Commoner!
No! You got it all wrong!
Commoners really aren't that
big a deal, I promise you!
[STUDENT 1E]
No! They are magnificent!
[STUDENT 1F]
And impressive, too!
We hope to be able
to study your ways!
[STUDENT 1G] We wish to learn
everything we can from you!
[STUDENT 1H]
You're so incredible!
[AIKA]
Nailed it!
And once I have,
I'll reveal my avatar
to the whole class!
[STUDENTS] You just have
to add hot water?
[AIKA]
See? See?
[KUJO] You have no idea how much
I wish you'd never woken up.
[REIKO] I'll just have
to have him take me.
I have no other choice!