[KUJO]
Are you awake, Kimito?
[KIMITO]
Yeah.
You've no idea how much
I wish you'd never woken up.
Hey, thanks a lot!
Real nice.
What a way to wake up.
Please don't take it personally,
but my morning chores
are quite burdensome.
If you'd only sleep all day,
then I'd have the morning off.
[KIMITO]
Oh. I see.
[KIMITO gasps]
Not cool!
I'm helping you
change your clothes.
Yeah. That's very nice
and all, but I got it covered!
No, this is a tradition.
This duty has always been
carried out by a Seikain maid.
You may be a sexual
deviant, Commoner.
But rules are rules.
And here at Seikain, you will
follow them no matter what.
[KIMITO]
That's right, I forgot.
If I don't act like a gay guy
with a muscle fetish,
then I'm totally screwed!
They'll kick me out and
ship me off to no man's land!
[KUJO] You're having disgusting,
immoral thoughts right now.
I can tell!
[KIMITO]
I am not!
[KUJO] And now you're thinking
about muscles, aren't you?
[KIMITO]
I am not!
[KAE]
Hello, Reiko.
Good morning!
And a good morning
to you, as well.
[KAE]
Is everything all right?
Ah, yes, I suppose.
[KUJO]
Right this way.
[KIMITO] How come we have to
go out through the back door?
Have you forgotten what
the reaction was like yesterday?
You create commotion.
I am trying to minimize it.
And as such,
till things calm down, this is
the best course of action.
[KIMITO]
Okay.
[BOTH]
Oof!
[KIMITO]
Watch out!
No!
This is my door, Commoner.
Back off!
[STUDENT 2A]
Have you ladies heard anything
about this Commoner?
[STUDENT 2B]
No, but I'm dying to know!
[KUJO]
This way. Quickly.
[KIMITO]
I get it.
You always take the back door
to avoid other people, right?
[AIKA]
Yeah.
But I gotta admit, you're the
last person I expected
to find sneaking to class.
Then again,
if we have this in common,
then clearly I have what it
takes to be popular, too!
Are you excited?
Today is the first official day
of our brand spankin' new
Commoner Club!
What's wrong with you?
Be excited!
[KIMITO]
I'm fine.
Just a little off my game.
How so?
[KIMITO] Well...
It's this whole maid thing.
In the Commoner world,
that isn't a custom.
For real?
Strangely, Commoners
don't have maids.
So...
I'm telling you what
I know about Commoners.
What if in exchange,
you taught me how things
work around here?
That sounds like an even
trade don't'cha think?
Yeah, that sounds
like a job for Reiko.
She'll tell you everything
you need to know and then some!
Cause she's super fancy!
I'd rather have you do it.
[AIKA]
Huh? Wait!
That doesn't make any sense,
why would you rather
have me than Reiko?
[KIMITO]
I don't know,
I guess you just seem
more down to earth.
Reiko's nice and all,
but she has this
crazy aura about her.
Like she's from another world.
Makes me feel uncomfortable.
I don't get that vibe
from you at all--
[KIMITO]
That hurt!
[AIKA]
You stupid Commoner!
Stay away from me, jerk!
[AIKA]
Ugh... crazy! How dare he...
[REIKO]
Hello, Kimito.
Good morning, my good sir.
Hi. Good morning.
[REIKO] I have been looking
all over for you.
I am oh so pleased
to find you here.
Yeah. Same.
[REIKO]
Good morning, Aika.
I hope you're well.
[REIKO]
Well, At any rate...
Could I have a moment
of your time after school?
You have my word:
you won't be disappointed.
[KIMITO]
Sure. Sounds good to me.
[REIKO]
Oh! That's wonderful!
I have a big night
planned for you.
After dinner, there will be a
welcome party in the auditorium.
We hope you'll come, Aika. Oh!
Dear. It appears
that once again
I've done something
to offend her sensibilities.
[KIMITO]
I don't get it.
Why does she get all cranky
like that over nothing?
[ENGLISH TEACHER 2A]
All right.
Who would like to translate
the next passage?
Miss Reiko?
[REIKO]
Please.
"The Duke put the milk
in the Spice of the Darjeeling."
Excellent reading!
[STUDENTS muttering]
[BOTANY TEACHER 2A]
Nicely done, Young Lady.
Very elegant work.
You're an incredible
botanist, Reiko!
[MIZUHO] Yes, your arrangement
is a stunning sight to behold!
What a perfect jump!
You just set a
new school record!
Your form is the true
embodiment of perfection!
Thank you very much,
dear friends.
All right, Aika,
it's your turn to shine.
[whistle blows]
[AIKA yelps]
[KIMITO] Well. That could'a
gone worse. Somehow.
[REIKO]
Uh... That's all right, Aika.
You did great!
[AIKA]
Shut up, Reiko.
You're next, Mr. Kimito!
[KIMITO]
Here goes nothin'!
[STUDENT 2D]
A brand new record!
That was truly
incredible, Kimito!
I didn't even
know it was possible
for a person to jump
as far as you just did!
[KIMITO] Relax. It's really
not that big of a deal.
[REIKO]
You were absolutely amazing!
Even if I worked every day
of my natural life,
I don't think I could come
close to making that jump!
It must be strange
possessing such power.
My coordination is so
lacking I can't make a landing.
[KIMITO laughs]
Where did our
social butterfly go?
Butterfly?
I don't understand.
Do you mean Aika?
Oh. Right.
Sometimes Commoners give their
friends sarcastic nicknames.
It's a sign affection.
Yep! It's kinda
like Commoner slang.
Or street talk.
Now that you
mention it, Kimito...
You and Aika were walking
together this morning,
were you not?
Not to pry...
But it appeared the two of you
were getting on splendidly.
[KIMITO]
Yeah.
It's true then.
If she can be a friend to you,
then the fault of our
estrangement is mine.
[KIMITO] I kinda wanna tell her
that Aika just wants everyone
to be her friend.
But I probably shouldn't get in
the middle of their thing.
[KIMITO]
I don't think it's your fault.
Whatever the cause is,
I just hope you don't
start to dislike her.
Honestly, I think that
would be a shame.
[REIKO]
How could I ever dislike her?
That's not possible.
[KIMITO]
Right.
[REIKO] But I do certainly
hope you are correct
in saying that
I haven't done anything
to incur Aika's displeasure.
If that's really true, I suppose
there's a ray of hope after all.
Hope's all I need.
In due time, I feel confident
we can all be friends.
I pray that you're right.
That would be
a dream come true.
Yes, it would.
We should do whatever
we can to make it so.
[KIMITO]
Whoa!
You're the guest of honor,
so you should lead the way.
[STUDENTS whispering]
[STUDENT 2E]
Here he is!
[STUDENT 2F] Is that really
how a Commoner walks?
[KIMITO]
Geez.
That's how closely
they're watching me?
[STUDENT 2G]
Look how he stumbled!
[STUDENT 2H] Is there some
meaning to the way he moves?
[KIMITO]
No!
What the heck?
This can't be Japanese.
I don't understand a word of it.
So, Kimito, what will
you be having for dinner?
The Japanese meal?
All right.
If that's what you're having,
then I shall do the same.
As shall I.
And so shall I!
As shall I, and I
couldn't be more excited!
[KUJO]
Thank you for your patience.
Hey, what the heck is this?
The Japanese meal.
I heard that Cup Men was the
staple food of the Commoner.
So out of regard for your ways.
That is stereotyping,
we don't all eat Cup Men
all the time.
You just clicked
your tongue again!
Don't do that!
[KUJO] So then, you're
declining the Japanese Meal?
Yes! Of course I--
Pardon me, but--
[KIMITO]
What?
[REIKO] It has such
an unusual aroma.
Do you eat it? Like food?
You don't know
what Cup Men is?
"Cup Men"?
Well, you know what
ramen is, don't you?
[REIKO]
Oh yes. I've heard stories.
Geez. It's not a legend.
It's just ramen.
Instant ramen, actually.
In other words,
it's the easy version.
You just have to add hot water,
and you can eat it.
[STUDENTS] You just have
to add hot water?
So... That's all the
preparation it requires?
Oh Reiko, I do not
understand this Cup Men at all!
[MIZUHO] Why does the
container have so many words
written on top?
[MAYA] I have some antique
porcelain at my house
adorned with ancient script.
I suppose it's similar.
[KIMITO]
Well, anyway.
We eat this a lot 'cause
it's convenient and cheap.
[REIKO] My! It truly looks
like actual food!
So many ingredients!
I recognize that as shrimp.
But what are those weird yellow
and brown things in the broth?
Simply by adding hot water,
one can give it
this culinary form?
How is that possible?
I don't know.
Do you wanna try it out?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KIMITO]
Uh...
Oh, Maya, please. Go ahead.
No, Kae. The honor is yours.
Ladies, please.
Let us not be impolite
to our guest.
This is a rare delicacy.
Let us all partake
in its wonder.
[STUDENTS]
Right!
If you would, Kujo?
As you wish, Miss Reiko.
[REIKO]
Just a moment, please.
If we are to receive such
a delicious treasure
as this from our honored guest,
then simple white porcelain
is far too uncivil.
[KIMITO]
Uh...
You know they're just noodles.
[REIKO] For this occasion,
let us use our best dishware!
[STUDENTS giggling, clapping]
So this is the
legendary "Cup Men"
Commoners eat for breakfast,
lunch and dinner?
Ooh! I do wonder
how it tastes!
The aroma is simply
lovely and exquisite!
[KIMITO] This is definitely
gonna be a massive letdown.
[REIKO] Thank you very much
for sharing, Kimito.
[KIMITO]
Yeah. Sure.
[REIKO] All right.
Let us all eat, then!
[STUDENTS]
Thank you for this meal!
[slurping]
[STUDENTS gasp]
This is so delicious!
[KIMITO]
Come on! Ramen?!
I've never tasted
anything like this!
Between the savory soup
and the texture of
the delicious noodles,
I honestly don't know what part
of the recipe I love the most!
It's wonderful.
And I want more!
[REIKO]
This is, without a doubt,
an unprecedented experience.
I shall never forget
these noodles or this day.
I swear.
I shall cherish this blessed
memory deep in my heart.
Thank you for bringing
this to us, Kimito!
[KIMITO]
I don't get it.
Why are noodles such
a big deal to them?
[AIKA sighs]
There really is nothing better
than eating lunch all by myself!
[REIKO]
Here we are at last.
Your welcoming party.
Are you surprised at this?
Yeah I am.
Thanks, Reiko. This is perfect.
Oh, well...
It's a passion of mine.
I do enjoy thinking up
delightful little gatherings
such as these.
Everyone,
a toast to Kimito for
transferring here!
[REIKO]
Hip, hip!
[STUDENTS]
Hooray!
Is something
the matter, Kimito?
[KIMITO]
What? No way.
I was just thinking
how awesome you are.
I mean, you put this whole
thing together, right?
[REIKO]
No, no.
You are the one who is
"awesome," as you say,
for you are well versed in a
myriad of customs unknown to us.
After learning of
your curious ways,
I feel as though a whole new
world has opened up for me.
Your compliments
fill me with such pride,
although I feel quite unworthy.
Forgive my boldness,
but would you care to dance?
[KIMITO]
Uh, oh, no. I don't dance.
Well, I never have before,
that is.
Commoners don't
go to things like this.
Fancy parties, I mean.
I wasn't aware.
Please forgive me my naiveté,
I did not mean to offend you.
[KIMITO]
No. Please.
I don't mind trying
it out if you want!
The only thing is...
I don't know how.
[REIKO]
Oh! Then I shall teach you.
What fun!
[KIMITO]
So what now? We dance?
Uh, Reiko? Are you okay?
[REIKO]
Yes.
[KIMITO] You don't have to
worry about doing a good job
or anything like that.
I can't dance at all,
so if you did mess up,
I don't even think I'd notice.
And if anyone's gonna
step on someone's foot, it's me.
Shall we continue?
Yeah. What do we have to lose?
Uh... Yes. Well...
[KIMITO]
We're totally dancing!!
[KIMITO yelling]
[STUDENT 2I] Such innovative
and provocative moves!
[STUDENT 2J] This must be
how all Commoners dance!
[KIMITO]
Like hell it is!
Oh crap, she looks like
she's gonna pass out again!
[REIKO gasps]
[KIMITO]
I can't let her fall!
[STUDENTS applaud]
[KIMITO]
Uh... uh... awkward.
[AIKA]
You're late!
Just how long were ya
gonna keep me waiting for?
I couldn't help it, okay?
They threw me a party,
I had to go!
Speaking of, why didn't
you make an appearance?
This is a club meeting, punk!
Shut up about your dance and
teach me some peasant stuff!
So what are we
gonna do first?
Hold on.
Gimme a second to think.
Let's see now, what's something
most normal people do?
Eat? Sleep?
[AIKA]
Say, Commoner.
What are all these things?
[KIMITO]
Are you kidding? Manga.
[AIKA]
What's manga?
[KIMITO]
You don't know manga?
How are you
supposed to read this?
Oh...
Let me think, I've never
had to explain it before.
Well, it's pretty
simple, actually.
You read it right to left.
And then top to bottom,
that make sense?
[AIKA]
"There must be..."
"...a mistral chaser." Wait.
What the heck
is a mistral chaser?
"The weapons--"
Oh good, so it's like
a violent story then!
"Whoosh!" "Ha!"
"All of it was
for this moment!"
"Avatar Form 2:
Soaring Izanami!"
So, how was it?
[AIKA]
I'm a little surprised at you.
Why didn't you say something
about this before?
[KIMITO]
About what?
About how all
Commoner high schoolers
have special psychic
abilities, stupid!
[KIMITO]
Was she raised in a box?
Oh man!
Wait... Does this mean...?
[KIMITO]
No, it's too much.
There's no way she'd
believe that. Is there?
If they can be psychics,
then I can too!
Since Commoners can
develop special powers,
there's no reason
a lady like me can't!
[KIMITO]
Yep, it's official!
This girl has lived
a sheltered life!
[AIKA]
And once I have,
I'll reveal my avatar
to the whole class!
That'll make 'em love me!
[laughs]
[IMAGINARY CLASSMATE 2A] Aika,
you're the most amazing person
of all time!
[IMAGINARY CLASSMATE 2B]
From now on,
Aika should be
at the center of class
so we can worship
her every move!
Aw, shucks.
You mean little ole' me?
All right.
If that's what you want, then
that's the way it's gotta be!
I rule!
[laughing]
And you!
You need to keep
it together, buddy.
Even once I've become the
most popular girl in school,
I'll still talk to you
every once in a while.
You should feel really honored.
[chuckles]
Well... You'd better
start training right away.
First I awaken the
dormant avatar within me
and then I put her
under my spell.
That the main idea?
[KIMITO]
No.
Like this!
[AIKA] But that's different
from the manga.
[KIMITO] Excuse me,
who's the Commoner here?
I think I am.
[AIKA]
Good point.
What's the next part?
Tell me, please!
[KIMITO] Okay, now try doing
everything I showed you
all together.
If you do it perfectly,
you should be able to stop time.
[AIKA] Father time,
hear my command and do as I say.
[AIKA]
Don't tick. Don't tock.
Freeze your ancient cogs.
Right now!
How come nothin'
cool's happening?
Did I just make time stop?
Hey.
Amazing! I did it!
I really, really, did it!
All right!
Stupid little Commoner,
look who's all frozen up!
See? See?
Right.
Now to write "I'm with stupid"
on your face!
[AIKA gasps]
[screams]
Whoa. My cheek.
It feels sore for some reason.
Wow, I wonder why?
[AIKA]
I see what this is.
There must be a limit to
how long I can stop time.
I'll have to test this
out more thoroughly later.
[KIMITO] For real though,
what's with the whole
"I'm with stupid" thing?
Hey, you. Tell me.
How'd you know what I was
gonna write on your forehead?
No. Don't tell me!
Don't tell me!
I totally just tricked you.
And you totally
just fell for it.
[crashing noise]
Dear Kimito...
Hello? Kiryu?
Please grab me a--
[KIMITO]
I shouldn't be here right now.
I know that.
We both do.
But I can't look away.
It's like a car crash only
if car crashes were beautiful.
Like if someone crashed
two muscle cars, or--
Wait, why am I thinking about
muscles at a time like this?
This isn't me! Is it?
No! Kujo's incepted me!
I need to leave.
Ahh! Sorry!
[REIKO]
It's settled then.
I'll just have to
have him take me.
I have no other choice!
[ENGLISH TEACHER 2A]
Everyone,
please open your
textbooks to page 28.
[KIMITO]
Will this be awkward?
Maybe we can just pretend
like nothing happened.
[ENGLISH TEACHER 2A]
Now then. Let's not dillydally.
Let's get to work right away.
This is real dense.
Hard to engage, you know?
Us, engaged?
Oh, no.
It's far too soon for that.
But... Then again,
in my grandmother's day,
dropping out of school and
getting engaged at an early age
was quite commonplace, so...
[KIMITO]
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Thinking out loud is all.
Please do continue.
Waiting for...
Our wedding day?
That seems early.
But all right. My answer's yes.
Never too early to plan.
But in order for the
ceremony to be perfect,
we'll have to start making
our arrangements right away.
Although, considering
how last minute this is,
I fear we'll run out of time
before we really get started.
[KIMITO] Why are you tearing
pages out of your book,
it's for learning.
Wait a sec, is that origami?
Why are you making origami out
of your frickin' textbook?
[REIKO]
"Travel." Yes.
Where should we go
on our honeymoon?
Domestic? Overseas?
[KAE] Reiko! What on earth
has come over you?
[KAREN]
My name is Karen Jinryo!
They're dead weight,
Kimito, we need to ditch them!
"It's wall-to-wall
muscles over here.
Having lots of
fun."
Was it you who undressed me?
How dare you
be so shameless!
Kimito, look out!
[KIMITO]
She sees it... my Eden...