[exhales]
[MOON (ERI)]
Kimito and Hakua,
it seems the chemistry between
you is neither good nor bad.
Because Hakua hardly ever speaks
and is not much of
a communicator,
you two will have to
work extremely hard
even to understand one another.
[door opes]
Miss Hakua. You seem upset,
is everything all right?
Can I get you anything?
[gasps]
Oh my!
Hakua... My Dear. Does this
mean what I think it does?
[exhales]
[MAIDS giggle]
[MORITA]
Really?
[MAID 3B]
So then that means--?
[SAKIMORI] Exactly what
you're thinking, yes!
Miss Hakua wants to know
Mr. Kagurazaka better,
and she wants him to
know her better, too!
The girl is becoming
a young woman at last!
If that's what the lady wants
then we should assist her.
Let's arrange for them to
spend some time together.
Excellent idea!
Yes, but, we musn't
let her realize that
we're infringing on her
personal business.
Agreed. We should be
as discreet as we can.
Under the radar!
You're right! We must find a
way to get the boy over here
in a manner that seems
perfectly innocent and casual.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[AIKA] Hey, Kimito. Have you
heard of a maid café before?
What is that?
[KAREN]
Sounds weird.
[exhales]
Well, you know what
a café is, right?
It's one of those,
but with maids.
Huh? Hold on a second.
When we first met,
you told me that Commoners
don't have any maids.
But when I started reading your
Manga, they were everywhere.
Yeah, that's true.
[AIKA] And they're
super weird, too!
Nothing like normal maids!
[gasps]
[AIKA] Like there was
one about a gun-obsessed,
former-terrorist robot-maid
who's super horny all the time
and has slimy, octopus-like
tentacles growing out of her!
You nasty pervert!
Hey, relax!
The maids from my manga are
supposed to be fantasies!
Commoners don't have maids.
And they wouldn't be
horny robots if we did.
So a maid café
is a fantasy, too?
It is. The maid's in a maid
café aren't like the maids
who work at this school
and make your bed
or do your laundry or whatever.
These maids do role play.
Like they're actually
from a manga.
[ALL] Like they're
actually from a manga?
Since manga girls aren't real,
some guys go to these cafes
to live out their fantasies.
[gasps]
Goodness me.
So scandalous.
[exhales]
[KIMITO]
It's like they say,
"people always want
what they can't have."
Cafe maids are like
an unattainable ideal.
Hence, those guys
being into them.
[HAKUA]
Hm...
[ALL]
Mm...
And Kimito, is that how you
feel about them, as well?
[KIMITO]
I mean... Sorta.
[ALL gasp]
[KIMITO] When I first got here
and found out that everyone
has a maid assigned to
them I was kind of excited.
I mean, these maids
aren't cartoon characters.
They're real,
honest to goodness maids!
Then, Kimito....
Am I to infer from this that
you have a thing for maids?
[KIMITO]
Yeah!
I guess so?
Then for the sake of
our Commoner education,
let us learn all about
these maid cafes!
[KIMITO]
Mm?
Sure. Why not?
[HAKUA]
Uh.
I will acquiesce.
Good! That settles it.
Hey! Stop trying
to be in charge!
For this occasion,
I'll reserve the cafeteria!
[door clatters]
It is our pleasure to
serve you today, master.
[gasps]
I can't do this! I'm nervous!
I've never been a
maidservant before!
Dear!
You all right there?
Uh. Yes. I'm as right as rain!
[REIKO] Um. Will there be
anyone else joining you today?
[KIMITO]
No, just me.
[REIKO] Then allow me to show
you to your table, good sir.
Here is your menu, master.
When you decide what
you'd like to order,
call for me and
I'll be right there.
Thanks. I'll let you know.
So. Do any of you
have questions, or--?
Ooh! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
What?
Why did blondie even
bother with asking you
how many people
are in your party.
I mean she obviously
knows you're by yourself,
it makes no sense!
She's role-playing.
It's kinda the whole
point of the exercise.
Now, now, Kimito.
Clearly Aika has strong opinions
about what we're
doing here today...
[KIMITO]
Hm? I guess she's playing nice.
[REIKO] ..perhaps she
should shut her mouth...
[KIMITO]
No she's not!
Don't get mad at me because
you're the worst
maid of all time!
Back me up you guys,
that was totally awkward, right?
She's wrong.
Shut up!
I thought you did
a magnificent job.
[gasps]
[AIKA grunts]
Well, don't just sit there with
that stupid look on your face!
Show us what to do next!
Do I have your permission
to continue forward, master?
Uh. Sure.
[clears throat]
And now. This is where things
really start to get going.
Because this next part is
where Commoner maids
and the maids you've grown
up with totally part ways.
[ALL]
Hm?
[KIMITO]
For example, if I ordered juice.
The maid would
serve that juice--
With her sweet love!
[ALL]
Eh?
I'm so sorry, Kimito,
but I haven't the faintest
idea to what you're referring.
Why don't you just
demonstrate it?
[KIMITO]
Well, I-I--
Please, if you don't mind,
that would be such a help.
[KIMITO gasps]
We're not gonna understand
until we see it in person.
[KIMITO]
Eh. You'll work it out.
[yelps]
Do it already, or else!
So... The secret
ingredient is this!
[giggles]
A little sugar. And some love!
[KIMITO]
Come on, don't reject my love!
[SAKIMORI] You say
that Mr. Kagurazaka
is interested in maids?
[MAIDS]
Yes.
[SAKIMORI]
Hm...
Got it.
[KIMITO] All right.
Let's pick up from
where you bring me the
rice omelet, shall we?
Here. One rice omelet.
Just let me know if
you need anything else.
And, I will now include
a secret ingredient
to make sure
it tastes good.
So get ready, master. Here goes.
Oh, did you order a rice omelet?
Well...
Here's some love, too--
Ack! I'm sorry, I can't!
It's just so embarrassing,
how could I--
[KIMITO]
Apologize to me
and to maid cafés everywhere
right this minute!
I will draw a bunny
rabbit with this ketchup!
That's oddly good.
[AIKA] Bad Hakua!
Put your clothes back on!
[KAREN grunts]
[KIMITO groans]
[KAREN] Served for your
pleasure with all of my love!
[KIMITO] Karen, I've gotta
be honest with you,
I'm not gonna eat that.
So you're in charge of games.
The secret ingredient,
is a little love.
This. This. Or this.
Paper, rock, or--
--scissors
--[KIMITO] Scissors!
The secret ingredient--
[KIMITO]
Oh, we're playing again?
Okay.
The secret ingredient
is a little love.
This. This. Or this.
Paper, rock, or--
--scissors!
--[KIMITO] Scissors!
The secret ingre--
[KIMITO]
There's no rule that says
you play till the maid wins.
All right then.
That's enough game time for
one day, don't you think?
So, master.
Now that we're past that,
what's next on the agenda?
Well. Let's see. There is
the singing and dancing.
Oh! I love to sing, more than
anything in the world!
Please, allow me!
Thanks, you idiot! Do you have
any idea what you've done?
Huh?
[REIKO]
Master!
I'm grateful for
this opportunity
and I promise I'll do my best!
[AIKA]
No, don't let her!
Please indulge me
in "Ave Maria."
[inhales]
[horrific singing]
[grunts, gasps]
[KIMITO]
Hakua! Look out!
[KIMITO grunts]
[singing continues]
[KAREN grunts]
It's great, but we've
heard enough!
[AIKA]
Please, stop singing!
You sound like a
dying wildebeest!
[singing]
You're a no-talent hack!
Well. How very rude.
People always compliment me
on how gifted I am
at singing opera.
[AIKA] Then they're
sparing your feelings!
They don't have the heart to
tell you that every time you
sing their souls start
to shrivel up and die!
Kimito, what did you think?
Uh. Well, I--
Uh! Hakua!
Just keep arguing, Kimito.
And wherever the blood
trail leads, don't follow it.
[KIMITO]
Stop being so creepy!
Please excuse me!
[gasps]
[KIMITO]
If you don't get off of her,
I'm gonna put you in
time out, you understand?
Oh, dear.
[ALL]
Hm?
Sorry to interrupt,
but I thought you
might need some help.
The rest of the maids and I will
wash these clothes for you.
Why don't you all go back
to your rooms and change?
That's another thing
that's completely different
about actual maids.
Whatever do you mean?
[KIMITO] Cafe maids
do a lot of things,
but cleaning isn't one of them.
[REIKO gasps]
[AIKA]
For real?
[KIMITO]
For real.
[AIKA]
What about laundry?
Or dressing you?
Or seeing you off
in the morning?
[KIMITO]
Yeah, no. None of the above.
[KAREN]
Correct me if I'm wrong here.
They serve you food.
They play silly,
role-playing, love games.
But when it comes to
personal care, they do nothing?
[KIMITO]
Yep.
That's ridiculous.
Can you even call that a maid?
So then. What is
the final verdict,
do you like Commoner
maids or not?
[KIMITO]
I don't dislike them?
[grunts]
[SAKIMORI]
Mr. Kagurazaka.
Huh?
Hey! Thanks again for
everything you did earlier.
My pleasure.
You real-world maids are
something else, that's for sure.
Do you think so?
Oh! I forgot!
If you are agreeable
to the idea,
would you like to come see
us at work sometime soon?
[KIMITO]
Sure. Sounds interesting.
[SAKIMORI giggles]
[SAKIMORI]
Make yourself at home. Please.
[KIMITO]
Thanks for having me.
I know I've been here before,
but now that I'm
seeing it again,
This place really
is massive, isn't it?
[SAKIMORI] It only takes
three dozen maids to clean,
so not really.
Well. Would you like me to give
you quick tour of the facility?
[KIMITO]
Hm? Yeah. Thanks.
This laboratory is where Miss
Hakua does most of her work.
[gasps]
[KIMITO]
Who are they?
Miss Hakua's
personal care staff.
They are responsible
for all aspects
of her day-to-day routine.
Wow.
[sighs]
[KIMITO]
Eh... Should I go?
[SAKIMORI]
Huh?
Kagurazaka's here, everyone!
[MAIDS gasp]
[KIMITO] That was cool! All that
knowledge just pours out of you!
Not cool. It's really amazing!
So, Miss Hakua.
How would you feel about
showing this handsome young
man around the facility?
Uh. But I came here
to watch the maids--
Well, nevermind.
[MAIDS]
Aww!
Pay no attention to them.
Come. We should get going.
[KIMITO]
Kay.
[HAKUA]
This is my sandbox.
I use it to clear my mind.
[KIMITO]
That makes sense.
So then, you designed
this sandcastle?
Wow, it's immaculate.
[KIMITO]
Anything I can do to help?
All right.
[MAIDS giggle]
Hello?
Hello. As it turns out, all of
us are on a ten-minute break.
Even maids need
a little "r and r.'
[MAIDS]
Yes, indeed!
Please pay us no more mind
than a tiny pebble
on the side of a road.
Weird.
[KIMITO]
So, what are we making?
A house. Will you
gather sand too?
[KIMITO]
Sure.
Hm? What's wrong?
[KIMITO] I guess my
hands are pretty big.
[KIMITO] Or maybe yours
are just really small.
[KIMITO laughs]
That won't make 'em any bigger.
[grunts]
[KIMITO]
Don't punch me!
There's nothing wrong
with small hands!
[MAIDS gasp]
Need anything, or...?
Nothing. We're great. Thanks.
Don't stop on our account.
Wait. Don't stop what?
Whatever you were doing.
[KIMITO]
All done!
Awesome house.
Miss Hakua.
It's half past noon, would you
like me to prepare your lunch?
It's that late already?
Well, are you hungry at all yet?
[stomach growls]
That answers that.
You really must
join us, Mr. Kagurazaka.
We'd be oh, so
honored if you did.
[KIMITO]
No, I shouldn't.
[SAKIMORI]
It's really no trouble.
It would be our
privilege to tend to
one of the friends
of our lady. Truly!
[KIMITO] Well, in that case,
I don't mind if I do.
So--?
What timing, it's lunch
for the maids as well.
Pay us no attention!
Think of us as nothing
more than lawn clippings!
[KIMITO]
Uh...
[SAKIMORI]
My apologies.
We're short on plates,
so I'm afraid the two of you
will have no choice
but to share one.
[KIMITO]
What?
We're hopeless romantics,
so we always draw hearts
on the most random
things you can imagine.
It says our names.
Oh, does it?
[KIMITO]
Not to be a bother,
but could I trouble
you for an extra plate?
[SAKIMORI]
What?
I'd like my own plate, please.
As I said, we have an unexpected
shortage at the moment.
Huh? But what
about those plates?
There's a whole
stack right--
[yells]
I'm so sorry. All of those
plates are now broken.
[KIMITO] Oh, come on,
that was clearly deliberate!
The work of a maid is grueling,
taxing and difficult,
to say the least. As such,
sometimes the stress causes
us to make terrible mistakes.
[KIMITO]
Yeah. Right. "Mistakes."
Well, the plate debacle aside.
It is time to eat lunch!
Bon appetite.
[KIMITO sighs]
[MAIDS giggle]
[KIMITO grunts]
[MAIDS chatter]
Is it good?
All right, then.
[MORITA] We're not
even here right now.
Think of us as a
residual thought
from the past, bouncing
through space and time.
[KIMITO]
What kinda sci-fi is this?
'Scuse me. Can I
have a spoon, too?
I wish I could oblige you.
But as fate would have it,
we're short on spoons, so please
continue indirectly kissing.
[KIMITO]
Uh...
Oops. Did I say kissing?
I didn't mean kissing.
I meant kiss-met-ting!
[KIMITO] Hey, look! I think I
solved your spoon problem.
Can I have one pl--
[yells]
[KIMITO groans]
Poor thing. She fears silver.
Like a werewolf, she spooks
even at the mention of it.
Morita, you must be exhausted.
[KIMITO]
Sounds psychosomatic.
She should see
someone about that.
[sighs]
[HAKUA]
Kimito?
Huh? Guess I'd better
try it at least. Thanks.
All right.
That's tasty.
[thudding]
Come on. Wake up!
Things are finally
starting to get exciting!
[KIMITO groans]
Thought you might like
something to drink.
[KIMITO]
Oh! Thank you very mu-- Ah...
I'm so sorry, but this
is our only cup you see.
[KIMITO]
Now, I know that can't be true!
[SAKIMORI] And that is the
only straw we have in stock.
[KIMITO] Why the heck would
anyone have a goofy thing
like that in the first place?
Look right there!
She's throwing out
a whole box of 'em!
My apologies,
but those straws are
defective and of no use to us.
[KIMITO] Okay, one or
two being defective, I buy,
but that many?
I mean, how bad could straw
makers suck at their jobs?
Well? Are you going
to drink or not?
[grunts]
[KIMITO]
I have to.
If I don't drink it,
this will never end.
[MAIDS grunt]
[MAIDS scream]
Seeing you two dining.
It's almost like watching two
lovebirds on a first date.
What? No it's not.
[KIMITO]
I just don't see her like that.
I mean, we're close, yeah.
And I like spending
time with her.
But it's nowhere near romantic.
[KIMITO]
If anything,
it's like I'm looking at
the little sis I never had.
[HAKUA gasps]
[KIMITO]
Uh? What's wrong?
[MAIDS gasp]
[SAKIMORI]
Head Maid!
[ALL grunt]
[KIMITO gasps] I didn't realize
she was that important!
[KUJO]
Sakimori.
Yes, ma'am!
An urgent verification
request from a company
has just now arrived.
There was no
response in the lab,
so the inquiry was
forwarded to me instead.
[MAIDS murmur]
I suppose we should
take off too.
What?
[KIMITO] I uh, hope I
didn't overstay my welcome.
And I hope I didn't get
you in trouble with Kujo.
She looked pretty pissed.
I wouldn't worry about
that if I were you.
So did you learn anything today?
Do you have a better
understanding of how things are?
Uh... If I'm being honest,
I don't know any more about
maids than I did
when I showed up.
I was referring to Miss Hakua.
[KIMITO]
Oh! Yeah!
I did get to see a side of
her life that I hadn't before,
so that was pretty cool.
[sighs]
[SAKIMORI] Please feel
free to come back anytime!
[KIMITO]
Thanks, I will!
[MAIDS]
Yahoo!
Cheers!
Congratulations girls,
today was a massive success!
Though, it was quite surprising
when the head maid came around.
Speaking of which,
did you know it was her
who chose Mr. Kagurazaka
to be Seikain's Shomin Sample?
Yes, I did. I hear
the powers that be
were all set to pick
another candidate.
But then the head
maid put a word in
and they went with Kimito.
That's unusual. I wonder what
inspired that suggestion.
It's obvious. The young
commoner has a fine reputation.
[MAID 3B]
Well, in at any rate,
we owe the head maid our thanks
for bringing Mr. Kagurazaka
into the fold!
Here's to many successes
from this day on!
And to the Seikain maids!
[MAIDS]
Here, here!
[gasps]
Oh! You want
your dinner, master?
Well. Here it is then.
With a little love!
[KAREN] Oh! So you're
in charge of games?
[HAKUA, KAREN] The secret
ingredient is a little love.
This. This. Or this.
Paper, rock, or...
scissors!
[gasps]
Oh! You wanna order
somethin' to drink, huh?
Well. Here it is, then.
Served. With a little love.
[AIKA groans]
So embarrassing!
[KUJO]
What are your intentions?
[KIMITO]
Guys are better, you know.
[ALL] We love muscles!
We love muscles!
You got me mad now!
Yakiniku seasoning.
I love muscles!
Dandy Aika? I like
the sound of that!