[PRESIDENT] I'm thrilled
to say that construction
on the new site
is finally complete!
So first thing tomorrow,
our students will be
taking a field trip!
Sounds like fun.
Where exactly are we going?
We have erected
a new theme park
in order to allow the ladies
to further experience
the particulars
of Commoner culture.
It's called... Shominland.
[KIMITO]
Are you for real?
That's where you come in,
Mr. Kagurazaka!
While at Shominland,
we want you to
offer the students
all the guidance
and advice you can.
[KIMITO]
You sure that's a good idea?
Ever since you
joined us here,
the atmosphere at school
has been much more cheerful.
Some of us were
worried your presence
might have a negative
influence on our students,
but it turns out
they were wrong.
Most boys have a tendency
to try and get girls riled up,
but not you.
Well... I'm glad I could help?
Then again, most boys aren't
Macho-man-loving perverts,
are they?
I'm not a
macho-man-loving pervert!
[KUJO]
You'd better be one.
Because if you're not,
and you're here posing
as a sexual deviant,
then for the sake of the ladies,
I'll have to clip
your genitalia!
My dream is to live
life wedged between
two oiled glutes!
[KUJO]
In any case...
The opportunity has now come
for you to put your
Commoner know-how
to its greatest purpose yet.
You must demonstrate your
abilities and knowledge
to their fullest extent.
This is, perhaps,
the most significant moment
in your entire life to date.
[KIMITO]
No pressure though, right?
[REIKO] I am very
anxious and excited.
I cannot wait to see this
Shominland firsthand!
Yeah. Me too.
"One teriyaki burger
meal upsized.
With a large cola
to drink, please."
The wait is over!
It would appear they
are letting people inside!
[MAYA]
Shall we go then?
[REIKO]
Yes!
Time to rock, Aika. You ready?
Yeah...
[KIMITO] This is the opportunity
you've been waiting for!
The reason for everything you've
done in the Commoner Club.
This is your moment!
[AIKA whimpering]
[KIMITO] Just do like we
practiced, and you'll be fine.
Sound off!
[AIKA] I will exchange
phone numbers!
[KIMITO]
You got this!
[AIKA]
Of course I do!
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Welcome to Shominland, ladies!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] This is a
one-of-a-kind theme park
designed to give you the
complete Commoner experience
in all its raw glory!
You're about to venture
into a foreign land
not of your own, so be safe
and have a good time out there!
[STUDENTS clapping]
[KIMITO]
Seriously?
[STUDENTS cheering]
[KIMITO] They ride up
on a fancy space elevator
and no one bats an eye.
Now they sound like
they're at a frickin' rave.
This place must be awesome.
Or not at all.
I bid you welcome
to Shominland:
A park modeled after
an average city block
in front of a train station.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Keep it together!
Don't quit on me!
We made it this far,
we can't give up now.
Muster what courage you have!
[STUDENT 4A laughs]
A traffic signal!
[STUDENT 6A]
Look, it's a crosswalk!
[STUDENT 6B]
I've read about these,
but I've never seen one before!
[STUDENT 6C]
Let us cross it!
[STUDENT 4A]
We must look both ways first.
[STUDENT 6C]
Oh! Yes, of course!
[STUDENTS chattering]
So, ya having a good time?
[AIKA]
Um...
[KIMITO yells]
The heck was that for?!
It is custom to pass out
tissues at train stations.
[KIMITO] That's typically
done one at a time!
[KUJO]
They are silky-soft.
The best tissues money can buy.
They include a moisturizer to
prevent irritation of the skin.
No matter how many you use,
they shall bring you
naught but comfort.
[KIMITO]
Hello?!
Now...
Allow me to direct you to
our first attraction, ladies.
[KUJO] This is, by far,
the most popular restaurant
amongst the Commoner populace.
[CLERKS]
How can I help you today?
[STUDENTS]
Ahh!
At this restaurant.
Before eating, you must
first place your order
at that counter.
[REIKO]
My word! Are you in earnest?
[KUJO] There are detailed
menus on the countertops.
Look them over thoroughly and
give your order to the clerk.
This is certainly unusual.
But after we complete our order,
then we may sit at a table?
No. You must first
wait to collect your food.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Oh my...
Let me make sure I understand.
We order... Then we stand there?
[KUJO]
Yes.
Food preparation can
take quite a long time.
We might be standing
there waiting for our meal
for hours and hours on end.
Wait. Why must this be?
That's the way it is.
Here, customers must carry
their own food to the table.
It's commoner custom.
[ALL gulp]
Behold! This is self-service.
[STUDENTS gasp]
How truly incredible this is!
They're so independent!
Indeed.
It appears we have quite
a bit to learn from them!
It makes me painfully aware
of the immense privilege
I was afforded in my childhood.
[STUDENTS] You commoners
are even more amazing
than I thought!
[KIMITO]
Uh...
I am ready to proceed.
Even if I must wait several
hours, I shall endure it.
Same here!
I will wait as long
as is required!
[KUJO]
Ladies.
I appreciate your patience, but
the wait won't be long at all.
This restaurant serves what
Commoner's call "fast food."
Expediency is the general idea.
Your meal will be
ready for consumption
within one minute of
your order's placement.
[STUDENTS]
Oh! My word!
My word!
[KIMITO]
They said that twice.
[STUDENT 6D]
I don't understand.
How do they prepare
it so quickly?
[STUDENT 6E]
It defies logic. It's insane.
[STUDENT 6F]
These Commoners.
Who are they, exactly?
[STUDENT 6G]
Well, they're...
They're Commoners, aren't they?
[STUDENT 6F]
They are indeed!
Now proceed to the counter
and place your orders.
Hey! This is it!
I've already taught you
how to order.
[KIMITO]
Teriyaki burger combo upsized
with a large cola to drink.
'Kay? Sound off!
Right. Teriyaki burger combo.
Large cola... upsized?
One more time!
[AIKA]
Teriyaki burger combo!
This is the moment
you've been waiting for,
so seize it.
Walk right up to
that counter and speak!
"Teriyaki burger combo.
Upsized with a large cola
to drink!" Right now!
[AIKA sighs]
[KIMITO]
What are you so worried about?
Go on!
[AIKA whimpering]
[KIMITO] Something tells me
this isn't gonna end well.
Umm...
I'd like to place my
order first, please.
[KAE]
Reiko is so amazingly brave!
[MAYA]
Good luck up there!
Good afternoon to you.
Will your order be
for here or to go?
[REIKO]
Not here.
If it's all right with you,
I would prefer to eat
over at the tables.
Please allow me
to clarify, Miss Reiko.
She is asking whether
you'll be eating
in the dining space here,
or whether you'd like
your meal wrapped up
so you may take it home.
Oh. I see.
I could bring it home for
a tea party, couldn't I?
[STUDENT 6H] Yes, it would
be like having a picnic,
but indoors!
[STUDENT 6I]
That would be lovely!
[CLERK 6B]
What would you like to order?
[REIKO gasps]
[KIMITO]
Ah, menu paralysis.
My old nemesis.
My friends and I
could never decide
what we wanted
to get here either.
And this place was
practically our home.
[REIKO]
Uh... Uh...
[KAE]
Reiko! Be strong!
This is your chance.
Quick, while she's
making up her mind!
[KIMITO]
It's hopeless.
The teriyaki burger meal.
It's the most popular
combo by far.
Oh, thank you.
You could quadruple size it,
but that's a lot of food to eat.
I'd just stick with
the standard upsize.
Right.
I would like to order one
teriyaki burger combo
upsized, please.
That'll be right up, Ma'am.
Your meal comes with a drink.
What would you like?
If I were you, I'd try
the new blended tea.
[REIKO] Wonderful,
I'll have the tea, then.
Thank you very much, Ma'am.
Please stand over there to the
side 'til your order is ready.
I do so appreciate
your assistance, Kimito.
[MAYA] He is a gentleman,
through and through.
[KAE]
Always there to lend a hand.
Can I have that?
[CLERK 6B] So, you'd like
a kids' meal then?
No. I don't need the meal.
I, uh... I just want the toy.
Oh yeah. Thank you.
[STUDENT 6Y]
This place really is amazing!
[MAYA]
Oh, my!
[STUDENT 6J]
I enjoy just looking at it.
All right. Let us eat.
[KIMITO] Wait a sec,
where did Aika go?
[KIMITO]
It's... incredible!
Never in this life has
my tongue been graced
with such sweet juices.
And how they squirt forth from
the moment my teeth
pierce the bun.
A bun baked with wheat
straight from the
fields of Elysium!
If ever I thought I loved
burgers before this moment,
then I was a fool.
No--A prisoner.
Chained in Plato's cave,
feeding on shadows,
woefully ignorant of
the true form of meat!
But I'm ascending now.
I taste veggies.
Lettuce crisper than a
bank of sunkissed snow.
The sharp, sweet tang
of artisanal pickles.
The savory damp of blood-red
tomato sinking into beef.
All hail the triumvirate
of veggie, bun and flesh!
All in proportion!
All in harmony!
You were wrong, Pythagoras.
You should've eaten meat!
Muscles are delicious!
In my mouth, I mean--No, damnit!
No, this isn't right!
[STUDENT 6K]
Umm, are you okay?
[STUDENT 6L]
Is something the matter?
[KIMITO] This burger is too good
and I won't stand for it!
If they think I'm gonna sit here
and let them sell a perfectly
crafted burger like this
at a fast food restaurant,
they're wrong!
Fast food burgers are
supposed to taste like crap!
That's a general rule of thumb!
And not only that, they're
supposed to be dirt-cheap!
You could charge
millions for this!
[KIMITO growls]
I won't let you make
a mockery of fast food!
So whoever made this--
Meet me outside.
[STUDENT 6M] Oh dear,
Kimito seems really upset.
I don't understand why,
but you're right,
he appears extremely enraged.
[SAKIMORI]
Hakua!
What are you doing?
Are you going to visit Kimito?
Oh, dear. He's out.
Kimito and the other students
took a trip to Shominland,
Seikain's new
Commoner theme park.
Kimito...
I just want to say how happy
I am that you're with us.
And on such a
monumental occasion!
I'm glad to be here.
Oh!
It appears they have many
plushies just over there, Reiko.
Shall we go play?
Sure!
I'll go with you, as well!
[game noises]
I did it, everyone!
[KIMITO]
Yup. That's Reiko.
[game music playing]
[KIMITO] Aika's really good
at the dancing game.
I was hoping she
would get to show it.
But most of these girls are
stuck at the claw machine.
Those plushies
are just too cute.
[KAREN grunting]
[KIMITO] They'll probably
come over here in a while.
We just have to be patient.
[TWIN 6A]
Excuse me!
Sorry to interrupt,
but if you're not busy,
would you mind showing
my sister and me
how to play the plushy game?
We're clueless,
we could use some help!
[KIMITO]
Well, uh...
[AIKA] Don't worry
about me, I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
I'm gonna go
buy somethin' to drink.
[KIMITO] I'm aiming for this one
right here, so watch close.
[KIMITO]
Here you go.
You would give this to me?
[KIMITO]
Of course.
Thanks so much, Kimito!
I will treasure this
for the rest of my life!
[TWINS laugh]
Hey. Do you wanna try it too?
I do.
Well... Here goes.
I hope it works.
[KIMITO]
That's perfect.
Now let go of the button!
Ooh... ah, ah!
Wh-What do I do now?
You're okay.
If I were you,
I'd aim for that blue one.
I think you can snag it.
[STUDENT 4I]
Oh...
[KIMITO]
Good luck.
[STUDENT 4I]
Right. Thanks!
Oh, Kimito!
[KIMITO]
Oh, yeah. That's it.
Almost there, just
a little bit deeper.
[STUDENT 4I]
Oh... oh!
[KIMITO]
How's that?
[STUDENT 4I]
Great! No, perfect.
Big and so strong.
What a wonderful feeling.
Here comes your prize.
No! Not yet!
Sorry, but I have to pull out.
No, please! I want more!
So much more!
[screaming]
[KIMITO]
Look! You got it!
[STUDENT 4I]
I enjoyed that very much.
Whelp, I'd better take off...
[gasps]
[STUDENT 6O]
Kimito!
Would you show me how
to do that, as well, please?
[overlapping chatter]
What do you say?
Please instruct us!
We'll be forever in your debt.
You got one
earlier easily enough.
[KIMITO]
That's weird.
Where did Aika run off to?
What is this?
Is it some kind of stage?
Oh. It's just a game
where you dance to music.
Want me to show you?
[STUDENTS]
Yes, please!
[game music plays]
[KIMITO]
See? Like this.
[STUDENTS]
Ooh!
[KIMITO]
It's pretty fun.
Well, do any of you
wanna give it a try?
[STUDENT 6R]
Yes!
Oh...
I wouldn't take off my shoes,
that's kinda gross.
Look, I think I won!
You were wonderful!
Slow down.
You have to beat 'em all to win!
[STUDENTS]
You can't be serious?
I am so sorry about that!
This game is far too hard.
Perhaps it's best we give up.
Commoner pastimes
could be too difficult
for us to achieve success.
[AIKA]
Are you kidding?
Just watch me!
See? Concentrate. It's easy!
[music continues]
[AIKA]
Ready? Go!
Up! Down! Up! Down!
Keep both feet
together as best you can!
The next part is hard,
so stay loose, kay?
[STUDENT 6R]
Uh... Right!
[AIKA]
And jump!
We're almost to the end!
Just keep your
movements nice and tight!
All right,
I'll do my best!
--[AIKA] Yeah!
--[STUDENTS cheering]
[AIKA]
We rocked!
I mean... Good job.
Thank you very much, Aika.
I'm impressed.
I had no idea you were
an expert at this game!
Well... Guess I am!
Aika!
I really hope you'll teach me
how to play it, too!
[STUDENT 6E]
Oh yes! Same here! Teach me!
[overlapping chatter]
Sure. I'd be glad to!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[AIKA] The most important thing
you need is a sense of rhythm.
[KIMITO]
You really did it.
[AIKA] You just have to practice
your moves and do your best!
[KAREN cooing, laughing]
[AIKA] I'd like to order an
extra grande hazelnut vanilla
almond Foamuccino,
heavy on the caramel,
heavy on the whipped
cocoa rhumba cream
with an extra shot
to top it off, please!
Wow! What an incredibly
artful order, Aika!
Seeing her imbued
with such confidence
in a drink order
is quite reassuring.
[AIKA laughs]
I do what I can!
Tell me this much, Aika.
When Commoners order a coffee,
do they all speak such
a complicated, strange,
and confusing language?
It is quite overwhelming.
Do you think we'll be able
to master this technique?
I wouldn't worry about it!
That was totally an
advanced-level order.
Just start off by asking for
a latte, iced or hot is fine.
Well, Reiko, is anything
on the menu catching your eye?
[STUDENT 6V] I am very curious
about these Foamuccinos.
[STUDENT 6Q]
What exactly is a Foamuccino?
[KAE]
Is everything all right?
[STUDENT 4A]
Yes, Aika, do tell us, please.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 4H] What is this
little hole in the top for?
Oh. Yes.
You must enlighten us,
what does the hole do?
Uh... Well...
I think I know.
Is the hole from
where one drinks?
That's right! Here, watch me.
I'll show you how
the Commoners do it.
[AIKA screaming]
[AIKA whimpering]
Are you all right?
Do we need
to fetch a physician?
Perhaps this will
help you cool down!
[AIKA]
Sorry about that!
These are real hot.
Slipped my mind.
Come back!
[DOG barks]
Yeah. That Classic Lit
test was a total disaster.
[STUDENT 4H] I'll say,
it was a difficult one indeed.
[KIMITO]
So tell me...
Are you two using
your cellphones?
Yes. Sometimes.
Not often though,
because we see each other
every day at school.
In reality,
there isn't much need.
True.
So you don't even send
each other messages in class?
[STUDENT 4H]
Oh, good gracious no.
We have to conceal
our phones at school
for fear of being reprimanded.
[STUDENT 6Q] We text
quite a bit in our rooms
before bedtime, though.
What about you?
Huh?
Obviously, I don't
have anyone to text.
In that case,
you should text with me!
Yes! For sure.
The three of us
should group text!
We should?
[AIKA]
Sure!
--[STUDENTS chattering]
--[AIKA laughing]
[STUDENT 6V] Would it be all
right if I texted you, too?
[AIKA]
Of course!
[laughter continues]
[SAKIMORI]
What are you doing, Hakua?
Are you all right?
Don't get too cocky.
[KAREN gasps]
It's the ultimate humiliation!
Kimito's lips are soft,
and feel really great!
[REIKO]
Yes, it is better.
I despise you, Kimito!
Guess this is the end
of the Commoner Club.
It sure is fun
having lots of friends!