[SAKIMORI] I am taking you
to the lab of Hakua Shiodome.
From today forward,
she's in your charge.
Yes. Right.
Taking care of Miss Hakua
carries with it
special rules and obligations
that are separate
from the needs of the other
ladies at this school,
so please familiarize
yourself with them at once.
To what rules and obligations
do you refer, ma'am?
She cannot dress
herself on her own,
and therefore
requires assistance.
[SAKIMORI]
That task will fall to you.
Yes of course.
Her diet is very strict,
and she must be fed from
a rigid, preset menu.
Other than those specific meals,
she will not eat
anything at all.
Understood?
I will do my best.
Now then.
It's time for you
to meet Miss Hakua.
With all my being,
I wish you'd never woken up.
How are you adjusting?
Have you grown accustomed
to life at Seikain yet?
No way.
I don't know if I'll
ever feel settled here.
[phone ringing]
[KIMITO]
"Hot spring woo-hoo"?
What does that mean?
Oh dear, was that
not explained to you?
You see, as a way
of thanking you
for agreeing to be
our Shomin Sample,
we have dramatically renovated
your childhood home.
Your bathroom has been
made into a natural hot spring.
Needless to say, your family
members are quite ecstatic.
[KIMITO] They sold me out
for a natural hot spring?!
In any case,
to ensure your family isn't
worried about you,
you should send them a text
telling them how much you
enjoy your new home.
"It's wall-to-wall
muscles over here.
Having lots of fun."
[KIMITO yells]
If I come out
to my family,
it'll be on my own terms!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[ENGLISH TEACHER 2A]
Mr. Kagurazaka.
Would you do the honors, please?
Uh... Okay.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 3A]
Ladies! There he is!
[STUDENT 3B]
Look!
He's resting his hand
on the doorknob!
[KIMITO] Come on, can't I
use the bathroom in peace?
[KIMITO]
Huh?
[KIMITO] Is that girl
a student here?
What is she doing,
writing graffiti?
[KIMITO] I can't just let her
deface school property.
[KIMITO yelps]
[KIMITO screeches]
[KIMITO]
Nope, nope, nope!
You're not doin' that!
[KIMITO] Please keep
your clothes on.
You're gonna catch a cold.
[STUDENT 3C]
Yes, that's correct.
I read primarily Heine, Rilke,
and Verlaine from the list.
[STUDENT 3D] My, you are
quite the avid reader!
[KIMITO]
Perfect...
That sure was a close one.
If they'd seen us like that...
Well, they would've
taken it the wrong way.
So could you
get dressed already?
Or, uh...
They're all gone.
[KIMITO]
Wait... Who is?
Was it you
who undressed me?
[KIMITO]
Nope! You did that yourself!
[HAKUA]
That sounds unlikely.
What would I need
to get undressed for?
[KIMITO]
How am I supposed to know?
Look, just do me a favor
and put your
clothes on, okay?
[HAKUA] Sorry, but I can't
comply with that request.
Why not?
[HAKUA]
I'm unable to dress myself.
[KIMITO gasps]
You're kidding, right?
[HAKUA sneezes]
[KIMITO] You can't do
the buttons, either, eh?
[KIMITO] Man. This is harder
than I thought it would be.
There. All done.
By the way,
I'm Hakua Shiodome.
Cool. My name's
Kimito Kagurazaka.
[HAKUA]
Kimito?
You probably saw me
at the orientation meeting?
I missed it.
I was in my lab all day.
[KIMITO]
Your lab?
[stomach growling]
That sound alerts me when
I have low blood sugar levels.
[KIMITO] In that case we should
get you something to eat.
[stomach growling]
I know what to do.
What food is this?
[KIMITO] Instant ramen.
Classic meal of the Commoner.
[KIMITO] But it's not
just instant ramen.
It's my original recipe.
"Chilled Chili-oil Delight."
You're gonna love it, trust me!
But I can't.
[KIMITO]
Uh... Bet you can.
C'mon, just try it.
It's awesome.
[KIMITO]
Just a bite?
It's really good.
[KIMITO]
What do you know?
You can eat by yourself.
[KIMITO]
Well?
[HAKUA]
It's edible.
[KIMITO] Well, it's time we got
you back to your own dorm.
How about I walk you there?
Okay no, I cannot have
her sleeping in my room.
Hey, wake up--
[KIMITO groans]
[KIMITO] Ow! Don't stand up
so suddenly, okay?
[KIMITO]
Not again!
[KIMITO] No! Do not get
naked in my room!
[AIKA]
I'm here, Commoner!
Now for today's lesson,
you and I will--
So, uh...
I know this looks bad,
but please listen!
Believe it or not, I was trying
to keep her clothes on her!
I'm a good person, Aika!
--[AIKA] Pervert!
--[KIMITO screaming]
[KIMITO]
Listen...
You should really learn how
to dress yourself, okay?
[KIMITO] You said it's
this way, right?
Come on.
[HAKUA]
You're coming home with me?
[KIMITO]
I'm just walking you there.
[HAKUA]
'Kay.
There it is.
[SAKIMORI]
I see.
So you escorted Miss Hakua
all the way here, did you?
I owe you my sincere thanks.
Now then...
[KIMITO]
Huh? A digital camera?
[SAKIMORI]
Yes.
It's extremely important
that we record everything
that Miss Hakua writes down.
As such, we must take a
picture of that courtyard.
What are you talking about?
[SAKIMORI]
You don't know?
Miss Hakua
participates globally
in the science and
technology industries,
as well as other
extremely important fields
of academic study.
Even now, prominent businessmen
from around the world
await her conclusions and
theories with baited breath.
Wow!
She's a true genius.
In fact, this complex
was erected using funds
earned from her
innovative patents
and cutting edge technologies.
Now, Miss,
let's make sure we
get you something to eat.
[KIMITO] Oh. There's no need for
that, she just ate at my place.
[SAKIMORI gasps]
[KIMITO]
Should she not have?
No...
Hakua, is this really true?
Have you eaten?
Did I do something wrong?
[SAKIMORI]
No, no!
But tell me,
what did you feed her?
[KIMITO] Instant ramen.
I made it myself.
It's a pretty good recipe.
[SAKIMORI]
Ramen?
[KIMITO]
Ramen.
[SAKIMORI]
Well... Thank you.
You sir, are far too kind!
Gotta go. Bye!
[KIMITO]
What's wrong?
Please don't leave.
[KIMITO]
Are you all right?
Me? Yes!
[KIMITO]
But why?
'Cause I'll miss you.
[KIMITO]
You sure you're all right?
[SAKIMORI]
Oh, perfect!
Please don't let me
get in the way
of your private conversation!
[KIMITO] Come over and
visit me sometime. Yeah?
[HAKUA]
Okay.
[KIMITO]
Cool. Bye.
[HAKUA]
I'll visit soon.
[MAID 3A]
Are you in earnest, Madam?
[SAKIMORI] At first, I honestly
thought that it was all a dream!
I couldn't believe
what I was hearing!
[SAKIMORI] Little Hakua, who
won't put on her own panties!
The girl one who has
absolutely no interests
outside of reading
books about science!
She grabbed onto his
shirtsleeve and then she said,
"Please don't leave me." Wow!
[MAIDS]
"Wow" is right!
[HAKUA sneezes]
[SAKIMORI] It was amazing!
I was stunned.
And that's not the
only surprise, ladies.
Guess what she told me?
[SAKIMORI]
She said she already ate!
[MAIDS]
Huh?!
But that's impossible.
I thought Miss Hakua
wouldn't eat anything
that wasn't on her pre-set menu.
Today is Wednesday, so it's
scallops au gratin day,
is it not?
This is truly a
remarkable occasion!
Get this. She ate
the Commoner's ramen!
[MAID 3B] Has she ever
deviated from the plan before?
[SAKIMORI]
No. Not even once!
[MAID 3B] Do you think it's
possible she has a crush
on the young man?
[MAID 3C] Doubtful.
It's Hakua we're talking about.
[MAID 3B] But she is a girl,
and appearances aside,
she is fourteen.
It's only natural.
[SAKIMORI giggles]
It appears we won't
be able to take our eyes
off the young miss anymore,
will we, ladies?
[REIKO]
Kimito.
Are you feeling prepared
for the botany test today?
I'm not exactly
an expert flower-arranger.
There's no reason
to fret, you'll be just fine.
Besides, if you require
any assistance,
I'd be happy to give it.
You can ask me for help
anytime you so desire.
[KIMITO] Thanks,
I'll take you up on that.
[REIKO]
Now and forever.
[KIMITO]
Uh...
[REIKO]
Oh!
[STUDENTS chattering]
What's up?
[KIMITO] Why is that girl
wearing a katana?
[KAREN shrieks]
Die, you filthy insect!
Stay still so I can kill you!
[KAREN]
Die! Die! Die!
[KIMITO yells]
[STUDENTS yell]
[KAREN crying]
I loathe bugs with a passion.
[KAREN gasps]
I simply can't believe
she had the boldness
to insult and
attack the Commoner!
No doubt about it,
Karen is a formidable lady!
She's not formidable.
She's just a nut job!
[KAREN]
Silence!
You worthless bug!
I'll slay you here and now!
[KIMITO]
Talk about crazy eyes!
[KAREN]
Shut up, you pond scum!
[KIMITO] Which is it,
am I a bug or pond scum?
[KAREN]
Don't correct me!
[KIMITO] Who the heck
are you anyway, lady?
My name is Karen Jinryo!
And I'm the lady who's going
to smite you with my blade.
Time for you to die!
Kimito, look out!
I'd run away!
[KIMITO yelling]
Prepare yourself, Commoner.
Today you breathe
your last breath--
Karen style sword art!
Resolution!
[KIMITO yelling]
Who said you
could avoid my attack?
Like I need permission!
[KIMITO yelling]
You're a nimble
little pond scum.
No. Bug!
[KIMITO] Still haven't made up
your mind about that?
You shut your mouth!
I know what to do with you.
[KAREN]
Karen style sword art.
Whirlwind Number Fifty-Eight:
Abundance!
[STUDENTS screaming]
Don't look at us,
you pervy Commoner!
[REIKO]
Oh my goodness.
Kimito's seen my
immodesty yet again,
how will I ever live
with such shame?
[KIMITO] How did she
make that happen?
This is nuts!
[KAREN]
You disgraceful man!
How dare you
be so shameless?
[KIMITO]
That was you, not me!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[KIMITO screams]
You bug!
You miserable, obscene bug!
No, please! Don't kill me!
I'm too young!
Damn it.
I have to fight back.
What choice do I have?
[KAREN]
I'll finish you!
[KIMITO]
Here goes nothing!
[KIMITO, KAREN yelling]
[KIMITO]
She sees it...
My Eden...
[KIMITO]
Hey. Are you all right?
Tell me.
How well do you
measure up compared
to other Commoner boys?
[KIMITO]
Hmm?
Answer me!
[KIMITO]
Uh...
Yeah, I'm one of
the weaker ones.
[KAREN]
Weak? No!
So the "Karen style"
I devised is futile
against the weakest
of the Commoner men?
[KIMITO]
You're self-taught?
That's amazing!
And by the way, I didn't say
I was the weakest one.
I cannot accept this!
I demand a rematch!
[KIMITO]
Again?
I must cut you down
and restore my sullied name!
[KIMITO]
No! Wait!
Die!
[KAREN]
Whoa... But how?
I didn't even see you attack me.
Uh, actually, I'm
pretty sure that wasn't me.
I think you did
that to yourself.
[KAREN]
And you're the weakest?
Unbelievable.
What savage people
you Commoners are.
I'm scared.
[KIMITO] I told you already,
I didn't do it.
You're the one who's been
slicing people's clothes off!
[KAREN]
So I did this?
How can that be?
[KIMITO]
I don't know.
[KAREN]
Wow...
[KIMITO]
You understand now?
[KAREN]
It's hopeless!
I am not worthy!
[KIMITO]
No, no, you are!
[KAREN]
All right.
As you've beat me
on the field of battle,
you are now my lord and master.
[KIMITO] I think you might
need professional help.
But always remember.
The moment you seem weaker
than me, I'll strike!
I'll kill you
on the spot, Bug!
[KIMITO] I've already got one
hell of a maid,
I don't need two!
[KAREN]
However, until then,
you may use me as you see fit.
[STUDENT 3H] I heard he
beat Karen into submission
and forced her
to become his servant!
[STUDENT 3I]
Commoners truly are incredible!
And savage, too!
[AIKA]
Look!
What's that?
My master plan
to become the most popular
and beloved girl
in all of Seikain!
I may not be very likeable,
and I'm certainly not very good
at inviting people to stuff,
but with this foolproof plan,
there's no way I can fail!
[AIKA laughs]
What's the matter?
You don't seem
too stoked about it.
No, I'm fine.
Right. So...
Anyway, what you do you
think of my awesome plan?
I don't think it's
a bad idea, really.
But it's tough to pull off.
I mean, first of all,
you're gonna need
a few dozen cell phones.
I think mine's
the only one of campus.
Well I was thinking you
could help me out with that!
Easier said than done.
If only there was somebody
at Seikain Girl's School
with a knack for science.
It could work.
[KIMITO]
Cool. So, Hakua,
have you done any work
with cell phones before?
Awesome!
And you definitely have a
bunch of samples in your lab?
It's settled then.
Lucky you.
[AIKA]
That's great and everything,
but why are you
sitting like that?!
She wouldn't budge when I asked.
Why don't you try?
You there! Remove your rump!
Despite her looks,
that girl's the same age as us.
Don't let her fool you!
Send her packing!
She's our age?
There's no way that's true.
Fine. I'll do it myself.
Hakua? Let's go sit
on a cushion, okay?
[AIKA groans]
What are you getting
so worked up about?
I am not getting worked up!
Pardon me.
[KIMITO]
What do you want?
As I said before--Kimito!
You. This girl.
What's going on here?
[KAREN]
You pointless thing.
So pointless. So very pointless.
Pointless, pointless, pointless.
[KIMITO]
So why are you here exactly?
[KAREN]
As I said before, Master.
I now belong to you.
So I'll be here
for your every need.
And I'll stay by your side.
Always.
Till I grow strong enough
to strike you down at last.
Then you die.
[KIMITO]
Yep. You're totally nuts.
But in a charming way!
Now that you've thrust
that nasty, indecent thing
in my face,
I have to kill you!
[KIMITO]
I didn't thrust anything!
Ahem! 'Scuse me!
You're still here?
I've been here
this whole time!
It's like you want me to
punch you in your stupid face!
You really might
want to see someone
about that anger
problem of yours.
I don't have
an anger problem!
Look at the clock.
Isn't it club time?
[KIMITO]
Yeah.
Well, in that case.
They're dead weight, Kimito.
We need to ditch 'em.
The more the merrier, right?
[AIKA]
Wrong!
I don't get it,
what's the matter with you?
Oh, I don't know,
maybe it's the way
you just sit there--
[AIKA screams]
Perfect!
What's that?
[AIKA]
Her maid dropped this off!
What, is she moving in?
I had these
brought here for you.
Awesome job.
At present,
they're unable to connect
to cellular services.
Should I fix it so they can?
Please.
Actually, we want to
make it so these cells
can only connect
with each other.
Okay.
Aika, do you wanna pick first?
Huh? Uh, yeah. Sure.
[AIKA] Hey. Thank you for
helping us out, I guess.
Would you like one?
[KAREN]
Hmph.
I am not interested in
your infantile trinkets.
Suit yourself.
[AIKA] Kimito!
Take a picture of me!
[KIMITO]
All right. Here goes!
[camera snaps]
[AIKA]
Ooh! Check me out!
Wow!
I'm so adorable I wanna
squeeze my own head off!
Do you wanna
take a picture, too?
I would like to
take one with you, yes.
[AIKA] Then I want to
take one too, Kimito!
[KIMITO] There's not room
for all three of us!
[AIKA]
Of course there is!
Hey. No tugging.
You're way too close.
Stop making this weird!
You're the one
invading my space!
[AIKA]
Tell that to Hakua, hypocrite!
[KIMITO]
Uh, hey, Hakua.
Why are you sitting
on my lap again?
Considering circumstances,
this position's needed.
There's no way we'll
all fit in this frame.
Hey, I know!
Karen can ta--
[KAREN]
I...
I want to be
in the picture, too!
[chuckles]
All right.
Group selfie time.
[AIKA] Watch where you're
putting your grimy hands!
[KIMITO]
It's not me, I swear!
[KAREN] You could always
sit on my lap instead.
[KIMITO]
Me?
[KAREN]
Not you, you pond scum bug!
[KUJO]
Sleep well.
Please don't wake up tomorrow.
[KIMITO]
Yeah, yeah, good night.
[REIKO]
Heya!
[KIMITO]
A club entry form?
[KAREN] When did those two
get so chummy?
[KIMITO]
Uh... Sorry!
Have you forgotten
about my plan?!
[KAREN]
Everything's pointless!
I really hope everyone
has a good time at the party!
Idiot!