[CHIBI whines]
Hey, what's wrong?
[AOI]
Is that the Umi-bouzu?
Really?
But, he's just a child.
Umi-bouzu, sir?
Is something the matter?
Did you perhaps
not like the taste?
[heartbeats]
[AOI gasps]
[UMI-BOUZU]
It was delicious.
But I'm still hungry,
and I'm lonely.
Hey! Why the heck
are you keeping
Umi-bouzu all alone
like this, Aoi?
Me?
But the others said that's
always been the rule.
Well, Umi-bouzu doesn't
like being all alone!
He and I are just the same!
He's so lonely.
And he's always so hungry, too.
Chibi...
So, you're lonely?
Yeah, that's right.
The fireworks are pretty.
And the food is delicious.
And the kagura is fun, too!
But no one ever comes
to share it with him!
Chibi. I understand.
[UMI-BOUZU]
Uh!
[gasping]
[GINJI gasps]
[RANMARU gasping]
[AOI]
It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You both want to
have a clear view
of the night kagura , don't you?
And if it's okay,
I'd like it if we ate
together, too.
You don't have to dine alone.
Really, Aoi?
Well, if I'm being
perfectly honest,
I am pretty hungry myself.
Oh, that's right!
Pick the food that you'd like
to eat from this list, okay?
Don't be shy and pick just one,
tell me every dish
that looks good to you.
[AOI] Ranmaru, don't
glare at me like that.
And Ginji... I'm sorry
to worry you.
But please understand.
I can't stand idly by
in the presence
of loneliness and
hunger. I just can't.
[KAI. MEI]
Hey, what's happening?
[KAI] They say that you should
never look at the umi-bouzu.
And that he's
misfortune incarnate.
I don't know exactly
why the umi-bouzu
brings misfortune with him,
but he's just a small ayakashi
who's very lonely,
and we need to do
something to help him.
He's not giant?
And he's lonely?
Not to mention he's still
very hungry, as well.
I can't leave a child like
that to fend for himself.
I'll need help.
Would you two like to
cook with me again?
[BOTH]
Uh.
Well, the two of us
are your chefs.
And it's our responsibility
to do what you say.
Thank you, Kai, Mei. Really.
To start with,
sukiyaki-style beef and tofu.
Use a pot bigger than
the one we planned.
Make sure to cook extra.
[KAI, MEI]
Understood.
I'm also thinking of
preparing a quiche, too.
What's a quiche?
Never heard of it.
It's a savory dish
using pie dough.
We'll bring it out whole,
then serve it at the table--
it's great for groups!
[KAI, MEI]
Oh...
I'll put it in the oven now,
so would you mind bringing
it over when it's done?
[BOTH]
Leave it to us!
[laughing]
Oh, my belly! That tickles!
Stop it, stop it!
[AOI laughs]
Thank you for being so patient.
Here's your fried chicken,
covered with a summer
orange jam sauce.
[UMI-BOUZU]
Wow. Ooh...
It seems like you've been
drinking, too, Chibi.
[CHIBI]
Umi-bouzu. Shared it with me.
Oh? Is that for me?
[UMI-BOUZU]
Mm-hm.
[AOI] I'm sure this is him
showing his appreciation,
so I won't refuse.
[AOI gasps]
Hold on. Where--?
[UMI-BOUZU wails]
The umi-bouzu?
[GINJI "...confined
in an enclosed space
in the farthest corner
of the ocean."
[AOI]
This is where you've been.
You're trapped in
this isolated place.
[UMI-BOUZU]
I'm lonely. I'm hungry.
[AOI]
I'm hungry.
Mom, please. I'm hungry.
You're just... like I was.
Do you like it?
[AOI] He's confined
to such a dark place.
Always by himself.
Wishing for food and company.
This is his only escape.
Once every hundred years.
To him, the southern land
is like a paradise.
And he's living in
a dream right now.
[UMI-BOUZU grunts]
[UMI-BOUZU sighs]
I know just what it's
like to be stuck alone
in a dark and scary place.
And what it's like to
desperately need food.
[UMI-BOUZU hums]
[AOI] Being starved of
both food and company.
That's no way to live.
[KAI, MEI] The quiche thing
is finished now! Mm?
Aoi? What's going on in here?
Is that child really
the umi-bouzu?
[UMI-BOUZU]
Ah...
Amazing! Aoi, what
is this thing?
This is called a quiche.
It's a spicy Japanese-style
curry flavor.
This has pumpkin, bacon.
And plenty of
fresh mushroom.
[CHIBI]
Wow. It smells so good!
Of course, we used
the curry powder
that the Master brought for me.
Now then, please dig in!
[AOI]
Like it?
[UMI-BOUZU]
Mm-hm!
Good, I'm glad.
Oh, yum, it's so delicious!
The outside is flaky.
And the inside's creamy!
Uh? What's the matter?
[gasps]
Thank you, but I can't
really taste anything.
[UMI-BOUZU grunting]
Well, if you insist.
[gasps]
[CHIBI]
Aoi?
[KAI, MEI]
Is something wrong?
[AOI]
This food... it's delicious.
[BOTH gasp]
It's good. I can
actually taste it!
[BOTH gasp]
I'm so glad!
Yeah, that's incredible!
Yay! Yay! Hip.
Hip. Hip. Hooray!
[RANMARU]
Hey.
Having fun?
I hope you're enjoying
this little "party"
while we're stuck dancing
the night kagura
outside all evening.
Master Ranmaru.
Is the night kagura
finished already?
No, not quite yet.
There's still the dance
of new beginnings,
the most important performance.
We're taking a break until
it's time to start that one.
[UMI-BOUZU gasping]
I apologize.
I did everything without asking
your permission first.
But, I...
[RANMARU]
I understand why you did it.
Huh?
You had a vision of
the Umi-Bouzu earlier.
And we were able to
bear witness to it, too.
[KAI, MEI] We'll bring out
the remaining dishes,
if that's okay.
Ginji, Ranmaru, why don't
the two of you join us?
Huh?!
Come on, we can use this as a
chance to get a little food
before we have to start again.
Well this completely ruins the
sacred mood of the ceremony.
Does it bother you that much?
Don't put words into my mouth.
[laughs]
[UMI-BOUZU]
Ahh!
[ALL laughing]
[AOI laughs]
[AOI]
The last event,
the night kagura dance of new
beginnings, is about to start.
♪♪♪
[AOI]
It really is over.
His dream is coming to an end.
[AOI]
Princess Iso.
This has been a
wonderful experience.
I'm truly glad that I was able
to make the dishes
of ocean treasure.
May those who live in
this land be able to live
peacefully for the
next hundred years.
Wait! Before you go!
Would you... like to stay
here with me instead?
[UMI-BOUZU]
Uh.
Mm-mm.
Thank you, but I
have to go back.
Well, at least
have some snacks.
There's a fig pie and a
summer orange jam pie.
[UMI-BOUZU]
Oh!
Hey, Umi-bouzu.
This is my best treasure.
It's a beautiful, shiny pearl
from a rainbow clam!
Take it and keep it with you!
Let's play again sometime!
[UMI-BOUZU] Thank you
for entertaining me.
I'll see you all again
in a hundred years.
[AOI]
In a hundred years.
I probably won't
be around anymore.
[AOI]
Goodbye...
[UMI-BOUZU grunting]
[BOTH]
Uh-oh!
Quick, everyone get
off the beach!
[GINJI]
Aoi!
[AOI]
Ginji...
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Does it taste good?
Yeah. It does.
It's so yummy.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] Good.
He'll be pleased to hear that.
Who do you mean?
[AOI]
You're going away already?
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] I won't be
coming back here ever again,
because from now on,
there will be no need.
[AOI]
No, it's too soon. Stay with me.
Please don't go, this can't
be the last time I see you.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Eat well.
Get your energy back. And live.
[GINJI]
We will meet again one day.
When you become an adult.
[AOI]
Ginji!
Oh, my. The umi-bouzu's
already leaving.
The ceremony was a
success after all, then.
How painfully boring.
Guess I'll go.
Oh!
Look who it is! Ogre god!
And what's your pleasure?
I've come here to
settle matters with you.
Ha.
Matters? And those would be?
[MASTER] I heard you sealed
away Aoi's sense of taste.
Oh, that. Yes, I did.
I'm regretting it now, though.
To tell you the truth,
I should have just
devoured that annoying
little human girl
when I had the chance.
[gasps]
[MASTER]
If you lay a finger on Aoi,
I will consume
every scrap of you.
From the marrow of your bones,
to the last piece of your soul,
until there's nothing left
of you in this world.
[RAIJU gasping]
[MASTER]
Once you die, the memories
of your meddling will
be lost with you forever.
[RAIJU gasping]
My goodness!
I wouldn't want to be
eaten up by the ogre god
in such a brutal fashion.
I'll take my leave of you then,
please pass my
regards on to Aoi.
[GINJI]
Aoi! Aoi!
[AOI grunting]
Oh, thank goodness,
are you okay?
It's you, Ginji.
I'm glad you're all right.
Just take it slow.
Please, be honest with me.
Are you the ayakashi?
The one who saved
me with that food
when I was just a little kid.
Aoi, I...
Why wouldn't you tell me
something so important?
Well you see Aoi,
it wasn't just me.
What?
It's true that it was me
who brought you food
from time to time,
but I wasn't alone.
The thing is, the one who
went to see you first
was also the one who prepared
the last thing you ate.
And that was someone else.
So, what does that mean?
Well truthfully,
I was just a stand-in.
While he was busy
cooking the food
that would serve to
alter your destiny,
I was simply keeping
an eye on you for him.
Can you tell me who he is?
Could it be the Master?
As much as I'd like to tell you,
I'm not at liberty
to say anything.
Uh...
I truly wish that I could,
please understand,
I'm just a helpless ayakashi.
My place is on the sidelines.
[AOI]
That's not true!
You can't even imagine how much
you being there reassured me,
and how much it meant
to me as well!
You... gave me the hope that
I needed to keep on living.
I'm glad, Aoi.
Oh, Ginji. You saved me.
Thank you so much!
[GINJI] It's me who
should be thanking you.
Wholeheartedly.
You were able to make
the ceremony successful.
If I hadn't met you
all those years ago,
that never would have happened.
[gasps]
You lived. You survived.
And then you came here
to the hidden realm.
And you appeared before me
when we needed you most.
I thank you, Aoi, from
the bottom of my heart.
Oh, Ginji. Ginji...
[AOI]
When we returned to Orio-ya,
everyone was exhausted from
taking care of so many guests.
It had taken so much energy.
But everyone was happy that
the ceremony was successful.
[GINJI]
Ranmaru.
You... resent my actions,
don't you?
Because I ran.
I ran away from the fate
of the southern land,
forcing everything
into your hands.
Your leaving was
a turning point.
The southern lands benefitted
from you going away.
What?
[RANMARU]
As a result, Aoi Tsubaki
and the master of Tenjin-ya
took action, so...
Ranmaru.
[RANMARU grunts]
[footsteps]
[RANMARU] At any rate, I
never expected the umi-bouzu
to be such a lonely creature.
You're right. We just assumed
that he would intentionally
bring calamity to this land,
without considering
any other possibility.
But the truth was
the complete opposite.
That dark place in the farthest
corner of the ocean opens
once every hundred years,
and the impurities that cause
disaster escape from it
when that happens.
[RANMARU]
But, if the ceremony succeeds,
the umi-bouzu is imbued with
the energy to push it back,
and that's what
keeps catastrophe
from befalling this land.
It never even crossed my mind
that that could be the case.
I suppose we'll have to credit
Miss Tsubaki for that.
The very basis of the ceremony
will have to change now.
It'll become a warm reception
to show our appreciation
to the umi-bouzu.
That sounds great.
Now, Ginji.
Time for you to go back.
Your home is somewhere
else now, isn't it?
Right!
[KAI, MEI]
Goodbye, Miss Tsubaki.
Can we see you again?
And cook together again someday?
Of course we can.
I want to eat more
yummy cucumbers
from the southern land!
Don't worry, I'm sure you'll
be able to come back
again real soon.
Having your cooperation
really was such a great help.
We've had the most incredible
sales since Orio-ya opened.
Yes, it was very
beneficial to us, too.
Though I'd have to admit,
I never thought I'd see
Tenjin-ya and Orio-ya
collaborate.
For sure. It's been
kind of a strange time.
Ha! All work and no play,
even during tearful
goodbyes, Akatsuki?
You're really no fun.
[AKATSUKI grunts]
But you've become a
fine front desk manager.
Yeah, well, I'm still not
a match for you yet.
Ha, ha!
After watching you work,
I couldn't help but be in awe
of your job performance.
[laughs] Follow my example and
keep trying hard, Nene!
I may surpass you pretty soon.
What's that?
Doing business together
was quite a success.
And also very enlightening.
I'd definitely want us
to do this again,
for the next ceremony.
These are the tomatoes I managed
to grow in that field.
I would love it if you
took some home with you.
[SHIZUNA] Thank you very much,
Teacher! I will!
Oh, Shizuna.
Come on, it's time for
us to head back now.
Yes, of course!
Shizuna! [cries]
[SHIZUNA] We can see each other
again soon, Teacher!
Oh, my goodness...
[RANMARU laughs]
Listen, Aoi.
Master?
Is there something the matter?
I'm proud of you.
It's amazing what
you accomplished
in such an unfamiliar place.
[AOI gasping]
Master. I have something to ask.
Yes, what is it?
[AOI]
It's just that...
I'll have to return your
kindness to you one day,
won't I?
Will you?
Did I do something
to deserve that?
[AOI laughs]
[AOI] At first, this was an
unfamiliar and scary place,
where I was brought
against my will.
But now I know that
every ayakashi here
is a wonderful person,
working hard every day,
and brimming with conviction.
It's wonderful.
Tenjin-ya is the place
my irreplaceable
friends and colleagues
call home,
and I suppose, I can
call it that now, too.
It's Tenjin-ya. I'm home.
[AOI] Now, it's time to open
the restaurant again!
Welcome to Moonflower!