[AOI]
Looking over these,
the umi-bouzu's likes and
dislikes seem pretty apparent.
The record from a hundred
years ago says...
...he wasn't satisfied
with the food.
Maybe because the menu
was chosen just to pair
with the liquor?
That'd make it pretty flat.
Plus, he didn't try any
clam or sea snail dishes.
Even though they're some of
the southern land's specialties.
But he did like the grilled
sea urchin a lot.
The sea urchin in this land is
sweet, so even kids can eat it.
[GINJI]
Sorry I'm late.
[sighs]
Wait, did something go wrong?
After all that, was
the Hourai's gem branch
that the toad brought a fake?
We're still not sure.
Raiju is the only person
who would be able to tell,
but he keeps dodging
the question.
[BOTH]
He's a tricky one.
He said he would
consider telling us
if we showed him
something interesting.
So Hideyoshi is performing his
loach-scooping dance for him
right now, though I don't
really know how that'll fare.
"Loach-scooping dance"?
[HIDEYOSHI chuckles]
[HIDEYOSHI grunting]
[sighs]
What do you have?
Kirisame, a Suiun drink.
According to Hatori, the taste
is about as close as you can get
to the tengu's secret liquor.
[AOI]
So, we're checking to see
if the dishes will pair
well with this instead?
[KAI] The secret liquor
is currently...
[MEI] ...being cleansed
for the ceremony.
It's not perfect,
but it should work.
I brought something else
for us to try, too.
Oh, wow!
[BOTH]
That beef looks good!
This is called Kiseki beef!
It's a well-known brand that's
the pride of the southern land.
And sukiyaki got a high mark,
so that can really
only mean one thing!
The spread doesn't have
to all be seafood,
even though the requirement
says "ocean treasure"!
What lovely marbling!
So would you all like
to give it a taste?
[ALL]
Mm-hm!
I'll cook us up some
garlic butter rice
to serve alongside it.
[KAI, MEI]
That sound is heavenly!
It smells so enticing, too!
Help me!
I take it you finished?
He told me to stop, and
then he said he lost some
of his spiritual power
because of me,
and now he's demanding
something to eat immediately!
He needs a meal!
I guess I'll make it.
Not possible.
You're far too busy
working on the ocean
treasure dishes right now.
You two do it. Please.
Can we at least eat our
beef and rice first?
Yeah, can we?
This has to be done right now!
[MEI, MAI]
Kiseki beef!
Don't worry, I'll save you some!
Heh. I have some vinegared
cucumber and daikon that I
made in advance, so let's have
them as palate cleansers.
That sounds good!
It tastes great!
[AOI] The more you chew, the
more the flavor comes to life!
Oh yeah, that's exactly it!
This food is delectable,
there's no doubt about that!
It would definitely
pair well with beer!
I wonder if this would
go with the liquor.
Shall we try and see?
It smells nice, and the
profile's good, as well.
But I worry that the sweetness
of the aroma might overpower
the flavors of the garlic steak.
Not everyone may be bothered by
it, but if that's your instinct,
it's probably better to
prepare other options.
Wow, this is kinda fun,
with just the two of us.
[AOI]
Uh.
To be fair. When I drink in
the evening, it's usually alone.
Oh, is that true? I find it
hard to picture that.
Unfortunately, that's the
reality of being a single guy.
So, you're saying you don't
have a girlfriend then, Ginji?
[GINJI coughs]
Where did that come from--
and so suddenly?
Because, you were just
talking about being single.
What? Would you really
assume that I wasn't?
Since I moved straight from
Orio-ya to Tenjin-ya,
I've always been very
busy my work duties.
Truth be told, I don't
have any experience
with that kind of thing.
I see.
Well, I shouldn't talk
but I can't imagine why.
If the rumors are all true,
you were pretty well-known
around the inn as "the last
good catch" at Tenjin-ya.
Do you think me shameful
for having come this far
as a man without ever
even knowing love
or having any sort
of relationship?
That's not it at all!
Ginji, you should really have
more confidence in yourself!
Well, then can I ask
about you, Aoi?
I know you were taken to the
hidden realm by the Master.
But, back in the apparent realm,
did you perhaps have someone?
No way!
That was quick.
I guess you could say I was
always Grandpa's little angel.
At least when I was small.
Heck, I even wanted to
marry him once I grew up.
[GINJI]
So Shiro was popular even with
his own granddaughter, huh?
[AOI]
But.
I did still have a
first crush, I guess.
Yeah. In my heart, I'm sure
that was my first love.
I was little then too, though.
You don't say.
Well, that's interesting.
[AOI gasping]
The story of your
very first love.
I'm sure the Master would
like to hear all about it.
[AOI]
What?
I've been noticing that
he keeps coming to Orio-ya
disguised as a fish peddler.
So how are things
going with him,
any new developments
between you two?
Absolutely not!
That ogre is exactly
the same as ever.
The Master's the Master, no-one
knows that better than you!
There you go again.
But even with that attitude
of yours towards him,
I don't think he could stop
worrying about you now,
even if he tried.
I mean, I guess.
It's true he's more approachable
than many think.
I understand now that
he's just mischievous.
[GINJI]
Uh.
But I, well, I still find
him very mysterious,
and he seems so aloof compared
to everyone else here.
I just don't get it.
What's the real reason
why the Master wants me
to be his bride so badly?
Is it because I'm
collateral for a loan?
Because I'm a human girl?
Can a guy decide to marry
for reasons like those,
but then really fall in love?
The whole situation seems
completely backwards!
Why doesn't he just
tell me how he feels?
Okay, relax...
Right, there'll be no more
relationship talk tonight!
Hold on now, are you
seriously drunk already, Aoi?
No, not yet, but...
Idea. How about...
...we try making roast beef
with this Kiseki cut, huh?
Okay sure, why not? I've never
had it before myself,
but I have heard it's pretty
popular in the apparent realm!
[door slides open]
[footsteps]
Do you still have...
...the grilled beef?
Oh, yeah, I do. I'll heat
some up for you now.
Are you two already done
cooking the meal for Raiju?
He didn't want any...
...food cooked by us.
Maybe I'll start
the preparations
for roast beef now
and suggest it
at tomorrow night's
tasting session.
Ranmaru will be back by then,
so I want to have him eat
your food and admit defeat.
Maybe that will
humble him a bit.
[laughs]
[CHIBI] Nom, nom, nom,
nom, nom, nom, nom.
[door slides open]
You're back real late
tonight, Aoi. What's up?
I was preparing what I
could for roast beef,
and I also had to check over
the menu and ingredients
for tomorrow's tasting
session with Ginji, so I just--
[yawns] I guess I lost
track of time. Yeah.
I'm concerned that you neglected
to put a cucumber dish
on the menu. Oh no, get up, Aoi!
You shouldn't fall asleep
here on the floor.
I'll do my best for
the tasting session.
Ugh, you reek of alcohol.
I should bake the bread first.
Then I'll finish up
the roast beef.
I also need to come up
with dessert ideas.
Mm? Looks like it could
rain at any minute.
[RAIJU]
Hello...
[gasps]
[AOI gasping]
[AOI screams]
Did I frighten you,
young miss? Oh, how cute.
[AOI]
I know who that is. It's Raiju!
Well, would you look at that.
You look just like
Shiro Tsubaki.
Especially when it comes
to your eyes and your mouth.
What the--?
What're you talking about?
Since Shiro was a man, he was
all sharp angles and bones,
but you look so soft and
delicate. How delicious.
[AOI yelps]
[AOI panting]
[AOI] The nerve of that guy.
Keep your hands to yourself.
Or what?
[screams]
Why are you still running
away from me, my dear?
[AOI screams]
Why? You can tell me.
I was told that you're a thunder
god, and you are, aren't you?
Well, I'm not good with
thunder and lightning!
I see--that's what it is.
[gasps]
[RAIJU] I don't mind
this reaction, really.
If you're that scared of me, I'm
truly honored, as an ayakashi.
I don't have time for you
or for any of this!
I've got an important job
that I have to do today
for the ceremony.
Oh, but I do wish for the
ceremony's utmost success,
I assure you of that,
little human.
You won't even do us the basic
courtesy of telling us
if the Hourai's gem branch
is the real thing!
You just keep messing with us!
[RAIJU]
Hm...?
What now? Something I said?
How should I put it?
Despite all your posturing,
you really do trust ayakashi
far too much, you know.
What do you mean?
[RAIJU] You were abducted
and exploited by ayakashi.
Yet you want to make
the ceremony successful
for those same captors of yours.
Fascinating how
nonsensical that is.
I'm just doing whatever it takes
to make sure I can survive here.
And if cooking is what
leads to me being protected,
then so be it. So it's not
just for the ayakashi!
Well, you certainly told me.
[AOI]
Do you have a problem with that?
You seem to have
quite a lot of sass
for a girl in a captive
situation, that's all.
[AOI]
I'm just desperate.
If no one thinks that
my food is delicious,
I won't be able to repay
the debt and go home.
Ah. I would like to try
some of this food
that the other ayakashi
so delight in.
Will you make something for me?
Sure, uh.
Are you saying you're hungry?
Well then, if that's the case!
[RAIJU]
As if I would really ask you to!
My, you're surprisingly
gullible.
Really.
I'm tired of eating dishes
made by human hands.
On top of that, your food seems
rather low-class, I'm afraid.
[AOI gasps]
[laughing]
You're a piece of work.
After all this time...
Normal food can't excite me.
There's only one type of dish
in the world you could prepare
that could even
hope to satisfy me.
And what dish is that?
[RAIJU]
Isn't it obvious? You, my dear.
[AOI gasping]
[RAIJU] The greatest delicacy
known to ayakashi
is the flesh of a human girl
with potent spiritual power.
There's no possible
way you could create
any culinary hodgepodge
that would be better.
[gasps] I see.
So I suppose you're just going
to eat me right here, right now?
It's really quite tempting,
but now isn't the ideal
time. Even so...
[gasps]
How exactly are you planning
on protecting yourself
against someone when you can't
use cooking as a weapon?
Or what if you became
unable to cook?
[gasping]
Unable to defend yourself or
do what you're most proud of?
Would you resign your fate to
becoming useless food yourself?
[AOI]
I hadn't thought about that.
Shiro was smart.
By setting you up
to marry the ogre.
Giving you the only shield that
could possibly protect you.
Stop it.
[RAIJU] To an ayakashi, the
only uses for a human girl
are to marry, or to
be eaten up whole.
[thunder cracks]
Stop it now!
[AOI gasps]
I didn't mean to upset you.
Accept this apology from me.
[AOI]
A matcha candy?
It's delicate, but tasty.
It's a sweet meant
to soothe your throat
called a Matcha Drop.
Honestly though. I'm just
so terribly bored.
That is why I meddle
until I'm hated and cursed
all across the land.
There are so few things
that still excite me
in the hidden realm.
Shiro was like a hit
from a powerful drug.
[gasps]
He was the kind of scum
who would cause trouble,
dump it on others
and then run away.
But he had the sort of bold
presence that made people
forgive him.
No matter what he did.
What could you possibly
offer to an ayakashi
who's known the likes
of someone like Shiro?
[AOI whimpers]
Are you really going to
shut yourself in a kitchen
and hope this goes away? Oh,
how excruciatingly boring!
I want to experience something
much more exciting than that!
Like Shiro.
I am not the same person
my grandpa was!
You should have just
quietly gone through
with your betrothal.
[yelps]
[AOI]
I'm sorry!
[RANMARU] Why are you
running around like that?
Are you slacking off?
Ranmaru, I...
[RANMARU]
Hm?
Oh no, there's a scary
looking dog in my way.
Let me be clear Raiju.
There is no need for you
to concern yourself with
this human and her affairs.
You have worked so
very hard, Ranmaru.
You took the trouble
to go to Youto,
and yet, you still
could not find
any of Hourai's gem branches,
isn't that right?
Such branches come from
a tree with spiritual power
that was given to the
ayakashi king as a present.
The tree was lost in
the Great Youto Fire,
a famous part of the
hidden realm's history.
Only a few branches
actually survived,
but no one knows who has
come to possess them
after all these years.
There is no way that
the nobles in Youto
would give any information
on them to a rural innkeeper
such as yourself.
Hey now, that--
It's not 300 years ago anymore.
Things are different now,
and we shall complete
the ceremony this time.
Have a good day.
Good luck with everything.
[AOI]
Thank you, Ranmaru.
[RANMARU]
I don't recall helping you.
I see you're back
to your old self.
[RANMARU]
Remember this, Miss Tsubaki.
At tonight's tasting session,
if you serve anything
odd or peculiar,
we'll roast and feed you
to the umi-bouzu instead.
Seriously? Jeez,
stop talking like that.
Three hundred years ago,
it was Raiju who
betrayed our land.
[gasps]
Stay very far away from him.
He is dangerous
and unpredictable.
And if the ceremony fails...
Well, we all have a lot to lose.
I understand.
[RANMARU] You should go get
prepared for the task ahead.
Prepare... Right.
[AOI] You seem like
such a sensitive guy,
but your writing is
so masculine, Ginji.
I don't know what that
means, but, uh, thanks?
[KAI, MEI]
This menu looks amazing!
I would like to try
the roast beef!
What'll we use to wrap
the fried food?
Raw tofu skin.
[KAI, MEI] Oh, the two of us
are good at making that!
That settles it. I'll leave that
dish up to the two of you.
Perfect!
We'll do our best!
[MEI] The temperature of
the ayakashi fire disc
may be a little too high.
Try this then. How about now?
Yeah, that's good!
Mistress Aoi! Let me
help you out, okay?
Ah! Ai is flat out ignoring me
and posing as Aoi's
devoted follower!
That's all right.
I'm going to prove to them
that I'm also an excellently
devoted follower to Aoi!
Please allow me to help
you out in the kitchen!
Oh, I didn't see you there!
I'm busy right now so I'll
play with you later, 'kay?
No! I can help you, please!
Let me help you, Aoi!
Okay now. No need to get upset.
[CHIBI hums]
[AOI] Wrap up the jam
pies for me, will you?
Yeah, I'll do it!
You sure perked up quickly.
[laughs] Aoi, you sort of treat
Chibi like you're his mother!
[AOI]
Aw. Don't say that.
Anyway, the official
participants of the tasting
session are Ranmaru and Hatori,
but I also heard that Tokihiko,
Hideyoshi, and Nene plan
to each come by in turn
to try out the food.
Hello all, I've brought the
cleansed secret liquor for you!
Oh, Hatori!
So, uh. Are we really having
the tasting session here?
[AOI] No, we decided to
use the next room over.
All right Hatori,
you and I are the ones
who have been put in charge
of all the heavy lifting.
It's time to get
this room into shape.
[HATORI] Is that why you told
me to arrive early?
Time to take a taste!
Oh, so tender!
Oh, it looks like beef tataki.
Yeah, I suppose it's pretty
similar. Would you like to try?
[KAI, MEI] Yes please,
of course we would!
[AOI]
Can I sample this, too?
That's the only one that
has two shrimp inside it!
Oh wow! Looks delicious!
Mistress Aoi!
[CHIBI]
Please let us have some, too!
[HATORI]
Hey!
Huh?
I can't believe you guys are
over there sneaking food
while we're stuck carrying
heavy tables and breakin' stuff!
Wait, breaking?
Did I hear that correctly?
Unfortunately, our sweet
Hatori got carried away,
flew around the room, and ended
up breaking the table's legs.
You don't have to sound so
extra cheery about it, Ginji!
Well, you are the one
that broke it, not me.
The point is, it seems
we'll have to have the tasting
session on another table.
It's much smaller.
But if we arrange everything
correctly it should work, right?
Oh my, this is seriously
the best you could manage?
I think that it's charming, like
a poor family's holiday dinner!
Whatever.
Are the dishes ready yet?
Yes, and please don't hold
back on your critique, okay?
Of course I won't.
Prepare yourself for
my honest disapproval.
Look, Ranmaru.
Do not go into this
underestimating Aoi's cooking.
Her food is absolutely--
Ginji, it's fine. I want
to hear his honest,
unfiltered opinion,
so I can handle it.
[RANMARU]
Hmph.
Here's to the ceremony's
success. Let's toast.
[GROUP]
Cheers, everyone!
Cheers, everyone.
Come on, this isn't a party!
Would it kill you to
have a little fun?
[GROUP laughs]
--[KAI, MEI] Oh, what a flavor!
--[CHIBI] This is super yummy.
[GROUP chatting, laughing]
[gasping]
[RAIJU] Now, let us have
our own secret party,
just the two of us.
[muffled] As expected, this
is totally different from
the manufactured Suiun
liquor. The flavor's great.
[AOI]
What? Am I...
[HATORI muffled] And that's why
it's called the secret liquor!
[RANMARU] The real
question is, was the girl
smart enough to make food
that pairs well with it?
Or is it being wasted.
[GINJI] Ranmaru! Stop being
so rude for once!
As soon as you eat it, you'll
understand how valuable
her food is to the ayakashi,
just wait and see.
Hold on. Aoi?
Hey, Aoi? What's this look,
are you feeling okay?
[GINJI gasping]
Aoi!
[RAIJU] Well now. How fortunate
that I wished you good luck.
[AOI whimpers]
[CHIBI]
Aoi? What's wrong?
Are you tired? Did you
have too much to drink?
Would you like some cucumber?
Aoi, you're gonna
be okay, right?
Aoi, wake up!