[MASTER]
Yes, indeed.
The hidden realm of ayakashi,
our domain.
And this building
where you find yourself
is known as Tenjin-ya.
Thus, to put it indelicately,
you are his collateral.
Now, why not just give
in and agree to be my bride?
I'll stay and work
till it's paid.
That settles the debt,
but I won't have to marry you.
The flavors of this dish...
...so good. Delightful.
My grandpa took care to
teach me all his secrets.
How would you like to
open your own restaurant here?
Huh?!
[AOI]
My grandfather's funeral
felt more like a festival
than anything else.
[WOMAN 1]
He was a terrible person!
[WOMAN 2]
You aren't kidding!
He was textbook scum,
through and through.
[WOMAN 3]
He told me, "You're my favorite,
the only one I love."
[MAN] It might not
have seemed like it,
but he always meant
what he said, in the moment.
[WOMAN 1] Bumming around
was his favorite pastime.
[WOMAN 2] He was the definition
of, "free-spirited!"
[WOMEN laughing]
[WOMAN 3]
I thought he'd never die,
even if someone
tried to kill him!
[MAN] And yet, he fell down
the stairs and hit his head.
[WOMAN 1]
So sudden, too.
[WOMAN 2] Well, we can't
complain about him now.
[MAN] I came here today just
to see his face one last time.
[AOI]
The long line of mourners
looked more like a scene
from a cheesy monster movie,
with all kinds
of strange creatures.
[chopping]
[AOI] When I'm feeling
overwhelmed,
I calm myself down by cooking.
And one thing's for sure--
I am more overwhelmed
now than I've ever been,
in all my 19 years.
What? I couldn't possibly
run a restaurant here!
Why not?
This tastes incredible.
I think it's a great idea.
[GINJI]
All right.
I've gotta get going now,
but you feel free to
make yourself at home in here.
Think it over.
I know it'd be a success,
so consider my idea?
And thanks for the food.
[door slides shut]
[AOI]
Chicken and potato stew,
pork with daikon,
stir-fried miso eggplant,
and pickled burdock root.
Well, I guess I'll feed
all this to Ginji.
[AOI]
Should I just try it out?
Opening a restaurant here?
I can't find any other job,
and I've got to pay back
Grandpa's debt somehow.
I do enjoy cooking,
and I've served food
to ayakashi
in the apparent realm before.
But, still...
Liking to cook and being
a chef are very different.
--[crash]
--[gasps]
[MALE 1]
Don't mess with us!
[MALE 2]
Or what?!
[gasps]
[MALE 1]
You stupid daruma!
[MALE 2]
You worthless tengu!
Go back to hell,
where you belong!
Damn you! See ya there!
Please stop this, honored tengu!
You, too, Chief Chef!
[ATTENDANT 1]
Front Desk Manager!
[ATTENDANT 2]
Please be careful!
[ATTENDANT 3]
What should we do?
You muscle-headed,
moose-brained jerks!
[DARUMA]
We'll break all your fat noses!
Um, what's going on here?
Well, those tengu
complained that our menu
is boring and predictable,
so the kitchen guys got mad.
The tengu said,
"We refuse to eat any of this!"
They were flippin'
tables and stuff,
'cause they're all drunk
from their banquet.
[AOI]
What? That's awful!
[KASUGA]
But, they are loyal customers,
and their elder's
one of the most
powerful ayakashi around.
He's on the same level as
our master innkeeper, ya know.
So...
Oh! The master's here!
[GUESTS gasp]
[whimpering]
Managing and young hostess?
The managing and young hostess--
Ah! Ow...
My! What awful manners!
She must learn to bow
to the master innkeeper
the moment he enters the room!
She cannot help being
coarse and insolent, Hostess.
She's a human girl, after all.
[AOI growls]
You are an eyesore...
--...Aoi Tsubaki.
--[AOI gasps]
You are nothing
but a human nuisance for us.
You owe a large debt
to Tenjin-ya,
so we'll endure you
until that's paid.
But I won't abide you
sticking your nose
in our disputes.
What? I just got worried!
I heard a loud noise,
and I came to--
Leave this place immediately,
or I will devour you,
and perhaps
give the tengu a taste.
[AOI gasps]
[O-RYO giggles]
[AOI cries]
[AOI sighs]
[AOI]
It's never going to work.
[inaudible]
Man! I'm done!
This calls
for some binge eating!
--[thud]
--[MATSUBA grunts]
What now? Who's out there?
[gasps]
[MATSUBA groaning]
He's passed out drunk!
[groaning continues]
[AOI]
Down you go now.
He kinda reminds me
of you, Grandpa.
[SHIRO snoring]
[grumbling]
[MATSUBA]
Hmm?
Where'd I end up this time?
What happened?
Oh jeez, that hurts. [groans]
[AOI] Are you okay, sir?
Take it easy.
Hello, there. Who are you?
[AOI]
Would you like a drink of water?
Guess so.
[MATSUBA]
Hmm... So, then, where am I?
This is the Tenjin-ya annex.
What?! Tenjin-ya?!
Oh, don't be alarmed.
You and I are
very much alone here.
This place is
considered abandoned
by the rest of the staff.
That so?
Hmm...
Well, then, mister.
I bet you're hungry.
I made some great side dishes.
[MATSUBA grunts]
What do you take me for, girl?
I couldn't eat food that was
made by a female.
[stomach growls]
I'll eat.
[MATSUBA]
Mmm, tasty!
Just spectacular!
But, it isn't enough.
Anything else on the menu?
Chicken and potato stew,
and stir-fried miso eggplant.
Great. Bring both.
So, then. What's your name?
I'm Aoi. Aoi Tsubaki.
Tsubaki?
[AOI]
Mm-hmm.
Are you, perhaps,
the daughter
of one Shiro Tsubaki?
Uh...
Close, but no.
I'm Shiro Tsubaki's
granddaughter.
I see! His granddaughter?
Why, do you know my grandpa?
I do, indeed.
Quite well.
We go way back. Hmm...
[MATSUBA laughing]
What's so funny, sir?
My name is Matsuba.
Master Matsuba.
[MATSUBA]
Aoi Tsubaki!
You're a great cook!
I've grown quite weary
of the food here at Tenjin-ya,
so this is lucky.
You've grown weary of it?
[MATSUBA] That chief chef
is stubborn as hell.
Serves the same dishes
every time we come here.
No matter how good
they might be,
you get tired of them.
I just suggested
that he mix things up a bit.
That's when he flew
off the handle.
So, you're who started
the big fight, then.
[MATSUBA grunts]
[MATSUBA]
Hmm...
[AOI]
Hmm?
[MATSUBA] Aoi, you remind me
quite a bit of Shiro.
Really? I don't feel like
I resemble him very much at all.
Your face, your energy,
but more than those,
his spiritual power.
--[AOI] Spiritual power?
--Heh.
[MATSUBA] Shiro was very wild,
for a human,
and he came to the hidden realm
of his own accord.
He was well-liked
by scores of ayakashi.
But still, far more
wanted him dead
and wanted to kill him
themselves.
[laughing]
That sure sounds
like Grandpa!
[MATSUBA]
You know, Aoi?
I owe my very life
to your grandfather.
Huh?
It all happened around
60 years back, or so.
[MATSUBA]
I had gotten too drunk,
like I do, and I fell
into the Daikanro River,
which runs through
the hidden realm.
Shiro jumped right
into the river,
and saved me
from a watery grave.
He was still a young man then.
In fact, he was still young
enough to be called a boy.
Wow. It was lucky that
he happened to be there.
Indeed. He had been
fishing on the shore.
By the way,
fishing in the Daikanro River
has been strictly prohibited
since ancient times.
Hmm... Well, that's
my Grandpa for you.
Although, he did jump in
the river to save a stranger.
So, then he had
a hidden generous side?
[MATSUBA] No, no, no.
The first thing he did
was bug me for a reward
for saving my life.
[AOI chuckles nervously]
[AOI] So what did you give him
in exchange for saving you?
Oh, well,
I didn't have anything on me
at the time
that would've sufficed,
so I gave him
a verbal IOU for a fan.
Why a fan?
[MATSUBA]
It's a tengu treasure.
I see.
[MATSUBA] But, I suppose he may
have forgotten my promise,
because he never did accept
his reward, that rascal.
Heh. Everything you've said
is so typical of Grandpa.
He really was
quite free-spirited.
A charming,
unreliable scoundrel.
An irresponsible human
who lived
for the present moment.
Yep, he sure did.
He left everything
in life to chance.
That's right.
I was always
especially fond of Shiro.
Most other ayakashi said,
"He's a lowlife,
he's even worse than ayakashi !"
We're a self-loathing bunch.
But he was amusing
and exhilarating to be around.
A lowlife,
even worse than ayakashi ?
You know?
I'd have to agree with them.
[MATSUBA]
And you'd know!
[AOI]
Grandpa taught me a lot, though.
Yeah?
How to cook, for starters.
[MATSUBA]
He did?
I guess what he liked
and what ayakashi like
are similar.
For food, at least.
Well, I find that
hard to believe.
[AOI]
Why?
He always used to complain
that the food
in the hidden realm
was too bland for him
to even stomach.
What?
[MATSUBA] Well, I suppose
his taste could have changed
as he got older. That happens.
So, then,
how's Shiro doing now?
Uh...
[MATSUBA]
Is he well?
[AOI]
Mmm...
[MATSUBA]
Hmm?
[AOI]
He passed away.
[MATSUBA sighs]
He had lived a long life,
but he died after
he fell down the stairs.
Death can surprise you, huh?
My word.
I'm going to miss him
a great deal.
[gasps]
I still can't believe how very
fragile you humans are,
that you can't even
live 100 years.
Uh...
[MATSUBA]
Thank you for the food.
[AOI]
Grandpa. You were incredible.
You made it to the hidden
realm on your own.
So wild and free-spirited.
It wasn't very nice
to offer your granddaughter
as collateral
for your debt, though.
For my last meal,
I hope I can eat
your cooking, Aoi.
[AOI]
Sadly,
your last supper
was awful hospital food.
I wish that I could
have cooked for him.
Just one more good meal.
[AOI]
This place is so relaxing.
So calm and quiet.
The ambiance is lovely.
It's too bad.
They're gonna tear it down soon.
--[knocking]
--[GINJI] Aoi!
[AOI]
Huh?
There you are!
Please come with me!
Uh...
[AOI]
Wait--
No time to talk, come on.
What's going on?
Huh?
Wh-What's this?
[MASTER]
Aoi?
What's wrong?
Last night, you served a meal
to the tengu elder, yes?
Uh, I did.
[AOI]
I guess he means Master Matsuba?
Was serving him a mistake?
[MATSUBA]
Ah!
My dear Aoi!
Hi.
Your help meant the world to me!
[gasps]
Oh, Master Matsuba!
I'm so glad to see you again.
Last night, I fell of
the Kuukaku-maru.
[AOI]
Huh?
The Kuukaku-maru ?
That's one of our
inn's airships.
The master arranged
an excursion on it last night,
as an apology
for the commotion,
and the way
the staff handled it.
Airship excursion?
[gasps]
[MATSUBA] I had a little
too much to drink,
and the sway of the ship
made matters a bit worse.
So, like an old,
bumbling idiot,
I fell right off
the side of the vessel.
[thud]
Aoi,
like an angel,
you took care of me
when you found me
on the ground,
and were even gracious enough
to cook me a meal.
For that, I became
quite fond of you.
And so, sweet Aoi,
I would like you
to take this gift.
[AOI]
A leaf?
[ALL]
What?!
Uh...
[AOI]
Why the shock?
Even he's flabbergasted!
Is this thing
really that valuable?
This is the tengu's
most treasured fan,
that I told you
about last night.
By rights, it belonged to Shiro.
Oh...
You sure about this?
Judging by the reaction
in the room,
that fan's incredibly precious.
I'm certain. Please take it.
[ALL gasp]
[AOI gasps]
[MATSUBA]
Now, for more important matters.
I've heard that you're here
as collateral
for Shiro's unpaid debt.
You poor little thing.
Rather than work
in some damn inn,
you should come live
on Mt. Shumon.
[gasps]
[AOI]
Mt. Shumon?
Yes. That's where
the tengu live.
I'm happy to pay off your debt.
And if you'd like,
you can marry one of my sons.
Uh...
[ALL gasp]
Master Matsuba.
[GINJI] She cannot do that.
I'm very sorry.
[gasps]
Why is that, Nine-Tail?
Because, you see,
Aoi is already promised
to someone else.
Tenjin-ya's Master Innkeeper.
[AKATSUKI]
Hmph.
Uh! You call her your fiancé,
and yet, you relegate her
to a shed out back!
That's an awful way
to treat your betrothed!
Shiro's granddaughter might
as well be my own granddaughter.
Aoi, come live with us.
[GINJI gasps]
I'm so sorry,
but I just can't do that.
Uh. Why can't you?
Your friend, Shiro Tsubaki,
was my grandfather.
So, it's my obligation
to make whatever trouble
he caused right again.
--[MATSUBA] Uh...
--And besides,
I made a promise to that ogre
that I would stay
and work off the debt myself.
I can't just go and break
that promise now.
Even though he'd probably prefer
that you pay off
the debt for me right away,
and save him the headache
of a human on staff.
[O-RYO]
Hmph!
And I'm sorry,
but I can't accept
this fan, either.
[MATSUBA] No, the least
you can do is take that.
If you do mean
to take on Shiro's debts,
then it's yours, as well,
since I made a promise
to give that fan to him.
You inherited that
promise when he passed.
I guess so.
Then I accept this fan
with the utmost gratitude.
[MATSUBA]
Good.
I wonder what it's used for.
Oh! It might look cool to lay
as a setting under my dishes!
[GINJI chuckles]
Ogre-god?
[MASTER] Yes, what is it,
Master Matsuba?
If Aoi is indeed your fiancé,
then you must
take better care of her.
I am aware of the history
between you and Shiro.
[AOI gasps]
[MATSUBA] But, his
granddaughter is not to blame.
Don't treat her poorly.
What?
But, I have no recollection
of treating her poorly, sir.
[MATSUBA]
Okay, play dumb.
Well, then...
I will forget
yesterday's mishap,
since Aoi's delicious food
made up for them.
We sincerely appreciate it.
We tengu got a bit
carried away, too.
Dear Aoi,
eating your scrumptious food
lifted my spirits,
and gave me such energy!
You should open up a little
restaurant in that place.
I'll be a repeat patron!
Indeed!
Master Matsuba is
right on the money with that!
Like I said, too,
you could have
a successful eatery
in that building!
Just hold on, Ginji.
And, Master Matsuba--
Don't be ridiculous!
She's a human girl!
I cannot accept this idea.
[MASTER]
One moment.
I'm the one who has
the final say here,
but now's not the time for that.
[AOI, GINJI sigh]
[MASTER]
Master Matsuba,
thank you kindly for your stay.
We appreciate your generosity.
We look forward to your
next visit very much, sir.
Very well, then.
[KASUGA]
You're awesome!
Seriously!
You got Tenjin-ya
out of trouble!
[AOI]
Hmm?
When Master Matsuba
vanished last night,
all the tengu were so angry!
And everyone here was saying
our relationship with them
--was ruined!
--[AOI gasps]
Hi! I'm Kasuga,
a shapeshifting tanuki.
Oh! Nice to meet you.
I'm Aoi Tsubaki.
Yeah, I know that.
Oh, hey! I wanna try
your famous cooking!
Uh...
[KASUGA]
I mean, even Master Matsuba
spoke highly of your food!
He said that it gave him energy!
That's awesome!
I definitely wanna try it!
[AOI]
Uh...
Heh. Uh!
[KASUGA gasps]
'Scuse me.
What is it?
I do wanna open
my own restaurant
in the annex building.
I think there are
a lot of people
who would wanna eat my food.
Maybe you should
give them that chance.
I just wanna repay
my grandfather's debt on my own.
Please let me.
--[MASTER] Come.
--[AOI gasps]
[gasps]
Wow! No way! We're flying!
This is the hidden realm?
[MASTER] It's not going
to be an easy task.
A human has never run
a restaurant for ayakashi
in the hidden realm before.
I'm determined to work hard.
Please let me do it.
Very well, then.
You can give it a try.
Thanks!
[CHIBI]
What? Aoi?
Are you starting your own
restaurant in the hidden realm?
You can't give cucumber pieces
to anyone else but me,
you got that?