[MEI]
Master Ranmaru.
There's something
that we need to ask.
Yes, what is it? By the look
of you all, it's serious.
Please allow me to cook them.
The dishes of ocean treasure.
[gasps]
I was afraid.
When Raiju sealed my
sense of taste away,
I had lost my most
important asset,
and my primary means of
surviving in the hidden realm.
So, I couldn't help it.
I felt powerless, set
adrift with no purpose.
Then there was the fear I'd get
eaten by some hungry ayakashi.
But, it turns out I was wrong.
Even if my taste buds happen
to be useless at the moment,
I've still got helpers
I know I can depend on.
Kai, the black crane,
and Mei, the white crane.
And, I've got Ginji, too.
I refuse to run.
I'll face this.
Well, Aoi.
I can attest to the fact that
losing your sense of taste
has had no effect on
the quality of your food.
I'm certain you can handle this.
Thanks, Ginji.
Ranmaru. I think
it's worth noting
that Princess Iso put
this task in Aoi's hands.
It's not like you to question
the princess' instructions,
and you've never had cause
to doubt her before, right?
Do you understand the stakes?
You cannot afford to fail.
Yes.
Then you shall cook the
dishes of ocean treasure.
By the power given to me
as Hachiyo of this land,
that is an order.
[ALL gasp]
[AOI]
Thanks, guys.
I owe it all to you two.
If you hadn't talked
to me this morning,
I wouldn't have had
the courage to ask.
[BOTH] We both want you to cook
the dishes of ocean treasure.
I can't.
We know you're scared.
If we'd lost our
sense of taste...
...I'm sure we'd
feel the same way,
and we'd stop cooking
for customers, too.
But, still.
[MEI, KAI] We think you're a
better chef than both of us,
and we don't want you
to let this stop you.
[gasps]
Wow.
I'm so touched.
You'll be our fearless
leader in the kitchen.
But we'll be with you
every step of the way.
And we can check the taste
when you're not sure.
[MEI, KAI]
Don't worry, it'll be just fine!
[AOI]
Thanks for believing in me.
We'll make the meal
a success, no doubt!
It's a way to get
Ginji home, too.
To take him back to
Tenjin-ya with you when you go.
Isn't it?
That is an added bonus, for
sure, but not the whole reason.
[MEI, KAI]
Uh?
Even though I may
have been brought
to the southern land by force,
ever since then, I've become
really fond of this place.
But especially
the ayakashi here.
That's the main reason.
I don't want anyone to suffer,
but I certainly don't want my
friends to endure hardships.
And I'd do anything I
could to help them.
[AOI] If the ceremony fails,
the southern land
will be visited by
awful calamities.
But I won't let that happen.
I will make the
ceremony a success,
no matter what it takes!
[MEI, KAI]
All right!
[footsteps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[TAICHI]
Master Ranmaru!
Master Hideyoshi requests
your presence at once!
[ALL]
Huh?
It's the umi-bouzu! Get ready!
So, it is.
[HIDEYOSHI]
Master.
I can't believe it's
been a hundred years.
[barks]
Is the umi-bouzu
finally showing up?
It certainly seems that way.
I understand that
it's still early,
but go and start the fireworks.
Yes, Sir!
The fireworks display
has a function.
It helps to guide the umi-bouzu,
and lets him know we're ready
for the ceremony to take
place on Jouno island.
So, that's the point of
making such a grand display?
[NENE]
Master Ranmaru!
[HATORI]
There's trouble!
Uh?
[BOTH panting]
What is it?
We're being inundated by
an insane number of guests!
The staff can't keep up!
Airships are swarming
us like locusts, too!
There's no way we can start
the fireworks like this!
[gasps]
[NENE] I heard Raiju was
promoting the ceremony in Youto,
but this is crazy!
He told folks this
year's event would be
even more spectacular
than usual.
Damn. That scoundrel means
to sabotage us again.
For such an old ayakashi,
he's really childish.
Yeah, and, true to form,
he's using a classic
confusion technique.
How should we handle this,
Master Ranmaru?
Well...
[barks]
Look! Up there!
[BOTH gasping]
Is that the Tenjin-maru?
Hold on, why are there
so many of them?
It's crazy!
What is going on?
[RANMARU grunts]
[gasps]
What? Why's the master here?
[MASTER]
Well, ladies and gentlemen.
What a pleasure.
[RANMARU grunts]
[HIDEYOSHI]
Curse you, Tenjin-ya!
We don't have time to fight
with you now. Go home!
[MASTER]
Yes, we will, in a moment.
But first, I've a burning
question for you:
did you obtain the gem branch?
If so, you must return my
employees to me at once,
as promised.
Hold on just a second, Master!
Oh, hello, Aoi, I haven't seen
you since you were abducted,
but I heard that Raiju sealed
off your sense of taste.
You poor dear,
and you look exhausted.
[gasps]
Okay, Master. You are
terrible at playing dumb.
Just seeing me is causing you to
tremble with emotion, isn't it?
No, that's 'cause I'm confused.
[laughs]
It's not funny! Stop!
Master...
I'm grateful you came to get us,
but we can't come back yet.
There's something we
have to do here first.
Is that so?
I'm going to cook the dishes of
ocean treasure for the ceremony.
I made a promise, and I
have to follow through,
as a favor to Princess Iso.
And also for Ranmaru!
[RANMARU gasps]
What are you doing?
If you're able to spare her,
I'd like Aoi's help
for just one more day.
[MASTER]
Oh?
I must say, this request
surprises me.
If I agree, will you
allow all of Tenjin-ya
to remain here for the event?
[RANMARU]
Huh?
Because of all the attention
this ceremony has been
getting in Youto
lately, it's natural
that all Tenjin-ya's customers
wanted to witness it.
Therefore, in order to cope
with the exodus of our guests.
We decided to bring
them in our fleet,
which has room to house them,
and we brought our
entire staff, as well.
If you are open to the idea,
we would like to propose
that our inns do business
together, just for today.
Us? Do business together?
[MASTER] And besides,
isn't it infuriating?
That those big shots in Youto
get to relish the drama and
chaos they've caused?
They do say the enemy of
one's enemy is his friend.
The consensus is
that our two inns
will forever be in
bitter competition.
We could work together
and give them a shock.
I think the idea sounds
exhilarating, don't you?
Ha. So, in other words,
we let your fleet anchor
here for the ceremony,
and in return, Tenjin-ya
will lend its staff.
Is that a fair assumption?
Indeed. That's the
deal I propose.
Also, we can provide
ships, if need be.
Yes, that'd be helpful!
Master Ranmaru,
how do you feel about it?
I trust you, Hideyoshi, so
do what you think is best.
Right. Thank you very much, sir.
I only ask that you
move the vessels.
Guide their course
to a safe place.
At the moment, their position
would interfere with
the fireworks.
Please, leave that part to me.
I'll take care of it.
By all means.
Miss O-Ryo, would you be willing
to assist me and my staff?
You really want to work with me?
We have way too
many guests here.
To tell you the truth, I would
be honored to have your support.
I suppose I could give
you a hand this evening.
Our room attendants are
spectacular, you know.
I'm glad to have them.
Great!
Then leave the fireworks
event to us, Master Ranmaru.
[barks]
All right, then. We'll make this
our greatest ceremony yet.
Let's go!
[MASTER]
Aoi?
[gasps]
What's this?
A token of my good wishes,
just in case you
find yourself in need.
I'm grateful for all you
do for me, Master.
Just do your best, yeah?
Don't trouble yourself
with anything but that.
Yep, you can bet on it!
Thank you, again!
[AOI] That's right,
all I can do is my best!
--[MEI, KAI] Ooh...
--Breathtaking!
You both look incredible!
I feel a little vulnerable.
But this is the purpose
of my female form.
I use it just for the ceremony.
Wow, I had no idea!
I've something for you.
[gasps]
[RANMARU]
You may have this back.
[gasps] You're giving
it back to me?
[RANMARU]
Hmph.
One last thing. Take this.
Take what?
Hey! My old kimono!
[CHIBI] That's the one you
wear to work at Moonflower!
The master had this custom
made specifically for you
to wear while you're
cooking tonight.
He must've known that
you'd be preparing
the dishes of ocean treasure,
even before we found out.
[gasps]
I know that you're taking on
an enormous responsibility
in doing this work
for the ceremony,
but I hope you can think of it
as just like being in the
kitchen at Moonflower.
Thanks, Ginji.
And yes. Agreed.
It'll be best for
everyone involved
if I don't overthink it.
Princess Iso did tell me that
the umi-bouzu had become
bored with the food
from the hidden realm
and craved something new.
So all I have to do
is cook what I like,
and the rest will
take care of itself.
There's no need to do
anything beyond that.
Exactly right.
Your food will be new to him,
but with familiar elements
that he'll find appealing,
there's no doubt in my mind.
That's your specialty, you know?
The whole reason
Moonflower was a hit.
For sure!
[RANMARU]
Hey!
[gasps]
[RANMARU]
We're approaching Jouno Island.
This is where we'll
host the umi-bouzu
for the duration of
tonight's event.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
[AOI inhales]
[AOI]
Just like cooking at Moonflower.
My home restaurant.
Now! Time to entertain!
[GINJI] Guided here by the
light from the fireworks,
the umi-bouzu will land
there, on the beach.
Then, he'll come in
past the tori gate
and follow the path to
the main building.
The structure facing that
is the kagura hall.
There's a stage there,
which is where Ranmaru and I
will dance the night kagura,
and the umi-bouzu
will watch us perform
from the main building.
I think I can picture all that.
So, he'll enjoy
the liquor and food
while you and Ranmaru
are dancing?
[GINJI]
Yes.
And then, once the
night kagura's over,
he'll return to the ocean,
to disappear for
another century.
[GINJI] Here it is, the main
building, where you'll cook.
[ALL gasping]
[KAI] All the treasures
for the ceremony.
[MEI] So, is the umi-bouzu going
to take these things with him?
No, for some reason he
never brings the treasure
back to the ocean, but he always
drinks the secret liquor.
Then what's the point of taking
the time to collect this stuff?
[GINJI]
Apparently, the important thing
to the umi-bouzu is the
simple act of offering.
To be honest, most of
this makes zero sense.
[KAI] That's the kagura hall
over there, isn't it?
[MEI] Will he have to watch the
dancing through the screen?
[GINJI]
That's right.
That means I'll have to serve
him the food from outside?
Yes, you just raise
the screen a little bit,
slide the dishes under it,
and he'll take them.
No one really understands
who the umi-bouzu is,
or why this ceremony is the
one thing that stands between
the southern land and
utter catastrophe.
[BOTH] No one understands
why we do this?
But, the most important
thing to remember
is that you must never pull the
screen more than you have to,
and never, ever look
upon the umi-bouzu.
Legend has it misfortune will
befall anyone who sees him,
so avoid that, at all costs.
That lore's been passed
down from ancient times.
'Kay.
And this is where you'll
be preparing the food.
[KAI]
The kitchen itself is old.
But the equipment's new!
Yeah!
Well, they brought the supplies.
Everything I asked for!
[CHIBI]
Cucumbers!
Wow, they smell so
fresh and delicious!
[AOI laughs]
Here, you deserve a treat!
Yummy, thanks so much, Aoi!
Om nom nom nom nom.
The night kagura's
supposed to begin
precisely at the
stroke of midnight.
As soon as the umi-bouzu lands
and gets settled in
the main building,
that's when you'll bring
the food, appetizers first.
But, we're not
allowed to see him.
How will we know when he's
ready for the first course
if we can't even take a peek?
[GINJI] Watch above the building
for an ayakashi fire.
That's the signal to start.
Well, that's good
to know, thanks.
All right, Ginji, the moment
of truth has arrived at last.
Ready to head up to the stage?
Mm. Yes.
Good luck to you Aoi,
and if you have any final
preparations to make,
now's the time to finish
those and stand by.
Okay, just a couple little
touches and I'll be ready, too.
I'm counting on you.
Right, see you on
the other side!
[AOI]
Thanks for your help, Ginji.
Well, friends, whaddaya say?
Are you ready to make
this meal a success?
I'll leave you two in
charge of the appetizers.
[KAI]
Sounds good!
[MEI] We'll cook them exactly
like we'd planned.
[AOI]
Perfect, then I'll take care
of the final preparations
for dessert!
For just one meal, there sure
is a lot to take care of!
It all feels like a gamble.
Yeah. This is new territory.
But we're the ones
who agreed to do this!
[AOI, MEI, KAI]
Heh!
Yay!
[GINJI]
This is it.
Here comes the umi-bouzu.
There he is!
Uh. He's... enormous.
[ALL gasp]
Everyone! Go to
your posts at once!
The umi-bouzu has
arrived on land!
[music plays]
The night kagura.
It's starting now.
The umi-bouzu's coming.
Time to see what we're made of.
[gasps]
He's already entered
the main building.
Okay, I'll go ahead and bring
out the appetizers, I guess.
[MEI, KAI]
Good luck!
Thanks, guys!
[AOI]
Don't be nervous.
Don't be nervous!
There's hot, simmered
pumpkin and bacon,
cold hors d'oeuvres made of raw
tofu skin and sea urchin,
and special squid shumai.
[AOI]
It's all gonna be okay.
I know it.
I have no doubt the
umi-bouzu will like these.
[gasps]
They're so lovely. Uh!
Hello, I've brought you
some appetizers.
[gasps]
[AOI] How strange.
His hand is so tiny.
Uh. Pardon, here's
a menu for you.
[AOI]
If you wouldn't mind,
please choose what
you'd like next.
Letting the umi-bouzu pick
what he wants to eat
is a good idea, huh?
Yeah, only Aoi could come
up with a plan like that.
[AOI] Getting to choose what
they want to eat is enough
to make anyone feel
like royalty, right?
So, I think I'll give
him a few options
and prepare the one he picks.
I can't imagine anyone's
ever thought to try that
for the ceremony before.
But I think it's great,
the umi-bouzu's gonna love it!
[AOI]
Uh?
Huh. Interesting.
Okay. The stir-friend shrimp
in miso-mayo
paste is tasty.
I'll have it right out.
I've got a surprise, friends--
he ordered the
stir-fried shrimp!
That's unexpected!
I thought for sure he'd
go for the kiseki beef.
[AOI]
Yeah, I did, too!
It's a good thing we
let him choose, right?
Looks like your strategy
is really paying off!
Yep! Okay, let's make the best
stir-fried shrimp in
miso-mayo paste ever!
[AOI laughs]
[AOI]
Thank you for your patience.
Here's your stir-fried shrimp
in miso-mayo paste!
We hope you like
the shrimp's texture,
and the mellow
profile of the dish.
Here it is.
[CHIBI] Mmmm!
I think I smell cucumber!
[gasps]
[CHIBI grunts]
[AOI gasping]
[RANMARU, GINJI gasp]
[RANMARU]
U-Uh...
[GINJI]
Uh...
[AOI] No, no, no, no, no!
What do I do?
Chibi! Come back now!
[CHIBI] Oh. So, you must
be the umi-bouzu, huh?
[AOI] Please, no!
Chibi's asking something!
[CHIBI]
Can I have a bite?
Some cucumber
with the mellow mayo!
It looks yummy!
[AOI] If I don't act fast,
everything will be ruined!
[CHIBI]
Thank you very much!
Om nom nom nom nom nom nom.
[AOI] Sounds like he shared
the cucumber, at least.
[CHIBI laughing]
Stop tickling my belly!
I'm trying to eat,
don't tickle me!
[AOI] He's tickling Chibi?
What is going on? What do I do?
I can't just let this continue!
Chibi! Time to come out!
[CHIBI screams]
Umi-bouzu!
What's the matter with you?
Sir? May I be of assistance?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[AOI screams]
[CHIBI] The ceremony has
gotten underway at last!
What? Mister Umi-bouzu,
what's with that sad face?
Aoi! You'd better do
your very best tonight,
for everyone's sake!