[AOI]
Smells so good!
Yes. I love that scent.
[BYAKUYA]
Pardon.
Does Aoi happen to be awake--
[gasps]
[BYAKUYA] Thank you for
making the anniversary dinner
an indisputable success.
The Royal Couple was full
of compliments for you.
It was my pleasure, sir.
And have you made
a full recovery?
Yes. I'm back up to 100%.
Moonflower reopens
tomorrow, thankfully.
Excellent.
Right, then.
Keep up the good work.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir!
Just a moment, Byakuya.
--Here. Take these.
--What are they?
Buttered croissant rolls.
Please share them with
the little ones, too!
--[BYAKUYA sputters]
--[AOI giggles]
Oh, ah, Ginji, a word?
[GINJI]
Yes?
Men from Orio-ya were
at the Imperial Court.
[GINJI gasps]
That's roused my suspicion
that they were somehow involved
in Aoi's kidnapping.
What? Oh, no.
I guess that will have to do.
[RITSUKO] Ah, what lovely
Tanabata decorations!
[AOI]
Mistress Ritsuko!
[RITSUKO]
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to the
Tanabata festival tomorrow!
Excuse me, Mistress Ritsuko?
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you all goodbye.
I collapsed after
I served you dessert.
I know, dear, Byakuya
told us what happened.
I hope you didn't overwork
yourself on our account.
In fact, I came to
express my gratitude.
Please accept this gift.
Go on, open it.
[AOI]
What is this?
A hagoromo .
At the Imperial Court
in the capital,
all of the women
wear these.
I can't accept a gift
this nice!
I insist.
It's a token of thanks
for reminding me
of the flavors of my home.
And all while feeling ill.
It must have been
quite difficult for you.
Trust me, I know how
it feels for someone
to make an attempt
on your life.
Mistress, may I ask you.
What made you marry someone
from this realm?
Oh, my.
What a question.
At the time Nui and I
got married,
the whole apparent realm
was at war.
[RITSUKO]
I was in school then,
in a town far away
from my parents
and everything I'd ever known.
They were back home in Nagasaki.
I adored books,
so, I went to a local
bookstore every day.
That little shop is
where I met Nuinoin,
who was visiting the apparent
realm incognito.
[RITSUKO] We found ourselves
spending a lot of time together,
talking about literature.
Soon, it was clear
we had fallen in love.
[RITSUKO]
Then, one day,
Nuinoin disappeared suddenly,
without a word of goodbye,
much less an explanation.
Soon after he left me--
one hot, late summer day,
my family and the rest
of my hometown
were reduced
to dust and ash.
[RITSUKO]
But I wasn't alone for long.
Around that time,
Nuinoin returned
to the apparent realm.
[RITSUKO]
He had come for me.
To bring me to another world,
and take care of me
for the rest of his life.
So that's my answer.
That's how I married someone
from the hidden realm.
Do you ever have
regrets about it?
No.
There have been some
tough times, of course,
but with Nui,
I've no regrets.
He's kept his promise
to stay by my side,
and I know he'll keep it
for the rest of his life.
As a matter of fact,
Nui alters his appearance
to match mine,
since we age differently.
Huh?
Ayakashi aren't like us;
they have a much longer life
expectancy than humans do.
But not to worry.
We have more longevity here than
we do in the apparent realm.
Huh? What's that mean?
There's something
about the food
in the hidden realm
that changes us.
I don't know how
it works, exactly,
but the more we eat,
the more like ayakashi
we become.
No way! And here I've been,
binge-eating hidden realm
food this entire time!
Nevertheless,
at the end of the day,
we are still human.
And the fact remains,
people die much younger
than ayakashi.
This is the inevitable truth
we and ayakashi must
accept when we intermarry.
You'll be fine.
Whoa, back up a bit.
It's not like I've
made up my mind yet.
Maybe I won't marry the master.
Ha, ha. Oh, yes, I forgot.
But one never truly knows
what the future will hold.
In any case,
preparation is still
the key to success.
This hagoromo does
a great deal to conceal
the enormous vulnerability
that comes with being human.
It has that power?
Listen, Aoi.
If you do become the wife
of a great yokai one day,
promise me that you'll
show no weakness
to malicious ayakashi
who would do you harm.
Come.
[AOI laughs]
Gorgeous!
This particular shawl
is the Seven Stars Hagoromo,
and its colors change
depending on the season.
[AOI]
Fascinating!
I hope you will use it someday.
Yes. It's an honor
to accept it.
Thank you, miss.
The somen noodles were great.
I appreciate that, sir!
Please enjoy the festival!
[AOI gasps]
Stunning!
It's nice to remember
to look up at the stars
every once in a while.
[MASTER]
Aoi.
Uh?
Oh, um, hi, Master.
What brings you here?
[MASTER]
Nothing.
Honestly, I just wanted
to see your face.
Oh, yeah?
Well, is it okay
that you're here
while everyone else
works their tails off?
Not that it matters,
but all the events
have concluded
without a single misstep.
Now, then.
I simply must eat somen noodles
while gazing up
at the Milky Way,
or my Tanabata
won't be complete.
All right! Coming right up.
[AOI]
Thanks for waiting.
Thank you, Aoi.
I am ravenous tonight.
But I was under
the impression
that ayakashi could survive
for a month or so without food.
Can't they?
Aoi.
Do you really think
that I only eat enough
to barely keep myself alive?
Uh, no, please,
eat as much as you want!
Heh.
Hey, I have a question for you.
What's that?
[AOI] You were the one
who rescued me, right?
From the underground storeroom?
I realized that I never
expressed my gratitude
to you for that.
So, thank you.
That's nice of you,
but all I did was save
my lovely bride.
Anyone would have done the same.
I'm not gonna
correct you this time.
[bell tinkles]
I sure seem to need
saving by ayakashi a lot--
it's embarrassing.
[MASTER] You mean you get
targeted by ayakashi a lot?
Yeah, I have been, but still.
[AOI] I wonder what
the master would say
if I asked him
about that memory.
Um, hey.
I love somen noodles.
I could eat them all
the time, I think.
They're tasty, Aoi.
You just boil 'em.
Anyone can make those ya know.
It's not just that,
and you know it.
Customers notice the details,
even when you think
they're trivial.
I'm getting drowsy.
I guess I'll just sleep
in this room tonight, Aoi.
Oh, no, you will not!
This is where I'm sleeping!
My point exactly.
I'll have much
better dreams tonight
if I sleep with my pretty
young bride in my arms.
I'll push you off the futon
before you get the chance.
[AOI grunting]
[groans]
He's too heavy for me.
What I put up with...
Although Aoi,
one never knows
what the future holds.
I wonder.
Will I marry the master?
Mm-mm.
I refuse to let that happen.
I hope Hikoboshi
and Orihime met tonight.
Sleep well, Master.
Have sweet dreams.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Here, eat this.
[gasps]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Does it taste good?
Yeah. It's so yummy.
[AOI crying softly]
[AOI] Don't leave!
You're going away already?
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] I won't be
coming back here ever again,
because from now on,
there will be no need.
Please stay here,
or take me.
Can I come?
We will meet again one day,
when you become an adult.
[gasps]
Why do I keep
having that same dream?
[O-RYO, KASUGA laughing]
So good!
Bread is the best ever!
So even though
Moonflower's closed today,
you were up baking
for the rest of us?
I baked way too much,
so don't be shy,
go ahead and eat your fill!
--[KASUGA] I love bread!
--[GINJI] Who doesn't?
Hey, uh, Sasuke,
don't you want some bread?
No thanks. I'm not
really a fan of it.
Oh, no, that's disappointing.
And this is my best batch.
Oh, then I guess
I'll try it.
My word!
What an incredible taste!
So, bread is actually good?
This is completely different
than the bread Shiro
gave me all those years ago.
The gross bread
my grandpa gave you,
how would you describe
its flavor?
It was kinda dry,
and very bland, and hard, too.
I would have choked if I had
eaten it without any water.
Sounds like Grandpa
gave you hardtack.
By the way, Aoi,
you seem in even higher spirits
than usual today.
Oh! You can tell?
Well, here's why.
I've got a guest room
for the night.
I'm trying Chief Chef's
full-course dinner!
Wow, that's so amazing!
[O-RYO]
Now I see.
I've been wondering
what all the fuss was about.
Akatski's mad that
it's happening the day
of the master's trip
to the apparent realm.
Oh, I didn't even know
the master was planning to go.
What for?
The master sometimes
works in the different realms,
including the apparent one.
I'm not sure what
he's doing this time.
Ah, I see. Interesting.
[UME]
All right!
Are you ready to go,
Mistress Aoi?
We can't wait!
We're so excited!
What are you even
doing here,
you weren't supposed
to tag along!
Why not? I'm your cute
devoted follower.
And like any good
follower should,
I accompany you everywhere,
to act as your mascot
and source of comfort,
should you ever need it!
Now, it's time to get
ourselves some pampering, Aoi!
Okay, okay.
[ALL]
Welcome, Madam!
Tenjin-ya is now
at your service.
Wow.
Allow me to take
your shoes, Miss.
Uh. Are you new?
Ah. I'm Chiaki,
shapeshifting tanuki
and shoe porter.
I have heard quite
a lot about you, Miss Aoi.
[AOI]
A shapeshifting tanuki?
You mean like Kasuga?
Heh. Yeah, I guess you could say
that Kasuga and I
are distant cousins.
Ah, nice.
Follow me to the front desk.
Welcome to Tenjin-ya,
Miss Tsubaki.
If you wouldn't mind, please
sign your name in the register.
Okay, weird, though.
If I can swallow
my pride and smile
for this charade, so can you.
[AOI grumbles]
Here ya go.
Thank you.
All right, here's the key
to your suite, miss.
If you should need
anything at all,
please don't hesitate
to pick up the phone
and dial the front desk
for assistance.
[KASUGA]
This is your room, Miss Aoi.
[laughs]
[AOI]
How lovely!
Okay then.
The main bath is open,
so feel free to head that way
and have a soak if you wish.
Do you need anything else now?
No, thank you.
I didn't bring a hair tie.
What now?
--[AOI] Hmm?
--Um, good evening,
Miss Aoi.
Ah, are you
the bath caretaker, then?
Yes, I'm Shizuna.
If you'd like to,
please use this hair tie.
Are you sure about that?
It's yours, after all.
Indeed, but I don't
mind sharing it.
Really?
Well, in that case, I accept.
Thanks so much.
--[CHIBI sighs]
--This feels amazing.
The water seems a bit denser
than usual, huh.
--[door opens]
--Huh?
Pardon, miss.
If you'll allow me
just a moment,
today's bath theme
is "summer citrus."
[AOI]
Huh.
Heh! Great!
Sweet Citrus Bath Enchantment.
It does smell
sweet and citrusy.
Did you do something
special to it?
Yes, an enchantment.
[AOI]
Oh, like, magic?
Exactly right,
a special ayakashi technique.
Wow, cool!
So, are you, like some kind
of witch or something?
[SHIZUNA]
Huh? What?
A witch?
What am I even talking about?
[SHIZUNA]
Uh. Um... Miss Aoi?
Huh?
I, um...
I just wanted to apologize.
[AOI]
Uh?
That day, when you
first came here,
and you asked me if you
could work in the baths--
I turned you down
and I feel terrible.
It's been on my mind,
I'm sorry.
Listen, don't worry about it.
I found work, and in
my own restaurant, to boot.
Oh, hey, you'll have
to come eat there some time.
It'll be on the house.
That means so much to me!
[AOI]
Hmm?
Master, what are you doing here?
Welcome back, Aoi. Oh, my.
You look lovely.
Jeez, how did you
get into my room?
I just thought we could
share it, sleep together.
Yeah, I don't think so.
--[MASTER sniffs]
--Hey.
What're you doing?
I thought I smelled
sweet summer citrus.
Have you been to the baths?
I have. Shizuna used an
enchantment in the water!
She is quite
a talented caretaker.
Her abilities are exceptional.
Many of our guests
delight in her.
They come to Tenjin-ya to enjoy
special enchantment techniques.
Oh, wow.
And he hasn't
even eaten yet! So...
...you know he must be tired.
Perhaps we should
just let him sleep?
Done!
[snoring]
--[door opens]
--[KIKUNO] Excuse me.
I'm here to begin
dinner service.
Oh, yay!
[KIKUNO] Here is this evening's
menu, sir and madam.
It's finally here!
I get to eat
the full-course dinner!
[MASTER]
Calm down, Aoi.
[laughs]
[AOI]
What a lovely, seasonal menu!
Those are dishes
our Chief Chef
has guarded for years.
So, let the feasting begin.
[AOI]
Yeah!
But first, an aperitif.
--[AOI] Uh...
--What's wrong?
I've never actually tasted
alcohol, just so you know.
You scared?
My grandpa had what
you might call a problem.
[MASTER scoffs]
Look, I don't think one
sip of a Kabosu cocktail
could lead to anything
too dangerous.
Anyway, in the event
that something did,
I am your future husband.
I'll still accept you
exactly as you are.
You're such a gentleman.
Hmm.
[clinking]
Verdict?
Good. It's easier to drink
than I had thought.
It tastes like juice.
Kabosu cocktails
are delicious.
Congratulations
on your drinking debut.
Now, let's eat, shall we?
You bet!
[KIKUNO]
Enjoy the first course.
It's lightly sweet,
and very tasty!
This dish is our
corn tempura.
The Chief Chef takes great pride
in that creation.
[AOI] I'm impressed that he can
make tempura from the kernels!
And he doesn't even
pop them, either!
Do you think he'd teach me
how he does it?
Perhaps.
It wouldn't hurt for you to ask.
But don't be surprised
if he says it's a trade secret.
[KIKUNO] And here we have
the sashimi du jour.
Uh, but it's still moving.
Oh, that's right,
we got a fresh
Red Snapper catch today.
[giggles]
So good! Wow!
The vegetables
are sweet, too!
[cries]
We're almost at the end
of this lovely dinner.
But I'm so full and happy!
[MASTER]
Really?
But we haven't had
the fruit course yet.
There's always room
for sweets!
Heh. I'm glad to hear it.
Wow. They're so pretty!
I can't even imagine
how the Chief Chef made them.
He's famous for
his special fruit dessert.
Mm! Even better than I thought!
[snoring]
[AOI sighs]
So, did you
enjoy the meal, Aoi?
Yeah. I can tell the Chief
Chef takes great care
and pride in his cooking.
I'm going to make it a point
to let other people
cook for me more.
It's such a great way
to expand my horizons
and get ideas
for new dishes.
I feel so inspired to get back
to Moonflower and cook!
As usual, you don't
hide your feelings.
I'm grateful that I had
this chance to eat with you.
Headed to the apparent realm?
Oh. I guess you heard, then?
Does that mean
you're going to miss me?
I won't. Not really.
Why so cold?
And after the delightful meal
we just shared, too.
It's only dinner,
it doesn't mean I'll miss you.
Aoi, here. Please take it.
Oh, what's this?
[MASTER]
A way of corresponding.
If you write a message here,
I'll receive it on my end.
I have one, too.
It's a bit like what you do
in the apparent realm.
"Exchanging emails,"
I believe it's called?
Oh.
I didn't know
this realm needed that.
Please us it if there are any
problems while I'm gone.
Whatever will happen
to me this time?
I'm just joking.
Yes, I'll definitely contact you
if anything weird happens.
[GINJI]
Excuse the interruption, Master.
They're almost ready to depart.
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'd like to come see you off.
Stay here. You should
take it easy, if you like.
No, it's fine. I'll go.
I mean, I am an official
employee of Tenjin-ya,
after all.
That's true.
All right, Ginji,
I leave Tenjin-ya
in the care of
your capable hands.
Yes. I'll do my best.
[MASTER]
Aoi, I'm going now.
Try not to do anything reckless.
I'll do my best.
And also...
Take care of everyone here.
Huh? Sure.
Hey, Master!
When you get back, I'll cook
something for you, 'kay?
So, be thinking about
what you want to eat
and I'll make it.
[sighs]
[GINJI] Looks like they made
it across Iwato just fine.
So, Ginji?
How long do you think the
Master'll be away on this trip?
Five or six days,
I think, give or take.
It's going to be that long?
[GINJI]
Why, will you miss him?
Huh? What?
No, I'm just curious.
And I imagine that things can
get rough when he's not here.
Oh, Aoi.
You're not being honest
with yourself.
Come on, like I said,
I was just--
[CHIAKI screams]
Oh, no! Ah, Young Master!
[BOTH]
Huh?
We have a problem.
I just saw him,
that awful man is here!
What "awful man"?
It's Hatori.
Orio-ya's front desk manager!
[grunts]
Orio-ya?
[barks]
[CHIBI] A bunch of
dangerous-looking ayakashi
just showed up!
And what's with that dog?
--He scares me!
--[dog barks]
[CHIBI whines]
It's licking me!
Please don't eat me!