[abaci clicking]
Chief of Accounting? I see.
[BYAKUYA]
Young Master.
[GINJI]
Yes, sir!
Here's a warning
for Moonflower.
Improve business,
or I'll shut it down.
--But, sir!
--Hold on!
I'm the one who asked to open
Moonflower in the first place.
I'm responsible--
[BYAKUYA]
Yes, as for you,
I suggest you marry
the master at once.
It seems that's
your only option.
[AOI grunts]
[sighs]
This is why I detest
human girls.
They lack any sort
of business acumen.
Huh?
You act unpredictably,
on impulse.
You are exactly like
your late grandfather.
Uh...
Shiro Tsubaki.
Just the sound of his name
makes me seethe with rage.
He brought nothing but
misfortune to Tenjin-ya.
Shameful.
[fan creaks]
[BYAKUYA] He'd treat other
guests to a round of alcohol
when he had no money.
He'd sneak into the kitchen
and help himself to food,
then he'd dance like a maniac,
and break our
sliding screens and doors.
Furthermore, he broke
a pot at the front desk
that was essentially
a national treasure!
[fan snaps]
[AOI]
Uh...
[panting]
[clears throat] Pardon.
Barring some miracle,
Moonflower will be closed.
So, if I were you,
I would get to work.
[BOTH sigh]
That man has no heart.
Just what you'd expect
from Captain Moneybags.
I can't believe we're
in danger of closing
when we were
just getting started.
We've got till the end
of the month,
so let's save Moonflower!
All right! I like
your spirit, Ginji!
[AOI]
But how can we save it?
I'm kind of at a loss.
Hey, Aoi! Are you busy?
If you're hungry,
look elsewhere.
I can't feed you
for free anymore!
[O-RYO]
That's harsh!
I was just helping you
with leftovers.
In fact, you should
be thanking me!
At least someone
was eating your food.
So rude.
Why is she always like this?
[O-RYO]
Anyway,
I have a small favor
to ask of you.
What now?
Make a bento for a customer?
He's a regular guest,
but he's kind of a nuisance.
Although he is quite
a popular novelist.
He writes columns
like this, as well.
He likes to stay at the inn
sometimes while he's working.
[AOI]
"Hakkabou's Diary." Interesting.
But lately, he hasn't been able
to make much progress with it.
So, to compensate,
he won't eat.
Oh, no.
If he collapses,
won't Tenjin-ya be held liable?
Exactly, so I thought
you could make him a bento
that nobody could resist.
But, if he's not able
to eat or write,
why would my bento
make any difference?
Look, this is your chance
to show off your skills!
I'm sure you can come up
with something
that will inspire this guy!
Yeah?
[AOI]
Mmm...
Oh, and he'll be here
for a week.
Pretty please?
Wait, what? For a whole week?
Mmm.
[AOI]
Hmm...
How are you supposed
to feed someone
when they see eating
as a chore?
This is like a puzzle.
Mmm?
[AOI] I guess it's gonna be
dead in here again today.
Uh?
[footsteps]
[AOI]
Hold on!
Master, wait for me!
[Master]
Hmm?
[panting]
Hi, Aoi.
Is something the matter?
You're getting soaked.
Oh, it's all right.
I just wanted to know
where you were going,
so I chased after you.
Mm?
You did?
Yeah...
Is something wrong with that?
[sigh] 'Course not.
I'm going up there.
Up the mountain?
I haven't had the chance
to see it yet.
Mind if I come with you?
Uh...
It'd be my pleasure.
Take a look over there.
Huh? [gasps]
Hot springs!
How nice!
Did you come up here in the rain
just to have a soak in them?
[laughing]
Why, did you wanna
get in with me?
'Scuse me?
That spring over there
is 90 degrees Celsius,
that one's 100,
and this is about 60 degrees.
Whoa, those are all way
too hot for humans. Scalding!
And why are they that strange,
reddish color?
The Vermilion Springs.
That's this place's
official name.
The water isn't poisonous,
though.
[bells ring]
[MASTER]
Oh, perfect timing.
[AOI]
Huh?
Oh, wow!
Are those eggs seriously
what I think they are?
What are you getting
so excited about?
Those are hot spring's eggs,
the most delicious things ever!
And these were actually made
in a real hot spring!
That's incredible!
That's quite an interesting
reaction to eggs.
What?
Uh...
[lights match]
[MASTER]
Aoi. Come over here.
[AOI]
Huh?
[gasps]
Sorry that I let you down.
I should've kept you dry.
Oh, um.
I didn't expect you to.
[gasps]
Well, why don't you
sit down, Master?
[MASTER]
Uh...
I said sit. Do it now.
Uh... Sure.
[AOI] Now it's my turn
to dry you off.
You're very conscientious, Aoi.
[AOI]
Mm... Uh...
Your horns are in the way.
Could you just take them off?
[MASTER]
That's mean of you to say.
My horns are what
make me an ogre.
[AOI gasps]
[AOI]
His kimono,
it's soaking wet.
He must've been
holding the umbrella
over me the entire time.
Uh!
Uh, what's wrong?
It just occurred to me
that I've never seen your face
from this angle before.
[gasps]
[AOI]
But,
I don't have the kind of face
that's worth staring at.
I'm grateful, Aoi.
[AOI]
You're very welcome.
[MASTER]
Shall we eat the eggs now?
[AOI]
Huh?
They're getting cold.
[MASTER]
Ah, I found it.
[AOI]
What is that?
I hope you like ramune.
Yeah! I didn't know
you had it here.
We use spring water.
It's naturally carbonated,
bottled at the source.
It's been popular here
for centuries.
Shall we see how the hot
spring eggs turned out today?
[tapping, egg cracks]
[AOI laughs]
[MASTER] Sprinkle a little bit
of salt on them.
I don't think I've ever had
ramune and hot spring eggs
together before. I can't wait!
[MASTER] That combination is
a summer treat in this area.
It won't be summer
for a few more weeks, though.
Ah!
Well, that's delicious!
Yes, indeed.
The flavors complement
each other perfectly!
[MASTER chuckles]
[MASTER]
I'm glad you enjoy it.
If you'd like to serve that
combination at Moonflower,
feel free to take
as much of both as you need.
Really? That's too kind.
Thank you!
[giggles]
Do you come up here often
to eat hot spring eggs
and drink ramune?
Yes, I do.
I consider this place
my own little private retreat.
Sometimes, when I want
to be alone,
I come up here
and get lost in the clouds.
That sounds nice.
I apologize
if I intruded on you.
No, it's all right.
Although I must say,
I was quite surprised by it.
[AOI]
Huh?
I didn't think
that you wanted...
Uh...
Never mind.
[grunts]
I relish these rare moments
when you and I get to be alone.
Uh...
I bet the kamaitchi
are out there somewhere,
keeping a sharp eye on us.
I don't think you can
really say that we're alone.
[MASTER]
I guess that's true.
Aoi...
How is Moonflower doing?
[AOI] Mmm...
Things are kind of rough.
Right now, at least.
[AOI]
But, I'm not giving up.
I'll keep trying.
I'm sure there are things
I can do to improve.
Wonderful.
Just don't push yourself
too hard.
You haven't been getting
much sleep, have you?
[AOI]
Huh?
I look out late at night,
and see your lights
are still on,
and you get up before the sun.
[AOI gasps]
[AOI]
You spy on me?
[MASTER]
Aoi...
I think Moonflower's secret
weapon could be its location.
Once you get the opportunity,
it could become
like a hidden gem.
Your food is delicious,
without question.
So, trust yourself and don't
feel pressure to rush success.
Take it one step at a time.
That helps, a lot.
Oh, you're so kind.
I've gotta say, you truly
are an extraordinary ogre.
Oh, am I the kind of ogre whom
you might consider marrying?
Never mind, I take back
everything I just said.
Right, no pressure,
take it one step a time.
No rush.
I will make that bento!
I wonder why he feels like
eating is such a hassle.
He uses his hands to write,
which means...
[humming]
Ah- ha, got it!
And finished.
This bento should allow him to
eat and write at the same time!
Mmm, I'll keep this in mind,
and do my best
for the whole week!
[O-RYO giggles]
[AOI]
Hey!
[laughing]
[AOI]
Huh? That mask is--!
[AYAKASHI] Uh, oh, right,
sorry about that!
Hello there. I'm Hakkabou!
I'm a yokai called a nyudo-bozu.
You're what?
Now, then.
I'm leaving tomorrow,
so I wanted to say
thanks before I go.
Oh...
I apologize for dropping by
like this unannounced.
Oh, that doesn't
bother me at all!
I'm happy to meet you,
although I thought
nyudo-bozu were giant.
Indeed. We have giant
and human forms,
but this is how I feel
most like myself, yep.
Interesting!
Well, every single
bento you made me
this past week
was delicious. [sigh]
And it was so lovely
to be able to eat them
while I was writing,
as well, yep?
I'm glad.
I really hoped that they'd work.
Uh--
[HAKKABOU] Uh, Is there
something wrong with this mask?
No, I just haven't seen another
one like that in this area.
[HAKKABOU] Ah, well,
I did purchase this one
in the southern land, yep.
Then, that makes sense.
I'm happy to give you
this one, if you like.
Oh, no! It's fine.
[AOI]
The southern land.
[HAKKABOU]
Wow!
This dish looks phenomenal!
[AOI] Can't wait to hear
what you think.
--It tastes spectacular!
--[AOI giggles]
Well, thank you.
I had no idea Tenjin-ya boasted
such a highly-skilled
human chef!
That's good news
worth spreading! Yep!
I only just started
working here.
And, what about yourself?
Been coming here long?
Yes. I've been visiting
Tenjin-ya since I was little.
As a matter of fact, I based
one of the main characters
in my first novel
on the Master Innkeeper!
Huh?
I wouldn't be who I am
without Tenjin-ya.
That's why I return here
whenever I get stuck
and require a little
extra inspiration, yep.
I get that!
[HAKKABOU]
But this time,
I even met a new friend.
What a bonus!
If you don't mind,
could you please
tell me your name,
my fair bento maiden?
Oh, of course!
--I'm Aoi Tsubaki.
--[clattering]
--Tsubaki?
--[AOI] Huh?
[HAKKABOU whimpers]
[screaming]
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong,
everything is right!
You're the grandchild
of Shiro Tsubaki,
and you're also
the innkeeper's future wife!
Huh? Okay?
At one point in time,
Shiro Tsubaki was the basis
for a great many villains
who appeared
in my popular novels!
One could even say
he was an anti-hero!
Really?
His granddaughter
is the ogre-bride?
To think, you will be wife
to his arch-rival,
the master of Tenjin-ya!
I'm on fire! It's fascinating!
What serendipity!
For real?
There is no time to waste!
Blank pages await me!
My work beckons,
I must answer!
[AOI]
Hey, Hakkabou!
Come back! Your mask!
[door slides open]
[CHIBI]
Jeez, it's really noisy!
What's going on out here?
I'm not quite sure.
Sorry.
[AOI] Don't rush,
one step at a time.
Now, back to work!
Well, looks like
the number of customers
hasn't gone up at all.
I know.
Tenjin-ya employees
are all we get.
[AOI]
Like, O-Ryo, and O-Ryo,
and sometimes O-Ryo!
I wonder if sprucing up the menu
with a new item would help.
We need more dessert
on the menu,
and ayakashi love azuki beans
cooked with a little sugar.
Azuki beans, huh?
Great idea!
You always have such
a positive attitude, Aoi!
Negativity will do us no good!
Focusing on the work is key!
Master told me to let go
of pressure, trust myself,
and keep at it,
one step at a time.
That is good advice.
Hmm...
I should make
something with azuki
that's not in the hidden realm.
I got it! This dish.
It's called cream anmitsu ,
and it's from
the apparent realm.
It's made by mixing
fresh cream
with bean paste
and a little sugar!
That does sound like
a perfect combination!
But, can you get heavy cream
in the hidden realm?
Yes!
We can negotiate with
the dairy supplier for it!
Great, will you do that part?
I would be happy to!
Bean paste and cream...
So good!
They'll love it!
[AOI]
All right, I think this is done.
I wonder when Ginji
is going to be back.
I know he'll wanna
give this a try.
--[jingling]
--Uh?
[AOI]
Huh? When did she get here?
Good afternoon.
Did you get lost?
I can smell azuki beans.
[AOI]
Huh?
That is the sweet smell
of boiled azuki beans.
You can have some,
if you're hungry.
Yes, I want azuki beans.
Here you go!
[GIRL]
What's this?
[AOI]
It's called azuki milk gelatin.
It's my first time making it,
so I can't promise
it'll be any good.
This dish isn't yokan ,
and I'm not familiar
with this gelatin, either.
It's quite yummy.
I'm so glad!
We don't have flavors like
this in the hidden realm.
Tell me, who might you be?
No one special, really.
I'm a human who was brought
to this realm by an ogre.
An ogre?
But, why?
[AOI]
Hmm...
Basically, my grandpa made
me collateral in his debt
and couldn't pay it.
Collateral?
I was told the debt
would be canceled
if I married the ogre.
But, I don't want to.
I asked to work off
the debt instead.
Why don't you want
to marry him?
You're referring to the master
innkeeper of Tenjin-ya, right?
Do you dislike him somehow?
Oh, no, it's not so much that.
He's not bad. I like him.
I just don't like to let
other people control my life.
Now, to top it all off,
the restaurant's failing.
But there's plenty I can do
to change that,
so I'll keep fighting.
Until I've tried every avenue,
I'm not going to give up.
Mmm...
Is there something on my face?
There's not.
Take this.
I want you to have it,
as a token of my thanks.
What?
You sure you wanna give it away?
I'll come visit you again,
dear Aoi.
[jingling]
Hold on. Where did she go?
[AOI]
Was she here?
Or did I imagine it?
Aoi!
I put in the order for heavy
cream with the dairy supplier!
You did?
So now, we'll be able
to have whipped cream,
and ice cream, and put butter
on everything, too!
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's good.
Aoi, is something the matter?
That girl who came in,
she might have been
a zashiki-warashi.
Really? Why would she come here?
Well she gave you
her temari ball,
which means she
really liked your food.
Zashiki-warashi come to the aid
of business owners
who pray for
increased prosperity.
A zashiki-warashi, huh?
I thought their hair
was jet black.
Ooh, I know!
I'll garnish the dish
with gold leaves,
so it sparkles
like her hair!
I'll call it...
My Bright Golden Milk Gelatin!
[laughs]
--[chatter]
--[GINJI] Thank you for waiting!
[KASUGA] Thanks so much
for your patience!
[AOI] Why are we slammed
all of a sudden?
[KASUGA] Yeah, we have
a full house again tonight!
It's been like this every day!
[sighs]
I am grateful,
but it's out of nowhere!
[O-RYO]
Aoi! You'll want to see this!
[AOI]
Huh?
[O-RYO] This is from
a few days ago, but look!
An article about Moonflower!
Oh, wow, I guess
Hakkabou wrote
about us in his column!
My dear, beautiful
ogre-bride of Tenjin-ya.
I must apologize
for my ill-mannered
and abrupt exit the other day.
I was able to finish
my manuscript
because of the delicious
bento you made for me.
"I'll stop by Moonflower
sometime soon to visit.
I so look forward to eating
more of your delicious food
from the apparent realm."
Oh wow, these people
read this and came here.
All thanks to Hakkabou!
Not so fast.
I was the one who suggested
that you make him the bento
in the first place.
Don't you forget that part!
Thank you, come again!
[BYAKUYA]
Keep up the good work.
Next month and for
the foreseeable future.
This is such a relief!
Is that all you needed
to discuss with us?
No, I haven't broached
the main subject yet.
A certain person
read that column,
and sent us a request.
It's straight from
the Imperial Court.
Wait, what? The Imperial Court?
From the Royal Family?
Indeed.
I would like you to cook
a special meal
for Master Nuinoin and his wife
on their anniversary.
Hold on a minute.
The Royal Family?
You want me to cook
for those fancy ayakashi ?
Yes, Mistress Ritsuko
is originally from
the apparent realm, actually.
[gasps]
[BYAKUYA] She heard about
Moonflower's reputation,
and she requested your cooking.
I assume it's because
she feels nostalgic at times
for the food from
the realm of her birth.
So, Aoi, will you
accept this job?
Yes, I accept.
I'll do it,
and I'll give it my best!
[CHIBI] Moonflower sure has
livened up a lot ever since
the zashiki-warashi
and nyudo-bozu came!
Aoi! Roll up your sleeves,
and do your best again
for your royal guests!