So, that's it.
Orio-ya.
[HIDEYOSHI]
We're here, human girl, so...
--...go!
--[AOI yelps]
Stop. There's no need
to be rude to her.
[chuckles]
Hideyoshi's a
shape-shifting monkey.
Shortly after I left,
he was promoted to young
master of Orio-ya.
He sure acts like a monkey,
in a lot of ways.
[gasping]
[AOI] This is just like when
I first came to Tenjin-ya.
I am departing to the
northwestern land at this time.
Ranmaru, ensure that you carry
out the ceremony without fail.
Yes, you can count on it,
Mistress Ougon-douji.
[AOI]
"Ceremony"?
What're they talking about?
[gasps]
[GINJI]
Aoi.
Wait, what are they going to do?
[screams]
[RANMARU] This room suits
you well, ogre bride.
Hey, you can't lock me in here!
It's false imprisonment!
Where I come from,
that is a crime!
Well, around here,
I make the laws.
This isn't a joke!
You better let me out right now!
You are such an annoying
little wench.
I never thought I'd feel sorry
for the master of Tenjin-ya.
'Scuse me?
We don't want you interfering
with our important event.
But if you'll make
yourself useful,
I'd be happy to let you out.
How dare you?!
How about this, you can test the
strength of your master's love?
Heh. If he really cares for you,
then surely he'll come
to your rescue, won't he?
[chuckles]
[ALL chuckle]
[AOI] They're testing
the master's love for me?
But if he comes to my aid,
it will cause trouble
for Tenjin-ya.
Come to think of it, am I
already causing them problems?
You let go of her this instant!
[AOI]
I wonder if Ginji is okay...
[TAICHI]
Hey, lady!
Uh?
Want a late-night snack?
[AOI]
What?
Some food? Heh. Yeah!
Wait, it's not poisoned, is it?
If you're that worried,
I'll eat it!
No, I'll take my chances.
Thank you for the food.
Stock made from kelp and dried
bonito, and I smell yuzu!
Is the fish flounder?
[AOI] It's very mild,
and the texture's lovely!
The rice tastes fantastic, too!
And now for the squid shumai.
I love the consistency
and the sweetness!
[TAICHI]
Isn't it good?
That's my most favorite dish.
All the chefs at Orio-ya
make such delicious stuff.
The seafood here is awesome.
We can't beat the eastern
land as far as quantity,
but the quality of ours
is every bit as great!
[AOI]
You sure seem knowledgeable.
Master Ranmaru told me
that I need to learn
all about the southern land if I
want to continue working here.
He even taught me about
all of this stuff himself!
[AOI] For what it's worth, this
boy seems to adore Ranmaru.
What's your name, by the way?
Uh? Oh, I'm Taichi,
and I am a night-sparrow.
[AOI]
Thanks a lot, Taichi.
So is this a guest room or what?
Oh, well. Guess I'll
bathe and get in bed.
[CHIBI]
Hi, Aoi!
Chibi!
You're all covered in crumbs,
what have you been eating now?
[CHIBI]
Oh, um, some crackers.
[splash]
[AOI sighs]
It's been such a long, hard day.
[AOI] Who was that
ayakashi who saved me
from my loneliness and hunger
all those years ago?
Could it really have been Ginji?
[AOI]
Did I just... fall asleep?
[AOI] I wonder if Ginji expected
all of this to happen.
I hope he's not somewhere
getting bullied mercilessly
by Ranmaru right now.
That's it.
I'm getting out of here.
Aw. Guess I ate too
much last night.
Speaking of eating,
where's Chibi?
[CHIBI]
Aoi! Hey, Aoi!
Uh? Chibi!
Where have you been?
That's a key!
Does it open this lock?
[CHIBI] Yeah, it does!
I got it from that ugly dog!
[AOI]
Nice work, Chibi!
[CHIBI]
Heh!
[gasps]
Wow!
How nice.
--Hey, you!
--Uh-oh.
What the hell are you
doing out of your room?!
Well... You see...
I, uh, was just looking at--
I thought I told you to stay in
your quarters, dumb human!
You're hurting me!
Let go!
You're gonna break my arm!
Stop lying. Disgusting.
Pretending to be
a delicate flower.
Humans are much weaker
than ayakashi.
I don't buy that I'm the first
one that you've ever met.
No, I met Shiro, sadly.
He taught me that humans
are evil, and very sneaky.
You're stubborn,
and refuse to die,
no matter how hard
we try to kill you.
[AOI]
Stop right there.
We're not all like that.
Shiro Tsubaki's a terrible
measure for most of us.
[GINJI]
Aoi!
[footsteps]
Oh, you're okay.
Yeah, how 'bout you?
This awful brute
didn't do anything
to rough you up, did he?
How rude. Tell me, have you
come to a decision yet
about next month's
fireworks event, Ginji?
I've decided to accept.
You can rest assured
that the event will be
a resounding success.
In fact, that's the sole reason
I've agreed to come
back to this place.
I intend to hold you to that.
And remember, you can't run
from this land after all.
Its curse will never
stop following you.
I apologize. I feel so terrible
for getting you wrapped
up in this situation.
It's okay.
I'm to blame for chasing
after you the way I did.
But I was scared you'd never
come back to Tenjin-ya.
[GINJI]
Ranmaru did that?
Yeah. No big deal.
You know, Ginji,
you really are a gentleman.
The girls say you're the last
good catch at Tenjin-ya.
"Last good catch"?
What an odd way to put it.
[HATORI]
Hey, Missy! There you are!
Oh, Hatori!
Be careful, he's a womanizer,
and the girls suggest
you throw him back.
Believe me, I know.
You certainly had a bit
of misfortune yesterday.
Ginji, I heard you had a
tough time too, didn't you?
You got that right.
I bet you knew what would
happen from the start.
[laughs] Well, can't say.
Wow, look at that view.
You're terrible at
deflecting, you know.
[HATORI]
What? Yeah, true. But, still.
Why don't we just try to think
positively about the future,
Ginji? The crucial moment is
fast approaching, good buddy.
I know. But thanks for
the reminder, friend.
So, we're good, then!
I'll do whatever I can to
make sure you get back
to Tenjin-ya, never fear.
Hatori, you're being incredibly
reassuring, what's up?
[HATORI] I'm all about
customer service here!
I'm not the same Hatori who was
in vacation mode at your inn.
[laughs]
[BOTH laugh sheepishly]
[HATORI]
Oh, breakfast!
You wanna go eat in the
employee dining hall?
I know Missy here
wants to try our food.
Heck yes!
[AOI] I can't wait to
taste this breakfast!
[HIDEYOSHI] Aoi Tsubaki!
We have you surrounded!
Wait one second, Hideyoshi.
You've got Ginji and
me surrounded, too.
[HIDEYOSHI] Well, you also
reek of Tenjin-ya,
so you're our enemies!
[AOI] Come on! We have a
right to eat breakfast, too!
[HIDEYOSHI]
How dare you make that claim?!
You're just a parasite!
[AOI] You're the ones
who brought me here!
Aoi Tsubaki, you are going back
to the basement
confinement room!
Why can't you let me
eat breakfast first,
at the very least?
Let her go!
[MATSUBA]
Hey! Isn't the bath open yet?
[EMPLOYEE 15C]
Not again.
[EMPLOYEE 15D]
That guy gets up too early.
Crap! My old man! Gotta go!
Master Matsuba!
[MATSUBA]
Mm? Oh, it's you!
[laughs]
Uh?
[EMPLOYEE 15E]
Uh...
Hey you! What the hell?!
Why are you manhandling my Aoi?!
Explain yourself!
Take your hands off her,
scoundrel! You ape!
No way.
This wench is a Tenjin-ya spy!
Do not speak of her
that way, cretin!
That lovely girl is my Aoi!
[MATSUBA yelling]
Lady Aoi! Please intervene,
I beg of you!
Of course.
--Please. Master Matsuba!
--Huh?
[AOI]
Stop destroying things.
You have to think
of the other guests.
I'm an early riser, and I don't
like to wait for my bath,
and these idiots were
treating you badly.
That's no excuse for all this.
Don't you remember what
you did to Tenjin-ya?
I don't wanna wait
for the fireworks.
I'm going back to
Mount Shumon right away.
[EMPLOYEES gasping]
Please don't be rash,
Master Matsuba.
You'll put us in a bind!
He's right, Old-man, you can't
just do stuff like that!
Uh. Big mistake.
He's gonna murder me!
Hatori! You stupid
little bastard,
how dare you open
your insolent mouth?!
[TENGU] Better run,
or it's over for you!
--[MATSUBA] Hold it!
--[HATORI] No way!
What's all this about?
[MATSUBA] Don't run!
You'll get tired eventually!
I just wonder if those two
are ever gonna get along.
Master Matsuba!
I think you're overreacting!
[MATSUBA] Hatori! Aren't you
Tenjin-ya's nine-tailed fox?
How dare you judge my
reaction, you idiot!
I have a right to pummel
my good-for-nothing son
with my own hands if I want to!
Of course! That's not
a problem, sir, feel free!
[HATORI]
Are you kidding me?!
I just thought you should know
the morning bath is ready!
I'm sure that a nice soak while
taking in the ocean view
will cure what ails you!
We'd be happy to bring
breakfast to your room
after you've had your bath.
I won't be needing breakfast
or a bath, thanks.
What if we asked Aoi to
prepare a very special meal
just for you, then?
--[MATSUBA] Hm?
--[AOI] Huh?!
A breakfast prepared just
for me by my dear Aoi? Mm!
This is her first time
cooking with seafood
from the southern land,
and I know she's
excited about it.
And I bet you're thrilled
to be the first one
to try her new dishes, too!
As a matter of fact,
I'm jealous.
Well, that doesn't
sound too bad at all!
How 'bout it Aoi, will you
make some food for me?
[AOI]
Uh...
[HATORI]
Uh!
If that's what you really want,
I would be happy to cook
a seafood breakfast
for you, Master Matsuba!
Oh, I'm glad to
hear it, my dear!
Been looking forward
to your food again!
Now, I think an open-air
bath is in order.
Ginji... What do you
think you're doing?
If Matsuba leaves,
it will put Orio-ya in a bind,
isn't that right?
If you can think of some other
way to keep him here
besides Aoi's cooking,
I'd be happy to hear it.
I guess you've got a point.
But don't think I'll let you
loose in our main kitchens.
Find somewhere else to cook.
You don't have to tell me,
I'm already brainstorming.
Hey, monkey! Let's go!
Thank goodness. Looks like
I narrowly escaped death.
I'm sorry that I
volunteered your services
without consulting
with you first.
Hey, did they lock you in the
confinement room last night?
Yeah, although, to be honest,
that place is incredibly
comfortable.
More importantly, we need to
find a kitchen and ingredients
for Matsuba's breakfast fast,
or this won't work.
That won't be a problem.
I've figured it out!
[AOI]
Where are we going, Ginji?
[GINJI]
To Orio-ya's old building.
[AOI]
Oh, yeah?
Yep, and here we are!
Come on in!
[laughs]
[GINJI] It's not as up-to-date
as the kitchen at Moonflower,
but it'll serve our
purpose for now.
Although we will have to
draw our water from outside.
So, things at Moonflower are
state-of-the-art for the
hidden realm, aren't they?
[GINJI] Yep. We'll need to give
this place a thorough cleaning
later, but for now, let's focus
on Master Matsuba's breakfast.
If his food isn't ready
by the time he's finished
his morning bath,
we'll be in trouble!
I don't know, he's got a
soft spot for you, Aoi,
so he might be more patient.
[GINJI]
Uh!
I had a feeling you two
might be cookin' back here.
Hey, Hatori.
I brought some gifts.
Just a few supplies.
[AOI] Cookware!
And clean kitchen towels?
How nice!
Did you get all this from
the employee dining hall?
Yeah, I'm friends with
the ladies who work there.
Though, I gotta admit,
it's not their best stuff.
[HATORI] The leftovers
from the main kitchen
are what get sent over to
the employee dining hall,
and these are the leftovers
from those leftovers,
but you get what
you get, you know?
[GINJI]
So, Aoi, do you think you can
make something with this?
Yep. Sure!
If you need anything
else, let me know.
I can fly over the main
kitchen and sneak in.
Don't you have your own
work to do, though?
That's none of your concern.
And, after all, this whole
situation was caused
by my old man's selfishness.
Then, can you track down
a few eggs for me?
And some garlic, too.
We also need a little ice
from the icicle woman.
Right. Just leave it to me!
All right. Aoi.
I'm curious to hear what
you're planning to make.
Well, since it's breakfast,
I'm gonna make eggs,
and something with these.
[AOI laughs]
We may not be at Moonflower,
but we've still found
ourselves in a kitchen.
[GINJI]
True.
I wonder what's going to happen
to Moonflower, though.
[AOI]
Worst case...
...if I end up stuck here,
and I can't go back to
Tenjin-ya for a while,
is that the end?
Do you think Moonflower
will be okay without me?
Please don't worry.
I'll try to figure something
out so that you can
go back to Tenjin-ya, and
Moonflower, before you know it.
[footsteps]
I found you some eggs!
That's great!
[GINJI] I'm amazed,
who gave them to you?
I borrowed them right from
Orio-ya's chicken coop.
Don'tcha just love me?
Whoa, that look is
colder than this ice.
I'm chilled to the bone.
[MATSUBA]
I've been waiting, Aoi!
[AOI] Thank you for your
patience, Master Matsuba.
Here you have a sautéed octopus
and bitter gourd
breakfast scramble,
and miso soup with shellfish!
Let me see.
[slurping]
Mm, tasty!
[MATSUBA] I adore the aroma
of garlic and dried bonito.
The texture's great!
Might get addicted to it!
I think it works with
octopus instead of pork,
and the mildness of
the eggs and tofu
tones down the bitterness of
the gourd, while complementing
the best parts of the of the
octopus's flavor profile.
So good!
By the way, Aoi, I'm surprised
to find you at Orio-ya,
what are you doing here?
Are you on vacation?
No, it's nothing like that.
I was brought-- Uh!
[AOI] Wait, if I tell him
that they kidnapped me,
he'll freak out.
I'm just helping out with things
over here for a little while.
They've got a big event coming
up, so they need me.
[MATSUBA] Oh, you must be
referring to the fireworks.
But I heard that Tenjin-ya
and Orio-ya don't get along.
So, I guess they do work
together sometimes.
Are you staying here
for a while, too?
[MATSUBA]
Yes, I was invited as one of the
guests of honor
for the fireworks.
I get bored quite easily these
days at Mount Shumon.
If you'll be around,
I might elect
to extend my stay
a little bit longer.
[MATSUBA] That was a
scrumptious breakfast!
[AOI]
Well, if you'll excuse me...
[ATTENDANTS gasp]
Looks like Master
Matsuba's breakfast
was a resounding success, huh?
[gasps]
If you're going to use
the old building,
you'd better clean up your mess.
What?!
And if you try to pull
anything funny,
I'll lock you back up in
the confinement room.
Got that?
First they abduct me,
and now I'm their slave?
Don't worry, I'll help you.
Ginji! I need to talk to you.
[AOI grunting]
Seriously.
That guy is such a task master!
[AOI sneezes]
[AOI yelps]
[NENE] Move it! We don't want a
human woman wandering around.
My apologies. Oh, uh--?
You've really been a pain in
the neck since you got here.
Who are you, anyway?
This is Orio-ya's Young Hostess.
She's Mistress Nene.
You don't know who
Mistress Nene is?
How pathetic can you be?
[ATTENDANTS]
Boo!
Okay, so you're the
Young Hostess here, fine.
Don't act all conceited
'cause Ranmaru gave you a task.
It doesn't mean anything.
Isn't it obvious that
he's just punishing me?
We know about you, ogre bride.
You're nothing
but an unattractive,
dull, stupid human woman
who should go back to the
apparent realm and never return.
Right girls?
Correct as usual, Mistress.
I know one thing, for sure.
She's the type old people
would be fond of.
I can understand why Master
Matsuba would be infatuated.
My great-grandfather's will
said that men in the fire clan
should strive to marry
human women to secure
the future of the family.
It's been said since
ancient times
that marrying human women
raises the rank of ayakashi.
Do you girls know why?
Well, do you?
--Uh!
--No, I don't.
--Nope.
--[ATTENDANT 15C] Why?
I'll tell ya later.
In any case, I deem you
Cinderella of the Old Building
and I think it suits you well.
[ATTENDANTS laugh]
[ATTENDANTS chattering]
For all her faults,
I will say this,
at least O-ryo came at me
without an entourage.
Uh! This is gonna
swell up a little.
[footsteps]
So, what now?
Look, it isn't that bad.
I accidentally tripped
in the hallway.
I don't like this a bit, Aoi.
You have to get
back to Tenjin-ya
as quickly as possible.
I've already talked with
Ranmaru about it, and--
I can't go back now.
[GINJI]
What?
I refuse to leave this
place without you, Ginji.
I still don't have any idea
why you decided to
return to Orio-ya.
I understand, Aoi.
I can tell you have
compelling reasons to stay.
And even though I'd love to
know exactly what they are,
I can't make you tell me.
I hope you know that I
won't ever give up on you.
Without you working there,
Moonflower will never
be at its very best.
So, until I understand,
I won't leave.
[groans]
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks for caring,
though, Ginji.
[RANMARU]
Aoi Tsubaki.
From this day forward,
I command you to cook
one meal per day
for Master Matsuba.
[gasps]
Ranmaru! She can't!
Orio-ya has received
a specific request
from Master Matsuba himself.
[gasping]
--You give that back to me!
--Stop it!
I'll be keeping this
for now. Rose quartz.
Looks expensive.
I'm assuming your
master gave you this.
If you try to run away,
I will toss this thing into
the middle of the ocean.
What, you can't do that!
How dare you drag her into this!
Come now!
You have your own mission
to worry about here.
Obtain what you
promised, or else.
Only those who produce results
can make demands of me.
The ceremony...
Fireworks.
[AOI] There's something going
on at Orio-ya, but what is it?
[AOI] No matter what the answer
is, or what happens here,
I have to do my best for
Master Matsuba, or I'm lost.
[CHIBI] Hmm, this shady inn
is definitely hiding something.
--[barking]
--What?! Is it really that?!
This is more serious
than I thought!
[barks]