[BYAKUYA]
Unlock, ink brush painting
of illusory hills and water!
[BYAKUYA]
This is an enchanted space,
where the Hourai's gem
branch has spread its roots
and become a tree,
overflowing with
spiritual power.
Be wary when there's
a thick fog.
Supposedly, it can
make inner desires
manifest in the
form of illusions.
Wow! Ha, ha!
[ALL gasping]
[AOI]
Incredible.
I can't believe we really
entered the world
inside the painting
on that hanging scroll!
This certainly looks like
an ink brush painting.
[gasps] Aoi! Look! There!
I wonder why they're
actually colorful.
The tree that grew out
of Hourai's gem branch
is surely affecting them.
That's right, it's a tree
that nurtures lives.
It may have even created the
bright animals you see here.
That's fascinating.
[GINJI, RANMARU gasp]
Hey, come on, guys.
Why are you at each
other's throats?
What do you mean,
we're being civil!
Ha! I see Ginji is as stubborn
and childish as ever,
and he still likes to argue
just to make things hard.
Hypocrite. I'm appalled
that you continue
to oppress those who
try to help you.
Whoa, there. Calm down.
Why don't we just
try to stay focused
on finding the gem branch?
[RANMARU] How dare you tell me
what to do, pathetic human?
All right, Aoi.
Where are we going next?
Up to the mountain's peak.
[BYAKUYA]
First, head toward the summit
and follow the rainbow-hued
spiritual power.
It will show you the way.
You should easily find the tree
grown from Hourai's gem branch.
[CHIBI]
All right!
I've never climbed
a mountain before!
Come on, then keep up,
you pitiful servants!
Servants, huh?
[AOI]
What is this?
A cabin?
[RANMARU] Nuinoin must have
built it as a getaway.
Wait, I'll shed some light.
How's that?
[AOI laughs]
Ritsuko did say that
they both like to read.
But I guess I underestimated
just how much.
Let's shelter here for a bit.
I'm sure they wouldn't
mind sharing the place.
[AOI] I'll make us a little
something warm to drink.
You guys like cocoa?
[GINJI]
Yes, sounds great.
What?
Listen to you, have you
already forgotten?
We're only here to
procure the gem branch.
We have to get it back to
Orio-ya by tomorrow evening.
[gasps] Yeah, but,
it's pouring rain.
I don't care. I'm going out!
No! Ranmaru, you should stay!
Well, that's that.
He just went to check out
the stretch of path ahead.
That way we can
leave immediately,
once the rain lets up a bit.
Heh. You two surprise me.
Despite your differences,
you do understand each other.
No, not at all.
Even though I've
known him all my life,
I honestly can't say I ever
truly understood him.
[GINJI]
The cocoa smells delightful.
Sweet and lovely,
it's very comforting.
[clattering]
[RANMARU]
Hey!
Ah, you're back!
That was faster than I thought!
[gasps] Ranmaru?
[AOI gasps]
Oh my goodness! So cute!
Shut up!
How dare you speak
so condescendingly?!
Well, you are totally adorable!
You look like a plushie,
not a Nobunaga.
Stupid, pea-brained kappa!
There's not a dog in any realm
who's cuter than Nobunaga!
All that aside, it seems
your spiritual power
depleted rather quickly.
Shut your mouth, Ginji!
This space is even
more mysterious
than we thought it was.
If you turn into your beast
form, you'll understand.
Your power will be
consumed just as fast.
Drink this, then.
You'll get some of it back.
What is this strange soup?
It's hot cocoa.
And I added some
coconut milk for flavor.
Yay, that did the trick!
Heh. Even without
your sense of taste,
you can still make food with a
great deal of spiritual power.
[CHIBI cheering]
Ah. This is really
incredible, Aoi!
[AOI]
Huh?
From what I see, every
volume in this collection
is exceptionally hard to find.
I'd expect nothing less
from Master Nuinoin.
Look at this one.
It's from the eternal realm!
That's pretty awesome.
And look what it's about.
The daidarabocchi, another
name for the umi-bouzu.
"Daidarabocchi is a monster.
A steward who manages the
impurities that have been born
out of the conflicts
between humans and yokai
in the eternal realm.
He became hard to handle,
so the humans in the eternal
realm locked him away,
to be confined in
an enclosed space
in the farthest corner
of the ocean."
They locked him away?
What did he do?
[CHIBI screams]
Chibi! What's the matter?
Come outside!
There's something weird!
Up in the sky!
[ALL gasp]
[AOI gasps]
What's that?
The rainbow spiritual power?
We should follow it!
[AOI gasps]
--[GINJI gasps]
--[AOI gasps]
It disappeared.
It's all right.
Let's just continue up
toward the summit.
Obviously, you don't
have to tell me!
It's too dangerous to
keep going any farther.
Why don't we rest here
for a little while?
[RANMARU growls]
We have to be patient now.
There's a lot riding
on tomorrow.
Yes, obviously, you don't
have to tell me that either!
Come on.
Stop fighting, let's eat.
[AOI] I made us hot
roast beef sandwiches,
and there are mushroom
skewers, too.
Oh, and figs for dessert!
It's a mish-mash of
stuff that I brought,
and a few things I've
gathered along the way
since we've been here.
But all things considered,
it turned out pretty well,
for a camp meal.
Ah! I've never had
it in a sandwich!
You're always teaching me
about new foods, Aoi!
I used the beef I
made yesterday.
Then I added a few
fresh vegetables,
some condiments, and voilà!
So, it's leftovers, then.
Although I have to admit,
it tastes good.
[laughs]
My goodness! Hear that?
Ranmaru finally deigned
to compliment you!
Ha! It's only because
I'm so hungry!
They do say hunger is
the best spice, after all.
[laughs]
[CHIBI]
Cucumber's good!
Nom nom nom nom nom.
[RANMARU]
I'm going to survey the area.
[AOI]
What?
[GINJI]
Fog is settling in.
It's too dangerous
to go out now.
I don't care.
I can't just sit here lazing
around, like you two.
[AOI]
And he's gone.
[GINJI]
He's just desperate, I think.
He's scared to make the same
mistake from 300 years ago.
So, what exactly happened?
With that year's ceremony.
[gasps]
It was a lot like right now.
We were trying to locate one
of Hourai's gem branches.
Raiju offered his help.
He said he knew where one was,
and he'd do what he could
to get it for us.
But at one point
in the process,
he said something so
insulting to Princess Iso,
that it shattered her
dignity completely.
[gasps]
I couldn't forgive him
for hurting her,
which made me become
cross and defiant.
He's arrogant, so that
choice made him furious.
And he disappeared before
getting the gem branch for us.
I see.
Although, I bet
that he'd planned
to cause trouble from the start.
Yes, I agree.
Because the moment
that I challenged him,
this look of pure satisfaction
fell across his face.
As if I had walked
right into his trap.
I shouldn't've been surprised.
I'm certain he was anxious
to see the ceremony fail
and chaos ensue.
He's always been a wicked,
miserable ayakashi.
Unforgivable.
[GINJI]
And to make matters even worse,
we lost Princess Iso
because of him.
After that, Ranmaru was
never the same again.
[AOI] Maybe, he felt like
he had to change,
in order to protect the
southern land, perhaps.
Is that what you think, too?
Yeah, I suppose that
is how I see it.
But grief is a funny thing.
I understood, but still.
I couldn't stay by
his side anymore,
and I stopped supporting him.
Hey, Ginji. Do you regret it?
Going to work at Tenjin-ya?
[gasps] I don't.
Not even for a second.
I've gained so much
from my time there.
Countless experiences that
mean the world to me.
And not only that, but
Tenjin-ya has been vital
in the ceremony this year.
Honestly.
Even though I want to face
Ranmaru and tell him how I feel,
I can't bring myself to.
Whenever I'm around him,
it's like I turn into
a stubborn kid.
I understand.
Do you want to save
the relationship?
If he were willing to,
would you try
to go back to being brothers?
Of course I would.
But only if Ranmaru
felt the same way.
[chiming]
You know,
I believe you can go back
to the way you were.
[gasps]
[AOI]
But if that happens,
Ginji might decide he wants to
stay at Orio-ya, after all.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah! The figs!
I forgot.
How about a palate cleanser?
Yeah, that sounds great!
[AOI] Man! I've never seen
such a perfectly ripe fig!
Delicious!
[AOI]
That's too bad.
I still can't taste it.
It's gonna be all right.
Don't worry.
[AOI]
Uh?
I have no doubt.
Before you know it,
your taste will come back,
and you'll enjoy
your food again.
I won't entertain
any other possibility.
It just isn't fair.
You should taste the
fruit of your efforts.
Thanks, Ginji.
You deserve that.
To eat hearty,
scrumptious meals,
and to savor every bite of them.
You should feel that happiness.
[gasps]
So, have faith.
You'll continue to cook,
and you'll do it well.
For all the ayakashi
in the realm.
They'll come from far and away
to experience your artistry.
Hey, tell me something.
Have you and I met before?
When I was a child, I mean.
[GINJI]
What?
Did you save my life
when I was little?
[GINJI gasping]
[AOI]
I knew it.
Please, tell me. [gasps]
It's Princess... Iso.
[AOI gasps]
[GINJI gasping]
Princess Iso, is that you?
Ginji, wait, that's not her--!
You're right.
Yes. It's an illusion, not real.
Remember Byakuya
telling us about it?
They come from the
tree's spiritual power.
[gasps] Ranmaru!
He might see it, too!
We have to go find him!
[gasps]
[RANMARU gasping]
That looks like Princess Iso!
[gasps]
Could it really be you?
[GINJI]
Ranmaru!
[AOI]
It's just an illusion!
[RANMARU exhales]
[AOI panting]
Are you okay?
Ha! Why, yes, of course.
What's with you?
Telling me not to leave,
then going out after me?
Don't act tough.
We were worried,
and you looked bewitched!
Have a little empathy!
[yelps]
[RANMARU gasps]
[GINJI]
Aoi!
[RANMARU grunts, screams]
[GINJI]
Ranmaru! No!
[AOI grunting]
[gasps]
Ranmaru! Please wake up!
Are you okay?
Yes, why are you
trembling, human girl?
I'm so relieved. Thank you!
Don't cry.
You know, if I hadn't
eaten your food earlier,
I may well have died.
That was quite a long fall.
This place is super
dangerous, huh?
Sure is.
Let's go.
But, wait!
I'm sure Ginji's
beside himself!
And I bet he's out
there looking for us.
Ha! Yes, indeed, he'd be
beside himself over you.
Though, I imagine he
would prefer that I
had perished in
that little spill.
[gasps] How can you say that?!
You're wrong!
He's the one who went
after you in the first place!
He was so scared.
He thought the illusion
would hurt you somehow!
That's right.
He cares about you immensely,
despite your differences.
Because you two are brothers!
You can't deny that.
You two and the Princess--
You're family, always!
That band.
You found it in the ruins
of the dragon palace?
It's Princess Iso's.
She gave it to me there.
It was her, the real princess,
not an illusion.
She called it her thought form.
She told me lots of stories.
All about you and Ginji as
little ayakashi, growing up.
She was really concerned.
She wants you guys to reconcile.
[gasps]
And also. That's
when she told me
to cook the dishes
of ocean treasure
for this year's ceremony.
But I can't. Because I--
I have no sense of taste now.
I'm so sorry.
Princess Iso, I'm sorry
I let you down.
What a pain.
I said not to cry.
[gasps]
Let's go.
Hold on.
Ginji knows me quite well.
He'll be expecting me to
prioritize finding the branch
over anything else.
In which case,
he'll probably make for the
summit, so we should, too.
I know that we'll
find him up there.
We'll get the branch as well.
[gasps]
Uh?
The rainbow spiritual power.
[AOI gasping]
[RANMARU]
Uh! Rainbow clams!
[laughs] Just like the
shell Master gave me.
Whoa! These shells
are super sparkly!
[gasps]
So, that's Hourai's gem tree?
It's so brilliant.
[GINJI]
Ranmaru!
Aoi!
Thank goodness!
You're both safe!
I was terrified!
[RANMARU]
Ha.
What you were seeking was right
in front of you the entire time.
Get your head out of
the clouds, now, Ginji.
Uh. Wha...?
[RANMARU grunting]
Ranmaru. We found it!
[growls]
Ginji.
Good job, guys.
Uh?!
[laughs] You're precious!
Don't say that!
[GINJI]
I'm so embarrassed.
Hey, look at me, I'm cute, too!
[GINJI, RANMARU sigh]
Come on, then, Aoi.
Don't just stand around!
[AOI]
Oh!
That's it. Time to go.
All right, then! Let's use
the communication ticket!
'Kay. Byakuya, now!
[ALL grunting]
Uh?
Aoi. Keep trying your best.
You're not quite done.
There's still something
left for you to do.
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
Yay! Look! They're back!
Finally!
Hey, Missy! Hi, Ginji!
You're all safe! What luck!
[NOBU barks]
Hi. We're back!
Oh? I see you got it--
the gem branch.
Although, I must tell you.
You're all looking a little
worse than you did before.
But, still, you did very well.
Thank you.
Excellent work.
Now we'll be able to
carry out the ceremony.
May I present...
And I officially accept it.
The fireworks event
will begin tonight.
I'll take those two.
They need a visit
to the infirmary.
I'll give them medicine to
recover their spiritual power.
Eating will help them more
than medicine would.
I'll cook up a little
something for them.
What're you talking about?
You need to take it easy!
You look like a
total mess, Missy!
Wow. Thanks a lot.
It's true. You need a hot
bath and rest, right now!
Bath? Yes, please! Thank you.
[AOI]
What's wrong?
Don't you guys want to come in?
No, thank you. Not yet. We're
not part of the group. 'Cause.
We haven't been working
here for that long.
Or even contributed
in a real way.
Uh. So, what's up?
The two of us had a big talk.
And we decided that...
Yeah? Go ahead.
Aoi Tsubaki...
We want you to cook them.
[BOTH]
The dishes of ocean treasure.
Huh?!
[CHIBI]
I'm so happy the fox and dog
have finally gotten over
themselves and made up!
And I got some bright,
shiny pearls, too!
What? Aoi's gonna cook the
dishes of ocean treasure?