[AOI]
Pardon us, Madam.
[YODOKO]
You're late!
[ALL gasp]
I'm starving in here, don't you
know I don't have all day?
[AOI] Our most sincere
apologies, ma'am.
We've made monjayaki for
you in the Konishki room.
[YODOKO grunts]
What is this?
It's the iron plate we'll
use to cook the monja.
Wait, monja ?
But, isn't that a food
that only commoners eat?
Well, you did request
an "interesting" dish,
so we thought you might like it.
It's an apparent-realm-style
monjayaki
made with sumptuous,
seafood ingredients,
--and we figured it might be
--"Apparent-realm-style"?
exciting for you to participate
in the cooking yourself.
I have to make it myself?
Sounds like a hassle.
[AOI]
I'll cook the first one.
Pay close attention
to how I do it.
Now, for the most exciting part.
[gasps] I've never seen this
way of cooking before.
[AOI] We form a ring like this
to keep the sauce inside.
Once the batter thickens,
you mix it with the other
ingredients,
then you stir-fry it.
Next, spread it into
a thin layer, like so.
And then eat it with this,
starting from the edge.
Pick it up, using a
scraping motion.
This stuff looks
half-cooked to me.
No, that's just how monja is.
[MITSUNARI]
Uh...
[YODOKO]
Uh! Oh no!
The outer wall is breached!
That happens all the time,
no need to panic.
Huh?
There you go, now grill it
like this for a bit.
Why does it look darker
than the first one?
If the heat's too high,
I'll adjust it.
No, it's miso pork monja ,
the sauce makes it darker.
The salt-flavored, seafood
monja has a lighter base.
It smells fantastic!
[BOTH]
It looks delicious.
Go ahead, Miss.
I simply adore this flavor!
Interesting!
We nailed it! Success achieved!
Mitsunari!
You must try this dish!
Thank you so much for offering,
Miss. I'd be happy to!
This is delicious!
Like nothing I've tasted!
It's a triple threat of fluffy,
soft, and crispy, too!
[BOTH]
Uh...
So good.
I get the impression
that you like
the mentai mochi
cheese monja, too.
Yes, this one's
incredibly tasty,
just like the rest of them.
But I like the cheese
best of all!
And I...
All right, you guys
have some too.
[MEI, KAI]
Yes, please, thanks!
I'll take you up on that.
It sure has an ayakashi-friendly
flavor, to it.
Yeah. The spiciness of the
mentaiko blends in so well.
Adding cheese to the
recipe was a great idea!
[YODOKO]
What do you two think?
It's yummy!
You're a surprisingly
good cook, Miss!
I want to get an iron
plate for my house,
then I can make this dish
whenever I have
a craving for it.
Now that you know how
to cook it, you can,
as long as you have
the ingredients!
Here, I'll give you the recipe.
Hold on, aren't you a chef?
Is it wise for you to give away
your recipes to other people?
Well, Moonflower isn't
a monjayaki restaurant,
so, it's all yours!
What the hell is this?!
[BOTH]
Hideyoshi!
I gave you permission to serve a
meal to the guest in the room.
I did not permit cooking here!
And why is that
woman with you?
[TOKIHIKO]
Calm down, Hideyoshi.
[gasps]
Thanks to Aoi's advice
and cooking expertise,
Mistress Yodoko was quite
satisfied with her meal tonight.
You should respect that fact.
Tokihiko. When did you start
shilling for this pathetic,
human ogre-bride?
You traitor!
Watch your mouth.
Kai, Mei, follow me, please.
Hurry up.
Wait. This involves me, too!
You're an outsider, so shut up.
I've got this.
You had better
clean this place up!
[sighs]
[door creaks]
[HATORI]
Hey, there, Missy.
Uh?
I heard that you helped the twin
cranes out of a little jam.
Yeah. I've been wondering
if Ranmaru was hard on them.
If they get punished,
I'll feel so bad.
Tokihiko and Mistress Yodoko
put in a good word for them,
so, they're not gonna be
punished, after all.
Mistress Yodoko did?
[HATORI] Plus, she accepted
an important request from us
related to the fireworks event.
Ranmaru only cares
about results.
I'm so relieved.
I was beside myself.
Those twins are amazing.
To let their pride go and ask
a stranger to help them out?
But you do deserve the
majority of the credit here.
And to think.
You did it out of the
goodness of your heart.
Cooking is the only way that
I can get close to ayakashi.
So, if I see an opportunity,
I never pass it up.
[HATORI] Missy, do you know
anything about our ceremony?
[AOI]
Not very much.
But I do know that it
takes place in secret,
once a century, during
the fireworks event.
[HATORI]
Yes. That's true.
Ranmaru and Ginji warned me
not to tell you what
I'm about to share.
And yet... I don't think
Mistress Ougon-Douji would
bring you to Orio-ya unless
she had an ulterior motive.
[AOI]
Mm?
After hearing how you handled
things with Mistress Yodoko,
I'm convinced now.
Ougon-Douji wants you here.
You'll be an important asset.
Tell me about the ceremony.
[HATORI]
Aoi, what exactly do you know
about the southern land?
I know that you have warm
weather and nice beaches.
It's more rural than other
hidden realm lands.
That's all.
[HATORI]
For its entire history,
this land's been plagued
by natural disasters.
Typhoons, tornadoes, tsunamis.
So, despite the nice weather
and abundant resources,
development has
never taken hold here.
It always ends up in ruins.
And, what's more,
there's a curse that
rises up from the sea.
[AOI]
That's right...
The southern land bears
an ancient curse.
[HATORI] There is an ayakashi
who seems to be connected to it.
Who brings such horrors
to these poor people.
[HATORI] One of the southern
land's past Hachiyos
came up with a plan
to hold a party
in honor of that ayakashi,
to try and calm him down.
And that became the ceremony.
[HATORI]
The plan was a great success.
And, as the story goes,
the southern land
became remarkably calm
for many years after that.
And then, the Hachiyo
built a shrine
specifically to hold
the ceremonies.
He established a system
to perform the ceremonies
once every hundred years.
I believe that was about
a thousand years ago now.
That long?
Yes, ma'am. But it
can't be carried out
unless we gather several
very valuable items.
The master said that they're
essentially national treasures.
He's right, and, to
make matters worse,
we never know the date
or the required items
until right before
it's about to start.
Finding all that in time must be
really hard for you guys to do.
Yes, in fact, 300 years ago,
they didn't get everything
that they needed, and
the ceremony failed.
And of course, as they feared,
the surging natural disasters
couldn't be stopped.
Legend has it that
the Hachiyo died.
Every land has its own fair
share of natural disasters,
that's just a normal
part of life.
But if our ceremony goes awry,
the extent of the damage
here would be catastrophic.
The Hachiyo bears such
a huge responsibility.
[HATORI] Word is, after the
previous Hachiyo passed,
Mistress Ougon-douji was the
acting one for a while, but--
Now Ranamaru has the job?
Yeah. And because
he was employed
by the previous Hachiyo,
he has the power to
conduct the ceremony.
Ginji does, too.
Ginji? Why?
In a certain sense of the word,
Ranmaru and he are
basically brothers.
At a Shinto shrine, you often
see "God's messengers,"
the komainu and the fox, right?
They're like mystical guardian
beasts who protect the shrine,
and they usually come in pairs.
That's the reason we
had to take Ginji away
from Tenjin-ya and
bring him here.
Because the items needed
for the coming ceremony
had been identified.
So, Ginji and the others,
they're out gathering
those items as we speak.
That's where he's been.
Yes, exactly.
Can you tell me what
those things are?
I would love to do that, Missy,
but if I tell you much more,
then I'll probably get fired.
Uh!
Hmph. But, I suppose
I did come here
because I felt like
I had a revelation,
and I was compelled to tell you
everything that I already have.
There are five things that
we have to find, and...
...the first one is
a rainbow umbrella.
This item belongs
to Mistress Yodoko,
but because you stepped in
and saved her stay with us,
she's going to allow
us to borrow it.
She literally accepted
because you gave her
the recipe for monjayaki.
Just because of the recipe?
And that leaves the
remaining four items.
Tengu's secret liquor.
Okay...
[HATORI]
A Mermaid's scale.
A Mermaid?!
[HATORI]
Hourai's gem branch.
And special dishes
prepared for the party,
made from ocean treasure.
[gasps]
As for tengu's liquor,
I'll have to ask my old man
to let me have some.
Do you think that Master
Matsuba would do that?
Well, that stuff is the prized
jewel of Mt. Shumon's tengu.
He'll take persuading.
Besides, I was disowned
because of that damn
liquor in the first place.
[sighs]
[HATORI]
So, I think that you'll be able
to go back to Tenjin-ya soon.
What? You mean before
the ceremony takes place?
I'm working with
Ginji and Tokihiko.
We're trying to negotiate
with Ranmaru.
We'll make the ceremony
a success, no matter what.
But how?
[HATORI]
Unless, of course,
you'd prefer to stay
here and help us.
Hey Hatori, I have a
small favor to ask of you.
[HATORI]
Hm?
Can you bring me some
chicken wing bones?
May I ask what for?
I'm going to put them in
Master Matsuba's meal tomorrow.
Think you can handle that?
Yeah! I'll get those bones
for you right away!
I'll ask the twins first,
and if they don't have 'em,
there is the chicken coop, too.
[AOI]
Hey, Hatori.
Uh?
Thanks so much, for sharing
all of that with me.
[gasps, laughs]
Of course, I wanted you
to know the full story.
You're a good girl, Missy.
Genuinely kind.
[CHIBI] Is your ankle
still hurting, Aoi?
No, I think it's all better.
The medication that the master
brought me is amazing. Wow!
[BOTH inhale, exhale]
I sure could get used to this
little pine grove by the ocean!
I could, too!
That reminds me, when you
run off, where do you go?
You've been disappearing a lot.
I swim in the surf
with my new friends!
I've met a whole bunch
of coral and clownfish!
So we go on treasure hunting
adventures together!
You could get swept out to sea!
I'm an expert swimmer, watch!
--Wahoo!
--[AOI] Hey!
--What will we find today?
--Come back!
The smell of eggplants on the
grill is truly irresistible!
[MASTER]
Yes, it's an amazing aroma.
Huh?
Oh Master, it's you!
Ow, hot!
What is this?
[AOI]
A light chicken soup.
It's made from vinegar,
soy sauce, and sugar.
It'll be done as soon
as the sugar cooks off.
I didn't see your cart
by the door today,
so I just assumed
you weren't coming.
That's because I parked it
in the pine grove instead.
Aoi. There's a special
place nearby
that I'd love to show you.
Oh, really, what kind
of place would that be?
It's a harbor.
A small fishing port, just
beyond the pine grove.
But I really shouldn't
take the risk
of leaving the old building.
The kid who's watching
me will be here soon.
If Ranmaru finds out
that I left this place,
he'll throw the hair ornament
into the middle of the ocean.
[MASTER]
Don't worry. I've got a plan.
[gasps]
Hey!
Ah, here it is.
[gasps]
Your spiritual power has
been fostering this flame
for quite a while now. So,
it's become your follower.
My follower?
[MASTER] Then, I poured my
own power into it yesterday.
That caused it to awaken.
Now, you try giving
it a command.
Try ordering it to transform
into Aoi Tsubaki.
I have no idea what you're
talking about, Master.
Just do it and you'll
see what happens.
Transform into Aoi Tsubaki now.
[gasps]
Huh?!
Although, this ayakashi, is an
unstable ogre fire creation.
There are some who
become powerful enough
to transform into humans.
[AOI]
Mm...
[MASTER] Master Tokihiko,
who is a shiranui,
became a formidable yokai
through a similar process.
Master! Oh, my Master!
Hey! You let go of him now!
[laughs] Isn't this exciting,
Aoi, now there are two of you!
Ugh, what are you acting
so pleased about?
Ah! Hello, Mistress Aoi!
What...?
She's rather like a newborn
baby, if you think about it.
I guess we had better
give her a name.
You seriously want to give
this green thing a name?
Of course I do.
She's the very first fruit
of our love, isn't she?
--[AOI] Huh?!
--I know! How about Ai?
You just took the "oh"
sound out of Aoi.
Yes, but isn't it cute.
Suits her!
Well, I suppose it's fine.
And how do you feel about that?
I love it!
Thank you for my name.
Hey, do something,
would you, please?
Just treat her like you
would our child.
After all, she loves you
like you're her mother.
Ah, my lovely chicken soup!
Once you deliver that
to Master Matsuba,
we can leave Ai here
while we step out.
Hey, I'm not going to faint
and then wake up back
at Tenjin-ya, am I?
The truth is, I would
prefer to have you home,
but I know you won't
come back without Ginji.
Uh.
So, to make sure you're safe,
I'm content to come
check on you.
I sort of enjoy pretending
to be a fish peddler!
[AOI]
Is that an old shrine?
The one Hatori mentioned?
That was used the time
the ceremony failed?
[MASTER]
Aoi.
I put my own spiritual power
into that straw hat.
As long as you're wearing it,
Orio-ya staff won't notice you.
You can relax a little
and enjoy the market.
[AOI]
Master, look at these!
They're beautiful! These
dried shrimp are huge!
She never has trouble
enjoying herself.
What?!
And... Chili paste with yuzu?
Now that's a rare sight, indeed.
It's a lot more difficult
to come by in the land
of the ogre gate.
I'm sorry to pressure you
into buying all this for me.
[MASTER] If you let me
taste what you cook
with these ingredients,
pressure me all you want.
[STORE OWNER 17A] Hold it
right there, you little brat!
Someone stop that thief!
[MASTER] This land has
abundant resources,
but it's also plagued
by disasters.
Hatori told me all about that.
[MASTER] It's incredibly hard
to get a stable job here.
The coastal areas are
especially dangerous,
so the only people who
choose to live here
are fishermen and
Orio-ya employees.
Scores of crooked businessmen
come here to make a quick buck,
then they desert the place.
You can see the orphans and
abandoned children everywhere.
[AOI]
Like Taichi and his siblings...
I had no idea.
Oh! Look, it's
Jinpachi the newbie!
[FISH PEDDLER 17B]
And he's with a woman!
Yes, she's my new wife.
Oh, yeah? Well,
lucky you, Jinpachi!
Jinpachi? Why did he
call you that?
It's an alias.
[AKAMA MASTER laughs] So,
you're the famous ogre bride?
Uh, yeah, that's me!
[MASTER] Akama Seafood has
always been very good to us.
They used to be a
well-established inn.
You can tell her
'bout that later.
We've got fresh yellow tail,
let me make you both
some atsumeshi !
Yellowtail atsumeshi ?!
[AKAMA MASTER] I'll be in
the kitchen for a bit,
but you two just make
yourselves right at home.
Come on, Aoi.
[AOI]
U-Uh...
[gasps]
[AOI]
Hi, there, friend!
Uh? Oh, Mistress Aoi!
I've missed you!
I'm glad to see you
looking so well, Mistress!
When I decided to come
to the southern land,
I asked Sasuke to come with me.
He's helping out at
Akama seafood, too.
[AOI]
How wonderful.
Master, we must leave this
place and take Mistress Aoi
straight back to safety at
Tenjin-ya without delay.
[AOI]
What?
No, Sasuke.
My ogre bride refuses to return
to Tenjin-ya without Ginji.
Really?
Look, I only need a little
bit more time here.
But we're speaking about
the treacherous Orio-ya!
Huh...
The food!
[AOI]
Wow, yellowtail atsumeshi !
Marinated sashimi bowl?
I heard that it's a
staff meal for fishermen
in the apparent realm.
Don't be shy, now,
please try it!
I have no doubt that
this is gonna be good!
Thanks for the food!
It's sweet!
The marinade really
brings out the flavor
of the rich, fatty yellowtail!
I poured some tea in
it to make chazuke,
and it's delicious
that way, too!
Yeah, I bet it is!
I just wish I could serve
something like this
at Moonflower!
[MASTER]
You'll be so inspired
to create new dishes
when you get back!
[AOI]
You're right!
Is your ankle feeling
completely healed, Aoi?
Yeah, it's kind of amazing.
The medicine in this
realm works so well!
Heh. Our bath caretakers
developed that
exceptional remedy under the
guiding hand of their chief.
Now I remember.
The medicinal bath water
Shizuna told me about.
Hey, Master?
Look at this.
A rainbow clam shell.
How sweet! And pretty.
[MASTER] This is an
exceptionally rare shell.
You can only find them
in the southern land.
Legend has it that they
travel through the sea
all the way from
the eternal realm.
Eternal?
It's a far-away place,
different from the hidden
and apparent realms.
The southern land is as close
to it as one can possibly get.
Take a look there,
across the water.
What?
[MASTER] That landmass
is called Jouno Island.
The general public is
strictly forbidden
from entering that place.
Can you guess why that is?
It's because that's where the
fireworks ceremony happens.
I want to know more
about the eternal realm.
[MASTER]
It's a strange, foreign kingdom.
In some eras it was ruled by
humans, in others by ayakashi.
[AOI]
Whoa.
[MASTER] I do wish I could take
you home with me right now,
but I cannot disrespect
your request
to remain here at Orio-ya.
And I appreciate that.
I'll stay, too, and support your
ambition from behind the scenes.
What do you mean by "ambition"?
[gasps]
These shells have great
beauty, but no power.
You could wear it as an amulet,
though I'm not sure you need
pretty little trinkets like this
to console you.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
[AOI] That form of yours,
it really isn't fair.
This, either.
Not fair, why?
Look it just isn't fair, okay?
Still...
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
[AOI]
Oh, no, Master, is that--?
Yes, it's Orio-ya.
[AOI gasping]
[CHIBI]
Oh, wow!
Tenjin-ya's green
kamaitachi is here, too?
So, he wants to form an
alliance with me after all!
Huh? He doesn't? I am upset!