[MASTER] And this building
where you find yourself
is known as Tenjin-ya.
Now why won't you
just give in and agree
to be my bride?
I'll stay and work
till it's paid--
that settles the debt,
but I won't have to marry you.
How would you like to
open your own restaurant here?
My name is Matsuba.
Master Matsuba.
You're a great cook.
And so, sweet Aoi.
I would like you
to take this gift.
[MASTER] It's not going to be
an easy task.
A human has never run
a restaurant for ayakashi
in the hidden realm before.
Very well, then.
You can give it a try.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
What do you wish me to do?
Say my name.
I wish to hear my name.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Aoi.
[gasps, giggles]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] Do you
have another wish, perhaps?
I'm very hungry,
and all I want
is my mom's curry and rice.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
This wish is difficult to grant.
But...
[AOI]
Gorgeous!
I didn't know
the Hidden Realm
had this much nature!
Yes, we have a variety
of environments here.
It must be big.
Tenjin-ya is located
at the Northeast end.
It's called the, "Ogre gate."
I see.
[MASTER]
The capital is surrounded
by eight lands
called the Hachiyo,
or "eight leaves."
The ayakashi who rule
each of these lands
also carry the title of Hachiyo.
Is Master Matsuba one of those?
Indeed, he rules
the land called Mt. Shumon.
Wow.
You did a great job
with Master Matsuba.
Your cooking protected
Tenjin-ya from great dishonor,
and for that,
you deserve a reward.
I do?
[UME, TAKE, MATSU]
Yeah, come on, Miss Aoi!
Ah! You scared me,
don't sneak up!
[MATSU]
Let us do your hair!
[TAKE]
Let us do your face, too!
[UME]
Let us get you dressed up!
[AOI] Whoa. I gotta say,
I wouldn't have
picked this one out
for myself, but I love it!
[MATSU]
It's so beautiful!
The master chose this kimono
especially for you!
What? Why would choosing
my clothes interest him?
[TAKE] If that coquettish
young hostess sees it,
I bet she'll be green with envy!
Wait, the young hostess?
[UME] Yes, she's head over heels
in love with the master.
[TAKE] She's even told most of
the staff at Tenjin-ya
that she's his mistress!
Can you believe it?
[MATSU]
Stop it!
You're spreading gossip,
true as it may be.
[UME, TAKE]
Yes, ma'am.
[AOI laughs nervously]
[MASTER]
Oh. Just as I thought,
the red camellias look
lovely on you.
I'm delighted to see
you like it, too, Aoi.
Um, yeah, I do like it.
It's so beautiful.
Thanks so much.
Now, final touch.
My, you wear it
incredibly well.
Wait. Doesn't the bud
seem bigger to you?
[MASTER]
It's made of rose quartz,
but it's enchanted to grow
like a real flower.
Soon, it will become
a full camellia blossom.
You mean it's gonna bloom?
Yes, and fall off one day,
just like a real flower.
[AOI]
What? It'll fall?
But, no then it's not gonna
be pretty anymore.
[MASTER chuckles]
[Aoi grumbles]
You must pay
your grandfather's debt
before the bloom falls
from its setting.
Now, you have your deadline.
Good luck.
[AOI grumbles]
[ATTENDANTS laugh]
Come, we're expected
to arrive soon.
Where to?
[AOI] It's unbelievable!
What is this place?
[MASTER] This is the capital
of the hidden realm.
It's called Youto.
Youto?
Right. It translates to,
" ayakashi capital."
The ayakashi king resides here.
[gasps]
Heh!
[MAN 3A] Look! Tenjin-ya's
Master Innkeeper!
[MAN 3B] Such a fine ogre,
if I do say so!
You're famous here,
aren't you?
I am, but listen, Aoi.
You must keep your mask on,
or they'll know you're human
and you'll be in danger.
Yeah, duh, I know that.
[AOI] It seems like
there's a festival going on.
[MASTER]
It's called Youto cut glass.
That name does make sense.
It's made using
a technique
from the apparent realm,
but we modified it,
so our method's unique.
Ah, well it sure is pretty.
This pink bowl
strikes your fancy?
I'll buy it for you.
What? No, it's okay!
Oh. Don't be shy.
I'm not. But they say
everything comes at a price,
and it's the truth.
[MASTER]
Oh...
"Oh." What?
[MASTER] I see.
You mean you don't want
to be treated
to a tasty meal right now?
[AOI]
What? Hm.
[AOI gasps]
These innards,
they're delicious!
It's grilled offal.
[AOI] Huh, I've never
had them like that.
They really are great!
So, did you order me
the offal hot pot
because it's your favorite?
My favorite meal?
It's something similar.
What is it, then?
If I had to choose,
I'd probably say it's
the blood entrails
of a young human girl.
[AOI groans]
Curiosity really does kill.
[SUZURAN]
Excuse me, may I come in?
Yes. Please.
[door opens]
It's been quite a while
since our last meeting,
Master Innkeeper of Tenjin-ya.
Aoi, meet one of
the most popular
geishas in the capital, Suzuran.
She's also
Akatsuki's younger sister.
What?
Wait, the front desk guy?
She's related to him?
Suzuran,
please meet Aoi Tsubaki,
Shiro Tsubaki's granddaughter.
Oh really, is that so?
Is he in the hidden realm
with you?
Uh, my grandfather is--
Shiro isn't in
the hidden realm now.
Aoi's the only Tsubaki here.
[SUZURAN]
I see.
Well, I hope he visits soon,
it's been a long time.
I must tell you, Mistress Aoi.
You resemble Shiro
a great deal.
[gasps]
[SUZURAN laughs]
Now, then, Suzuran,
it's been so long.
I would love to hear you
play shamisen for us.
[SUZURAN]
Of course.
[music plays]
[music continues]
[door closes]
Wow! Suzuran's
shamisen's great!
She's very talented,
and the offal hot pot
was incredible, too!
Thanks for treating me.
Yes, you're quite welcome.
How'd you like to go
get some dessert?
You bet!
Honesty. I like it.
[AOI] I feel like I'm being
watched by an ayakashi.
[MAN 3C]
Keep it moving, lady!
Uh!
[AOI]
Where's the master?
Ah! Ah!
That hurt.
[AOI]
An ice patch?
[AOI gasps]
[MAN 3D]
She's human.
[MAN 3E]
A human girl!
[MAN 3F]
Looks tasty.
[ALL chattering]
[AOI gasps]
[growling]
[ALL screaming]
[AOI]
Whoa, awesome!
I didn't know this thing
packed so much wind power!
Hey, come back!
[AOI grunts]
[O-RYO grunts]
[AOI]
You're that snow woman!
[O-RYO]
Get off!
How dare you, you beast?
I think you stole my line!
You put ice in my path
and threw snow balls.
I almost got eaten
by ayakashi back there!
Heh, I wish they had eaten you.
You're just a human girl who has
no business with the master.
He's far out of your league.
So that's why you were spying.
Uh! 'Scuse me?
I know.
You snuck onto the ship
today before we set sail.
What? Go away.
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
Hold it!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B]
Stop her!
[AOI]
Is that Suzuran?
Help me! Where's the master?
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
She went down that street!
[AOI]
Come on!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
Hey, where'd she go?
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B]
That way!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
Dammit! Find her!
[footsteps]
[AOI sighs]
Are you okay?
What was that all about?
I was. Those men--
[footsteps]
How dare you two
just run off and leave me!
What's wrong with you?
Those men who were
chasing after you just now,
they are the ittan-momen
from Yahata-ya.
What's that?
A large and well-known
kimono shop.
They have both money and power.
Suzuran, what made them
come after you?
[SUZURAN]
I was...
I was just sold off.
Yahata-ya's young master
always bothered me
and made advances.
When I got to
the geisha house earlier,
I was commanded
to marry into Yahata-ya.
[SUZURAN] I heard they paid
an enormous sum for me.
How awful!
I'm not the least bit
surprised to hear it.
That man is a
low-life womanizer.
He's always harassed
the female staff
at Tenjin-ya, too.
So he's a rich, stalker type
who does whatever he wants?
Huh? Stalker?
[MASTER]
I see what's going on.
[SUZURAN]
Master, I'm so relieved!
Uhm, I...
So young hostess,
did you plan
to be back at Tenjin-ya
before the master
knew you were gone?
Oh, just shut up!
That's none of
your concern, human!
I guess,
but you don't have to yell.
[MASTER]
This way.
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
There she is!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B] We knew
you'd come to the harbor.
[ITTAN MOMEN 3C]
Tenjin-ya!
How nice,
the ittan-momen tracked us.
Wait, I thought
ittan-momen were fluttery,
cloth-like spirits.
Every ayakashi is different.
They each have
their own human form.
Suzuran, go ahead
and board the ship.
[SUZURAN]
Right.
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
Hey, hold it right there!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B]
Young Master!
Well, well.
It's been quite a while,
Master innkeeper of Tenjin-ya.
I would like you
to hand over Suzuran, please.
As heir to the Yahata-ya,
I own her.
I've already gone
through the formalities
and cleared
the bureaucratic hurdles.
What a nice surprise.
It's Yahata-ya's young master.
About Suzuran,
she's our front desk
manager's younger sister.
I thought a little
sibling bonding time
was in order for them.
So we're taking her back
to Tenjin-ya for a bit.
Lies! How dare you interfere?!
Besides, Young Master.
I am under the impression
that Suzuran
doesn't even like you.
So this idea of forcing her
to marry you,
it seems a little selfish
on your part, wouldn't you say?
Hey. Look who's
talking, mister!
I never!
What an egregious affront!
You will regret this.
I should declare war.
Why are they leaving
without us onboard?
[TANNOSUKE]
Stop them!
And, fire!
Ah! Oh, no! Arrows!
My, you decided
to protect me? How kind!
[AOI] No, it was self-defense.
This thing is incredible!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
What? The tengu treasure fan?
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B] Yeah, but
why does that girl have it?
Hey! You, there!
Just who in the world are you?
Are you a tengu?
What? Why should I
tell you anything?
This girl is
Shiro Tsubaki's granddaughter,
Aoi Tsubaki. She also happens
to be my fiancée,
just so you know.
Did you just say Shiro
Tsubaki's granddaughter?
What? And she's
going to marry you?
Absurd!
[AOI gasps]
[ITTAN MOMEN 3A]
This is an absolute tragedy!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3B] It's the end
of the hidden realm!
[ITTAN MOMEN 3C]
Awful ogre bride of Tenjin-ya!
What? What did he call me?
[ITTAN MOMEN]
Ogre bride! Ogre bride!
Ogre bride!
Hey, I don't like that name!
Well, I'm back.
Suzuran?
Big brother!
Hey, what are you doing here?
The master just saved me
from a terrible fate!
I would've-- I would've--
Oh, Brother!
[sobbing]
What? What happened to you?
Breathe!
[HOSTESS]
O-Ryo!
Where've you been?
You disappeared
without permission--
at a very busy time!
[O-RYO] I know.
I'm incredibly sorry, Mistress.
This behavior's intolerable.
I assumed you had
great potential,
which is why I recommended
that you become young hostess.
And yet you repay my kindness
by disgracing me?
Um, I was just-- I was--
O-Ryo, I commanded you
to look after
Tenjin-ya while I was gone.
Why did you choose
to disobey me?
I'm-- I'm so sorry.
I was very worried
about you, Master.
Enough. Your sweet, repentant
act won't work on me this time.
I saw what you did to Aoi.
[gasps]
It appears you're still
far too immature
to be young hostess.
[O-RYO cries]
[MASTER] I order you to be
confined to your room,
until your punishment
is decided.
[O-RYO cries]
[AOI]
I still can't believe
how relaxed
this place makes me!
[GINJI]
Welcome back, Chef Aoi.
How did you enjoy
your trip to Youto?
Tell me, were you able
to have a good time
taking in all the sights
there with the Master?
Did I "have a good time"?
U-Um, the whole trip
was chaos, honestly.
Oh?
[GINJI]
I see what you mean.
You certainly had
your hands full!
All right, what is all of this?
Well, I figured we should
start planning the menu
for your new restaurant.
These will help us brainstorm.
Oh, good call.
We have to come up
with a wide variety
of dishes to appeal
to all kinds of ayakashi.
Here. I want you to try this.
Is it alcohol?
[GINJI]
No, it's fruit juice.
Delicious! It's sweet
cherry juice, right?
Cherries that have been simmered
with a bit of sugar mixed in.
You're exactly right.
We're in
a cherry-growing district.
This is one of the most popular
items in our gift shop,
but some of the bottle labels
got messed up
in the fight with the tengu,
so I asked if we could have
some of the damaged ones.
Spectacular! I'd like to make
some kind of dessert using this.
Yes. Great!
I wonder what else we can
put on our new menu.
The dishes served
in the main building
are all more traditional fare.
So in our place, let's focus on
dishes from the apparent realm.
Ones mostly still unknown
to us here in the hidden realm.
Uh, you'll have to help me
learn what those are.
Right. The rice omelette
you made me, for example.
I know it'd be a hit!
I'm happy you liked it.
Anything else you can think of?
Let me see...
Well, curry and rice, maybe?
I know that dish
is your favorite.
Curry, huh?
We could add a little fruit
to make it sweet enough
for the ayakashi palate.
Good idea! I can't wait
to help experiment!
All right, I'd better get back
to my official work now.
Ginji, thank you
for all your help.
Heh.
He's really into all this.
Hold on. How did Ginji even
know I liked curry and rice.
That's odd.
[KASUGA]
Hey! Miss Aoi!
[AOI]
Kasuga? Hey. What's going on?
[KASUGA]
Miss O-Ryo collapsed!
[CHIBI] The hidden realm can
be just as tough a place
as the apparent realm, huh?
But it's okay, don't worry!
I bet if you give the Snow Woman
some cucumber pieces,
she'll be your friend too!