[flute plays]
My, my.
You were able to obtain
the mermaid scale, then?
What good thinking,
sending that human
girl in pursuit of it.
Do you plan to have
her cook the dishes
made of ocean treasure
for the ceremony?
I will say that provisions
are going smoothly.
So delighted to hear it.
That leaves Hourai's gem branch.
This is oddly reminiscent
of three centuries ago.
Hmph.
Well, best of luck
with all that.
[chuckles]
[GINJI] The dishes
made of ocean treasure
will be served with
tengu secret liquor,
so I tried to pick ingredients
that will go well with that.
Wow, imitation crab!
And there's shredded
kelp here, too!
Do you have any good ideas,
off the top of your head?
It's tough, since I don't know
what the umi-bouzu's enjoys.
What kind of dishes have
been served before?
[GINJI] Hm... We've made
things like fried lotus root,
different kinds of tempura,
sea urchin. Oh!
And sea snails in miso
vinegar were a big hit.
[KAI]
Sounds tasty.
[MEI]
I want it all now!
Do we have access
to records on that?
Of course!
They're a great resource.
Let's go and check 'em out!
[TAICHI]
You guys! There's trouble!
What's wrong, Taichi?
It's, uh. A friend of yours!
She just showed up here!
Huh?
She's a Tenjin-ya employee,
and she has these really
mean, scary eyes!
Look, would you give
it a rest, Mister?
Who do you even presume
that I might be?
You're Tenjin-ya's
young hostess, right?
[O-RYO laughs]
Wrong answer, my good sir.
I'm nothing but
a room attendant.
Didn't you hear
I'd been demoted?
Why do you sound
so happy about it?
None of your business.
Now, give me a room!
I took stellar care of
Hatori and his friend
when they stayed at our place!
What kind of establishment
wouldn't return the favor?
[laughs nervously]
[HATORI]
Hmph.
[NENE gasps]
It's that woman!
Hi!
Hey, there, O-Ryo!
Aoi, it is so good to see you!
Not dead!
I was worried these savages
might've eaten you alive!
No, if they had, I'm pretty sure
word would have
spread to Tenjin-ya.
You're looking quite well,
too, Young Master!
I hope you're not
getting bullied.
Uh. No, you don't have
to worry about that.
'Scuse me!
Are you finished havin' your
little reunion over there?
[RANMARU]
What's all the fuss about?
[HIDEYOSHI]
Master Ranmaru!
Hatori. They treated
you and Tokihiko well.
Do the same.
Absolutely, sir.
Hideyoshi, follow me.
Sir.
I had no idea that
Orio-ya's lead manager
was so easy on the eyes.
Why didn't you tell me?
[AOI] I thought you were
into men like our master.
Oh, I like all sexy men
who have money and power.
Anyway, you took our
master off the market,
so why waste my time?
[NENE]
Hey, you!
Snow woman of Tenjin-ya!
Don't start thinking that
you're hot stuff 'cause
Master Ranmaru's
letting you stay here!
Pardon? I'm ice cold.
You're the little,
hot-head fire rat.
"Little hot-head"? Who cares?
I'd rather be that than an old,
demoted snow crone!
What? "Snow crone"?
How dare you speak
to me that way!
I'm not old!
Bet your frozen face,
you're an old, demoted
snow crone! Stupid old,
demoted snow crone!
Ugh! How 'bout I give
that babyface of yours
a hefty dose of frostbite?
Go ahead, I'd love to see
how you handle my fire!
[AOI laughs nervously]
Ladies, please.
You're both pretty, why don't
you just kiss and play nice?
[O-RYO, NENE]
Shut up, ya worthless tengu!
That was just mean.
[AOI, GINJI]
He walked right into that.
[NENE] Hmph. Since I
don't have a choice,
I'll show you to your room.
But, the inn isn't
officially open,
so don't go wandering
around making trouble.
I have no intention of doing so.
Well then, right this
way, please, madam.
And we would be happy
to carry your bag for you.
That'd be lovely.
I am really looking forward
to dinner tonight!
I simply can't wait to try that
famous southern land seafood!
Why's she here? Did the
master send her to help?
I'm going out now.
May I ask where, sir?
To the capital.
I don't have any time to waver.
[GINJI]
If you look through these,
you'll find all the dishes that
they've served in the past.
[BOTH gasp]
[AOI] Looks like the inn's
really busy tonight.
Yeah, seems like
everyone's on edge.
You think O-Ryo's
up to her tricks?
[HATORI]
No, it's nothing like that.
Just a group of rowdy guests
giving us some issues.
What do you mean?
How are they being troublesome?
I don't even know how they
could have heard about this,
but they're saying that,
if we let them stay here,
they'll sell us one of
hourai's gem branches.
What? Do you think
it's legitimate?
We still don't have
any proof yet.
[GINJI grunts]
[TOAD GUESTS chattering]
[TOAD 21A]
I've got an affliction,
and the only cure
is more alcohol!
[TOAD 21B]
Keep the saké flowing!
So is that coral-looking
thing hourai's gem branch?
I'm not sure.
[AOI]
The stakes are really high here.
You'd think Ranmaru'd
be more hands-on.
[GINJI]
He usually is, but he left
on very important business
before they arrived.
What? That's weird.
Give me some more
booze, fire rat!
Uh, yes, right away! [laughs]
Why are you runnin'
away, beautiful?
Everybody, look at my dance!
[SERVER 21A yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[crash]
We're terribly sorry, sir.
[NENE] We'll get you
cleaned up right away!
I've never had such
poor service! I'm leaving!
Hey! You brute!
What did you just say?
You had better watch
your mouth boy,
or I'll happily take
my gem branch elsewhere!
[NENE] I'm so sorry, sir.
I didn't mean to offend you!
I'm the only one to blame!
Your pathetic apology
is worthless!
I demand to speak
to the lead manager!
I should do something to help!
Stay hidden!
You have to remember
that you're human.
Stay as far away as you can
from ayakashi like that.
But why? This was those
toads' fault to begin with!
[GINJI growls]
[O-RYO] Why don't you allow me
to handle this one?
O-Ryo!
You sure about that?
[O-RYO laughs]
Sit back and watch an expert.
Well, well. If it isn't
my favorite oogama,
Mister Yukichi!
What's this? Who are you?
[O-RYO] It's me, O-Ryo!
From Tenjin-ya, remember?
What a fortunate coincidence
for little ol' me,
running into you here!
Oh, it's you!
[O-RYO] Are you drinking with
the room attendants again?
Then I showed up at
the perfect time!
You're so generous
and impressive,
even for a wealthy merchant.
Aren't I though? You said it!
Our meeting like this
must be destiny.
Would you allow me
to join you for a drink?
Sure!
Oh, room attendants!
You'd better keep
the booze flowing!
We're just getting
started tonight!
Now, have a drinky-poo!
Yes, please!
All right!
That's Tenjin-ya's former
young hostess for you!
Yeah, she's got
this one covered.
She's amazing when it comes
to dealing with unruly drunks.
Are you okay? Nene?
I guess.
Who does this woman
think she is?
[TOAD GUESTS
chattering, laughing]
[AOI sighs]
Yet another glorious day!
Uh?
You looking for something?
Ogre bride, it's you!
Will you please stop
calling me that?
Seriously, what did
you lose. I can help.
No, you can't.
But I'm looking for something
cute, pink, round, and fluffy.
Hold on, fluffy?
What in the world...?
Huh...
Mm! I think I may have found it!
Ow! Hot!
[HIDEYOSHI]
Come out, Nene!
[AOI]
Huh? Nene?
For real, stop it. This is
no time to be a wimp.
The ceremony's coming up soon,
and you can't be in this
form when it does!
Dang it! Don't bite!
Oh, I forgot that
she was a fire rat!
Why isn't she in her usual form?
[HIDEYOSHI]
She takes this one whenever
she's feeling depressed.
Ow! Come on, what did
you do that for?!
If I could revert to my
normal form, I would!
You stupid monkey! Jeez!
Stupid monkey?!
I should just toss you
right into the ocean!
[HATORI] Hey, guys, what's with
all the racket down here?
You're bothering
the guests, you know.
[AOI]
Oops. Were we being loud?
Stop it!
[HATORI]
Nene. You can take the day off.
I talked to Ranmaru, and he
said you needed a break.
[NENE] Does this mean
I'm getting fired?
Is that what this means?
No, it's nothing like that.
We're just going to need
our young hostess
in top shape for
the fireworks event.
He requested that you
rest up while you can.
Really? But I...
[HATORI grunts]
Can I ask a favor, missy?
Uh. Yeah?
I really hate to impose,
but would you mind
taking care of her for
the rest of the day?
Uh... Huh?!
I'm surprised.
I never thought Nene would be
the type to pout like this.
She can be a bit neurotic.
Always overthinking and
worrying about stupid stuff.
Yesterday was hard.
[inaudible]
[HIDEYOSHI groans]
You little--!
Now, now. There's no reason
for you to bring up a sore
spot like yesterday.
[HIDEYOSHI]
What?
Are you accusing me of not
understanding how women think?
That's exactly what
I'm accusing you of,
'cause you're a man,
and I've been dealing
with you for a while.
That's rude!
[AOI] Oh, save it.
Why don't you let me take over?
Don't you have work
you need to do now?
All right.
Take good care of her.
[door closes]
[AOI] Your food's ready.
Come on, time to eat.
I sent the noisy guy away.
Get some nourishment, or you'll
never go back to normal.
You're so cute!
[NENE]
Yeah, of course I am.
[giggles]
[AOI]
Here, try this, too.
[NENE]
Uh?
It's clam chowder.
[slurping]
That tastes weird.
Oh, do you mean it tastes bad?
[NENE]
No, it's really good.
I just think a soup made with
milk and clams is so bizarre.
I can't wrap my head around
why it was invented.
Hey, seems like
you're getting better!
Nope, you're bigger,
but still a fire rat.
I already told you,
I have no control
over it at all.
[AOI] It seems like this
is an unconscious,
psychological thing.
I know what to do!
Heck, yeah!
[NENE] It's not nice of you to
drag me here against my will.
C'mon, you've got
the whole day off.
I figured we should
take advantage!
And I want to shop
for ingredients!
I'm going back.
I don't want anyone in town
to see me out in this form.
I hear that,
but no one here cares.
Oh.
Jeez, you're so right.
I guess they don't really care.
Come on, now, let's shop.
I think you'll have fun
if you just relax.
[AOI]
Hm? Is that...?
[AOI] It's nata de coco.
I love this stuff!
I never dreamed I'd be able
to eat it in the hidden realm!
[NENE] Um. What is this nata de
whatever you're talking about?
[AOI]
It's nata de coco,
and it's a dessert from
the apparent realm
that I'm really surprised
to see here!
[MASTER]
Thank you for your patience.
[AOI]
Uh! Huh? Master, it's you!
What're you doing working
in a shop like this?
Like what?
Oh, is this a friend of yours?
I, uh... Well, you see...
I thought you were
a fish peddler.
That's right, I just decided
to get a second job.
[NENE] You should be careful
moonlighting like this.
Your employers might
get mad and retaliate.
My, aren't you a clever
little fire rat.
What's with this texture?
It's totally different
than gelatin.
This is super chewy.
I know, right?
Don't you think it's
delicious, though?
You said that it's from
the apparent realm.
Yeah, it used to be
incredibly popular there.
I see. I think I like it, too.
[laughs]
[NENE] I wonder...
what's the matter with me.
What?
[NENE]
Hey. Can I ask you something?
Is there someone in your life
that you admired, and,
it got so intense that you
started feeling really jealous
and angry at them?
That intense? I'm not
really sure about that.
I don't think so,
but it's probably because
I've never met anyone
who was great enough
to make me feel that way.
[NENE]
Right.
But I gather you have.
[NENE]
Mm-hm...
Are you talking about O-Ryo?
When I was younger,
a very long time ago,
I went on a vacation with my
grandparents to Tenjin-ya.
While I was there,
I bumped into a drunk.
[GUEST 21A]
Ouch!
What's your problem,
dumb little girl!
[whimpers]
[O-RYO]
Oh, there you are!
I've been looking
all over for you.
Would you like to have
dinner with me tonight?
The hot saké is
going to get cold,
so we had better hurry back!
Come on, let's go!
[GUEST 21A]
You bet!
[O-RYO laughs]
You ready?
[GUEST 21A]
Yeah!
I was just thinking it was
time for another drink!
Later, she snuck me snacks
and told me not to
worry about him.
She's the reason I decided
to be a room attendant
in the first place.
Wow, I had no idea.
[NENE] But I feel like I'll
never be as wonderful as her.
Why?
I just know it's true.
And, so, when Hideyoshi and
Ranmaru talked about her,
all I wanted was to run
away and hide somewhere.
I don't measure up.
[NENE] And I couldn't
control that feeling,
so, it got to the point
where I couldn't
hear anyone say her name.
I know how pathetic
this must sound.
No, not at all.
I think you're
incredible, you know?
Do you really?
[AOI]
I do. It takes a lot of courage
to acknowledge a feeling as
uncomfortable as jealousy.
And that's a lot healthier
than lying to yourself
about this stuff!
Interesting. Never
thought of that.
Anyway. Why was I even chosen
to be the young hostess?
Are you saying that
you don't enjoy it?
Oh, no, it isn't that at all.
I truly adore being
the young hostess.
It may be that I'm a
little tender hearted,
but I need to get
stronger to succeed.
Tell me, aren't you even
a little bit afraid?
About what?
[NENE] You're a human,
and you're in charge
of the dishes of ocean treasure,
plus a lot of other
responsibilities.
Yeah, that makes sense, but, no.
You see, if I notice an
ayakashi who needs help,
and if I know there's something
I can do to assist them,
then why wouldn't
I want to do it?
Huh. I've been meaning to ask.
Is your foot okay, Aoi?
[AOI]
She called me by my name!
[NENE] Did you hear me?
How's your foot feeling?
What? Oh, uh, my foot?
I'm the one who tripped you
when you first got here.
Right, you were!
I'm sorry. I just lashed
out at you that day,
and I had no good reason.
It's okay, no hard feelings.
My foot's healed!
Seriously?!
You mean, I've been beating
myself up for nothing?
[laughs]
[gasps] Oh no, I changed back,
but I'm still wearing my
young hostess kimono!
Don't worry.
You look so precious!
I know that.
[laughs]
[AOI] If you'd like,
you can wear this.
Thank you for everything, Aoi.
You are a really good listener.
I am?
[AOI]
Thank you for the snack, sir.
Wait, I have something
else you might like.
[AOI] What?! Coconut
milk and coconut oil?
No way! Whoa!
I never thought I'd see
those around here!
Your excitement seems
disproportionate.
Yes, I'll take 'em!
Give me three cans of milk
and one can of oil, please!
Right away!
[laughing]
Oh, yeah, take this
hat as a souvenir.
[grunts]
Yep, it looks great.
Uh, thanks, I guess, but...
I mean, it is just a straw
hat for farming work.
Do your best, all right?
Yeah, you don't have to tell me.
[NENE]
Mm...?
[NENE] Hey, are you dating
that fish peddler?
Tell the truth!
Huh?!
Seems like it. Things
could get ugly, y'know.
I heard that Tenjin-ya's
Master is a scary guy.
If he finds out, he'll kill you!
Or worse. You'll be fresh fodder
for the front page
of the Weekly Youto !
We're not dating!
You sure about that?
[AOI]
What about you?
What is your relationship
with Hideyoshi like?
[NENE]
Hideyoshi? Why?
[AOI] He was really
concerned about you earlier.
Got me thinking.
[NENE] Hmm. He's just an
old friend of the family.
His house was next door to ours.
[AOI]
Oh, I could see that.
Also, he was
infamous around town
for being kind of naughty.
Ha, yeah, I could totally
see that being the case.
But then Ranmaru
started getting involved.
He recognized
Hideyoshi's abilities,
brought him to the inn,
and it changed his life.
Ranmaru did that for him?
Yeah, but Hideyoshi has
an even tougher row to hoe
than I do over there. Since
he's always getting compared
to the former young master.
I think that, as far
as Ranmaru's concerned,
no one could be better
at the job than Ginji was.
No matter how
special Hideyoshi is.
He can't compete with someone
who was like a
brother to his boss.
Nevertheless, Hideyoshi
always works hard
and never complains,
and I respect him for that
above everything else.
That's great.
This one looks really nice,
think I might have to get it.
Now that I look more closely,
I recognize you.
You're the young
hostess at Orio-ya.
You're right about that, mister.
That's our Nene, isn't it?
[CHILD 21A]
Wow, it is Nene!
[CHILD 21B]
Wanna play with us?
[CHILDREN chattering]
[WOMAN 21B] Take these, we'd be
honored for you to have them.
[NENE]
What?
[WOMAN 21A] Stop by my place
whenever you'd like!
[CHILD 21B] Come with us
to the beach sometime!
[OLD MAN 21A]
And take this back with you!
[AOI]
I know this,
O-Ryo would never have
gotten this reception.
[HIDEYOSHI] I see she went
back to her normal form.
[AOI]
Yeah.
Did she tell you why all
this might have happened?
Well, from what I gathered,
she just lost her composure.
I have to admit,
I misunderstood her initially.
But I think she's a kind person.
Of course she is,
otherwise Ranmaru never
would have made her young
hostess in the first place.
She's still quite inexperienced,
so I see why she
gets discouraged.
But there are those of us here
who understand and
accept her as she is.
I hope one day she really
lets that truth sink in.
Yeah I do, too. Because
she deserves to know.
[AOI]
Hey, Hideyoshi?
Yeah? What?
Be honest with me, do you
perhaps have feelings for Nene?
Yeah, of course I do,
you got a problem with that?
Uh. I don't.
[AOI]
Aw, man.
I asked him to tease him,
but he admitted it.
But promise you won't tell
her I said that, 'kay?
'Cause she has feelings
for Ranmaru, not me.
I know it's weird,
but I'm rooting for them.
Kay, bye.
[AOI]
When we first met,
I thought he was completely
unpleasant, but I was wrong.
I happen to be rooting
for you, Hideyoshi.
I like Orio-ya,
and its people!
[CHIBI] That ogre god sure can
work in any kind of business!
Maybe he'll become
a greengrocer!
Then I could have all
the cucumbers I want,
whenever I want! Awesome!