[hammering]
Oh, I get it, cause
the restaurant opens at dusk.
So, "Moonflower," makes sense!
[AOI]
Mm-hmm!
Master Matsuba
came up with the name.
[MATSUBA]
How's this?
[AOI] Akatsuki!
Just a little to the right!
[groans]
[AOI] Here you go!
Thanks for your help everyone!
[O-RYO]
Mayonnaise.
It's mellow and rich.
I think I'm in love.
[GINJI] What flavor is in
these yellow rice balls?
Oh, those are my
special curry recipe.
Can't wait!
Aw, yeah,
curry is my favorite!
[O-RYO]
Gimme one!
[laughing]
They're everything
I could hope for! So tasty!
[O-RYO]
Hey. What flavor is this one?
[AOI] You're just gonna have
to try it and see!
--[stomach growling]
--[KASUGA] What? Tell us!
[O-RYO]
I'm gonna eat every single kind!
[AKATSUKI]
Rude. Better save me some.
[KASUGA]
Amazing! One more to try!
Would you like
to try some, Master?
[AOI]
Well?
I like it.
Honestly? Do you?
[MASTER] So, tomorrow's
finally opening night?
Yes. Aoi has worked diligently
to make this happen.
[CHIBI]
Aoi! Aoi!
Easy, now, Chibi.
Where have you been?
I took a little dip
in that pond over there.
If I don't replenish the water
on my head plate,
then I'll dry right up!
Look, a carp tried
to eat me and bit my face.
[AOI]
Oh, no.
Well, maybe this'll
make it feel better.
All right!
It's plum and cucumber!
This will make me feel better!
Aoi, you're the best ever!
[ALL growling]
Oh. The Kaikaku-maru!
I wonder which guests
are on the ship today.
What's all that?
[AOI]
Banana peels?
[DARUMA C]
I'm looking forward to this!
I can't wait to see
that human girl
slip on those and fall!
Yeah, slip and fall.
Slip and fall!
[AOI]
Oldest trick in the book.
[DARUMAS yelp]
How long have
you been there?
I guess you guys don't
have enough work in the kitchen.
[DARUMA C]
You shut up!
The chief chef
sent us here
on a mission to do some
very important surveillance!
[BOTH]
On a mission!
[AOI]
Huh?
[DARUMA 1C] There's
no way in a million years
that you can cook food
that tastes as delicious
as our chief chef's does!
You're just a useless,
human eyesore!
Yeah, a human eyesore!
Eyesore!
We heard the tengu made
a reservation for your opening,
we can't wait for you
to cook so badly
that they go on a rampage
to bring the house down!
[DARUMA A]
Serves you right!
[DARUMA B]
Yeah, serves you right!
[DARUMAS snickering]
If you want to waste
all your energy hating me,
then go ahead. Uh, hey!
You come back and
clean up this mess right now!
[DARUMAS]
Do it yourself!
[DARUMAS laugh]
[AOI]
Sheesh.
So many.
I hope they had
to eat all these.
[gasps, grumbles]
[NINJA]
This is when... you die!
[AOI gasps]
[grunting]
[SASUKE]
Mistress Aoi!
Please get somewhere
safe, quickly!
[AOI]
Wait, who is that?
--[SASUKE] Hurry, go!
--[AOI] Oh, right!
[BOTH grunting]
--[grunting]
--[bones crunching]
[roaring]
Watch out!
[AOI yelps]
[NINJA gasps]
[AOI]
Sorry about that!
[SASUKE grunts]
[SASUKE]
Alas. He got away.
I hope you weren't injured,
Mistress Aoi.
[AOI]
I-I wasn't.
So, um, who are you?
[SASUKE]
Oh, my apologies.
My name is Sasuke,
and I'm a kamaitachi.
I'm in the security guard
family at Tenjin-ya.
Security... family?
Yes, indeed,
the kamaitachi family business
has always been providing
patrol detail.
We also maintain the grounds.
It's yardwork in the morning
and afternoon.
Then we're on patrol
duty at night.
So, you clean the yard?
[whistles]
[gasps]
Whoa! Now I understand!
--[KAMAITACHI laugh]
--[SASUKE] I'm glad, ma'am.
[AOI]
Okay!
I think that
should do the trick.
I sustain little cuts
and scratches
like this one all the time.
Maybe. But you wouldn't
want it to get infected.
I'm grateful, ma'am.
[AOI]
The gratitude is all mine.
If you hadn't shown up,
I would've gotten skewered.
No. It all happened
because we allowed
an intruder on the grounds.
Our lack of vigilance
endangered you!
Do you have any idea
who that was?
That was, um...
[stomach growls]
How rude! I beg your
pardon, Mistress!
[giggles] It's fine.
I know! Why don't you sample
one of the new menu items
before you leave?
Yes! Please.
[AOI chuckles]
[SASUKE]
I-I'd love to.
[AOI]
Thanks for your patience.
[gasps] What's this?
That is a loco moco bowl
with potato salad.
Thank you for the food!
The flavor is
simply spectacular!
--[CHIBI grunts]
--[SASUKE] Hm?
[CHIBI] Oh, I didn't know
you had a guest.
[AOI]
Hi, Chibi.
We're weak, green ayakashi .
Allies?
Well, I don't know,
Sasuke's pretty strong
in his own right, so...
I think he'll be just fine.
Strong, hmm?
[CHIBI growling]
I sense that he has
the same frailty as I do.
Green ayakashi are delicate.
We're super cute,
but we need to be protected
a little more than others.
That's just how we are,
it's a fact!
Sasuke, feel free
to squish him, if you want.
Right. Better get ready.
[CHIBI groaning]
How dare you betray me!
I never agreed to form
an alliance with you.
--[CHIBI] I'm... offended.
--[AOI giggles]
Aoi, please.
Give me some cucumbers
right away.
Must binge now.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom...
[SASUKE]
Thank you, that was delicious.
I'm so full I could
almost burst!
[AOI] I'm so glad!
Well, come by any time!
I'm always happy to feed you,
a growing young man
needs to be nourished!
You're kind,
but I'm not young in the least.
Especially in your terms.
I'm many decades
older than you.
[AOI]
Huh?
I'm the same age
as Master Shiro.
No way, you're super cute
for your age!
If you can believe it,
I've been working in Tenjin-ya
ever since the day I was born,
which was more than
80 years ago.
[AOI]
Eighty years ago?
Indeed, but still.
I went through a rebellious
period in my younger years.
[gasps]
[SASUKE] Master Shiro was always
one of my main champions.
[AOI]
Grandpa was?
We used to sneak into
the kitchen and help ourselves.
We'd play pranks on the guests,
and peek into the women's bath!
Uh! That last one
was Shiro's pastime.
I never participated.
Yeah, sure you didn't.
Master Shiro and I
would start trouble
and get scolded
for it all the time!
And, yet,
I admired your grandfather.
He was a mentor to me.
He was brave.
Afraid of no ayakashi,
and so strong,
he could wrestle them
all to the ground!
He argued well enough
to silence anyone!
Your grandfather
certainly was a real man!
He loved to show off
how fast he could run,
like a thundering river.
He put all us kamaitachi
to shame.
[SASUKE]
Mistress Aoi.
Huh?
I must say,
you resemble your
grandfather a great deal.
It's uncanny.
Yeah, that's what they say.
[AOI sighs]
[SASUKE] We'll be sure to
tighten up security around here,
so you can rest assured
that you're safe.
--'Night.
--I apprecia-- Uh!
Typical kamaitachi.
Just in case
of some unforeseen emergency,
I should get in a little
practice swinging my fan.
[MASTER]
An assassin?
Who was the culprit?
[SASUKE] The others went
in pursuit of him,
but I was told that
they acted carelessly
and let him slip away.
It appears that he's
highly skilled.
Is Aoi safe?
Yes.
She treated my wounds
and fed me delicious food.
Ah, of course.
That sounds like her.
You must remain
vigilant and continue
to guard Aoi and Moonflower.
[SASUKE]
I will.
[chopping]
[MASTER]
Aoi.
We're going to town,
come with us.
But I haven't finished
preparations for tonight yet.
[MASTER]
Just for a little while.
Come on, Aoi.
Don't you wanna eat tasty food?
[AOI gasps]
[AOI]
So good!
[CLERK]
Oh, good day to you, Master!
[AOI] So, this is
the Ginten district, then?
I've been wanting to check
it out ever since I saw it
from way up in the sky!
Aoi, wait!
You're going to get lost
if you stray
too far away from us!
[AOI]
Don't worry!
I can see Tenjin-ya!
Plus! I've got my fan!
She really terrifies
me, that girl.
Yes. She takes
after her grandfather.
Hey, I can hear you guys!
[OSONO]
Here, our freshly picked tea.
Oh, my! You're the ogre bride!
[AOI]
Huh?
[OSONO]
You're famous!
[AOI groans]
I'm in the paper!
[OSONO]
The master's recent engagement
has been quite the hot
topic of discussion
around here
in the women's club.
I heard that all the girls
who wanted a chance
with the master
were so disappointed
that they stayed in their beds
for three whole days.
You're such a trouble maker,
Miss Ogre Bride.
[AOI] I wish I could stay
in bed for three days.
[AOI]
That's a lot of ogre masks.
[GINJI]
The master innkeeper
is also the ruler
of the Northeast Land.
He's popular,
so ogre masks are too.
[AOI] Huh. I'm looking
for one in particular.
I don't see it.
Hey!
[gasps]
[ROKUSUKE]
What is it?
Girl?
[ROKUSUKE sniffs]
I know that smell.
So you're a human girl.
[ROKUSUKE]
Could it be?
[MASTER]
What are you doing?
[ROKUSUKE gasps]
[ROKUSUKE] Oh! Master
Innkeeper of Tenjin-ya!
Thank you for your continued
patronage, sir.
You know him?
We're grateful
to do business
with you as well, Rokusuke.
Aoi.
This is Master Rokusuke
from Mizumaki farm.
They sell us fruit and
vegetables at wholesale prices.
What?
We get our produce
from his farm?
Are you the ones who sell us
that delicious cherry juice?
[ROKUSUKE]
Yes.
It's great!
Pardon me, Master.
Could this young lady
be your young wife,
about whom I've been
hearing so much?
Wife? Uh.
[MASTER]
Indeed, I'm impressed.
I sensed the
spiritual power in her
from our cucumbers.
[AOI]
Huh? Sensed cucumbers?
She appeared to be a human,
so I just put it together.
Anyway, better be going!
Good day!
Uh, uh...
Thank you for your business!
[MASTER] Why did you go off
by yourself?
[WAITRESS]
Welcome, Masters!
Thank you for waiting!
Three chicken tempura meals!
How lucky that is was
Master Rokusuke you saw.
A more violent ayakashi
would have devoured you.
I'm sorry.
[MASTER]
Unbelievable.
I'm starting
to sympathize with mothers
who have to chase
after their children
running around
wherever they please.
I'm not a child,
and you are not my mother!
For your safety, remain
with me when we're out.
[GINJI] Now, now, Master,
it's okay. Stop.
Aoi feels bad enough,
so, let's move past it!
And the chicken tempura plates
are going to get cold.
--[AOI] Let's eat!
--[GINJI] Yes, let's eat!
This chicken's so good!
Such a light flavor!
Yes, this area is well
known for its tempura.
Do you know
how to make tempura?
We could add some dishes
to the Moonflower menu.
I do, and I'll consider that!
By the way,
why did you switch
to your childlike form?
[GINJI]
What?
[chuckles]
Why? Is that bad?
Ginji uses his
shapeshifting skills
to get close to people
and sometimes
to take advantage of them.
Heh.
When he wants me
to pay for his meals,
he always conveniently
chooses this form.
[AOI]
Great strategy.
[GINJI]
Well... Heh, heh...
You two really crack me up.
You seem to have such
a friendly relationship.
Is that because you've been
working together so long?
Actually, I haven't been
employed at Tenjin-ya
for very long.
I believe it's only been
about 50 years or so.
Fifty years is a lot!
Ginji was working
for our top competitor
before he came
to join my staff,
but then I swooped in
and poached him away.
[AOI]
Is that true?
Well, that's not
the whole story.
Ah. What a tasty meal!
Jeez, do these
stairs ever end?
[GINJI] It's great to exercise
after dinner!
This particular
Ogre Gate Iwato Shrine
brings divine favor
for matchmaking.
Now is the perfect time
for you to visit it.
What? I don't understand.
[GINJI] This shrine's
matchmaking benefits businesses.
It shines good fortune
on professional networks
and associations.
That makes sense.
[MASTER] Aoi, good business
is about much more
than simply turning a profit.
That's only one small part.
You must make yourself
indispensable to clients.
Create deep relationships
and bring value
to every encounter.
That's important.
Interesting. I like that.
I hope Moonflower
brings great joy
to everyone who
comes to eat there.
[AOI]
Me, too!
[AOI gasping]
[AOI] I've encountered
all kinds of ayakashi,
especially since I came
to the hidden realm.
I know I'll be meeting so many
more in the days still to come.
I want ayakashi
to enjoy Moonflower,
and to feel happy every time
they come through its doors.
[AOI]
Welcome, everyone!
I want to thank each of you
for being here tonight!
Because of you
Moonflower's open now,
and I hope you enjoy
celebrating with us!
[MATSUBA]
Well, my friends. Here's to Aoi,
and to Moonflower's success.
May its prosperity never end!
Cheers!
[ALL]
[AOI laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[MATSUBA]
No, I'll never leave!
You can get along without me!
I wanna stay with Aoi! Stop it!
You can always come back
and eat here again!
[MATSUBA]
...you put me down!
[sighs] I'm beat!
[GINJI]
Well, Aoi...
Huh?
I would call that a success!
[cutlery clattering]
[MATSUBA] Aoi's food is
the best I've ever tasted!
[AOI]
I agree.
I'm so glad they
enjoyed themselves.
They'll be back, right?
I would love to have
some regulars.
I've just gotta
keep working hard.
[GINJI]
Yes.
[rain pouring]
[CHIBI]
It's been a whole week now.
And nobody's come here to eat!
[AOI]
You don't have to rub it in.
Should we turn this
into a cucumber stand?
[CHIBI]
Aw, yeah! A cucumber stand?
I'm all for that!
We'll change the name!
Hurry and make a new sign!
[GINJI]
Aoi! We've got a major problem!
We've just been summoned,
by the head
of the accounting office.
Uh?
[steady tapping]
Um. Hi.
[tap]
[BYAKUYA]
Yes, how do you do?
I'm the chief of accounting
here at Tenjin-ya.
I'm in charge of this
establishment's finances.
My name is Byakuya.
So...
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
[CHIBI squeals]
Aoi had to go see
a scary-looking man!
What's gonna happen?
Is Moonflower gonna
be forced to close?
Aoi, you've gotta
do something!