It's straight from
the Imperial Court.
Wait, what?
The Imperial Court?
From the Royal Family?
[BYAKUYA]
Indeed.
I would like you
to cook a special meal
for Master Nuinoin and his wife
on their anniversary.
[AOI] Hold on a minute.
The Royal Family?
You want me to cook
for those fancy ayakashi ?
Yes, Mistress Ritsuko
is originally
from the apparent realm,
actually.
[AOI gasps]
[BYAKUYA] She heard about
Moonflower's reputation.
And she requested
your cooking.
I assume it's because
she feels nostalgic at times
for the food from the
realm of her birth.
So, Aoi, will you
accept this job?
Yes, I accept.
I'll do it,
and I'll give it my best!
[thunder rumbles]
[rain pouring]
[AOI]
Am I locked in a storeroom?
[DARUMA C] I'm only
keeping you down there
for about two days.
--[AOI] Huh?
--[DARUMA C] You know,
until the royal couple's
anniversary has passed.
You what?! Hold on!
Why would you...?!
[DARUMA C laughing]
[AOI whimpers]
[thunder crashes]
[crying]
[whimpers]
[rain pouring]
Hello?
Are you gonna eat me?
[thunder crashes]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Are you not afraid?
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] Aren't
you going to call for help?
[AOI]
No.
I'm not scared
of you at all,
because I'm gonna
die soon, anyway.
[whimpers]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Don't worry.
You have nothing
to fear, Aoi.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
You're safe now.
You're not going to die.
[rain pouring]
[thunder crashes]
[AOI groans]
So cold. From the rain?
[gasps]
[AOI]
What is this place?
A refrigerated room?
[amulet hums]
[gasps]
Right, the pendant.
It feels warm.
--[thunder crashes]
--[AOI whimpers]
[AOI grunting]
[banging]
[panting]
[AOI grunts]
[grunting]
[yelps]
Let me out!
Someone please
let me out of here!
I have to be somewhere!
There's something I have to do!
I'm scared. Help me.
[AOI] It's so dark.
So cold. I can't breathe.
[pendant humming]
[MASTER muffled]
Aoi! Can you hear me?
Don't be afraid.
You have nothing to fear, Aoi.
[AOI]
Is this real,
or am I still dreaming
about when I was little?
[AOI]
Master, is that you?
What happened? Am I dead?
She opened her eyes!
I think she's waking up!
You're such a lucky devil.
I don't know how you do it.
Humans aren't usually
quite as tough
as you seem to be,
in your own way.
[gasps]
No, Aoi, don't.
You're not
supposed to be up yet.
What time is it now?
You remember going to the
eastern land yesterday, right?
It's a little past noon
on the following day.
Tonight's the
Royal Anniversary!
--I've gotta--
--No!
I think not,
you almost died!
What?
The young master brought
the news back here.
And when the master heard,
he skipped the Hachiyo Night
Meeting in Youto entirely,
just so he could find you,
and rescue you himself.
I put my trust in you
to take care of the rest.
[inhales, exhales]
If you must go,
I won't stop you.
Thank you for being
so dependable.
Oh it was him, then.
I didn't dream
that he saved me.
[AOI]
When it all happened,
I was so dizzy
and disoriented.
Do you wanna know
who locked you up Aoi?
It was the kitchen apprentices,
those three dumb daruma.
What? They did it?
It's terrible!
Those reckless jerks
locked you
in the market's
underground storeroom!
They said they meant
you no harm,
but that room
isn't used much,
so no one knew the cooling
system was broken.
Still, what they did
was very dangerous!
They should
have known better.
Human girls are frail.
Where are the master
and the others right now?
My supervision was
sorely lacking, sir.
I wouldn't dare ask you
to forgive them.
They're idiots,
but I know they didn't
mean to hurt her.
They only did it in the hope
that I would cook for
the Royal Couple instead.
And so, with deep regrets,
I must resign.
[DARUMAS gasp]
[CHIEF CHEF]
I'll leave Tenjin-ya at once.
Stop this! Now!
You can't leave Tenjin-ya,
Chief Chef,
'cause I refuse to let you!
Uh...
...are you attempting
to defend those
who put you
in such grave danger?
Huh?
No way, but the Chief Chef
can't quit now!
If he does, I'll never
get the opportunity
to try his full-course dinner!
Uh?
[AOI]
If you're gonna leave,
then the least you could do
is wait until I've had a chance
to try your cooking!
[gasps]
[laughing]
Hey! Stop that!
You don't have to laugh
at me in front of everyone!
Aoi, aren't you
the slightest bit angry?
Of course I am!
Ordinarily, I'd forgive.
But now, to top it off,
he'd rob me of the chance
to taste his special menu!
[stomach growls]
[laughing]
She's so selfish!
Frivolous!
Her pointless arguments!
She certainly
is Shiro's granddaughter!
Fine, laugh at me
if you want.
[GINJI gasps]
Oh, thanks, Ginji.
I'm glad you're okay.
Don't worry about me.
I'm very sorry.
I let you down yesterday.
What're you talking about?
I'm here now, aren't I?
[gasps]
[MASTER] This amulet
led me to your location
in the market storeroom.
This thing? That's how
you were able to save me?
The ogre fire
is like a familiar.
I can find it anywhere,
but this particular flame
will soon die.
Ah, I found it.
Here, Aoi. Eat this.
Do you always keep
dorayaki in your clothes?
As for you, Chief Chef...
You said you'd be
willing to quit
in order to
settle this matter.
But my ogre bride has
expressed her discontentment
with that solution,
and she is terrifying.
I cannot go against
the wishes of my future wife,
so all of you
must remain in my employ
for the foreseeable future.
Alas, you must
accept your fate.
A harsh one,
though it may be.
Yes, Master. I understand.
I'll happily serve
your ogre-bride
the full-course
Tenjin-ya meal, on the house!
What? For free?
Of course.
[laughing] You're a shrewd one!
Aoi, you take some time
to recuperate from this ordeal.
Leave the Royal
Anniversary to me.
I'll take care of it.
You should rest.
No way.
You can spoil me later.
Right now, I want to make sure
they have the perfect meal.
[gasps]
At this point,
there's not enough time
to serve the dishes
I had originally planned to,
but I'll have to
make it work anyway.
If I can't,
then do I even deserve
to run my own restaurant?
When is the Royal
Couple arriving?
We're expecting
them at 6:30.
That gives you
about four hours.
That's not enough time
for beef stew.
Mmm...
Honestly, I think
your usual cooking
is impressive enough, Aoi.
[AOI]
Huh? Do you really think so?
I've seen how you can improvise,
and you cook quickly,
even working with the
ingredients available to you.
Your food's never been anything
less than delicious.
The bento you made for me
was simply spectacular.
I swear the meat
melted in my mouth.
Are you serious?
--Hey, Aoi!
--[AOI] Huh?
Make the stewed
pork belly?
But I don't have
any more pork belly.
You're welcome to use
what we have in the kitchen.
[AOI]
Really?
Yes, it's the least I could do.
You're free to use
anything of ours,
don't even bother asking.
Thanks, Chief Chef!
I appreciate it!
I had better get back
to Moonflower.
Oh! Don't you worry!
I haven't forgotten
about you three just yet!
[DARUMAS gasp]
[AOI] You hurry up
and climb the mountain
out back right away!
And bring me some hot
spring eggs and ramune!
[DARUMAS]
Ah! Yes, ma'am!
Thanks, Ginji.
For all those nice things
you said back there.
It really meant a lot.
Well, the whole mess
was all my fault
to begin with.
I should have been
more cautious.
I can imagine
how scary it was,
trapped in such
a small, dark, cold, place.
And you were hungry, too.
It sounds just like--
[gasps]
What, Ginji?
When you get back
to Moonflower,
don't you dare start before
you eat a little something.
It'll be a while
before we get the pork belly,
so, there's time to take
care of yourself first.
Welcome back, Aoi!
Did O-Ryo leave already?
She had to go to work.
Huh?
[KASUGA] Oh! O-Ryo made
those before she left.
She told me she just reheated
some leftover rice
that you had frozen.
This kamaboko is from the
souvenir shop here at Tenjin-ya.
I had them give me the ones
that were about to expire.
You guys. Wow.
Whelp, I'm headed to work!
[GINJI] I know they're just
hoping for a reward,
but it's still nice
that they help you for free.
[water sloshing]
[cutlery clinking]
[chopping]
[sizzling]
[AOI] It's almost 6:30.
Not much time left.
[AOI groans]
I'm hot.
They're walking up now.
[gasps]
Welcome to Moonflower.
We hope you found it easily.
Thank you, we enjoyed the walk.
We appreciate all of this.
I know we didn't
give much notice.
So, we're all
the more grateful.
And we're grateful
that you chose
to celebrate at Moonflower.
Your anniversary
is very special.
We're so glad you're
spending it with us.
Might you be
the fair bento maiden--
the one Hakkabou raves about?
Yes. Um...
My name is Aoi Tsubaki.
[gasps]
Well then,
please allow me
to show you to your table.
Lovely! Just delightful!
This is a nice "hole-in-the-wall
place," right, darling?
[laughs] I agree, my love.
Thank you very much.
Uh, this is cucumber
and okra in plum-miso
mayonnaise.
Oh! Mayonnaise
is a sauce made of--
Wow. Nui, did you hear that?
She said it's dressed
in mayonnaise!
I haven't eaten that in ages!
You mean you've had it?
I just assumed
that you hadn't.
Yes, but, well, it was rare
when I was in the
apparent realm.
Of course,
that was in wartime.
It was like gold.
Well these days,
it's quite affordable.
But, since it's still hard
to get in the hidden realm,
I whipped up this batch.
Wow, did you really?
How lovely!
[AOI]
Now drop this off!
Got it!
[BOTH laughing]
[GINJI]
Thank you for your patience.
Fried eggplant with
grated daikon in ponzu.
Wow.
[sighs]
Back to work.
I can't afford
to take a break right now!
Thank you both
for waiting.
The stewed pork belly!
[sobs softly]
[AOI]
What's the matter?
Does she not like it?
--[RITSUKO cries]
--[NUINOIN] Mmm?
[AOI]
I knew it.
Um, Madam?
[RITSUKO]
The taste brings back memories.
I never imagined
that I'd have stewed
pork belly in the hidden realm.
I'm so overwhelmed.
[crying softly]
[gasps]
Oh, my love.
Is it a dish from your hometown
in the apparent realm?
[gasps]
I'm sorry to startle you
like that, dear.
Mm-mm.
[RITSUKO]
It was all very delicious.
The pork belly
tastes like home.
I come from a town
called Nagasaki.
To think that, even at my age,
a flavor still has the power
to make me feel homesick.
[AOI]
I have to wonder.
Did the master
suggest that dish
because he knew
it was special to her?
Perfect. Every bit.
Yes, it is, indeed.
Pardon, but could I trouble
you for some white rice?
[AOI]
Of course!
[water boiling]
This just keeps
getting better!
I think it's about time
for seconds.
[NUINOIN] My stomach says no,
but my taste buds say yes!
All right.
Time to prepare dessert.
[BOTH gasp]
[AOI] And for the
final dish of the evening,
I've prepared
a fruit salad.
It's so pretty!
Almost looks like jewelry!
Don't you agree, Nui?
[NUINOIN]
Yes, it does!
I wonder what this one is.
[BOTH laughing]
[sighs]
[MASTER] Aoi worked
a little too hard today.
I'm very sorry, sir.
The fault is all mine.
I should have watched
her more closely.
You've been repeating
that same line a lot today,
haven't you?
I keep forcing you to look
after this reckless girl,
so, I share
the responsibility.
Don't worry about it too much.
Raise your head, dear Ginji.
Are you sure you don't
blame me for her state?
I can bear it, sir.
Bear what?
[GINJI] A stricter punishment.
I deserve it.
Don't tell me you question
my authority on the matter.
[GINJI]
No! Not at all.
Well, when Byakuya returns,
he'll have his say.
[MASTER]
He might agree with you
that I've been too lenient,
so be prepared.
He may suggest a salary cut.
And I will respectfully
accept it.
You know, she's an
amazing young woman.
To say that Master Nuinoin
and Mistress Reetsko
enjoyed her cooking
is an understatement.
They were so grateful,
the lady even wept over it.
[MASTER] What do you think
about Aoi's abduction?
We know the daruma
were involved,
they admitted as much,
but were they the only ones?
No.
The paralysis
technique was used.
And spiriting away, as well.
I find it hard to believe,
honestly,
that the daruma
could have mastered
such advanced practices.
[MASTER]
If you're calling them advanced,
then whoever used them must be
powerful ayakashi, indeed.
[GINJI]
I wonder if the assassin
who attacked Aoi
in the courtyard
could also have been connected
to her abduction somehow.
I believe the likelihood
of that is quite high.
Was it an employee?
Or someone above me?
Perhaps a Hachiyo,
or someone higher?
[MASTER]
Or could it be, Orio-ya?
[GINJI gasps]
[AOI groans]
Where am I?
Oh, Aoi. I'm so glad
that you're awake!
Ginji, hi.
[screams]
Did I miss the Royal Dinner?
Or do something
even worse than that?
Please tell me
I didn't pass out
before serving their dessert!
[GINJI] Aoi, please, calm down
and take a breath!
Everything went perfectly
with the anniversary dinner.
Oh, that's right.
I collapsed at the end.
They loved it.
Mistress Ritsuko
was especially impressed.
You passed out
just after they left.
They had no idea
anything was wrong.
Huh?
Oh, good. It seems
your fever has broken.
[stomach growling]
Not again. Sheesh.
Heh. I'm hungry, too.
I'll be waiting
for you out front.
[door closes]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[sighs]
Oh, hi.
I didn't know
you were in there.
Aoi, you sure toss
and turn a lot.
You almost crushed me
a dozen times.
While you were out
with a fever,
the fox had a hard time
trying to get you
back on the futon.
It was hilarious.
You were sleeping
for a long time.
I'm super hungry now.
There were some cucumbers
left in the fridge, right?
You could have helped
yourself to those.
I waited for you
to wake up,
so you could feed me.
[gasps]
Oh no.
I'll make you
something right away.
Om, nom, nom, nom,
nom, nom, nom, nom.
Did you buy all of
this fancy stuff
at the foreign
delicacy market?
[AOI]
I did.
Ingredients for making
beef stew, some flour,
and spices for making curry.
You'll make
good use of it all.
You can just serve it
in the restaurant.
I guess this means
I'll have to come up
with some new menu items, huh?
By the way,
who do you think
that girl could have been?
What girl?
The zashiki-warashi.
The one who came in here
the other day.
[AOI] I saw her in the harbor
town in the eastern land.
I wandered off after her,
like I was lured away
against my will.
[AOI] A very young girl
with blonde hair.
[gasps]
She was blonde?
A zashiki-warashi?
--What is it?
--[GINJI gasps]
It's just what you're
describing is rare.
Zashiki-warashi
aren't usually blonde.
[CHIBI]
You've worked so hard, Aoi!
What? Now it's time
to have our reward?
Delicious food? Yay!
Let's eat Tenjin-ya's
full-course cucumbers!