[HATORI]
Hello?
Is it a Tenjin-ya policy
to make guests wait in
the lobby for an eternity?
[GINJI]
Orio-ya...
My most sincere apologies.
[TOKIHIKO] It's our own
fault for showing up
without a reservation like this.
There's nothing the front
desk manager can do for us.
At any rate, Akatsuki,
it's hilarious that
you're front desk manager.
Did you forget you're the one
who appointed me to this
position when you left?
Please wait just a moment, sir.
Heh!
Ah!
Hey, Ginji, it's been forever!
You traitor to Orio-ya.
[grunts]
[AOI] I guess he and Ginji
know each other?
[KASUGA]
Yeah.
Ginji used to work at Orio-ya
before coming here.
I didn't know that.
We regret having to
turn you away, sir.
But, unfortunately, our inn
is fully booked at this time.
It's been a while,
so I was looking forward to it.
What a shame.
Hatori.
It's out of their hands.
Reservations are a must
during the busy season.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm very sorry.
[HATORI] Are you sure there's
no way to accommodate us?
[AOI] I could let them
have the room I'm in.
[gasps]
It's not like
I really need it.
I can sleep in Moonflower.
I've already enjoyed everything
I've wanted to anyway.
Aoi, there's no need.
We got lucky, Mister Nobu!
Say hello to the sweet lady,
now, like a good doggie.
[barks]
[laughs]
Ginji.
I'm glad to see you
looking so well.
But usually, the master
comes out to greet us.
Is he away at the moment?
Yes, he is.
And, uh, the bath caretaker?
Shizuna?
Never mind, forget it.
Hatori, let's go visit
the hot springs first.
Hmph!
Uh...
Looks like we've taken
on some unwelcome guests.
Damn right.
That's Hatori, a tengu,
and the front desk manager
at Orio-ya.
His cohort, Tokihiko, is the
chief bath caretaker there.
Ah, right.
[AKATSUKI]
Back to work, everybody!
[EMPLOYEES]
Yes, sir!
And I'm sleeping at work!
Now I'm here
and I can't sleep.
Guess I could make
myself useful.
[CHIBI crying]
Uh, what's the matter?
[SYSTEM]
You've got mail!
[AOI]
Quit screaming!
I wonder if that means
I've got a message
from the master on this thing.
Is he already
in the apparent realm?
--[chiming]
--[AOI gasps]
[MASTER] They said you gave up
your room to the guests
from Orio-ya.
Yeah, it was probably
a good choice.
I wanted to cook
at Moonflower, anyway.
[MASTER] If you want me to bring
you something from here,
let me know.
What do I need
from that realm?
Huh.
I'll have to think about it.
[TOKIHIKO]
But why not, Shizuna?
After all this time!
Will you please
just let me go?
Excuse me,
what's going on here?
This is none of your
concern, don't interrupt, human.
I came to get Shizuna, and
that's between her and myself.
[gasps] But, that's--
I'm sorry about this.
[TOKIHIKO gasps]
Whoa, nice work!
[SHIZUNA]
Come on!
Shizuna, come back, please!
Hear me out!
[SHIZUNA]
Tokihiko is a shiranui,
an ayakashi who possesses
the highest grade of fire
in this realm.
He's a great yokai
and my teacher,
who took me in and
looked after me.
So he's your mentor?
Career-wise?
That's right.
Now he wants me to come back
to Orio-ya and work there.
He says he never wanted me
to leave to begin with.
Huh. In that case,
are you planning to go
back there and work with him?
Oh, no, ma'am.
I have no intention
of leaving Tenjin-ya.
I want to work here.
I owe the master so much
for taking me in,
and I have my own apprentice
to think of, as well.
[AOI]
Ah, Kazune, right.
I get that Tokihiko
was your teacher,
but, um, still,
don't you hate him
for barging in
and putting you on the spot?
No. I could never hate him!
Sometimes he comes off
as serious
and a little extreme
in the way he expresses himself.
He's very overprotective
and persistent.
He misunderstands
things easily,
and then he gets
his feelings hurt.
If I'm perfectly honest,
he can be a gloomy pain
in the neck most of the time.
But I've always felt
close to him.
--[gasps]
--Huh?
No. Not like that.
Not like what?
After all.
I'm just a nure-onna with
no real redeeming qualities,
born in a poor, mountainous
part of the southern land.
But Tokihiko rescued me.
He brought me up strictly
but always cared for me well.
[SHIZUNA] I'm grateful
for his influence,
and I know he changed
my fate for the better.
[SHIZUNA] Tenjin-ya has
the best hot springs
in the hidden realm,
and in order to compete
with them,
Orio-ya spent
a great deal of money
to find new sources.
Motivated by the desire
to help my teacher,
I searched all over for unknown
thermal spring veins,
until one day,
I finally found a new source.
But it was in a
forbidden place, full of magic,
where we weren't supposed
to be digging.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
Shizuna!
No, Teacher!
[SHIZUNA] My teacher shielded me
from the demon,
and in doing so,
was injured
in a way that
scarred him for life.
That blue flame
at his forehead
is the visible manifestation
of his power continually
leaking from the scar.
Since I caused such a
great loss for Orio-ya,
they decided to terminate
my employment.
Master Tokihiko
defended me
and fought for my job
to the very end.
But I wasn't able
to forgive myself.
[footsteps]
[SHIZUNA]
Then one day,
the master of Tenjin-ya
found me and took me in.
It's been a long time
since I enjoyed a hot meal
that someone prepared
just for me!
Oh, I almost forgot this.
Thanks for lending it to me.
[SHIZUNA]
You're welcome.
This is the first thing
my teacher ever gave to me
not long after I met him.
Hi, teacher!
[SHIZUNA]
While I was in training,
he used to tie my hair back
with this string,
so it's special to me.
I can tell how much you
adore Tokihiko,
so why don't you go back
to be with him?
I guess...
I don't quite feel
I've paid my penance yet.
But I think I will soon.
I've decided to work hard here
at Tenjin-ya until that day.
The master told me
something interesting.
He said that
a lot of the people
who come to this inn
regularly say
that your baths
are a major draw for them.
[gasps]
[AOI] People are so impressed
with your work
that they're raving about it.
Honestly, I'm a little
jealous of that!
[chuckles]
[AOI]
Here you go.
What's this?
[AOI]
It's a dessert called sorbet.
Red eggplants?
That's a new one!
Is that what you call tomatoes
in the hidden realm?
[SHIZUNA]
This is so tasty!
My teacher loves to grow
his own produce.
He especially likes tending
to his red eggplants.
I used to dislike vegetables,
but over time,
as I helped him cook,
I came to like them
more and more.
Makes sense.
--Ah, found you at last!
--[AOI] What's up?
Emergency senior staff meeting.
I bet it's about those guys
from Orio-ya.
Oh, you're right.
Thank you, Aoi.
I feel a lot better now,
for some reason.
Happy to hear it!
--[KASUGA] C'mon, hurry!
--[SHIZUNA] I am!
That poor girl.
I understand what it's like
to have complicated feelings.
I bet Tokihiko's
got the wrong idea.
He probably just thinks
that Shizuna's rejecting him,
but it's not like that at all.
My dear.
[SHIZUNA]
He looked thin to me.
Gaunt, even.
Maybe it's because
of his injury.
Still, I'm not ready.
I haven't earned
the right to go back.
Are you okay?
You look kind of sick.
[SHIZUNA gasps]
Yes, I'm fine.
Sorry to make you worry.
[BOTH gasp]
[tinkles]
[AOI]
There must be some way
I can help Shizuna
and Tokihiko.
I'm at a loss,
I don't know what to do.
[SYSTEM] You've got mail!
You've got mail!
That startled me.
[SYSTEM] You've got mail!
You've got mail!
[AOI] "Have you decided
what you want from here?"
The master can be so kind.
I'd like to ask you to run
some errands for me.
[MASTER] I hear that
"running errands"
is one of the husband's duties
in the apparent realm.
[AOI] I want you to bring me
some chocolate, please.
[MASTER] Would you like me
to bring any particular brand?
[AOI] A big bag of generic,
semi-sweet, baking chocolate.
Oh, and I also
need dry yeast,
baking powder, and flour.
[MASTER]
Good, just leave it to me.
I look forward to trying
some of your bread.
[AOI] I wonder whether
the master approves of me
as a Tenjin-ya employee.
If he expected something
that I wasn't doing,
he would tell me,
wouldn't he?
I hope so.
[MASTER] Make sure you're taking
good care of everyone
at Tenjin-ya while I'm gone.
[gasps]
[MASTER]
Good night, Aoi.
I'll do my very best running
errands for you tomorrow.
I know you will.
You have a good night,
too, Master.
I do cook with confidence.
I have no doubts there.
[AOI]
I'm glad to have learned
how much Shizuna and Tokihiko
like tomatoes.
That knowledge could
prove very useful.
[dog grunts]
[AOI]
You're that dog from Orio-ya!
Huh? Bad dog!
[TOKIHIKO] Have you seen--
Uh. What're you doing?
Hey!
Hi there. [chuckles]
He took your food!
Was it for sale?
No, sir. It was just
a little experiment.
It's all right.
That's a relief.
[AOI]
Shizuna was just here--
What, did you
say Shizuna?
Yes, I did.
I've decided to work
hard here at Tenjin-ya
until that day.
Never mind.
Forget I mentioned her.
Well, then.
Awkward.
[GINJI]
Aoi?
Did something just happen?
What's wrong?
[AOI]
So that dog.
Is he a staff member
at Orio-ya?
Well, he functions
first and foremost
as the inn's unofficial mascot.
He's been there ever since
Orio-ya's inception.
His official title is
"advertising manager,"
and the staff all
call him "Mister Nobu."
These have a nice,
simple flavor.
Yeah, in the apparent realm,
snacks made from okara
are very popular.
They're low calorie
and have lots of fiber.
I bet Mister Nobunaga
was lured in here by the smell.
Aoi, are you sure you're okay?
What? Yeah.
I'm positive.
--[sizzling]
--Huh? Uh!
[BOY]
Yeah!
[CHILDREN laughing]
No running in the hallway!
I mean it.
Please slow down.
[CHILDREN]
Scary man!
[AKATSUKI]
Stop right now!
Akatsuki hasn't changed
in the least.
[TOKIHIKO]
Shizuna!
[SHIZUNA]
I told you.
I can't come back to Orio-ya
with you, and that's final!
[sobs softly]
[TOKIHIKO]
I'm begging you.
[SHIZUNA]
I'm sorry about this!
--[SHIZUNA grunts]
--[TOKIHIKO groans]
[SHIZUNA crying]
[TOKIHIKO groans]
Are you okay down there?
I think she hates me.
Not that I blame her.
I can understand why.
I'm overprotective, serious,
and annoyingly
persistent, too.
Believe me.
[crying]
Um, sir,
pull yourself together.
Shizuna left this
hair tie behind
when she was asked to leave.
I've kept it safe
this entire time.
[TOKIHIKO] She won't come back
to work with me ever again,
or so it seems.
I suppose I had better
return this to her.
[TOKIHIKO] You and Shizuna
appear to be close,
if I'm not mistaken.
Please give her that,
if you don't mind.
Will do.
Ugh. What should I do?
Aoi, is the sorbet ready yet?
Wait a sec.
Isn't this the same string
that you returned
to Shizuna earlier today?
[AOI]
It's just like it.
But I guess it was a pair.
Meaning they're two identical
strings that go together.
[CHIBI]
I wouldn't have guessed that.
[AOI] But if I do give
this one to Shizuna,
those two might
not speak again.
Hey, Shizuna.
Oh, hello there!
[AOI]
Do you have a moment?
[SHIZUNA]
Huh? Yes.
[AOI] I made something
that I'd like you to have.
It's called tomato ketchup.
[SHIZUNA]
"Ketchup"?
[gasps]
I can smell the red eggplant!
Here, give this a taste.
[SHIZUNA giggles]
[AOI]
How is it?
Delicious!
Imagine a condiment
that has all the flavor
of a tasty red eggplant!
I want to put it on everything!
[AOI] Yep, and you can make
sauces with it, too.
I have a lot,
so this jar's all yours.
Wow, thank you!
And if you wouldn't mind,
could you teach me
how to make things
with this ketchup stuff?
Be happy to!
You love tomatoes, don't you?
I do, very much!
Do you think it's partly
'cause they remind you
of your teacher?
[gasps]
[AOI] If I teach you to cook
with ketchup,
it'll be my first-time cooking
with a female friend.
[SHIZUNA]
That's surprising!
[AOI]
Yeah.
I didn't have many friends
before I came here.
[AOI]
Try it with some ketchup, too.
[GINJI]
Okay.
That's great!
It's a wonderful complement
to the beef-wrapped okra!
I agree!
And save room, 'cause
there's tomato sorbet, too.
Ginji.
You've known both
Tokihiko and Shizuna
for a long time,
haven't you--
back in the days
when you worked at Orio-ya?
That's right.
But it's not like we were
especially close, or anything.
Why do you want to know?
Well, she might want
to go back and work there.
I know she misses
her teacher a whole lot.
[GINJI] But she can't
go back to Orio-ya.
Because she caused
such a serious injury?
I know she still has
regrets about all that,
even though Tokihiko
forgave her a long time ago.
No, she can't return
because she was fired.
This isn't just a problem
between teacher
and student anymore.
She has a very strong
sense of duty,
and I'm sure
she feels an obligation
to stay at Tenjin-ya
because the master took her in.
So, then what is
she supposed to do?
[GINJI]
She's trying her best.
Isn't that why she's been
avoiding Tokihiko
altogether while he's here?
You might be right, but, still,
I don't think that's
a long-term solution.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
be of more help.
Even though it may be futile,
I could never just sit
back and do nothing.
Because I understand
how they both must be feeling.
Good morning, Tokihiko.
[dog barks]
[AOI] Um, would you be
interested in having dinner
at Moonflower this evening?
Don't worry, it would
be on the house.
[TOKIHIKO]
Uh...
I thought you might like
to have a casual dinner
without anybody bothering you.
But, I--
Great idea!
Hatori!
This guy's so boring,
he isn't interested in eating.
Although, I gotta say,
he wasn't always like this.
Please shut up!
How would you like
some new tomato dishes?
Tomatoes?
I do like those a lot.
Uh?
[AOI] You wanna give
this back to Shizuna?
Then you should do it yourself.
We'll be waiting for you
at Moonflower.
[AOI] Don't run, be brave
and tell him how you feel.
Pretend like your fears
don't exist.
You just gotta
take a deep breath
and be true to yourself!
Just tell him what
you really desire.
Share your deepest
wishes for your life!
Deepest wishes?
I smell tomatoes!
Is that tonight's
main ingredient?
Sure is, and with
Shizuna helping me,
we'll get it all finished
even sooner than I thought!
[SHIZUNA] I'm so grateful
you gave me this opportunity
to learn how to cook
so many tomato dishes!
[GINJI]
Indeed!
Now I'm creating
a Napolitan dish,
but with udon noodles
in place of spaghetti!
[GINJI]
Wow, really?
But we don't have any sausage
or bacon around here.
We'll make meatballs instead
with minced pork and beef.
So I'll call it, "Udon
Napolitan with Meatballs!"
[SHIZUNA]
How can I help with that?
I'm going to put you in
charge of making the meatballs,
which are the most
important part!
And Tokihiko's
going to help you!
[clears throat]
What? Teacher, you're here?
That's quite a surprise.
I'm making meatballs
with my teacher?
We've got quite
a few reservations,
so I need you to make
as many as possible.
But I--
[AOI]
Hatori told me that Tokihiko
isn't interested
in food these days,
and I don't like
the sound of that.
Okay. I'll do it.
I'd be honored to cook
with my teacher,
to work with him
after all this time.
[TOKIHIKO gasps]
Hey, Tokihiko!
Shizuna might want
to use that string,
if you happen
to have it on you.
Shizuna.
Yes, sir?
You should tie
your hair back
if you're going
to prepare food.
[gasps]
[SHIZUNA]
Yes, sir!
Thank you, teacher!
Of course.
This is adorable!
Looks like we're ready to begin.
It's time to wash your hands
and get started rolling
those meatballs!
[AOI] Once you've rolled
all the meat,
then we'll sear those
to perfection on the griddle!
[SHIZUNA]
Right!
[sizzling]
[TOKIHIKO]
Done.
Oh, wow!
It's perfect!
I'm so glad!
Now, let's eat some!
Tasty.
I've never had this before,
and yet it tastes so familiar.
Yes.
One day, I'll have
paid for my mistakes,
and I'll be useful again.
Then I can come back to you.
Well, you'll always
have a place you can return to.
So, keep working hard,
and I'll wait for you.
That girl is even
sharper than I thought.
Hmm.
[CHIBI] I'm glad that
sweet nure-onna
and her teacher
patched things up!
Ah! But now a tengu
has appeared?
This is scary!
Will Moonflower get torn apart?