That ship.
Whose is it?
Could it be...?
It's one of Orio-ya's.
[gasps]
You're kidding me!
They sent the master
ship over here?
Why would they go to
all that trouble for us?
Ranmaru.
[HIDEYOSHI]
Testing, testing.
I trust you can all hear me?
[AOI]
The same mask.
Oh, that's right.
Apparently it's common
in the southern land.
[HAKKABOU]
Well, I did purchase this one
in the southern land. Yep.
[HIDEYOSHI]
Pardon our late visit.
This is the Seiran-maru
from Orio-ya.
We have come to retrieve
our employees.
Well, don't just stand there.
The head of Orio-ya
would like to say hello.
[AOI gasping]
I appreciate that you
would go to the trouble
of coming all the way here.
Lead manager of
Orio-ya, Ranmaru.
What business do you have?
[RANMARU]
"Business"?
I believe we said we're here
to say hello, didn't we?
I hear that you've been treating
our employees quite well.
Heh.
Uh!
Ranmaru here's no joke.
He's called the "dog god,"
because he's a komainu.
On top of that, he's also the
lead manager over at Orio-ya.
[AOI]
"Dog god"? "Lead manager"?
Then is he like the equivalent
to our master?
Well yeah, officially he is,
but there's one key difference.
Unlike here,
there's someone higher up
on the food chain
than him at Orio-ya.
And who would that be?
[HIDEYOSHI]
Mistress Ougon-Douji
will now honor you
with her presence!
[TENJINYA murmur]
[AOI]
This light!
I've seen it somewhere before.
[gasps]
That's what I thought.
It's that girl.
Mistress Ougon-Douji.
Uh...
Why are we kneeling,
who is that anyway?
The one I mentioned
who's above Ranmaru.
Mistress Ougon-Douji,
the real head of Orio-ya.
Are you serious?
That little girl?
She's also Tenjin-ya's founder.
What? She's our founder?
I've actually run
into her before.
But I assumed she
was a kid though.
[HATORI]
Far from it!
She was the very first mistress
innkeeper of Tenjin-ya.
Huh? But now she's Orio-ya's?
[HATORI] Uh-huh. She left
Tenjin-ya in the hands
of the master, and created
Orio-ya in the southern land.
That was all a really
long time ago.
[gasps]
[OUGON DOUJI]
People of Tenjin-ya.
Raise your heads.
It has been a while,
Master Ogre God.
[MASTER] To think that you
would come to Tenjin-ya.
What could possibly be worth
your personal appearance?
I was under the impression that
you'd never visit here again.
[laughs] Making sarcastic
remarks towards me?
My goodness. Relax.
We've come to retrieve
our employees, that's all.
You came yourself for that?
[OUGON DOUJI laughs]
Come now, you three.
You've spent enough time here.
Whatever you say, ma'am.
As you wish, mistress.
Know that I'll be looking
forward to the next time
we shall see each
other, Shizuna.
Yes, I'll do the same, Teacher.
I'll devote myself to work
until that day comes.
Heh.
[OUGON DOUJI]
Now...
Tenjin-ya's young master, Ginji.
[GINJI grunts]
You too shall return
to Orio-ya with us.
What?!
They're gonna take him?
Why Ginji? What do you mean?
[AOI]
Ginji...
[OUGON DOUJI]
That was supposed to be
the agreement from
the beginning.
That after working
50 years for Tenjin-ya,
you'd come back to Orio-ya.
[TENJINYA gasping]
There will be no objection.
This is a personal transfer,
so to speak.
Uh, I--
Can't we do something?
Forgive me,
Mistress Ougon-douji.
But what on earth
do you mean by that?
I know for a fact we've
never had a transfer done
for personal reasons
in the past.
Besides, Tenjin-ya and Orio-ya
are two different entitie--
Quiet. Accounting Chief Byakuya.
[gasps]
[OUGON DOUJI]
This isn't open for discussion.
Both inns owe their
existence to me.
I have the right to do
with them as I wish.
Isn't that right...
...Master Ogre God?
[MASTER]
Yes.
Master. You can't!
[gasps]
[OUGON DOUJI]
Hmph.
Ginji, that was an order
from Mistress Ougon-Douji.
Stand up and
come with us already.
[gasps] But, Ginji...
Yes, I understand.
[gasps]
[GINJI]
My co-workers at Tenjin-ya.
Thank you for everything.
I'm going back to Orio-ya now.
[gasps]
I'm sorry. I know it's sudden,
but there's something
that I need to do there.
[MASTER]
Ginji.
Are you okay with this?
I made this agreement
a long time ago.
[MASTER]
Then do as you will.
Someone stop him.
[O-RYO, KASUGA]
Young Master!
[AKATSUKI]
You're leaving us?!
So strange. Do you
think the young master
was a spy for Orio-ya
or something?
Of course not! No way!
Then again, who knows?
Why? I don't understand.
Ginji, wait!
[MASTER]
Stop it, Aoi. You can't.
But if we don't stop him,
he's gonna leave!
Yes, I know.
But he has made his
decision on the matter.
Why are you acting like
this is no big deal?
Do you not care if
Tenjin-ya loses Ginji?
If we lose Ginji?
Aoi.
Why abandon him?
Is it just because he used
to work for their inn?
That's a horrible reason.
I worked for Orio-ya,
which happens to be this inn's
main rival, remember?
Sometimes I worry
that the staff here
doesn't trust me
because of that.
This isn't right, at all!
[GINJI]
I'm sorry, Aoi.
[gasps]
Was it you, Ginji?
Were you the one?
No, Ginji, please wait!
[grunts] I still need to ask!
Was it you? I have to know.
All right, everyone's
accounted for.
Let's go back to Orio-ya.
Please, do something!
You have to make
him stay, Master!
It's his decision to make.
[gasps]
That being said,
I hope you haven't forgotten
our promise either, Ginji.
[gasps] Hold on a second!
What is it, you silly
little human girl?
We have no business with you!
Well I have business
with you, okay?
Do you happen to know
what this is?
Huh?
Nobunaga!
[barking]
[ORIOYA murmur]
[NOBU howls]
Want some okara cookies?
--[BYAKUYA] No, Aoi!
--[SASUKE] Mistress Aoi!
What are you doing?
Hey, what're you...?
Now, then.
You give Ginji back to us.
[MASTER]
Aoi!
[screams] Nobunaga!
You wench! How could you?
Taking our beloved mascot
hostage is a dirty move!
You've done it now!
[EMPLOYEE 14D] She's using
Nobunaga as a shield!
[EMPLOYEE 14E]
How despicable!
[EMPLOYEE 14F]
She's just like her grandfather!
[EMPLOYEE 14G]
Ogre bride's a fitting name!
Come on!
This is way too reckless!
What can we do?
You heard me, give Ginji
back to us right now.
If not, I'm going to blow
you and your ship away.
[GINJI]
Aoi don't, stop!
[AOI gasps]
[AOI]
Huh?!
Aoi!
[AOI gasping]
[AOI]
Hm?
♪ Kagome, Kagome ♪
♪ When will the bird break
through the cage? ♪
♪ When will it be free? ♪
[AOI] I didn't come to the
hidden realm of my own will.
[MASTER sighs]
I'm really quite hungry.
I said that I'm hungry.
[AOI]
What? A reward?
How considerate!
[AOI laughs]
So pretty!
U-Uh!
[AOI gasping]
[SHIRO] Those who can see them
are more vulnerable to attack.
So, be careful, Aoi.
[MASTER] Welcome to the
hidden realm, my lovely.
You are now my bride.
[AOI]
Ever since I was a child,
I've been able to see ayakashi.
But despite seeing them for
practically my entire life,
I never dreamed that one day
I'd go to the hidden realm.
[MASTER]
Aoi.
[gasping]
Ayakashi.
My lovely bride?
Huh?! Wha--? Huh?
[MASTER] One day, he went on
an extravagant spree here
at Tenjin-ya, which sent
him deep into debt.
Thus, to put it indelicately,
you are his collateral.
I'm what? How could he?
[AOI] The idea of becoming the
bride of an ogre was absurd.
So I told him I'd
work off the debt.
[AOI]
I found myself at Tenjin-ya.
An inn in the hidden realm.
[GINJI grunts]
I thought you might
be feeling hungry,
so I brought you a little snack.
The master doesn't know
about this, though.
Oh! And I didn't poison
them or anything like that.
[AOI] At first, it felt like
I was surrounded by enemies.
But Ginji never
treated me that way.
He was always kind.
[AOI] Haven't you worked
up an appetite?
Thanks!
[AOI]
Done! Here it is!
I used soy sauce with
Japanese toppings.
Delicious!
I've got it!
Chef Aoi,
how would you like to open up
your own restaurant out here?
[AOI]
At Ginji's suggestion,
I decided to open
up a restaurant,
and named it Moonflower.
[MATSUBA]
Anything else on the menu?
Great. Bring both.
For that, I became
quite fond of you.
This is the tengu's
honored treasure.
By rights, it belonged to Shiro.
You inherited that
promise when he passed.
Well, it means you're
truly Shiro's granddaughter.
No doubt about that.
Well, now it's time for
me to go back to bed.
Huh? Miss O-ryo,
succumbing to her despair?
[O-RYO] I'm not the young
hostess anymore, so, yes.
I'm just a snow woman who's
confined to her quarters.
Which means, heh, I can
do whatever I want today,
as long as I stay in my room!
[AOI]
I learned practically everything
I know about cooking
from my grandpa.
He may have been a man who'd
set his own granddaughter up
as collateral for his loan,
but there's no denying
that him teaching me how to
cook has been instrumental
in me making a life
for myself at Tenjin-ya.
[SHIRO]
Listen, Aoi.
You'll need to learn to cook.
I'll teach you.
If he has a grave somewhere,
then that is the place I belong.
I want to spend the rest
of my days near him,
in the realm where
we lived together.
[AOI]
What about Akatsuki?
Shouldn't you at least try
to make up before you go?
That would be quite futile.
My brother and I are
both very stubborn.
I hope that he can get over it.
When my grandpa died,
it was so sudden.
I didn't get closure.
He was here one day,
then he was dead.
But you have that
chance with Suzuran!
[growling] Why does he still
have so much power over her?
He abandoned both of us!
So you'd abandon her, too?
It's not gonna be an
easy journey for her,
and her brother
should see her off!
You would regret
not supporting her!
[inaudible]
I understand how strongly
my brother feels
about me going to
the apparent realm.
The fact that he helped
make this dish
so I could remember
Shiro's cooking...
It reminds me how
much he loves me.
That's the only goodbye I need.
You know.
It just occurred to me.
You're a bit like a younger
sister to Akatsuki and myself,
in a way. Because
all three of us
were raised by the same
person, weren't we?
That makes us sort
of like a family.
It's been a long time.
I've missed you.
[AOI] Oh, Grandpa.
I hope you're somewhere nearby.
[SUZURAN]
What do you plan to do?
Are you going back now?
Actually, I can't
return on my own.
Someone from the hidden
realm has to bring me.
I hope you're hungry
for curry, Master.
I can make it as spicy or
as sweet as you want it.
I do like the curry from
the apparent realm,
mainly because it's what you
humans call "comfort food."
Thank you.
I'm glad you feel that way.
I would miss you.
This particular Ogre
Gate Iwato Shrine
brings divine favor
for matchmaking.
So now is the perfect time
for you to visit it.
[GINJI] This shrine's
matchmaking benefits businesses.
It shines good fortune
on professional networks
and associations.
That makes sense.
[MASTER] Aoi, good business
is about much more than
simply turning a profit.
That's only one small part.
You must make yourself
indispensable to clients.
Create deep relationships and
bring value to every encounter.
That's important.
Interesting.
I like that.
I hope Moonflower
brings great joy
to everyone who
comes to eat there.
[GROUP]
Cheers!
[ALL laughing, chattering]
[AOI]
Somewhere along the way,
Tenjin-ya became an
important place to me.
It's where my friends are,
and where I belong.
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
Does it taste good?
Yeah. It's so yummy.
[AOI] When I was a child,
an ayakashi saved my life.
I've always wanted to see that
ayakashi again someday, but...
[AOI]
Ginji.
Was it you who saved
me back then?
Please, tell me.
I have to ask him.
I have to find out.
[grunting]
Uh!
[gasps]
Come here, Nobunaga.
You're with us now, you're safe.
That savage woman
can't take you again.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
[RANMARU]
Well, well.
It seems a pathetic human
girl has boarded our ship
without permission.
What will we do?
Is the lowly thing
scared of me? [laughs]
I guess it's not surprising.
Mistress Ougon-Douji's spiriting
away technique is so refined
that even Tenjin-ya's
master couldn't stop it!
[gasps]
I'm talking to you, woman.
If we are to take you back
to Orio-ya with us,
we'll be hard pressed
to find a use for you.
But since you're Shiro
Tsubaki's granddaughter
and the ogre god's bride,
we may be able to hang you
up as a display piece.
[RANMARU laughs]
[GINJI]
Ranmaru.
Take your damn hands off her.
Ginji, what are you--
[RANMARU]
Ginji. Heh.
Still playing the part
of a gentleman?
[GINJI]
Aoi is the master's fiancée.
I will not allow you to treat
her with such disrespect.
[gasps]
[RANMARU]
You "won't allow" me?
Just who exactly do you
think you're talking to?
Your old master
no longer matters.
You aren't working for Tenjin-ya
anymore, so get it together.
[gasps]
[RANMARU]
Come.
Let's return to our inn.
To Orio-ya.
So that's... Orio-ya.
Oh, no!
Aoi's been abducted!
Why does this keep happening?
Who's gonna feed me now?
And what's gonna happen to
Moonflower and Tenjin-ya?