[AOI]
Are you gonna eat me?
[AOI] If that's what
you came here to do,
then do it, if you want.
I'll be dead soon, anyway.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI]
I'm confused.
Are you saying you don't want
to get out of this place?
[AOI]
No, but I can't leave,
because I'm scared of
thunder and lightning.
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] I see,
but if you remain in this world,
you will die. You'll
suffer starvation.
There is another realm where
you'll have to go, eventually.
That realm needs you, but you
are not quite ready yet.
[gasps]
[MYSTERIOUS AYAKASHI] You must
promise me one thing.
Many years from now, when
you've grown into an adult,
I'll come back for you.
When I do, I will
make you my bride,
and when that happens, promise
that you'll try to love me.
[AOI] Hold on, tell me
who you are, at least!
[GINJI]
Aoi.
Can you hear me?
You're awake!
[sighs]
Thank goodness, I hope
you're feeling better.
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault for letting you
drink a strong, natural liquor
from the hidden realm.
You're not even used
to drinking regular alcohol
from the apparent realm.
I imagine that your
throat really hurts.
Your body had to process a
substance with a great deal
of spiritual power.
It's only natural to faint.
[AOI] Wow, this is what
a hangover feels like?
[GINJI]
We brought you to the infirmary.
Tokihiko acts as both
the bath caretaker
and the doctor in
residence here.
You're still running a fever.
And it's gotten quite late.
You should stay
and get some rest.
[BOTH]
We're so glad you're awake.
We were scared!
[MEI] Tokihiko said to
give you this miso soup
made with freshwater clams.
He tells us it's a good cure
for hangovers. Want some?
[AOI] Yum, miso soup.
It smells so good.
[gasps]
[KAI]
Well? Do you like it?
Do you think it might work?
Be careful. Try not to
eat it so fast! Please!
[GINJI]
Mm? What's going on?
Did you lose your voice?
Can she write? Hold on.
[KAI, MEI]
Mm?
[gasps]
[BOTH]
You can't taste anything at all?
Really? That's odd. It's common
for humans to get sick
from drinking liquor with high
levels of spiritual power,
but it shouldn't cause you
to lose any of your senses.
You must have fallen victim
to some kind of curse.
From whom?
In the hours before
having the liquor,
did you eat or drink
anything strange?
Or touch something odd?
[gasps]
[AOI] Of course! The Matcha
Drop Raiju gave to me!
He is an ancient ayakashi,
and the worst kind, too.
He would know of many spells,
some created specifically
to do harm.
How dare he mess with Aoi?
It must have been a cursed seed.
Those react with the spiritual
power of the secret liquor
and can block one's
ability to taste.
[AOI]
Oh, no!
Unforgivable!
I don't care if he's here
to observe the ceremony,
I'm going to kick him
out of this inn
before he can hurt anybody else!
No, calm down!
Lashing out will only
make the situation worse.
All we can do is
plan our next move
as quickly and
quietly as possible.
[gasps]
What a mess this has
turned out to be.
Ranmaru!
[RANMARU] That settles it, then.
I've made up my mind.
You'll no longer cook
for the umi-bouzu.
I can't trust you with that.
Don't do this.
It may be temporary,
so her sense of taste could
come back at any moment!
Have you forgotten how few days
are left before the ceremony?
We don't have the luxury of
waiting for her to recover.
That's absurd!
[AOI]
No, it isn't.
This ceremony will
determine the fate
of all the ayakashi
in this land.
I can't taste anything right
now. How could I expect him
to let me cook the dishes
of ocean treasure?
I wouldn't.
It is unfortunate that
we won't have your skill.
But luckily, the twins have
been working alongside you,
watching your technique.
[RANMARU]
Do you know what this means?
Under the circumstances.
We don't have a choice.
[GINJI grunts]
Thank you, but there's no reason
for you to apologize now.
It's plain to see Raiju
is the perpetrator here.
[BOTH growl]
[RANMARU] It's also clear we
weren't nearly vigilant enough,
and because of our slip,
I simply can't allow you
to cook for the ceremony.
Try not to let
this get you down.
You're an incredibly
strong person.
One who always manages to rise
to the occasion, no matter what.
So, we forced our
expectations on you.
We forgot that you're human.
And, that does carry
a certain frailty.
You're much more vulnerable
to attack than ayakashi are.
I can't help but place
all the blame on myself.
I feel I broke my promise to
support and watch over you.
[AOI]
He's wrong. This is my fault.
I ignored every warning.
[AOI]
I was still taken in by Raiju,
and I ended up getting hurt.
[ATTENDANT 23A]
Excuse me, Ginji?
Master Ranmaru is
asking to see you.
[GINJI] What you need
most right now is to rest.
So try not to worry.
We'll make sure everything's
taken care of.
[AOI]
I should have known better.
Grandpa warned me about this
stuff from the very beginning.
[AOI] It's almost like
everything was going too well
to be true, but I see now.
There are some ayakashi who
have ill will for no reason,
but for the sake
of causing harm.
[BOTH]
Don't worry.
We'll do our best...
...with the dishes
of ocean treasure.
[RANMARU]
Hm.
It's unfortunate that we
can't serve Aoi's cooking
to the umi-bouzu, who would
benefit from the spiritual power
in her food, but we
don't have a choice.
Where is Raiju staying?
Still in the Tougenkyou room?
I will handle him, you stay
out of it. Understand?
[panting]
[AOI] Maybe I should try cooking
something, just to see.
[gasps]
[AOI] My taste could be
coming back. Who knows?
[AOI]
Still nothing.
What will I do if it
stays like this forever?
[SHIRO]
When you meet hungry ayakashi,
make sure you have delicious
food on hand to give them.
If you do that, then they won't
have any excuse to eat you!
[AOI]
I feel so useless.
Like I have no real
purpose in life.
[CHIBI]
Hi, Aoi!
[CHIBI] That looks so tasty!
Can I have some of it?
I'm happy to be your follower,
Aoi, because it means
I get to eat your delicious
cooking every day!
[AOI]
That's sweet.
Everything's gonna be all
right. So don't be sad.
No, Ginji, wait!
I'm just going to ask
him about an antidote
for the spell he put on Aoi!
[door slides]
[AOI]
I wonder if this is any good.
[door slides]
[RAIJU]
It must be hard for you,
knowing you're nothing more
than a meal for ayakashi.
[AOI]
Raiju!
Were you sad to find your sense
of taste had been sealed off?
[AOI]
Give it back! My voice, too!
You'll pay for this!
Sorry, I can't hear you!
Now, you finally understand.
Ayakashi in this world
aren't always as kind as
you've known them to be.
Don't listen to him!
[AOI]
But many of them are kind.
Like Chibi. He trusts
and loves me.
And there's the ayakashi
from my childhood, too.
It's the same with humans--
some are good, and some
are awful, like you!
[RAIJU]
Oh?
I see you've cooked, dear,
even after what happened.
Well, since I'm already here,
I should try the food everyone
seems to be raving about.
[gasps]
This is awful.
The worst meal ever, if
you ask me! Ugh. So nasty.
Disgusting. Truly. Sick.
[gasps]
Not only have you lost the
opportunity to cook the dishes
made of ocean treasure,
but with food this bad,
you'll never run
Moonflower again, either.
Good luck with that debt.
[laughs]
[CHIBI grunting] You better stop
being mean and lying to Aoi!
I tasted that omelet she made,
and it was delicious!
What's this? Get away from
me, you little nuisance.
[CHIBI whimpers]
[CHIBI screams]
[AOI]
Chibi!
Now, my lovely.
Why don't I eat you
here, in secret.
It's how I most enjoy
deviance, after all.
I do feel kind of bad
for the ogre-god,
but it's so much fun getting
a rise out of someone
who's so aloof and untouchable.
[AOI gasps]
[GINJI] You get your filthy
hands off her!
Let go of Aoi and back
away from her, now.
[gasps]
Ah, Ginji, what a
pleasant surprise.
Aoi is the master of
Tenjin-ya's beloved fiancée.
So unless you want
some real trouble,
I suggest you let
her go and leave.
Oh? Real trouble?
From whom? You gave me
that insolent attitude
300 years ago. That's why your
precious Princess Iso died.
[gasps]
Don't ever forget that I could
easily sabotage your
little ceremony
according to my whims.
[GINJI grunts]
[RAIJU] Surely, you've thought
about eating this tasty
morsel before? Miss Tsubaki
looks delicious, does she not?
[AOI whimpers]
I refuse to play your
sick little games.
How could I imagine eating
someone like Aoi?
I've never thought that!
Not even once, because I'm
not despicable, like you!
Huh?
To me, Aoi represents hope,
like no one I've ever known.
When I look in her eyes, I
see an innocence she's had
since she was small.
[gasps]
And then, when she cooks,
she makes food with the
power to warm any heart.
Just because she loves to do it!
That alone is enough
to restore my hope!
[AOI]
I was right.
Ginji was the ayakashi
who saved me!
I am so utterly disappointed.
Modern ayakashi have become
so annoyingly soft.
In the olden times, we
ate humans without mercy.
And we lived and thrived
under the veil of darkness,
where fear and power
control everything!
[GINJI grunts]
[BYAKUYA] You're as crooked and
melodramatic as ever, Raiju.
[BYAKUYA] Only a fool refuses to
adapt to the changing times.
[RAIJU gasping]
I see you still haven't
forgotten my pretty face.
You old rake.
But, Byakuya! How?
Why are you here?!
[GINJI]
Uh!
[BYAKUYA] Our investigation
revealed the truth.
You were behind the assassin
who infiltrated Tenjin-ya
and made an attempt
on Aoi's life.
You're an unemployed reprobate,
rotten to your stinking core!
Amorality aside, per the
terms of Shiro's contract,
Aoi belongs with our master.
You'll be punished for
violating said terms.
I will not!
[GINJI]
Ah! It's okay!
Oh, but must I insist.
You must learn your lesson,
and I am happy to teach you!
[RAIJU screams]
No need to be afraid
now, he's gone.
I guess he ran away,
the coward.
Well, I'll beat him to a pulp
the next time I see him.
Already did, but you used
your words as weapons. Heh.
It's funny. Raiju
acts big and bad
until you show up, and then
he seems like a child.
He's a living fossil who's
wasted his life on trifles.
If he had only devoted his life
to diligent work, like me,
he would be fine.
More importantly...
...I've brought some
guests with me today.
[gasps]
It's been too long
since we last met.
How have you been?
[BOTH gasp]
So, it's true. You lost
your voice, then?
You poor darling.
Once again, thank you
so much for coming today,
Master Nuinoin and
Mistress Ritsuko.
I'm sure you're
probably wondering
what's going on here, Aoi.
It's quite a lucky development.
The Royal Couple's
here to help us.
They own one of Hourai's
gem branches, actually.
[gasps]
[GINJI]
As a matter of fact,
the Master is who
initially discovered
they were in possession
of the branch.
He sent O-Ryo here
to alert Ranmaru.
That's when Ranmaru went
to Youto to look into it.
Byakuya used to be an officer of
the Imperial Court, remember?
Through him, we invited
the Royal Couple to join us.
[gasps]
[GINJI]
We had to do it that way.
If Orio-ya had
asked them directly,
Raiju would have interfered.
The Master negotiated with
Orio-ya in return for his help
and asked that you and I
be released to go back
to Tenjin-ya, when all
is said and done here.
[RANMARU]
Mm.
[AOI]
Wow. I had no idea.
In addition, since the two
of you have been gone,
Tenjin-ya has been mired
in chaos and confusion,
and Moonflower sustained
a substantial profit loss.
When the ceremony is over,
we will compensate for that
damage, with interest.
[RITSUKO]
It's a well-known fact, Aoi,
but I wonder if you've heard it.
That all ayakashi have a strong
affinity for dramatic narrative.
[AOI]
So, they like a good story?
The great yokai in Youto
are especially fond of this.
And Raiju is the
worst of them all.
Out of boredom, yokai like him
control ayakashi for
their own amusement.
As a result, some fall
victim to these whims
and meet tragic ends.
It's a horrid,
despicable pastime,
and it's only practiced by the
coldest, most jaded of them all.
[BYAKUYA] Ougon-douji
and the Master played
their parts expertly, that's
why the plan succeeded.
So, arrangements for the
ceremony are nearly complete.
I wish you success
with everything,
and I hope you serve Raiju
appropriate justice.
It's a shame that the
gem branch we purchased
from the oogama was
really a counterfeit.
If I may, what is
the real branch like?
Well, one thing's for sure,
it's far less ornamental.
That's a lovely hanging
scroll, what's it for?
[BYAKUYA] Nuinoin purchased
it in the apparent realm,
but there's something
special about it.
The ink brush painting is a
bewitched contained space.
Commonly called a "threshold."
[RANMARU]
Fascinating.
Ritsuko and I have always
stored our family heirlooms
inside this painting.
To keep them safe.
Yes. This idiot took a
sacred contained space
and relegated it to little
more than a broom closet.
[AOI] He just called the ruler
of this world an idiot!
I'm not the brightest
in the realm.
I'm confused, are you saying
their Hourai's gem branch
is stored somewhere
in this painting?
[BYAKUYA]
Yes, exactly.
As I recall, it settled and took
root somewhere near the summit.
I'm sure it's grown into
a glorious tree by now.
They're happy to lend their
Hourai's gem branch to you all.
They deem Orio-ya's protection
of this land a noble cause.
But, it's up to you to go into
the painting and find the tree.
I'll take on that task myself.
I'll climb mountains,
or even go through them.
Whatever it takes, I'll do it.
You don't have the time.
You have to stay and oversee
preparations for the ceremony.
[RANMARU] Hideyoshi can do that
in my stead, with Nene's help.
Tokihiko and Hatori
can assist as well.
My executive staff
is more than capable.
You must take care
while in the space.
Its magic will consume a great
deal of your spiritual power.
Interesting. So, it's
like a survival game.
We should find a way to
replenish within the space.
Why not bring Aoi?
She could cook for you
and restore your power
with her food.
[gasps]
We could, but she's
not healed yet.
We should ask what she thinks.
You're not one to
back down from a fight.
Don't you want to thwart
Raiju's sabotage attempt?
[AOI] If I go, I might end
up just being a burden.
But, still...
Right. I want you to take
this special tincture.
[AOI]
What's that?
[BYAKUYA] This is the
Tenjin Hyper Infusion.
It's a highly effective
medication developed
in our basement
lab at Tenjin-ya.
That's great! They finished it!
[BYAKUYA]
Shizuna entrusted it to me.
She wanted to
make sure you had it
in case something
happened to you.
[AOI] Thanks, Shizuna.
That means the world to me.
Even though Aoi's
sense of taste
has been sealed off by
some powerful magic,
this medicine should
bring her some relief.
It's incredibly bitter,
but right now, that
won't be an issue.
That's somewhat lucky.
I wouldn't want to taste it.
[cork pops]
[AOI]
I can't breathe!
[RANMARU] Are you able to
give us further details about
the painting? We'd appreciate
anything you can share.
[gasps]
[GINJI]
Hello! I'm glad you're awake!
Good news, your
fever came down.
Hopefully you're starting
to feel better.
[stomach grumbles]
[GINJI] Don't worry,
I made you breakfast.
Food is a huge part of your life
and you should
be able to enjoy it.
You can't taste right now,
so I focused on texture
and appearance.
And I put my heart
into it, I guess.
[AOI]
I still can't taste anything.
But I can tell by the popping
that there's ikura ,
and the crispy ones
are lotus root.
Also, I can smell the aroma
of the stock in the soup.
So, what do you think of it?
[GINJI]
I'm so glad.
[AOI]
Oh, Ginji.
He's only ever been kind
to me. It's so sweet.
He said he put his heart into
making my breakfast today.
Okay!
Hey, you just spoke! I heard it!
[AOI]
Did my voice come back?
I'm better!
Your voice is, at least!
I'm so happy to be able
to hear you again!
[AOI laughs]
We should take the leftover
roast beef from
the tasting session. Even
if it doesn't taste good,
I'll make sure you
eat it, anyway!
[CHIBI grunting]
You know, I think the medicine's
working too well.
It's my breakfast. 'Cause
Ginji put his heart into it.
Hey! Don't tell him that!
[RANMARU]
Hm...
[AOI] How are we supposed
to get inside?
There's a special key. Until
you return, I'll have it
and the scroll on my person,
to keep you as safe as possible.
And when you're ready
to come out
just throw this communication
ticket in to the air.
'Kay...
[BYAKUYA] This is an enchanted
space, where the Hourai's
gem branch has spread its
roots and become a tree,
overflowing with
spiritual power.
Be wary when there's a thick
fog. Supposedly, it can make
inner desires manifest in
the form of illusions.
Illusions?
[BYAKUYA]
Unlock,
ink brush painting of
illusory hills and water!
[CHIBI] I'm so glad Aoi
got her voice back!
But a devoted follower's
work is never done!
That mysterious space
inside the scroll...
I'm gonna go there to
protect her from harm!