[AOI] Hold on,
why'd you bring her here?
[KASUGA]
Her fever made her collapse.
And, to be perfectly frank,
everyone around here
pretty much hates O-Ryo,
so no one else
would look after her.
What about
all her hangers-on?
They just kissed up to her
'cause she's the young hostess,
but they don't really like her.
She's got more enemies
than friends.
That's terrible.
Makes me sad.
[KASUGA] Well, I thought you
might have time to nurse her.
[AOI]
She's burning up!
I think I remember
hearing from somebody
that Miss O-Ryo
gets sick easily.
Sorry, I should really
be getting back to work.
I'll leave the fever
reducer here, okay?
[door slides]
Huh?
Master...
I'm sorry, Master.
[AOI]
Hmm...
Ah, here it is. Eureka!
"High Fevers in Snow Women.
Snow Women can become feverish
if they're nearby fire
too long."
[AOI]
"To counteract this,
cool the patient down.
Avoid allowing the patient
to ingest anything warm.
Instead, administer
cold foods and water.
Icy treats can be a big help."
By, "icy treats,"
they must mean ice cream
and sorbet
and things like that, I guess.
But I don't have heavy cream,
so what now?
[AOI]
Tofu?
I swear I saw
a blender in here.
[gasps] There you are!
[AOI]
I made you some tofu ice cream.
You should eat a little,
then take your medicine.
[O-RYO]
Mm, I don't want it!
Leave me alone.
Save your charity
for someone who needs it.
If you've got the energy
to cop that attitude,
you're all right.
Exactly, I feel fine,
so I should get back to work.
What're you talking about?
You have a fever.
All you're gonna
do today is rest.
Don't tell me what to do!
My job as young hostess
is the only good thing I have!
[AOI] Well, then, you should
have thought about that
before you acted so recklessly
and made the master angry.
[O-RYO] None of this ever
would have happened
if you hadn't shown up
in the hidden realm.
Just eat something so you
can take your medicine, okay?
It's a fever reducer,
so it'll make you feel better.
Kasuga was nice enough
to bring it for you.
[door slides]
She had better at least
try to eat.
Uh?
[O-RYO grunting]
[AOI]
Hey.
I made a cherry-flavored
ice cream, too.
Want some?
I do.
So, you only recently became
the young hostess, right?
You've been talking
to Kasuga, huh?
I have, and I've been wondering.
Why's this job so great that
you'd make enemies to get it?
[O-RYO] I wanted the master
to notice me.
To think I'm special.
I needed him to be
proud of my success,
so he would see my value.
But do you really believe
the young hostess position
carries that much weight
with the master?
[O-RYO]
Not the position, per se.
He just hates anyone
with no ambition,
who doesn't want to grow.
He respects those
who are willing to work hard
to reach
their full potential.
Potential?
[O-RYO] At this inn,
employees can rise up
in the ranks with no limit,
if they're willing
to prove themselves.
[AOI] I did get permission
to open a restaurant here,
but whether he recognizes
my worth
or not still depends
on how hard I work at that.
Why would you even want
to take care of me like this?
I don't know.
I guess because
Kasuga asked me.
You are such an odd girl.
Normally, if someone you
hate is at a weak point,
you take advantage of it.
Hmph. That'd be too much work.
I don't have the energy.
But ayakashi are vengeful,
so I get why you'd say that.
[O-RYO scoffs]
Don't you dare judge me.
[AOI] Look, do you really
like the master that much?
To the point that you'd
kill me for him?
Huh? Of course I do.
If it weren't for the master,
I wouldn't be
the woman I am today.
[AOI]
Hm?
I was born
in the northern land,
which is just west
of the northeast land,
where we're sitting now.
When I was a child,
my family was poor,
so they sent me to a nearby town
to work as a live-in maid.
I was a lowly country girl
with no manners,
so the mistress spent
the majority of her time
punishing me.
Even so, that was better
than the hunger pangs
I lived with before.
So I considered myself lucky.
[O-RYO] I'd been working there
a few years when I accompanied
my mistress to Tenjin-ya
for the first time.
It was the most beautiful
place I'd ever seen.
[plate shatters]
[O-RYO]
As fate would have it,
I broke an expensive plate that
the mistress had brought back
from the apparent realm
to give the master as a gift.
[O-RYO]
When the mistress got angry
and began
to beat me mercilessly...
[O-RYO] ...the ogre-god master
stepped in to help me.
He treated my wounds,
and then he made
all the necessary arrangements
so I could leave
the mistress's charge
and come to work as a room
attendant here at Tenjin-ya.
[gasps]
Right.
So then the master
has a kind side
that he keeps a secret.
You probably don't know this,
but I'm not the only one here
that the master has saved.
The front desk manager,
for example.
And Suzuran, the geisha.
He rescued them as well.
They came from the apparent
realm, originally.
[O-RYO] I can't believe
I disappointed the master!
Did you really think
he wouldn't find out
you straight-up
ignored his orders?
[O-RYO]
I don't know.
[O-RYO] I worked so hard
to become independent.
Just to gain his recognition.
[O-RYO] But he stopped
paying attention to me.
And then you showed up,
and everything got worse.
I don't know why I'm
sharing all this with you
when I don't even like you!
I'm sure it's because
of the fever.
[O-RYO] Even so, that was
better than the hunger pangs
I lived with before.
[AOI'S MOTHER]
Aoi.
[AOI'S MOTHER] Don't go outside,
no matter what.
You got that?
Keep the door shut tight,
even if someone comes by.
[AOI]
Mm-hmm.
Come back, Mommy.
[thunder rumbles]
[AOI]
Mommy! Please come home soon!
[AOI cries]
[AOI]
I'm so hungry, Mommy. Please...
Where did you go?
[AOI]
All right, then.
[gasps]
[AOI]
What is this?
[gasps]
[AOI]
It's the bowl from Youto!
This pink bowl
strikes your fancy?
I'll buy it for you.
What? No, it's okay!
[AOI]
Is this from the master?
That reminds me.
I wonder how Suzuran is doing.
[footsteps]
[AOI sighing, panting]
[TAKE] Mistress Suzuran's room
is right this way.
[AKATSUKI]
Like hell you are!
[crowd chattering]
What is going on in there?
[AOI]
A giant spider fight?
[AKATSUKI]
Open your eyes, Suzuran!
[SUZURAN]
Leave me alone!
I can do as I please!
[AKATSUKI grunting]
You're being ridiculous!
[SUZURAN]
Shut up! You're ridiculous!
You're a fool, Brother!
Hold on, you mean
those spiders are--
[TAKE] Mistress Suzuran
and the manager
are having a siblings' brawl.
[screams]
[AKATSUKI]
Shiro is dead!
Why would you still want to go
to the Apparent Realm?
[SUZURAN]
Why wouldn't I?
I've been working hard for years
to save up enough money
to go back!
It's where all my best memories
of Shiro were made!
Suzuran wins this round.
[AKATSUKI screams]
[MASTER]
Uh?
Aoi, I'm glad you like the bowl,
but I don't think it makes
a very good helmet.
It had never occurred to me
to wear it as a helmet,
and yet, here we are.
[laughs]
[MASTER] You're an amusing
young lady, you know that?
Have you warmed up
enough yet, Aoi?
[AOI sighs]
Yes, thanks.
[MASTER]
I'll make us some tea,
but feel free to have some of
those daifuku while you wait.
I've been wondering
about Akatsuki and Suzuran.
What on earth made them get into
that knock-down-drag-out
fight today?
[MASTER] You're aware that
Akatsuki and Suzuran
are ayakashi from the
Apparent Realm, yes?
[AOI]
Mm-hmm.
[MASTER]
Well, you see,
about 40 years ago,
when Shiro was traveling
between the Apparent Realm
and the hidden one...
...there was a disturbance
involving a wandering
spider ayakashi
that was attacking humans.
It was trying to find shelter
in the apparent realm.
That spider ayakashi was
none other than Akatsuki.
[MASTER] Then, Shiro,
who was traveling aimlessly
between the two worlds,
suddenly appeared
before the spider,
who got more than
he bargained for.
[MASTER] After that, the story
is that Shiro took
in the siblings
and cared for them.
But that doesn't make sense.
Then why would Akatsuki
hate my grandpa?
[MASTER]
I'm not sure.
I can't speak for him.
But he says he never wants
to serve a guy
like that ever again.
Well, I can't say
that surprises me.
Even now, Suzuran feels
an intense loyalty to Shiro
and claims to be forever
in his debt.
[AOI]
I can see that.
[MASTER] I took the two of them
back to the hidden realm with me
at your grandfather's request.
[MASTER] That's when Akatsuki
started working at Tenjin-ya,
and Suzuran began her training
in the capital
to become a geisha.
[MASTER]
Shiro often visited the capital,
where he could see Suzuran dance
and listen to her play
the shamisen.
But, according to Suzuran.
When Shiro passed, he hadn't
been to see her in ten years.
[AOI]
Ten years?
Do you think she's really going
back to the Apparent Realm?
It would appear that she's
determined to do as much.
But doesn't she care
that Akatsuki's so against it?
[MASTER]
Suzuran is no longer a child.
She's going there with money
that she earned on her own.
So how can he stop her?
You're right, he might not
be able to stop her.
[AOI] But the Apparent Realm
is rough for ayakashi.
The ones I see are always hungry
and never seem to be at peace,
so it makes sense
that he would be worried.
[MASTER]
By the way.
I heard you're taking care
of O-Ryo.
[AOI]
Yeah, she's got a little fever.
She took some medicine,
so she just needs to rest
another day or two.
Thank you for the tea.
Are you seriously planning
to take away O-Ryo's title?
And does that upset you?
You're like a father to her,
so she feels
a deep affection for you.
That's why she was
jealous of me.
She didn't know how to
handle it,
and because of that,
she made some mistakes.
[MASTER]
I am not O-Ryo's father.
She must decide whether
she wants to be
an independent young hostess
or someone who relies on me.
She cannot be both,
and she should know that.
Yeah, I understand.
To think that you're caring
for an ayakashi
who meant you harm.
Shiro was never one to do
what I expected him to, either.
Well, speaking of which,
you bought me
the cut glass bowl,
even though I specifically
asked you not to.
[MASTER]
What, you don't like it?
No, I didn't say that.
I knew it.
I love it, actually. [giggles]
I like when you smile.
[AOI]
Hey. What's your favorite food,
and no jokes
about human entrails!
What if that's
really my favorite?
I wanna make a "thank you"
dish, but I won't cook people!
I have a strict policy
of not revealing my favorite
food without just cause.
I wouldn't want anyone
to use it against me.
What? That's ridiculous!
[MASTER chuckling]
[MASTER] Well, you must be
getting tired now.
You should go back and get
some much-needed sleep.
O-Ryo is using my quarters
in the annex.
Is there somewhere else
I could stay?
[MASTER] Would you like
to sleep in my room?
I can have another pillow
brought in, my lovely bride.
Nope, I'll pass!
I'd rather camp out in an alley,
thank you, sir.
Yes, well,
your restaurant journey
starts tomorrow,
so work hard.
Or the alley, it is.
Hey, Master, I have a teensy
little favor to ask you.
A rare occurrence, what is it?
[AOI]
That matcha.
Do you think I could
have some of it?
I'd like to make a
matcha-flavored tofu ice cream.
[AOI]
All right!
This is awesome,
thank you so much Master!
[AOI giggling]
I never would have
guessed that,
of all the gifts I bestowed,
this would be her favorite.
[AOI giggling]
Uh...
Hey, what room is Suzuran
staying in right now?
She's in temporary quarters.
Repairs on the Large
Camellia Room
should be completed
by tomorrow.
I see.
Do you wish to go back
to the Apparent Realm?
Are you still attached to it,
like Suzuran?
I'm human.
So, yes, I am attached.
It's natural that I'd want
to go back someday.
But, why?
Well, why wouldn't I?
With Shiro dead and gone,
it isn't as though you have
family there any longer.
[scoffs] Sensitivity isn't
your strong suit.
I'm still a student, after all.
I want to go back
and finish school.
I just figured I should gauge
your feelings on the matter.
[scoffs]
[groans] I slept funny.
Oh, nice, her fever's broken!
[AOI yawning]
[gasps]
[AOI]
Oh my goodness!
Are you Akatsuki?
[AKATSUKI shudders]
Don't speak my name.
Don't even talk to me!
Have you been sitting out here
since yesterday?
[AKATSUKI] Back off!
Just leave me alone, will ya?
Hey!
The earth spider manager
isn't as tough
as I thought he would be.
I mean, his little sister
beat him up.
[AKATSUKI]
Stop! How dare you, human?
Let me go at once! I'll eat you!
[AOI]
Oh, calm down, or I'll eat you!
I'll cook with soy sauce
and sugar
and make a tasty tsukudani
with steamed rice!
Or how 'bout I just
deep fry you
and eat you legs first,
like a nice soft-shell crab?
[AKATSUKI gasps]
[AOI]
Okay, let's see.
"There are three main treatments
for injured earth spiders.
Treatment one, leave them
to heal on their own.
Treatment two,
administer spiritual power.
Treatment three, administer
foods with high concentrations
of spiritual power." All right.
Hey, earth spiders
just eat, like,
bugs and stuff, don't they?
[AKATSUKI]
Like hell we eat bugs!
I'm starving here!
Aoi, make me something
to eat, would ya?
[AOI]
Whoa, why are you acting like
we're friends all the sudden?
What do you want?
Something cold, like your soul?
Don't be rude.
I'm not sick anymore, so I don't
have to stick to ice cream.
What I'm craving is
a bowl of oyakodon.
And I mean a giant bowl!
Okay, but don't blame me
if you gain weight.
[O-RYO] I don't even care
anymore, just give me food!
And, not just any food,
I want oyakodon , in case you
didn't hear me the first time!
Oh, yeah.
Do you want some, too,
earth spider?
[AKATSUKI]
Who'd eat a meal made
by Shiro Tsubaki's
granddaughter?
Huh? Wait.
Akatsuki, that's you?
[O-RYO]
Look, don't be daft.
Aoi's cooking has
a special component
that can restore
spiritual power.
You should just eat it,
or you might not get
your full strength back.
[AKATSUKI]
Shut up, snow woman.
You got demoted
for being "daft,"
so don't talk to me like
you're still the young hostess.
Wow, so sorry to care about your
healing, Attitude-tsuki.
[mixing]
I can't believe my cooking
really has that kind of power.
Well, it means you're truly
Shiro's granddaughter.
No doubt about that.
[AKATSUKI scoffs]
I still don't understand
what you mean.
How does my cooking
have spiritual power?
Is it the same way food
restores stamina in humans?
Oh, but more importantly,
how does it taste?
Well, to be honest with you,
I would say this dish
isn't half bad.
Thank you for the food.
Well, now it's time for me
to go back to bed.
Huh? Miss O-Ryo, succumbing
to her despair?
[O-RYO] I'm not the young
hostess anymore, so, yes.
I'm just a snow woman
who's confined to her quarters.
Which means, heh, I can to do
whatever I want today,
as long as I stay in my room!
[chuckles]
[CHIBI sighing] That ice cream
sure looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
Can I have some, too?
And when do I get to see
my sweet Miss Aoi?