[AOI]
Eat me if you want to.
[AOI] If that's what
you're going to do,
then get it over with.
[AOI cries]
[AOI]
I'm gonna be dead soon, anyway,
so it doesn't even matter.
But, if you don't eat me,
just stay with me, please.
Don't leave me alone.
Promise me!
[AOI]
When I was a very young girl,
an ayakashi saved my life.
[AOI]
I'll never forget that.
I was shocked by its kindness,
so the memory keeps
coming back to me.
[AOI panting]
[AOI]
Ever since I can remember,
I've been able to see
supernatural monsters
that are called, " ayakashi. "
[AOI]
Some of these are dangerous
if you make eye contact
with them.
[AOI]
But, some of them?
They're harmless,
and I'd even deign
to call some cute.
[AYAKASHI cheer]
[AYAKASHI chewing]
[whimpers]
[AOI]
You sly little thing!
[CHIBI] Oh, Aoi! Thank you
for the yummy food!
[AOI]
He really is clever.
[chuckles]
[footsteps]
[AOI grunts]
Uh...
[AOI gasps]
[MALE AYAKASHI sighs]
[MALE AYAKASHI]
I'm really quite hungry.
I said that I'm hungry.
[sighs]
How 'bout this?
You said you're hungry, right?
I wouldn't want you to attack
humans because you're starving.
[whimpers]
[AOI]
'Kay, bye.
[MALE AYAKASHI]
This is delicious, Aoi.
How does he know my name?
Uh...
[AOI] Because I've always
been able to see them,
even when I was tiny,
my mother couldn't love me.
[AOI]
And she abandoned me.
But, somebody else
came to the orphanage
to save me
from that terrible life.
My grandfather.
[GRANDPA]
Listen, Aoi.
You'll need to learn to cook.
I'll teach you.
[AOI]
Nothing is permanent, though.
And a few days ago, he passed.
[AOI]
But, honestly,
I'm accustomed to being alone.
He left me enough money
to make sure
I could get by day-to-day,
at least.
I don't really need much.
As long as I don't go hungry,
I'm all right.
I'm satisfied.
[AOI]
What?
A reward? How considerate!
[AOI giggles]
So pretty!
Maybe he was a rare,
nice ayakashi,
and what's wrapped
in this cloth?
[AOI]
U-Uh...
[AOI gasps]
[GRANDPA]
Those who can see them
are more vulnerable to attack.
So, be careful, Aoi.
[AOI]
Grandpa. I'm sorry.
I let my guard down.
[MALE AYAKASHI]
Welcome to the hidden realm,
my lovely.
You are now my bride.
[AOI gasps]
[gasps]
--[MALE AYAKASHI] Aoi...
--[AOI gasps]
Ayakashi .
[AOI]
An ogre?
But, I feel like...
I've seen him before.
How are you feeling,
my lovely bride?
Huh, wha... Huh?
Yes, Aoi, I mean you.
You are going to be my wife.
Huh?
I'm gonna be what?
Huh?!
[MALE AYAKASHI]
Hmph.
Wait, hold on! I didn't--
[AYAKASHI 1]
Master, think this through!
With all due respect, maybe
she's not the right choice.
[AYAKASHI 2]
He's got a good point.
[AYAKASHI 3] A lowly human
girl like this one?
[AYAKASHI 4]
She's ugly, and far too skinny.
[AOI]
That's mean, I can hear you.
[AYAKASHI 1] She's nowhere
near suited to you, Master.
Huh?
[AOI gasps]
Where the heck am I?
What is this place?
[MASTER]
You're in the hidden realm.
I'm in the "hidden realm"?
[MASTER] Yes, indeed.
The hidden realm of ayakashi.
Our domain.
And this building
where you find yourself
is known as Tenjin-ya.
Tenjin-ya.
Uh! Tenjin-ya?
[AOI]
I've seen it before!
In a picture I found
in Grandpa's things!
But, who are you?
I'm the keeper of Tenjin-ya.
They call me, "Ogre-god,"
sometimes "Master Innkeeper."
[gasps] I saw you
in that picture.
So, did you know
my grandfather, then?
He could also see ayakashi.
Did he come here, too?
He did. I am a very old
friend of his, actually.
And so,
I am the ogre who will
become your husband.
[AOI]
That again?
Stop with that nonsense!
You're making all of this up,
and I'm not having any of it!
[AYAKASHI 1]
Hey! You will show him respect!
I'm not making it up.
Your grandfather,
or Shiro, as I called him,
promised you to me
a long time ago.
[AOI]
That's a lie.
He did whatever he wanted,
but there's no way.
He'd never have made
that promise without asking!
Shiro had a rare gift,
the ability to travel
between worlds.
The apparent realm,
where humans dwell,
and this, the hidden realm.
[MASTER] One day, he went
on an extravagant spree
here at Tenjin-ya,
which sent him deep into debt.
So, we struck a deal.
If he couldn't pay me back,
he'd give me his granddaughter
in marriage in place of payment.
Thus, to put it indelicately,
you are his collateral.
I'm what? How could he?
[AOI]
Grandpa...
So that means you are
required to marry me.
You have no choice.
No way!
[MASTER]
Uh.
You just kidnapped me--
how could I agree to this?
And besides, I do not want
to marry an ogre!
I refuse, that's final!
[MASTER]
You won't, no matter what, then?
I see.
I had better make sure
that my bride
knows her place around here.
Huh?
[MASTER] Give my bride
the "Torture in Hell" treatment.
Huh? "Torture in Hell"?
Uh, no thanks.
[ATTENDANT 1]
This is the hot water torture.
[AOI]
Huh?
[ATTENDANT 2]
This is the skinning torture.
[AOI]
What?
[ATTENDANT 3]
This is the binding torture.
[AOI]
Uh...
That's what they call torture?
Ayakashi are weird.
[MASTER] So, how are you
liking Tenjin-ya?
My, you look
breathtakingly beautiful
in our inn's signature yukata,
my lovely wife-to-be.
I'm not your wife-to-be.
So, you still refuse
to accept my proposal?
Ugh, my grandpa's gone now,
can't you just forgive the debt
and find someone else?
[gasps]
When we eat human girls
who possess strong
spiritual powers,
they taste
the most delicious. So...
Eat me?
You'd taste like a delicacy,
so you're special.
You're dear to me,
so I cannot eat you.
Thus, you're forbidden
and tempting,
which makes me want
to eat you even more.
But, I cannot do it.
It's said that this dilemma
can be the most exhilarating
pleasure of them all.
[AOI]
What are you talking about?
On top of all that,
you just happen to be
Shiro's granddaughter.
He's a very famous human
among the ayakashi, you know.
That fact alone
makes you valuable,
even without
your beauty and power.
Why is he famous?
You'll find out soon.
Now...
...why not give in
and agree to be my bride?
How much is it?
[MASTER]
Hmm?
The debt that Grandpa owed.
Well, let's see. All told,
it's about 1,000,000 yen.
Huh?
Let me pay it back.
I can just work it off.
[Master]
Hmm...
I'll stay and work
till it's paid.
That settles the debt,
but I won't have to marry you.
That's not even possible.
[AOI] You don't know that,
just let me try!
Plus, none of your employees
want you to marry me, either.
So, why don't we make
a compromise?
Or, at least, think it over.
Well, this is quite interesting.
A human, trying to
negotiate with me?
You arrogant brat.
[whimpers]
I'll permit you to attempt to
find a job here at Tenjin-ya.
But, if that's the case,
and you get hired,
then you'll be treated
as an employee,
not my bride-to-be.
So, you won't be allowed
to stay in a guest room,
or get the benefit
of my protection.
Furthermore, you'll lose
your right to complain.
Even if someone around
here devours you.
You're showing your
true colors now, Ogre!
[MASTER] Don't blame me
for the bargain you struck.
[AOI]
Why, Grandpa?
[SHIRO]
Eating is essential,
for both humans and ayakashi.
When ayakashi get too hungry,
sometimes it can lead them
to prey on people.
Someone like you,
who has strong spiritual power,
is more likely to be targeted.
If that happens,
try to appease them
by offering some food.
[AOI] Grandpa was irresponsible
in a lot of ways,
and yet, I loved him,
despite all that.
But, now this?
[MASTER] To put it indelicately,
you are his collateral.
[AOI]
Oh, Grandpa.
Did you ever actually
care about me at all?
If so, how could you?
[AOI]
Ugh, I'm so hungry.
--[door rattles]
--[gasps]
[footsteps]
--[AOI grunts]
--[BOY] Uh!
I thought you might
be feeling hungry,
so I brought you a little snack.
[AOI]
Inari sushi?!
[BOY] The master doesn't
know about this, though.
Oh! And I didn't poison them
or anything like that.
[AOI]
Uh...
Sorry, I guess I should
introduce myself.
I'm the nine-tailed fox, Ginji,
and I'm the young master
here at Tenjin-ya.
Hi, Ginji.
Wait, so if you're
the young master,
you're the other master's son?
Huh? No, that's not
how it works.
The master and I are
relatively close in age.
And I can take nine
different forms
by using my
shapeshifting technique.
Oh! You were in
the fox mask I saw earlier?
Yeah!
I thought I'd be
less likely to scare you
if I showed up
to introduce myself like this.
But, maybe you'd have
preferred my female form.
Whoa! Crazy!
[GINJI]
Or what about...
...my cute, little, fluffy form?
Aw! You're adorable!
[stomach growls]
Eh...
[AOI]
Thank you for this food.
It's delicious!
I'm glad to hear that!
I'm sure you have
a lot of concerns
about marrying
someone you don't know,
but the master really
is wonderful, for an ogre.
Huh?
He's stoic and ruthless,
but at the same time,
he's got an enormous
heart of gold.
Contradictory.
Not at all!
Everyone on staff adores
working for him.
And he also happens to be
one of the most powerful
and high-ranking ogre-gods
in the entire hidden realm!
I still have no intention
of marrying that guy.
Ogre, or whatever he is.
It doesn't matter.
I won't do it!
But, wait--
I'll work here,
for as long as it takes me
to repay my grandpa's debt.
Who knows if it's even possible.
But still. I won't ever know
unless I try, right?
Aoi, listen...
I can cook, so I know
I can work as a kitchen hand.
I guess that's what
I'll apply for.
Women aren't allowed
to work in the kitchen.
Huh? Hmm...
Well, all right, I guess
I'll find something else.
I'll brainstorm about
other jobs you could get.
I'd appreciate it.
[AOI]
That hit the spot.
Well, I'm really glad
you liked it.
Especially since that's
the only dish
I know how to cook.
Wait, you mean
you actually made those?
Yeah, I did.
Thanks, Ginji.
They were delicious,
awesome job.
[GINJI giggles]
[AOI]
That's twice now.
I ate food from this realm
once before.
Uh...
[AOI]
A long time ago,
when I was a little girl...
[AOI] ...a very kind ayakashi
shared its food with me.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
[AOI laughs]
[AOI] Right! Time to seize the
day, and find myself a job!
No way!
A human girl can't possibly
have what it takes
to be a room attendant
at Tenjin-ya.
Please, ma'am.
I'll work hard--
[HOSTESS]
The answer is no.
I'm honestly offended that
a skinny little brat like you
is even the master's
prospective bride,
much less an employee of mine.
I, young hostess O-Ryo,
reject your request
and that's final!
--[AOI] Uh...
--[O-RYO scoffs]
[AOI]
I'm begging you!
We have enough workers here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Welp, that's a no.
I'll just try the kitchen.
Get lost!
No women allowed! Go!
[AOI]
It's no use.
I guess finding a job
is hopeless.
No one here wants help
from the likes of me.
[sighs]
Is being an ogre's bride
my only option after all?
No! I will not do it!
Huh?
[AOI]
Uh...
What are these?
Is it safe to follow these guys?
Or is that asking for trouble?
[AOI grunts]
Huh?
Uh!
[AOI gasping]
[AOI]
Is anyone here?
Looks like a restaurant.
--[MAN] Hey, Aoi!
--[AOI gasps]
Uh, who's there?
Don't worry, it's me.
Ginji, that is.
Oh, hi. It is?
Oh, this is what
I usually look like.
[AOI gasps]
So, what brought you here?
This place is kind of
off the beaten path.
I stumbled upon it
in my futile job search.
I see.
This is some kind of
restaurant, isn't it?
Yeah, or it used to be.
It was a restaurant until about
two days ago, but it closed.
The building is going to be
torn down soon, sadly.
But, why did it close?
It seems like a nice place.
[sighs]
Yeah, you'd think that,
but it's had nothing
but lousy luck.
No matter what, nothing seems
to thrive in this location.
Teahouse.
A games arcade.
Souvenir shop.
The little restaurant.
It doesn't matter.
They've all failed miserably.
I believed it would be different
with the restaurant, honestly.
Since the guests always say
they get tired of the fancy,
rich food that the kitchen
in the main building prepares.
But, that didn't work, either.
Even though I tried
everything I could
to entice the guests
to come in.
Entice them? Uh...
[AOI] Maybe the arrows
were a bad choice.
So, that's why I'm here.
I'm clearing out the last of
the leftover ingredients
and equipment.
Leftover ingredients?
Yeah, I'm planning to offer
everything that's still usable
to the kitchen staff
over in the main building.
Before you do that,
would you mind
if I use some of it?
[GINJI]
Hmm?
Haven't you worked up
an appetite?
You did make inari sushi
for me last night, after all.
So, um, I thought
I would return the favor,
if you'd be interested.
[GINJI]
What? Are you sure?
Yeah, of course.
Matter of fact, it would
really mean a lot to me.
Cooking for people always
cheers me up when I'm down.
Deal!
Is there any particular food
that you've been craving
from the apparent realm?
Ah! There is!
I've been wanting something
called "rice omelette"!
A rice omelette?
I can't stop thinking about it!
"Rice Omelette."
A food from the apparent realm
that's similar to inari sushi.
Ah!
The wrapping on those
is comparable!
Great, you got it!
One rice omelette, comin' up!
Thanks!
[AOI]
Done! Here it is!
Since there was no ketchup,
I used soy sauce
with Japanese-style
toppings instead.
[GINJI]
Mmm...
It smells wonderful!
Enjoy!
[GINJI]
All right.
[AOI]
Mmm...
Delicious!
[AOI chuckles]
Seriously, this is so good!
[AOI giggles]
The flavors of this dish,
they delight
the ayakashi palate.
My grandpa took care to
teach me all his secrets.
I like to use sweet soy sauce,
like in cuisine from Kyushu.
The condiments
in the hidden realm
taste more like they do there.
Well, I'm impressed!
I've got it!
Chef Aoi, how would you
like to open up
your own restaurant out here?
Uh...
Huh?!
[AYAKASHI 5]
A human has come to marry
the master of Tenjin-ya?
[AYAKASHI 6]
The news arrived not long ago.
[AYAKASHI 5]
Well, isn't that interesting?
And so close to the day
of the ceremony, too.
Yeah.
How would that work?
Me? Open a restaurant here?
[CHIBI]
This is just awful!
Aoi's been abducted
to the hidden realm!
Who's going to feed me
now that she's gone?
Oh, Aoi! I hope you come back
to feed me soon!