Uh. My ankle hurts,
and I don't have
many supplies left.
What will I do about
Master Matsuba?
Not to mention
my dinner tonight...
If only I could go out
and do a little shopping,
but I don't have
the money for that!
Uh! This is terrible!
I have absolutely nothing
to work with here!
[crash]
Uh! What was that?
Are those...
...Mackerel?
What are they doing up here?
"I thought you might want
to make something with these
wing mackerel. I enjoy
them simmered in miso."
I know this handwriting.
Hello, Master, are you
still around here?!
Well, Master or no.
It's time to get to work.
Heh, heh! The miso is
smelling fantastic!
I guess things worked
out okay for tonight!
Taichi! You wanna
join me for dinner?!
Oh, he isn't out here.
Just when I wanted
to return the favor.
[CHIBI sighs]
Ah, Chibi.
You're just in time to eat.
No, I'm too exhausted,
even for dinner.
[sighs]
And I'm still full of delicious
southern land cucumbers.
Cucumbers? Where on earth
did you get those?
How rude.
What happened to his devotion?
I haven't had a meal
by myself in a while.
I wonder how all my
friends are doing.
[growls]
Hey Aoi! When did you get back?!
--[gasps]
--Ug! What's with this pot?
My arm's numb,
but it's still not clean!
What do you want?!
Just what do you two think
you're doing in here?
Uh. Nothing.
We're not trying to keep
the place clean and ready
for when Aoi gets back
or anything like that.
[AKATSUKI]
Huh?
[KASUGA laughs]
Nice try, Young Hostess.
I'm so restless.
I wonder what's
going on at Orio-ya.
I hope Aoi is all right.
[BYAKUYA gasps]
[DARUMA 1C] There! The stove
is so clean it sparkles!
Uh! Accounting Chief!
Good, the knives
are sharpened, too.
Oh, Master Byakuya!
Look at you lot.
The chief chef even.
What are you doing? How could
you just leave your posts?
Uh, we're very sorry.
We just felt like we
had to do something.
To get it ready
for Aoi's return.
I hate to be pessimistic, but we
can't guarantee she will return.
We do apologize, sir.
But I have no doubt that Aoi
will be here very soon!
Yes! I truly believe the master
will bring her home
to us without fail!
And if she can't cook
right away when he does,
it'll be a problem for business!
I'm surprised. It appears
that none of you understand.
[ALL sigh]
Since both the master
and young master
are absent right now,
you are all responsible for
keeping things running here.
Just think of it this way:
would it matter that you've kept
this place clean if
Tenjin-ya goes under?
Moonflower would go
down with the ship.
[ALL gasp]
I haven't given up on Aoi.
There is still hope.
But for her sake,
and not just ours,
we must keep up
business as usual.
I suppose you're right.
So, to your posts
at once, everyone!
Your thoughtfulness
will not be in vain.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
Byakuya, I leave Tenjin-ya
in your capable hands.
I'll do my best, Master.
Please don't worry about things
on this end, just be careful.
[HIDEYOSHI] Human girl.
What are you doing?
Uh? Come on.
[AOI]
Well, of course it's you.
Look, I couldn't find
anywhere better to sleep, so.
Are you serious?
The confinement room?
If I'm not being confined,
then it's just a room, isn't it?
You're a weirdo.
Hey, tell me something.
Where can I find Ranmaru.
Call him Master Ranmaru!
You little dimwit.
[AOI] Foul-mouthed,
shapeshifting monkey...
Okay, then, where
is "Master Ranmaru"?
I wanna talk to him in person
and make a formal request
for food supplies. Ingredients
for Master Matsuba's meals.
You'd better leave those
requests to Ginji.
You have no right to bother the
master with your silly demands.
I'd prefer to do that, honestly,
but I don't know where Ginji is.
Do you know?
Who gives a damn?
I hope he drowned!
He is so edgy.
I bet he just needs to eat.
[groans] I guess I'll head
to the old building and
get some work done.
Uh?
[inhales, exhales]
[AOI screams]
[AOI] This is clearly
targeted harassment.
I never had it this
bad at Tenjin-ya.
[sighs]
[AOI]
Huh...?
[scraping]
[AOI]
Who's there?
[MAN]
Oh, Aoi.
What happened to you out there?
Don't tell me you're getting
bullied by the staff.
What?
[MAN] Your hair and
clothes are soaking wet.
Come on. I'll dry them for you.
[AOI]
Mm... Mm... I know that voice.
Could it be...?
Master, is that you?
Guilty as charged.
Wait, one second.
What's the matter?
Does the towel smell like fish?
I can get another one
if you'd prefer.
No, it isn't that at all.
How do I know it's really you?
[gasps] What would make
you think otherwise?
[AOI]
Well, nothing, really.
Except that you look
like a college kid,
and your horns are gone.
You know there's no way
I could come to Orio-ya
looking like my usual form.
I disguise myself in
the apparent realm, too.
I've gotten quite good at it.
[MASTER chuckles]
[MASTER laughs]
I can imagine.
Well, now that you're
convinced it's really me,
please stay still.
[gasps]
[AOI]
Oh...
Ranmaru confiscated
the hair ornament.
But don't worry,
I'm gonna get it back.
Just knowing you're okay
is enough for me.
No way! I like it.
I want him to return it!
[MASTER gasps]
Do you really?
[AOI]
Uh... It's not fair.
Is it just my imagination,
or is the master closer
to me than usual?
Anyway. I brought a spare
change of clothes for you,
in addition to the ingredients,
if you'd like to change.
I can't believe you
thought of that.
Why would that be
a surprise to you?
I want you to be comfortable.
[AOI]
Thanks.
I will wear them, since you were
kind enough to bring them.
I'm glad.
So, this is when you leave.
What? You won't let me stay?
Truly an ogre bride.
Well, you're a fish
peddler, so there!
But that's beside the point.
I have to change-- get out!
But what happens if I run
into any Orio-ya employees?
I'm not sure that my
disguise would work
on the executive staff.
[AOI] Oh, fine, then turn
around and stay that way.
Or I could help you.
[AOI] How's everyone
doing at Tenjin-ya?
Are they okay?
[MASTER] A few of them were
upset that Orio-ya deceived us,
but other than that,
there've been no problems.
We had a staff meeting,
and it was decided that I
should be the one to come
to the southern land.
[AOI]
Because, out of everyone,
you had the most
free time, am I right?
You are, though I'm not worried,
with Tenjin-ya in
Byakuya's care.
[AOI]
Mm. I see.
Okay, done.
[MASTER] Oh. That kimono
suits you very well.
You look like a
blushing newlywed.
I'm starting to get
a crystal-clear picture
of what your tastes are.
[MASTER chuckles]
I had better get going now.
I have to make deliveries
to both the kitchen
and dining hall.
Okay.
I guess I can
walk you out, then.
[gasps]
Is something the matter?
Your ankle's swollen.
It's not bad.
I'm sure it'll be better soon.
[MASTER] You shouldn't be
putting weight on it, Aoi.
[AOI]
Thanks, Master.
Aoi. You only have
to say the word
and I'll help you escape
from this place.
I refuse to leave here
without taking Ginji with me.
It's all or nothing.
I'm worried.
I haven't seen him
since yesterday.
I hope he's getting enough to
eat, and able to sleep at night.
But, most of all, I hope
that the employees here
aren't bullying him and
calling him a traitor.
Who knew Ginji warranted
so much attention.
[AOI]
That's rude.
Ginji is an Orio-ya
employee now.
[AOI] You're even colder
than I thought.
I was under the impression that
you two were close friends.
Or is there something else?
Some hidden reason you can't
bring him back with
us to Tenjin-ya?
[MASTER]
It's... complex.
Also, what's the big deal
with this fireworks event?
It's all anyone talks about, and
it feels so unsettling somehow.
Ginji's stuck here
for the time being.
He agreed to do
something at Orio-ya,
and he must go through with it.
It's related to
the fireworks event
that the hotel is
preparing to host.
But the mood is too intense
for such a common thing.
It isn't common.
It holds special significance
in the southern land.
Once every century,
during the fireworks,
Orio-ya carries out a
ritualistic ceremony.
Ceremony?
[AOI] All of this is starting
to make more sense.
Ensure that you carry out
the ceremony without fail.
No matter the cost, they must
complete the full observance,
because the southern land
bears an ancient curse.
Is there anything that I
could do to help them?
You've already started doing it.
[AOI] You mean by stopping
Master Matsuba from leaving?
I see.
Well, then. I certainly can't
go back to Tenjin-ya now.
As for Ginji,
I'm sure he never wanted to
drag you into this mess,
and yet, Orio-ya is having
such a hard time preparing
for the fireworks that they were
forced to ask for your help.
Why is it that much
work for them?
It would be hard for anyone,
because they have to
gather several items
for the ceremony that are
essentially national treasures.
[AOI]
Like, relics or something?
[AOI gasps]
I'm glad that you're
an early riser.
It means we can have
more of these
secret morning meetings
while you're here.
Will you pass by
on your way back?
Yes, I will, but there will be a
watchman on patrol at that time.
Then I'll hang a
bucket full of ice
from that pine tree out front,
so make sure you check it
when you come by again.
There might be a treat.
I want to say thank you
for dressing my ankle,
so I'll make you a bento
with mackerel cooked in miso.
This is a first for me! A bento
delivered in a bucket of ice.
I can't tell you how much
I'm looking forward to that.
It even makes being a fish
peddler worthwhile.
Oh, yeah?
Well, now I'm going to make sure
that mackerel is frozen solid.
[laughs] Fine, do your worst.
You forget that,
with my ogre fire,
I'm able to reheat pretty
much anything.
Which reminds me.
Aoi, may I see your pendant?
What? Of course, here.
What did you do to it?
Heh. I'll be seeing
you around, Aoi.
Thanks for stopping by, Master.
I've actually missed you.
[MATSUBA] So this is what
fried oyster tastes like?
It's incredible, Aoi!
How could anything be so good!
Wow! Seconds, please! Seconds!
Of course. Right away.
[MATSUBA]
And keep 'em comin'. I'm hungry!
[AOI]
The oysters the master brought
were an even bigger hit
than I thought they'd be.
[laughs] She's really doing
a stellar job, huh?
[barks]
I'm so relieved that
Master Matsuba
enjoyed his meal again today.
[KAI]
Hey, lady.
[MEI]
Aoi Tsubaki.
Uh? Who's there?
[BOTH]
We're right behind you.
[AOI gasps]
[KAI]
I'm Kai, a black crane.
[MEI]
And I'm Mei, a white crane.
[AOI]
Are you twins?
Yeah, we are.
We work as chefs
here at Orio-ya.
[BOTH]
Yay!
Do you need something from me?
[BOTH]
Yes, we do.
We've ended up in a little
bit of a predicament.
We'd be really grateful if you
would help us out of it.
Orio-ya employees want my help?
Sounds suspicious!
Whoa, hold on a second!
It's nothing like that, really.
Just listen.
We're incredibly curious
about your cooking.
Tokihiko suggested that we ask
you to help us with this.
He trusts you.
What? Tokihiko said that?
Yodoko's a rain woman.
Yeah, and when she
loses her temper,
she likes to make it storm,
which isn't good.
Because of the fireworks
event that's coming up,
we've been appeasing her, but...
[BOTH] Now she's saying she's
getting tired of Orio-ya's food.
We're in an awful bind.
If she makes it rain because
of us, we're dead meat!
Ranmaru will probably throw us
into the middle of the ocean!
[AOI]
He sounds like a Yakuza boss.
So, what is it that
you want from me?
The lady tells us she
wants to eat interesting,
fun food that she's
never tasted before.
But we don't have any clue
what to cook for her!
[BOTH] So, we want you
to teach us about food
from the apparent realm.
But... Are you sure you
won't get in trouble?
Everyone at Orio-ya hates
my guts, don't they?
[BOTH]
No, not us.
We only started working
here a year ago.
We have no stake in the rivalry
between your inn and Orio-ya.
[BOTH]
Right?
[sighs] Okay, then let's
start thinking of solutions
to your problem together.
[BOTH]
She'll help, yay!
[AOI] But before we do,
can I ask a question?
[BOTH]
Sure, what?
I ate some squid shumai on
the day I was brought here.
And I have been wondering
about it ever since then.
I guess you guys are the chefs
who made it for me, right?
[BOTH]
Yeah, that was us.
I hope you're not gonna ask
us how to make it though.
'Cause we can't tell you
our trade secrets.
We promised Ranmaru we
wouldn't give that away.
No, of course not.
I just want to eat it again.
It was very delicious.
[BOTH]
What?
[AOI]
I beg you! Make me some more!
[BOTH]
Hm...
Huh?
[KAI, MEI]
Bring it in. Fist bump.
[AOI]
Mm...
[KAI, MEI]
Yay!
[AOI] Hmm. Does that
mean we have a deal?
[MITSUNARI]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I specifically asked you to
bring me the weekly Youto,
and yet you deliver this?
That's the wrong one!
Oh, my apologies, mistress.
Ugh. Really. You're useless.
You hear me, Mitsunari?
--Useless!
--[MITSUNARI] Sorry!
You're right, she's harsh.
Yeah, I told you so.
She's scary.
She has a short fuse and
will kick you for nothing.
[MEI] That attendant
gets assigned to her
because he loves the abuse.
[AOI]
A spoiled rich girl, huh?
Do I spy those two tsuru-douji
chefs hiding in the shadows?
[KAI, MEI]
She saw us!
[YODOKO] And who is that
girl you have with you?
I've never seen her before.
[KAI] Uh, she's going to be
cooking your meals with us
this evening, so we
brought her to meet you.
Her name's Aoi Tsubaki.
Hello, ma'am.
[YODOKO]
Aoi Tsubaki?
Are you the granddaughter of one
Shiro Tsubaki, by any chance?
I am.
And you married Tenjin-ya's
master innkeeper
recently, did you not?
No, ma'am, that is just a rumor.
[YODOKO] Your restaurant,
is that also a rumor?
Actually, that part's true.
As I recall, you serve apparent
realm Japanese food,
and Hakkabou's reports indicate
that he likes to eat there.
So, you're the famous Aoi, then.
I sincerely hope to live up
to Hakkabou's claims
about my skills when I cook
for you tonight, Madam Yodoko.
[BOTH]
Indeed.
I'm so looking forward to it.
Now, you may leave.
[KAI sighs]
I was freaking out.
[MEI] I thought she was
gonna yell at us again.
You guys threw me under
the bus. Not cool.
It's a good thing you're cute.
Now, then, tell me what kind
of flavors Yodoko likes.
[BOTH]
What?
She prefers really bold foods.
For an ayakashi,
she likes it hot and spicy.
[AOI]
Anything she doesn't eat?
For sure, but she's
totally fickle. Like...
...two days ago,
she hated deep-fried tofu.
Two days before that,
it was duck meat...
But there seems to be a pattern.
What she dislikes doesn't
change for two days.
[AOI]
Then what was it yesterday?
[BOTH]
Um, Natto .
Then what I'm thinking
of might just work.
How about we make
her monjayaki ?
What? Monjayaki ?
Yep. She can participate
in the cooking
and have a little fun, right?
But that's more of a snack
food than a meal, isn't it?
It is, but, because of that, she
probably hasn't had it before.
We'll bring out an iron plate
for her to grill it on, too.
Also, there're so many wonderful
varieties of seafood out here,
and I wanna cook with them
all, in any way I can!
Interesting.
It might work.
[ALL]
Yay!
[ALL laugh]
Even though it is
considered junk food,
we're gonna make it
kind of healthy!
For seafood, we'll use squid,
shrimp, and clams.
Let's throw in some okra, too!
We'll make classic pork monja ,
and everyone's favorite,
mentai-mochi-mochi-monja!
[KAI, MEI]
All right!
If you need mentaiko ,
we've got that!
That's a specialty
of the southern land,
so we can get ahold
of it easily.
Oh, do you have cheese?
I still have yet to
see it anywhere
since I first came to
the hidden realm.
They have it in
the northern land,
since dairy farming is
so widespread there.
But, even so, it isn't
a very common food
in any of the other parts of
the hidden realm either.
Oh, that means we'd have a
hard time finding it, right?
[BOTH] Shouldn't be
too hard. In fact...
...I'm pretty sure
specialty cheese
is still offered on
the room service menu.
Premium packages offer
in-room dining.
We'll go ask the employees
there for some.
What? Are you sure that's okay?
[BOTH]
Yep. Just leave it to us!
Finally.
Now. Time to taste.
I'm proud to present my favorite
junk food: the potato chip!
They're best fresh
from the fryer!
Gotta crush 'em up to
add them to the monja mix.
What're you doing
in here, lady?
You're cooking something
really scary.
There's nothing scary here.
These are potato chips.
You wanna try?
What? Are you sure it's okay
for me to eat this stuff?
Yes, of course!
Whoa! So good! Oh, man! Yummy!
Hey, Lady, can you make
these again sometime?
I've gotta share them
with my siblings!
Oh, you have siblings?
Yep, sure do!
I have an older brother and some
younger brothers and sisters!
We all live together
down by the harbor.
We're poor, so we can't
afford to live inland,
'cause it's a whole
lot nicer up there.
[AOI] Did something happen
to your parents?
[TAICHI] They went away
somewhere a long time ago.
But then Master Ranmaru
hired me to work here.
My older brother is a sailor
on one of Orio-ya's airships.
So, the two of us are able to
support our younger siblings.
That's admirable, especially
considering how young you are.
It's common for children
to work in the southern land,
since this area's so poor.
But thanks, lady.
[AOI] Come to think of it,
Shizuna said the same thing.
The southern land
is growing fast, though,
and a lot of that is
thanks to Orio-ya.
But Ranmaru says we still
don't have a lot of things
that are common in other
hidden realm lands.
'Kay, gotta go,
thanks for the food!
[AOI] Ranmaru may be
a brute, but it's clear
that he cares a great deal
about the southern land.
[AOI] Once I get
the cheese, that's it!
[BOTH]
Thanks for waiting!
[AOI] Wow! That cheese
looks delicious!
[TOKIHIKO]
I'd like to help you cook, too.
If that's all right?
[AOI]
Thanks, Tokihiko!
I apologize for making you
help with this, truly.
You've been so kind.
Hatori and I have been
protesting to Ranmaru
about the way he's
mistreated you.
I've been surprised and a
bit bewildered by it all,
to be honest, but, it's fine!
My current focus is making a
monjayaki for Mistress Yodoko.
Your ability to adapt
never ceases to amaze me.
I heard you were in need
of an iron hot plate?
I can take care of
heating it up for you.
Thanks so much!
[BOTH]
That's a shiranui for you!
Okay! Looks like we've got
all the ingredients now!
Ready? Let's do this!
[BOTH]
Yay!
[AOI] Soldiers.
Let's head into battle!
[CHIBI] It appears that Aoi
found more underlings to train!
And Aoi's underlings
are my underlings!
Hey, you twins!
Bring me some more
cucumbers at once!