[DIAO]
Battle hasn't even started yet!
We won't get swallowed up!
[BING GUI] The Fei Xin Force's
main unit escaped the dragnet
before we could close in.
Then, they joined up
with their scattered troops.
Regrouping so quickly.
Clearly, they must have gotten
some brains on board, finally.
This one move will show me just
what their tactician's made of!
They're here!
The enemy vanguard!
[DIAO]
Out of all 4,000 troops,
a quarter of them
are now on the move.
And an elite force, at that!
They definitely
don't want this over.
[TIAN XIAO]
He Liao Diao!
If we don't intercept
the enemy, they will--
No mind!
[DIAO] They can't
tell from over there...
...that the Wei army has lots
of branching paths on their way!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
The enemy has dispersed!
That's good!
[DIAO]
With their manpower scattered
and the narrow path before them,
they've got a small attack area!
[DIAO] That's how our
five hundred troops can prevail
over their thousand troops!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Firstly, we will use
our heavy-weight men
to block off one path for them.
[DIAO] After that,
we march onward through force
and push the enemy to
the crossroads.
That way, we will have
capped off the entrance
to all the smaller paths.
Something's not right behind!
Say what?
[WEI SOLDIER 236C]
Enemies behind us?
[WEI SOLDIER 236D]
Impossible!
With all of their
escape paths suddenly cut off,
they'll dive into confusion.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[DIAO] And that's exactly
when we strike hard!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER laughs]
These guys are total pushovers!
They have absolutely
no idea what's going on!
Yeah, I'd say so.
They're just like how
we used to be in the past!
Stay firm!
We don't need an
escape path anyway!
Yes, commander!
All troops focus only
on the enemy before you!
They are hardly
powerful enough to match us!
[TIAN XIAO gasps]
[DAO QING]
First off tighten ranks!
[TIAN XIAO]
Oh no! We need to regroup!
[DIAO] No, now we know
where their leader is!
Kill him and
his unit is done for!
[yelling]
[WEI SOLDIERS]
Dao Qing, sir!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 236B]
Tian You!
If this were a real fight,
you would be no match
for us whatsoever.
[WEI MESSENGER 236A]
Urgent report!
Commander Dao Qing
has been killed,
and his unit
almost destroyed!
[WEI SOLDIER 236E]
What did you say?
[WEI SOLDIER 236F]
It happened so soon!
Bing Gui...
[BING GUI]
I have underestimated them.
The vanguard must
charge immediately!
[WEI SOLDIERS]
Sir!
He Liao Diao! The enemy...
...they're spreading out
and advancing!
[JIAN YONG] Bing Gui...
Do you think the
same thing would happen
if we go down
that path instead, then?
No need to worry.
That strategy
was just a stopgap.
That can only be effective
if our troops are concentrated
at the narrowed path,
as you can see.
If we split up our troops
and send them down every path,
their puny squad won't
be able to stop them all.
Once we get through,
we'll be at the heart
of their camp in no time.
[DIAO] Quick thinking.
These guys really mean business!
[TIAN XIAO gasps]
[TIAN XIAO] Now they're coming
through unguarded paths!
He Liao Diao!
The narrowed path
battle is done!
Already done?
Have all posted troops
assemble by Xin to the right!
To the right?
Aren't we defending our camp?
We simply cannot
spare the manpower for that!
I had always intended
to leave this place to rot.
What? But we--
[DIAO] Expose the camp
to draw in the enemy.
For the significantly small and
injured Fei Xin Force to win,
this can't be drawn out.
It needs to be a short war!
Come on, let's go, guys!
[DIAO] If we manage
to take their main camp
before they take ours,
we will win!
[distant yelling]
[WEI SOLDIER 236G] Enemies
headed our way from the left!
Are they after us?
That's absurd.
[TIAN XIAO] Go! Go!
[MENG YI] He Liao Diao...
[MENG YI]
...there are two main ways
to destroy a heavily
guarded main camp.
So then, I would have
to say that the one that's most
commonly used during a battle
is still plain old brute force.
Of course, that way
comes at great cost.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MENG YI] Then again,
that is precisely
why it works so well.
[LONG YOU]
Follow the commander!
[WEI SOLDIER 236H] They are
now fighting on the left!
We're being pushed back!
[BING GUI] Don't flinch!
Send backup to boost numbers.
[WEI SOLDIER 236H]
Yes, sir!
Ha! What now?
Ending with force instead of
a real proper strategy? Haha!
Some tactician they've got now!
Not quite.
A brute-force attack
is a good call.
Huh?
Your enemy will be racking
their brains, too,
so you can rarely win with an
unconventional tactic alone.
A brute-force attack tactic
is almost always
the very final move.
It's really just a matter
of when to use it, you see.
[BING GUI] You could say
the enemy tactician we targeted
right after mobilizing
made the best choice.
[JIAN YONG] You seem confident,
Bing Gui, to be heaping praise.
I'm not praising, I'm
just saying they weren't stupid.
Four defense formation!
Into position!
Stop them from the front
and thin them from the sides!
Considering the
Fei Xin Force's might,
earlier Wei armies probably
would have lost this charge.
But now we have
thoroughly trained generals
and my regular soldiers
in our camp.
Plus, we saw
the destructive power
of the Fei Xin Force
in Shanyang,
so there's absolutely no chance
of us misjudging our response!
[BING GUI] They don't have
a snowball's chance
whatsoever right now!
Xin, sir!
All this enemy backup.
[SOLDIER] These guys make
for one tough front line!
[TIAN XIAO] The enemy's
response is unusually swift!
They're overwhelming
our commander!
[TIAN XIAO] The enemy
is right at our feet!
We need to retreat,
He Liao Diao!
[DIAO] Leave them!
Leave them? But uh...
Take rocks and
throw them down, now!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[TIAN XIAO] He Liao Diao!
Ready to give the signal?
[DIAO] Not yet!
[DIAO] Hang in there, everyone.
[DIAO] And Xin!
This strategy...
What's that brat doing?
You must be doing okay
if you can still
call her names!
Be quiet!
[JIAN YONG]
We still can't crush them?
Tenacious little buggers.
[BING GUI]
Let's finish this.
Send in more backup!
Surround the back and do not let
their commander Xin escape now!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WEI SOLDIER 236L]
Kill Xin of the Fei Xin Force!
Enemy backup inbound!
Even more than before!
All right.
Here we go then, men!
Let's show them what the
Fei Xin Force is really made of!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[FEI XIN FORCE]
Those bastards!
[TIAN XIAO] Hurry up,
He Liao Diao! The enemy!
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO] Their defense is
entirely focused on Xin now!
Right now!
Raise the signal flag!
--Hm?
--Huh?
What's that?
That strange noise?
[BING GUI] Behind us?
[rumbling noise]
[MENG YI] The second way to
strike an enemy's main camp
is to use an ingenious trick to
open a hole in their defense,
then unleash a lethal one-hit
surprise attack right after.
[YOUNGER LIE] Guo Bei's men
of the Fei Xin Force, go!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WEI SOLDIER 236M]
They're attacking us?
[WEI SOLDIER 236N]
It's an attack!
[XIN] Diao, you really
are something else!
Are you seriously using me
as a decoy right now?
Hey! Did we capture
their generals?
Hahaha! We did it!
[TIAN YONG]
Why haven't you killed them?
[YOUNGER LIE] The lady tactician
said to take them alive.
[TIAN YONG] Take them alive?
[YOUNGER LIE] She said
it's a battle of subjugation.
What?
Well either way, they'll
be very pleased to see them
at main camp!
Hey, look up, you guys!
[WEI PING] The main camp--our
main camp is burning now!
[PEI LANG]
What? What's happening?
[PEI LANG] Just as we
took down their camp?
We did use most of
our soldiers for the attack.
There must've been almost
no one guarding the camp.
Uh, what did you say?
Don't tell me that brat
ended up sacrificing herself.
Hey now!
Don't go writing me off!
[XIN] Diao!
[TIAN YONG]
The brat!
So what's with our camp?
Oh, they probably
set fire to it
out of spite for losing.
And because I wasn't there.
[YUAN] How'd you manage to
escape the surrounding troops
with so few men?
[DIAO] You have got to
secure a solid escape route
from the beginning!
[laughing]
[WEI PING]
Amazing!
Completely out of this world!
Seems like you have
some guts, you know!
Hey. Bing Gui?
This little girl
really and truly
--led us to victory today!
--Oh yeah!
[PEI LANG] When you're wrong,
you're wrong, right, Tian Yong?
[TIAN YONG]
Eh, it was just a fluke.
[PEI LANG]
Hey, take it like a man!
[BING GUI]
Quit yanking my chain!
This? This little
tiny girl right here?
I am the great Bing Gui,
one of Wei's top
eight elite tacticians,
and I lost today
to someone like her?
[BING GUI]
I refuse to accept that.
This attack was
an impractical creation,
the worst plan of all time!
It worked only because
the Fei Xin Force
just happened to have
good fighting strength!
Because if it was any other
unit, the decoys would be dead!
[BING GUI] You must have
significant casualties!
[XIN] Hey.
Quit your yapping now, old man.
Me? "Old man"?
Then her plan
was pretty amazing,
using the power
of the Fei Xin Force
to its greatest
potential in the very end.
Face it, this was a battle
of wits, and you just lost
to He Liao Diao, our tactician!
Catch that name?
Make sure you remember it!
Um, Xin...
[XIN] Take them with you.
All right! We have won!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[cheering continues]
[curtain opens]
[XIN] Hey.
Hi, Xin!
What are you doing over here?
It's been a good long while
since we properly celebrated.
Come on.
No, I'm good.
I have to work out strategies
for the terrain that's
coming up real soon, you know.
[XIN] Yeah, but you
can do that tomorrow.
Well, no, I cannot!
If I... If I make
just the slightest mistake,
dozens of people
will die once again.
I need a solid plan this time.
[XIN] You really
shouldn't burden yourself
with the number of casualties.
But I do, I have to!
Why can't you
understand the stakes?
[DIAO] Every direction
I give on the battlefield
takes into account just how many
men might die out there for us.
Look, Diao--
[DIAO] I am truly
cut out for this work,
and I showed that aptitude
in my first battle.
However, when I think
of what lies ahead,
I can't help but get scared.
Nearly a hundred troops
died in this battle, you know.
How many hundreds more
will there be in the end?
Even the nice man who told me
that I looked like his
daughter, just earlier...
He died by my strategy.
He went out of his way to
offer encouragement, and I--
And I--
[DIAO] I can't bring him back.
That smile of his.
[curtain opens]
You should just
leave now, then.
[XIN] Go to war,
and you'll kill someone.
Friend or enemy, who knows
how much blood and tears
are spilled behind the scenes?
And the victors carry all that
with them as they move forward.
That's why your back
gets heavier and heavier
with every single win.
[XIN] If you came over here
not knowing about that pain,
just leave now.
I'm not going anywhere!
I was just talking about
how much worse it was,
in a real battle!
It's a pain worse than I
had ever imagined, you know!
I didn't come here on
a whim, do you understand me?
[laughs]
Right on!
That's why this old veteran in
front of you is gonna teach you
the trick to sticking
around out here!
Give me your hand, then!
What?
[XIN] Come on! Like this!
[DIAO] Hey, Xin!
That hurts a lot!
Just keep going!
[XIN] The pain of losing
a comrade is the same
for tacticians
and soldiers alike.
However, we happen
to know the best way
to overcome that pain,
as you'll soon see.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[laughing continues]
[XIN] We all share it
and make it hurt less
by celebrating over the top
and send it packing.
You do it too, then.
Because you're one of us,
and now you know.
[GUO BEI'S SOLDIERS] And-a one,
and-a two, and-a one-two-three!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 236E]
I'm gonna die!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 236F]
You guys are the best!
And you want me to do that?
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 236G]
Hey, it's the lady tactician!
[WEI PING]
No! Don't look down!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 236H]
There she is!
Over here, Miss Diao!
Come down!
I still don't like her!
Be quiet, Tian Yong!
Hey, Xin.
[XIN]
What? What is it?
[DIAO] Will you let go of
my hand? It's mortifying!
Don't be such a jerk!
It's not like I was trying to--
Yes I know, I know!
Right, let's do this!
[QING] Xin is here!
[WEI PING]
Oh, who needs you?
[XIN]
Say what?
So who doesn't need me?
[laughing]
[DIAO] Thanks a lot, Xin.
[yawning]
Hey!
Lieutenant Chu Shui
and his troops are back!
[TIAN XIAO] I've brought back
Lieutenant Chu Shui.
[DIAO] I see.
It must have been rough
handling your supply work
with the main camp
moving all over the place.
I will take over
all that kind of stuff
from now onwards, understand?
So you can just go right back
to the front of the lines now.
And just who
is this girl, then?
I thought you said
you told him before!
This is Xin's little sister?
[DIAO, TIAN XIAO]
No, no, no!
[TIAN XIAO]
This is He Liao Diao,
and she's our new
tactician you see!
Yep, it's all finally
coming together!
[NARRATOR] From then on,
the Fei Xin Force went on
to crush their opposition.
[gasps]
[XIN yelling]
[NARRATOR] The Wei army
that had gathered at Lijing
to try to reclaim Shanyang
were instead rounded up
by the dozen,
and in ten short days,
Lijing was finally conquered.
[SOLDIERS cheering]
The Fei Xin Force
has come all this way?
That's right, with no enemies
left to go after Lijing,
they're moving north.
I hear they'd be working
with the Le Hua Force
in order to rout
Wei troops in Weizi.
It really does appear
like they've gotten
their old strength
right back now.
Even stronger.
In the Lijing Offensive,
they didn't just take out
the enemies they had,
they fought as if battling
absolutely all of the Wei troops
throughout the region
they were in, you see.
And with the help
and the positions
of the adjacent
fellow Qin armies,
they treated all of Lijing like
one big battlefield, and won!
And so, that truly
was wide-scale warfare.
Clearly, the Fei Xin Force
possesses a might
they never had
in times before.
Now that they're coming
into their own
as solid independent reserves,
they're truly powerful.