I have only five years' grace
remaining now, I'm afraid.
In five years, I will
be 22 years old.
[DIAO gasps]
So that means--
My crowning ceremony.
Once I am finally crowned,
I will be recognized
as Qin's ruler both
at home and abroad.
When that happens,
some in Lü's faction
are sure to come
over to my side.
Five years is plenty!
Xin?
We're not playing
around here at all.
If they're comin' in five
years to put an end to this,
that's when we fight!
Exactly so.
And Xin, what about
you exactly, then?
Can you make general
in five short years?
[XIN]
A general in five years?
The general I mobilize
with my very first command
will be you, Xin!
[gasps]
[XIN]
Five more years.
Even if Lü Buwei does
come to crush him,
I do believe that Zheng will be
the undisputed king of all Qin.
Which means...
I'll do it, Zheng!
In five years I'll be a general,
you can bet on it!
[XIN yells]
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
The Fei Xin Force!
[NARRATOR] After the Qin-Zhao
alliance was complete,
and Xin returned to
the Fei Xin Force,
the squadron only
continued to grow,
displaying its ferocity
on the front lines.
[gasps] Song Zuo!
[SONG ZUO]
Huh?
Well, well, so you are the squad
that's been pushin' its
luck around these parts.
H-He's huge!
Way bigger than Long Chuan!
Bring your commander out front!
Gang Tan here will send
his head into orbit
with my three-headed mace!
[XIN]
Darn it.
[yells]
[GANG TAN groans]
I can't be wasting time
on dimwits like you.
Because I only have five years.
[WEI SOLDIERS whimper]
R-Re-Retreat!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[WEI PING laughs]
We just keep on winning!
Soon, no one will
stand up to us!
Go Fei Xin Force!
Aren't you full o' yourself!
You hardly even lift
a finger out there.
That's true, but boy,
he can really talk us up!
Oh, shut up!
Why not bask a little in the
afterglow of another victory?
Um, I guess.
What I mean by this is...
Who really knows if
Wei Ping'll be alive tomorrow?
Now, wait a second!
I am so not gonna die!
I'll come home alive
so Dong Mei can love me up!
My sweet baby Dong Mei!
--[FEI XIN FORCE laughs]
--Mmm! My baby! Mmm!
[BI] Is that the face of
a victorious commander?
[gasps]
Long time no see, Xin.
Hey, Bi!
[BI]
Talk about a surprise!
To think the Fei Xin Force is
this famous on the front lines.
As soon as I heard,
I knew you'd be here.
Only 'cause these
front lines are small.
Doesn't take much to get
your name out there.
All of this really
means nothing to me.
Just as I thought,
you are chomping at the bit.
I knew it was worth coming
all this way to see you.
Uh, now that you mention it,
what are you doing out here?
I'm on my way to my
post at Yashui Castle.
Xin, the results of the
Qin and Zhao alliance
are coming to the light.
[XIN, FEI XIN FORCE gasp]
[BI]
Our strategy to attack Wei!
Since we don't have to be
wary of Zhao anymore,
we can focus absolutely
all of our military power
exclusively on Wei, you see.
So Xianyang's formed a grand
strategy to send troops
into Shanyang in Wei
to take the region's 20 castles
in just one fell swoop.
[XIN]
How is that even possible?
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
[BI] This is still
highly confidential.
But, I came all this way
to tell you anyway, Xin.
[gasps]
[BI] If you want to keep
climbing the ranks,
your best bet is to win big
in a really huge battle
like this one. But first,
you absolutely have to be placed
in a very crucial position
right within the army,
do you understand me?
Why is that?
You can't expect great results
at the edges of the battlefield.
For logistical
support, you know.
[WEI PING]
Hm. Makes sense.
So this is no time
to be disheartened, Xin.
The Wei offensive
will likely get started
in less than a year from now.
Until then, keep chalking up win
after win, no matter how small,
and get into a better position
for the actual real fight!
However, this information's
already been leaked
to military commanders,
I should warn you.
You can clearly tell.
It's obvious by all of the
ambitious men at the front lines
ready to put all of what
I've said into practice.
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
Yes, of course, Bi.
We are not the only ones that
are shooting for the stars.
But that doesn't mean
we're gonna lose to them!
You go get them, Xin.
[chuckles]
[BI]
Hm?
Thanks for coming out here
to tell me all of this.
I can always count
on you, my man, Bi.
Do not thank me.
You are like a little brother
I have to keep my eye on,
you understand?
[BI, XIN laugh]
Give me some intel on
the units in this area.
Their scale for instance,
their achievements--
Anything will do.
Sir!
[BI] Maybe that was a
little meddling of me.
[NARRATOR] Some days later,
an unusually large battle
was unfolding on the front lines
where Xin and his troops
found themselves.
The Wei army had mustered
from throughout the area
to push back the front lines,
and were now more
than 10,000 strong.
The Qin army mustered their
troops to the north and south,
intending to attack
Wei from both sides.
It was the first midsized battle
in this part of the kingdom.
Here we go, Commander.
There's 10,000 troops.
No sittin' this one
out now, huh, Xin?
Right.
The Fei Xin Force will stay
an independent reserve squadron.
We can go where we want
during the battle,
but don't count on
any other help.
Wait for the best chance,
and go for their general
on our sheer strength!
[TIAN YONG grunts]
[XIN] Qiang Lei, what's your
take on all of this?
The Qin army will likely
make it to the main force
before reaching stalemate.
If you want their general,
start back here first,
circle around behind their
main force, then rush them.
Of course, it won't be easy
to break through
their defenses at all.
[FEI XIN FORCE gasping]
[XIN]
Yuan? Lu Yan?
No objections.
Same here.
Okay.
Let's do this!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
Push! Push!
Push on in!
I-It's no use!
We can't reach Wei's
main force right now!
We're only losing soldiers
on our side instead!
If this keeps up--
[COMMANDER 204A growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[HORSEMAN 204A] What's that
squadron over there?
They're dodging the
defensive formation
and circling behind the
enemy's main force!
Th-That is--
[COMMANDER 204A]
The Fei Xin Force!
Come on, we're
breaking through!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
[WEI SOLDIER 204G]
What's with these guys?
[WEI SOLDIER 204H]
S-Such might!
Hey! What are you doing?
Don't let them through!
If they get past us, the main
force will be totally ex--
[XIN grunts]
[WEI COMMANDER 204A groans]
[XIN grunting]
[WEI SOLDIERS groaning]
[XIN]
Here we go!
Your general's gonna be...
...history!
[YANG]
What?
There's still nothing going on
between you and His Highness?
Uh, huh, um.
[XIANG] I go to his bedchamber,
but he always tells me
to just sit quietly beside him.
[YANG] But Xiang, His Highness
has kept on summoning you
time and time again!
Usually people don't get
called more than once if...
Hmm...
[gasps] What's wrong?
[YANG]
Hm? Hm...
I don't see anything special
about you whatsoever.
So why you specifically?
I-I have no idea!
That girl bolts at the
most suspicious of times.
Xiang, wait up, come on!
Let me get a
better look at you!
--[XIANG] Stop it, Yang!
--[YANG] C'mon, Xiang!
--I said I don't know!
--Get back here!
[ZHENG] So Wei has made it
to our borders again.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Yes.
There have been ongoing
skirmishes at the front line
for days, now.
[ZHENG] We must make haste
with the Wei offensive.
[ZHENG]
Five years.
Sire?
[ZHENG]
Keep climbing fast.
I'm waiting for you, Xin.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Go, go, go!
Keep up with your commander!
[gasps]
[XIN]
Yes!
We're through!
Take their general!
[gasps]
[FEI XIN FORCE gasping]
[XIN]
What is all this?
[YUAN]
Th-They've all been killed.
The main force, obliterated?
Wh-What's going on here?
[XIN]
What's this?
Someone's here.
[XIN, FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
[WANG BEN]
Well, well!
What have we here?
So we weren't the only ones
after the main force.
Unfortunately, you're a little
too late, I would say.
[XIN] So they got to the
enemy general before we did?
[XIN]
Who is this guy, exactly?
A horseman squad?
[FAN YANG]
You there! Foot soldiers!
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
Whose squad are you? Answer now!
We belong to Qin's
northern army!
We're the special
300-man Fei Xin Force!
And who would you be?
Say what?
[HORSEMEN]
The Fei Xin Force?
Wh-Whose squad are you exactly?
What gives?
Identify yourselves now!
We happen to be
the Yu Feng Force,
the special 300-man squadron
in Qin's southern army.
[XIN]
Huh?
A special 300-man squadron?
Uh, exactly like our squad?
I see.
So you are that Fei Xin Force.
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIERS laugh]
Huh?
[laughing continues]
[XIN] What's so funny,
you bunch o' jerks?
[WANG BEN]
Ha. Apologies.
Forgive our rudeness.
But you see, I can explain it.
We hear so much of the famed
Fei Xin Force these days.
Being a fellow
special force ourselves,
we've been on the
lookout for them
for a long time now, you see.
But to learn that the
rumors were right,
and you really are a
bunch of country soldiers?
Why, we could hardly
believe our eyes.
--Forgive us.
--[YU FENG FORCE laughs]
[TIAN YONG growls]
[laughing continues]
Quit laughin'!
[YU FENG FORCE gasp]
So what if we're
country soldiers then?
We're 300 men strong,
the same as all of you!
We are definitely far from
the same, you imbecile.
Say what?
[WANG BEN] The Yu Feng Force
is an elite squadron
made up of noblemen
educated in military school
from a young age.
We wield swords and swing spears
long before any farm
child grips a hoe,
and have both individual and
group combat drummed into us.
Whereas you are novices at war,
meant to be working
the fields, quite simply.
I see why'd you be
so happy to pull off
a string of victories at all,
but the idea that your squadron
is on a par with ours
makes me ill.
Actually, just having you foot
soldiers in a special squad
in the first place
is a big mistake.
No doubt about it.
So quite frankly, your
presence on the battlefield
is most akin...
...to that of an ant.
[XIN, FEI XIN FORCE growl]
An ant?
[WANG BEN] Ants faithfully carry
out orders from above,
regardless of their
own self-interest.
It's what they do best, you see.
Devoting yourselves to this
is the most crucial duty
for you foot soldiers.
It's not to belittle you
peasants whatsoever, of course.
With an army of over 100,000,
80% is made of foot soldiers,
like yourselves.
You're the fundamental
power of any army,
and without you,
we cannot fight.
However, ants can
only be ants.
That's what they are.
Leave the high-level,
independent-reserve work to us.
You go back to your
post and work hard.
Dreams don't cut it.
Though, I can sadly
see some fool
putting you all up
to this scheme.
[gasps]
[BI]
I knew it.
Make any small mention
of the Wei offensive,
and little squads start
showing up from everywhere.
[BI]
Including the Yu Feng Force.
A 300-man squadron that is
exceedingly skilled and strong.
But that commander of theirs...
[BI]
Hang in there, Xin.
[FAN YANG]
Shall we then, sir?
We must take the general's head
and put an end to this battle.
Yes.
Not so fast!
[WANG BEN, FAN YANG]
Huh?
X-Xin, sir, easy there!
You're talking to a nobleper--
Enough!
So what exactly have I been
listening to all this time?
Noble or not, doesn't matter.
Once the fighting starts,
you should know, you moron!
These hands of ours have
killed high-falutin' guys
just like you!
Who's the moron here?
Did you not fully understand
my story about the ants?
[YU FENG FORCE laughs]
Lieutenant Fan Yang!
[FAN YANG]
Sir!
Wh-What in the--
Troops! Attention!
[FEI XIN FORCE gasp]
[laughs] There we go!
Now do you
understand your place?
[laughing]
[FEI XIN FORCE growls]
You bastard!
Don't do it.
[laughing]
[gasps]
[WANG BEN]
Hm?
[XIN]
Well, that does it.
Gramps, get down off your
horse right now and apologize.
Unless you want me
to drag you off it.
Oh!
With that toy sword
of yours, you will?
[XIN grunts]
[XIN]
Why, you--!
Xin, sir!
I'd like to give some candid
advice to you in particular:
You were a servant,
and now openly brag
about becoming the
greatest general,
or something like that.
[XIN growls]
[WANG BEN]
Now, among the nobility,
talented young
commanders like myself
are coming to the force,
I will have you know.
The battle to be the next
general has already begun,
but there's not even a
speck of room in there
for a roadside weed like you.
I'd advise you to know
your limitations well.
You'll command no more
than 1,000 men.
[XIN gasps]
[XIN yells]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Xi-Xin...
No way.
It's a reverse thrust.
[XIN grunts]
[YUAN, WEI PING]
Xin!
[FAN YANG] Why bother
using the Dragon Finger
on the likes of him, sir?
[XIN grunts]
Dragon?
A piercing technique, tracing
weaving orbits in midair,
like a dragon.
This guy here, he's tough.
[WANG BEN] Honestly, you've
been a thorn in our side.
Now's the time to make
the crucial gap between us
absolutely crystal clear.
[XIN]
I-I'll get you.
[WANG BEN] Remember this,
commander of the Fei Xin Force:
My name is Wang Ben.
Wang Ben.
Wang?
Wang!
Yes.
Of the very same clan as your
dearly beloved Wang Yi.
Unlike Wang Yi, though,
This Wang carries on
the family name!
[gasps]
[WANG BEN] We'll stay on this
front line for a while yet.
So you'd better get used
to lots of disappointment,
I'm afraid.