[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
of the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
Bingo, Mr. 1,000-Man-
Commander-For-A-Day.
So right now,
I'll take your life too.
[FAN YANG]
Defend General Wang Ben!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[laughs] I wonder if you can!
Move, now.
Me, move now?
I've got this one.
[MESSENGER 219A]
The first unit is struggling!
[MESSENGER 219B] Yan Bi's and
Tai Yun's squads are destroyed!
[MESSENGER 219C]
General Tu Men has taken up arms
and is now standing
on the front lines!
Two 1,000-men squads have
gone down just like that, now?
Hey, wait a moment.
Yan Bi and Tai Yun
were both appointed
as commanders last
minute, am I correct?
[gasps]
[YUAN]
So are they saying that
the special 1,000-man commanders
aren't fit for real battle?
[growls]
[XIN] What's going on
with the Yu Feng Force?
Huh, messenger guy?
Like I would actually know?
Who the heck are you, anyway?
[XIN]
Wang Ben.
Single combat?
No, thank you, though.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Right, men,
make quick work of them.
[SOLDIERS yell]
What is this?
Here they come!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[FAN YANG]
Wh-What might!
This has nothing to do with
coordination within the squad.
This enemy is
frighteningly strong!
This squad isn't like the rest,
There must be two, three
hundred elites among them.
Though, surely even they have
far less experience than my men.
In any case, our squad
is under Lun Hu,
one of the Big Four
directly linked to
General Lian Po...
...who fought solidly
through and survived
the big era of Zhao's
first Three Greats,
and Qin's Six Greats.
[FAN YANG]
One of Lian Po's Big Four?
[chuckles]
[yelps]
[SOLDIER gasp]
[WANG BEN]
It makes no difference.
No matter how strong
your troops really are,
take out their commander,
and the squad will be destroyed.
Then it's all over.
[LUN HU]
That's very true, yes.
[laughs] You've got a point.
And if you want it as badly
as you're suggesting,
there'll be no hard feelings.
[TU MEN'S ADJUTANT]
General Tu Men,
don't push yourself too hard!
I know that very well!
[TU MEN] My merely standing
at the fore of this battle
has revitalized the
troops a little, it seems.
But losing two of
8,000 troops so quickly,
I fear it is too big a blow
for us to endure now.
My lord!
May I suggest falling back
for now and regrouping?
[TU MEN]
No!
Victory for these once
identically sized vanguards,
depends greatly on the morale
of all troops on both sides!
We will turn the tide of
this battle, no matter what!
I'll visit the hurting
squads to inspire them!
Come now!
[TU MEN'S ADJUTANT]
Yes, sir!
[RONG BEI'S FLAG BEARER 219A]
Second unit,
prepare to sally forth!
Take your positions!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[laughs]
What can I say?
Time to clean up
the first unit's mess!
[laughs]
Fei Xin Force!
Is Xin here?
[XIN]
Huh?
Yeah!
[RONG BEI] The first unit's
status is just as reported.
The enemy is
probably going after
the ad-hoc 1,000-man
commanders first.
[gasps]
[RONG BEI]
Which means
you better fully understand the
fact that your Fei Xin Force
is most likely next in line!
Don't go down too fast.
It'd be an inconvenience!
Same goes for you, Chang Fan!
[CHANG FAN]
Yes, sir!
[XIN]
It's just what I really wanted!
[RONG BEI]
You good over there?
Let's get a move on!
[SOLDIER]
Yes, Sir!
[XIN] Chu Shui, is the
cavalry ready now?
[FEI XIN FORCE CAVALRY yells]
Right!
You too, Yuan?
[YUAN]
Always!
[XIN]
Good!
Qiang Lei?
[XIN]
Check!
Let's do this!
Second unit!
Go now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[LI CHONG]
The second unit is on the move!
Commanding general Rong Bei,
8,000 troops, 2,000 of which
are the ad-hoc Fei Xin Force
and the Chang Fan Force!
Oopsy!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER 219A]
Lun Hu can't get near him!
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219B]
That's Wang Ben for you!
That's right, see?
It's just one-sided!
[FAN YANG]
No, that's not it.
Wang Ben's been dealing
some full-powered thrusts,
the likes of which we
rarely ever see in battle.
And in spite of this,
that man's body hasn't
a single scratch at all.
What a surprise!
I really have fought with
countless spearmen in my day,
let me tell you.
But I must admit that
you stand above the rest.
Those spear skills!
You're young, but your
proficiency comes through.
[FAN YANG]
It's only natural.
That unflagging energy.
He may have been born
with a real innate
talent for the spear,
but he was never once
arrogant about it.
His hands split open,
their blood spurted,
and snow was made
vapor in its heat.
Wang Ben here was given a
daredevil warrior's incessant
and strenuous training
from an early age,
wields the spear as though
already an expert!
[WANG BEN grunts]
[LUN HU]
He's getting even faster.
[WANG BEN grunts]
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
There it is!
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219E]
It's the...
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219F]
...Dragon Finger!
[WANG BEN, FAN YANG gasp]
[YU FENG SOLDIER 219D]
He...
[YU FENG SOLDIER 219E]
...did it!
[FAN YANG]
No!
He missed him!
[LUN HU]
At first, I wasn't entirely sure
that I'd dodged it.
But as I said before,
when you've fought
with enough spearmen,
you tend to see these kinds
of tricks a time or two.
And well,
did you know?
[WANG BEN gasps]
[FAN YANG growls]
[LUN HU] Right after
a major move like that,
there's always a little opening.
[FAN YANG]
His sword!
When did he throw that?
[LUN HU] It really seems
like the Qin army has lots
of pretty ambitious
young fellows, these days.
But you see,
you were unlucky today.
[YU FENG FORCE gasps]
[WANG BEN grunting]
[FAN YANG grunts]
[FAN YANG]
My spear, it's bent in two!
How strong is this scoundrel?
[FAN YANG grunts]
Fall back, Yu Feng Force!
Get in front of
Wang Ben, right now!
[LUN HU giggles]
Nope no, that won't work!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIERS yell]
[WANG BEN]
Don't pull out blindly!
You'll be hit from behind.
Sir!
We stay here, and we will fight!
Next time, I won't miss.
[LUN HU]
My!
[rumbling]
What's that rumbling?
The Qin army's second unit!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
We're coming, vanguard!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER 219B]
Lun Hu, sir!
The enemy's second unit
approaches with 8,000!
We're making contact!
[BAI GUIXI]
General Lian Po,
we should send out our
own reinforcements.
[LIAN PO]
No need now.
Huh?
[LIAN PO] Keep sending these
defective armies out there,
and we will just keep
getting the same result.
Commander Chang Fan!
The first unit has
now been split up!
[SOLDIER 219A]
The seventh unit is destroyed!
[SOLDIER 219B]
The eighth unit too!
Send the fourth
unit out in front!
[CHANG FAN'S ADJUTANT]
The fourth unit?
There is no fourth unit!
What did you say?
[NARRATOR] A squad's strength
on the battlefield depends on
a unified consciousness
and precise coordination.
Without these,
a squad can't show its
offensive or defensive powers.
[SOLDIER 219A]
The enemy cavalry approaches!
[NARRATOR] If even the
Yu Feng Force was struggling,
the rest of the squads
were finding it impossible
to fight in a real battle.
[RONG BEI'S ADJUTANT]
Rong Bei, sir!
Chang Fan's squad is hurting!
Send help right away!
Mmm. So, they're no good.
What about the Fei Xin Force?
It seems they have also
been split up and--
[NARRATOR]
There was one strange thing:
alone among all of the squads...
[NARRATOR] ...the Fei Xin Force
emanated the brightest,
and the most intense light!
Go!
What is that over there?
[LUN HU'S ADJUTANT] Lun Hu, sir,
there's shouting to the left.
[LUN HU]
I hear it.
What a strange, odd upsurge.
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219G]
The shouts came
from this side, here!
[YU FENG SOLDIER 219H]
Which squad was that?
[WANG BEN]
The Fei Xin Force.
[HUANG]
Wh-What's with these guys?
That's one very mixed-up squad,
and with not a speck
of coordination
between infantry and cavalry.
So why haven't they
been destroyed already?
How can they be this strong?
No, they're not just
mixed up, they are just--
[NARRATOR] There was a trick
to the Fei Xin Force's actions
that fateful day.
[CHU SHUI] And next, if we in
the cavalry are right over here,
the infantry moves down here,
and circles to here.
At the same time,
split into two,
with one half following
the cavalry.
But watch this here,
and right here, too.
If the enemy shows up
here, we have to--
Let's just forget
about it, Chu Shui.
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
[XIN] We really have got
plenty of faith in our brawn,
but we're not so great
at brains, honestly.
There's no use springing
a joint attack plan on us.
It's bound to fail
pathetically, see?
[XIN]
It'd be even better,
if we fought separately
this time around.
We can handle being on our own,
and I'm sure you
Guo Bei folks will be fine.
B-But then what's the point of
our being a 1,000-man army--
That's not it.
I think Xin's definitely
right about all of this.
I had the feeling,
as I was explaining it
that we couldn't
fight that way now.
All right, then.
Let's forget all
about that, for now.
Just one thing.
Let's go out there
as a 1,000-man unit
with one very simple, very
easy arrangement in mind.
An arrangement?
[CHU SHUI]
That is...
[XIN grunts]
[WEI SOLDIER 219B groans]
[XIN gasps]
[XIN]
The flag!
[NARRATOR]
The arrangement held that,
given the signal,
at any time, and fighting
absolutely any foe,
Commander Xin
would set his sights
on the previously
agreed-upon enemy,
And at that moment,
all 1,000 troops
would attack as one!
Wow! What raw power!
Their main force
went flyin', there!
Never seen that before!
Xin, sir!
Yep!
[XIN] You bet we've never
had that kinda power before!
If we can fight like that
with one simple tactic...
Imagine what this unit'd be
if we came together as one!
[CHU SHUI] That's not all
a 1,000-man unit can do!
[gasps]
[XIN]
Chu Shui!
Look around you, now.
[CHU SHUI] The offensive
power of the Fei Xin Force
is spreading to the others,
and the whole Qin army
is starting to rally
incredibly hard!
[BAI GUIXI]
General Lian Po, sir!
What is this?
All right!
Time to go all out!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
Lun Hu, sir, the action's
over there, see?
That's odd.
To think the Wei army
could lose the upper hand
so very easily now.
There clearly must be a real
live wire in Qin's second unit.
Well, let's cut 'im down!
Yes sir!
--[gong ringing]
--[LUN HU'S CAVALRY gasping]
What on Earth is that
horrid deafening sound?
What's going on?
--[gong ringing]
--[CHU SHUI] A gong?
A signal.
Signal?
What, already?
They'll come.
The enemy's second unit.
[BAI GUIXI] General Lian Po,
what's that sound?
[LIAN PO]
If you think Lian Po
would send a second unit
of mere reinforcements,
you're greatly mistaken!
[BAI GUIXI grunts]
[LIAN PO]
Look at that, Bai Guixi!
He's got this early
battle in the bag now.
What's keepin' 'em?
If they're gonna come,
just come, then!
It has stopped!
I think.
[rumbling]
[XIN gasps]
[XIN]
Smoke?
[SOLDIERS gasping, yelping]
[POPS] The battlefield is
enveloped in smoke right now!
They're setting fires?
[LE HUA FORCE SOLDIER 219A]
No, there's no fire,
it's simply smoke covering
the field at the moment!
[POPS]
A smokescreen?
And on such a huge
scale as this?
[CHU SHUI]
Xin! Are you all right?
Chu Shui!
[CHU SHUI]
We are through.
With no visibility,
everyone's stopped dead.
[XIN growls]
And just right when we were
getting on a roll, there!
[CHU SHUI]
It's an enemy strategy.
Ha! You think this smoke
will be able to stop us?
Come on, now!
As if a little break in fighting
will change the tide of battle!
When it clears up, we will--
[LUN HU laughs]
Wow they're quite furious!
However, here's where it
starts getting really scary.
Fire!
Get down!
[FAN YANG]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS yelping]
Absurd!
Are they insane, taking out all
their allies just like that?
[FAN YANG] The Wei soldiers
have all disappeared!
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219I]
We have to back down!
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219J]
No, they're behind us, too!
[YU FENG FORCE SOLDIER 219I]
What?
[WANG BEN] The smoke is
moving with the soldiers.
Does the Wei army
plan on fighting in this?
[SOLDIER 219C groans]
Let's change location!
The enemy is memorizing
where we've been
and attacking those very spots!
So if we take a new
position in all this smoke,
they're bound to lose us?
Right! Fei Xin Force,
let's move!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
[CHU SHUI] We might encounter
the enemy on the way!
Be careful!
[XIN]
Go!
[NARRATOR] At that very moment,
the Yu Feng and all of the other
squads were also
fast on the move.
The Wei archers couldn't
see the Qin squads
in the thick smoke,
and it was impossible to tell
where they were headed
from their footsteps.
However...
[YU FENG FORCE yelling, yelping]
[FAN YANG]
What?
[NARRATOR] The Wei archers
had accurately tracked down
the Qin army somehow
through the zero-visibility
at this point in time,
making things trickier.
Qu Hai!
Darn!
What's going on?
How can all this be?
[LUN HU laughs]
One big ball of confusion!
So there's nothing left for me
to do in this early stage?
After all,
once they get caught up
in his techniques,
there's no escaping them.
[XUAN FENG'S ADJUTANT]
Xuan Feng, sir!
Nothing unusual to
report at the moment!
I know that!
Just save your breath!
All of this is too easy.
Just bring it out,
would you, then?
[XUAN FENG'S ADJUTANT]
Already now, sir?
Stop asking questions
and simply bring it out!
Honestly, every
country's the same.
Nothing but idiots!
Especially those Qin soldiers.
Getting incredibly flustered
over such a simple tactic.
What a bore, huh?
Is there no one out there with
half a brain anymore, then?
[bell ringing]
[QIANG LEI]
I get it.
So that's how it is.
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS groans]
[XIN]
Where do we go now?
[QIANG LEI]
It's the same everywhere.
[XIN]
Qiang Lei!
They're using sound
to figure out our position.
[XIN]
Sound?
[QIANG LEI] There are
troops hidden all around us
sending out
signals with sound.
They move when we move, telling
the archers our exact location.
Say what?
Ya know, I have heard a bell
mixed in with all the noise.
So if we get rid
of those troops,
we get rid of the arrows, huh?
[CHU SHUI] But they'll be
expecting us to do that.
If we kill them,
they'd be replaced.
It would just
never end that way.
Do you understand what I mean?
We have already lost track of
most of our allies currently,
due to the thickness
of this smoke
that they blew onto
the battlefield,
but the Wei troops know
exactly where everyone is.
Friend and foe, see?
They'll be stamping out
the small scattered units,
one by one.
We've got to get out of
this smoke, and then we'll--
[rumbling]
[YUAN] What can that
be signaling, do ya think?
[XIN]
No, wait a sec!
That's no signal!
[gasps] Do you mean--
It can't be!
I'm afraid so.
Oh, no!
[PEI LANG]
Armored Wei chariots!
[yells]
Darnit!
Hey, you just get
outta there, will ya!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[XIN]
War chariots, of all things!
[CHU SHUI]
Protect the commander!
[XIN] Never mind,
just protect the infantry!
[XIN]
War chariots in this smoke?
Now what?
How can we--
[QIANG LEI]
Xin.
[XIN]
Huh?
[QIANG LEI]
There's only one...
Only one way through this.