My Lord Zheng.
No one else will
become a greater king,
having experienced the
hardships that you have.
And so then, I am certain.
[gasps]
You will be a greater king
than anyone else has ever been.
[ZHENG]
Zi Xia!
Darn it! Darn it!
[ZI XIA]
Lord Zheng, your face.
Your demons have left you now!
Your eyes, they're so
beautiful now.
[ZHENG sobs]
Zi Xia!
After Zi Xia breathed her last,
and I'd crossed
the border to Qin
with Lord Changwen
and his troops,
a sharp pain ran
through my left hand.
Pain had returned to me.
And not only pain,
but taste, smell, all senses.
The human body is a
truly mysterious thing.
[XIANG sobs]
[ZHENG] I have never
spoken of Zi Xia before.
I truly thought I would never
speak of her in my life.
So then, why now?
[ZHENG sighs]
Something maybe is just,
changing within me,
once again, I think.
[gasps]
[XIANG] Zi Xia's story
was just so very shocking.
How hard it must have been
on His Highness all this time.
Someone so special
dying before his eyes.
[YANG]
Good morning, Xiang!
[XIANG]
Oh, Yang. Good morning.
Have you just come from
His Highness's chamber, then?
[XIANG]
Mm...
Oh? What's wrong, Xiang?
You seem down.
Huh? No, not at all.
It's just--
[YANG gasps]
Ha, ha, I understand.
Let me guess. His Highness
hates you now?
[gasps] Come on!
What is it really, though?
I am so sorry, Yang.
I don't want to worry you.
Oh...
[XIANG]
But I'm all right now.
After all I do have you,
am I right?
[YANG]
Mh-mm!
[XIANG]
Yang?
[YANG]
Hmm?
[XIANG] I know I can't
say that I love His Highness.
Especially right now.
Eh?
[XIANG]
After hearing all about Zi Xia,
how could I confess my love
for him so incredibly hastily?
Hey, Xiang?
I just want to
help His Highness
in whatever small way
that I possibly can.
That's all, really.
[YANG] She really does
love him badly,
doesn't she, now?
[XIN]
Well, well, well.
Man, will you all
get a load of this!
[NARRATOR]
In the fifth year of
the future Shi Huangdi's reign,
the Kingdom of Qin
dispatched an army
of over 200,000
to conquer the area
around Shanyang
in the Kingdom of Wei.
This key military
and transport region
was to be taken over and
subsequently annexed to Qin.
[QIN SOLDIERS cheer]
[NARRATOR] The commanding
general assigned to this
grand operation was
the famed Bai Lao of Qin,
General Meng Ao.
[laughs] Do not get
too worked up.
That's how you get hurt.
[NARRATOR] General Meng Ao
divided the troops into three,
to be led by himself
and by his two lieutenants.
These three armies
would carry out
a carefully coordinated
invasion thereafter.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Xin and his Fei Xin Force
were at the front
of the main army,
led by General Meng Ao himself.
[XIN chuckles] That's typical
Meng Ao for all you guys!
Now he really understands
the true power
of the great Fei Xin Force!
We had some pretty
crazy campaigns
along the way, though.
I really believe
that all those
piecemeal victories paid off!
[TIAN YONG]
Yeah!
[QIN SOLDIER 210A]
Here comes the cavalry!
Clear the way!
[XIN, SOLDIERS yelp]
Hey, you!
Wang Ben!
[WANG BEN]
Hm.
[XIN grunts]
[FAN YANG cackles]
[XIN gasps]
They certainly are
a lucky bunch
to have made it up
to the main ranks.
Just look at them
looking all tough now,
aren't they, sir?
Why, these poor little peons
will now be bragging
about this feat
for years and years to come!
[FAN YANG laughs]
That old man just really
pushes my buttons so badly.
Commander of the
Fei Xin Force.
I shall give you yet another
piece of advice, so listen.
[XIN]
Hm.
The upcoming battle
is greater than
every single skirmish that you
have fought so far, you see.
Greater even than the battle
you participated with
Zhao two years ago.
A real honest-to-goodness war.
An ant who flexes
his muscles out there
will soon be trampled.
That also goes for
your soldiers as well.
Be very careful.
Got all of that?
[growls]
Heh.
[FEI XIN FORCE growls]
So, shall we then?
[XIN]
Thanks for the tip.
[WANG BEN]
Hm?
Allow me to give
you one piece
of advice in return, Wang Ben.
You should know
the biggest victories
in this war will be won
by the Fei Xin Force!
Then we will be
ranked higher than
every single one of you guys,
and we will definitely work
all of you like ants!
So prepare yourselves!
Know who'll be one of the
world's greatest generals?
Me, that's who!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[gasps]
Yeah, that's correct!
Yeah!
[WEI PING]
You said it!
[XIN]
This battle will propel me
right down that path to general!
Wait for me, Zheng!
Your Highness has
gone in person
to request prompt assistance
with regards to this matter,
so why has the Inner Palace
made no response whatsoever?
[COURTIER 210B] One cannot
know what the Queen Dowager
is thinking or what
her move will be, exactly.
[COURTIER 210C]
It could just be as
Lord Changwen had feared.
She may well be poison.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Hm...
Ah, Si Shi, you were
the one so eager
to change the balance of power
in one swift swoop,
were you not?
Perhaps you have mis--
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Enough!
It is completely
absurd to blame
Si Shi at this late hour.
While we stand idly by,
it is a fact that the gap
in power between us
and Lü Buwei is only increasing.
It is with this
precise knowledge that
His Highness went to see
his mother, the Queen Dowager.
All we can do now
is to wait patiently.
[COURTIERS gasp]
[door creaks]
[MESSENGER 210A] The heads
of the houses of Liao, Fan,
and Jie have arrived now!
They seek an audience
with the king
right away, what shall I do?
[COURTIER 210A]
Huh? Say what?
[COURTIER 210B] The houses
of Liao, Fan, and Jie?
[COURTIER 210C] The heads
of the three royal families
behind the power
of the Inner Palace.
And they've all come seeking a
royal audience, which means...
[COURTIERS gasping, murmuring]
The Inner Palace must have
definitely taken our side!
This really is major!
With the Inner Palace
as our ally,
Lü Buwei really
can't touch us,
even if he wanted to!
In addition to all that,
knowing the Inner Palace
has joined us
might persuade him
to join our camp
as well from now onwards, too.
Rhe power map of
the Imperial Court
could be entirely rewritten!
I will permit an audience!
Show the heads of the
royal families right inside!
[XIANG] Ooh! It sure has
gotten pretty late!
It's so dark and so scary.
[sighs]
Ah! And I have to
go back through that
pitch-black hallway?
No way, no way, no way!
[ZI XIA] The moon
always seems to shine
more beautifully when
you look up at it
right from the depths of sorrow.
Almost as if it's
laughing at you
from up above in the skies.
But then, someone showed me
that wasn't how it was at all.
[ZI XIA] "The moon shines
brighter than usual
just to cheer you up,
and carry you onward."
[QUEEN DOWAGER laughs]
[XIANG]
Is someone there?
[gasps]
[XIANG]
The Queen Dowager!
What's she doing here?
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Right this way.
[XIANG]
She's not alone, it seems!
[XIANG] Minister Lü?
Wh-What can this mean?
Are you sure about this?
Because there's no turning back
afterwards, Minister Lü.
If I'm discovered,
my head will roll.
And having come all the way
into the Inner Palace,
clearly I have no intention
of turning back.
[laughs]
[LÜ BUWEI] Presently,
what I wonder is whether
you are prepared, too, madam.
For all of the power
of the Inner Palace
that you solely control,
for you to now be
aligned with me, Lü Buwei.
It is truly a grotesque
and hostile act
against your own blood
in your son,
the king, wouldn't you say?
[gasps]
[XIANG] D-Did he just say
the power of the Inner Palace
would align with
Minister Lü? Oh no.
[laughs]
[XIANG] But why? Isn't she
on His Highness's side?
The Queen Dowager
is his mother after all!
[QUEEN DOWAGER laughs]
Don't give Zheng
another thought.
As it happens,
I just met with him.
Just as a little test,
mind you, of course.
So I could really see if
a single spark
of maternal feelings
was alight within me
after everything
was said and done, you see.
Oh?
But it was just as I thought.
I felt nothing.
His face and his
words, his eyes.
I felt not a single thing.
With the exception
of complete apathy.
[XIANG]
No. Oh no!
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Whatever happens to Zheng
is no business of mine.
[XIANG]
That's her own flesh and blood
that she's talking about!
I thought it was very strange
when I heard that the heads of
all the three royal families,
usually so averse
to the spotlight,
had gone all this way
to see the king.
So, all of this
commotion was purely
just in order to
try to lure me into
the Inner Palace again
wasn't it then?
[QUEEN DOWAGER laughs]
I have cursed no man
more than I have you.
Hated no man more
than you, as well.
And yet, somehow, no man
excites me more than you,
excite me truly. I'll admit it.
[LÜ BUWEI]
This, too, may change.
[LÜ BUWEI] Seventeen years ago,
when we met in Handan,
the capital of Zhao,
this woman truly
sparkled beyond anyone.
So many people gathered,
even from distant towns just
to catch a glimpse of her
as she danced
truly bewitchingly.
[LÜ BUWEI]
This peerless beauty brimming
with innocence and grace,
was beloved by all,
praised as the Jewel
of all of Handan.
Now she is but a shadow
of her former self.
Was it all my doing, maybe?
[LÜ BUWEI]
Jewel of Handan.
[QUEEN DOWAGER gasps]
Never say that name
to me ever again, okay?
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Seventeen years ago,
I was at the
very height of happiness.
[QUEEN DOWAGER] Because of
a man named Lü Buwei,
with whom I exchanged
heartfelt promises
to love and accompany
for a lifetime,
I never had any doubt
that my future would be
anything but happiness.
I truly believed
this with all my heart.
But one day,
you decided to bring me
to meet a royal
from a foreign land.
And you said to me--
me, your faithfully intended...
[LÜ BUWEI]
"Jewel of Handan.
As of today, this is
the man you shall love."
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Our love, our promise,
our happiness, our future...
[QUEEN DOWAGER] All illusions!
Nothing more, truly.
I knew, even then,
all young and naive,
that you had put
everything you owned
into Zi Chu of Qin.
You and your
money drove Zi Chu
right into Qin's royal throne,
for which you
made him promise you
the coveted position
of becoming minister.
You made me just a mere tool
in your own rise
to power, Lü Buwei!
That's exactly right.
I make no excuse.
[XIANG gasps]
That is a relief.
If you were the kind of man
who'd make excuses now,
I'd just be completely forced
to give you up as well,
and that'd be a problem.
The joke is on the
king's faction solely,
I would have to say, then.
They truly believe
they have brought
the complete power
of the Inner Palace
onto their side now.
--[XIANG gasps, sobs]
--[LÜ BUWEI laughs]
You've the chance.
Why wouldn't you just stamp them
all out instead, my dearest?
So then, you and I can,
those lovers from
seventeen years ago,
can take over
that foreign land of Qin
and get that
happy ending after all.
[LÜ BUWEI chuckles]
[XIANG sobs]
The Queen Dowager
and Minister Lü,
were at one point
really lovers?
I don't quite understand.
But I feel something
quite dreadful
is about to happen.
I've got to tell
His Highness now!
[bushes rustle]
[XIANG gasps]
[foosteps scuff]
[sword clinks, thuds]
[XIANG gasps]
[XIANG] I've got to...
tell His Highness.
[YANG yawns]
My turn for morning
clean-up again, huh?
That's it!
What's this?
[gasps]
[YANG]
Xi--Xiang!
Xiang? Xiang!
[YANG gapss]
Blood.
Stay with me!
You have to, Xiang!
Xiang. Xiang! Xiang? Xiang!
Somebody? Anybody, please!
Xiang!