[NARRATOR] A fierce battle is
nearing its end, finally,
as Meng Ao comes face to face
with Lian Po at long last.
Can the perpetual loser of
the past settle the score
once and for all with his
lifetime foe this time around?
The era was about
Qin's six great generals,
as well as Zhao's Three Greats.
Holding the lives of
millions of soldiers
in the palms of your hands,
and risking both body and soul
as we clashed decisively
with one another during battle!
[LIAN PO]
When I lost those opponents,
I can admit I
lost some passion,
but having survived
that incredible golden age
left me with an adamantine body!
Did you honestly believe
you could blow that away
with your 40 measly
years of emotions?
I must say you have gravely
underestimated me, Meng Ao!
[XIN]
So this... is Lian Po!
The great general who
fought on equal footing
with General Wang Yi and
the rest of his peers.
And like Wang Yi,
he gives off this
crazy sense of intimidation
just standing there.
[XIN]
But unlike Wang Yi,
Lian Po is standing
there as an enemy.
[XIN]
It's hard to breathe,
like someone's squeezing
my heart aggressively.
[XIN]
This pressure is unbelievable!
Ha! So you acknowledge that
your fire is out, do you now?
And somehow you decided to enter
the battlefield regardless,
despite being aware
of this, then?
Well, obviously, I was not
solely going after you.
My targets were Wang Jian
and Huan Yi.
I did get in a
little confrontation
with Wang Jian before.
But I regret to say that it
wasn't especially inspiring.
[MENG AO laughs]
[MENG AO]
You liar!
[LIAN PO growls]
Wang Jian and Huan Yi
are on a par
with the six great generals and
you know that very well.
If you truly felt nothing
as you say, it's only because
that's not what you were really
seeking after all, you see.
[MENG AO] Lian Po, it's clear to
me that you actually returned
because of the utter
indignation that you feel
regarding Wang Yi's death which
took place one year ago now.
[gasping]
[XIN] He returned because of
General Wang Yi's death?
Wang Yi fatally lost
to Pang Nuan
and the virtually
unknown Li Mu then,
and he sadly wound up
completely overwhelmed
by the tidal wave of time.
In fact, the six great generals
and the Three Greats,
well, with you as the
major exception,
are all currently.
[LIAN PO growls]
[MENG AO] But you won't stand
for any of that now,
will you, Lian Po?
There's no use in
fighting it. This--
[LIAN PO] What of the
tidal wave of time, exactly?
The strong are mighty
until the end!
Whether you are old or sick,
once you are on the battlefield
the rule is only to win!
[gasps]
But Wang Yi was
mightily defeated and slain.
Sure, he had been away from
the battlefield for a while,
this incredibly tough man
who had fought me
in one hard-pitched
battle after another.
After his return,
it took just one battle.
[LIAN PO] One battle to
sully the reputations
of six great generals
and Three Greats.
That pathetic fool.
[gasps]
[growls]
[XIN] Cut it out
with that nonsense!
Huh?
[gasps]
[LIAN PO growls]
[XIN growls]
[LIAN PO] A child.
You're out of your league.
If you have something
that you need to say to me,
say it once you have a
name worth giving.
Well, I already have it!
Xin of the Fei Xin Force!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[LIAN PO]
Is that--
The name is Xin,
of the fierce Fei Xin Force,
who killed Lun Hu
by these hands!
[WEI SOLDIERS gasping]
General Lun Hu's
been killed already?
No way, that's absurd!
Agreed, but then...
That sure does look
a lot like Lun Hu's sword.
[QIN SOLDIER A] Xin of the
Fei Xin Force killed Lun Hu?
[QIN SOLDIER B] So the central
army's battle is ours, then?
--[SOLDIERS gasping]
--[LIAN PO growls]
[LIAN PO] Isn't it about time
you got new swords?
[LUN HU] Nah. Sharpen them up
and they'll be good as new.
After all, these beauties were
a gift from you, my lord.
I'll fight with them
until the day I die.
[LIAN PO snarls]
Ahh...
So, you killed Lun Hu, then?
[LE HUA SOLDIER A]
C-Commander!
What are you doing, Xin?!
Get out of there now!
[XIN] I may not be in peak
fighting condition just yet.
[LIAN PO snarls]
Stop, Xin!
[XIN]
But that's no reason to run.
[horse whinnies]
[XIN]
Besides, I'd like to fight him.
To be able to feel the power
of one of the old Three Greats,
equal in might to
Qin's six great generals!
Xin, what are you--?!
[XIN]
I know it's crazy.
[XIN] But it's like I was being
pushed to do this all along,
for my whole life.
[XIN] by General Wang Yi,
and Lun Hu, too!
[LIAN PO yells]
[growls]
[yells]
You imp!
[XIN grunts]
[gasping]
[LIAN PO gasps]
[LIAN PO]
What?!
It-it figures... a great
general... hits real hard...
...just like that,
right there...
[LIAN PO] He managed
to somehow stop my blow?!
[LIAN PO] What's really
going on with that sword?
What's with...
[XIN grunts]
[LIAN PO]
...this strange boy?!
[XIN yells]
[LIAN PO gasps]
[XIN yelps]
[gasping]
[XIN grunts]
[QIN SOLDIER C]
Wh-Whoa!
[XIN grunts]
[XIN yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
What's the matter
with you guards?!
Protect that man, now!
[LIAN PO growls]
[MENG AO]
That is quite enough!
[gasps]
[MENG AO] I'm certain that
you know by now, Lian Po,
but of your Big Four, Xuan Feng
has fallen, followed by Lun Hu.
The young man who killed
Lun Hu is stopping
your blade at this very moment!
This era is clearly moving on
toward the next scene,
as everyone can see.
However!
That takes nothing...
Absolutely nothing away from
that incredible golden age
of the past!
That is why, Lian Po,
you are already--
[WANG YI laughs]
[WANG YI]
Are you not satisfied, yet?
[WANG YI giggles]
You have already got me beat.
All those battles you've fought,
and you are still trying
to light that old fire.
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] Why not
give it a rest, General?
Those old golden days
are now done and over with,
don't you see it?
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling
[WEI SOLDIER E]
Hurry!
The general is already
fighting at the summit!
[MENG AO SOLDIER A]
Run! Forget your posts!
Assist General Meng Ao!
If this were to continue,
the difference in manpower
will only grow.
Do you understand exactly
what I'm saying, Lian Po, sir?
[LIAN PO]
The tidal wave of time.
[XIN grunts]
What is it to do with me?
Xin!
Commander, please stand down!
It's you!
[growls]
This has now ceased
to be a proper duel!
Get in there and take
Meng Ao's head, now!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
Here they come! You must
protect the general, now!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MENG TIAN]
A free-for-all? Perfect.
Qin's got a definite
numbers advantage.
[LIAN PO yells]
[QIN SOLDIERS scream]
[MENG TIAN]
Lian Po.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[growls]
[XIN]
Uh-oh. I can't move!
Xin!
[LIAN PO snarls]
Hold on, Lian Po!
That young man was at
Wang Yi's deathbed
and is the person who
inherited his poleaxe!
[LIAN PO]
What?
Wang Yi's poleaxe? To this boy?
[LIAN PO growls]
[LIAN PO]
No wonder, then.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
There is something
I have always wondered.
So you must answer me
honestly, now, boy.
What was Wang Yi's death
really like, then?
Did he die defeated but
with his stellar reputation
completely intact, still?
Or did he die, with his face
twisted into a grimace
of just absolute regret?
Neither of those two.
He said,
"Time goes on with each
mighty man killed
by the next one in line."
He said, "This is why a world
at war is so interesting,"
and died with a smile.
He looked just like...
...one of the world's
greatest generals
anyone would dream to be,
the personification of
majestic heroism!
Each one of the words you
have just uttered rings true.
[LIAN PO]
I see now.
That's just like you, Wang Yi.
[LIAN PO] Once you told me
that the golden era
was over and done with,
yet embers still smoldered
deep within you as
well, didn't they?
But you have never
have returned to battle
with half-baked intentions.
Without a doubt, you must have
found another battle
worth fighting for
in your eyes.
Even if you strayed
from that crucial path
with your first step.
Yes, I see. And still,
you reconciled it all
so you could then die
smiling in the very end.
[LIAN PO laughs]
[LIAN PO]
Honestly...
The nerve of those fools,
going on ahead of me
just like that.
[MENG AO]
Lian Po.
With the six great
generals all dead,
you have no more foes left,
now have you?
To go on fighting
regardless is sheer futility,
if I may say so myself.
But if you would find
some real significance
in this current battle
we have here,
let it be the great general
Lian Po's final conflict
when he lays down
his weapon at long last.
[laughs]
I can always just remove it
from you instead of arm and all,
don't you worry
about any of that.
So, shall I send you
to be alongside Wang Yi
and the rest right now, then?
As a good old friend,
I fully intend to see this
through to the very end!
[MENG TIAN]
Grandpa...
General Meng Ao.
Huh? What could that sound be?
Why do you hesitate
in the slightest, my dear lord?!
New enemy troops!
[MENG AO SOLDIER D] They're
coming in from the side now!
Impossible, because that's a
sheer cliff face there!
It's General Jie Zifang!
General Jie Zifang
is coming now!
[MENG TIAN]
Jie Zifang?
[MENG AO SOLDIER B]
There aren't many of them!
The big one in the front
is their leader!
Get him!
[MENG AO SOLDIERS yell]
[JIE ZIFANG]
Oh, cut the commotion!
It's over!
You hear me, Qin army?
Who's that guy, anyway?
[MENG TIAN] Jie Zifang's
the leader of the Big Four!
Why'd he show up now?
Hey, look at that, over there!
--[MENG TIAN] What the...
--What is it this time?
[MENG AO SOLDIER E]
Smoke? Is there a fire
happening in their main camp?
But how, in this heavy rain?
That's no... ordinary fire.
[WANG BEN]
That's a smoke signal.
This can't mean--
We've taken the
Wei army's main camp?
[HUAN YI SOLDIER A] The fires
we signal with keep going out!
[HUAN YI SOLDIER B]
Make them bigger!
Throw on more oil!
[growls]
[ZHONG GUI]
Hey, boss!
It appears that the
Wei guys down there
have all surrendered now.
It looks like Lei Tu
really pulled it off!
[HUAN YI]
Hey, nice work then!
Okay...
I'm pleased to say that
now it's your turn,
General Bai Guixi.
Oh, you scoundrel!
How did-- Just tell me, did you
not run from Jie Zifang's men
deep into the mountains?
[HUAN YI] Run?
Us, here? You're funny.
[HUAN YI, SOLDIERS laugh]
[HUAN YI]
No, you see,
we intentionally dragged
Jie Zifang into the mountains.
While he was searching
for the main unit,
I was cleverly moving on my own
with a 4,000-man detached force.
There's no way he
could've found me,
no matter how hard
he looked for me then.
What should I do now?
Normally I'd get this
over with quickly,
but I happen to feel a
little bit sorry for you.
You're commanding
general in name only.
Lian Po's been
pulling all the strings.
Doesn't make sense for
you to take responsibility
when you haven't done anything.
Better start begging.
[BAI GUIXI gasps]
[HUAN YI]
Lay flat on the ground,
beg like a madman
for forgiveness,
and I'll spare your life.
[BAI GUIXI'S SOLDIERS gasp]
[growls]
[BAI GUIXI growls]
Don't make a fool
of me, you whelp!
I am Bai Guixi,
commanding general of 120,000!
I would rather die
a hundred deaths
than bow my head to Qin people!
I'll show you the
pride of a Wei man!
Now come on, kill me!
[BAI GUIXI]
Come on, do it!
What's the matter, Huan Yi?!
[laughs]
What are you, afraid?!
What's his deal, then?
[HUAN YI]
Talk about a wet blanket.
--[BAI GUIXI gasps]
--[HUAN YI] Hey, Zhong Gui,
take him with you.
[BAI GUIXI grunts]
As if I would.
[BAI GUIXI screams]
[HUAN YI UNDERLING laughs]
[gasping]
[BAI GUIXI'S UNDERLING A]
General Bai Guixi!
Oh, whoops!
[laughs]
And after all that
big talk, too.
Just hang in there, all right?
Hey, Bai Guixi, tons of people
have died in this war,
on both sides combined.
And you being a
general and all...
...you ought to share
their pain a little,
don't you think?
Some of my own men are
waiting on the other side.
[HUAN YI] The damned fool.
If he'd begged me for his life,
I would have let him have it.
That's the pride of a
military man.
What rubbish.
[HUAN YI] Zhong Gui,
take his head, right away.
On it.
Well then, that's this
place sorted out.
Now to see how they're
doing over there.
[XIN]
The Wei main camp has fallen!
Huan Yi!
We have done it!
We've won the battle now!
[MENG TIAN] No. I mean,
right now we have,
but what'll they do now,
with their general dead?
Go get him, men!
Take Meng Ao's head so that we
can even the score, immediately!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
I'm borrowing this!
Take General Meng Ao
to a safe place!
If we can just
weather this storm,
victory really will be ours!
[JIE ZIFANG]
That's not happening!
And a horse for me--
My lord! Hurry up!
[MENG AO SOLDIER G]
Darn it, here he comes!
[MENG AO SOLDIER I]
We can't stop Jie Zifang!
[JIE ZIFANG]
What the heck, girlie man?!
[MENG TIAN]
At best, we kill each other.
But there's still one enemy
we really can't handle.
[MENG AO SOLDIER J]
Mobilize!
[MENG AO SOLDIER K] Surround
Lian Po, and kill him at once!
[LIAN PO yells]
[MENG TIAN]
Lian Po!
[JIE ZIFANG]
Move it!
Meng Ao's ghastly head
is all mine, now!
[growls]
Meng Tian!
[MENG TIAN grunts]
[growls]
No, Xin!
Listen up, Jie Zifang!
Yes, my lord!
[LIAN PO]
Stop it! We're leaving!
[gasping]
[XIN grunts]
We lost this time around.