[NARRATOR] 262 BC:
the era of King Zhao of Qin,
the dreaded "God of Battle."
The kingdoms of
Qin and Zhao clashed
in the former Han lands
of Shangdang.
Their deciding battle
was in Changping.
Qin's commanding
general was Bai Ki,
Zhao's was Lian Po.
But both kingdoms were evenly
matched in this great battle,
and it went on for two years
with no end in sight.
[NARRATOR]
Having run out of patience
with this stagnant situation,
the King of Zhao made
a most foolish decision,
replacing commanding
general Lian Po
with the hot-blooded
young general Zhao Kuo.
After two years of deadlock,
the floodgates opened wide.
[ZHAO KUO grunts]
[ZHAO SOLDIERS groan, yell]
[ZHAO KUO]
An ambush!
So they've sniffed out
our suicide force?
[ZHAO KUO grunts]
That's the
Qin army lieutenant!
I am the Zhao army
commanding general, Zhao Kuo!
I have no business
with a mere lieutenant!
[WANG YI] Two years of
intense war are now ruined,
all because of you.
May death give you a
fresh start, you silly man.
[NARRATOR]
In the ninth month of 260 BC,
the opposing army
under the defeated
commanding general Zhao Kuo,
raised the white flag,
with 400,000
troops surrendering.
However, here Bai Ki
issued a fearsome command.
[NARRATOR]
He ordered every last one
of the surrendering Zhao
troops to be buried alive.
[NARRATOR]
All 400,000 of them!
[NARRATOR] How deep the sorrow
and anger of the families
of those 400,000
slain must run!
[NARRATOR] How intense
and deep the curses
the Zhao people wished
upon the Qin people were!
[baby cries]
[NARRATOR] But... some months
after this atrocity,
a child of Qin royalty was born
in the Zhao capital of Handan.
That small infant was me.
My father, his name was
Zi Chu at the time, you see,
he had been handed over to
Zhao as a hostage back then.
And yet,
our King Zhao was still
preparing for battle with Zhao.
[gasps]
Don't be surprised.
That is just
politics for you, Xiang.
[XIANG]
Um. But he survived.
[ZHENG] Yes, but Zhao was
planning to assassinate him.
However, a man
paid off the killer
and freed my father afterwards.
And so, how did Your Highness
return with him then after?
No.
My mother and I
were left behind in Zhao.
[XIANG] Mmm.
Day has broken.
We will stop here now.
[birds chirping]
[ZHENG] Hm. Mmm.
Why is it ever
since seeing my mother,
that this wound's
been throbbing?
[LADY MEI
inhales deeply, exhales]
[grunts lightly]
[LADY MEI] What possible
good could come of you
marching along right
behind me all day, huh?
How thoroughly aggravating!
There you go again with
those creepy eyes of yours!
[LADY MEI grunts]
Ugh!
[gasps]
Darn you little brat!
Uh! Someone's here.
[LADY MEI]
Don't just stand there!
[LADY MEI gasps]
[ZHAO MAN 207A]
Hey, lady.
You're her.
You're that lady aren't you?
[LADY MEI chuckles]
[LADY MEI,
ZHAO MAN 207A laughing]
[ZHAO MAN 207A]
Later. I'll be around, okay?
[LADY MEI gulps, exhales]
Hm?
[LADY MEI] What's with that
greedy look you have, huh?
If you want something to eat,
why don't you bow
your head and ask for it?
[LADY MEI grunts]
Uh!
Take that and be gone, fast!
Honestly, what kind
of son would put
his own mother
in this position?
Who'd ever
take you for royalty?
[LADY MEI]
I am not amused!
[crickets chirping]
[ZHENG sighs]
Hm? What is it, Xiang?
Your Highness seems tired.
Do you think so?
Yes. Usually Your Highness
reads so hungrily
but that's just
not the case tonight.
Am I really that
voracious, you think?
Ah! N-No, Your Highness!
I-I didn't mean it like that.
I know you didn't.
I was just teasing.
[sighs]
[ZHENG] Perhaps, I could
talk about her with you now.
[XIANG gasps]
[ZHENG] About Zi Xia.
[XIANG] Zi Xia?
[ZHENG] You mentioned
a Hika earlier today
but her name is Zi Xia.
[gasps] So what, um,
what kind of person is she?
[ZHENG] She was the head of
Handan's black marketeers
when I became indebted
to her... for saving my life.
[birds chirping]
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[DAO JIAN] What do you mean,
"under consideration"?
[grunts]
Dao Jian, my lord.
Hngh!
What's this "under
consideration" you said?
Aren't you here in Handan
because you've accepted
the task already?
Not quite.
We've come here to decide
whether we should
accept or not.
So why not just tell us
the plan already then?
You black marketeers
shouldn't press your luck.
This plan is quite crucial
to our kingdom--
we won't reveal it so readily.
And if we ever do
decide to tell you, somehow,
we will have to
kill you swiftly after.
Now look who's actually
pressing his luck?
Don't you get it yet?
This is Handan, my old friend!
The second anyone finds out
you're really from Qin,
you'll be torn to pieces
and thrown to the dogs.
We haven't forgotten
about Changping,
you understand me?
[DAO JIAN grunts]
[ZI XIA] Hey now everyone,
enough kidding around
already, Jiang Zhang.
We're all merchants.
Only shop talk
gets us hot under the collar.
Hey! Long time no see!
Lookin' good!
[ZI XIA]
You too, Ya Men!
[YA MEN]
Er. Cut that out now!
I am Zi Xia, the real leader
of this little group.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
[DAN YUAN, DAO JIAN] Hmmm?
[JIANG ZHANG]
This is shop talk,
that's why things
were gettin' heated.
All you've said is you
want to transport a person,
and you expect us
to go along with it?
These men are just
being real cautious
because the stakes
are so high right now.
Let me tell you what
I do know for certain.
Huh?
[ZI XIA]
First of all,
King Zhao
died three days ago.
[JIANG ZHANG, YA MEN gasp]
Are you serious, Zi Xia?
The God of Battle finally di--
Keep it down now!
[DAO JIAN]
Woman, how did you--?
Even among the Royal Court,
only a fraction know
of the King's passing!
Rats know the way of rats,
you see, you men of Qin.
[grunts]
And what, then?
And An Guo the Crown Prince
will now be the king,
then, with the younger son,
Zi Chu becoming the
rightful prince, of course.
Zi Chu? I have heard
that name before.
Wait. Isn't that
the one who was
a hostage here
for a dozen years?
The prince Lü Buwei
put his whole fortune
into carryin' favor with?
But, didn't he
and a Zhao woman there?
Yes, but even as Lü Buwei
helped Zi Chu escape,
he couldn't find a way
to flee with both of them
in tow with him, and so,
they were left alone
here in Zhao.
[YA MEN] Hang on! Transporting
a person, you don't mean--
[ZI XIA] Yes.
Just as that sly fox got
Zi Chu out of here swiftly
seven years back
from today, the plan is to
deliver his son Zheng
back to the Kingdom of Qin.
[JIANG ZHANG grunts]
[YA MEN gasps]
Since you know so much already,
let's just cut to the chase.
You must realize
how serious this all is.
And now,
for you there is simply
no going back from this.
--[ZI XIA] Just a moment.
--[DAO JIAN] Uh?
We'll consider taking this on
once we have met Lord Zheng.
First, you must let me see him.
[DAO JIAN]
What do you hope to gain?
It's only natural for
a merchant to check on
the goods she carries
around, don't you think?
Only then will
a decision be made.
[DAN YUAN, TIAN CI grunt]
Watch your mouth woman!
The nerve of calling
our royalty "goods!"
Just shut up!
Our commander is doin'
the asking right now,
so just do it!
[distant clanging]
[TOWNSMAN 207A]
After him!
[TOWNSMAN 207B]
Don't let him get away!
--[TOWNSMEN yelling]
--[YA MEN] A little bandit, huh?
C'mere everyone!
It's him again!
It's Zheng!
[TOWNSMEN shouting]
[TOWNSMAN 207D]
Stupid brat!
[DAN YUAN, TIAN CI grunt]
--[TOWNSMAN 207E] Kill him!
--[TOWNSMAN 207F] Murder him!
[TOWNSMAN 207G]
Aggravating kid!
[TOWNSMAN 207H]
That brat stealing food again!
[TOWNSMAN 207I]
He's not going anywhere!
[YA MEN]
Zheng, huh?
Not the same Zheng
we were just talking about?
[ZI XIA]
Huh?
[YA MEN] He sure looks like
a poor sneak thief to me!
[TOWNSMAN 207K]
Let me do it.
I lost my dad
and my big brother
in the battle of Changping!
Uh. Oh.
This cannot be good.
[yells]
[ZHENG yells]
Now you have done it!
Yeah, destroy him!
Uh... And they are off!
[ZHENG grunting]
Hey, he isn't
half bad, I'd say!
[groans]
All right! He's all ours!
[TOWNSMAN 207C]
Lemme at him!
[DAO JIAN]
Why you!
Wait! If you go right now,
you'll only
rile them up even more.
But if this keeps up--
[ZI XIA]
It's all right.
They know the boy
is a Qin hostage,
so they won't dare kill him.
They're not insane.
[TOWNSMEN cheering]
Okay, that's enough!
Rough him up but don't kill him
or they'll come for us!
Aw, come on man!
A little more
won't kill the kid!
[TOWNSMAN 207M]
He's out cold. Leave him now!
Well, well, then how
about we break his arm,
him being a thief and all?
[ALL gasp]
[TOWNSMAN 207K]
All right!
Hold him steady,
won't you now?
[ZI XIA]
Stop it!
[TOWNSMAN 207K] Heeeh?
Not even a
Qin person would do
what you're doing to him.
[TOWNSMEN gasp]
[DAO JIAN grunts]
[TOWNSMAN 207N]
Hey! Wait up!
At the very least thank
the lady, you Qin mongrel!
[ZHENG groans]
[TOWNSMEN grumble]
Huh?
[TOWNSMAN 207N]
And don't come back!
Heh. You see what
you get from him, lady?
There's nothing to be gained
from helping a lout like that.
Those eyes of his
aren't even human!
[ZI XIA] Hm.
[indistinctive chatter]
[YA MEN] So, I think
I got him pretty figured out.
He's starving.
I mean really starving.
[YA MEN] Since his father
left seven years ago,
there's been no money from Qin.
And since his mother gave birth
to royalty in an enemy land,
she's being treated
just as badly.
Plus, with so little on the
job front, she wound up as--
--[ZI XIA] Hm.
--[YA MEN] Uuh! Sorry.
So, what do we do now then?
Well, we can't accept now.
It's a matter of time
when the King of Zhao
hears about
the King dying in Qin,
and the very first thing
he will do when
he finds out about
all of this is...
...murder Zheng.
[ZI XIA] Hmmm.
[YA MEN]
Probably.
If someone like him were to
become King of Qin one day,
he will definitely
end up hating Zhao.
And once Zheng's
finally out of the picture,
all of the Zhao gates will be
shut-as tightly as possible.
Which means even we won't
be able to get out of here.
It's a gamble to
try leaving the country
before the news reaches the
ears of the King of Zhao.
If we mess up,
we will be tortured to death
as just a bunch of traitors.
That is a chance
I am not willing to take.
[JIANG ZHANG] All right, then.
Okay with you, Zi Xia?
We can't accept this job.
Sorry for that.
And we will not breathe a word
of this to anyone at all.
Don't worry, we black
marketeers are tight-lipped.
See you.
They're only Zhao
underground merchants.
Shall we slay them?
Well, no. We can't afford
to cause trouble now.
Hey, you!
What happened to your leader,
that Zi Xia woman?
Good point.
She just up and disappeared.
[ZI XIA] Hmmm.
[ZI XIA]
Do you hate the moon?
[ZHENG]
You're her from before?
[ZI XIA] I used to hate
it once, as well. The moon.
The moon always seems
to shine more beautifully
when you look up at it right
from the very depths of sorrow.
Almost as if it's laughing at
you from up above in the skies.
"Don't give me that!"
That's how I used to
gaze at the moon
once upon a time, you see.
But then someone showed me
that wasn't how it was at all.
My adopted father,
a wandering peddler.
We--I mean, me and Ya Men,
and Jiang Zhang too,
the guys from earlier today--
my father saved all us once,
from the brink of starvation.
These are the words
he left me with then:
"The moon shines
brighter than usual
just to cheer you up,
and carry you onward."
[ZHENG gasps]
[ZHENG]
I'm going out, Mother.
[TOWNSMAN 207C]
It's Zheng! There he is again!
--[TOWNSMEN shouting]
--[ZHENG panting]
[ZHENG]
Uh!
Uh. Hello?
I'm back. Mother?
[ZHENG gasps]
[ZHENG]
More men again?
[DAO JIAN]
Wait Zheng, my lord!
We have come here for you!
[ZHENG gasps]
[DAO JIAN] We deeply regret
your long years of suffering!
My lord Zheng!
The time has come for you
to return to Qin again!
You are going
back to Qin now!
[ZHENG]
To... Qin?
[DAO JIAN] King Zhao has
passed away, and your father
has become the crown prince.
That means he will
be the next king,
and after him, the next
king will be you, Zheng!
[ZHENG gasps]
Me, King?
[screaming]
[DAO JIAN]
Lord Zheng?
What is the matter,
[TIAN CI] Oh no!
Quickly take him to the cart!
[YA MEN] Those old fellows
are planning on
doing it all themselves!
[JIANG ZHANG]
It won't work.
Those two can't
even leave Handan.
Hey Zi Xia!
They're heading out!
What's up?
You've been awfully quiet.
[ZI XIA]
Hmmm.
Having second thoughts?
[ZI XIA]
Not at all guys.
Jiang Zhang. Ya Men.
Have you both forgotten
about our adopted father?
the hand that rescued us
from a certain death?
Wait, what is all of this?
Of course we haven't
forgotten, Zi Xia.
[ZI XIA]
Then you'll understand.
Standing before us now
is one young boy.
A boy who will likely
be killed at once
if no one offers him a hand.
[ZI XIA] So then, what second
thoughts could we have?
Our choice is crystal clear.
Wouldn't you say, guys?
[DAN YUAN] Are you sure
we can get him out of here
on our own, Dao Jian sir?
We have no choice!
There's absolutely no time to
revise the plan at this stage!
--[TIAN CI] L-Lord Dao Jian!
--[DAO JIAN] Aah!
[ZI XIA] You'll need
some real preparation
to slip through the gates
this late at night.
Ugh! It's you again!
We accept the job.
By the name of Zi Xia,
the black marketeer,
I'll deliver Lord Zheng
to the Kingdom of Qin.