[NARRATOR]
In the middle of a fierce battle
between Qin and Wei,
they meet again:
Xin and Lun Hu.
Which of them will be
able to overcome his limits
and have his own way
in the end?
[NARRATOR]
Their blistering-hot emotions
truly are making sparks fly!
Now just get down here!
We'll settle this with a duel!
I will take you on
bare-handed!
Sir?
Your banter hasn't
changed a bit, I see!
Ah, but that's a
very good thing.
All right, let's begin!
[MA LING]
Yes sir!
Take your positions!
[QIN SOLDIERS yell]
[QIN SOLDIER I]
Round up the troops!
[QIN SOLDIER J]
On the double!
You're utterly no fun.
[laughs]
Lian Po didn't come
alone after all.
[MENG AO SOLDIER B]
Of course he didn't!
[MENG AO SOLDIER C]
What is really going on here?
[NARRATOR] The greatest duties
of the headquarters,
that is, a commander
and all of his staff,
are producing an overall
picture of the battle at hand
and leading its army to victory.
The plans both sides
had drawn up for this battle,
shared a few points in common.
[NARRATOR] Meng Ao and Lian Po,
though sworn enemies,
were in reality exceedingly
similar in some ways
and close at heart.
[MENG AO]
The overall plan I had devised
for this very battle here...
...utilizes the main central
army as if it were a shield,
In order to bear the brunt
of the harshest attacks
that Lian Po's central
army can give us.
In the meantime,
the two lieutenants
Huan Yi and Wang Jian
will serve as our
main attack team
with their great
offensive power,
moving in from
both flanks at once.
They will crush the
opposing Wei army
and go for their
main camp afterwards.
[LIAN PO] The Wei army's
main attack force
consists of Lun Hu's army
at the very center of it.
However,
we should send our flanks
after the enemy's lieutenants,
destroy them, or at
the very least, hold them back.
Then surround Meng Ao's
main camp completely.
[MENG AO]
In other words...
[LIAN PO] ...our strategy's
built on three fields:
left, right, and center.
[MENG AO]
The same tactics.
[LIAN PO] Anyone could come up
with that much, really.
But here's where it
gets tricky:
[MENG AO]
We respond in different ways.
I've ordered them
to mainly focus on defense.
[LIAN PO]
I came out swinging ruthlessly,
and won without question.
It's a given.
[LIAN PO]
I lost Xuan Feng very early on,
but then Jie Zifang's army
rushed in quickly thereafter.
In the free-for-all
that followed,
Huan Yi's army,
some of Qin's hardest hitters,
went silent.
That's all it took for
us to dominate.
I really believe that what
truly turned the tide
more than anything else,
was the right-flank battle.
My own army mobilized,
and Wang Jian's army
promptly retreated far and deep.
No--They ran away from me.
PO] Meng Ao, are you sure
you haven't made
some gross miscalculation?
Presently, you have
lost half of the brawn
you have been counting on, and
you let me rush your main camp
from behind,
regrettably for you.
I have been working
on this for so long now
that even putting Bai Guixi
in charge was part of my plan.
Now Lun Hu has to
destroy the central army.
I attack from behind,
the main camp gets caught in
the middle, and it's all over.
[laughs]
[MENG AO laughs]
[MENG AO]
Nothing to fret about.
To him, I'm always a loser
no matter what happens.
[MA GONG]
My lord?
Send all the main camp's
troops to the very back.
[MA LING]
A-All of them?
But Sir when the-the enemy
gets past the central army
at the front--
[MENG AO]
I don't care.
[MENG AO] Lian Po, it seems
that I have always lost to you.
So I expected this to happen.
And having expected it,
I can cope with it
incredibly well.
Furthermore...
[MENG AO]
I constructed this fortress
solely for you to
attack it, you see.
Behold:
my Meng Ao-style anti-Lian Po
counterstrike formation!
[LIAN PO growls]
You mean to tell me
he did all of this in secret?
I heard that he is
big on defense,
which would mean fewer chinks.
Huh? Hey, wait
a second! Ha, ha!
Get a load of that fortress!
[WEI SOLDIER D] I know! It's so
inelegant and inefficient!
[LIAN PO]
No...
It's not bad at all.
You did pretty well for someone
that is so mediocre, Meng Ao!
[MENG AO]
Oh, but of course.
I've been planning and plotting
this formation for years,
all to draw your attacks
when the day finally came
for both of us to
engage in battle once again.
[LIAN PO]
Hmm...
This could prove to be
just a little tricky.
There's too many horsemen
that have half dismount.
[WEI SOLDIER E]
Yes sir!
The archers are just fine.
Put the shields in front
to take the arrows.
[WEI SOLDIER F]
Yes sir!
[LIAN PO]
All right, here we go, Meng Ao.
I will take your head by my own
hand, I can promise you that.
[LI CHONG]
The enemy is on the move!
[MA LIANG]
Where's Lian Po striking from?
[GUO JIAO]
My lord!
[MENG AO]
Come on then, Lian Po.
Enter this fortress
and you are the dead man!
Stay aware of
your surroundings!
There are enemy soldiers
wandering the area,
just like us.
[BI'S SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[BI] We brought up
the rear just fine,
but now we're separated
from Wang Jiang's squad,
and lost, to boot.
We picked up other squads along
the way, so we're plenty strong.
Better get back to the
front lines on the double.
Huh...?
[BI'S SOLDIER B]
Bi, sir, is that--
[BI]
General Meng Ao's main camp?
Exactly how lost are we, then?
[shouting]
[BI]
Oh, no! Are they under attack?!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[screams]
[LIAN PO growls]
[gasps]
[MA LING]
Lian Po has mobilized!
Ah... Commander!
Lian Po is coming this way!
[QIN COMMANDER A]
Don't panic!
Ha! That fool!
We've got you now, Lian Po!
Huh?
[QIN COMMANDER A] If you want
to avoid a rain of arrows,
it's standard practice
to attack from the sides.
That's why we've hidden archers
in the woods on either side see?
With arrows from the
front and the sides,
even Lian Po
won't stand a chance!
[laughs]
That's the legendary
general, Lian Po!
His tactics are outdated!
Fire!
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[QIN COMMANDER A]
Are they in their right minds?!
Why would they
fire on their allies?!
[LI CHONG]
My lord, what is this?!
[MENG AO]
The bordering area of the forest
is already in enemy hands.
[LIAN PO growls]
[QIN SOLDIERS screaming]
[LI CHONG]
Lian Po just went right on in.
[MA LING] They're breaching
the front ranks!
[GUO JIAO]
The right edge is done!
[MA LING]
My lord!
Never fear. The true
terror of this fortress
starts right now!
All right, then!
They're thin on the ground here!
[LIAN PO SOLDIER B]
We can do this!
[LIAN PO SOLDIER C]
We'll tear Meng Ao apart!
[LIAN PO SOLDIERS cheer]
What the--
It is a...
[LIAN PO SOLDIER A]
...a dead end?!
[LIAN PO SOLDIER D]
What's going on there?
[LIAN PO SOLDIER E]
What is it?
[LIAN PO SOLDIER B]
No! Stay back! Listen to me!
[MENG AO ARCHER A]
Now! Fire!
[LIAN PO SOLDIERS screaming]
General, it appears
some of our squads are done for.
The broken-path plan:
Clearly cutting off pathways
to corner the enemy effectively.
[LIAN PO] And unlike Wang Jian's
drum-tight fortress from before,
Meng Ao's is, at first glance,
messy and full of holes.
However,
start to climb it and you'll
discover dead-end routes
that are invisible
when viewed from below.
Meng Ao planned it that way:
ideal pits for
trapping his prey.
He sprinkled the entire
fortress with these traps,
laying them out like a maze.
This fortress isn't for defense.
No, it's clearly made
for striking back
at the foes who enter.
Damn you, Meng Ao.
So you're serious about
attacking me, aren't you?
[GUO JIAO]
Amazing!
Here I thought we'd
slowed them down,
but we've killed them!
[MA LING]
Leave it to our lord
to come up with
something like this!
[GUO JIAO] We built it
as we were instructed,
but we had no idea.
[GUO JIAO]
Talk about a surprise!
[MA LING] What's surprising
is how it shut down
Lian Po's sneak attack!
Did you anticipate his
timely arrival then, my lord?
[MENG AO] Lian Po is a general
of many faces, you see.
[MENG AO] Before war he,
is a resourceful general
who comes up with
complex plans.
And when the fighting begins,
he's an intuitive general
with his finger on the
very pulse of war.
Once he decides to defend,
he becomes a protective general,
the steel wall that guarded
Changpei for two years.
And when it's time to attack,
he's a fierce general
who strikes with deadly force,
in regular tactics or in
very clever schemes.
He has even been known
to head up his own vanguard
ruthlessly sometimes.
That's how intrepid he is,
to his very core.
Intrepid, and a show-off
like none other you have seen.
[laughs]
[MENG AO]
So yes, I saw this coming.
[MA LING]
Remarkable, my lord!
I tip my hat to you.
I must say, it really is uncanny
just how well you know Lian Po.
[MENG AO] Indeed, merely losing
to him so many times over
as a young man, I came
to learn Lian Po well.
But that's not all.
It's been about 40 years
since I came to the land of Qin.
In this time, I have not
fought Lian Po, not even once.
Yet I know all the
minutest details
of Lian Po's every
moves in battle.
I spent a great
deal of money
to gather that information
and even secretly went
to watch some battles myself.
[MENG AO]
That is right:
I have always...
[MENG AO]
...kept a close eye on Lian Po
[XIN grunts]
This is the end of the
line for you!
Xin, sir!
[WEI PING growls]
Xin's fighting so
hard over there,
we gotta win this here,
right men?
[yelling]
[LUN HU SOLDIER A] Don't let
the Fei Xin Force beat you!
[LUN HU SOLDIER B]
Show them what we're made of!
[LUN HU SOLDIERS yell]
What are you
looking at, you rat?!
[XIN]
Right, now!
The other squads are
joining up with ours now.
If we grow, we won't get out
of one of those dead ends!
[laughs]
Don't fret,
just leave it to me, now.
[ZHAO MESSENGER A]
A new report!
Yesterday, Lian Po's army
appeared at the right
flank and pushed
Wang Jian's army far back!
[KAINE] The general
himself at the right.
[LI MU] This doesn't
look good for Meng Ao.
Lian Po must be creeping up
behind him right about now.
Meng Ao will have to go
without his revenge, then.
[gasps]
[LI MU]
What do you mean?
Huh? Oh! I, um...
It's just that Meng Ao kept
losing to General Lian Po
when he was
in the land of Qi.
It is unclear whether Lian Po
remembers this, but for Meng Ao
this battle is the first
revenge match they have engaged
in decades, my lord.
Ah. I am originally from
Qi myself, as you can see.
I found it rather moving, and--
And again, had I
not mentioned it?
Um, Li Mu, sir?
If only you'd said
something sooner.
[ZHAO TACTICIAN A]
Huh?
[KAINE]
Li Mu, sir?
[LI MU]
I'm almost 100% certain
it's not the case for
General Lian Po,
but when a mighty
commander gets tripped up,
there's always a moment
of inattention or two.
Whenever I go into war,
I do my utmost to
throw my foe off his guard.
[LI MU] If general Lian Po
remembers Meng Ao,
that itself is to
Meng Ao's benefit.
That's because the winner
tends to view his opponent as
being of a certain caliber.
What is the matter, sir?
[LI MU]
No. That's right.
There's a lot more.
If Meng Ao does in fact
harbor something
incredibly sinister deep
within him for Lian Po.
then he'd have had a complete
40 years to perfect a strategy
against the biggest rival
that he has ever had.
It's become clear to me
at long last:
If Meng Ao is
even a bit better
than Lian Po's
idea of Meng Ao...
[LIAN PO]
This way!
[MA LING]
Damn it!
We can't manage to
snare Lian Po's squad!
[ZHU KE]
He's very lucky!
[LIAN PO]
Over here!
[MENG AO ADVISOR A]
He's going down?
[gasps]
Another trap he's dodged!
It... can't be.
[ZHU KE] Does Lian Po
know where the traps are?
[LIAN PO growls]
[LI CHONG]
Impossible!
You cannot see their
layout from down below!
He couldn't have known!
[MENG AO]
Even if he cannot see them,
he can guess
where they might be.
One can still see the
entire fortress
from below before entering.
Given where the fences are
and the layout of the mountain,
it wouldn't be impossible
to pinpoint likely spots.
[ZHU KE] So, he looked at
the fortress first
and knew there were traps?
[MA LING] Um, but even if-even
if he could work out
where they were,
he'd lose the big picture
as soon as he went in.
Memorizing the correct path
through such an intricate maze
so incredibly quickly?
It can't be done!
[MENG AO]
And yet, my esteemed ones,
Lian Po has done it.
He's dodged another one!
They're already halfway up!
[LIAN PO'S ADVISOR A]
All right! Raise the flag!
The general's got us
on the right path now!
[WEI SOLDIERS]
Yes sir!
Whoa! Look! Over there!
[MENG AO]
So, he's come at last.
Lian Po, I know you
incredibly well.
The talent that allows you to
etch this maze's path
into your brain and
follow it to the letter...
[MENG AO]
...comes as no surprise.
And so then, I shall use
your own sheer cleverness
against you here.
Move them, right now!
What-What's that?
There's a new path now
leading straight to a trap!
[MA LING]
There he goes!
Got him!
We've got him!
My lord!
Meng Ao, sir!
[MENG AO] Lian Po,
this fortress's greatest weapon,
the product of 40 years of
careful planning
and dedicated polish.
The maze you figured out
in advance?
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[MENG AO] It can easily be
reconfigured after the fact.
[LIAN PO SOLDIERS]
A dead end? Dead end?
[LIAN PO]
Oh no.
Fire!
[XIN]
Behind me,
I know something's
going on at the main camp.
But I can't be thinking
about that right now.
Right now...
[XIN] ...if I take
my eyes off this guy...
...I'm a goner!
[YUAN]
Xin.
Fight alongside the
five-man squad over there!
Don't give them an inch!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS yell]
Cavalry fights cavalry!
Infantry, back down!
Men, listen up!
Put all you've got
into this one fight!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS yell]
[CHU SHUI]
Xin...
I'll handle the squad.
And in return for this...
[CHU SHUI] ...you've got
to take Lun Hu's head!
[XIN]
Sorry, Yuan, Chu Shui.
[LUN HU] He's done a fine job
stopping my advance.
Partly thanks to that
wheel thinning the ranks.
These intervening Fei Xin
troops are powerful too.
Both the cavalry
and the infantry.
And then, there's the
other squads
who also answered the
call to join the fray, as well.
In short, the source of the
Qin's army morale around here
is the leader of the
Fei Xin Force, Xin.
This young man here.
He's practically playing
general already, isn't he?
[LUN HU]
His military might aside,
I didn't have his magnetism,
his charisma at that age.
[LUN HU]
This young man really is...
[LUN HU] Do you
understand the significance
of this undertaking,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
If you fall, the Qin army
here will be destroyed,
and we will rush off to
kill Meng Ao promptly.
Keep babbling!
If I take you down right now,
we win the whole central battle!
[XIN]
My path! It's cleared!
[yells]
[horse whinnies,
XIN yells]
A sword-strike to the
thigh while on horseback?
That's lethal.
[XIN]
No!
[XIN screams]