[NARRATOR]
A ceremony was underway
in Xianyang to appoint
the ministers
who would hold sway
over Qin's future.
Lü Buwei had seized
the highest post
of Chancellor of State
in his recent coup d'état,
but in order to firm
up that standing,
he would need on his side
both the Minister of the
Left and of the Right
cabinet positions
directly concerned
with deciding affairs of state.
However...
Pardon me, Cai Ze,
who are those
old men over there?
[CAI ZE]
Retainers of the king's
younger half-brother?
For the likes of them to be
out in public like this--
Well, so now to announce
all of the appointments.
First of all,
we appoint Lord Changping
to Minister of the
Right, immediately!
[CIVIL SERVANTS gasp]
[CAI ZE gasps]
Next, the Minister of the Left!
[LI SI grunts]
[OLD MAN ON PLATFORM]
Lord Changwen is hereby
appointed to
Minister of the Left!
[CIVIL SERVANTS]
Ooh!
My lord!
Heh.
[growls]
[CAI ZE]
Be patient Li Si.
Your time will certainly
come soon enough.
I am well aware of that.
[LORD CHANGPING] I saw most
of this coming and yet,
I did not know the king's
half-brother had
such unabashed power.
[CHENG JIAO]
Absolutely all of us released
that night were royalty,
and all of us are truly powerful
with secret connections.
It is incredibly
clear to me that
you should have
released us earlier,
Ying Zheng.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Was this a good idea?
I wholeheartedly believe
that involving Cheng Jiao
made our faction
a real match for Lü Buwei's,
but from another perspective,
Cheng Jiao has become
more powerful.
It's like fighting poison
with poison, and
it is poison, after all.
[LÜ BUWEI laughs]
Very well done, Your Highness.
However, joining ranks
with your former enemy;
I think his victims
must be turning in
their graves right now.
It is a greater pity for
one's path to crumble.
[LÜ BUWEI]
"Path"?
Ah, but if I have
drank the poison
of the Inner Palace,
and you have drank the poison
that is your half-brother,
I suppose it all comes
down to which poison
is the stronger of
the two, as you can see!
It's how this should be weighed.
[ZHENG]
Incorrect.
Hm?
The strength of the
poison isn't the key.
I believe this all
comes down to
who is stronger, you or I.
[gasps]
It is I who is, of course.
[LÜ BUWEI]
Young sire,
how great you have
become as of late.
[NARRATOR]
Some days later,
the Fei Xin Force had
finally made its way
to Qin's eastern
outpost of Dongjin.
Other squadrons,
including the Yu Feng
and Le Hua Forces,
had already gathered at Dongjin
to regroup along the Qin border.
We are here at long last.
Later than I expected.
We had our reasons
to be quite late.
That's right.
[NARRATOR]
Here, the Fei Xin Force
would replace all of the members
it had lost during the battle
while guarding the border.
I am Xin, the commander
of the Fei Xin Force!
I'm gonna make this speech
really short and sweet,
so greenhorns and
old hands, listen up!
The Fei Xin Force has only
one thing to do now,
which is to crush
the enemy before us,
and that's it!
We just finished a big war,
so it feels like stuff's
calming down,
but there're still strong
forces out there.
The Fei Xin Force will
keep on crushing them
till the whole Middle Kingdom
knows our names by memory!
And don't you ever forget it!
Got that?
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[YUAN]
This is different.
Not like when he was an
ad-hoc 1,000-man commander,
his speech now has
a different resolve!
Yeah!
What's wrong, Wei Ping?
[WEI PING sniffs]
It's just that, um,
seeing Xin up there like that
a few short years
after our battle
with Wei under General Biao,
and he's now a
1,000-man commander!
And a real good one at that!
If you guys saw him grow up
back in Cheng Hu Village,
you would cry, too!
I guess he really
left you in the dust,
huh, Wei Ping?
Mao! Why, you little...!
Stop talking!
[MAO]
Sorry! Sorry!
[WEI PING]
Mao!
Our ranks have
thinned considerably
since then, too.
Xie Ci, Shan He, Fa Jian,
YRu Yi, Wen Xue, Bang,
and then, Wei Dao.
Yes, that's right.
I really do wish they could
all see the Fei Xin Force
as it stands today.
All of us right here
are the ones who made it.
And not to get
overly sentimental,
but I don't wanna
lose anyone else.
[QU HAI]
Ze Gui, you know that
is a real tall order.
[ZE GUI]
Yes, I know that. It is a war.
In wartimes, some people just
stay behind,
and some stay alive.
You mean Lieutenant
Qiang Lei, then?
I think she said she was
heading for Zhao right now.
[KID 239A]
Wow, Xin!
[QIANG LEI]
Huh?
[KIDS laughing]
[KID 239B]
That's one huge water bug, Xin!
That's right!
We'll make medicine out of it!
Mom will be so thrilled!
Wait Xin, lemme
touch it, first!
No way! Catch your own bugs!
You meanie! Xin won't share!
What'd you say, you jerk?
[XIN]
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
[KID 239A]
It's the waterbug!
Ow! It hurts!
Someone grab it quickly, go!
[QIANG LEI]
Friends, huh?
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[QIANG LEI]
I know, Lu Sui.
Right now,
I must find Xiang's adversary,
YMu Lian.
[MENG TIAN]
Hey, Xin.
Hey there, Meng Tian.
So you made it, then.
I heard your speech.
Not very commander-y,
but I must say
it was incredibly you, Xin.
Come on, quit teasin' me.
Come with me
for a moment, Xin
What now?
I'm kinda busy here, you know.
[MENG TIAN]
It won't take long.
[XIN]
Ugh, fine.
[NARRATOR]
Back in Xianyang, something
even more joyful for Xin and
his friends came to light.
[gasps] Why didn't you tell me?
I had no idea, Xiang!
[XIANG]
Well, I just--
[YANG]
So?
Did you tell
His Highness immediately?
Uh-huh.
[YANG]
And?
[ZHENG]
Hm?
[XIANG]
Mm...
[ZHENG]
Xiang?
Ah! Um, yes?
What is it?
Is there something you
want to say to me, now?
[XIANG]
As you wish, Your Highness.
[ZHENG]
Go ahead.
[XIANG]
All right, so here goes:
The truth is, I--
--I can't hear you.
--[XIANG gasps]
Speak up, would you please?
Well, I am carrying your child!
[ZHENG gasps]
[XIANG gasps] Please do
forgive me, Your Highness.
I-I don't know what I should do.
[XIANG sobs]
[ZHENG]
So that's what it was, Xiang.
[gasps]
I see.
We have something to protect.
[gasps]
Oh, Your Highness!
[YANG sobs]
O-Oh, thank goodness.
I'm happy for you, Xiang!
I really am! I am!
Oh my, Yang!
[XIANG]
Thank you! Yang!
[YANG]
Oh, Xiang!
[sobs] Congratulations, sire!
My heartfelt
congratulations to you!
Yes, well, thank you so much.
You have my congratulations,
Your Highness.
The kingdom of Qin can now
build upon a firm
foundation of prosperity
from this great news, now.
As Chancellor of State,
I can think of
nothing so felicitous.
In fact, you know what?
This calls for a kingdom-wide
celebratory banquet
in three days' time!
What do you think, huh?
Minister of the Right and Left?
It is a fine idea.
I've no objections to that.
[LÜ BUWEI]
Your Highness, I have obtained
consent from them both.
I appreciate your
thoughtfulness, Chancellor.
Your Highness.
My lord.
The wind is blowing
our way, at last.
That's right.
The Royal Court's power
has just managed
to truly hold its ground.
Lü Buwei won't be able
to make any obvious
moves for now.
Which is why
this is exactly when
we get to revel
in our happiness!
Yes, sir!
[LÜ BUWEI] I have said my
expected congratulations,
but your future won't be
as firm as all that, I'm afraid,
Your Highness.
[ZHENG]
Lü Buwei.
You are just like an
insect infesting our land.
My goal is a unified
Middle Kingdom.
Therefore, I shall relentlessly
eliminate anyone
who blocks my path.
Prepare yourself, Lü Buwei!
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
What?
Zheng's baby?
Ha! Isn't that quite amusing!
[ZHAO GAO]
Madam?
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Well, isn't it humorous?
And him barely knowing his
own father's face, at that!
Heh.
If you could even
call that a dad.
[QUEEN DOWAGER laughing]
[MENG TIAN]
Oh, Xin, did you hear?
[XIN]
Huh?
[MENG TIAN] My teacher's
Minister of the Right,
and Lord Changwen is now
Minister of the Left.
Li Si was rumored
for the Minister
of the Left position,
but it seems that
Lord Changwen's faction
pushed him through.
[XIN] So the old man made
it Minister of the Left?
Um.
Did you just call the
Minister of the Left
an "old man"?
Well, I guess.
Zheng is getting
ready to wage a war
on Lü Buwei!
And the king and Chancellor.
Man we gotta tell Diao,
she's gonna flip
when she hears this!
I can't wait to tell her!
[laughs]
Ugh.
Well then, man.
Is that all you
wanted to say to me?
[MENG TIAN]
Hardly.
We'll get to the point
on the east wall.
[XIN]
Ugh.
Uh--!
Wang Ben!
What are you doing here?
I asked him to come.
[WANG BEN]
That's right.
[MENG TIAN]
So, you were saying
that on your way here
you ran into Li Mu?
Yeah.
Please, tell us about it.
Well, it was about
five days before
we arrived right here.
We were in an
area where the Wei,
Zhao, Han, and Chu borders
are tangled together.
We got word of
an enemy sighting,
so we were hiding up on
a cliff, spying on them.
[XIN]
The carriage stopped!
[XIN] Well, even if I
did get a look at him,
I wouldn't know where
this guy is fro--
[gasps]
[XIN]
Li Mu?
And Kaine!
Commander, they'll see you!
[XIN]
My curiosity got the best of me,
so Diao and I
decided to follow him.
[DIAO, XIN gasp]
[XIN]
A tent?
Out here in the forest?
[XIN grunts]
[leaves rustle]
[KAINE]
Scoundrel!
[gasps]
[gasps] I-It's you!
Hey there.
[KAINE]
Why are the two of you here?
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
[LI MU]
Ya know, you really are
a thick thorn right in my side,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force.
And you,
He Liao Diao.
Long time no see, huh, Li Mu?
Yeah, you're right.
I didn't recognize you.
[XIN]
Holed up here, all sneaky.
You cooking up
another plot, Li Mu?
'Cause it looks like
there's someone
in that tent of yours.
So, who is it?
That is absolutely
none of your concern.
[XIN grunts]
[ZHAO SPEARMAN 239A]
March now!
What?
Be quiet and just walk!
That hurts, you jerk!
What gives?
Quit poking me, that hurts!
Hey, Li Mu! Are you
gonna kill him?
Well, now. Do you think I will?
[XIN] Are you so sure you wanna
send your bodyguards away?
[LI MU] Truly, an alliance
is a handy thing to have.
[XIN]
Huh?
Here I am, someone you would
normally be killing quickly,
and thanks to the
Qin-Zhao alliance,
you can't lay a finger
on me, can you?
However, an alliance
isn't really
about not attacking one another.
You know what I mean, Xin?
[gasps]
[LI MU]
What's more important
is what you'll do,
and what you stand to gain
when it's all over.
[XIN]
Then I guess we're the ones
who came out ahead.
Qin got Shanyang,
which is an insanely
massive military base,
but Zhao did not get
much territory at all
in their fight against Yan.
[LI MU]
As long as you think land's
the only thing you
can win in battle,
you will never be
able to defeat me.
What?
What's that supposed to mean?
Li Mu!
You are plotting
something, aren't you?
[LI MU] As if I'd ever
give a straight answer
to a question posed like that.
Still, would ya like to know?
Quit toying with me!
[LI MU]
Very well.
Shall we duel for an answer?
[grunts]
If you were to win the duel,
I will gladly reveal my
dastardly scheme to you.
What did you say?
[DIAO]
Are you sure, Kaine?
Should we be here?
[KAINE]
Sure.
I'm curious to know
what's going on.
[DIAO] Do you think
Li Mu's really going to--
No way.
Li Mu is the chancellor
of Zhao, after all.
He would do nothing
of the sort.
I'm more worried about Dingbat.
It's Xin.
If he so much as
touches Li Mu, I will--
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Li Mu, I really don't know why
you are going through
all this nonsense now.
However, if we're gonna fight,
I'm gonna fight to kill,
just so you know!
If you do manage
to kill me somehow,
you can definitely quash my
plot right there and then.
[gasps]
[KAINE]
Li Mu, sir!
[XIN, LI MU]
Hm?
We've got company.
Is that a problem for you?
[XIN grunts]
[XIN]
Not at all!
Li Mu, sir!
Wait, Xin! He's not serious?
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[XIN]
Why, you...!
[XIN grunts]
He just knocked Xin back!
Li Mu the tactician?
You fools!
[DIAO]
Huh?
Your stupid mistake
was to merely
assume that Li Mu is
simply a tactician!
Li Mu was once...
[gasps]
[DIAO]
Those muscles!
No, all those old scars!
Ha, ha! I figured
as much, really.
The very first time I saw you
in Xianyang, I had a feeling,
here was a fighter
who'd definitely
seen plenty of action!
And I mean that no way
could some gangly
planner take out the likes
of the great General Wang Yi.
And well, as it turns out,
you're a beast with both brains
and bravery at your command!
[LI MU] Is that why
you agreed to duel me,
to find that out?
'Course it is!
You think I'd actually
kill you here?
Because you are much like a wall
I've got to overcome,
do you understand?
[LI MU] You're definitely
coming along, I see.
Your killing of Lun Hu was
most definitely
not just for show.
[XIN]
As if.
What happened afterwards?
[XIN]
As much as I hate to say it,
he let me and Diao go
in front of the
entire Li Mu army.
[MENG TIAN]
I see.
I do wonder what Li Mu is up to.
What'd you think, Wang Ben?
A secret meeting
for a new alliance.
Yeah, probably so.
[XIN]
That's what Diao said, too.
[DIAO]
Li Mu.
If the chancellor
of Zhao himself
is indeed secretly
meeting someone out here,
you'd think the other party
would have to be
a chancellor too.
Besides,
it would be worst
for Qin if it were
the Chu chancellor,
the two of you discussing
a Chu-Zhao alliance
all alone, right here.
Assuming the worst is
just what a tactician
should do, He Liao Diao.
I can definitely tell
you're the brains
behind the Fei Xin Force.
So, it is an alliance!
As I told Xin before:
what really matters
is not the alliance itself,
but its goals and the outcome.
Then that very outcome
perfectly leads into the
next goal, you know.
Uh, what do you mean--
[LI MU]
I can give you this warning
here and now, however.
You may be racking
up combat experience,
but the real truth is...
You do not understand
the true terror of war.
[BOTH gasp]
[XIN]
Who do you think I am?
This gonna be fun, Li Mu.
No matter what schemes
you put together against Qin,
you can bet I'll face them,
and send them flying!
I wish you luck.
[WANG BEN]
A Chu-Zhao alliance.
The sound of it
gives me chills.
If it did actually transpire,
then what could Qin do about it?
Like join up with Wei?
It's not a Chu-Zhao pact!
[MENG TIAN, WANG BEN]
Hm?
Something was really
off about Li Mu.
He must be pulling off something
even bigger than
what he admitted
to me back there!
With Wang Yi dead and
General Meng Ao retired
after being injured
in that last war,
there's no denying Qin's
lack of military strength.
If another war were
to break out now.
A storm is heading to
the Middle Kingdom.
[XIN] Yeah, with that
guy in the middle
of it all, I'm sure of it!
That Li Mu.
[XIN]
But it's not all bad.
We'll be going around giving
all the other kingdoms what for.
A big war is what
we've been waiting for!
We'll never get
anywhere dawdling!
I'm gonna overwrite
those legends
with my own hands now!
[WANG BEN]
Hm...
Unified Middle Kingdom.
That's what Lian Po
said before, right?
Unify the Middle Kingdom?
There's a legendary
feat for you.
Zheng-- I mean,
our king once told me before.
What exactly unifying the
Middle Kingdom meant to him.
Putting an end to
500 years of fighting.
So no matter what
storm's heading my way,
I'm just gonna fight through it!
You'll see.
That will be
my path to being the
world's greatest general!
[XIN]
Isn't that right...
...Zheng?
[XIN]
Fei Xin Force!
Let's do this!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[yells] Out of my way!
[XIN] Here comes Xin
of the Fei Xin Force!