[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set on
a major victory.
[WANG JIAN]
Very well.
I shall hand over
my troops to you.
[BI gasps]
[WANG JIAN]
Round up the squads nearby
and you should
have your 5,000.
You now have commanding
authority over them.
[WANG JIAN]
Bi!
Henceforth, you're a
5,000-man commander.
So now, go stop Qiang Yan
of the Wei army!
[BI]
Me? A 5,000-man commander?
We can do this. We can win!
You don't scare me, Qiang Yan!
{SOLDIERS yelling, grunting]
[yelling]
[BI]
The straits.
It's an area of low ground that
is surrounded by sheer cliffs.
A fairly gentle slope enters
the straits at one end of it,
while a narrow,
cliff-bound path exits
at the other end of the strait.
[WEI SOLDIERS screaming]
[BI] If an attacker can
get on top of those cliffs,
they can rain down arrows
from that high ground,
destroying the enemy's power.
Then, at the right moment,
race down the cliffs
to finish the job.
Keep going, or you'll just
be eating enemy arrows!
Hurry! Keep going!
It's no use! Our path's blocked,
we can't move!
[BI] With their
clifftop escape route blocked,
the soldiers under attack
will rush their only exit,
the narrow path out,
The bottleneck will
hinder their movements.
[QIN SOLDIERS yelling]
[WEI SOLDIER C]
No good!
They're blocking
the rear route, too!
[BI] Once the enemy is
focused on the way out,
it's easy to
surround them from behind.
[BI] In other words, if you can
lure the enemy into the straits
and maintain control
of the cliffs,
you can fairly easily take
down twice as many men!
[QIN SOLDIERS yelling]
[BI'S UNDERLING A]
Bi, sir!
It appears that our army has
completely overwhelmed
the enemy now!
They can no longer
run or fight back!
They are incapacitated!
[BI]
All right.
Excellent!
We've got 'em!
With 5,000 men
currently in my command,
I'll take down one of Lian Po's
Big Four: General Qiang Yan,
and his 10,000 troops, as well!
We will now finish this
battle immediately,
giving the foe no chance!
Troops, you must
descend the cliffs
and strike their general
Qiang Yan, right away!
Was that really such a
good idea, Wang Jian, sir?
Giving Bi 5,000 more men
on top of the thousand
in his command?
[WANG JIAN]
My judgment is impeccable.
[WANG JIAN] He will prove
an excellent decoy.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Qiang Yan! The enemy is pouring
down from the cliffs now!
It seems their entire army
is after our main camp!
Keep the defense
formation intact.
Once we've pulled
them in, we attack.
[QIANG YAN'S UNDERLINGS]
Sir!
[QIANG YAN'S UNDERLING B]
Qiang Yan, sir!
Enemy troops have broken through
our defenses and are closing in!
It seems we will have no choice
but to fight our way out.
Unless we hold our ground and
beat them at their own game.
What shall we do, my lord?
Pardon me, sir?
[QIANG YAN'S UNDERLING C]
Qiang Yan, Sir!
Just stay strong! Go onward!
Go in there and take
Qiang Yan's head right now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[BI'S UNDERLING B]
General Bi!
We've just received word
from the unit
stationed in the
northeast woods!
This is the only battle that
concerns us at this very moment!
But, sir!
Those same troops who had
been fighting hard
right until yesterday have now
suddenly disappeared, you see!
[BI] The enemy's unit...
has just disappeared?!
[BI gasps]
[BI]
Oh no! It couldn't be...
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
What? What's this?!
[BI'S UNDERLING A] The enemy!
Wei soldiers on
top of the cliff!
That's just absurd!
Where'd they come from?!
[BI] He has signaled with his
arrows to stay coordinated
with all of the armies
fighting elsewhere!
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling]
[BI gasps]
No! Get everyone back up
on the cliff, right away!
They'll use the straits
against us! Right now!
[BI'S UNDERLING A] We can't,
sir! It's too late for that!
[BI'S UNDERLING C] The enemy has
gained control of the clifftops!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[BI'S UNDERLING D]
Commander Bi!
[BI'S UNDERLING C]
What is it now?!
[BI'S UNDERLING D]
Enemies from behind!
[BI'S UNDERLING C]
What?!
Oh no! Protect Commander Bi!
[BI'S UNDERLING C]
Run now!
[BI'S UNDERLING B]
But to where, exactly?!
[screaming]
Just keep running!
Gather allies and regroup,
then find a way, any way,
out of this place right now!
You must be the commander
in charge here. Am I correct?
[gasps]
[BI] So this is one
of Lian Po's Big Four:
Qiang Yan!
[BI]
I just-- I can't move!
[WEI SOLDIERS screaming]
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[BI]
General Wang Jian!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[yelling continues]
So you're Qiang Yan, aren't you?
[WANG JIAN]
The clifftops belong to us, now.
[BI] We have the advantage
of the straits once again!
[WANG JIAN]
You lose this time, Qiang Yan.
Impossible!
How could we have overlooked
their incoming reinforcements?
[WEI SOLDIER D]
We're done for!
[WEI SOLDIER E]
We'll be slaughtered!
[BI'S UNDERLING C]
Bi, sir, does this mean...
...that we have won just now?
We're all saved?
[BI'S UNDERLING A yells]
[BI] Yes, it's true,
victory is definitely ours now.
And yet...
...where on earth did those
clifftop reinforcements
come from, exactly?
An army of 5 or 6,000
cannot just show up
so easily like that.
Clearly, they were ready
and waiting for the right time.
[BI] General Wang Jian.
He must have known all along
that we couldn't
possibly defeat Qiang Yan
without all this
additional help!
The losing commander
must now die.
Such is the iron law
of the battlefield, Qiang Yan.
Qiang Yan, sir! We will be
able to hold them off!
You must escape as we do so!
But... I am a merciful man.
I shall offer to you
a single path to survival.
[WANG JIAN]
From now on,
you shall serve only me.
And praise me as your only lord,
pledge me all your fealty,
and I shall spare your life
and those of all your
men present here.
Pardon me?
[BI] What? He's
recommending surrender?!
[WANG JIAN]
You shall not be servants.
I promise each of you land,
as well as sufficient pay
for your livelihoods.
And you, Qiang Yan.
You shall be my very own
personal advisor.
So he's recruiting us now?
How can a commander possibly
give us all land and pay?
Does he think we'll be
fooled by such nonsense?
The war's not even
over just yet!
He must think we're stupid!
I speak in all seriousness.
At this moment, my land
has a desperate need
of a war-strong man
such as yourself.
[QIANG YAN
"My land"?
[BI] What is General Wang Jian
going on about right now?
[WANG JIAN] You will not
regret it, Qiang Yan.
[WANG JIAN] However...
If you refuse,
these straits will be made into
a sea of blood immediately.
[growling, gasping]
Wow, his arrows are
able to pierce a shield
of specially forged
steel, somehow!
Amazing.
If he's turned his bow
upon Wang Jian--
Shall we then tear him apart
right now, sir?
[WANG JIAN]
No. Take him alive.
[growling]
[QIANG YAN] Wang Jian, there's
something I must ask you first.
Not a step closer, Qiang Yan!
Throw down your bow!
When we gained the upper hand in
the early stages of the battle--
was that really your plan?
That's correct.
What does he mean,
Qiang Yan, sir?
You see, there's a reason
we didn't notice the Qin army
atop those cliffs before.
I get it now.
They didn't come
from elsewhere.
They were hidden here,
waiting before the battle began.
Before the battle even began?
You mean he knew
we would be fighting here?
It was all planned?
[BI]
General Wang Jian.
[By the time he
gave me 5,000 men
and told me to go
after Qiang Yan,
he had already hidden his
troops here long before.
So, I... was nothing
but a decoy!
Still...
So then, he couldn't put
together such an army
without our noticing.
Hidden or otherwise!
It's a trick!
We scattered exactly like the
Qin army scattered as well,
and we were keeping track
of their every movement.
We would have surely noticed a
5,000-man army disappear!
No. We did not note
their every movement.
Because one army
successfully evaded our grasp.
That was his main army.
Wang Jian's main army
began their retreat so quickly
that we knew very few details of
their scale or equipment,
if any.
That is true.
We closely followed the movement
of the retreating army
but not numbers.
Before we realized it, he must
have split up the main army.
[BI] Which means... the troops
who appeared on the cliff
were a part of
General Wang Jian's main army.
[QIANG YAN] Wang Jian knew this
land was special terrain
due to the straits.
Thus, he knew we'd
be fighting here.
Well, more accurately,
he knew he could use a decoy
to compel us subconsciously
to select this very place
for our upcoming battle.
Consequently, in order to attack
once we'd chose
the battleground,
he would've had to hide
his troops right here
ahead of time you see.
and to put those
troops together,
he had to pull out his main army
as soon as possible.
Additionally, to make that
retreat look quite natural,
Wang Jian's troops
let themselves
be pushed further back,
and purposely,
they struggled
in the early stages.
No way!
That's when this began?
[BI] What on earth
is this battle anyway?
Just how far ahead
was this all planned?
It is hard to believe.
To have foreseen this
with the faintest of clues,
his opponent's very
state of mind,
a shift in the tide of war.
He has surpassed the
bounds of humanity.
[QIANG YAN]
He is a monster, and...
...esteemed personage.
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[screaming]
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[laughs]
You really did exactly
everything that I thought
you would do, Wang Jian!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] It was then, that a
strange phenomenon occurred.
[NARRATOR] All sound vanished
from the bellowing battlefield.
Completely.
[NARRATOR]
Qin and Wei alike at this time,
every soldier on the scene stood
stock-still and simply stared.
[NARRATOR] And then,
they all felt their
temperature rise tremendously
at the same time.
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[BI]
This... This is... Lian Po!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[XIN]
What is this... sensation?
Feels just like...
...when General Wang Yi
used to appear
on the battlefield back then.
[LUN HU] I see you've made
your move at last, my lord.
[XIN]
No doubt about it...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[XIN] ...he is one of the
world's greatest generals!