[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
[NARRATOR] It was the day
after the Fei Xin,
Yu Feng, and Le Hua Forces
had launched their attack
on Lun Hu's camp.
Um, Xin, sir?
[laughs]
Guess they can't see me, huh?
[NARRATOR]
The men who risked their lives
in the battle at its
very center,
came to a strange realization.
Why, yes, certainly.
[NARRATOR] Finally,
the curtain was now rising
on the final day of the
Great Shanyang Offensive!
What?!
What do you mean when you
say we're the rear reserves?!
After that stunt you pulled
yesterday, what did you expect?
And what more,
watch your loud mouth!
[XIN groans]
[RONG BEI] Today the Le Hua,
Yu Feng and Fei Xin Forces
will play nice together
in the rear reserves.
Did he say... in the rear?
It figures, I guess.
[XIN] But General, we only
just got the morale up high!
Oh, quit grumbling now.
Chances are Lun Hu will show up,
and when he does,
the rear reserves
really are the place to be.
Huh?!
The general is
absolutely right, Xin, sir.
[CHU SHUI]
If we were in the front line,
we'd only encounter Lun Hu
if we were lucky enough
for him to attack directly.
But given this broader post,
we can deal with Lun Hu
at any time we please.
[XIN]
Hey, you're right!
So then, the general's
giving us Lun--
The lot of you ought to be drawn
and quartered for violating
martial law, I'll have you know.
Heh. But Tu Men and
I really believe that
your utter dominance in
breaking through Lun Hu's camp
is the real deal.
Just don't screw up this time...
...Xin.
[XIN grunts]
[laughs]
[RONG BEI] Now, until the
opportunity presents itself,
stay back and enjoy
the view of my butt!
[gasps]
[RONG BEI] The clouds
are thick this morning.
[RONG BEI]
We're in for a rough one.
[NARRATOR] Day six of the
battle of the Liuyi Plains.
As usual Meng Ao's main
line-abreast defensive formation
was in position to strike
at the approaching Wei army.
General Tu Men headed up
the right flank,
with General Rong Bei
in the left flank.
The Le Hua and Yu Feng Forces
were in the right rear,
and the Fei Xin Force
in the left rear
took their respective
positions as reserves.
[NARRATOR] Meng Ao's
main troops stood atop a plateau
behind the central army
overlooking the Liuyi Plains.
Are Jie Zifang's
back up here yet?
Not yet, sir.
[LUN HU]
I'll use his soldiers
to replace the ones
I've lost so far.
But how well can those
heavyweights truly fit
into my fighting style,
and so quickly?
I suppose I could ask the same
about these Wei soldiers.
[WEI LIANG]
General Lun Hu!
I'm afraid you've misunderstood!
This is no comeback
for General Lian Po,
or any of his men whatsoever.
It's about the people
of Wei defending our land
from all of those pesky invading
Qin dogs coming for us!
We all came to fight
to protect our land
and our families, as well!
That sentiment,
those very lives,
they rest in your hands as we
fight right now, you see!
Please, Sir.
I'm asking you to have
more faith in our power.
If we lack the might you expect
to serve as your troops,
we will make up for
any shortfall with our resolve!
[WEI SOLDIERS cheer]
Right.
I can fight well enough
with these, then.
No more waiting for
Jie Zifang's troops now.
Wei Liang, wasn't it?
Yes!
We're after the head of
commanding general Meng Ao now,
at the back of
their central army.
I'll need you all to fight
like crazy warriors
out there, got it?
[WEI LIANG]
Yes sir!
[WEI SOLDIERS cheer]
Those little Wei idiots have
had a sudden jump in morale.
Meng Tian, sir,
is this it, then?
Indeed.
Today's the real deal, isn't it?
Yep.
Bring it on, Lun Hu!
[LUN HU]
All troops.
Charge right now!
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling]
[WEI SPEARMAN A]
Kill them!
[WEI SPEARMAN B]
Kill the Qin mongrels now!
[yelling continues]
[CHU SHUI] The vanguard
looks to be under heavy attack
at the moment.
Yuan, can you see
Lun Hu from up there?
Not from here, I'm afraid.
We've been posted to a
fair amount of land back here,
but running into Lun Hu
is entirely down to luck.
[ZHU KE] Their strength
is lopsided, I think.
[gasps]
[ZHU KE]
Lun Hu's on the very right!
Meng Tian, sir, it seems
he's headed for us, now.
And the Yu Feng Force, too.
Prepare to move at a
moment's notice!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Stay strong right now!
Show them how
incredibly fearsome
the great Qin army
truly is, men!
[QIN SOLDIERS yell]
Xin, sir!
Intense fighting
incoming on the right!
Lun Hu hasn't
hit the right flank?
That's not it.
It's not?
Today, Lun Hu means
real business.
If he does show up,
it surely won't be there.
[RONG BEI] The enemy troops
in back are on the move.
[RONG BEI]
The right flank is circling
in the opposite direction.
[RONG BEI]
What this? What's going on here?
[FEI XIN SOLDIER A] Whoa!
There's a huge dust cloud
up ahead!
[GUO JIAO] General Meng Ao,
look over there!
Two gigantic maelstroms?
[ZHU KE] And they're
slowly moving forward.
That's the wheel.
I've only heard of
the wheel in mere rumors.
It's said that Lun Hu once
used a unique wheel tactic
to pierce the
defenses of Wang Yi,
one of Qin's six great generals.
Wait a second! They're about
to spring something!
Beef up the left and
right flanks right now!
[RONG BEI ADVISOR A]
Yes sir!
[ZHU KE] General Rong Bei
is responding fast!
[GUO JIAO] He's bolstered the
troops facing the maelstroms!
[QIN SOLDIER A]
Stop them this instant!
[QIN SOLDIER B]
They have too much momentum!
[MENG AO] So this is the
true nature of the wheel.
[MENG AO] By rotating away
swiftly from one another,
the maelstroms split
the line left and right.
And once a chink
forms between them,
the tip can thrust in
like the deadliest drill ever!
No, that wheel attack
is directly aimed at...
[MENG AO]
Rong Bei's unit!
We're in for it now.
Wang Ben,
it's the left flank, sir!
Meng Tian, sir!
[MENG TIAN]
Is that Fei Xin territory?
Commander!
Yeah!
[XIN]
No doubt about it.
That's Lun Hu!
[WEI LIANG]
This is some fighting style!
It's all we can do
to just to keep up.
Then again, I've not seen a
breakthrough attack like this.
Stay strong, Wei troops!
This is the moment of truth!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Here they come! On your guard!
You must step down, sir!
[RONG BEI ADVISOR B]
Please, General, hurry!
[RONG BEI ADVISOR C]
General, sir!
[RONG BEI]
That Lun Hu.
It's like he's on a
whole other level.
I'll have to leave
the rest to a man
young enough
to be my son!
[RONG BEI]
If I can't follow through,
I must at least land
a blow on him!
Lun Hu!
[yells]
[RONG BEI]
My lord... I hope...
...you will win...
[ZHU KE]
What happened?
General Rong Bei's flag is gone!
[GUO JIAO]
It can't be!
[MENG AO]
Rong Bei...
[LUN HU] The Qin army is
paralyzed by the loss
of their commander at
this very moment.
Now, on to strike
their main camp next.
[GUO JIAO]
Uh-oh...
If the line was broken
with that attack,
then there's just a
tiny reserve corps
standing between us
and them right now!
General Meng Ao!
[XIN]
Lun Hu.
Let's do this right now, gang!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Fei Xin Force, wait a second!
You can't all go together!
And why not, Mr. Messenger?
There's another army on standby
among the
enemy troops facing you!
Leave 200 behind as
safety reinforcements!
[CHU SHUI]
Ridiculous!
Why wouldn't we strike
with all we've got?!
You can't. That's an order!
[XIN growls]
Hey, Yuan!
Round up 200 of
our wounded and hurry!
[YUAN]
Huh? Er, yes, sir!
[XIN]
Qiang Lei!
You're in charge here
from now on!
[gasping]
[YUAN] He's leaving
Lieutenant Qiang Lei?
Don't tell me,
he's wounded now?
[CHU SHUI] So when Lun Hu's
men had us surrounded...
You can keep your
bizarre concern for me.
[XIN]
That's not it!
Look, we don't know what'll
happen in today's fight,
so I need you to be in
charge of these men!
Besides, you've helped me
plenty already.
[XIN]
Qiang Lei.
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
[XIN]
Right! Come on! Now, men!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS yell]
Stop them!
[yelling, screaming]
[WEI LIANG] Excellent, they
have no means of stopping us
from now onward!
We fight through to Meng Ao's
camp and take him down swiftly!
[yelling]
Hear this, all you
stupid Qin dogs:
You've lost this one!
[yelling]
[screaming]
[gasping]
Lun Hu!
After the commander!
Right away, men!
[yelling]
[gasping]
[ZHU KE]
General!
[ZHU KE] The enemy's
stopped in their tracks!
[XIN]
I'm done running.
You can't escape!
Time to finish this,
Lun Hu!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS cheer]
[yells]
Lieutenant Qiang Lei, they will
be all right, won't they?
The commander and troops?
[XIN grunting]
Well, well, young boy!
I thought that right arm
of yours would be useless.
[XIN]
He's fighting one-handed!
Ha!
And it looks like your left arm
is totally out of commission!
[QU HAI]
Xin!
Go left!
Just circle around his
wounded left side now!
Don't need you to spell it out!
[CHU SHUI]
It's no use.
Lun Hu's horsemanship
won't let him get turned around.
He's fighting so calmly
for someone whose hand
was totally destroyed
just yesterday.
[CHU SHUI] He really must
have gone through a hell
beyond our wildest imagination
in all his time fighting
alongside Lian Po...
[MENG AO]
Xin...
[MENG AO gasps]
My lord?
It seems that something
happened at the rear.
[BOTH grunt]
[XIN]
What's with this guy?
Compared to just yesterday--
Xin, sir!
[LUN HU] Don't think for a
second that I'm weaker today.
It'd be a grave mistake.
[LUN HU] I've been
through plenty of battles
with only one
good hand you know,
And, well, besides, I have
another commitment after this.
Commitment?
They're getting insanely
worked up out in front now.
We missed out, darn it.
Figures huh?
The rear lookouts always wind up
staring at the mountains.
Moron! This is serious business!
We got a pretty gentle slope
here behind the main camp.
The enemy'll have to force
their way in from the front,
or sneak up on us
from behind.
[QIN GUARD A] But they can't
send a big army into the back.
Well, for sure they can, if it's
a surprise attack, that is.
Ha! As if they could just
bring down the main camp!
No way, man!
[grunts]
I just really wanna see
all the fighting out in front!
Not that I wanna do any of it.
[QIN GUARD B]
Hey!
[QIN GUARD A]
What's up?
[QIN GUARD B]
What's that there?
[QIN GUARD A] Uh...
A horseman alone?
[QIN GUARD B]
The enemy?
[QIN GUARD A]
I don't know, but it's just one.
[QIN GUARD B]
What's his deal, anyway?
Huh?
My lord?
[LIAN PO]
Hey there, Meng Ao!
Found that backbone
of yours yet?
The great Lian Po has
come to pay you a visit!
[gasping]
It's really Lian Po?
No way! Is it really him?
That intimidating
presence is his.
He's even much bigger
than they say!
What's he doing here alone?
[LIAN PO laughs]
My lord, is that truly Lian Po?
Absurd.
[MENG AO]
Lian Po. Were you afraid of me?
Truthfully?
Now just get down here!
We'll settle this with a duel!
A-A duel he said?
Is he serious?
'Cause Meng Ao, would never go
for something crazy like that!
[LIAN PO] We had our share
of duels back in the day!
Remember? You wet
yourself and ran away!
Now I'm suggesting we
pick up where we left off!
Come on, Meng Ao!
I will take you on
bare-handed!
[laughs]
Sir?
Your banter has not
changed a bit, I see!
Ah, but that's a
very good thing.
All right, let's begin!
[MA LING]
Yes sir!
Take your positions!
[QIN SOLDIERS yell]
[QIN SOLDIER I]
Round up the troops!
[QIN SOLDIER J]
On the double!
You're utterly no fun.
[laughs]
Hey guys, look there!
[gasping]
All right. Shall we, then?