[NARRATOR] In the middle
of a fierce battle
between Qin and Wei,
they meet again:
Xin and Lun Hu.
Which of them will be
able to overcome his limits
and have his own way
in the end?
[NARRATOR]
The blistering-hot emotions
truly are making sparks fly!
[LUN HU] Do you understand
the significance
of this undertaking,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
If you fall, the Qin army
here will be destroyed,
and we will rush off to
kill Meng Ao promptly.
Keep babbling!
If I take you down right now,
we win the whole central battle!
[XIN]
My path! It's clear!
[yells]
[horse whinnies]
[XIN grunts]
Commander!
Xin!
[XIN]
You... rat!
[CHU SHUI]
Uh-oh!
In an unstable fight
on horseback,
You must grab on
with your legs!
[CHU SHUI]
Otherwise,
he'll never be able
to stop Lun Hu's blade!
[XIN grunts]
[LUN HU]
And now... to end this.
[XIN yells]
[BOTH grunt]
Xin!
Commander!
Our general!
Oh, Lun Hu, my lord!
[BOTH whimper]
[grunts]
This comes after he
stopped that full-bodied blow.
If this turns into a
ground battle now
with that badly-wounded leg
he just injured...
[CHU SHUI] No!
Come on, Xin, Sir,
don't stand down!
You have a battle to fight.
[grunts]
[LUN HU]
Honestly.
You have real guts, it's true.
You saw you were at a
loss on horseback,
so you risked going into a fight
on the ground instead of that?
[grunts]
That was most definitely a
very good call on your part.
For if you'd gone on
just like that,
the fight would've been
over really quickly.
[LUN HU] Not that it changes
my overwhelming advantage
over you in any way, truthfully.
[grunts]
I mean, are you able to
even stand on that leg,
Xin, of the Fei Xin Force?
[XIN grunts]
No problem at all, I see!
[XIN] Having to fight and battle
hard with only one healthy leg?
Piao and I trained plenty
of times that way!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS cheer]
Go! Xin!
[cheering continues]
[LUN HU]
So tenacious.
What is it then,
this unusually resilient
spirit that he possesses?
What exactly has been
sustaining him all this time?
What's going on?
Did something happen at the
main camp, or what?
[LUN HU]
I apologize, my lord,
and ask your patience.
[LUN HU]
I'll be right there.
Fire!
[QIN SOLDIER A]
Keep firing! Don't let up!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MENG AO] Send in the
reinforcements, right now!
You must gather up
absolutely every soldier
that's near the trap!
This is the moment where we
finally end it and win, men!
[MENG AO]
Take him out!
Take out Lian Po
once and for all!
[yelling]
Where exactly is
General Lian Po?
We must all protect him,
no matter what, men!
It's no use;
now we can't even move!
If we could withstand
these arrows--
All troops, you must go
underneath right away!
They have just
hidden under the corpses!
So bring out the
spear corps immediately!
Where is Lian Po?
Well then, men?
Did we get Lian Po or not?
[QIN SOLDIER D] I can't tell
for sure, not in this rubble.
Keep shooting!
Until no one's moving,
I think that'll surely do the
trick, so just don't stop!
Fire!
[gasps]
[gasping]
Huh...?
[LIAN PO yells]
[screaming]
[yells]
[yelling, screaming]
[LIAN PO yells]
[screaming]
Listen to me clearly, troops!
Knock every last
miserable Qin soldier
off this cliff, immediately!
[yelling]
[QIN SOLDIERS screaming]
[MENG AO]
No, it can't be!
[ZHU KE] The soldiers
that were posted to the traps
have all been shoved
off the cliff!
[MA LING]
What on earth is going on?!
How exactly did Lian Po
wind up on the cliff-top?
But I thought that he
was stuck in that trap,
attacked by a load of arrows!
[MENG AO]
No, he wasn't.
We saw enemy flags in the trap
and merely assumed Lian Po was
down there with everybody else
trapped in the pit as well.
However, there may
have been blind spots
along the path to the
trap as we saw it,
unfortunately for us, that is.
Lian Po quite cleverly
divided his troops into two
and led his half down
a completely different path
from the one we've had
before us, you see.
And then, afterwards,
just before he reached the trap
he must have headed straight
for the very top, I think.
Lian Po has even managed
to somehow figure out
this fortress' ace in the hole.
[LIAN PO snarls]
[MENG AO]
My elaborate scheme
has failed terribly!
[screaming]
Well done, my lord. Truly.
I honestly did have my doubts.
[LIAN PO] Once I got a very good
look at the fortress maze here,
I figured it'd come into
play in the scheme somehow.
However, to reshape
routes and then trap your foe
right after he had
entered your maze,
you need an eye for predicting
your enemies' movements
and a precise military eye
to be able to judge when exactly
you ought to put your
men into motion.
I wasn't sure that
mediocre Meng Ao up there,
would really put such
a bothersome and incredibly
complicated plan
into actual action.
But just in case, I came up
with a way to deal with spots
that were more
likely to be traps.
You see how that
turned out?
Meng Ao...
He used his grudge against me
for all those past defeats,
and did some careful
preparation, indeed.
This truly is a
mighty fine fortress
that he built over here.
However,
it would quite honestly
take far more than 40 years
of hard planning to get even
one elaborate scheme over me,
Meng Ao!
[LIAN PO growls]
[ZHU KE] Lian Po is
advancing right now!
[MA LING] It can't
be! How is it that simple, then?
He may have escaped the trap,
but he should still be stuck
in the maze!
Once again, he has
managed to use
my strategy against me, here.
[gasping]
In shifting the maze around
in order to lure Lian Po
into an elaborate trap,
several other paths
came to lead directly to us
over here, you see.
[gasping]
Furthermore, focusing our
manpower around the traps.
to be able to strike
at the enemy in one fell swoop
in turn left us with some
very poorly defended areas.
[MENG AO]
And so, most likely.
that's where Lian Po
is headed right now!
[LIAN PO]
I'm now on my way up
just to be able to
see you, Meng Ao.
I can't possibly leave Lun Hu
waiting around, after all!
[screaming]
[LIAN PO yells]
[LIAN PO growls]
[yelling]
[gasping]
[LIAN PO yells]
[LI CHONG]
There's no stopping him.
Because he's already almost
here, as you can clearly see!
[MA GONG]
My lord!
[MA LING]
Lian Po is coming!
Come on, don't fret, he's
only almost here, after all.
There's still plenty of mountain
between him and the top,
as you all well know.
[MENG AO] And there's
absolutely no maze or the like
that's this high up, either.
All we can do is
go back to basics:
put together a
garrison unit and defend.
You see, with no tricks
left in his way,
Lian Po will be forced to
battle us head on.
He will have no other choice
but to take out
every last garrison on his
way up over here.
But, my lord...
Still, we must act.
[MA GONG]
With Lian Po's momentum,
it's only a matter of time
before he arrives!
So, it's just a matter of
time, then, is it?
That's excellent!
[gasping]
Because that
strategy right there
is the fighting style of the
old-school Meng Ao's army!
[gasping]
Just think it over
calmly right now.
When you break it down,
this Meng Ao army
consists of three armies
led by me and my
two lieutenants.
Each of these divisions
has a very clear and
simple role to play.
Our main army defends arduously,
keeping me, the general,
from being killed.
In the meantime,
one of the lieutenants' armies
naturally goes right after
the enemy general.
That's the same strategy
I've always used
to lead us to victory
over the years!
However, Wang Jian is holed up
in the rear fortress my lord,
and unfortunately somehow, Huan
Yi is still nowhere to be found!
If we, his allies, have lost
sight of Huan Yi at the moment,
then without a shadow of a
doubt, so too have our enemies.
It can't be.
[MENG AO] My battle lies in
trusting that "It can't be"
and keeping it alive,
you understand?
[WANG BEN grunts]
Fan Yang! Go help out
the right squadron!
The enemy will
destroy them at this rate!
But my lord, the battle--
I will handle things here!
Hurry!
[FAN YANG]
Yes sir!
[yelling]
[WANG BEN] They must have
put their best soldiers
in this squad,
to make sure we're not
focused solely on Lun Hu.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MENG TIAN] But the Wei army is
unusually powerful today.
Not a single one of you
rotten Qin invaders
is getting out alive right now!
[MENG TIAN] I know what it's
like,
fighting a battle you believe
you simply cannot lose.
[MENG TIAN] No, there's
absolutely no leaving our post
in these conditions.
I beg you, hang in there, Xin!
[yelling, shouting]
[XIN grunts]
This is not good!
He can't take it anymore!
Let's go help Xin right now!
[yelling]
[CHU SHUI]
Wait!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS gasp]
Lieutenant Chu Shui!
If we step in there right now,
that means Xin needed
his men to help him
when this is a single combat.
And with Xin aiming to be one of
the world's greatest generals,
that disgrace will haunt him
for the rest of his life!
You don't understand!
None of that matters if he
dies here right now!
He won't die now!
Our beloved commander
will not die now!
[whimpering]
Well, Yuan...
[XIN yells]
[LUN HU grunts]
[XIN]
Just one second.
That's all I need.
[XIN]
Once Lun Hu gives me an opening,
I can take him down.
[XIN]
In a heartbeat!
[grunting]
[WEI LIANG]
I know all too well.
I really understand just how
imperative single combat
can be for a general.
[WEI LIANG] But right now,
we're dealing with something
even more important
than all of that!
[WEI LIANG]
Forgive us, Lun Hu, sir!
[LUN HU HORSEMAN B]
Don't do it, Wei Liang!
[WEI LIANG] I would understand
if you cut me down after this,
but at this moment,
we simply cannot lose.
No matter what!
[WEI LIANG] That brat's eyes
are far from dead.
This one's... dangerous
Xin, sir!
[WEI LIANG growls]
[yells]
Get out of my way,
you stupid little Qin dog!
[BOTH grunt]
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] It truly did happen
in the blink of an eye.
[NARRATOR] Whether it was an
irrepressible impulse,
now that Guo Bei's
revenge was within sight.
Or perhaps, it was Chu Shui's
instinct for self-defense.
[NARRATOR] The fierce desire to
kill that instantly welled up
deep inside the
veins of Chu Shui
was turned upon Lun Hu.
[NARRATOR]
Lun Hu dealt a countering blow.
[NARRATOR] And then, in the
split second his attention
was turned away from himself...
[XIN]
I think that... it worked!
I-It can't be.
My lord Lun Hu has fallen!
Xin! We're coming now!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER A]
Lieutenant Chu Shui!
He's hanging on somehow!
Are you all right, Xin?
Settle down. Those are merely
just his death throes.
'Cause right now,
he won't get up again.
No way could he get... up...
He's standing...
with that wound!
Without a doubt...
he is a monster!
Lun Hu, you rat!
Well, my lord is...
waiting for me...
I can't possibly...
lose here now.