[NARRATOR]
The battle for Shanyang ended
in the Qin army's victory,
and the defeated
general, Lian Po,
returned to the capital of
Daliang soon thereafter.
[KING JINGMIN]
Li...
Lian Po!
[LIAN PO]
It was an unforgiveable fiasco.
If it is your will, sire,
I understand if you behead me.
[KING JINGMIN]
What are you saying?
I know very well that you made
the best decision possible
on behalf of the land of Wei
at that given time.
I have not the
slightest intention
of blaming you for this.
However,
the most I could do right now
is call off your death sentence.
Forgive me, Lian Po.
I hereby banish you
from the land of Wei.
[NARRATOR] History books
tell us that after leaving Wei,
Lian Po was exiled again
to the land of Chu.
There, the Zhao hero, Lian Po,
lived out the rest of his days,
never once returning
to his homeland.
[XIANG hums]
[YANG]
Xiang!
Morning! You're sure
in a good mood.
Uh, I spent the, um, night.
[YANG]
Huh?
[gasps] Wait a sec, what?
What's that? You don't mean--
No, no, no! Not that! Not that!
No, nothing happened!
Um, it's just, the war is over,
and His Highness
seemed so very happy.
[YANG]
What? What's that about?
So, absolutely nothing is
going on between you two?
I thought that incident earlier
would have set off sparks.
Well, I uh,
it's not like there's
nothing going on
at all, you see.
Huh? What'd you say?
Uh! Oh! No, nothing!
[YANG]
Hm...
[MINISTERS, SOLDIERS chatter]
[LORD CHANGWEN] What's with
that outfit you have?
Do you intend to show up at
the awards ceremony like that?
Huh? Well, what's
wrong with it?
Besides, this is really
all I have, you know!
Well, if armor is permitted,
I suppose that thing
you have is, as well.
Hey, you had me worried there.
Okay, let's do this.
Awards thingy, here we come!
[XIN laughs]
Is everyone gonna
be praising me?
[chuckles]
You really are something else.
[XIN] An awards ceremony,
how about that!
[XIN] What are you
looking at, old man?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
How far he's come
in such an incredibly
short time.
What are you
lookin' at, old man?
[LORD CHANGWEN] You really are a
big deal now, aren't you, Xin?
What are you doing, old man?
Come on!
[LORD CHANGWEN] The most
powerful members of the Court
will be at today's
ceremony, you know.
Remember your manners,
and behave accordingly!
[XIN]
I know, I know, calm down!
Whoa. This is amazing!
Um, uh-oh, suddenly
I'm getting nervous.
You idiot! You sit
in back! Move now!
Huh? What old man?
[whispering] Over here, now,
because you are killing me!
[XIN]
Hey! Meng Tian!
Is Wang Ben here?
No, the Yu Feng Force is
out there guarding Shanyang.
Huh?
Uh, well, you sure are
dressed weird, man.
--Look who's talking!
--Keep it down now, both of you!
All present, salute!
[XIN, MENG TIAN gasp]
[QIN MINISTER A] The High King
is making his entrance!
[MENG TIAN]
So that's the High King, huh?
Can't see him too well
from back here.
[XIN] Oh! He's got
himself new clothes.
Very well, everyone.
Let the awards
ceremony begin now!
[XIN]
Lü Buwei!
That's right!
Almost forgot that half of these
guys are Zheng's enemies.
And first up, then,
are three great men of truly
extraordinary bravery.
These very special three will
receive congratulatory swords
directly from His Majesty.
So then, Lord Changping?
Sir.
First things first,
the commanding general
who led Qin's army to
ultimate grand victory:
General Meng Ao!
[MINISTERS, SOLDIERS cheer]
Oh, General Meng Ao!
Listen to those cheers!
[LORD CHANGPING]
The general will go up one rank
in the peerage, and receive
the lands of Jiabai and Chan,
2,000 gold pieces,
and ten treasures.
[MINISTERS, SOLDIERS
cheer, gasp]
You have done well.
Please take care of yourself.
[MENG AO chuckles]
I thank you.
Next up is the lieutenant who
killed the enemy's tactician
and their commanding general:
General Huan Yi!
[MINISTERS, SOLDIERS cheer]
Yeah, way to go, boss!
It's about time!
[LORD CHANGPING] The general
will go up two ranks
in the peerage,
and receive the lands of
Qing Bei, Qinglin, and Dake,
2,000 gold pieces,
and ten treasures.
You have done quite well,
General Huan Yi.
[HUAN YI]
I thank you.
[ZHENG] So this is Huan Yi,
Qin's very own hidden talent.
[HUAN YI]
So this is our king,
the very one who lost
authority to his minister.
How does he look like, anyway?
[XIN gasps]
[HUAN YI]
Hmm.
Way to go there, boss man!
[HUAN YI'S MEN cheer]
[HUAN YI]
What's a coddled puppet doing
with eyes like that, exactly?
Why do they give off such
a fierce and haunting light?
Last, but definitely not least,
the man who killed a key enemy
general by himself,
300-man commander Xin
of the Fei Xin Force!
Forward!
--[XIN] Uh...
--[CROWD murmurs]
What did he say?
The award goes to
a 300-man commander?
A 300-man commander
who served in this war
as an ad-hoc
1,000-man commander!
Xin of the Fei Xin Force!
Come forward!
[CROWD murmurs]
[XIN]
Um, er, here!
[CIVIL SERVANT C]
What, him?
[CIVIL SERVANT D] Awarded
for a temporary position?
Um, are you okay, Xin?
[TU MEN groans]
Hey!
[XIN]
Uh, I--
Oh man, this is hopeless.
[XIN]
What am I exactly doing?
My-My body won't move right!
[CROWD laughs]
[MILITARY OFFICER A]
Why's he walking like that?
[MILITARY OFFICER B]
His face is stuck!
[XIN grunts]
[XIN gasps]
I think that's enough
entertainment for now,
correct, Xin?
[CROWD laughs]
[XIN]
Shut up! I meant to do that!
[chuckles]
[gasps] He got over his nerves.
[LORD CHANGPING]
To continue,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force
will go up three ranks
in the peerage immediately,
and receive 500 gold pieces,
five treasures,
and an official promotion to
become a 1,000-man commander!
[XIN] I'm officially a
1,000-man commander?
Yes!
[LORD CHANGPING]
Um, hey now!
[CROWD laughs]
[ZHENG]
Xin of the Fei Xin Force,
you have done well.
[XIN]
What do I do now, Zheng?
Didn't you see the other
two go before you?
Go down on one knee
and say "Thank you," now.
[XIN]
I thank you.
[NARRATOR] For some reason, all
those present were enthralled
by the sight of these
two in this very moment.
Despite the difference in rank
between king and commander,
it seemed entirely
fitting, somehow,
to see both of them together.
Such beauty brought a momentary
hush upon the audience,
and then...
[cheers and applause]
[NARRATOR]
...in the next moment,
the room broke out in
great cheers and applause.
Yet the two in the middle of it
all were just doing their best
to hold back the laughter
welling up within them both.
[XIN, ZHENG chuckle]
[LÜ BUWEI]
Well, that's over.
[LI SI]
Yes, sir.
It is now time for my battle
to start right back once again.
I wonder who will be present
at the next awards ceremony
for it all.
[LÜ BUWEI laughs]
[ZHENG]
What did you expect?
Anyone who knows
the civilian Xin
couldn't help but laugh.
[XIN]
Come on!
It wasn't that easy
doing all that with you!
[XIN, ZHENG laugh]
Oh, right, then.
There's something I really
need to tell you.
[ZHENG]
Huh?
Just being one of the
world's greatest generals
isn't gonna cut it
right now, Zheng.
Looks like my path and yours
have started to overlap,
don't you think?
My path?
A unified Middle Kingdom!
[gasps]
Pull off a real daring feat
we could never have even
dreamed of achieving,
and you shall be
revered by history!
A daring feat?
Like what, then?
[LIAN PO]
Say, the...
...Unification of
Middle Kingdom!
[ZHENG] I see. So Lian Po
said that, then?
[XIN] Yeah. It's about
overwriting their legends.
And to be able to do that,
we are gonna need
both the military and
the royal might, as well.
And, to be honest,
I just don't really get
all of this "nation"
business whatsoever.
But even I can see
that this would be
a really major deal
for everyone.
It is truly such a huge
undertaking no one's managed.
A huge undertaking, huh?
I like the sound of that!
There are many obstacles
standing between us
and that path, you know.
But I'm telling you, we're
bursting with might over here!
Let's do it then, Zheng!
[ZHENG]
Yes!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[NARRATOR] It was some months
after the awards ceremony,
and skirmishes between
the Qin and Wei armies
were still breaking out
in Lijing, near Shanyang.
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Urgent message!
The first and second units!
They've been destroyed!
Where are the reinforcements?
They-They are here!
It's them!
It's "them"?
Yes! The 1,000-man
indie reserves
that did so splendidly in
the Shanyang Offensive!
[QIN MESSENGER B]
The Fei Xin Force!
[XIN]
Yah!
Let's go! Come on, guys!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[LU XIAN]
Meng Tian, sir!
Hey, you're back now
again, good work!
How'd it go?
Same as always, we just shoved
them back into the mountains.
That is my
good commander!
Can I ask you
something, Lu Xian?
Don't the women of Wei have
a certain glamour to them?
Every one of them
a real beauty!
If I may sir,
there's a strange rumor
going around town right now.
[MENG TIAN hums]
The base on the
front lines of Lijing--
Yeah, where the
Fei Xin Force is now.
They must be riding high
now that they are
a 1,000-man unit.
Those poor Wei troops!
Yes Sir. Precisely,
it's about the Fei Xin Force.
[MENG TIAN]
Hm?
[LU XIAN] Word is
they're on a losing streak
and their commander Xin
is in danger of having
his rank stripped from him.
Huh?
We lost again.
We lost again!
Why?!
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
What in the world
is going on?
Ever since we became
the new Fei Xin Force,
we haven't won
a single battle!
Are these battles not
big enough for any of you
to take seriously or what?
Um... Of course
that's not it!
Whoa, Xin.
Don't take it out on us!
Shut it, Wei Ping!
This is what happens when
you guys get fancy new armor
and now you think
you're great stuff!
Please, Xin,
calm down!
Seriously though, guys,
why can't we ever win
all of a sudden, then?
The 1,000-man commanders
that we're up against
are not well-known, too.
Maybe Lieutenant
Qiang Lei's leaving
was a really big blow
after all, right?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Don't say that, Mao.
Qiang Lei didn't win
all of those battles
single-handedly, you know.
Losing just one person
wouldn't make us
this incredibly weak.
[MAO]
It's not just that--
I'm really talking about
the tactics that we're using.
[XIN]
Huh?
Which tactics?
I mean Lieutenant Qiang Lei was
really the one who came up with
absolutely all of the
strategies we've used.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Oh, now that you mention it.
But at the moment,
Lieutenant Chu Shui's
taken over that same position.
He's not doing it.
Chu Shui's too busy
to be handing supplies
and stuff like that right now.
So, who's doing our strategies
if he's not doing them?
It's me and Yuan.
[FEI XIN FORCE gasp]
[FEI XIN FORCE]
That's it?!
Do you jokers realize
what you've done?
How many injuries
have we suffered
because of the two of you?
Now wait just
a minute, here!
Suddenly you're blaming our
strategies for all our losses?
What else is there to
blame at, you big fool?
Enough already
with this, Xin!
You do realize
you're only barely smarter
than a rock, right?
Yeah Xin,
this is too much!
[XIN grunts]
[MENG TIAN]
I figured this was going on.
[XIN, FEI XIN FORCE gasp]
[XIN]
Oh, Meng Tian!
Um, hi guys.
[XIN]
So, you see?
I say we charge in like, tada!
And then we go all kaboom,
and then the cavalry's all
like kapow, right over here,
and then we win!
You see? Not half bad,
am I right?
Uh, did you seriously fight
with that very strategy
you just said?
[XIN]
Well, sure.
But how were you
not all wiped out?
[WEI PING]
You see? You see?
[QU HAI] I knew our
strategies were bad!
[MENG TIAN] Doesn't anyone else
have a knack for tactics here?
[QU HAI]
No, not really.
I mean we all started out as
country soldiers, you see.
How about on
Guo Bei's squad?
Because surely they must have
had a tactician on hand
that they could spare.
No way! We were all about
the brawn here, you see.
We left all of the strategizing
to Guo Bei himself!
You see? So clearly
we gotta keep up with-- Ah!
[FEI XIN FORCE]
Enough!
Hey, this is serious!
[XIN]
I'm... being serious, too!
[MENG TIAN]
Listen up,
right now the Fei Xin Force
is in a really bad spot.
We can't have the reinforcements
losing to everyone all the time.
And these rumors about
you being demoted.
Honestly they do have the
ring of truth to them, Xin.
[WEI PING]
S-Seriously?
[MENG TIAN] But there's
no good way to fix this
within your unit.
You've had relatively
few casualties
because your foes
haven't been that tough.
So you know,
right now, the 300 members
of the Le Hua Force
could wipe the floor with you.
Aahh! That's super bad news!
But what do we do?
Guess it's come to this.
We have to try to get Lieutenant
Qiang Lei back quickly--
[XIN]
No way!
[WEI PING]
Uh, but it's--
No way that's happening.
[sighs]
Well all right, then.
You did help us out greatly back
at Grandpa's main camp before.
Then I'll take this chance
to return you the favor.
Uh, how exactly?
I'll call in an excellent
tactician I know
to serve the Fei Xin Force.
A-A tactician?
[MENG TIAN] Well, he's my
little brother, but still.
[XIN]
Cut it out!
Don't go calling in your
little brother on us!
[MENG TIAN] Look, just listen
to what I'm saying here!
A 1.000-man unit is
really too big to fight
on momentum alone.
You absolutely need someone who
could put together strategies!
[grunts]
[QIN MESSENGER C]
Report!
The tactician has passed Beiye
and will arrive in three days!
I just don't like this!
[FEI XIN FORCE gasp]
So this newbie gets to
come to boss us around
just 'cause he happens
to be a tactician?
Some stranger coming in
out of nowhere?
Nope! I don't like this!
Hey Xin, you know we're in
no position to complain at all!
Since Meng Tian had
that talk with us,
we haven't won
a single battle!
That's five losses
in a row, five!
[TIAN YONG] But does that
mean we have to rely
on outsiders now?
Tian Yong!
As if we weren't ashamed!
Do we really need an outsider
right here, Meng Tian's brother?
Not you guys, too!
[horse hooves clacking]
Xin!
[NARRATOR] Long-standing units
often have strong bonds
among their members,
but can feel just as strongly
about not letting
outsiders in as well.
Even the Fei Xin Force, which
started with only 100 men,
showed signs of this fact.
I can't entrust their lives
to orders from someone
who isn't even one of us!
[NARRATOR]
However, come their next battle,
the Fei Xin Force
lost yet again.
Qin lost a crucial bridge,
and Lijing's defense
was forced back onto
the far bank of the river.
And then,
the cart bearing
their new tactician
finally came to
the Fei Xin Force.
Xin sir, he is here.
Let's meet him.
[XIN grunts]
So wasn't Meng Yi due to arrive
at the Fei Xin Force
today, then?
Yeah, they have really got
their backs to the wall now.
Doubt they're happy about it.
Ah, but you know
my brother.
They'll do fine.
[gasps]
It has been a while,
dear brother!
[MENG TIAN, LU XIAN gasp]
[MENG TIAN]
Huh?
Meng Yi! What exactly
are you doing right here?
[MENG YI]
Um, what do you mean?
Didn't you get my message?
I have a position
here at Weizicheng,
so I can't take on
the other job.
I thought you heard, Tian.
I-I didn't.
And the Fei Xin
Force's tactician?
I sent a suitable substitute.
A substitute?
[BODYGUARD A]
We have arrived now.
[XIN growls]
Okay!
Wha--
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS]
What is that?
[XIN]
What--
What are you
doing over here?
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS]
They know each other?
[DIAO laughs]
[DIAO]
I knew you'd be surprised!
Honestly, I was positive that
it would still be a long time
before I'd be coming
to you like this,
so I was a little
surprised myself.
But, you know,
what can you do?
I've arrived to
help you out, Xin!
Diao!