[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
Tomorrow, Le Hua Force,
Yu Feng Force,
and the Fei Xin Force
altogether will kill Lun Hu!
Then let's talk strategy.
Firstly, the Le Hua Force goes
after Lun Hu's main camp alone.
Right now!
What's this?
[MENG TIAN] Phase one
of our strategy will be:
[MENG TIAN] The Le Hua Force
will not go after Lun Hu!
[LUN HU] A mere 800 troops,
split into five teams.
[LUN HU]
What are they attempting,
coming after the main camp
with its 5,000 men?
Right! Going in!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LUN HU] And they're waltzing
right in, aren't they?
This is no clever plan.
It's plain bizarre!
[LUN HU]
They're charging to their death.
[GUO JIAO] Meng Ao, sir!
It's the young lord!
The Le Hua Force is
attacking the camp alone!
[MENG AO groans]
Dear Meng Tian,
what on earth are you--
[GUO JIAO]
Call them back at once!
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Yes sir!
[MENG AO]
Wait a moment.
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Sir?
[MENG WU]
Father, about Meng Tian.
Will he remain a
300-man commander?
Being overprotective
will stunt his growth.
[MENG AO] As will
too much neglect, I'd say.
[MENG WU] You should
consider trusting him more.
[MENG WU] He may be a girlish
lad, but I see far more in him
than in any of those
thousand-men commanders.
You ought to understand that
more than anyone else, Father.
[MENG WU]
Trust fully in Meng Tian.
If he dies, then he dies.
But whatever happens,
he dies a man.
[MENG AO]
Meng Tian...
[MENG TIAN]
Grandpa, look! See? A crab!
[MENG TIAN laughs]
[MENG AO] Take a message
to General Tu Men.
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Sir!
[MENG AO "The Le Hua Force
are independent.
Let them go on
doing as they wish."
[QIN MESSENGER A]
B-But sir...
[MENG AO]
Go now.
[QIN MESSENGER A]
Yes, sir!
[MENG AO]
I am fully aware, Meng Tian.
[MENG AO] I know you are,
without question,
the most gifted in three
generations of Meng soldiers.
[MENG AO]
However...
[MENG AO] ...you cannot die
in vain, you see.
The enemy is launching
an unexpected invasion!
[GUI]
What does this mean?
[LUN HU] They're just aiming
at the seams in our defense.
If that's truly
their little plan,
it's really not much of one.
After all,
those spots are covered...
[gasps]
[screaming]
[LUN HU] ...with soldiers
with at least a hundred battles
under their belts.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LE HUA SOLDIER E]
Meng Tian, sir!
[MENG TIAN]
Yeah!
There they are: Lun Hu's men!
[CHU SHUI] The infantry should
be able to handle things
around here. The cavalry
can move out, too.
Xin, sir!
Xin?
[growls]
[XIN]
Huh?!
You're not going after Lun Hu?!
What's the matter
with you, Meng Tian?!
The Le Hua Force's target
will be Lun Hu's men.
Wha--?
Lun Hu's men, then?
You're saying we
go after his troops?
[MENG TIAN]
That's right.
What do you mean "that's right"?
Lun Hu is a monster, to be sure.
However, he alone
can't destroy enemies
by the hundreds, much less
thousands at that, you see?
Behind Lun Hu are the troops who
always fight right beside him,
battle after battle,
without fail.
Lun Hu's destructive power is in
commanding those very troops.
When Lun Hu was exiled,
he brought 700
chosen soldiers with him to Wei.
During this battle, they've been
surrounding Lun Hu, as well,
waiting for the
opportunity to charge.
The Le Hua Force will
go after those 700 troops
and take them out.
So that way, Lun Hu has
absolutely no real way
to strike Meng Ao's main camp
like he intends to do.
[MENG TIAN]
Well, I suppose it's more
about laying some groundwork,
don't you think so?
[XIN]
Groundwork?
[WANG BEN] I don't believe
that it's that easy.
The Yu Feng Force fought them
that first day of war.
They bested us in individual
and in group strength as well.
You want to get the jump
on the unstoppable Lun Hu
and his specially chosen troops.
But if you challenge them,
the only one who'll wind up
with casualties is the
Le Hua Force, Meng Tian.
[CHU SHUI] Why aren't we
mobilizing, Xin, sir?
Aren't we supposed
to be fighting alongside
the Le Hua Force now?!
If this keeps up, they will--
[XIN] Stay put
and wait for the signal!
This is part of
Meng Tian's strategy.
Wang Ben sir, it seems
the Le Hua Force is struggling.
Perhaps this strategy
was a terrible mistake.
No, I do not think so.
You need an attack
framework to take down
a big game like Lun Hu, you see.
It's an attack framework,
you say, then?
[WANG BEN]
When we attack Lun Hu,
his powerful troops will prove a
huge obstacle to us all here.
[WANG BEN]
Meng Tian is attempting
to get rid of them first.
Obviously, this is
no simple task. But still...
He's the one who
took on this prep work,
drawing first blood after all.
[WANG BEN]
You've really made up your mind,
haven't you now, Meng Tian?
The ever-temperamental
Le Hua Force.
Once you show your
enthusiasm at the forefront...
[grunts]
[WANG BEN] ...they'll get
worked up into a lather,
and put more than their
usual force on display.
What gives, men?
Are you tired already?!
[LE HUA SOLDIERS yell]
[LUN HU]
My soldiers, being killed?
[XIN]
W-Wait a second!
What gives, Meng Tian?
Why do you have to be the one
sacrificing yourself
in that way?!
Silly. I am not setting out
to be some martyr.
The Yu Feng Force
and Fei Xin Force
can't fulfill this vital role
the way they stand now.
Only the Le Hua Force can.
And we will, rest assured.
We will bring down Lun Hu!
[MENG TIAN]
We three forces, that is!
Right, it's time now!
[gasps]
[CHU SHUI]
Is that--?
[MENG TIAN]
Wang Ben, and Xin...
...the rest is up to you!
It's the... signal!
Come on, Fei Xin Force!
Go, Yu Feng Force!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Will the infantry
be all right back there?
The sergeants know
the gist of our plan.
The bigger issue here
is whether we can reach
Lun Hu before the Le Hua Force
is ultimately defeated.
[yelling]
[LE HUA SOLDIER G]
Meng Tian, sir!
We are hurting pretty bad!
If we keep losing any more men,
we'll fall apart completely!
Yes, I know that!
But Lun Hu's troops
have thinned out plenty, too.
Pull my soldiers back and
have them assemble immediately.
[GUI gasps]
You said your soldiers, sir?
Yes, I did, and hurry up, now.
Fill those holes over there
with new Wei recruits.
Strengthen the perimeter,
and don't let any escape.
[GUI]
Yes sir!
[LUN HU]
Oh dear...
This whole time they
were coming after my men.
Such precious elements,
and I only have so many of them.
Yaah!
Forget the small fry! Plow
through and send 'em flying!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[gasps]
What's all this?!
The enemy's reaction to us
is significantly slow!
Let's go! Find an opening
and run through it!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS yell]
Yes, we can do this!
Keep this pace and we
can make up for lost time!
[XIN]
Oh yeah, I know!
It's like I said, it's all just
going according to our plans!
They got a late start now.
Correct, sir?
That's right.
When the Le Hua Force
suddenly ran out ahead,
the enemy would've been watching
for other units to mobilize.
But it was only the
Le Hua Force.
Their no-hesitation rush
into the Wei army's main camp
surely drew the
enemy's attention.
The later we mobilize, the
more the enemy would be focused
on the Le Hua Force
running wild in their midst.
With no enemies in
the cavalry's way,
we can reach Lun Hu's camp
in the blink of an eye,
if you know what I mean.
[gasping]
[YU FENG SOLDIER A]
The main camp! Let's go!
Meng Tian, sir, the Fei Xin
and Yu Feng forces
are approaching!
Good! Then how
about we give them
one more special
little present?
Attention flanks!
Retreat at once!
We'll be backing down
now, as well!
[yelling]
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER D]
They're running!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER E]
After them!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER F]
Don't let them get away!
[gasps]
[XIN]
He... He made us a path!
[FAN YANG]
W-Wang Ben, sir! Is this--
Argh. It's impossible.
This, too, is Meng Tian's doing?
I can't believe it!
Fighting in this manner,
and with one of Lian Po's
right-hand men, no less.
And bringing three
young rivals together
into one allied force,
on top of it?!
[FAN YANG]
The talent that made him
our first thousand-man
commander was not for show.
In fact, I think Meng Tian's
skills may already be
far beyond that level
at this very moment!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER G]
A-Another unit is closing in
from the left! 300 strong!
[GUI]
What?!
And from the right, too, sir!
Ridiculous! How can it be?!
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER G]
Look how far they've come
already, General!
Look, right there!
The main camp's flags!
Lun Hu's right in front of us!
[CHU SHUI]
Lun Hu!
[FORMER GUO BEI SOLDIER A]
Lun Hu...
[FORMER GUO BEI SOLDIER B]
Time to avenge Guo Bei!
In front, they're coming!
Say what?!
[growling]
[screaming]
[XIN whimpers]
[XIN]
They got us!
[FORMER GUO BEI SOLDIER C]
Out of the way, you idiots!
[screaming]
What the world?
They're crazy strong!
The soldiers wearing white...
They can't possibly be!
Lun Hu's troops!
Kill them all now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Lun Hu's soldiers are
right here, of all places!
Why exactly didn't
Meng Tian take care of all
of these goons then, Sir?
[WANG BEN]
They must be the last troops
guarding Lun Hu's perimeter.
[FAN YANG] And they're
certainly not holding back!
What audacity!
Like one big wave
of constant attack.
But if we can make it
through this,
there'll be no one left
to protect Lun Hu!
[XIN grunts]
Hey!
[XIN]
I said get outta my way!
Right! Almost there!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER A]
Um, commander?
Look behind us!
There's no one there!
No one at all!
[XIN]
What?
What are you doing, Xin, sir?
Keep up the charge right now!
[CHU SHUI] Lun Hu is just trying
to delay the inevitable!
Xin, I do believe
you can take him down!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[XIN]
Chu Shui!
[CHU SHUI grunts]
Go, Xin! Go right now!
Don't worry about us! Go take
Lun Hu's head right now!
[XIN]
Chu Shui...
[LUN HU'S SOLDIER L]
Kill him!
[CHU SHUI]
Hurry up!
Chu Shui!
[QIANG LEI]
I will head back.
Qiang Lei!
The Fei Xin Force still needs
him at this very moment.
[XIN]
Okay. He's all yours.
And I...
...am taking down Lun Hu!
[LUN HU]
What hurts the most, I believe,
is losing over half of my
personal specialized troops.
Now I have to come up with
something really interesting
for the main event.
[LUN HU]
But that's all. Definitely.
Everything else...
[LUN HU]
...is incredibly unimportant.
[XIN growls]
[LUN HU]
Even if the enemy does close in,
it's not like they can
actually ever kill me.
[growls]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Are you all right now,
Chu Shui?
[CHU SHUI]
Q-Qiang Lei?
Why did you come back?
[QIANG LEI] I decided to
pull back and fight here.
[CHU SHUI gasps]
This means that you're
not going with Xin?
No. I definitely
do not want to lead
those Lun Hu troops
directly to him.
Let Xin do it.
He can handle Lun Hu.
[LUN HU]
Oh?
Aren't you that
Fei Xin Force fellow?
That, um...
It's Xin.
And so, we meet once again.
[XIN] And this time,
you're not running away, Lun Hu.
[LUN HU laughs]
[LUN HU]
It's the other way around.
I won't do you the
favor of running.
[XIN]
What did you say?!
[LUN HU] You and
Mr. Spearman way over there?
You've both entirely
underestimated
your opponent's might, you see.
Did you really think that
the two of you
could even touch
someone of my grand stature?
[XIN snarls]
[WANG BEN growls]
Just quit messing around!
[XIN yells]
Is-Is that all you got?
[LUN HU]
I don't mind two at once,
but let's do this
more efficiently.
[LUN HU]
You look easier to deal with.
I'll save you for later.
So the first one to
take his lumps will be...
[WANG BEN gasps]
[growls]
Wang Ben, Sir!
Yaaah!
Uwaaugh!
[LUN HU]
Out of the way.
[WANG BEN growls]
[LUN HU]
Oh, wow!
You are plenty determined,
but your wounds have
taken the edge off now.
[WANG BEN]
Idiot.
[LUN HU]
Oh, he's fast!
Xin of the Fei Xin Force.
If that's what you're up to,
I've no choice.
[WANG BEN]
He's going for Xin!
[LUN HU]
I guess I'll start with you.
Stop it! Xin!
[XIN growls
[gasping]
[XIN] So who's
underestimating who, now?!
Lun Hu?
I will make darn
sure that you know
who the strongest one here is!
[MA LING growls] What's going on
with Lun Hu's main camp?
[HUANG GONG] The dust clouds
from all the fighting
make it impossible to see!
[LI CHONG]
The Le Hua Force has withdrawn,
but the Yu Feng and
Fei Xin Forces
have moved in instead!
Working with the
Le Hua Force, I assume.
And all three of them are now
acting independently, too!
They may be independent reserves
right now, but if they don't win
they'll have to answer for it!
[MENG AO laughs]
[MENG AO]
Well, naturally they would!
[MENG AO] And I'm one hundred
percent positive
no one knows that better
than those three themselves.
Wang Ben... Xin...
[yells]
[LUN HU]
This is real fighting.
[LUN HU] So, he's the type
who pours on the power
according to his
opponent's strength.
[LUN HU] I suppose everyone's
like that to some extent.
However, with this boy,
it truly is like night and day.
[yells]
[LUN HU]
And then,
there's the strange weight
of this one's blow.
[LUN HU]
Whoops!
Darn it, Wang Ben!
Get out of my way!
Get out of MY way!
He is all mine to kill!
[XIN]
Oh no, he isn't!
Lun Hu!
[gasping]
[gasping, laughing]
Is... he human? Im not sure!
[chuckles]
You are strong,
I'll give you that.
I'm starting to believe
you really did land a blow
on Wang Yi after all.
[LUN HU] I would rather you
didn't make light of that event.
Huh?
[LUN HU]
I mean,
you don't know what it's like
to be up against Wang Yi.
Or someone like him.
[XIN laughs]
[XIN]
Who are you trying to kid?
We know, all right.
Heck, the guy next to you
is related to General Wang Yi.
[LUN HU]
Related to--
And what about you?
Who am I? I'm the man
who got Wang Yi's poleax.
And his dying wish
as well, you see!
[XIN] And I'm the man who'll
surpass all those generals.
To be the greatest general that
all of history has ever had!
Wang Yi's poleax and
his dying wish?
And the greatest general
that history has ever had?
Aren't you thinking big?
Then you'll be surpassing
my lord General Lian Po as well.
[XIN]
Obviously! After I kill you,
I'm definitely going straight
for Lian Po, next!
[XIN grunts]
[LUN HU] I do wish you
wouldn't get so carried away.
After all, you see,
your lives will be ending here.
[XIN growls]