[NARRATOR] One day,
the Qin army units,
chiefly responsible
for successfully conquering
the Shanyang region,
and the civil servants,
who would oversee
the area's administration,
were gathered together
at Shanyang Castle.
What's the big deal?
Rounding us all up here
when it's too hot for this!
I believe they
must want to thank us
for conquering Shanyang.
But then why are
the civil servants here?
It's odd.
Meng Tian, sir,
have you heard anything?
Nothing.
It's... It's the Yu Feng Force!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[QIN SOLDIER 237B]
The Yu Feng Force that went off
to conquer Shanggui?
They're back now?
[QIN SOLDIER 237C] There's
their thousand-man commander,
Wang Ben!
[XIN] Ha! Oh, him.
Finally got around to
conquering his assigned post!
Took him long enough!
[laughs]
That's not it!
The Yu Feng Force
took care of the enemies
at their post right away,
then went around conquering
three other places.
What?
[gong sounds]
[XIN] What's with the guys
in black over there?
[gasps]
Wait, could it be?
Meng Tian, sir, isn't that--
Indeed.
The Imperial Headquarters,
a special convoy linked
to the Qin imperial court.
In other words,
we have important government
officials here today.
That is...
...Lord Changping, and Li Si!
[QIN SOLDIER 237A]
What? The top brass?
[QIN SOLDIER 237B]
The commander-in-chief
on the front lines?
[DIAO] Teacher...
[MENG TIAN]
And behind our teacher
is the head
administrator, Li Si.
I don't like
the looks of this.
[WANG BEN] So two of
Lü Buwei's Four Pillars
are here in Shanyang?
[LORD CHANGPING] Listen, now,
I hereby announce
Qin's plans for Shanyang.
From this very moment onwards,
Shanyang will be only known as
the Dong Commandery
of the great Kingdom of Qin.
[CROWD murmurs quietly]
Therefore,
ten thousand Qin residents
will be relocated here.
What? All of them?
The land will be governed
according to the laws of Qin
under head administrator Li Si
and his very capable hands.
Those who cannot
accept these changes
will be forcibly
removed at once,
even the current inhabitants.
[gasps]
[MENG TIAN] There it is.
We must all be fully aware
that the Dong Commandery
is now a Qin territory that
we must defend with our lives,
as it is our land now!
I have said my part.
What in the world is this?
An expression of grit.
Expression of what?
[NARRATOR] Kingdoms stole
territory from one another
throughout this era.
Often, the stolen territories
were re-stolen soon after.
[NARRATOR] The exception,
moving in residents and
making the area a commandery,
indicated a strong determination
never to relinquish it.
Making this a national policy
meant it would happen
the next time, as well.
In short, this proclamation
in the fifth year
of the future
Shi Huangdi's reign
was a declaration
of war to all kingdoms,
showing that Qin was serious
about expanding its territory.
[LI MU] I guess we'll
have to do this, then.
[KAINE] Li Mu, sir.
[LI MU]
General Gongsun Long...
...prepare to raise an army.
Sir!
[LI MU] Send word to Generals
Wan Ji and Li Bai, as well.
We'll enter war with
a hundred thousand troops.
So we are definitely violating
our alliance with Qin, then?
No. We will quite
simply attack Yan.
The kingdom of Yan?
Sir, you'll be
commanding general?
[LI MU] No.
It's about time we finally
gave him a good wake-up call.
[cracking, squishing]
[NARRATOR] It was some time
after Shanyang was reborn
as the Dong Commandery.
Xin and the Fei Xin Force
had been given
a brand new assignment
elsewhere now.
They were to guard Qin's border
with the large land of Chu,
an area always on high alert.
[yelling]
Calm down, Xin.
This is just what being
a border guard is all about.
[XIN] Oh man!
But those Chu guys are really
ticking me off, you know!
If they're gonna sneak over
every day to check up on us,
why not attack us already?
[WEI PING] I know
just how you feel, but--
Bad news!
What's happening, Yuan?
Did Chu make a move now?
[YUAN]
Xin, Chu won't be attacking
at a dreadful
time like this!
Then what exactly
is the bad news, then?
It's Pang Nuan!
He's back again!
What? What did you say?
[XIN] Pang Nuan is back
as commanding general?
[DIAO] Yes, definitely.
Just like in MNyáng,
he's the commanding general,
with Li Mu behind him actually
controlling the army, too.
All of their troops have already
met with the Yan army by now.
[WEI PING] All their troops?
[XIN] Pang Nuan...
[DIAO]
The Yan army has the same:
One hundred thousand troops.
[XIN] One hundred thousand
versus one hundred thousand?
That's a massive battle
to whip up out of nowhere.
[DIAO] Just as Qin
attacked Shanyang in Wei,
Zhao must want to strike
their own sworn enemies
while the alliance is
still in effect, you see.
[XIN] I get it.
Li Mu did say sometime before
that the Qin-Zhao alliance
would let them
focus on fighting Yan.
Hey, Diao!
What's this Yan
place like, anyway?
It's a riddle
wrapped up in an enigma.
Yan is far from Qin
on the eastern coast.
It has no battle
records over decades.
We don't know what kind
of commanders they have.
But they do have one great
general whose name is known
throughout the Middle Kingdom.
Say what?
Just who is this--this general?
Ju Xin.
Forty years ago,
when Qi had Yan cornered,
he and the late
war hero, Yue Yi,
pushed and pushed Qi
all the way back
to the brink of
ultimate destruction.
And he is one
of theirs, isn't he?
[DIAO] Yeah.
He was originally from Zhao.
Had he stayed,
he would have been
one of that era's Three Greats,
along with Lian Po.
One of the Three Greats
of Lian Po's era.
But Zhao's got Li Mu
and Pang Nuan, right?
That's one tangled-up battle,
all right.
[XIN] Yeah.
No matter who wins,
it isn't gonna be over
and done with that easily.
[NARRATOR] Word of the
sudden large-scale battle
between Zhao and Yan
rocked Xin deep down
to his very soul.
[NARRATOR] In the meantime,
the pointless standoff with Chu
would go on for three
more days, unfortunately.
I-Is it really
all true, then?
[DIAO] Well, actually,
we just got word ourselves that
the battle between Zhao
and Yan has been decided.
What'd you say?
One hundred thousand versus one
hundred thousand and it's done?
[DIAO]
That's not the half of it!
It just took one day.
It was over in exactly one day.
But how did it end, exactly?
[DIAO] Apparently Li Mu's
tactics had the Yan army
at Zhao's mercy at first.
However, then came
the great Ju Xin,
who saw through Li Mu's tactics
and launched a counterstrike.
But Zhao ultimately
had Pang Nuan to play.
[laughing]
Oh, he's one-handed?
[grunting]
[XIN] So it came down to
a duel between the generals,
and so Pang Nuan ultimately
beat Yan's general Ju Xin.
That guy is a total monster,
through and through!
Li Mu got his battle with Yan
in the end, just as he said.
Of course,
it's really far from over.
So they'll be coming
for Qin next, correct?
Exactly.
The alliance
remains in effect still,
but Zhao is getting
antsy right now.
It looks like Chu is
about to make a move.
You understand
why we were assigned
to guard the border now?
Something...
very evil could happen
at any moment, you see.
[XIN] Are we gonna
end up fighting Chu?
Maybe not right away,
I don't think.
But Chu is huge.
Their territory truly is
about the size
of six kingdoms combined.
One is as big as six?
It's that big?
[DIAO] To be honest,
even the size of their military
is just beyond all
our wildest imaginations.
But isn't that weird?
If they are that strong,
how come they haven't
attacked us, then?
Because their sheer size
also turns out to be
what holds them back.
Chu is so broad,
they share borders with Qin,
Han, Wei, Zhao and Qi,
a full five kingdoms.
[DIAO] They have no choice
but to be prudent
when it comes to invasions.
If they attack, they may
well be attacked themselves.
I understand.
So when you're that big,
you just can't move so fast.
That being said, though,
word is they have
the power ready
to crush any kingdom that does
decide to attack them anyway.
Which is why everyone's
been avoiding a full-on battle
with Chu all this time.
But so doesn't that
mean that we won't ever
battle with Chu, either, then?
[DIAO] No.
The Qin army headquarters
have drawn up a plan
and are working on a strategy
for a huge battle with Chu.
The Dong Commandery
proclamation is proof
that those plans
are coming along.
[WEI PING] Seriously?
[NARRATOR] However, the Chu army
made no discernible moves,
and Xin's squadron received
no new orders, either.
[yawning]
Hey, look up!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237B]
Shift's over, finally!
[XIN snoring]
[laughing softly]
[DIAO screams]
Hey why are you sleeping
over here, then?
And... And not only that,
but this, too--
Huh? Yeah, why am I...?
Was I sleepwalking?
I'm sorry.
"Sorry"?
I'll give you "sorry"!
[XIN yells]
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237C] Good
morning there, Tactician Diao!
Good morning!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237D]
[DIAO] It's been more
than three months
since I became the tactician
of the Fei Xin Force.
I'm pretty used to
the place already, I'd say.
Even though I'm a woman,
there's been no
funny business happening,
likely because
I'm Xin's good friend.
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237F]
Ah!
You gotta get on
my case first thing?
[DIAO] These guys are
foulmouthed and boorish,
exactly like Xin is.
But I'm comfortable
being here, regardless.
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237H]
Hey!
Bunch of dummies.
[laughs]
He Liao Diao.
Are there new orders?
Indeed, at last.
[NARRATOR] The Fei Xin Force
had guarded the Chu border
for three months when
they finally received
their new orders.
They were relieved of
their border-guard duties
and sent to the far east,
to a castle town named Dongjin.
[NARRATOR] Just as the
Qin army left the border,
so did the Chu army...
...almost as if
by common agreement.
[DIAO] This isn't good.
What's up there, Diao?
Already, we're someplace
that's not on the map.
This is unexplored
territory for the Qin Army.
I suppose that puts us
on the front lines
of an eastward invasion.
Proceed with caution.
The Wei, Zhao, and Chu borders
converge right here, you see.
We don't know
who might show up now.
[XIN] Okay.
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237J]
All troops, be on alert!
Proceed with caution!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237K]
We need more scouts!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237L] Keep an
eye on the brush to the left!
And with us here
right on the outside, guys.
You said you wanted
to be on the edges!
And found the middle too hot!
Just quit yammering at me
from the side like that, okay?
[rustling noise]
A-An enemy?
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
What? Was that Wei Ping?
Now, wait a second,
Wei Ping! Look there!
Huh?
[rustling noise]
Help me, please...
[QING] Hey! Guys!
[WEI PING] Get Xin!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 237M]
Watch for enemies!
You awake?
Drink this slowly.
[XIN] What happened?
Walled town in Xu.
Attacked by... Han army.
--Han.
Han, huh?
Someplace we haven't fought yet.
Do you know this Xu, Diao?
No, I've never heard of it.
Hey, Xu belongs to Chu,
or Wei, or Zhao?
Whose is it?
It is nobody's at all
because Xu is a country.
I come from Xu, you see.
I'm Xiu, that's my name.
What is he talking about?
But no such place exists!
No, wait a sec.
The Middle Kingdom
once consisted
of about over a
hundred kingdoms,
which merged over 500 years
into seven kingdoms.
But I've heard that
some tiny mountain kingdoms
avoided being absorbed
by those seven,
and could still be out there
as we speak, hanging on.
So this Xu place...
You're saying it's not
that far from here, then?
[XIU] Please. Please help.
They will kill
everyone in their sight.
Please, my... my mother.
Save her, please.
[XIU sobbing]
You sure this is okay,
acting alone?
But what about
Dongjin, then, huh?
Of course it's not okay.
It's a clear violation
of orders!
Lieutenant!
I know.
But this is one of the
better things about Xin.
You lead the way
from now on, okay?
I... will, then.
You got a problem
with this, Diao?
[DIAO] Of course I don't.
[NARRATOR] Here, our story will
take a step backward in time,
its stage shifting to the
Qin capital, Xianyang.
The Fei Xin Force
had just taken on guard duty
at the Chu border,
and something big
was happening in Xianyang.
[CIVIL SERVANT 237A]
Report!
The houses of Gao Li and Lin
now side with
Lü Buwei's faction!
[CIVIL SERVANT 237B]
As does the Yue Zhuo clan!
[CIVIL SERVANT 237C] Yu Bai Shi
went from a neutral position
to side with the minister!
Hmm...
I expected this, and yet...
It has escalated so fast.
[NARRATOR]
When Lü Buwei's relationship
with the Queen Dowager
came to light,
his faction lost
some of its power.
Now, however, they
were suddenly starting to rally.
Meanwhile, powerful
allies left Zheng's side
one after another quite rapidly.
Behind all of this were the
active machinations of Lü Buwei.
[NARRATOR] He then sent out
a man to the Queen Dowager--
A man she found infatuating.
[NARRATOR] In this way,
Lü Buwei maintained a
relationship with her in secret
while riding out their scandal.
Consequently, his ties
to the Inner Palace
grew stronger than ever before.
[footsteps approaching]
[LÜ BUWEI]
Oh, it's you, Li Si!
For you to somehow
regain so much power
as you have right now,
while Lord Changping and I
were both away for awhile,
I am truly astonished.
[chuckles]
[LI SI] And yet,
the deep involvement
of the Inner Palace's power
could well be considered
a double-edged sword.
What is this?
You're angry I made my move
without telling you?
This is about nothing
so childish as that.
[laughs]
Forgive me, forgive me.
In my own way I meant
only to be mindful
of how very busy you are.
That, and well, this was also
just desserts in a fun way.
But enough of that.
It's settled now.
Now, to let out some
of my pent-up frustrations.
Li Si?
[LI SI] Sir.
I think it's time to
graduate from being a minister.
Sir?
[NARRATOR]
A short while later,
Lü Buwei moved above
his post as minister
to become Chancellor of State.
This was the highest
office possible,
with only the king
right above it.
[NARRATOR] Although the
position had always been vacant,
Lü Buwei used his faction's
might to claim it for himself.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
Zheng and his court
could not stop this outrage.
[CIVIL SERVANT 237A groans]
And after we'd come so far!
Thanks to the
Inner Palace's power,
we'll soon be unable to hold
back Lü Buwei's faction.
[CIVIL SERVANT 237B]
Now I suppose we'll have to
start all over again from the--
[ZHENG] We cannot!
If we don't dig in
our heels right here,
our chance at victory
will be delayed again.
We must keep pace
with their power,
regardless of what
this may entail!
But we have no more
means at our disposal,
my Lord.
[SI SHI] Your Highness?
[ZHENG] Follow me.
Is... Is this the--
No way!
[SI SHI] Your Highness!
Come, now.
Open it.
[QIN SOLDIER 237D]
Your Highness!
[ZHENG]
It's been a while...
...Cheng Jiao.