[XIANG] And so after
all of that, what happened?
[ZHENG] I was put onto the
marketeers' horse cart.
But I have few memories
of what happened around then.
I dreamt.
[gasps]
Horrible dreams
I never had before.
[wind blows, grass rustling]
[ZHENG] Huh?
[HALLUCINATION laughing]
--[ZHENG gasping]
--[HALLUCINATION laughing]
[ZHENG]
Huh? Huh?!
[HALLUCINATION]
Who's gonna be the king now?
--[ZHENG] Uuuh!
--[HALLUCINATION laughing]
[ZHENG] Eeh!
[HALLUCINATION]
Who's gonna be the king?
Who is it?
[yells]
[horses neigh]
You're awake now finally.
Is it you?
[ZI XIA] Hm.
[gasps]
[ZHENG] Uuuh...
[yells, screams]
--[DAO JIAN] What's wrong?
--[ZHENG screaming]
Please! Please,
calm yourself, my lord!
You must be frightened
to wake up
and find yourself
on a horse cart.
But I-I can explain.
Please, let me explain!
Calm yourself
my lord, please!
[DAO JIAN]
And that's where we stand.
We are currently plotting
your mother's return
by a different route.
Do not worry.
You will surely be
reunited in Xianyang.
We still have a way
to go before the gate.
Why don't you just rest
for a little while longer.
[DAO JIAN]
Hm.
And you can reach the gate
for sure like this, then?
[ZI XIA]
It's the best way.
We're taking our usual road
to avoid arousing suspicion.
This road will pass through
five different gates
on our way out of Zhao.
Once we're past those,
we'll be cleared for Qin.
Hmmm. Five you say?
We--we were prepared for this,
but you do have
a way to get us past
the inspectors, am I right?
Oh come on now.
Just leave that to us.
We're not amateurs.
So there're five gates
till Qin from now.
[ZI XIA]
No need to worry at all.
Trust me, Zi Xia
will get you to Qin
safe and sound. You will see.
Hm?
Is this real? At all?
[ZI XIA]
Of course it is real.
[ZHAO SOLDIERS,
MERCHANTS chatter]
--[eerie music plays]
--[chattering continues]
[eerie music continues]
[TIAN CI grunts]
[DAO JIAN gasps,
DAN YUAN grunts]
All right, here we go!
There is an empty rice bundle.
Lord Zheng, you go in there.
I will take
the reins from now on,
just follow my lead.
[CIVIL SERVANT 208A]
Next! And hurry it up!
C'mon! Next!
What kind of cargo is this?
Aren't these gold coins?
Grab him right now!
Huh? No!
It's not--please, don't! No!
[whimpers]
[CIVIL SERVANT 208A]
All right, next!
[CIVIL SERVANT 208A grunts]
[ZI XIA]
Thanks again!
Yep! Go on through now!
[CIVIL SERVANT 208A]
Okay, next!
[DAO JIAN] Hmmm.
Wh-What was all that?
That's all it takes
to pass a gate?
Us black marketeers
deal in illegal goods,
you understand me?
We must always, always be
prepared for everything.
[TIAN CI, DAN YUAN sigh]
[YA MEN]
Don't get the wrong idea.
Not all black marketeers
can slip through
just like that, like us.
She can because she's Zi Xia.
After she took over,
our business grew to easily
twice the size
as it was before.
[laughs]
Just good business sense!
[DAO JIAN] Lü Buwei
recommended these youngsters
so fiercely.
Actually, I had my doubts,
but now, I understand.
[ZI XIA] Now that I
get a good look at him,
he's just a mess of bruises.
It must be a daily thing.
[ZHENG breathes shakily]
[ZI XIA]
Lord Zheng?
[ZHENG breathes shakily]
[GHOSTS] Can't breathe.
Can't breathe. The pain.
Can't breathe.
Can't breathe. Can't breathe.
[GHOST 208A] Don't go.
We won't let you, Zheng.
Can't breathe.
[GHOST 208C]
As if we'd let you go.
[GHOST 208D]
To the depths of the earth.
The depths of the earth.
[ZHENG] Shut up! I had
nothing to do with Changping!
I'm going back to Qin!
[HALLUCINATION]
Doing what? To Qin?
Who is? Who is?
Doing what? Going back?
Back to Qin and then what?
[laughs intensely]
You're kidding, right?
[HALLUCINATION]
After all, you're already--
[ZHENG screaming]
[DAO JIAN]
What happened?
[YA MEN]
Not again!
--[ZHENG panting]
--[ZI XIA] Lord Zheng!
[panting]
[DAO JIAN] So Lord Zheng
is acting strange?
[ZI XIA] Mm.
But anyone can be
tormented by dreams.
It's normal.
He's likely
still a bit confused
by his sudden change
in circumstances.
But maybe--
Regardless, we must first
of all escape Zhao safely.
And only that, Zi Xia.
[ZI XIA sighs]
[DAO JIAN]
Another gate.
Into the bundle, Lord Zheng.
[ZI XIA] So getting out
of Zhao comes first, hm?
That's true, but--
[horses neigh]
[ZHAO SOLDIERS murmur]
[chuckles]
Hey, that's nice!
My shift's finally
over in about...
[MAO YING]
Oh, Zi Xia! Zi Xia!
It's been so long!
You look so well,
dear Mao Ying.
I haven't seen you
around here lately.
You weren't possibly avoiding
me now, were you, my dear?
I would never do that!
[laughs] Why don't you
rest here a while?
I'll get you some tea.
[ZI XIA] I'd love to,
but we're in a bit of a hurry.
Too bad! Spend some time
with me for once!
Or I will just order
a cargo inspection
and make you stay here
against your will!
[ZI XIA] I certainly
wouldn't want you to do that.
But there are so many
customers of mine
waiting for their goods, so
let's have that tea another--
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
--[ZI XIA] Hey!
--[ZHAO SOLDIER 208D] Uh.
[MAO YING] Hey! Wh-What do
you think you're doing?
[ZHAO SOLDIER 208D]
Me? Doing some test shots!
Bought this bow yesterday and
thought I'd try it out now.
[ZI XIA] Cut that out.
It's not a joke!
Don't be angry, Zi Xia!
The thing is,
this guy's brand-new,
and he doesn't know
the protocol!
[ZI XIA grunts]
[MAO YING] Uh-guh-guh!
G-Go on, now.
[ZI XIA]
Mm.
Blood?
[ZI XIA] I haven't heard
any screams or whimpers
ever since we left the gate.
Has he passed out?
Or is he--
Lord Zheng!
Pull it out. I can't.
Ugh!
My lord Zheng!
You are all right
and you endured that without
even uttering a single word!
[ZI XIA]
Hang on.
What child wouldn't cry
as an arrow pierces his arm?
H-H-Here I go.
[ZI XIA] What human
wouldn't even blink an eye
as that arrow is
pulled from his arm?
What's with this child?
[ZI XIA] Hardship in your
younger years really can
suppress your emotions.
We war orphans were the same
until our adopted
father took us in.
But, to not budge
after taking an arrow?
That goes beyond
mere emotions, I'd say.
The boy is clearly not normal.
Something's definitely going on,
in his body and mind.
[NARRATOR] Four days after
Zi Xia and crew left Handan,
at last they arrived at the
fifth and final gate, Lü Gan.
Once past Lü Gan,
it was a half-day's
distance to the border
between Qin and Zhao.
[ZI XIA]
Is something wrong?
The moon's out once again.
True, that it is.
I like your eyes when you're
looking at the moon,
Lord Zheng.
[ZHENG] Sometimes I can't
tell dream from reality.
That must be
really difficult for you.
Just remember that
when I'm right here,
it's all very real.
--[ZHENG] Zi Xia.
--[ZI XIA] Huh?
Do you really think I'll
be able to go back to Qin?
It's like I said before,
I'm taking you back. Period.
[CIVIL SERVANTS,
ZHAO SOLDIERS chatter]
[CIVIL SERVANT 208B]
You may pass!
Hang on there, now!
[DAO JIAN]
Huh?
[CIVIL SERVANT 208C]
What's going on, Zi Xia?
I don't recognize
half these people!
Who are they, huh?
We were short a few,
so I just hired them
in a village.
Oh well, they may be older
but they're of no use to me!
In fact they're just
weighing me down.
I'll just leave them here,
and you can put them
on the next cart out.
Aah. Ugh!
Oh fine, fine! Get outta
the way! Goodbye!
[DAN YUAN huffs]
That... was... a close one!
Uuh!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 208F]
A smoke signal!
It's the signal for
an emergency lockdown!
Close the gate!
[TIAN CI gasps]
The gate's been shut!
Have they found out
about Lord Zheng?
M-Made it by a hair.
[laughs]
We did it! We made it in time!
Past all, every single gate!
Now we can finally
get back to Qin!
[laughs]
[JIANG ZHANG] This is no
time for rejoicing!
If they were to
find out about Zheng,
they will be after us all!
With their whole army!
They're quite right.
No need for
disguises right now.
We'll find a place
to dump our cargo,
then it's full speed ahead!
The Zhao cavalry
is fast, gentlemen!
[DAO JIAN] Our rendezvous
point is just ahead.
There should already be
troops there waiting for us.
No signs that
we're being followed.
We can go through!
Zi Xia, you really
did save us all.
Things would never
have gone this smoothly
without your help.
We thank you!
[ZI XIA]
Saved you all?
[ZI XIA] But have I truly
saved this poor child?
[sighs]
I promise you'll be
home soon, Lord Zheng.
Just think, once you
become the king,
you'll be in the lap
of pure and genuine luxury!
If I were ten years
younger or so,
I could maybe even
be your wife.
Aah! Living the
high life with you!
Maybe "wife"'s too much.
Concubine? Or servant?
[giggles]
[ZI XIA] Lord Zheng?
Are you all right?
Lord Zheng? Lord Zheng?
--[HALLUCINATION] Wait.
--[ZHENG gasps]
[HALLUCINATION]
Just. Hang on.
Zheng. Zheng.
Who's gonna be the king now?
Who's gonna be the king?
Who is it?
Zheng. Zheng. Zheng.
[ZHENG gasping]
[HALLUCINATION]
Going back to Qin to be king?
You must be dreaming.
[laughs]
Enough of this nonsense,
get off the cart.
You can't possibly go to Qin.
Shut up now!
Lord Zheng?
What's the matter?
Lord Zheng!
[HALLUCINATION]
Who exactly will celebrate
your homecoming?
Who will? Your father?
Don't make me laugh.
He tossed you aside
seven years ago
when he came back to Qin,
am I correct?
Even your own mother
has shunned you as well.
If it weren't for you,
then she could have
gone back to being
a lady of Zhao!
If it weren't for you.
Stop! Stop it! Stop!
[ZI XIA] Zheng!
What's wrong Lord Zheng?
[HALLUCINATION laughs]
Discarded by your father
and shunned by your mother.
If you go back now
you'll only be
a nuisance to them all.
There's no real place for you
in Qin and you know it.
But the biggest problem
still is always you.
Your mind and
your body are so bizarre.
He-heh. A normal person
isn't so blasé
when he's shot with an arrow--
a sane person, that is!
You're smart so you
must have realized long ago,
someone like you could
never ever actually be king!
So, how long are you
going to stay on that cart?
Get down off there now!
[ZHENG yelling]
[JIANG ZHANG]
Zheng's fallen off!
--[TIAN CI] What?
--[DAO JIAN] Stop!
[BOTH whinny]
[ZI XIA]
I'll get him!
Everyone else wait there!
[YA MEN]
Zi Xia!
Man. What is really going on?
[JIANG ZHANG]
Like I know?
That little brat.
We are running out
of time here!
[ZI XIA]
Lord Zheng!
[ZHENG]
Stay back!
I... I can't go back to Qin.
What do you mean?
But you'll be there so soon.
[ZHENG] I can't.
There's a reason!
[ZHENG gasps]
--[squelch]
--[ZI XIA] Aah!
What are you doing?
Are you in your right mind?
There's no pain at all!
Huh?
And it is
not just the pain.
It's the flavors. The smells.
The heat, and even the cold.
I feel nothing,
nothing at all.
I don't understand.
That just can't be true.
[ZHENG] Uh!
Someone like that
could never be king.
But how can this be?
Ever since I can remember,
I knew I was royalty,
and my heart trembled
with the sheer honor of it.
But one step outside,
and I was in the middle
of a hostile land.
Worse, the land whose
400 thousand soldiers
Qin had slaughtered
at Changping.
[ZHENG]
The animosity toward Qin
rained down upon me
without mercy.
While enduring that
overwhelming violence,
I saw the situation in which
I had been placed at birth,
and despaired.
As the days of
abuse continued,
my heart closed more tightly,
until eventually,
I could feel nothing at all.
[ZI XIA]
How awful.
To think, he was driven
to such intense extremes.
And to think...
...this child,
this prince of Qin,
was born in Zhao.
Because of that ill fortune
wholly beyond his control...
...he was made to
bear the brunt of
their Changping grudge.
A child not yet ten,
to whom no one
held out a helping hand,
left all alone.
This whole time.
--[ZI XIA] You can be king!
--[ZHENG gasps]
[ZI XIA] I'll make sure
of it. I promise.
If you have no pain,
I will just feel it for you!
Flavors, smells, all of it!
But, it's all right.
I really think
you can feel just fine.
That night, weren't we
both sitting there
moved by the moon's pure glow?
It's all right.
I'm with you now.
We'll go back to Qin together.
[ZHENG inhales deeply]
[MERCHANT 208B]
This is ridiculous!
[MERCHANT 208C]
I've got negotiating to do!
[MERCHANT 208D] The gate's
closed? Since when?
[MERCHANT 208E]
Who's responsible for this?
[MERCHANT 208F]
It's the Yellow Pennant!
Those are the king's horses!
[MERCHANT 208G]
What?
[ZHAO HORSEMAN 208A]
Who's in charge here?
Show yourself! Now!
[CIVIL SERVANT 208C] It is I.
What is this concerning?
Did a merchant named
Zi Xia pass through here?
Yes, about twelve hours ago.
[ZHAO HORSEMAN 208A]
Open the gate at once!
[MERCHANT 208H]
The cavalry!
[MERCHANT 208I]
Wow!
[MERCHANT 208J] Is there
a battle on the way?
[CIVIL SERVANT 208C]
That Zi Xia.
What's she done now?
[ZI XIA]
Come.
[ZHENG] Uuh.
[groans]
Lord Zheng!
Tell me, are you all right?
[HALLUCINATION]
What's with her?
Zheng's not going back.
You can't have him.
We'll take him away.
To the depths
of the earth with us.
Don't meddle, woman.
Or we'll take you, too.
Take you to
the depths of the earth.
Get away from me!
The ghosts who possess me
are after you, Zi Xia!
Ghosts, you say?
[gasps]
[GHOSTS moaning]
[ZI XIA quavered breathing]
[HALLUCINATION laughs]
[ZHENG]
It's no use, Zi Xia.
There is--there is no
escaping them now.
[ZI XIA grunts]
[GHOSTS moaning]
Pull yourself together!
There's no such
thing as ghosts!
None of that is real!
There's no one here
with you but me!
Those are all just illusions!
[HALLUCINATION screams]
[GHOSTS moan]
♪
--[ZI XIA sighs]
--[ZHENG] Mmnn.
[ZHENG] So warm.
That's right.
This is new.
This warmth here.
It's the first time
I've ever had anyone...
...hold me like this.