[NARRATOR]
In the middle of a fierce battle
between Qin and Wei,
they meet again:
Xin and Lun Hu.
Which of them will be
able to overcome his limits
and have his own way
in the end?
Their blistering-hot emotions
truly are making sparks fly!
[XIN 'Cause right now,
he won't get up again.
No way could he get... up...
Lun Hu, you rat!
Well, my lord is
waiting for me.
I can't possibly
lose here now.
I simply cannot lose now.
Because I am the heaven-sent
Sword of Lian Po, you see.
[XIN gasps]
[XIN]
Heaven--
[LUN HU]
Only a handful of generals.
are adored by the heavens.
It was destiny.
For my lord to have
rescued me like he did,
from the very brink of death.
It was written in the stars.
[XIN]
Rescued? By Lian Po?
[LUN HU] It started as an
all-too-common tale.
A tiny village, caught up
in the horrors of war.
Its inhabitants all dead.
But my little sister and I
managed to survive, somehow,
Only to wait
death by starvation.
[LUN HU] I honestly don't recall
how many days went by.
[LUN HU]
And then,
I met him.
There's a little boy survivor.
Give him water and
something to eat.
[LIAN PO UNDERLING A]
Sir.
I am grateful, but please,
first, my little sister.
Help her please, sir.
I can't help her.
[gasps]
[LUN HU] Heaven help me,
I hadn't noticed until then:
My sister had long since
passed away next to me.
[LUN HU laughs]
[LUN HU] That part about my
sister wasn't relevant.
Still, the great
general Lian Po
had saved my life.
Do you think
it was coincidence?
Someone like me, with my
innate talent for warfare
in that setting of need,
and Lian Po?
A genius that is then saved
by a great military genius?
It's like Xuan Feng
always used to say,
only a handful of generals are
adored by the heavens, you see.
Lian Po truly
was one of them,
and the heavens
introduced him to me,
his very own sword.
Therefore, I--
I cannot lose, not here
and not right now--
[XIN]
It's all lies!
To hear you say that everything
simply comes down
to something as
intangible as fate!
That isn't it!
We're fighting here!
All of us, on our own two feet!
Even the person you are today is
the result of risking your life
and fighting your butt off
to be Lian Po's sword!
But, I know how important
chance encounters can be.
I mean, you ran into
Lian Po and I, later on,
I met and grew up
with a man who,
without a shadow of a doubt,
would've been even greater
than Lian Po.
[gasping]
Wei Ping!
Uh-huh.
[WEI PING]
Piao!
I'm lucky that he
gave me a dream.
And he died way too soon.
Instead, I met someone else,
someone even more incredible.
[XIN]
Then, absolutely every single
of my irreplaceable allies,
who'd come and gone.
And the person
who'd be the sensible
guidepost along my path.
Maybe you'd say
that isn't coincidence,
and maybe you're correct.
But I can't see some
fickle heaven and hand it in!
I'm simply carrying my
memories of all those people
along with me in my path!
Lun Hu!
Fighting you has given me
the strength to keep going on!
[laughs]
Well said.
So, since you're the
one who's going to die.
[grunting]
[LUN HU]
You are definitely right, Xin.
That first meeting is
down to fate.
But the rest is up to us.
[LUN HU] However, heaven does
make miracles happen, sometimes.
[LUN HU]
My lord...
Wang Yi has died,
then the formidable
Li Mu appeared,
and a youthful power
is coming into bud
in the Qin army right now.
I suppose this age is moving
into the next war-torn era.
[LUN HU]
In fact,
my duties perhaps may have
come to an end, finally,
when my lord went into exile
and left the front lines.
[LUN HU] But still,
my fighting here today
may well be according
to divine plan.
You really were strong,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force.
[XIN growls]
[LUN HU]
Xin.
In time, you too...
[LUN HU screams]
Lun Hu, you were one
incredibly tricky enemy,
set for death a
thousand times.
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
Finally! He won!
He defeated Lun Hu!
One of Lian Po's
Big Four is no more!
So that means--
Right!
We got the general's
head that we needed,
that miserable little rat!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
Wang Ben, sir, it's--
[WANG BEN]
I hear it.
[LUN HU SOLDIER A]
Lun Hu, sir!
[LUN HU SOLDIER B]
Darn!
The enemy--Lun Hu's troops!
[FORMER GUO BEI SOLDIER A]
Leave them to us, now!
[FORMER GUO BEI SOLDIER B]
Guo Bei's men
will most definitely give them a
heck of a send-off!
[gasps] Xin! Hurry please,
and take his head!
You've got to parade it
right here so people know!
[XIN]
Lun Hu.
[YUAN]
Xin.
There's no need for that now!
The truth will just get out!
Spread the word that
Commander Xin
has defeated the enemy
general Lun Hu!
[FEI XIN FORCE yelling]
[YUAN]
How's Lieutenant Chu Shui?
I believe his wound
doesn't look fatal!
We just need to stop
the bleeding now!
That's good!
Hey, Wei Ping?
Yeah.
It does looks like
everything worked out
all right for us, anyway.
Huh? What is wrong,
Long Chuan?
Something's a little off.
Back where we left Lieutenant
Qiang Lei and the others--
there's no sign of anyone.
[WEI SOLDIER B laughs]
Did you honestly
think this was over?!
You bunch of simpletons!
General Lun Hu had a
separate army of reserves,
that was moving
alongside this main unit!
That way we could strike
where there were fewer troops
while you were all concentrated
here, you naive idiots!
Huh? What's that?
If that's where you
left your little buddies,
they are all definitely being
wiped out right about now!
[laughs]
Those reserves
are the private army of
General Jie Zifang,
and as you know,
they're 500 strong!
[laughs]
I have had enough of
this foolishness now!
Long Chuan! Look for them!
You can't see them?
I-In this rain,
this far away?
No, Xin!
[SONG ZUO]
We're coming too!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
You dumb invaders.
Serves you right!
[XIN]
Qiang Lei.
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
Qiang Lei!
[NARRATOR] At this time,
it was about one hour
before Xin claimed
Lun Hu's head.
Qiang Lei and 200 soldiers
had been left at the rear.
What's up
with the commander?
I think he's going
one-on-one with Lun Hu,
but it's hard
to tell from here.
Huh?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[QIANG LEI]
What is that about?
A-A wave of foes!
And they're huge!
The infantry's scattering
like so many twigs!
Incoming!
[FOOT SOLDIER B]
What's the hold up, reserves?
Get in here and help us!
Hurry up!
But we don't have a remote
chance at stopping that!
You fool! What are you saying?
That's exactly what
us reserves are here for!
[WOUNDED SOLDIER C]
B-but.
[WOUNDED SOLDIER D]
Let's go!
[QIANG LEI]
We shouldn't be going.
With these troops,
and me like this...
...we can't stop them.
Hurry up now, Fei Xin Force!
Lieutenant!
[WOUNDED SOLDIERS yelling]
[QIANG LEI]
Xiang...
[QIANG LEI] I won't be able to
avenge my sister if I'm dead.
If we go through,
we're just as good as dead!
Shouldn't we just--
Don't say that nonsense!
You're from the Fei Xin Force!
Our beloved commander is risking
his life in battle as we speak!
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[QIANG LEI]
I'm sorry, Xiang.
Right now, I'm a lieutenant
of the Fei Xin Force.
Come on!
[WOUNDED SOLDIERS shouting]
[QIANG LEI] Darn it!
Have I always been this stupid?
[QIANG XIANG]
You must be careful, Qiang Lei.
Spend time with fools and
you'll wind up one yourself.
[QIANG LEI]
That explains it.
[WOUNDED SOLDIER A]
Lieutenant Qiang Lei...
...is smiling?
[yelling, screaming]
[WEI PING]
They're all... dead now...
[TIAN YONG]
Darnit!
Where's Lieutenant
Qiang Lei and the rest?
[QU HAI]
Commander!
[XIN]
Huh?
He's still got life in him!
He's from my old squad!
So what happened here?
I-I'm sorry.
They were much too strong.
We were helpless.
But...
Lieutenant Qiang Lei, in spite
of his own deep pain, he...
...he alone did...
Qiang Lei, you say?
[TAI GUAN] Apologies.
We were utterly useless.
They were just... too terrible.
The lieutenant, the lieutenant--
[QIANG LEI
This is... the only home I have.
To go back to now...
That's why...
I'm leaving when this battle--
[QIANG LEI]
--is finally over and done with.
I don't know how many months,
how many years it will take,
but I will have my revenge.
[QIANG LEI] And once I have,
when I come back
here, finally then...
[XIN] Cut it out.
This isn't funny Qiang Lei.
[QIANG LEI]
...I think I should be
able to move forward,
with you guys
in the Fei Xin Force,
you'll all be my home.
[XIN] What is she doing?
That colossal idiot!
Where are you, Qiang Lei?!
[XIN gasps]
Oh no! A bunch of
massive soldiers over here.
Are these Jie
Zifang's men, then?
[WEI PING]
And all of 'em wiped out.
What on earth?
Not... human...
[gasps]
Th-That thing is not human.
[QIANG LEI]
Oh.
It's just you.
[XIN]
Qiang Lei!
What are you, nuts?!
How could you let things
get this bad?!
How are you going to
avenge your sister
if you're just dead?
How mean. I did
the best that I could.
Are you done... with your thing?
[XIN]
It's done.
I killed Lun Hu and everything.
[QIANG LEI]
I see...
Xin?
[QIANG LEI]
Let me go. Your stupid spreads.
[XIN]
Be quiet!
[FOOT SOLDIER C] Is Lieutenant
Qiang Lei really all right?
Yeah, he's over here!
You mean to say that he
killed these brutes alone?
He is certainly not a human.
There he is!
[FOOT SOLDIER D] What are the
sergeant and the rest
doing over there?
[TIAN YONG]
No way...
[YUAN]
It can't be...
[WEI PING]
Q-Qiang Lei...
...is a woman?
What is the meaning of this?
Don't tell us that you knew
that Qiang Lei was a woman!
[TIAN YONG]
Did the cat get your tongue?
[WEI PING]
How long did you know?
[FEI XIN FORCE yelling]
[QU HAI]
You need to explain!
[TIAN YQU]
Quit your yelping, everyone!
[gasping]
[TIAN YQU] How many times did
Qiang Lei save your skins, huh?
What could it possibly matter
at this stage if she's a woman?!
Think about it for a minute,
mastering such sword
skills with her female body,
mingling with men on
the battlefield.
What a massive burden
she must bear!
[XIN]
You got it backwards.
Turns out she's
empty inside, you see.
There was a real harsh rule,
back where she grew up.
And under that rule,
she fully intended to die for
the big sister she grew up with.
[XIN] But in the end,
her sister was killed,
and she survived
through real adversity.
[XIN] Ever since then,
she's been on a journey
to avenge her sister.
For someone like her,
that's all there is.
Getting revenge was
her only purpose in life.
Certainly, she might've
planned on dying
as soon as she got that
revenge of hers.
Lately, she really had been
changing, little by little.
Moving from the revenge.
Beyond it, even.
Finding a place where
she could be at last:
[XIN]
The Fei Xin Force.
[XIN] Now I'm not going to
tell you to pretend
you didn't notice.
Just treat her the same
as always, okay?
After all,
she's a really
amazing friend to have.
It's gonna be
all right, Xin, sir.
Tian YRu is quite right:
Qiang Lei is Qiang Lei,
like always.
This doesn't change anything.
[WEI PING]
But something has to change!
Wei Ping.
One day the enemy is bound to
find out she's really a woman!
Soon, there will be guys
starting to come after her,
and if they capture her,
they'll do awful things to her!
We gotta make sure
that doesn't happen.
We are definitely major
weaklings compared to Qiang Lei,
but we gotta start keeping
her safe from harm,
little by little, you guys!
That about sums it up.
Ha! Since when did
Wei Ping make any sense?
Heck, I think you are the one
who needed the
most saving of all!
[WEI PING gasps]
You and your posing!
[WEI PING]
Oh, be quiet!
[FEI XIN FORCE laughs]
[LONG YQU]
Toughen up, will you, Wei Ping?
[WEI PING]
Be quiet, I said!
[XIN]
Glad you're here, Qiang Lei.
[LU YAN] Us old-timers will tend
to Lieutenant Qiang Lei
and her needs from now on,
don't you worry.
[XIN]
Thanks, Lu Yan.
[WEI PING] You'll need
some attention too, Xin.
[XIN]
Yeah.
--Ow!
--Can you stand?
Just stop the bleeding on
my leg right now.
And bring me a horse,
immediately.
Hey, Yuan!
How's their army look?
Sir, their momentum
has slowed down now,
with word of Lun Hu's death,
but they haven't fallen
completely yet.
probably because Lun Hu
was just not a native born
Wei general, and because an
invaded people's morale
is not easily broken.
But we do have the upper hand.
[YUAN]
For now.
[XIN] Sorry Yuan,
can you take over for me?
[YUAN gasps]
Xin, you can't mean...
Yeah.
There's one last place
I got to go now.