Is-Is this the--
No way...
[SI SHI]
Your Highness!
Come now.
Open it.
[QIN SOLDIER 237D]
Your Highness!
It's been a while,
Cheng Jiao.
[CHENG JIAO chuckles]
So you've come, Ying Zheng.
You kept ignoring my proposals
and kept me trapped inside here
in this musty old castle
all of this time.
Proposals?
From Cheng Jiao?
You will help me
overthrow Lü Buwei.
In return, I shall release
all your sidekicks
imprisoned here with you now.
That has always been the offer
you had put before me,
correct, Cheng Jiao?
Stop, Your Highness!
Releasing an entire faction
that still holds so
much power is too risky!
[CHENG JIAO]
Be quiet, Lord Changwen.
I am the king's
younger half-brother
and pureblood royalty, too.
You just have no right
to constrain what
I do or do not.
Your Highness.
[ZHENG]
Cheng Jiao.
I have no intention
of forgiving you
for inciting a rebellion,
all for some
self-righteous ideal.
[ZHENG]
However, the situation is grave,
and time is of the essence, now.
Our only chance to drive a wedge
into Lü Buwei's power is now.
You must lend me your
power, Cheng Jiao!
[CHENG JIAO sighs]
[CHENG JIAO] Don't look down
on me and order me around.
This is a parity bargain
with both parties
seeking to benefit.
Simply shut your mouth
and let us go now.
[CHENG JIAO]
There's a familiar face.
One time and on my command
you went right after
Ying Zheng's head,
and now you serve
as his advisor.
[SI SHI grunts]
Wow, look how very far
you've come now, Si Shi.
You can relax, Lord Changwen.
I'm not about to up
and break my promise.
[LORD CHANGWEN grunts]
I can't forgive Zheng,
who sits on the royal throne
despite the fact that he is
undoubtedly of impure blood,
but more so, I cannot abide
that foreign merchant
rising above his station
to occupy a place of power!
It is my duty as royalty
to set the kingdom right.
Just watch me.
I shall use my network
of royal disciples now,
to gather up the necessary power
to match that dumb cur!
[LORD CHANGWEN, SI SHI gasp]
[ZHENG]
You misunderstand, Cheng Jiao.
[CHENG JIAO]
Hm?
I am not just looking to match
Lü Buwei's sheer power.
I mean to far surpass it!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
I don't care for
their secret motives,
or if their help starts
and ends with this.
You see,
bring as many people as you can
to our side in the
next seven days!
In the next seven days?
What do you mean?
[ZHENG]
I mean that Jie Shi colluded
with you in sparking
the rebellion.
His court spot's been
open since his death.
With Lü Buwei having
swiftly ascended
to Chancellor of State,
it left both
minister seats free.
However, those
seats will be filled
by Lü Buwei's men,
Lord Changping and Li Si.
That won't be official
for seven days.
[gasps]
[SI SHI]
It can't be!
Ying Zheng, you little--
[ZHENG]
Lord Changwen!
Sire!
Your taking on a
civil service position
to assist me
is now more
meaningful than ever.
Your Highness.
[ZHENG] We will use Lü Buwei's
Chancellor of State
power-grab against him,
and take this chance to
claim power for ourselves!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHENG JIAO]
Payback on this loan
will be pricey, Ying Zheng.
[ZHENG]
Save your nonsense.
You know your debt
to me is far greater.
[NARRATOR] Here, our story
returns in time and place
to the Fei Xin Force,
approaching the
tiny country of Xu
under attack by the Han army.
We almost there?
Is this Xu place you
ran from nearby?
It is.
[gasps]
[XIN gasps]
[FEI XIN FORCE gasping]
Awful.
These are all children here.
Every single one of them.
What on Earth
happened over here?
The people of Xu tried
to get their children out.
But when the Han
army found them...
So the only one to
escape was this kid.
[YUAN, CHU SHUI gasp]
If it's bad here,
what must it be like inside?
My mom... in the inner fortress.
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
[explosion thunders]
[gasps]
[SOLIDERS gasp]
[XIN]
Diao! What's that?
Sounds like the Han army
trying to break down
the inner fortress
door right now.
Which means that
we can still make it.
[DIAO]
Yeah!
Got a plan?
Given the size of
the place before us,
there are about
2,000 Han troops.
They beat us in numbers,
but if we pull off
a surprise attack,
we could win!
Catch them off guard,
and take them all at once!
[XIN]
Got it!
Xiu, wait here.
We're gonna save your mom,
and all the rest too.
Thanks, mister.
Come on! Let's do this, men!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
[MA GUAN]
Get that door open!
When that's finally done,
all we gotta do is take
care of whoever's inside!
[HAN SOLDIERS grunting]
[XU MEN grunting]
It's done, Chief Elder!
It can't hold out much longer!
Chief Elder!
[WOMAN]
What's gonna happen?
[CHIEF ELDER]
So, this is it.
[XU MAN 238A]
Chief Elder, sir!
Eh? Hm?
[XU MAN 238A] The Han army's
attacks have stopped now!
[rapid footsteps]
[XU MAN 238A] Something strange
is happening out there!
[XIN]
Yah! Yah!
[HAN SOLDIERS gasping]
[XIN]
Cavalry, charge!
[HAN SOLDIER 238A]
Ma Guan, sir!
The Qin army is here!
[HAN SOLDIER 238A]
The Fei Xin Force is here!
[XIN yells]
[yells]
[TIAN YOU, YUAN yell]
--[PEI LANG, QU HAI yell]
--[HAN SOLDIERS groan]
[HAN SOLDIERS yell]
[CHONG YUAN grunts]
[HAN SOLDIERS groan]
[TIAN YONG, LONG YOU yell]
[WEI PING yells]
[ZE GUI yells]
[HAN SOLDIER 238C groans]
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 238A yelps]
[SONG ZUO gasps]
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS groan]
Don't get carried away,
Qin mountain monkeys!
Where's your commander,
the one who killed Lun Hu,
one of Lian Po's Big Four?
Two-thousand-man commander?
Ma Guan will gladly take you!
So he's their leader.
Out of the way! I'll handle him!
Watch out, Xin!
He's definitely no slouch!
I know!
Chu Shui! Xin's going alone?
He's fine!
Don't let a little dumb luck
go to your head, little whelp!
[CHU SHUI] Because, ever since
his battle with Lun Hu...
[XIN grunts]
Impudent brat!
[CHU SHUI]
Xin's gotten much better
at fighting on horseback!
What's this?
[yells]
[MA GUAN groans]
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
Commander Ma Guan.
With just one blow.
Listen, Han army troops!
Listen up real good!
[XIN]
Killing children with no chance
of defending themselves?
Xin of the Fei Xin Force
does not tolerate
the likes of you!
[HAN SOLDIERS gasp]
[HAN SOLDIER 238D]
Run away!
[HAN SOLDIER 238E]
Retreat!
[gasps]
Mother!
Oh, Xiu! Oh, Xiu!
Thank goodness! Thank
goodness you're all right!
[XIU]
Mother! Mother!
[DIAO, XIN sigh]
[CHIEF ELDER] You are
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
[DIAO, XIN]
Huh?
You took the head
of General Feng Ji,
in the battle you
had against Zhao,
and recently, you also
defeated General Lun Hu
in the war with Wei.
Over here, we have
heard about you.
Qin's brave and young commander.
What?
And now you have saved
the country of Xu
in its time of crisis.
I can't thank you enough
for what you've done for us.
Wow.
So this tiny place really
is a country after all.
You've managed all these years,
where many borders intersect,
and wars don't cease.
Yes. There is a reason
Xu has survived for
all these many years.
I'll explain.
Xu is under the protection
of the three kingdoms
of Wei, Zhao and Chu.
[DIAO, XIN gasp]
Protection, you say?
But just how would
that be, then?
In these times of war,
knowing the doings of other
lands is really paramount.
Any place where
this special information
can be safely obtained,
would be greatly prized,
as you can see.
[DIAO, XIN]
Hm...
So then,
you provide special
and secret enemy intel
to your three neighbors.
In return, they
guarantee your safety.
In other words,
you make a living
in black-market information.
[CHIEF ELDER]
I offer no defense.
It is what the weak
can do to stay alive,
in a world that is
constantly at war, you see.
[CHIEF ELDER] Xu and its
environs are surrounded
by steep mountains and
swaths of deep, lush forest,
making it extremely difficult
for any outsider
to find us, really.
It's another trait in our favor.
In fact, only the most
important officials
of Wei, Zhao, and Chu,
such as their chancellors,
know of Xu's existence.
That is why we can
go on existing
as a mere staging
area for intrigue
with many varied
undercover agents,
under secret orders
from those officials
trading with us behind
closed doors, you see.
[XIN, DIAO gasp]
[DIAO]
Hang on...
In a battle between
two kingdoms,
gathering intel on one's enemy
is of the utmost importance,
and putting together a strategy
from that intel is essential.
Does Qin have a place that's
just like this, then?
Because, if they do not...
So then, what's with
that Han army, anyway?
I didn't think they
would even know about
this little place, really.
Earlier, a Han squadron
got lost in the woods,
and happened to stumble
across Xu over here.
Han came to demand that
we manipulate our intel
to confuse our three neighbors.
[DIAO, XIN gasp]
[CHIEF ELDER] We refused,
as we here stand firmly
on neutral ground.
But you see where that
got us by doing so.
[CHIEF ELDER]
Take this with you, please.
It's a map of the area.
I have drawn in the path
that will lead you
to your destination, Dongjin.
Forgive me, it's my way
to show my gratitude
for saving our country.
Don't worry, Gramps.
We didn't do it for any reward.
The map is greatly appreciated.
We didn't even have one.
Do you think you will
be all right without us?
If the Han army attacks again--
I believe that earlier attack
has put the fear of
Xin into them now.
I doubt they'll
return anytime soon.
If not, we can ask our neighbors
for their assistance.
I am positive they
won't stand idly by
in that case.
After all, Xu is their crucial
information-clearing house.
So information is
your weapon, isn't it?
Ha, ha. Guess there are lots
of different ways to fight.
Right! Let's head out
to Dongjin, right now!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[XIU]
Mister!
[XIN]
Huh?
Hey, it's Xiu!
[XIN] How're your injuries?
You doing okay?
Yeah. But they still hurt.
[XIN laughs] Suck it up!
Those are wounds of honor!
Your efforts here saved
this country, you know!
[XIU]
Thanks, mister!
I will never, ever forget you,
for as long as I live!
[XIN]
Yep!
And I definitely will not
forget you either, Xiu!
[XIN]
See ya!
This map is insanely detailed.
According to this,
if we'd not just
stopped at Xu just now,
we would've run into
Wei and Zhao garrisons.
Taking the long way
will still get us
to Dongjin faster,
won't it, then?
[laughs] That's right,
helping people pays off!
[whistle blows]
That's Shi's whistle!
It means he's spotted an enemy!
All troops, halt now!
That's strange.
The chief elder said there
were no enemies here.
Look at them all now.
Three thousand.
But whose are they, exactly?
Can't tell when all
their flags are down.
[DIAO]
And what are they doing here
in the first place?
Xu's chief elder said only
the highest-ranking officials
rom Wei, Zhao,
and Chu even know
these roads exist
in the first place.
So then, these people
must be here
on the orders of a big shot.
Look down.
[XIN]
Whoa! Now that's a big carriage!
So then, are you
really telling me
that the big shot himself
came all the way out here?
[XIN]
The carriage stopped!
Here comes the man in charge.
Well, even if I did
get a look at him,
I wouldn't know
where this guy is fro--
[gasps]
That's Li Mu!
And Kaine!
Commander, they'll see you!
[XIN]
What's going on?
That's Li Mu.
What is he doing here?