[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent:
the legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
Any last words now,
old-timer?
[XUAN FENG]
You may be ignorant,
but you aren't without
some aptitude. Hmph.
I could let you be
my apprentice, Huan Yi.
I don't think so.
You are nobody.
[LIAN PO]
Forgive me, Xuan Feng.
I let you die
such a mundane death.
I can't say these soft-hearted
things on the battlefield,
to lose someone with whom I'd
cheated death all those times.
[LIAN PO] However, I won't
be pinning you for Xuan Feng.
I am about to pay
Qin right back
with their soldiers'
own corpses and blood!
[SOLDIERS laughing, cheering]
General Huan Yi is amazing!
He avenged us here
in the central army!
He's so mind-blowing!
Thank goodness!
I was scared that the old
geezer was gonna suddenly spring
another weird tactic on us
like he tended to do!
It's so funny how
you're always scared!
[growls]
[lauging]
[XIN]
Xuan Feng.
I can't believe it...
That old fool,
cut down so easily?!
[SOLDIERS laughing]
Are they sure about this?
Huh, Meng Tian?
They are.
General Huan Yi disguised
himself as a messenger
and sneaked into the
main enemy camp right after.
[XIN]
What?! I need details!
Wait. But first of all,
I need to go now.
You come if you want.
Where to, though?
General Lun Hu.
I understand how you feel,
but we need a war council.
Everyone in the central army
is in an uproar over our tactics
now that we've lost
the left flank.
--[WEI GENERAL A] Please, sir--
--[LUN HU] Oh, be quiet.
[gasps]
I lost both my parents
due to a war, you see.
My lord saved me from
the very brink of starvation.
And this is exactly why
I have always given my all
in the service of
being my lord's sword.
But it was Xuan Feng
who taught me everything
I know about strategy.
[LUN HU] If Lian Po is my
father, he was my grandfather.
Second in line with a
kindness I must repay.
[LUN HU] Although, it is true
that it was Xuan Feng's misstep
that led to his own execution.
But for someone like you
to say you understand how I feel
is insanely irritating.
[gasps]
Well I-I mean, that is--
[LUN HU] Don't you worry.
My lord is staying up all night
figuring out a
new strategy as we speak.
All we need to do is follow it.
[WEI GENERAL A]
Yes sir!
[XIN growls]
[growls]
Why exactly would you drag me
all the way out here, anyway?!
Come on, don't be that way.
I have something
important to discuss.
Besides, aren't you
somewhat worried
about the poor
Yu Feng Force now?
Just a little?
And how is his
wound healing now?
Wha--?! Not at all!
[MENG TIAN] We've come
to visit you, Wang Ben!
Incoming!
Oh! You seem well!
What do you want?
[MENG TIAN laughs]
You see?!
I told you there's no point
worrying about this guy!
Get out. You're in my way.
Never mind! I was just leaving!
[MENG TIAN] Now, now.
Just sit down, both of you.
[WANG BEN]
Don't get between us.
[MENG TIAN] Wang Ben,
you heard about General Huan Yi
taking down Xuan Feng?
[WANG BEN]
Yes.
[MENG TIAN]
Shocking, right?
Not quite.
Don't you lie!
[laughs]
He really went down
fairly quickly for a man
who had both of you in such
a bind, don't you think?
Be quiet!
My spear was this close to
reaching that old geezer's
ugly looking head!
Well, it surprised me.
I'd heard General Huan Yi
was a real military genius,
but I never for a moment
thought he could pull off
something as big as this.
We three are looking
upward at this moment,
and just above us is a wall.
[gasps]
We need to think about
where we go from here,
if only to get over
that big wall above.
Right here is the main
camp with the Qin army's
commanding general
Meng Ao, see?
The central army to
which we all belong
is positioned out
in front of it.
To our right is the right flank
led by General Huan Yi,
and on our left is the left
flank led by General Wang Jian.
So as you can see, the Wei
army's main camp is around here.
That's where their commanding
general, Bai Guixi is.
Right now, Lian Po
is probably there, too.
Just in front
of their main camp,
and directly facing us, as well,
is their central army base
led by Lun Hu.
They also have their own left
and right flanks as you can see.
This is a very big setup.
Just get to the point now.
[MENG TIAN]
After slaying Xuan Feng,
Huan Yi and his troops up and
vanished from everyone's radar.
Some think he's after
the enemy's main camp,
moving right over here,
but in fact,
he has pulled back to the rear
and is quickly regrouping.
He's regrouping?
Yeah.
Xuan Feng truly hated Huan Yi,
but Huan Yi hated Jie Zifang.
General Huan Yi's
main forces were attacked
by Jie Zifang's army,
and lost half their
troops in battle.
Jie Zi-who?
The general who is heading up
the enemy's left flank.
Although if Jie Zifang
has lost track of Huan Yi,
he can't be too rash.
Meanwhile, on the opposite
side of the battlefield,
Qiang Yan's right flank troops
have just entered the fray now.
I doubt Wang Jian can overcome
them the way things are now.
Correct, right, Wang Ben?
What I mean is, with both
the right and left flanks
in a tight deadlock now,
this battle seems to be
going nowhere really fast.
Oh man, I've just had enough
of this right-left talk!
We are fighting Lun Hu,
smack in the middle.
You just don't know anything.
Do you, then?
Say what?!
Actually, I do believe that
you're half right, anyway, Xin.
It is very true,
our main problem at hand
is Lun Hu right
in the middle of things.
But the issue is that his
movements are closely tied
to those of the
left and right flanks.
[XIN]
Huh?
[WANG BEN]
These past three days,
Lun Hu's central army
has waited for either flank
to push back their opponent
while they pull their punches.
[XIN gasps]
Since day two, our sheer
dedication to defense,
has helped keep
our casualties low.
It makes sense that Lun Hu,
one of Lian Po's Big Four,
is holding back
at this very moment.
Wait, Wang Ben, did you
look into Lun Hu already?
A little.
I had a Wei captive questioned.
Oh, okay. It figures.
[XIN]
Hey, no fair!
Don't keep me
out of the loop over here!
Lian Po has four generals
right under him
that are known as the Big Four.
All of them have a history of
fighting alongside Lian Po and
are exceptionally powerful.
[MENG TIAN]
Jie Zifang is their leader,
and he has chalked up
over a hundred victories
on his own,
all without Lian Po.
[MENG TIAN] Qiang Yan
is one of the top ten archers
in the Middle Kingdom
and he was the hero
of a state that confronted
the land of Zhao.
He gave Lian Po
his fair share of trouble,
but once his state fell,
Qiang Yan swore his fealty.
Xuan Feng worked as Lian Po's
staff officer for years.
He was talented enough
to serve as the commander
of the entire Zhao army
due to his cleverness.
So that old guy
was way up there in rank!
Moreover, Xuan Feng also was
the one to teach strategy
to a young Lian Po.
Lian Po is mourning Xuan Feng.
Which is why he'll be driven to
go all-out to win this battle.
[XIN gasps]
Finally, this
brings us to Lun Hu,
the man we're currently
facing right now.
If you knew Lian Po's
war records, you'd understand.
Indeed, Lun Hu is without
a doubt the most dangerous
of all of the Big Four.
Whenever Lian Po is
involved in a big battle,
Lun Hu is always there
getting decisive results.
He's scarily good at
breaking through ranks.
There's no telling how many
main army camps he's attacked.
He even broke through
General Wang Yi's main forces
and landed a
deathly blow to him.
[XIN]
What?
He landed the lethal blow...
...on the mighty Wang Yi?!
I get it now.
Lun Hu has definitely
been holding back on us.
You got that right.
[WANG BEN] If the enemy's
left or right flank
circles behind General Meng Ao
and cuts off his escape route,
Lun Hu can waltz
right in and attack.
Do you think our central army
can stop Lun Hu,
who's fighting in
earnest right now?
[WANG BEN]
Frankly speaking, no.
[XIN]
Uh?
[sighs]
I agree. I guess not.
[XIN]
Now hang on!
What are you really saying here?
Don't be giving up
before the battle's even begun!
Huan Yi beat Xuan Feng
and we're aiming
even higher than that!
We got no business not
going after Lun Hu!
He who landed a blow
on General Wang Yi!
He's way up there!
I say bring it on!
We'll pay it back in spades!
Yeah!
Works out great!
I fought with him first,
so he can definitely be
one of the general's
heads I'm aiming for.
It's perfect!
I'll take the head of Lun Hu,
one of Lian Po's Big Four,
and you can both bet on it!
And then,
I'll shoot up the ranks
leaving you two in the dust!
Anyone is able to talk real big.
You're out of your depth.
Say what?!
[MENG TIAN laughs]
Xin, you are half correct in
this case once again, it seems.
We do have to kill Lun Hu,
who's clearly aiming
to go after
Grandfather's main camp.
However,
it certainly won't be in
retaliation for his attack.
So, Meng Tian,
what are you trying to say?
If we cannot stop a marauding
Lun Hu, we'll stop his attack.
[MENG TIAN] Meaning we
defeat him right before
he can strike us first,
do you both understand?
[gasps]
Tomorrow, Le Hua Force,
Yu Feng Force,
and the Fei Xin Force
all together will kill Lun Hu!
Le Hua Force!
[gasping]
I truly believe that
our strongest point
is our ability to
handle both precise
and cool-headed fighting,
and crude and bloody brawling.
[POPS]
The young sir, making a speech?
[LU XIAN]
That's new.
[MENG TIAN] And so today
it'll be the latter.
As you know, I'm not fond
of this kind of thing.
But we are currently faced
with something
that only we can achieve.
Therefore, today will be
a battle most deadly!
[POPS] Ah, I see.
So that's what it is.
[LU XIAN] He's got an
important mission for us now.
It's been a while.
My apologies,
but I do trust you.
[SOLDIERS cheer]
What's that?
What's the Le Hua Force
getting all worked up about?
There's something's different
about the Le Hua Force today.
Chu Shui.
Sir?
[XIN]
We, uh, need to talk.
[WEI MESSENGER A]
General Lun Hu!
[LUN HU]
Hmm?
[WEI MESSENGER A]
A message from the main camp!
[LUN HU]
The fighting's been postponed.
The Xuan Feng memorial battle
begins tomorrow, then?
Got it!
Then shall we get started?
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Stand firm, now!
Keep your defense strong, men!
[yelling]
[TU MEN]
Remain calm and fight!
[yelling]
[TU MEN'S UNDERLING A]
General Tu Men! Look over there!
A unit has ignored orders
and is now entering the fray!
[TU MEN]
What?!
The Le Hua Force!
[QIN MESSENGER A]
General Tu Men!
A message from Commander
Meng Tian of the Le Hua Force!
"I inform you that the
Le Hua Force will henceforth
be an independent unit.
We are leaving our post"!
They have what?!
You just saved us the trouble
of going out there to kill you!
Surround him and take his head!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[gasping]
Le Hua Force!
Now advance to the right!
[yelling]
[MENG TIAN]
There's Lun Hu's main camp.
Lun Hu, sir, one of the
enemy's units is headed directly
towards us at this moment!
Oh, wow! Who do you believe
they're going after?
Me, then?
I don't think that was in
the Qin army's original plan.
If they're acting on their own,
it's practically suicide.
[MENG TIAN]
Oh, I know.
I know how hard it
is for us three rivals
to join together right now,
considering everything.
But if we don't,
we'll fall together.
The Le Hua Force cannot
kill Lun Hu on its own.
The same goes for the
Yu Feng and Fei Xin Forces.
Don't be painting us
with the same brush!
I really think that it's great
that we've been solid rivals
all this time, honestly,
but our situation's
changed harshly.
The Yu Feng, Le Hua,
and Fei Xin Forces have taken
three castles altogether,
distinguishing
themselves in war.
But honestly, our fame isn't
exactly ringing through Qin,
much less anywhere else.
[MENG TIAN] And yet,
here we are, fighting
against that Lian Po now.
Once the legendary great general
Lian Po joined the battle,
the whole Middle Kingdom
had its eyes on
the Shanyang Offensive's
timely final showdown.
[gasps]
[XIN] The whole
Middle Kingdom... watching us?
[MENG TIAN] However,
we cannot get Lun Hu the way
we've stood so far.
If we don't switch it up,
our commanding general Meng Ao
is simply a sitting
duck, you see.
If anyone decides to go
right after General Meng Ao,
we'll just lose to Lian Po,
who's not even currently
leading the Zhao army,
which he trained himself
and can freely
and easily control,
but the Wei army he
commands as an outsider.
The world's greatest general
will be a hot topic.
[growling]
I honestly never thought
I would ever hear those words
come directly out of your
mouth, Meng Tian.
I guess not.
I haven't been as passionate
about that very issue
as you two have been,
I'll admit.
But I'm a different man
this time around.
That I can promise you,
Wang Ben.
[WANG BEN]
Hmm?
[MENG TIAN]
As I said earlier,
we simply can't afford
to let Meng Ao be killed.
After all, he is my
very dear Grandfather,
as both of you are well aware.
He watches over
his positive grandson.
Taking your own private feelings
with you onto the battlefield.
How absurd.
[XIN]
It's not absurd!
Everyone's fighting to protect
something precious,
defending their line in the sand
and for what they believe in.
[XIN]
All right, Meng Tian.
The Fei Xin Force is
with you in this now.
We just gotta tell the
entire Middle Kingdom:
The leading role in this
whole war is about to be recast!
Well? What about you, Wang Ben?
It depends on our strategy.
[MENG TIAN]
Then let's talk strategy.
Firstly, the Le Hua Force goes
after Lun Hu's main camp alone.
Ah, I see.
A wedge formation.
They'll need a
focused breakthrough
if they're coming
after me with so few.
Okay, Qin army, show me
how you can pierce through!
[XIN]
Wait a second!
So you're the only ones
who will actually get to go
take down Lun Hu?
[MENG TIAN laughs]
[MENG TIAN] We can't do that.
Hence our plan, remember?
Come on, troops!
[LE HUA SOLDIERS yell]
Focused breakthrough,
on the way!
Garrison in position!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
Right now!
[growls]
What's this?
[MENG TIAN] Phase one
of our strategy will be:
[MENG TIAN] The Le Hua Force
will not go after Lun Hu!