[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying
Zheng, the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling]
Those men--
[screaming]
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARRATOR]
It was said that Wei's soldiers
were so incredibly serious
that they lacked
raw explosive power.
But with Lian Po's presence,
they broke free of those bonds.
[WEI SOLDIER A]
Kill them!
[BI'S UNDERLING A]
Commander Bi!
[BI'S UNDERLING B]
Sir, the sheer momentum
of the Wei infantry--
[BI]
Stay calm. Just stay calm.
A commander needs to be
cool-headed at a time like this.
[gasps]
[BI] The clifftops are still
under our control, though.
[BI] The Qin army still has all
the advantages of this terrain!
The only part of the
clifftops we've lost
is right where Lian Po
suddenly appeared.
I've got it!
Given how fast Lian Po
came here from their main camp,
as well as how we didn't
see him coming over here at all,
[BI] I would generously
estimate his troops
currently at about
a thousand men!
Taking into account the
casualties thus far,
I'd say there are maybe
about 8,000 Wei troops,
to Qin's 10 at the moment.
Almost no difference on
numbers alone.
Lian Po's appearance may
have given their morale a boost,
but we still have the absolute
advantage in these straits!
[BI] Defeating Lian Po all
comes down to how we fight!
[WANG JIAN'S ADVISOR A]
Qiang Yan is fleeing
to the other side!
[WANG JIAN]
Let him go.
Our central army is a
complete mess right now.
Get the commanders
to rebuild our formations.
Sir!
[LIAN PO] So it appears
that they're the ones
regrouping first, at the moment.
[laughs]
And what exactly will your
next move be then, Wang Jian?
[NARRATOR] Lian Po was very
interested in discovering
what Wang Jian's actions
would be from here on out.
The armies were
matched in numbers.
The Qin army had the benefit
of the most ideal terrain
while the Wei army
was high on morale.
A strategist couldn't ask
for better ingredients
with which to show his skills.
[WANG JIAN'S ADVISOR A]
All squads have been regrouped!
[WANG JIAN] Just make sure
that they don't chip away
at our main units, though.
[WANG JIAN'S ADVISOR B]
Understood, sir.
[NARRATOR] Wang Yi
thought him to be on a par
with Qin's six great generals.
It remained to be seen
what Wang Jian would cook up.
Lian Po was using
this battle as a yardstick
to truly measure
Wang Jian's military worth.
[NARRATOR] However,
Wang Jian would betray Lian Po's
expectations most splendidly.
All right.
All troops retreat now!
[BI]
We're pulling out?
With such a
good opportunity, why?
I don't know!
We're bringing up the rear,
so just look sharp!
[WANG JIAN]
Apologies, Lian Po,
I'm naturally only
interested in battles
that I'm guaranteed to win.
[LIAN PO]
I understand you.
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
Commander, sir, move ahead!
Not yet!
We cannot leave the infantry!
Cavalry provide backup now!
That's reckless!
Behind us, there's--
I don't understand.
Why are you so happy to have
been thwarted in this manner?
Am I happy, then?
Seems so.
[laughs]
Perhaps I am!
Tell me, who among Qin's
six great generals
have you fought against,
Qiang Yan?
Of the six great generals?
[QIANG YAN]
Bai Qi...
Wang He...
Wang Yi...
Liao...
These four.
Who was the most
intense of those four?
Intense?
For me that was Liao, I believe.
Our mutual emphasis on
offense always meant
countless casualties
on both sides, you see.
[laughs]
Liao's attacks always
were particularly atrocious.
So who of those four was
the hardest to handle, then?
Bai Qi, the leader
of the six great generals.
[LIAN PO] I thought so.
He was my toughest, too.
Though Bai Qi was
no risk-taker, really.
No matter how tasty
the bait dangled before him,
he never rose to take it.
The more muscular
my approach became,
the more slow and relaxed
his response to me was.
He always had a good read
on his opponent's
state of mind, as well.
I would chase Bai Qi too far
out of sheer anger
only to have him retaliate.
That was our
little routine, see.
[LIAN PO laughs]
Why mention all of
this right now, then?
The thing is that somehow,
watching Wang Jian
as he sauntered away
reminded me so much of
Bai Qi and how he used to be.
Then Wang Jian is
equal to Bai Qi?
[LIAN PO laughs]
[LIAN PO] Well, I really
wouldn't go that far.
However, I honestly do believe
that their fighting styles
have several points in common.
And very similar
fighting styles between them.
It may indicate they share
a pretty similar view
of the world, as well.
That could be true,
but his scheme to appear in the
straits was truly excellent.
But based on that alone?
In any case,
Bai Qi was a real monster.
[WEI MESSENGER A]
Alert! Alert!
Right up ahead! It's the
enemy's, the enemy's uh--
Just please, hurry onward!
[LIAN PO] Field warfare,
castle onslaughts,
sieges, Bai Qi
really did it all.
How many times I chased
after his army just like this?
Wherever he ran to he would have
something just waiting there
to stop me right in my
tracks on time.
For example, you'd be here
in the mountains
and before you know it...
[gasping]
[LIAN PO]
...he'd have constructed
an enormous castle before me!
Well played.
Few commanders can
build a fortification
in the middle of a campaign.
This is enough to know
the extent of his skill.
Could he have built this
in expectation of my arrival?
[LIAN PO laughs]
[LIAN PO]
What a surprise!
To think a man like you
was still hiding in the shadows
of the six great generals,
Wang Jian!
[QIANG YAN]
A natural stronghold.
Wang Jian has seen more terrain
in this battle than anyone else.
But to find something
like this and those straits?
We aren't prepared
to attack this fortress,
and to strike unprepared
means many casualties.
Killing him would be
next to impossible.
[LIAN PO growls]
What's this?
Wang Jian, you idiot!
[LIAN PO yells]
[growls]
[LIAN PO]
Qiang Yan!
Sir?
[LIAN PO]
Prepare a camp.
We'll surround this fortress!
[QIANG YAN]
Yes sir!
[growling]
[QIN SOLDIER F]
What exactly is up with them?
[QIN SOLDIER G]
That's the Fei Xin Force.
It appears their commander
still has not returned.
[NARRATOR]
Enemy attacks during the battle
between the central armies
had plunged the Qin army's
formations into disorder.
The battle was so chaotic that
the squads that had gone alone
still had not returned
to their original positions.
Please, you must get
some rest, Lieutenant.
Ah! Look there!
X-Xin!
It's Xin!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS
yelling, cheering]
[FEI XIN SOLDIER D]
It's Xin!
[sighs]
Meng Tian, my lord,
Generals Tu Men and
Rong Bei await.
Yes, I know.
We may still have someone
on our tail, men!
We can't rest now!
Stay alert and keep going!
[BI]
What are you, General Wang Jian?
What are you thinking?
[BI]
Firstly, using us as a decoy,
then sacrificing
all those soldiers
only to run right afterwards?
Never mind Qiang Yan.
You're the one
I don't understand.
[LIAN PO]
Rare is the commander
with fortress-building
capabilities.
Of the six great generals,
only Bai Qi could do so.
I had my share of trouble
with Bai Qi's defenses.
This fine building
stands up to any of his.
The depth of his
schemes and uniqueness,
I really believe match up to
those of Bai Qi back in the day.
Although, I'd say this
is where you differ greatly.
See, Wang Jian,
you are a lieutenant,
and in this battle you
believed yourself to be
the Qin army's best and
brightest of them all,
quite frankly.
Your behavior made
this all incredibly clear now.
Definitely.
[LIAN PO] It may be
difficult for us to strike
Wang Jian in that fortress,
but on the other hand,
we have him trapped
right there as well.
If the Qin army's main power
is in its left and right flanks,
this'll be a great blow.
Plus, this erases half the means
the Qin army had to cope
with a worst-case scenario.
Surely he must have
realized all of this, too!
[WANG JIAN] At this moment,
my land has a desperate need
of a war-strong man
such as yourself.
It seems Wang Jian is lacking
something imperative
needed as a very good commander.
[LIAN PO]
Greatly lacking!
The man is twisted indeed.
Wang Jian, I know why
you never let the sun
shine on you until today
going back to the
days of King Zhao.
A commander who puts himself
first, truly cannot be trusted.
No matter how skilled
you are in battle,
no one will see you as a
hero when this is all over.
You surely stand a completely
different path than we do.
[LIAN PO] I won't go so far as
to discount you completely,
but I've lost interest.
Qiang Yan,
I leave this place to you.
After all is said and done,
Wang Jian has removed himself
from the battlefield.
He won't be making
any moves for a while.
And you, my lord?
Going back to basics.
War is about killing the
general, am I right?
Perhaps it's time I give that
miserable acquaintance of mine
a proper send-off.
[LIAN PO] I'll have this war
over by tomorrow, Qiang Yan!
[QIANG YAN]
Yes sir!
[MENG AO laughs]
[MENG AO]
So, Tu Men and Rong Bei
have given you a
piece of their minds.
Yes, and one slap
apiece at that, too.
[MENG AO laughs]
Well, I am really
pleased it ended there.
Well, what is it you needed,
General Meng Ao?
Enough of that.
At this very moment,
we're just a grandpa and
his grandson simply talking.
Come here, Tian.
What's the matter, Grandpa?
You're acting different.
I don't like it one bit,
you know.
[MENG AO]
Don't say that, Tian.
Strangely, there are some things
you come to understand
at my age.
It is just like when a
desperate battle
is rapidly approaching him.
See, that's just
not like you at all.
Remaining calm and reasonable
in battle is the Bai Lao way!
[MENG AO laughs]
Usually, yes. However,
this time around...
...this time,
I will not back down.
[sighs]
[XIN grunts]
Xin, you look--those wounds!
I-I see bone!
Hah! They do look a little deep.
Wait here.
I will bring some medicine.
All you dirty gawkers,
just get out!
You'll make his wounds worse.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[WEI PING] Huh? Seriously?!
Get away from him!
Go on, get out!
I see. So it has
left its mark now.
That terrible wound.
[ZHENG]
Does your wound still hurt?
[XIANG]
Huh? Oh!
No, the pain's really
all gone now, my lord!
So why, then?
Whoa! Whoa, whoa!
[ZHENG]
Look, Xiang.
[ZHENG] I got these during
my brother's uprising.
Are they ugly?
Absolutely not! Not at all!
You lie.
I'm not lying! I swear!
They're proof that Your Highness
managed to survive--
Therefore, I don't find
them ugly at all!
So then, I don't find
your wound ugly, either.
It is beautiful.
[gasps]
Do you believe me?
Y-Yes...
Yes I do.
I believe you...
[yells]
[QIANG LEI]
Oh, grow up.
Hey! What is that stuff?!
It's a traditional medicine
from my village,
compounded from some
very special fine herbs.
I've been gathering them the
whole time we've been marching,
but this shell-full
is all it made.
Use that precious stuff
on yourself, then, you dummy!
Chu Shui told me
how you were biting off
more than you can chew!
The thing is, I don't
screw up quite like you do.
[XIN screams]
[XIN]
Thank you.
Hey, what's up?
[QIANG LEI]
That Lun Hu guy--
I take it he was strong?
"Strong" doesn't even
begin to cover it.
I mean he wasn't a monster
like that Pang Nuan guy was,
but then again, you can't
go comparing them.
He had the strength of a man
who'd fought many battles,
who'd faced death and
overcome his own limits
time and time again.
And me, too. I...
...don't know how to put it...
I just feel like I've
really overcome
one of my own limits, as well.
[QIANG LEI]
I see. So that's what it is.
Even all beat-up like this,
his presence is bigger and
radiates more than ever before.
[XIN] I guess it's kinda weird
for the loser to be saying that.
[XIN chuckles]
[XIN]
But listen,
all these people were dying and
I went and screwed it up.
And I'm gonna settle that
once and for all!
Next time for sure.
I'll kill him
with my bare hands!
Then you need to get
some sleep and recover.
You are not fighting anyone
till that fever's gone.
With your help and medicine,
I'll be back to my old self!
[QIANG LEI]
You will not.
[XIN laughs]
Things aren't that
convenient, are they?
[gasps]
What is this?
Are you sleeping here?
That medicine is
very strong, you know.
So your body might reject it.
I will keep an eye
on you for a while.
[XIN] But really,
you just want to be with me.
[QIANG LEI]
Never mind that.
If your condition worsens,
feel free to die.
[XIN]
I was kidding! Kidding!
[WANG BEN shouts]
[grunts]
[XIN]
Once this war's over,
we won't be able
to just talk like this.
I hate to say this,
but I'll miss it.
[QIANG LEI] Don't worry about
things past tomorrow.
I'm positive that this war
just won't end that easily,
you know.
[XIN]
Yeah...
I guess you're right.
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS murmuring]
[WEI PING grunts]
Now that I look around, it's
like everyone's injured, too.
Well, of course they are.
How many days has it been?
It makes sense having
many injured soldiers.
But you know that Xin's
really hurt worst of all.
With a fever on
top of those cuts
he'll be flat on his back
for two or three d--
[WEI PING grunts]
Hey, who did that?!
It's too early for--
[gasps]
Hey, what's up, Wei Ping?
X-Xin?!
Are you really okay now?!
Just fine, see?
And...
...see this right here?!
[gasping]
[FEI XIN SOLDIER F]
That's our commander!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER H]
Amazing!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER I]
That went down to the bone!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 226J]
Xin, all right!
Um, you sure
healed up quick, Xin.
Honestly, I thought your
right hand was a goner.
It was Qiang Lei.
Gave me some great special
medicine for the wounds.
[QIANG LEI]
It wasn't just the medicine.
[XIN]
Qiang Lei?
[QIANG LEI] It was
half thanks to the medicine,
and half thanks
to your own crazy
power of recovery, as well.
[XIN]
Qiang Lei...
Qiang Lei!
Today is the day that
we crush the Wei army!
Right! Get ready
for another charge!
We're gonna hit 'em hard!
[cheering]
[LUN HU chuckles]
They're starting the
day off right!
Sounds like it!
[NARRATOR] This was the
sixth day in the battle
on the Liuyi Plains.
It had been about two and a half
months since the Qin army
had embarked on the
Shanyang Offensive.
Even though they had
taken 16 fortified cities,
their goal was still
to secure Shanyang,
the militarily vital
stronghold beyond them all.
Unless the Qin army
could destroy Wei
which had moved to
protect Shanyang,
their entire offensive would
surely end in utter failure.
Defending Wei,
attacking Qin, as well as
the strong foes from
other lands who watched them,
the myriad great thoughts
and expectations
of the entire Middle Kingdom
were focused solely on Shanyang.
Um, Xin, sir?
[laughs]
I guess they can't
see me, huh?
[NARRATOR] And there,
the men who risked their lives
in the battle at its
very center,
came to a strange realization.
Why, yes, certainly.
[NARRATOR] Finally,
the curtain was now rising.
on the final day of the
Great Shanyang Offensive!