What is the matter, dear sire?
[ZHENG]
Has it been a year already?
[NARRATOR]
The kingdom of Qin had invaded
the smaller Han
to expand its territory.
Neighboring Zhao jumped
at the chance to draw Qin
into a dangerous battle.
Stepping up as
commanding general
was the Strange Bird of Qin:
Wang Yi, the last of
the six great generals,
feared throughout
the Middle Kingdom.
Zhao sent forth as their
commanding general Pang Nuan,
a so-called god of war
with deep ties to Wang Yi.
The two men clashed violently.
[NARRATOR]
Just as strategist, Li Mu,
one of Zhao's
Three Greats, had planned.
Thus, Wang Yi was
skillfully manipulated
into dying a hero's death.
[NARRATOR] Without the absolute
symbol of their army,
Qin's military power waned,
and the neighboring lands
of Zhao, Wei, Han, and Chu
started launching
invasion after invasion.
But now, every Qin man,
woman, and child knew:
The time for action had come!
Kill them all!
Squash those Qin worms!
Kill them now!
[MAN groans]
[cackles]
We've got this!
[NARRATOR]
Aflame with fierce battles,
the front lines also featured
a group of singularly
dynamic fighters.
Captain! New troops
from the right!
[yelling, crashing]
But that is--
[yells]
[WEI SOLDIER 201B]
The Fei Xin Force!
[NARRATOR] This hundred-man
squadron had come together
under Wang Yi
in the Zhao battle.
Proving their prowess there,
the Fei Xin Force grew
into a 300-man unit with
many ten-man sergeants.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[NARRATOR] The Fei Xin Force's
master swordsman, Chong Yuan.
[NARRATOR] The cool-headed
spearman, Song Zuo.
[NARRATOR]
The herculean Long Chuan.
[yells]
[WEI SOLDIER 201E groans]
[NARRATOR] The clownish,
but hard-hitting Wei Ping.
The group fighting
expert, Ze Gui.
The oldest sergeant, Lu Yan.
The short-tempered and
argumentative Tian Yong.
The intimidating
veteran, Pei Lang.
The dependable Tian You.
[WEI SOLDIER 201F groans]
[NARRATOR]
The talented leader, Yuan.
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[NARRATOR] She who dances down
the gods of war, Qiang Lei.
And at the head of the
entire Fei Xin Force...
[XIN grunting]
[WEI SOLDIERS groaning]
Hey, there's that brat!
[NARRATOR]
...is a backwater servant boy
who fought his way up the ranks
to command a unit
of 300 men strong.
[XIN yells]
[WEI SOLDIERS groan]
[NARRATOR]
This was none other than Xin,
captain of the Fei Xin Force.
Shout our victory!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
He has left me that weapon,
intending on improving himself
until he is worthy of it.
I have been entrusted
with a nation.
I cannot lament my helplessness.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Sire.
[ZHENG]
Lord Changwen.
I will unify the Middle Kingdom,
no matter what it takes me!
[SI SHI] But do you have the
means to defeat that man, then?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Si Shi!
By whose authority do you--
[ZHENG]
I summoned him.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
You did, sire?
[NARRATOR] Si Shi. When Zheng's
younger half-brother,
Cheng Jiao, plotted
an uprising with Jie Shi,
his Minister of the Left,
the level-headed Si Shi
gave his support as
Jie Shi's right hand.
Cheng Jiao didn't
bring an uprising,
because of his popularity,
nor Jie Shi's ambition.
It was because Si Shi took part
in all of the planning.
He also had to seize the
remnants of Jie Shi's faction,
But, I'll have him serve
as a close advisor.
[SI SHI]
There you have it.
[LORD CHANGWEN gasps]
[SI SHI]
As it happens, sire,
we've received word
of troubling behavior
from Lu Buwei.
[ZHENG]
Say what?
We do not know the specifics,
but you should know,
Your Highness.
That man...
What is he planning?
[LU BUWEI]
Now, where are you?
Where is my little prey now?
[QUAN yelps]
[LU BUWEI] Aha! Gotcha!
[LU BUWEI]
And who might this be?
Well, if it isn't
the little Quan!
[NARRATOR] Qin's Minister
of the Right, Lu Buwei.
Once a mere Zhou merchant,
his insatiable thirst
for wealth and fame
propelled him up the
ranks to become the ruler
of Qin in all but name.
[NARRATOR] With a faction
of the best in warfare,
politics, diplomacy, and law,
Lu Buwei had designs
on taking the Qin
throne for himself.
Now, powerless to confront him
in the face of such
naked ambition,
Zheng's camp could only wait
for the other shoe to drop.
The greatest threat
for Zheng, the king of Qin,
may not be the
surrounding nations
and the battles they wage.
Indeed, it may be Lu Buwei.
[NARRATOR] A minor irregularity
was causing a stir in Zhao.
[KAINE]
Li Mu, my lord!
King Daoxiang is beside himself.
Lord Chunping is
nowhere to be found!
Lord Chunping, you say?
[KAINE] Yes, His Highness's
absolute favorite.
He'd have no reason to
vanish of his own accord.
[LI MU] This could get
very messy indeed.
[YANG]
Xiang, wait up!
What is it?
You assume your post as
the king's companion today!
So, why are you running away?
[XIANG]
But-but-but, not me!
I can't!
[YANG]
Xiang!
Are you all right, Xiang?
Why can't you tell me?
There have been dozens of
ladies called by the king,
but it has always been
only for one day.
I think I am much
too childish for this.
What do you mean?
Why do you think
His Highness said as much:
It is your devotion that counts!
[gasps]
Really?
Well, er, maybe?
[XIANG]
You see?
Plus, I'm so clumsy.
I just know I'll make
lots of mistakes here.
[YANG]
Don't be silly!
We don't draw straws for this,
I will have you know.
You were chosen on your merits!
[gasps]
Do your best.
[door creaks]
[XIANG]
I beg your pardon.
M-M-My name is Xiang.
Starting today, I will be
your cam-er, um--
I'll be your companion!
It's my pleasure.
[gasps]
[XIANG]
Yes, but pleasure what?
And how exactly then?
Er, um...
So then...
What would Your Highness
like me to do first, exactly?
You need not do anything.
Huh?
Just being here is good enough.
Yes, sire.
[LORD CHUNPING]
Many thanks.
[LU BUWEI] How kind of you
to come all this way.
Well. It's been
a while, Lu Buwei.
I am glad to see you again.
[LU BUWEI]
And you, Lord Chunping.
[LORD CHUNPING gasps]
But, Lu Buwei!
What does this mean?
The answer to that question
will have to wait
until next time.
[gasps]
[LU BUWEI laughs]
[NARRATOR] Si Shi's advice
came seconds too late.
The situation surrounding Zheng
silently grew ever more tense.
Attacks from other kingdoms,
Lu Buwei's plotting,
and a darkness that lurked
in a most unexpected place.
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
And just when exactly
will I get my wish then?
Huh, Zhao Gao?
[ZHAO GAO]
Madam.
We have, in fact, reached
a conclusion in that regard.
[QUEEN DOWAGER]
Let's hear it.
[door creaks]
Care for a drink then,
Lord Changping?
[LORD CHANGPING]
This is a school, Cai Ze.
[CAI ZE] Waiting for the
minister to make a move is dull.
[LORD CHANGPING]
He does us no favors.
It seems the one
you had your eye on
is coming along
quite nicely, correct?
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
Mmm.
Do you still want him after all?
Or not?
Well, no.
[CAI ZE]
You give up on him?
[LORD CHANGPING]
Quite the opposite.
I want to see how far he'll go.
For now, Cai Ze,
we will just
leave him out there.
[CAI ZE]
Oh, I see.
And the little straw man
you are training now
is to help speed up
Xin's progress?
[LORD CHANGPING]
That, I do not know for sure.
[MENG YI]
Can't sleep, huh, Diao?
[DIAO]
Meng Yi.
Tactician school's just
not easy, that's for sure.
I knew that well coming in.
Kaine told me so.
You do not understand anything.
If you're going
to be a tactician,
you need to truly grasp
what that really means.
What it means?
Indeed.
It's more sad and painful
to be a tactician,
than being a soldier
out on the front lines.
Painful...
...and terrible.
[DIAO]
It's not me I worry about.
I just wonder how
he's doing out there.
[MENG YI]
Xin?
[DIAO]
Yeah.
I bet he keeps on
charging onward,
getting farther away.
[MENG YI]
No, sometimes he stays put.
He must know, the real
battle is only beginning.
[DIAO]
The real battle, you say?
[MENG YI] You can really feel
the times changing fast.
The battlefields are full
of young and talented
generals of Xin's generation.
They are hardworking rivals,
ready to butt heads.
[DIAO]
Hardworking rivals?
[MENG YI]
Just like my older brother.
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO]
Do you really have a brother?
I have never ever met him then!
[MENG YI] He never did
like to be tied down.
He really loves his freedom.
[DIAO]
Huh?
More talented people are
on their way, you will see.
[FEI XIN FORCE laughing]
Check this out, Mao!
See your upper arm,
this bit right here?
Whoa! Seriously?
Right? Right?
Any grown-ups knows about that?
[FEI XIN FORCE laughing]
But I think that Dong Mei's
are much softer than mine, see?
What are you talking about?
[WEI PING]
How 'bout your wife Ze Gui?
Oh, now, see this is
a lot more like Dong Mei!
[ZE GUI]
What?
[PEI LANG]
Why brood all by your lonesome?
All these battles end in massive
victories, thanks to us.
[XIN]
They're all two-bit battles.
[GROUP gasps]
[XIN] What's the point in
beating a bunch of small fries?
It is not fully pointless.
Our actions have led to
actual victories, though.
We are getting actual
results out there.
[PEI LANG]
This isn't about takin' on
one big name after another.
I get where you're
coming from, but be patient.
Big fights don't
come along every day.
[XIN growls]
[XIN]
Li Mu!
Hey, Xin!
What the heck, Song Zuo?
You can go ahead and act
as solemn as you like, man,
but there is nothing
big on the way though.
Uh--
[SONG ZUO] This is the time
to fatten up our troops
and store up our strength!
Just relax a little bit,
would you now?
Enjoy this time
with everyone here.
That is one of the keys
to a stronger squad.
Uh?
[XIN]
Yeah, you're so right.
[WEI PING]
Yes! Just like this!
Hey! The captain's here!
Here, give this
a little squeeze!
[XIN]
Huh?
[WEI PING]
This here is Dong Mei!
Wh-What in the world?
[TIAN YONG groans]
[WEI PING grunts]
You big idiot!
The legend has it
that a woman's breast
feels exactly like
her child's arm!
Besides, that's just
an old wives' tale!
What? No, it's not?
No way. No!
Look I just miss Dong Mei
a lot, can you feel my pain?
[FEI XIN FORCE laughing]
[WEI PING]
What's with you guys?
Don't you miss
your wives and kids?
What about you, Ze Gui?
[ZE GUI]
Well, uh, actually--
Huh?
[XIN]
You should stay here with us.
If it's tough getting all
buddy-buddy, well, I'm here.
[QIANG LEI]
Well no, I was--
[XIN]
Just come on!
[FEI XIN FORCE laughing]
[QIANG LEI] I only wanted
to relieve myself.
Hm?
[laughing]
What's with you?
N-Nothing! Nothing at all.
Yeah right, "nothing at all"!
[QIANG LEI]
Lay off.
[WEI PING] Have I got
an embarrassing story
about Xin for you!
Say what? Hey, Wei Ping!
Wait till you hear the
dirt I have on Wei Ping!
[WEI PING]
Don't you dare!
[NARRATOR]
The Fei Xin Force remained
as an unattached
special squadron,
running from battle to
battle as reinforcements.
Their opponents weren't
much of a challenge
after the pitched Zhao battle,
and victory came
quickly and often.
Their allies grew
to rely on them,
while their enemies
learned to fear them.
In short, both the
Fei Xin Force's name and Xin's
had begun to resonate
on front lines everywhere.
Ah. Y'know, we've
gotten awful famous
for never losing one
single battle up to now.
If a cute girl
came up to you to say:
Aren't you that
super-famous Wei Ping?
So, what would you do then,
if that happened, Wei Ping?
[WEI PING]
Huh? A cute girl came up to me?
So you mean that--
Dummy!
Dong Mei's the
only girl for you!
Don't worry, I will
gladly take care
of the village girls.
[WEI PING]
Well but, hang on a sec!
I have rights too!
[QING]
Bad news!
[MAO]
Bad, terrible awful!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 201B]
What is it? Qing, Mao! An enemy?
No, not now. It's not that.
There was a battle between
the Yan and those
Zhao army guys!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
The Yan...
...and the Zhao?
[laughs] Exactly as we thought!
[MAO]
Hm.
[QING] The general who led the
Zhao against the Yan was Li Mu!
Well, go on!
How did the battle turn out?
Li Mu toppled two
massive Yan castles;
they seem to be Wudui
and also Fangcheng.
[XIN growls]
[QING grunts]
Wudui and Fangcheng, you said?
Those two are impregnable.
[QING]
It was terribly one-sided.
The Yan army was
completely helpless.
So, he is making a bold move.
Ehmm.
All right!
Time for us to--
[SONG ZUO] Maybe just save
your swagger a minute now.
Song Zuo!
Yan is off in the opposite
direction from Qin.
If Zhao went after Yan,
they must be
looking eastward.
Which means we will
not be facing them
any time soon, now.
If we are preoccupied
with an enemy,
we are not going to fight,
the small fry might
sneak up on us.
You make a good point.
Yes. Song Zuo's quite right.
[NARRATOR] But something
even more unexpected
was happening over in Xianyang.
[JIANG YA]
Oh, no!
He Liao Diao! Meng Yi!
This is bad!
[DIAO]
Hm?
What happened, Jiang Ya?
[JIANG YA]
The Zhao, their chancellor
is coming to Qin right now!
[MENG YI gasps]
[MENG YI]
Zhao's chancellor?
Coming of his own accord?
Why would he?
[JIANG YA]
Oh, we do not know.
but he is definitely coming!
The palace has been
thrown into utter chaos,
I'm telling you!
And after last year's invasion.
What could the chancellor
be up to now?
[JIANG YA] But that's not
the only shocking news
that I've heard!
[DIAO]
Huh?
You ready?
Take a deep breath and listen!
Meng Yi, He Liao Diao.
The chancellor that will be
visiting Qin very soon...
[JIANG YA]
...is none other than...
...Li Mu!