[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Wang Ben, Meng Tian, and Xin.
These bold soldiers and
aspiring great generals
were together here now,
ready to usher in
a brand-new age!
[QIANG LEI]
That's why...
That's why I'm leaving
when this battle
is finally over and done with.
I don't know how many months,
how many years it will take,
but I will have my revenge.
And once I have, when I
come back here, finally then,
I-I think I should be able
to move forward with you guys
in the Fei Xin Force.
You'll all be my home.
Let's win it, Qiang Lei.
[QIANG LEI]
Yeah.
[NARRATOR]
Shanyang, the key position
holding down western Wei,
is home to four
castle towns.
Exactly west of those
lay the Liuyi Plains.
[NARRATOR]
Despite the name,
these plains are
complex terrain,
encompassing great
mountains, forests,
and even swampland as well.
Here, where one trades
ease of movement
willingly for the
ability to enact
an impressively vast
myriad of tactics,
was the site the unparalleled
martial master, Lian Po
had chosen for the battle.
So you have come, Meng Ao!
[QIANG YAN] I'm afraid I still
don't quite understand.
I'm afraid I don't believe
Meng Ao is powerful enough
to really entertain my lord.
[LIAN PO]
No, not at all!
Meng Ao is the most
common general
you could ever come across.
And yet...
Despite this very fact,
he somehow has
a lot of campaigns
under his belt.
It's as Wang Yi told me,
In place of any actual ability,
Meng Ao possesses
really powerful twin swords
instead of that, you see.
Twin swords, he said?
[LIAN PO]
Seems Meng Ao's two lieutenants
are just absolute monsters,
the likes of which the world
has truly never
seen before them.
[LIAN PO] Well then, my dearest
Meng Ao, we are quite anxious
to see you swing them
around before us,
these very special little
twin swords of yours!
[NARRATOR]
Qin commanding general, Meng Ao
and his army had
arrived at the Liuyi Plains,
site of this decisive battle.
[laughs]
Ah, we have been
waiting for you.
Our esteemed
General Meng Ao.
[MENG AO laughs]
Really fine work, you two!
What's with them, down there?
[MENG TIAN]
Oh right!
You really don't
know, do you, Xin?
Not you again.
Those are Grandfather's
two lieutenants there.
Lieutenants?
[MENG TIAN] General Huan Yi
and General Wang Jian.
Huan Yi and Wang Jian?
Never heard of 'em.
They must really not
be that great, huh?
What are you
talking about, Xin?
They're monsters, both of them!
They're monsters?
[MENG TIAN] In fact, most of
Grandfather's military successes
truly are thanks to them.
Neither one is
well-known as a general
because of particular
reasons, you see.
What "reasons"?
Well, General Huan Yi
was once the head
of a big band of marauders
whose controlling territory was
the mountains of southern Qin.
Say what?
[MENG TIAN]
He's a real brutal man.
Even after being
appointed general,
he can't shake the violent
temper of his marauder days.
They say, Huan Yi once
took down a castle town
and beheaded every single one
of its inhabitants mercilessly,
all by himself.
Every inhabitant?
Oh, man.
[MENG TIAN]
Huan Yi the Headhunter.
That heavy nickname
still follows him around
to this very day.
He's simply the
worst kind of brute!
How'd he become a
lieutenant, anyway--
Because he's a
war genius, you see.
[MENG TIAN]
Back when he was a marauder,
Qin sent out all kinds
of punitive forces
to put a stop to his cruelty.
However, they never managed
to successfully win out
over Huan Yi's unique tactics,
strategies that no one could've
ever have taught him
in the first place.
Yes, perhaps it was very
shameful for Grandfather
to take him on right now,
but even setting
all of that aside,
his power really more
than makes up for it.
So what exactly is the deal
with that Wang Jian general?
General Wang Jian is
simply Wang Ben's father.
Huh?
[MENG TIAN]
And that means
he is the current head
of the same Wang clan
that gave us the
great general Wang Yi.
Head of the Wang clan
like General Wang Yi was.
[POPS]
Young sir! Hurry, please!
[MENG TIAN]
You got it! Coming!
[XIN]
Meng Tian, wait up!
Earlier you said that both those
lieutenants had "reasons."
So what exactly is
Wang Jian's reason, then?
[MENG TIAN]
Wang Jian is just perhaps
the most dangerous man in Qin.
He has been driven
into the deep shadows
ever since the time
of King Zhao's ruling.
What does that mean exactly?
Well, you see,
from what I hear,
he has a particularly high
ambition he wishes to achieve.
Word is, he very much
wants to be King.
King, you say?
How can that be?
[MENG AO laughs]
I will really be counting on
you yet again, dear gentlemen.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the Wei army had also arrived
at the Liuyi Plains.
There, atop Mt. Malian and
overlooking the main forces,
stood Wei's commanding
general, Bai Guixi!
[JIE ZIFANG]
What is this?!
[LUN HU] Our lord isn't
the commanding general?
[JIE ZIFANG]
I don't know this Bai Guixi!
Who on Earth is he?
[QIANG YAN] I believe that he
was one of the lieutenants
in General Wu Qing's
battle against Qin.
[XUAN FENG]
Yes, the coward who turned tail
the very second Wang Yi
glared at him at once!
[BAI GUIXI]
I'm not listening to this.
I'm not listening to
any of this nonsense!
[LIAN PO laughs]
Well, then!
Surprised, aren't you?
I'm glad I didn't say anything!
This is really no
laughing matter, my lord!
What is the true meaning
of all of this, then?
Why is he our
commanding general?
Reason number one is morale!
[JIE ZIFANG]
Huh?
Well, those both in Wei
and abroad currently believe
that I have been kept
off the battlefield
these past three years
purposely because
of the sheer lack of
the King's trust in me.
My suddenly turn-up as
a commanding general
would hardly boost the
Wei troops' morale!
Very good point.
[LIAN PO] But what's more,
by using this man
with nothing to recommend
him but the inexplicable love
of his countrymen,
this Zhen Yanxi--
[LUN HU]
It's Bai Guixi, my lord.
[LIAN PO] I can pull the
strings from the shadows.
It's just much easier that way!
[LIAN PO laughs]
And, well, there are
other additional reasons,
I suppose too.
Oh! You have a guilty conscience
because you still
miss Zhao, right?
Understood, my lord.
If it is your decision,
we will accept it gladly.
You do seem happy to be
on the battlefield again.
[LIAN PO]
As do you all!
Bai Guixi!
[BAI GUIXI]
Hm?
Get over here!
Time for the usual, now!
Woohoo!
"The usual"?
Jie Zifang!
My lord!
[LIAN PO]
Good fortune!
[JIE ZIFANG]
And on you, my lord!
[LIAN PO grunting]
[gasps]
Next up, Lun Hu!
[LUN HU]
Aw, yeah! It's been so long!
[LIAN PO]
Good fortune to you!
[LUN HU]
That's the stuff!
Next up, Qiang Yan!
[QIANG YAN]
Sir!
Next! Xuan Feng, come here!
[XUAN FENG]
Ah. I think not.
[LIAN PO laughs]
[LIAN PO]
Next! Bai Guixi!
Eek! I, no, I just
don't think that--
[LIAN PO grunting]
[whimpers]
[LIAN PO]
May fortune be with you!
[BAI GUIXI]
Th-The pain.
No, th-the heat!
What is this?
This sensation? This--
This elation?
[BAI GUIXI] I feel this power
from the pit of my stomach.
Power welling up swiftly
all through me!
[BAI GUIXI grunts, yells]
[yells]
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[laughs]
Now then, shall we get started?
What do you all think?
Sir!
Sir.
Take your positions now!
[MESSENGER 218A] The Wei's
army's commanding general
is not Lian Po! It's Bai Guixi!
Repeat: Wei's commanding
general is Bai Guixi!
Lian Po's not in charge
of this whole thing?
Why wouldn't he be?
Meng Tian, my lord!
If it's not Lian Po, then--
[MENG TIAN]
Things just got tricky.
Now we can't count on Lian Po
to be in the main force.
[MENG AO]
Lian Po.
No matter what moves you make,
I will no longer be perplexed.
I have strengthened my resolve
since I battled you last!
[ADJUTANT 218A] Wang Jian, sir,
a smoke signal from the camp.
"Good luck in battle," it says.
[HUAN YI]
That's a new thing.
Old Bai Lao is getting
worked up for once, right now.
[MENG AO]
Lian Po!
It is I who shall
have the last laugh!
You will see!
First unit, take the
vanguard now! Forward!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[CHU SHUI]
Here we go.
[XIN]
Yeah.
[QIN SOLDIER 218A]
Yu Feng Force, coming through!
[XIN]
Wang Ben.
Seems like he got folded
into the first unit?
He's gonna get all the
glory before us again!
[MENG TIAN] An ad-hoc 1,000-man
squad in the first unit?
That's rough.
I'm sure that's a straw even
Wang Ben didn't wanna draw.
First unit, you couldn't ask
for a better opportunity.
Wouldn't ya say so, sir?
Let's show both the
Wei army and our allies
the absolute and sheer potency
of the Yu Feng Force right now!
Yes...
And him, as well.
A message from the general to
all troops of the first unit,
so listen carefully now!
This crucial first foray
will definitely determine
the very direction of the war!
Use all your power
to crush the enemy!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[LUN HU'S ADJUTANT]
Lun Hu, sir,
we are prepared
for mobilization.
Okay!
It's so quiet.
Do you think our
army's first unit
will be all right
starting up just like this?
[LIAN PO]
Hm...
[XIN gasps]
First unit!
Charge, now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Shall we?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[grunts]
[WEI SOLDIERS yelling]
Don't falter!
Go surround that spear boy and
take him down immediately!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[grunting]
Oh no, the first unit is
being forced back swiftly.
Shall I send the
second unit?
[laughs]
No need to panic.
I'll have you know,
this is when
your Wei soldiers
really start to shine!
Wait for it and see!
[BAI GUIXI]
Huh?
The fifth unit will
push in on the left.
Sir!
Seventh unit,
lead them to the right.
Eighth unit, you must
rush in right there.
Yes, sir!
Fifth unit, adjust formation!
Go to the left and
strike the enemy!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[GENERAL 218D]
Eighth unit, charge right now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[LUN HU]
Hm!
My lord was definitely right.
Wei's troops are all business.
I may be a stranger,
but they still follow
my orders to the letter.
Quite commendable!
Let's see, right now!
I guess I'll get started.
Might as well.
Our army has now pushed
them right back!
And they're taking the
offensive, it appears!
Ugh!
There he goes, finally!
Lun Hu!
[MESSENGER 218B]
General Tu Men!
Thousand-man commander
Tai Yun has just been slain!
[TU MEN]
Say what?
Tai Yun's squad was a
temporary 1,000-man unit.
So they weren't
strong enough, after all.
[MESSENGER 218C]
General!
The enemy's elite unit has
attacked Yan Bi's squad
and 1,000-man commander
Yan Bi has fallen!
What did you say?
[TU MEN]
Yan Bi's squad was another
temporary 1,000-man unit,
just like Tai Yun's also was.
It can't be!
Is someone now
targeting them?
[YU FENG SOLDIER 218A]
The fourth unit is struggling!
[FAN YANG]
Call back the second unit
and send them as
reinforcements, immediately!
[YU FENG SOLDIER 218A]
Sir!
[YU FENG SOLDIER 218B] The right
garrison is being pushed back!
What's taking them?
Seventh unit,
you are much too slow!
[YU FENG SOLDIER 218C]
The ninth unit has been captured
at the rear!
[FAN YANG]
What?!
[WANG BEN]
The squad is moving slower
with these extra 700 troops.
Slower than we're used to
with the Yu Feng Force.
[FAN YANG]
Zhou!
Go help the ninth unit now!
I will stay and
protect Wang Ben!
Sir!
[WANG BEN] The slower we move,
the more it will take
to tease open a seam now.
These new soldiers
are skilled,
but I knew they just
didn't measure up
to the battle-bred 300 men that
have been in the Yu Feng Force.
But, I didn't know how much
it would hold us back
fighting beside them
as we currently are!
[YU FENG SOLDIER 218D]
Wang Ben sir!
Lieutenant Fan Yang!
There's a new wave
coming from the left!
From the left, too? Fine!
Send the third unit
after them, right now!
But first, the right!
Get the right unit back
into formation, quickly!
[WANG BEN]
No.
First, we must face this.
Huh?
[SOLDIERS yelping, groaning]
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 218A groans]
[LUN HU]
Look close and you can tell
which squads are under command,
and which squads
aren't whatsoever.
The former is strong, of course,
and the latter is quite weak.
Furthermore, all of the weak
squads in the Qin army
truly are my handiwork,
having assassinated
all those commanders
and forced them to form
temporary squads, purposely.
I see.
So, you're the one responsible
for killing our 1,000-man
commanders at Jinliguan.
Bingo, Mr. 1,000-Man-
Commander-For-A-Day.
So right now,
I'll take your life too.
[FAN YANG]
Defend General Wang Ben!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[laughs] I wonder if you can!
Move now.
Me, move now?
I've got this one.