[NARRATOR] In the wake of his
success in the war with Wei,
Xin was made a
1,000-man commander.
But the Fei Xin Force kept
losing their front-line battles
guarding Qin's new territory,
and soon, Xin was
in danger of losing
his newly assigned higher rank.
Upon learning the problem
lay in their strategies,
Meng Tian called in a tactician
from the capital Xianyang:
his brother Meng Yi.
Or so he thought!
Paying Xin and his troops
a visit instead was...
[XIN]
What?
What are you
doing over here?
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS]
They know each other?!
[DIAO laughs]
[DIAO]
I knew you'd be surprised!
Honestly, I was positive that
it would still be a long time
before I'd be coming
to you like this,
so I was a little
surprised myself.
But, you know,
what can you do?
I've arrived to
help you out, Xin!
Diao!
Huh?
So then you--
You're here now instead
of Meng Tian's brother?
[LONG YQU] You mean, this
will be our new tactician?
[FEI XIN FORCE murmurs]
This little brat?
Are you kidding me?
And, well, furthermore--
We can deal with that later.
Long time no see, huh, Diao?
Wow, you sure have grown up!
That silly coat
won't fit much longer!
[DIAO gasps]
[XIN laughs]
What's this I see?
Seems like now, you went and got
yourself a real girly face!
--[XIN laughs]
--[DIAO] Huh?
[XIN]
How did that happen?
You been eatin'
your three squares?
[QU HAI] What are you
talking about, commander?
She very clearly is a woman.
[XIN]
Uh?
[DIAO sighs]
[DIAO] How long has it been
since I last saw Xin?
I've grown so
much since then.
He'll probably...
Too late to worry about that!
[DIAO]
I have already sorted through
all my feelings on
that matter, anyway!
A-A woman?
Yeah, right! As if, you guys!
[FEI XIN FORCE mumbles]
What the heck, Qu Hai?
[DIAO] He doesn't know?
I guess that must mean that--
No, I'm done being
vague and evasive.
What matters most now
is whether I can do my job
here as a tactician.
After all, I came here prepared
never to return to Shanyang!
[DIAO]
Xin!
[XIN]
Huh?
[DIAO] What he's saying isn't
wrong whatsoever, you see.
Uhh...
I'm sorry, Xin.
The truth is, I'm a girl.
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
I'm sorry I kept it
from you, but--
[XIN]
Diao,
don't tell me that you're
playing along with these idiots?
[clothes rustle]
[QING, WEI PING,
FEI XIN SOLDIERS gasp]
Oh no.
[DIAO]
You son of a--
--[blows landing]
--[XIN screams]
[DAO QING grunts]
Oh, Dao Qing, you really
do look very well.
[DAO QING]
What's this? You have come, too?
That's right.
Heard Lijing here was our way in
for reclaiming Shanyang.
[DAO QING chuckles]
That's not the only
reason you're here.
Ha! Ha! He saw right through me!
I'm after the Fei Xin Force.
[DAO QING] We really owe them
for what they did to us
in the Shanyang Offensive.
Of course-- the central army
was never the same
after Lun Hu was
strongly defeated.
If we had been stationed
at the general's side,
he'd still be alive.
So right now it's payback time
for us three men here,
after choking down
their truly bitter pill.
Well, as luck would have it,
the Fei Xin Force isn't doing
too good right now.
Well, that takes some of the fun
out of it, but yeah, all right.
This is the time
where we hack up
the hateful Xin of
the Fei Xin Force!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[grunting]
Whoa!
[YI]
Whoops! Where does this go?
Uh, Um, oh.
How about next to
that one there?
[YI]
Okay, here? And the rest?
[DIAO]
Oh, well, this can go there too.
[YI]
Got it.
[DIAO]
Um, that one goes here.
And put that one outside.
[YI]
Sure thing.
Hey there, Xin,
are you really letting that
little girl onto our squad?
[XIN groans]
If they lived together,
how did he never notice?
That commander of ours really
is pretty dumb, you know?
[XIN]
I'm right here!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS gasp]
[XIN groans]
[XIN]
When you think about it,
it does kinda ring a bell.
[XIN]
Diao, wanna go take a leak?
[DIAO]
Go by yourself, you idiot!
[XIN]
It's so hot!
You sure you don't
wanna take a dip?
[DIAO]
Put some clothes on, you idiot!
[XIN]
Diao, can we eat this?
[DIAO] Don't barge in
like that, you idiot!
[XIN] But why does she
have to be a woman, too?
What is this crazy
world coming to?
[TIAN YONG, WEI PING]
Hm...
[XIN]
Must be the times we live in.
Yeah, that's it.
[TIAN YONG, WEI PING,
QU HAI gasp]
Aw, well, I don't mind.
It's like my little brother
became my little sister.
No big deal.
[horse hooves thumping]
[FEI XIN CAVALRY A]
Urgent report!
The enemy is on the move!
A thousand troops
at the base of Mt. Xing,
all headed this
way immediately!
Say what?
They're coming already?
[FEI XIN CAVALRY A]
Yes, sir!
[DIAO]
"The base"? That doesn't help!
There are three paths there!
Are they coming by the coast,
the river, or the mountains?
Along the coast!
[DIAO]
How many horsemen?
I don't know
for certain!
W-Who are you?
[DIAO]
Fetch a map!
Send a patrol to
Mt. Zhen and Mt. Ba!
There might be other
enemy units working with them!
[XIN] Diao, how do you
know this area so well?
I memorized it all
on my way over here.
What's the hold up?
Where's the map?
Enough of your
meddling, little girl!
This is no place
for kids, you hear me?
Damn eyesore.
Now get out fast
before I kick you!
That Tian Yong is serious!
She's gonna cry!
That poor thing!
You jerk!
What--?
What did you...
What did you call me?!
I know any new tactician
is bound to encounter
some resentment.
But right now is just not
the time or place at all!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS,
QU HAI, WEI PING gasp]
[DIAO] Do you have a remote
idea of just how important
this area is for Shanyang?
That's why I'm here, but if
you keep going as you were,
there'll be no going back!
[TIAN YONG] Get out of here,
you mouthy brat!
[XIN]
That's enough, Tian Yong!
But I was--
[XIN]
I'll do the talking!
[TIAN YONG grunts]
[XIN] Diao, I know
you were serious
about becoming a tactician,
studying it and all.
[XIN]
Truth is, though,
I don't know for sure what
you're truly capable of yet.
So you can't just go
ordering the squad around
like you were doing
just a second ago.
Okay?
I'll let you come with us
to the main camp
but we'll run things
the same as always.
Yeah, I got it. Sure, Xin.
[YUAN] All units, prepare
to move out! Hurry!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
[DIAO sighs]
We brought them in just now,
but we have to carry them out.
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO]
Oh, you're that, um, well.
Yi.
[DIAO]
Yes, Yi.
Now, then.
Oh, here, I will do it.
[YI]
Come on, scooch.
[YI grunts]
Hang in there, buddy.
Huh?
I learned from
Lieutenant Qiang Lei,
that male or female
doesn't matter out here.
[DIAO]
Hm.
And also...
Huh?
[YI]
Never mind.
What was it?
[YI]
My wife back home,
you look a little like her
when she was young.
[DIAO]
Huh?!
[YI] Or maybe my daughter,
given your age.
Both are real cute.
Oh, come on, now.
[YI laughs] Just, you know,
do your very best.
[DIAO]
Hm.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[FEI XIN MESSENGER A] Report!
Tian Yong's unit is struggling!
Say what?
[FEI XIN MESSENGER A]
They need reinforcements!
[XIN]
Got it!
[FEI XIN MESSENGER B] The same
goes for Long YRu's unit, too!
Send out Wei Ping's and
Ze Gui's units on the double!
Sir!
[DIAO]
Wait up!
[XIN gasps]
Those two units
do not need help.
What are you talking about?
I mean that they are in
places they can afford to leave.
If they're struggling,
they should flee
to the underbrush at
the rear and regroup.
I'm far more
concerned about
Pei Lang's, Chong Yuan's,
and Tian YRu's posts, you see.
[YUAN, XIN gasp]
[DIAO] If this spot falls
to Wei, it'll cut off
lines of communication
to our units nearby.
And once the enemy
notices all this,
they'll come at us really hard.
It would be better to send
the reinforcements over there.
[YUAN]
To Pei Lang and the other two?
But, we've heard
nothing from them.
[XIN]
Diao!
[YUAN]
Eh?
You promised earlier that
you would keep out of this!
Talking to myself.
[XIN growls]
[YUAN]
Commander, what should we do?
What do you mean "what"?
We do what I said!
Send reinforcements to
Tian Yong and Long YRu!
[YUAN]
Sir!
[NARRATOR] However, Xin's
strategy backfired once again.
Just as Diao predicted,
the enemy had stationed
several troops
near the other three commanders.
What might!
When did the Wei army
get this strong?
They're definitely
on a whole other level
than the soldiers
we fought before!
[FEI XIN CAVALRY B]
Urgent report!
[YUAN, XIN]
Uh!
Pei Lang's, Chong Yuan's and
Tian YRu's units have collapsed,
and the enemy has
taken their camps!
[XIN]
What?!
They have cut off all of
our lines of communication!
There's no telling how
the other units are!
What is this?
Xin, sir!
[XIN]
Bring me my horse, now!
I'm taking them back!
[DIAO]
Don't, Xin!
They have already
set a trap now!
[XIN grunts]
[DIAO]
Please, Xin...
...let me lead.
[DIAO]
Make a decision!
Hurry up, or the scattered
squads will most certainly
be wiped out to their roots.
[XIN grunting]
[DIAO]
Xin!
[XIN]
All right.
Where could they be?
That's really strange.
Given the personality
of that Xin,
I expected him to rush over
to take back this territory.
Any changes in
the Fei Xin Force?
None that we are
aware of presently, sir.
[BING GUI grunts]
Well, then.
[WEI MESSENGER A]
Report! Report!
The enemy's main camp
has suddenly disappeared
as of right now!
Vanished?
So, they're on their
way here now?
No.
[JIAN YONG]
Hm?
They could potentially
be looking for allies
and trying to regroup.
[gasps]
Set up a dragnet!
The enemy's main unit
left with 100 men!
If we find them,
we can smash them easily!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[WEI PING yells]
Watch where you're walkin'!
[WEI PING]
Be quiet!
[XIN] Why are we in
these woods again?
[DIAO] They'll find us
if we use the road!
Just go as fast as you can!
It all comes down to speed!
[NARRATOR] As the Wei tactician,
Bing Gui had surmised,
the Fei Xin Force's
main camp at Diao's direction
was dashing around, gathering
their scattered comrades.
Meanwhile...
[WEI SOLDIER B]
Stay alert! They are nearby!
[WEI SOLDIER C]
Kill them all!
[NARRATOR]
In response,
Bing Gui had laid out
a large-scale dragnet.
[NARRATOR]
However,
by the time the
dragnet was in place,
Diao and the squad had already
fled to its far side.
[laughs]
--[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
--We did it, Diao!
[DIAO]
We haven't done anything yet.
This is where it gets serious.
We move the main camp
to the hill ahead!
Show me the map!
I'll mark where the
scattered units are!
Go find them!
[FEI XIN FORCE yells]
[MENG TIAN]
A girl?
[MENG YI]
Yes.
[MENG TIAN]
Huh?
[MENG YI] I'm not standing up
for her or anything,
but gender is not much
of an issue for a tactician.
Well, I suppose.
As long as this works.
That much I can pledge.
What I mean is,
she's received our teacher's
special tactician's permit.
[MENG TIAN]
From your teacher?
The first early permit
since you, brother.
I'm the only one at
school who can match her
at tabletop tactics,
I will have you know.
Well, all right, then.
[MENG TIAN]
Then all that's left...
...is her aptitude for
the tactician position.
[gasps]
[MENG TIAN]
Without it,
no amount of talent will ever
let her shine as a tactician.
[MENG YI]
It turns out,
He Liao Diao has already
experienced battle
which is a plus.
[MENG TIAN]
Hm.
But still, though.
We won't know for sure
until we see how
it all turns out.
[QING]
Hey, there they are!
I got Tian Yong's
unit right here!
[QU HAI] You guys are
all right too, I see!
[laughs]
Pretty gutsy of you to
move the main camp, then!
Guess even Xin has
his good days, huh?
[QU HAI]
It wasn't Xin.
Huh?
[QU HAI] This is all courtesy
of the girl tactician.
What? Seriously?
[LONG YQU]
You're not the only ones.
She found us as well,
completely cut off and
wandering around aimlessly.
Yeah, and us too.
Us as well.
[PEI LANG] She figured out where
all the scattered units were
and gathered us
together on insight alone.
Looks like that brat's
no ordinary girl, after all.
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO]
They're here!
[MENG YI]
A tactician's aptitude
is always tested in
their first battle.
Aptitude?
Because we're still
only theoretical tacticians.
We don't know the terror
in going to the battlefield.
If you don't kill these guys,
the enemy will close in,
can you stay calm?
How about when...
...you have to set two
people up to kill one another?
[DIAO gasps]
[MENG YI] The pieces we handle
so casually every day,
represent the lives of hundreds
of real live human beings.
The terror of war's greater
than you can imagine.
Plenty of budding tacticians
got swallowed up in that
and were crushed,
totally helpless.
[XIN]
Diao! The enemy is here!
D-Diao?
[DIAO] After experiencing
several battles,
I thought I knew
what it was like.
But I was wrong.
The heat and the bloodlust
carried on the wind!
It's never felt this
insanely oppressive before.
I get it now.
[DIAO] This is what it's
like on the battlefield!
[DIAO] And the battle
hasn't even started yet!
I won't get swallowed up!
Hey there, Diao!
Oh, I know!
Here we go!
Get into position!
[FEI XIN SOLDIERS grunt]
[DIAO] I'll swallow up
the battlefield, instead.
Huh?
[JIAN YONG laughs]
So now they are on the move!
Dao Qing's to the front!
[WEI SOLDIER D]
Yes, sir!
Dao Qing? Are you sure?
He's got 1,000
elite troops with him!
It'll be done soon!
Well then, so be it.
Dao Qing's unit!
We're taking point now!
Consider it an honor!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[BING GUI] The Fei Xin Force's
main unit escaped the dragnet
before we could close in.
Then, they joined up
with their scattered troops.
Regrouping so quickly.
Clearly, they must have gotten
some brains on board, finally.
Let us go!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
[BING GUI]
This one move will show me
just what their
tactician's made of!
[DIAO grunts]
They're here!
The enemy vanguard!
Eight hundred, maybe 1,000
with about 200 cavalry!
Oh, I'm Tian Xiao,
your faithful adjutant now.
[DIAO]
Yes, hello, Tian Xiao.
It's 300 cavalry
and 700 infantry.
[TIAN XIAO]
Yes ma'am!
[DIAO]
Out of all 4,000 troops,
a quarter of them are
now on the move.
And an elite force at that!
They definitely don't
want this over,
they're clearly trying
to see how we react.
[DIAO] They mean to
directly gauge my ability!
[DIAO]
This is perfect!
[TIAN XIAO gasps]
All troops stand by,
right now!
[XIN]
Huh?
So we're not going
anywhere then?
[DIAO] Suddenly,
it's 1,000 versus 1,000.
But if we lose too much
manpower right here,
we won't be able to
fight their other 3,000.
We have to factor
that into our tactics
and defeat them efficiently.
[TIAN XIAO]
He Liao Diao!
If we don't intercept
the enemy, they will--
No mind!
[TIAN XIAO gasps]
[DIAO] They can't tell
from over there...
[DIAO] ...that the Wei army
has lots of branching paths
on their way!
This is where we will...
Bury their 1,000-man
vanguard, let's go!