[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
of the neighboring land of Wei.
Wang Ben, Meng Tian, and Xin.
These bold soldiers and
aspiring great generals
were together here now,
ready to usher in
a brand new age!
Having assassinated many of
Meng Ao's 1,000-man commanders,
Lun Hu fought
one-on-one with Xin,
then vanished like the wind.
But Meng Ao's army was able
to persevere through this,
remaining ultra-vigilant
and prepared
for another possible attack.
[MENG TIAN]
Xin?
Do you have a second?
Oh man, you again.
Can't stay away?
[MENG TIAN]
Don't you make that face.
I'm here because something's
been on my mind.
[XIN]
What is that?
[MENG TIAN] Well, it's all of
those commanders being killed.
You must have heard
all about it by now.
Did you pick up on
anything then, Xin?
[XIN]
What do you mean?
Like, how they were different
from all the Wei troops
we've seen so far.
Different, you say?
Well, uh...
[MENG TIAN]
Hm.
There was this geezer-brat who
was saying all this random stuff
about the heavens,
or something.
Huh?! A geezer-brat?
[XIN] I thought he was
a 300-man commander,
but he was a general!
[XIN laughs]
Name's Lun Ho,
or Land Ho, I dunno.
[MENG TIAN]
Whoa, whoa! He's a general!
At least remember his name!
Well, whoever he is,
he's insanely powerful.
And I get this terrible feeling
he was holding back with me.
He's unlike anyone that
we've fought so far.
Do you know anything
about General Lian Po?
[XIN]
Lian Po?
Oh, He's some famous
general guy, right?
Quite strong and
all that, I believe?
"Strong" doesn't
begin to cover it!
He's actually one of Zhao's
Three Greats, as mighty as
Qin's six great generals
I'll have you know!
What? Lian Po was one of
the Three Greats, then?
Lian Po seems to be
currently in exile in Wei.
However, as a former
Zhao general like him,
Wei's King Jingmin
doesn't really trust him.
So in the three years
Lian Po's been exiled there,
the King has not allowed him
to command the Wei army,
not even once.
The entire Middle Kingdom
believes Lian Po
to currently be
out of commission.
But, what if that's all
nonsense in reality?
Huh?
Because, if the dispassionate
treatment towards Lian Po
is a massive Wei lie,
we'll be stepping
blindly into a place
where one of the Three Greats
is lying in wait
just to get to us in the end.
Ah! What?
But then--
[MENG WU]
I see your intuition is still
the only mature thing about you.
[MENG TIAN, XIN gasp]
G-General Meng Wu?!
[MENG WU]
Just where are you going, Tian?
[MENG TIAN gasps]
Father of mine!
It has been so long!
I'm glad to see
you're looking well.
Wait, he is your,
um, your father?
O-Oh, uh, didn't I mention it?
Uh, you look nothing alike!
[laughs]
Say there, boy, what became
of Wang Yi's poleax?
[MENG TIAN, XIN]
Uh...
It's still a little
too heavy for me.
[MENG TIAN]
Xin has Wang Yi's weapon?
If you are never going to use
it, I'll take it off your hands.
Yeah, right!
So then, Father, what brings
you way over here?
I didn't expect you to
be joining this campaign.
I'm here as Lord
Changping's messenger
concerning the matter
you were discussing earlier.
[MENG TIAN] Xin, that general
you fought earlier on today
was working for Lian Po,
without a doubt.
Looks that way.
Which can only mean
we're already caught
up in his scheme.
Yeah, but being up against
one of the Three Greats
is all the more reason
why we cannot lose!
May I, my lord?
Right now?
What is it?
There's something I
do not understand.
My motivation?
[QIANG YAN]
Yes.
Why my lord would suddenly
rise up at this very moment,
after remaining silent
for three years.
Because he encouraged me to do
so, three years ago, so you see.
"He" sir? Who did?
One of Qin's six
great generals, Wang Yi.
[QIANG YAN]
I have not forgotten.
Three years ago is when
our Wei exile began.
However, you said Wang Yi
suggested this to you?
That's right, he suggested it
when you were travelling
between Wei and
Zhao at the time.
So, did Wang Yi send
you a missive then?
[laughs]
Not a missive, no.
The man himself appeared
before me in the flesh,
at the very residence that
was provided to me in Wei.
[LIAN PO]
Wang Yi.
Do you know what?
You always did have
this paralyzing effect on me.
You have my sympathies for
all your troubles, Lian Po.
[LIAN PO]
How good of you to come.
Come in!
I have prepared good
liquor like before a war!
I'll keep you here drinking
for a full ten days!
[LIAN PO laughs]
[WANG YI laughs]
Much obliged.
[LIAN PO] Wang Yi had had
to go through all that trouble
to cross borders just
to be able to visit me
in Wei exiled from Zhao.
Along the way, he had
stuck his nose into a battle
between Wu Qing and Lord Biao,
so his visit had to remain
a big secret at the time.
Surprising indeed.
How happy you must have been,
enjoying your time with him.
Indeed, happy to
bring tears to my eyes.
But then again,
I really did cry
plenty that night!
[LIAN PO laughs]
[LIAN PO] If Lin Xiangru
of the Three Greats and I
were friends, who would
gladly risk our necks
for one another at any time,
Wang Yi and his fellow
generals were my greatest,
and definitely
most hated foes.
But at the same time, they were
friends with whom I shared
suffering and joy alike.
So when the head of the
six great generals, Bai Qi,
had killed himself,
I wept badly.
And when Liao was done in
by some dirty rogue,
I shook with complete rage.
Then...
How did Wang Yi manage
to successfully
entice you, my lord?
All that deep blood-tingling
and heavy heart-pounding action
are in the past.
The world's dull.
General, I understand
your sorrow all too well,
I must admit.
However, you see,
if there ever comes a time
when you will take a stand,
let it be in battle
against Meng Ao's army.
That should prove a very
pleasant diversion.
[LIAN PO growls]
Meng Ao?
You mean...
...that pathetic
mediocre general?
[LIAN PO]
Mediocre?
You've really got that right!
[laughs]
[TU MEN]
Lian Po is on the move now?
[RONG BEI] This isn't good
at all, General Tu Men.
Any castle he guards is
practically impervious!
Even when General Bai Qi
took on Lian Po--
Settle down, now.
There is absolutely
no reason to panic.
[QIN SOLDIERS gasp]
Lian Po's arrival was not
unexpected in the slightest.
My lieutenants have always
had detailed plans in place
to deal with him, you see.
[QIN SOLDIERS gasp]
[MENG AO laughs]
It was very good of you
to tell me this, my dearest son.
Knowing this so early means
we can take our time
building our strategy.
It seems today's war council
will run a bit long.
Why don't I find us
something to drink?
That's classic Meng Ao!
He barely bats an eye
at the mention of Lian Po.
[MENG AO]
So, Lian Po is back now.
[MENG WU ADVISOR 216A]
Bluffing, you say?
Yes.
General Meng Ao?
It didn't look like
he was bluffing.
This isn't the
first time my father
has done battle with Lian Po.
[MENG WU ADVISOR 216B]
What? But that can't be right.
[MENG WU] You know very
well that my father and I
are originally from
the kingdom of Qi.
[MENG WU ADVISOR 216B]
Yes, but--
[MENG WU] My father is of the
same generation as Lian Po.
As young soldiers, they fought
each other countless times
in battles between
Qi and Zhao.
What's more,
my father has never been
able to win against him.
What?
No, it can't be.
So when the path to becoming
general was closed to him in Qi,
he was shunted over to Qin
with his young son in tow.
Father soon found
success in Qin,
but never faced Lian Po again.
It has been something that
has haunted him ever since.
I really doubt Lian Po even
remembers fighting my father
to begin with, truthfully.
For my father,
Lian Po is just like one
huge wall that is simply
insurmountable in his view.
[NARRATOR]
Meng Ao had a strange habit.
[NARRATOR] When he was under
excessive mental pressure,
he would remove his
general's armor at once
and simply transform into
an old and grimy foot soldier
and take a stroll
around the camp.
He would cap this off
by sinking back
into a quiet field,
and quite simply emptying
his head in nature.
However, that night...
Lian Po.
Why him and why right now, then?
Still, hmm.
Quite an incredibly nice moon.
[XIN]
Yes!
Dinner is served, finally!
[XIN laughs]
[groans]
Sorry for stomping on you.
Your nose stop bleeding?
You'll be okay.
Ugh...
Hang on, lemme get
you a little nibble.
Did you actually catch
that rabbit yourself?
Yeah!
It's my own delicious dinner!
Our rations aren't enough
to fill my hungry belly.
Those higher-ups sure are
stingy to us, huh, Gramps?
[MENG AO]
Mm.
[XIN]
Here!
[MENG AO]
Oh!
[XIN]
Whoa, Gramps!
You're huge!
Who are you? And that beard?
Oh wow! You gotta tell me, now!
[MENG AO laughs]
How very strange.
I've never seen a big
ol' foot soldier like you
around here before.
[laughs] Oh, no?
I have never seen a
youngster foot soldier
like you before, either.
I am actually quite
surprised, myself.
I'm no youngster foot soldier!
Xin of the Fei Xin Force,
a proper 300-man commander!
[MENG AO]
Hm. The Fei Xin Force?
The special forces
so dubbed by Wang Yi?
So then, this is Xin
of the Fei Xin Force.
The one who inherited
Wang Yi's poleax.
[laughs]
So, what're you doing out here?
Well, I was actually
just taking a little
escape from reality.
[laughs] Whaddya mean?
Do old men still have lots of
stuff to worry about, as well?
[MENG AO]
Of course we do!
With great experience
comes serious concerns.
Well, let this 300-man
commander hear 'em!
All right, then.
Don't mind if I
spill them out to you.
When I was younger,
I never once was able to win
a fight against this one fellow.
[XIN]
Yep, that happens.
Now I'm just a really old man,
see, and it looks like
I'll be fighting him again
in the very near future.
But it appears that he hasn't
grown weak with age at all.
Instead, he's in his
very prime these days.
It boggles my mind.
Wow, I can't imagine being that
old and still in your prime.
Yes. He is a monster.
[laughs] It's serious,
is it not?
So, an old man has to take
on this massive monster.
Hmm.
I just don't see the point
in worrying about it.
I mean, you did it, Gramps!
Huh? Wait, boy,
have you listened
to a word I have said to you?
'Course I have!
You gotta fight this monster guy
that's still in his prime,
and you've never managed to
beat him before, am I correct?
But you already did it!
Wait, what do you mean
by "did it", exactly?
You got yourself the
perfect opportunity
to turn the tables on this guy
around this time, for sure!
Huh?
[XIN] Okay then, the winner is
the last man standing, right?
You will win now, and run after.
Then you'll surely have
won the whole thing, see?
Huh?
[laughs]
Whoa!
You startled me!
Well, you are definitely
right about that, Commander.
If I win now,
I will turn the tables,
and victory will be mine!
[laughs]
O-Oh yeah.
You show 'im, Gramps!
[yawns]
[GUO JIAO]
As you know, the recent attacks
have left us short
some commanders!
Those units will either be
led by their lieutenants,
or they'll be dissolved
and incorporated
into other units immediately!
Listen, Xin!
This is really important!
[yawns]
[GUO JIAO] However, two
1,000-man commander positions
remain open right now.
Therefore,
we will now be promoting
two 300-man commanders
on the spot,
so listen carefully!
Huh?
Huh? Did he just--
He said they're promoting
300-man commanders
into 1,000-man commanders!
This is great, Xin!
Now you can--
No, just wait a second.
They are promoting
only two commanders,
it sounded like.
Who will they choose?
What's your take, Qiang Lei?
If we're going only by rights,
it'll be Wang Ben and Meng Tian.
[growls]
Aw, hey, wait!
What's going on?
Now those selected:
First up is...
[GUO JIAO]
Meng Tian of the Le Hua Force!
You are hereby promoted
to 1,000-man commander!
Yours will become
a 1,000-man unit
with an extra 700 troops!
[LE HUA FORCE cheers]
You really did it,
Meng Tian, sir!
At long last!
I'm conflicted.
[XIN]
Meng Tian...
What did you expect?
He already was at the
1,000-man command level.
O-Oh yeah.
So then, uh...
Who's the other one?
[GUO JIAO] And the second
300-man commander to be promoted
as of this moment
is none other than...
[GUO JIAO]
Wang Ben of the Yu Feng Force!
[YU FENG FORCE cheers]
[laughs] It was only natural
you'd be chosen, sir,
in absolutely every
sense of the word!
[POPS laughs]
[growls] Figured it
would be them!
They do get good results
out in the battlefield,
and they are
nobility, after all.
Are you all right, Xin, sir?
[XIN]
Well, I...
X-Xin, sir.
Xin.
Commander.
You are all dismissed!
[MENG AO]
Wait.
[TU MEN]
Meng Ao, sir! What is it?
Xin of the Fei Xin Force!
Come forward.
Xin, sir, the
general's calling you!
Xin, sir!
Y-Yeah.
[XIN] General Meng Ao
is now calling me?
Huh?
[MENG AO giggles]
Y-You're that guy from last--
[MENG AO laughs] If we consider
the sheer ability shown
by Xin of the
Fei Xin Force here,
it is true that
on this campaign
he is definitely outshone
by both Meng Tian
and Wang Ben together.
However, if we look at the
prowess shown in the past
battle with Zhao,
we see he has demonstrated
might beyond that
of a 300-man commander.
In other words, it truly
is worth creating
a third commander's
post just for him
at this moment, as well.
Huh?
Wha--?
[GUO JIAO]
But--
I don't understand, sir,
if we need another commander,
there are plenty
to choose from.
Then there's the problem of him
simply being of servant stock.
And why is that
a problem, exactly?
Er, n-nothing.
This is just an
arbitrary decision
that was made on a whim.
Accepting this promotion
will naturally provoke the ire
of those around
you right now.
To silence their objections
once and for all,
I must add a rather extreme
requirement on top of this.
[XIN]
An extreme requirement?
You must take
the enemy's head.
[XIN, SOLDIERS gasp]
[MENG AO] Specifically,
the heads of three or more
1,000-man commanders,
or the head of one general.
If you do not
deliver my requests,
you will be demoted
three ranks,
and must start again
from corporal.
In short,
if you fail,
then, the Fei Xin Force
will be disbanded.
Well, then?
Will you still accept this,
Xin of the Fei Xin Force?
[XIN]
Ha! Like I said previously,
that's nothin' worth worrying
about, really, Gramps!
[MENG AO]
Mm-hm.
Impertinent!
How dare you speak
to the general like that!
Anyone who'd back down
'cause he's afraid of failure,
woulda been better off
just stayin' at home, I say!
Starting over from corporal?
If I screw up,
I'll start over from the bottom
rung as a foot soldier!
What's more, I'm thinking much,
much bigger than just
one lousy general's head.
Huh?
This Xin here is
going after the head
of commanding enemy
general, Lian Po!
[MENG AO]
Mmm.
Very well.
Xin of the Fei Xin Force,
you are hereby promoted
to a 1,000-man commander!
The Fei Xin Force will
also gain 700 troops
to become a
1,000-man unit!
[FEI XIN FORCE cheers]
[XIN]
We did it!
A 1,000-man commander?
I'm sure he's
quite strong and all,
but he's still very
much a child.
Is he sure about this?
[MENG WU]
My father's military skill
may lag behind that
of other generals.
but as a judge of
character, however,
he truthfully is without equal.
If that is who's
recommending him,
he should be fine.