[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
of the neighboring land of Wei.
Wang Ben, Meng Tian, and Xin:
these bold soldiers and
aspiring great generals
were together here now, ready
to usher in a brand-new age!
[gasps] Xin, sir, look!
[gasps]
[XIN]
What is it?
[YUAN] The Yu Feng Force finally
managed to gain a foothold,
but the ladder brigade
isn't following up on it.
[gasps]
--I bet...
--[YUAN, XIN] Huh?
...this was the Yu Feng
Force's sneak attack
that other squads
don't know about.
But that means--
Uh-huh.
[SOLDIERS roar]
[XIN]
The Yu Feng Force is alone
and helpless with that army!
[MENG TIAN]
However, it's all gone
just according to plan so far.
[MENG TIAN] Why don't
we just see what you can do
from way up there,
Wang Ben.
[WANG BEN]
Hmph.
[SOLDIERS roar]
Kill them!
Just go in there and smash them!
[WEI SOLDIER D]
Gang up on 'em!
They seem to be getting
shoved off to the left.
They won't be able to strike
the crucial wall
commander like that.
[MENG TIAN]
Hmmm.
[MENG TIAN gasps]
Oh, I get it now!
Huh?
[XIN] The guys
who put up the smokescreen
are standing by on their horses?
[ADJUTANT laughs] They're
nearly done for now, sir!
[laughs] Wang Ben, sir!
[FAN YANG]
You truly are
a force to be reckoned with.
Defenses, now!
[XIN, YUAN]
Huh?
What in the--
What's this?
They've set up a base,
of all places!
[FENG BO]
Hmm...
Oh!
[FENG BO]
Rope?
From the beginning,
I was never after
just your head.
Oh!
It can't be! But that is just
right over the castle gates!
Gatekeepers look sharp!
The enemy is approaching!
[WEI SOLDIERS gasp]
Enemies!
[GATE GUARD B]
They mean to open the gates!
[GATE GUARD C]
Kill them!
[GATE GUARD D]
Don't let them open anything!
[FAN YANG]
Too late!
The smokescreen brigade
is waiting down below
to storm the castle
at the precise moment
when we open the
gates from within!
[FAN YANG]
There's not a speck of fat
to trim in this strategy.
Who'd ever believe
it came from the mind
of such a young commander?
They all ought to keep a
very close eye on him now!
Soon the whole world
will be singing his praises:
Such is the prowess of Wang Ben!
Open!
Yahoo!
[WANG BEN, FAN YANG gasp]
[FAN YANG]
Wha--
[XIN gasps]
Ah! What on earth
is going on up there?
Huh?
What are they doing?
[NARRATOR]
The commanders guarding
the castle walls
were speechless.
Before they knew it,
the Qin flag was flying high
above over the main castle,
where the lord resided.
Meaning Gaolang
Castle had fallen.
From Meng Tian's Le Hua Force
storming the gates
to the fall of the castle,
the job was completely over,
as quick as lightning.
[YU FENG CORPORAL A]
Le Hua Force!
Exactly what do you
think you are all doing?
This gate was only
for Yu Feng to storm!
You do not get to slip
in and snatch it away!
That's brazen thievery,
plain and simple!
Shame on you!
Did you say thief?
You mean to insult
Meng Tian so unabashedly?
[YU FENG CORPORAL A]
And why wouldn't we insult him?
You Le Hua Force jokers
are always just a bunch of--
[LE HUA CORPORAL A]
Always what? Out with it!
[YU FENG CORPORAL A]
All right! Fine!
But you asked for it!
You're always gett....
C'mon now Xin.
It's got nothing to do with us.
[LE HUA CORPORAL A] And you're
always stealing our thunder!
No, that's you.
It's really not us!
[WANG BEN]
Stop it. That's enough.
They are all free to pass
through the open gate.
The problem truly lies
in our letting them get
there first, you see.
But Wang Ben, sir.
But Wang Ben, sir!
You see, it's like I said!
[YU FENG CORPORAL A]
Meng Tian! Why you.
[chuckles] Kidding!
We owe you one, and we'll
pay you back someday.
That is for sure.
No need. I'll just make
sure my future strategies
include a pitfall
with your name on it.
Count on that.
[laughs] Yikes! That's scary!
Hmm?
[MENG TIAN]
Hey! Xin of the Fei Xin Force!
Why watch from down there?
Come on up already!
[WEI PING]
Uh!
[XIN grunts]
[WANG BEN]
Let's go.
[YU FENG CORPORAL B]
Sir!
Oh dear!
Gone so fast without even
a proper thank you first?
I simply don't talk to losers.
Who you calling
a loser Wang Ben?
You punks don't
play fair at all!
Bringing in a big old
thing like you did.
Because even we could take down
a castle easily with
that crazy massive thing!
[WANG BEN]
Just as it's not unfair
for one who knows the
sword to wield a sword...
[XIN gasps]
[WANG BEN]
...I simply used the siege tower
I happened to have on hand.
You find the strangest faults.
Nobility is a gift,
too, you know.
You little--
[chuckles] Now, now!
Don't get so riled up!
It's only the first castle.
We are just
getting started. Huh?
[XIN]
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey, do you smell smoke?
Uh. Huh?
[FEI XIN SOLDIER A]
Fire!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER B]
There's fire all over the town!
Can't be...
[MENG TIAN]
Wait!
We really shouldn't
get involved.
What do you mean?
Let me go, darnit!
[WEI PING]
Hey, Xin!
Xin!
Xin, sir!
Qiang Lei, you take over now!
[panting]
[civilians crying, wailing]
[XIN]
Wha--
Hey, what are you all doing?
--Hmm?
--Huh?
[XIN growls]
No! Please, Xin!
Stay back!
Let me go Yuan!
Why are you stopping me?
They're on our side!
Fighting allies is a crime!
It might even cost
you your head!
[LUAN TONG]
What are they doing here?
You over there!
This place belongs
to my 1,000-man squad!
If you're looking for
some loot, look elsewhere!
Idiot!
X-Xin sir!
--Let me go! Let me go Yuan!
--Help me, hold him!
Xin!
This is just how it is!
[XIN gasps]
[YUAN] Truth is,
we have only had victory
in all of our minds,
but this battle is an invasion.
Unfortunately, this kind of
thing comes with the territory.
Always.
[XIN] I know this.
Oh, I know all right.
I know that war
isn't pretty whatsoever.
But that doesn't mean...
...I gotta shut up and let
this kind of thing slide!
We won't let it slide.
The army has rules
and regulations.
You there commander!
Stop your rampage once
and for all, right now!
The enemy has
already surrendered!
This is a clear violation
of military law!
We'll be reporting
this to your superiors!
Don't make things worse.
It really is for your own good!
Huh?
[laughter]
So. That's what their
whole deal really is!
Man, what a pain!
My name is Luan Tong.
So get lost!
You newbies just don't know
the first thing about war!
Sure, there's a law
in the army about
killing someone who's
already surrendered,
but nobody obeys it!
This here is a special privilege
for the winner,
you understand me?
[whimpers]
[LUAN TONG]
And don't you forget it!
Nearly 100 of my own
men died in this battle.
Stop it!
[WEI CIVILIAN A]
Auuugh!
[LUAN TONG spits]
It doesn't matter
how many Wei pigs die!
Do you finally get the picture?
[XIN growls]
You monster!
Hahaha! A complete idiot!
He's gone out in front.
Kill the kid now!
Sir!
Xin, please, sir!
Just don't kill them!
Aaah!
[XIN]
Just this guy.
[XIN grunts]
[YUAN]
Meng Tian!
[MENG TIAN]
I know you know that killing a
1,000-man commander, will
mean that you lose everything.
Everything.
[XIN grunts]
Shut up!
[MENG TIAN]
Xin.
Is it worth all your dreams
of being a great general?
[XIN groans]
[LUAN TONG]
You punk.
Do you know exactly what
you're getting yourself
into right now, huh?
A nothing like yourself kills
a 1,000-man commander like me,
and that means your head.
Do you understand me now?
All your little buddies here
will get swept up
in this mess, as well.
The man is telling you
the truth, I'm afraid.
[MENG TIAN]
Put the sword away, Xin.
[LUAN TONG]
You brat!
Tell your minions to lay off
their underhanded
ways, right now.
Then swear you
won't lay a finger
on any surrendered townsfolk
ever again, you hear me!
[laughs] Stupid!
I'm not gonna make them stop
and I'm gonna keep doing
what I want with these losers!
Heck that's why I go to war.
I love that part!
Got it?
You march in here all righteous
with no clue about reality?
Nothing upsets
me more than that!
[XIN growls]
[gasping]
Now you have done it...
Nothing angers me more
than people like you
who blame reality,
trying to justify all
the nonsense they pull!
[XIN]
"Everybody does it"?
What kind of an excuse is that?
Evil is evil!
Xin of the Fei Xin Force,
will never put up
with an evil man
no matter his reasons!
It does not matter if he is
a 1,000-man commander,
a general, or a king!
It's just, that's
the way I fight.
Always has been
and always will be.
Period!
[gasping]
[XIN]
Pretending I didn't see all this
just outta fear
of being punished?
What world's greatest
general does that?
[gasps]
[cheering]
[WEI PING]
Xin!
[UNDERLING B]
Wh-What are they up to?
Never mind that. Just kill them!
Avenge our commander right now!
Hold on! That's the
famous Fei Xin Force
hailing from the eastern front!
It is?
But to just let him kill
a 1,000-man commander?
Oh don't you worry about that.
He killed a
1,000-man commander.
He'll definitely
be court-martialed
and beheaded before
you know it. [laughs]
What? Are you kidding me?
Why's he the one
getting pardoned,
and we are the ones
getting interrogated instead?
He has not been pardoned.
He is being held overnight.
Xin of the Fei
Xin Force struck back
in self-defense after the
1,000-man commander
Luan Tong attacked him first.
I understand Luan Tong's
wounds weren't even that deep.
However, the excessive
barbarism you displayed
toward all of
the surrendered foes
does call for a
court-martial, understand?
It has been
approved now. Approach!
I shall start
with you, Lieutenant.
Uh... H-Hey!
Let me go you goons!
Listen! Just listen all right?
We're not the
only ones you know!
Everybody's doing it!
Men from my own squad--
Thank goodness.
Just because that commander
is still alive somehow,
doesn't mean
I wasn't worried that Xin
would lose his head
over this. I'm relieved.
Does this happen often?
Huh?
I mean this all just turned out
a little too well
for us, I would say.
Well. You're right. Uh?
[YUAN]
Qiang Lei?
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Come on. You too, come here!
[UNDERLING B]
Ow! Hands off!
So how's that for
you then, young sir?
You have been
very helpful, General.
I'll surely pay
you back before long.
Oh ho, those are some
really fine words indeed!
I'll be waiting with bated
breath.
[WANG BEN]
So this is your doing?
[MENG TIAN]
Hmm?
Wang Ben!
Unlike you I have
no qualms about trading
on my father's and grandfather's
influence when needed.
Making this kind
of thing go away?
Piece of cake, you see.
Why would you
help someone like him?
He's really a child.
He leads 300 men,
yet he cannot
control his emotions?
It would serve him
if he were beheaded.
Taking down one
or two rogue commanders
won't change a thing whatsoever.
If you really want to
make changes in the army,
you have got to be at the top.
Yes, exactly.
And that's why we've been
continually closing our eyes
to all of these heinous,
barbaric acts.
But you know,
I'm very certain
Xin knows that, too.
He knew full well,
and still did what he did.
[MENG TIAN] His confidence
in himself is unwavering,
straight as an arrow that
is flying through the air.
He truly has his very own path
to becoming one of the
world's greatest generals.
What can I say? I like him,
that fiery Xin of
the Fei Xin Force.
[WANG BEN] Confidence
or no, a fool is still a fool.
What is more, he's starting out
fatally far down the ladder.
[MENG TIAN]
Hmm.
And despite that fact,
I have been thinking that...
[WANG BEN]
Hmm?
[MENG TIAN]
...he could be a formidable foe
for us somewhere down the road
Yikes, right?
[WANG BEN]
Don't make me laugh.
[girl crying]
[QIN SOLDIER C] We don't
want to have to hurt you.
What are you gonna do
with your parents gone?
Just come quietly now.
We get paid well y'know.
You can live a pretty good life.
You think they'll sell,
looking all poor and
the way they do now?
That's a good point.
Let's look somewhere else.
[gasps]
[QIN SOLDIER C]
Yeah, right.
Huh?
Why let you live if
you won't bring us money?
So what if you're kids?
The people of Wei are our
sworn enemies, you know!
Huh?!
[CHUN sobbing]
Thank you so much.
Are you all right?
Uh, we are.
Amazing.
You shielded your sister?
Well, she's my sister.
What is your sister's name?
[CHUN'S BIG SISTER]
It's Chun.
Chun, you can't keep crying.
Your big sister
can't be helping you
all the time, you know.
You must be a big girl,
and join forces with
her now, you understand?
You two are sisters, after all.
Yes.
[QIANG LEI]
Can you walk?
I'll take you to where
the rest of the villagers are.
You'll both be safe there.
Wait! I'm not gonna cry!
Huh?
Hmm. Huh?
[QIANG LEI]
You want out?
[XIN] Nah, I'm good.
I'm reflecting.
I'm glad I got off
with a slap on the wrist,
but I really put you
and the rest
of the squad in an
incredibly tight spot.
So I decided
to stay up all night
really thinking
about everything I did.
Not that I regret cutting
down that punk, you know.
[QIANG LEI]
Right.
Bye.
Uh. Whoa! Hang on!
I got some time on my hands.
Stick around and talk!
You said you were reflecting.
[XIN] Oh and bring me
something to eat, wouldja?
I'm starving!
[QIANG LEI]
You must be kidding.
[NARRATOR]
The furor over Xin attacking
a 1,000-man commander, was
prevented from boiling over
thanks to Meng Tian's
maneuvering.
The Fei Xin Force
was now a little more
well known than before
among the Qin army
and the people of Wei
for both new and
different reasons.
Meanwhile, credit
for this first battle
went to Wang Ben
of the Yu Feng Force
and Meng Tian of
the Le Hua Force.
Their two squadrons brought down
the first castle, Gaolang,
in but a single day.
[NARRATOR] The following
morning, there came word
that General Meng Ao's
two lieutenants had
taken down their own Wei
castles with detached forces.
[NARRATOR]
The Qin army's offensive
was off to a really solid start.
[NARRATOR]
However, no one was able
to realize at the time,
that further on down the road,
they would be facing off against
an unthinkably huge opponent.
Those Qin mongrels
have brutally invaded our land.
Now even Xuzhong
and Xuxi have fallen.
And yet, my heart
remains free from terror
because you are here,
standing on our side.
[KING JINGMIN] Formerly
part of Zhao's Three Greats.
General Lian Po!
In the three years
that you have been
exiled to our land,
never before have I been
so grateful for your presence!