[NARRATOR]
Under the rule of Ying Zheng,
the king who aimed
for unification,
the kingdom of Qin
launched an invasion
on the neighboring land of Wei.
Their opponent: the
legendary general Lian Po.
The young commanders stepped
onto a relentless battlefield,
their sights set
on a major victory.
[screaming]
[SOLDIERS yelling, screaming]
[NARRATOR] In the first battle
on the Liuyi Plains,
Meng Ao's army found itself
at the mercy of an evil scheme
contrived by Xuan Feng,
one of Lian Po's Big Four.
Only the Fei Xin and Yu Feng
Forces retaliated,
but made no headway.
Therefore, the central army
suffered a staggering defeat.
They toyed with us horribly and
left us in pieces afterwards!
Damn it! Damn it all!
[NARRATOR]
If this continued,
a drop in morale would be
all but guaranteed.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[NARRATOR]
However...
The Fei Xin and Yu Feng Forces
refused to back down in the face
of the enemy's
incredibly devious plot,
instead destroying them
with their courageous attack!
What's more,
the enemy fled rapidly,
and our army's casualties
were kept to a minimum.
That said, then,
I'd call this a real victory!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[NARRATOR] Meng Ao's army held
up Xin and Wang Ben
to stave off flagging morale
rather successfully.
They emphasized how the two
units drove off the enemy forces,
and boasted of their feat.
Those troops who
knew of the defeat
badly needed to be inspired,
and to be moved to add their
voices to the loud cheers.
More like public humiliation.
Behold the two fools
who drove off the foe!
And you got yourself hurt.
Must be doubly embarrassing
for you, am I right then?
Your appearance is
what's embarrassing.
You'll drop their morale
with your dirt-poor look.
You're a spoiled brat!
[WANG BEN] Back off.
I don't trust myself right now.
[XIN growls]
[ADVISOR A]
Cut that out, you two!
Meng Tian, my lord.
It worked out.
If they hadn't attacked
the main forces like so,
we would've ended up with a
lot more casualties than we did.
They've set themselves apart,
that's for sure.
Not that we even got
our turn this time.
[MENG AO]
It's a bit forced, perhaps,
but as long as it keeps
morale up I'm happy.
[MENG AO] Besides, I believe it
is time for my twin swords
to finally make their move.
[MENG AO] Keep your head.
No need to hurry, Meng Ao.
[NARRATOR] On day two,
Meng Ao's central army,
having suffered a major
defeat in their first sortie,
was hurriedly putting
its squads back together.
[GENERAL A] Move, Fei Xin Force!
You're way over there!
[XIN] We're going, we're going!
Get off my back!
[gasps]
Attention!
[laughs]
[MENG AO]
Don't you rush, now!
You'll just trip and
hurt yourselves!
[gasping]
[QIN SOLDIER A]
General Meng Ao!
[QIN SOLDIER B]
It's Bai Lao!
[QIN SOLDIER C] Bai Lao himself
has come all the way here
just to rally us onward!
I'm here to share one
of our tactics with you.
Our tactics?
That's defense!
[gasps]
Defense?
[MENG AO] The lieutenants
deployed to the left and right
of the battlefield will soon
be entering the fight.
Both of their armies will
now be tearing into the enemy,
and will be fighting their way
to get to the main camp.
Therefore, we in the central
army must dedicate ourselves
to defense until the right
opportunity presents itself.
Keep me safe and we will win;
it is quite simple!
[MENG AO] For this reason,
you must fight hard so
your units stay together.
By doing so, you will most
definitely safeguard
your own lives as well.
[gasping]
[MENG AO]
Is that understood, my troops...
...my comrades...
...my brothers...
...my dearest children?
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[NARRATOR] It was a typically
Meng Ao-style appeal.
This un-general-like way of
speech shook the very hearts
of the rank-and-file troops
that listened below him.
[NARRATOR] It was on this day
that the fighting began on
the sides of the battlefield.
The first to make
his move was...
[WEI MESSENGER A] Report!
General Qiang Yan's
right-flank army is now in war
with Wang Jian's
left-flank army!
So it's begun!
[WEI MESSENGER A] It was all
General Qiang Yan's doing!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LIAN PO]
So they're evenly matched
in troops' numerical strength.
But don't you take us
lightly, Wang Jian!
Qiang Yan,
one of my Big Four,
has a formidable trick
up his sleeve, you'll see.
[COMMANDER A]
Go into the valley!
We'll surround their
right flank from below!
[LIAN PO] Qiang Yan moves
his troops with arrows.
And an arrow in Qiang Yan's
ten fingers flies twice as far
as anyone else's in all
of the Middle Kingdom.
Which means Qiang Yan
can control several
units at once,
as they all run between
the mountains out there.
[QIN SOLDIER B]
They're coming from below, too!
[QIN SOLDIER C]
We're surrounded!
[LIAN PO] Any general with a
brain would be taken aback
by the force of
Qiang Yan's attacks.
I remember, at one point,
his army even had me
scratching my head
profusely back in the day!
Normally, these types of troops
would be kept in check
and fall prey to
Qiang Yan fairly easily,
but I doubt that will
happen this time around.
Isn't that right, Wang Jian?
[LIAN PO] Let's see
your true power, then.
The kind of power which Wang Yi
swore put you right on a par
with the famed
Qin's six great generals.
[QIN MESSENGER A] Report!
[QIN MESSENGER A] Wang Jian's
army is being repelled!
The front line is breaking in
the face of the enemy's attacks!
Say what?! General Meng Ao?
[MENG AO laughs]
[MENG AO] Nobody fret right now.
Because Wang Jian is made
of much more than this.
[MENG AO laughs]
[WEI MESSENGER B] Report!
[LIAN PO]
Hmm?!
General Jie Zifang's front lines
are seeing movement now!
[LIAN PO] So they're
starting too, aren't they?
There's one target left,
then: Huan Yi.
[WEI MESSENGER C] Report!
The first unit
has been attacked,
and there are many
other casualties!
[JIE ZIFANG] Really?
What about the reinforcements?
Well, they withdrew
when the first unit was hit,
and it appears they
have gone into hiding.
They did what?
[NARRATOR] This was exactly
how Huan Yi fought.
Rather than just striking
from the very front,
his squadron split
into smaller subunits
and went right into hiding
just before unleashing
sneak attacks.
Using the element of surprise,
they struck suddenly,
then retreated over
and over, day or night.
If at any point Wei troops
happened to get in too deep,
Huan Yi's men rose up
as one to destroy them
as if they'd been waiting.
Jie Zifang had heard
the man was dauntless,
but these irregular attacks
puzzled him much more
than he let on.
[NARRATOR]
Afterwards,
both the central army
and Wang Jian's troops
fought their way
arduously to deadlocks.
But reports came daily of
victories won by Huan Yi's army.
Then, on the fourth day...
[QIN MESSENGER B] Report!
General Huan Yi's unit
has attacked
another enemy supply division!
I think that's a typical
Huan Yi thing to do!
I can almost see the faces
of those poor enemy generals!
This tactic really makes the
most of his robber past,
doesn't it?
[laughs]
[gasps]
A thousand pardons, sir.
It is a slip of the tongue.
Right.
Surely Lian Po isn't just
standing on the sidelines
watching all of this.
It's about time for him
to finally make a new move.
And I do believe
this time around,
this battle truly is
do or die for both of us.
I'm counting on you, Huan Yi.
[MO LUN laughs]
[MO LUN] A nice haul,
just like the other, boss!
[WEI SOLDIER A] You fool...
Cowardice is all
you've ever known.
You filthy Qin monkeys.
Be quiet now, you little worm.
[gasps]
[WEI SOLDIER A screams]
Let's see.
Our little present should be
arriving right about now.
[NARRATOR] The surprise attacks
weren't the only thing
worrying Jie Zifang
at this very moment.
There was more.
We've received another one, sir.
Who is this man?
[WEI SOLDIER B] The thousand-man
commander from the eighth unit
who went missing
two days ago.
[JIE ZIFANG]
And in the bags?
Well, uh, you see, sir...
Open them now.
[JIE ZIFANG'S ADVISOR A]
Sir!
I wouldn't do that if I were--
[JIE ZIFANG'S ADVISOR A]
Out of the way!
[screams]
[gasping]
[JIE ZIFANG]
You mean all of those bags...
[WEI MESSENGER D]
Report! Another one has arrived!
I-It contains--
Enough!
[JIE ZIFANG] Normally,
atrocities such as this
would easily raise
the enemy's morale,
but this is going too far.
Frankly, if we've
come to this point,
all of the troops
will instead
be completely
terrified of Huan Yi.
A tricky opponent for sure...
[JIE ZIFANG]
...Huan Yi the Headhunter.
[XUAN FENG]
What are you fretting about?
[JIE ZIFANG]
Hmm?
[XUAN FENG] You are Lian Po's
right-hand man, correct?
Hardly worthy of
heading up the Big Four!
[JIE ZIFANG] Xuan Feng!
General Xuan Feng?
General Xuan Feng!
Xuan Feng, sir,
what brings you here?
[XUAN FENG] This left flank
that you have right here.
I will be taking it over
for a while.
[gasping]
On our lord's orders?
That's right.
Don't let it get to you, though.
Dare I say that your might
may be beyond reproach.
But if the left flank
lags behind at all,
it'll affect the
outcome of the battle.
It's all about finishing this up
and then moving on to the next.
You see,
your more traditional attack
style isn't a good fit
for Huan Yi's very peculiar
approach to battle.
I see, so that is
why you're here.
A schemer for a schemer,
is that correct?
[XUAN FENG] Hmph.
Don't lump me in with him.
I think those mind games
are just a cheap trick.
I'll have the opportunity to
show him the importance
of real military
strategy this time!
Huh. Well, that should
do it now. Let's go.
[HUAN YI] Why don't you tell
them about this place now?
[HEI YING] Got it.
[ZHANG HU] Boss!
[ZHANG HU] Their main camp
is on the move it seems!
And they are headed straight
towards our main camp!
[HUAN YI] That's strange.
Their camp should be hidden in
some very hard-to-find spot,
as it usually tends to be.
[ZHANG HU] We've heard from a
reliable third party
that their left flank is now
being led by Xuan Feng instead.
The same guy who did
in the central army?
Xuan Feng happens to be
Lian Po's most vital strategist.
So, then, boss?
[XUAN FENG] His strategy has a
definite fatal flaw, you see.
The Huan Yi army is a cloud
of flies swarming the Wei army
with little fragments
of their military muscle.
They send us dead bodies
to crush our morale
and once it hits bottom,
they regroup and attack
afterwards as
one massive squadron.
But that's much too slow,
you dumb fools.
A scattered army
means we can waltz in
and eliminate their
main camp fairly easily
whenever we please.
And just like that,
this battle is over.
Using their tactics
against them.
However, Huan Yi's main forces
moved quickly
into the mountains
exactly when the
battle first began.
We have been searching
for them all this time, Sir.
[XUAN FENG] Naturally, they're
using this strategy only because
they're counting on
never being found, you see.
It's not the kind of thing you
find by simply looking for it.
But look at the terrain,
where we are,
as well as where they
have struck previously,
and--
Right here. This is where
Huan Yi's main camp is.
Jie Zifang, take over the
main army and go after his head.
[JIE ZIFANG] Yes sir!
[JIE ZIFANG]
Just leave it to Xuan Feng.
We've found you, Huan Yi!
[JIE ZIFANG]
Holding firm, huh?
He was well aware that we were
closing in, yet he didn't run.
He's got guts,
I'll give him that.
And much more!
Listen troops! Onward!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[WEI MESSENGER E]
A message!
A report for Xuan Feng!
Jie Zifang's main army has
attacked the main enemy camp!
Oh! Already? It is exactly
as you surmised, Xuan Feng!
Then it's over.
Once they cross swords, it's
no use for Huan Yi to cook up
any of his shrewd
little schemes.
No matter how brave he is,
it simply won't matter
at this point.
[SOLDIERS yelling, screaming]
[XUAN FENG]
They can't get to Jie Zifang!
[growls, yells]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[yells]
No!
In any case, his foe-smashing
power is actually pretty equal
to that of Lian Po's clout.
[XUAN FENG]
What's this?
Why do you messengers have
blood splatter all over...
...your armor?!
[gasping]
Good eye, old-timer.
[XUAN FENG] Huan Yi?
That's right.
Any last words now, old-timer?
Disguising yourself
as a mere enemy soldier
to infiltrate is no substitute
for strategy, you dumb fool.
Not to mention a commander
doing it himself.
Strategy... Who needs it?
Y'see, I just make sure to do
whatever my opponent
hates the most.
[HUAN YI] Plus,
I've always been good at this--
Sneaking right in
when nobody's home.
[XUAN FENG]
You may be ignorant,
but you aren't without
some aptitude. Hmph.
I could let you be
my apprentice, Huan Yi.
I don't think so.
You are nobody.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[grunts]
Come on!
Protect your position
with everything you've got!
[SOLDIER screams]
Xin, sir!
Do you hear that?
[gong crash]
Is that a gong?
Yes, probably the enemy's.
[gasps]
My Lord, something
has happened to the enemy.
[NARRATOR] That gong
was delivering a message
from the main Wei forces camp
to every battlefield
out there in the mountains.
[NARRATOR] Therefore,
all of Lian Po's generals
got the news at about
the same time.
Xuan Feng, one of the Big Four,
had just been killed.
[LUN HU] It can't be...
Xuan Feng was killed?
[QIANG YAN] Wasn't Xuan Feng
at the main camp?
How can this be?
[gasps]
[JIE ZIFANG]
No! That's... impossible!
[WEI MESSENGER E]
Huan Yi made himself scarce,
immediately after
killing Xuan Feng!
What?
Then it's conceivable
Huan Yi could be
going after this camp, too?
[gasps]
[snarling]
[LIAN PO] You've done it now,
Huan Yi... and the Qin army.
Let's-Let's recall
our generals for now,
and just regroup right away.
[LIAN PO] No need!
[gasps]
Night is falling very soon.
Let the squadrons camp out
where they are.
[BAI GUIXI]
But Lian Po, sir--
Losing Xuan Feng means
I need to rethink
our fighting style immediately.
Alert me if
anything else comes up.
[LIAN PO]
Forgive me, Xuan Feng.
I let you die
such a mundane death.
I can't say these soft-hearted
things on the battlefield.
To lose someone with whom I'd
cheated death all those times.
However, I won't be
pinning you for Xuan Feng.
I am about to pay
Qin right back
with their soldiers'
own corpses and blood!
[MENG AO]
Now I've finally paid you back--
No, now I'm one move
ahead of you, Lian Po.