Wow, my dream of
becoming super
famous has finally
come true! Sort of.
The truth is, the
enemy is using my
identity to lure in
Tuxedo Mask, so they
can steal his
Rainbow Crystals!
Tuxedo Mask, look
out!
That does it! Time
for the real Sailor
Moon to take action!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Hey! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
This job's not easy
by the way...
We have to find and
protect the Legendary
Silver Crystal before
the bad guys get it.
But in order to do that,
we need to find the Seven
Rainbow Crystals and the
people holding them!
Pretty crazy, huh?
But now there are
four of us Sailor
Guardians, so I think
everything's gonna
work out just fine!
(giggling)
"Enter Venus, the
last Sailor Guardian"
Now to end your life
once and for all!
Hm?
Not while I'm
around, Nephrite.
Tuxedo Mask,
my hero!
(angry growl)
Ahhhh!
Enough of this!
Explain yourself,
Zoisite. What is
the purpose of this?
Why would you think
I would wish to
see these images?
Well, Queen Beryl,
every time we have
Sailor Moon within
our grasp someone
comes to her rescue
and it's always the
same person, as those
scenes reveal.
Yes. So? It's Tuxedo
Mask. Have you finally
figured out his true
identity?
Unfortunately, no. We
still don't know who
he is. But, my Queen,
we know one thing for
sure. And that is he
will only appear when
he knows Sailor Moon
is in great danger.
All we have to do is
place Sailor Moon in
peril and Tuxedo Mask
will come to us.
If he does appear,
will you be able to
retrieve the two
Rainbow Crystals he
has stolen?
You do realize that
this is the last chance
you'll have to succeed,
right, Zoisite?
Yes...
... And I won't
fail you.
Not so fast,
Zoisite.
Huh?
Oh, Kunzite!
Listen, if your plan is
to lure Tuxedo Mask out
into the open so that
you can deal with him,
then the first thing
you need to do is
separate him from the
Sailor Guardians.
With your permission,
I'd be happy to take
on that part of the
job, my Queen.
Very well. Bring me all
seven of the Rainbow
Crystals. And do not
fail me this time.
Yes, my Queen!
Though I swear
allegiance to Queen
Beryl. I am doing this
for no one but you,
Kunzite. I would give
my very life for you!
(scared screams)
You behind the
counter! Money
in the bag!
C'mon! Make
it quick!
(painful grunt)
Huh?! Who the
hell are you?!
This just in! Another
arrest was made today
by the mysterious hero
calling herself the
Pretty Guardian Sailor
Moon. According to
witnesses, a man armed
with a rifle entered
the Tozai Bank's Juban
branch around two p.m.
The suspect fired
several rounds and was
demanding money from
a bank teller when the
Pretty Guardian entered
and quickly subdu-
Huh?! Usagi?!
No way!
I'm goin' in!
Now this is my idea of
how a schoolgirl should
spend her day off! Eating
every dessert she wants!
Yeah, well, you're
going to need a
bigger school uniform
if you keep it up!
I can't help myself!
I just have to try
all of them!
Huh?
Aaaghh!
(gasps)
Oh no!
Somebody help us!
I'm losin' my grip!
Ahh-Ahh!
Ahhh!
(gasps)
Ahhhh!
(crowd cheering)
Could she have cut
those ropes herself?
Sailor Moon...
Why in the world does
she have to dress up
as Sailor Moon? Now
everyone thinks she's
some huge hero and
I'm not even getting
any credit for it! Wah!
Agh, just calm
down, Usagi!
Right now, we have
to tell Luna about
this and then go find
that faker!
Mmm-hmm!
The only ones with any
chance of catching her
are the Sailor Guardians
and Tuxedo Mask himself!
And the minute he
shows up. That'll
be that. The end of
Tuxedo Mask!
I could've sworn she
came this way, but
now I've lost her.
So a Sailor Moon
impostor has
appeared?
Yeah! I saw her on
the news catching
that bank robber!
That was when I
knew for sure it
was the fake and
not our Usagi.
Yeah, you got that
right! If the real
Sailor Moon worked
that hard there'd
be no work left for
us to do around here!
Very funny!
What I want to know
is, what is this
impostor after? Whose
side is she on anyway?
That's a good
question, Ami.
Luna, do you think
she might be the
fifth Guardian?
Huh?! Well let me
think about that for
a sec, uh...
I don't care who
this Sailor Moon
wannabe is! How
dare she go around
using my name
without asking
my permission!
I'm about to call
a lawyer and sue
her for stealing
my act!
(annoyed groans)
Get it together,
Usagi! You're
missing the point!
(terrified scream)
Let's go,
you guys!
Right!
(evil chuckle)
It's her!
(shocked gasps)
And look! He looks
like he's from the
Dark Kingdom!
Come on everyone!
We have to help her!
No wait!
She's right! It's
probably a trap!
I don't care if it's
a trap! I can't ignore
someone in danger, even
if she is my impostor!
You're right.
Hm!
Come on! Let's
transform!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Mercury Power
Mars Power
Make Up!
Jupiter Power
Make UP!
Sailor Moon!
This world is filled
with too much light.
It disgusts me.
True beauty is the
glow of darkness, and
the shadow of the
Dark Kingdom will
soon cover this
world.
You up there! Let
my impostor go!
You're one sick puppy
to tie up a girl and
leave her hanging from
a crane, you know that?!
I am the Pretty
Guardian...
Who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
That's right! And
I'm Sailor Mercury!
And don't you
forget Sailor
Mars!
And last, I'm
Sailor Jupiter!
And now in the name
of the Moon. We're
all here to punish
you good!
I've been expecting
you Sailor Guardians. I
am Kunzite, one of the
Four Kings of Heaven.
It's nice to meet
you but, now you
will die!
Behold, I bring you
darkness! Isn't it
beautiful?!
That's pretty
impressive.
Fire!
Soul!
(stunned gasp)
Great, that attack
was totally lame
Sailor Mars!
(evil laugh)
He's strong!
What's wrong?
Supreme!
Thunder!
(shocked gasps)
The darkness is
just swallowing
our attacks!
(evil laughter)
If that's all the
strength you Sailor
Guardians have, then
I guess it's time
to end this charade.
(shocked gasps)
Sailor Moon!
Could this be
a trap?
Hang on!
(evil laughter)
(painful grunt)
Y-You're not
Sailor Moon!
(callous laughter)
Zoisite!
Oh, you poor thing.
That must've hurt!
Don't worry, in just
a minute you won't
feel anything!
Zoi!
(mocking laughter)
Run if you want! You're
not getting away with
those Rainbow Crystals,
Tuxedo Mask!
Augh! We're all
trapped in here!
Not if I can
help it!
Supreme!
Thunder!
No use! That thing
keeps on absorbing
our attacks!
Ahh!
(evil laugh)
You're finished. My
barrier's impenetrable.
(gasp)
(evil chuckling)
Found you...
Die!
(strained groans)
Zoi!
(shocked gasp)
It can't be!
Well, well, what a
handsome face you've
been hiding!
But it still won't
save your life!
(strained groans)
(evil chuckling)
Prepare to die!
Crescent
Beam!
That hurt! Who?!
(gasp)
Who are you?!
Dammit! Huh?!
I don't know who
you are, but you'll
pay for making a
fool out of me!
I'll tear you into
pieces, you hear me?!
(evil laughing)
We're running
out of air!
Can't breathe!
How do you like the
taste of my darkness?
Kunzite, we may
have a problem.
I had Tuxedo Mask
but he got away,
and there's another
enemy, as well.
You had one job
to do! And you let
Tuxedo Mask get away?!
I'm sorry I let
you down, but
I'm not done!
Listen to me, Tuxedo
Mask! I know you're
here somewhere,
hiding! Come on out!
What?! Tuxedo
Mask is here?!
Your darling Guardians
are almost gone! Wanna
save them?! Just give
yourself up! And hand
over the Rainbow
Crystals! Or else!
No! Don't do it!
You've got to stay
away! Don't give
up the Crystals!
Sailor Moon!
Wait!
Huh?
(gasp)
Well well well!
Look who's decided
to join us! You see
Kunzite, I knew we
would defeat these
losers in the end!
Struggling only makes
the pain worse. You
should just give up.
Don't listen to him!
No matter how hopeless
things may seem, you
must never give up!
Her again!
Come out, you!
(surprised gasps)
(gasp)
I know that voice!
A Sailor Guardian?!
I am the fifth and
final Pretty Guardian
who fights for justice!
I am Sailor Venus!
Crescent
Beam!
(painful howls)
Kunzite, no!
The barrier's broken!
I can breathe again!
(gasp)
Wait a minute.
You're Sailor V
aren't you?!
(gasp)
That is correct! She's
Sailor V! Known as the
Guardian of Justice!
But her true identity
is the Pretty Guardian,
Sailor Venus!
Good to see
ya, Luna.
Artemis!
Stay back! Just
watch, I'll make
these pests pay for
hurting you, Kunzite!
Zoisite! Kunzite!
Cease operations
immediately!
(surprised gasp)
Queen Beryl?!
Retreat. There has
been a change in
our plans.
But, my Queen!
Silence! You'll
do as I say!
As you wish.
But we almost
had them.
So, you win for now
Guardians but we
shall return!
(gasp)
Tuxedo Mask!
Where are you?!
He's gone already.
Oh well, at least
we survived a
fight again.
The team is complete.
The five Guardians and
both of the cats are
finally here together.
Yeah, and we welcome
you Sailor Venus.
(giggles)
(realization gasp)
Wait a minute!
Could you be the
Moon Princess?!
(giggle)
Big trouble, Usagi!
Zoisite has gotten
hold of all seven
Rainbow Crystals!
What? How?!
It turns out
Mamoru had them!
Why would he have
them?! Oh never mind,
it doesn't matter, we
have to go save him!
No way! It's
obviously a trap!
It's too dangerous!
But, what if
Mamoru is hurt?!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"The Shining Silver
Crystal: The Moon
Princess Appears."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.