You offer free haircuts
to girls who have little
money, but want to look
great. But you don't
care about their feelings
when you tamper with their
hair! You devious monsters
are unforgivable!
You agree with me,
don't you, Tuxedo
Mask?
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon, I'll punish
you!
Endymion!
(gasp)
No more...
I don't want to be a
Moon Princess anymore.
Constantly fighting
the Dark Kingdom
and monsters.
I just don't want
to do that. I want
to be a normal girl.
Don't say that Usagi.
You can never forget
that you made a promise.
It looks like her trauma
was more serious than I
thought. Now I'm getting
really worried.
(gasp)
Usagi, Usagi, wake up,
you're crushing me!
I'm so worried about
you. Where are you
right now?
Please be safe.
Tuxedo Mask.
Usagi...
"Usagi's Confusion:
Is Tuxedo Mask Evil?"
Check it out, Usagi!
This ad says a new hair
salon just opened up
in the Juban district!
It happens to be owned
by Kariko Tokoyama,
last month's World Hair
Design Contest winner.
But here's the best
part! Hold on to your
seat. Are you ready?
She's having a grand
opening and offering
free haircuts to
everybody who attends.
Isn't that great?!
We all have to go!
Yeah, sure...
(awkward sighs)
What's the matter?
You seem like your
really depressed.
Yeah, sure...
Usagi hasn't been
sleeping well. Just
when I think she's
finally dozed off,
she starts talking
in her sleep, and
having nightmares
about Tuxedo Mask!
Oh, my...
Do we know what happened
to Tuxedo Mask after he
was abducted by the enemy?
We don't. We only
know he's still
missing.
Usagi is so worried
about him that she
she can't think of
anything else!
It's painful seeing
her like that.
That's a real problem.
We need Usagi to get
serious about being the
Princess before
something bad
happens!
But, you really
can't blame her.
The one she loves has
been taken away and we
haven't heard a word
about him since then.
I totally understand
what pain she must
be going through.
It's highly unusual
to see you sympathizing
like this with Usagi.
Usagi, you crybaby!
Mamoru got hurt trying
to protect you! This is
how you pay him back?!
Oh, sorry.
As hard as it might
be, now is not the
time for Usagi to
be flakey.
Right! I agree that
in order to crush
the Dark Kingdom's
ambitions...
...we have to get her
back on track as a full-
fledged Princess, and we
have to do it soon! She
needs to use the
Silver Crystal!
There must be
something that we
can come up with
that will help her.
Crying doesn't suit
you, Bun-head.
You're just
being mean.
Is he mean? Or is
my hair style really
that weird?
This ad says a new
hair salon just
opened up in the
Juban District!
Oh, I see you're
looking at that ad
for the new hair
salon.
Minako?!
Hi Usagi! Sorry, I
called but there was
no answer, so I just
came over.
Hey, I just had a
thought. Why not try a
new hair style? It might
make you feel better.
Yeah?
Something like a
sophisticated and
sleek bob-cut.
Maybe a wavy style
that's bold and
bouncy.
Or how about long and
straight for a classic
and chic look?
Sometimes changing
your hairstyle is just
the kind of thing a
girl needs to pick up
her spirits.
Yeah...
Maybe I'll give
it a try...
Kunzite...
Queen Beryl...
We must secure the
Legendary Silver
Crystal from Sailor
Moon no matter what
it takes.
Yes, my queen.
I assume you've
discovered Sailor
Moon's identity
by now?
Please, give me
a bit more time.
Be very quick
about it.
Uncover Sailor Moon's
identity as soon as
possible, so that we
can retrieve the
Silver Crystal.
Leave it to me. My
new plan is ready to
be put into action.
Oh?
This is a strand of
hair from Sailor Moon,
which I obtained in
battle. I intend to
find the girl who has
matching strands of
hair. Then I will have
uncovered Sailor Moon's
true identity!
Very well. Proceed
with caution.
Yes, my queen.
Welcome...
Thanks for coming to
Hair Salon Kariko.
How may I help you?
I'd like you to take
a look at her hair
and see what new style
would look best on her.
Why of course.
Oh! What beautiful
hair. Come this way.
O-Okay...
Let me know if I
pull you hair or
massage your scalp
too hard.
Okay...
I sure hope this
works to cheer her
up, so she can be
her old self again.
Please stay still
for a moment.
She's not Sailor Moon.
So far none of these
girls have hair that
matches up.
Thank you for
waiting.
Huh?
Please, follow me to
the hair steamer.
Ah. I'm not here to
have my hair done. I
just came with a friend.
While you're waiting,
you really should try
our revolutionary
hair steamer.
We use a special steam
that instantly repairs
split ends and sun damage,
which sometimes you're
not even aware you
have!
(impressed laugh)
Sounds pretty good,
and after all it
is free!
Just sit still
for a bit.
(gasp)
Yes, I've found
you, Sailor Moon.
Could you massage a
little more on the
right, please?
(evil chuckle)
Finally! I've
discovered Sailor
Moon's true identity!
(evil chuckle)
Sailor Moon!
Uhh, Miss Kariko, are
you finished with my
shampoo yet?
I know who you are.
You're Sailor Moon!
No!
Stop!
What?!
Minako!
(dazed sighs)
You idiot!
Don't you dare
sleep yet!
C'mon! Hand over
the Silver Crystal!
What? What are
you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
My computer says your
hair is an exact match
to Sailor Moon's so
don't you dare
tell me otherwise!
My hair?
I must've gotten
some of Usagi's hair
tangled in mine when
I was brushing it!
(forceful grunt)
I want that Silver
Crystal and I want
it right now!
If you still refuse,
I have ways to make
you change your mind.
(scared sigh)
(evil chuckle)
(evil laugh)
She's a monster?!
This is horrible. The
Dark Kingdom turned
Miss Kariko into a
monster just so they
could get to me!
Hold on, Minako.
Don't worry, I'm
gonna save you!
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
(evil chuckle)
Hold it right there!
Huh?
That girl isn't
Sailor Moon!
That's impossible!
You offer free
haircuts to girls
who have little money.
But you don't care
about their feelings
when you mess with
their hearts!
I, Sailor Moon,
will not forgive...
...such devious
monsters!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish
you.
Ha! So you walked
in here on your own.
Just like a slug
jumping into salt.
A slug dissolves
in salt!
I am Mitsuaami and
I shall melt you...
...into goo!
Ahhh!
I have to help her...
Let me dry your
hair. It looks
wet.
(attacking yell)
Ahhhhh!
Now it's time to
shave off all
that hair!
(scared gasp)
(crazy laughter)
No-no-no-no-no
no-no-no-no-no!
Ahh!
(choking cough)
Curse you!
All right Mitsuaami!
It's time to end this!
I'm going to use this Moon
Stick to turn you back
into Miss Kariko Tokoyama,
the hair designer!
Moon Healing...
(painful gasp)
(gasp)
A rose...
Could it be?
Am I imagining it?
That you?
Tuxedo Mask?
It really is you!
Thank goodness!
You're mistaken,
I'm not Tuxedo Mask.
What?!
I am the commander
of the Dark Kingdom.
I am Endymion.
You-You can't be!
Sailor Moon, hand
over the Silver
Crystal.
What did they
do to you?
(forceful grunts)
The trimmer's powered
up and ready to go!
(scared gasp)
Ahhhh!
Mitsuaami! Retrieve
the Silver Crystal!
Yes, sir!
Oh no! It
can't be!
I'm going to give you
such a good trim, you'll
never need to come back
for more!
No thanks!
I need to let all
the Guardians know
right away!
Tuxedo Mask has
become an enemy!
Venus Power!
Make up!
(angry growl)
(scared scream)
(attack yell)
(scared whimper)
Stop moving! I still
want to give you your
cut!
Ahh!
Huh?
You need to be more
careful! You could
take somebody's head
off with that thing!
Stop wasting
time, Mitsuaami!
Get that Silver
Crystal!
No way...
(attack scream)
Ahhh!
(evil chuckle)
Time for that
trim, my dear!
Stop right there!
Huh?
All right!
Fire!
Supreme!
Soul!
Thunder!
(painful yell)
Bubble!
Spray!
Now! Sailor Moon!
Moon Healing!
Escalation!
Shampoo!
Rinse!
Refresh!
Tuxedo Mask!
I'm so glad you're
back safe and sound.
Mamoru...
Sailor Mars...
That guy is not the
Tuxedo Mask you used
to know, believe me!
He's now one of the
commanders of the
Dark Kingdom! He's
Endymion!
(gasp)
N-No!
She's kidding, right?
Tuxedo Mask, please
tell me what she
said is not true!
Roses have many thorns.
And you should know
that even red roses turn
black when they wilt.
What are you saying?
Are you really
planning to fight
all five of us?
Hurting young women
has never been my
style, but to get
the crystal, I'm
prepared to do
what's needed.
(gasp)
Endymion, retreat
for now.
Hm?
This is a direct
order from Queen
Metalia!
Sailor Guardians,
your death at my
hands has been
postponed.
Huh?!
A woman's friendship
is quite fragile.
Even a slight breeze
can make it fall
apart, like a flower
in the wind.
Be careful of that.
(gasp)
Farewell!
Queen Metalia, why
have you called me
back?
Endymion. I
cannot let you
die.
Huh?
It appears that Endymion
has become a warrior of
the Dark Kingdom, both
in body and soul.
Yes, the brainwashing
was extremely effective.
(laughing)
Now that Endymion has
proven himself to be
dedicated to us, we
must think of ways
to make good use
of his loyalty.
(evil laugh)
Hm?
Miss Kariko was turned
into a monster because
of me. If we don't stop
the Dark Kingdom, more
innocent people like
her will suffer. I
won't let that happen.
Hey! Sounds like she's
accepting her Princess
responsibilities.
Yay! Tuxedo Mask is
safe! All is right
in my world!
(cheerful giggling)
I don't know Artemis,
she sounds pretty
much the same to me.
Well, I think she's
putting on a brave
front by making light
of everything.
At the very least,
she's showing that
she's grown up and
is moving on.
You should, too.
You can't let it
bother you forever.
Mm. You're right.
(determined grunt)
I'm sure that Tuxedo
Mask was tricked by
the bad guys into
believing he was one
of them and they've
got him in their
clutches! And now
it's up to me to
turn him back to
normal with my
overwhelming power
of love!
Well, it's official!
I have signed up and
entered the Princess
Training Program!
You don't look very
good, Usagi. Did you
get food poisoning
or something?
I have learned to
become an elegant
and proper lady.
I don't think you're
quite there yet!
Now I'll be able to
share a dance with
Tuxedo Mask at the
ball!
Oh, boy.
Good luck!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Let's Become a Princess:
Usagi's Bizarre Training."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.