What could this warm
glow be? Am I really
the Moon Princess? I
don't know how to deal
with this, or what
to do anymore! What
can I do? Tuxedo Mask,
everyone, please, lend
me your strength!
Mamoru ended up getting
badly hurt while he was
trying to protect Usagi.
Responding to Usagi's
tears, the Rainbow
Crystals came together
and formed the Legendary
Silver Crystal! I don't
believe it. After all
this time, Usagi was
the Princess we've been
searching for! There's
no mistake! This warm
aura belongs to the Moon
Princess, and no other.
At last, she has awakened!
"Returning Memory: Usagi
and Mamoru's Past"
Sailor Moon...
You're the Princess!
Princess Serenity!
What?
Luna, did you just
say 'Princess'? Are
you telling us that
Sailor Moon is the
Moon Princess we've
been searching for
this whole time?
And on top of all
that, Tuxedo Mask
is actually Mamoru?
(stunned breath)
So the Princess has
awakened, has she?
Fine. First, I'll get
rid of her, and then
I'll grab the Silver
Crystal! Zoi!
What's this?!
(painful yell)
Tuxedo Mask...
You're hurt, all
because of me!
S-Serenity!
(gasp)
I'm able to remember
everything now.
Serenity!
I am Endymion.
Endymion...
That's right, I
remember now, I
am Serenity!
(blushing sigh)
Endymion!
Endymion...
You're Endymion!
My one true love.
Endymion...
Sailor Moon!
She's okay!
Looks like she
just passed out.
Oh, thank goodness!
It's understandable.
It must have been her
memories of being
the Princess,
rushing back and
overloading her
mind.
Mamoru, can you
hear me? Please
say something!
He's in pretty
bad shape.
I won't let
you get away!
I found her,
Kunzite...
It was her all
along. Sailor Moon
turned out to be
the Moon Princess.
Yes, I see. Her
awakening explains
it. The Rainbow
Crystals must have
been drawn to her.
I will let you
all live just a
little longer.
(gasp)
Mamoru!
Where is it they
could have taken
him?
Kunzite, you fool!
Not only did you let
the Silver Crystal
fall into enemy hands,
you have also
awakened the
Moon Princess!
Yes, my Queen, I
have no excuses.
Fortunately, the
Princess has just
awakened, and does
not yet have full
control over the
Silver Crystal.
I'll need a
little more time.
Very well. Do
not fail me.
Then there's you,
Zoisite. Are you
ready to accept
your doom?
Please, my Queen!
Give me another
chance!
You disobeyed my
orders, and tried
to kill Tuxedo
Mask, didn't you?!
Yes, but
that was...
Did you think you
could fool me with
your lies?!
I take responsibility
for that!
Please!
Ahhh!
Kunzite!
Hmph! Now dispose
of that trash.
Yes...
Oh Great Ruler,
Queen Metalia! I
call on you to
awaken now!
Endymion! How
I've missed you!
I must admit, we
never imagined that
the former Prince of
the Kingdom of Earth,
would end up being
reincarnated in
this era!
Regardless of the
circumstances, heal
Endymion with the
power of darkness
immediately!
Yes, my Queen!
Zoisite, please
forgive me. I tried
to convince Queen
Beryl to bring
you back, but...
I'm sure you tried
your best, Kunzite.
I'm just happy,
knowing that I get
to die in your arms.
My love, can you please
grant me one last wish?
Anything...
I want to die,
in a beautiful
place.
This is perfect.
Thank you, Kunzite,
for everything.
Know this in your
heart, Kunzite. I
will always love you.
And I will love
you, Zoisite.
Sailor Moon!
Are you sure this
is the way out?
I'm pretty sure,
according to the
sensors.
But we do have
a problem.
What kind of
problem?
Amazingly enough,
this appears to be
a complexly sealed,
projective space.
I mean. Theoretically,
it's not connected to
the three-dimensional
space we just came
from. It's more of a
two-dimensional space.
You see, the polarity
of this tunnel is in
inverse phase, and it's
connected to the other
space through a zero
dimension.
(sigh)
I don't understand
any of those words.
(sigh)
Good thing we have
Sailor Mercury for
this situation.
We've gotta move! If
we stick around here,
those guys are sure
to find us.
Right!
Sailor Moon!
I think she's
starting to
come to.
Huh?
Tuxedo Mask!
Where? Where is
he? Where is he,
tell me, please!
Is he dead?
He's still alive!
Really?
The enemy took him
away. We don't know
where he is.
The enemy?
Oh.
Everyone. I want
you to listen.
Now that the Princess
has awakened, it's
important that you
hear the whole story.
Starting with this.
Luna, when the Princess
finally woke up, did
you notice that all
your memories
returned?
Yes, very clearly!
Wait a minute.
What are you
talking about?
He's talking about
our previous lives.
And more than that.
About the Moon Kingdom,
Silver Millennium.
A long time ago...
...there was a kingdom
called Silver Millennium,
that existed on the moon.
It was a very
peaceful paradise.
But then, something
terrible happened.
The earth was taken
over by an evil entity!
Within a short time,
its forces attacked
us, to steal the
absolute power of the
Silver Crystal, stored
within Silver Millennium.
The Kingdom was
destroyed in a
fierce battle. But
with the power of
the Silver Crystal,
we managed to seal
away the evil entity.
And, you four are the
reincarnations of the
Guardians who fought
that battle.
Wait just a minute!
Are you saying that
we're all beings from
the Moon World?
Not really. All of us
are beings of this
Earth. The mothers and
fathers that we know
are actually our
true parents.
That was the wish of
the Moon Queen. She
wanted the Princess
and you four girls
to live happily on
this plant as ordinary
humans. That's why she
chose this era for
reincarnation.
Because it was
so peaceful.
But it hasn't worked
out quite as she
hoped. Someone has
released that evil
entity into the world.
I see now. That
evil entity is the
Dark Kingdom's boss,
isn't it?
That's correct. I'm
sorry it had to come
to this. If it weren't
for them, you would
have all lived your
lives peacefully as
normal young girls.
But, if we don't
protect the Silver
Crystal and defeat
the enemy, there will
be no future for
any of us!
I feel that it's
our destiny to
fight this battle!
Do you all understand?
We can't allow the
tragedies of the past
to be repeated. We
have to work together
and defeat this threat!
Absolutely!
We'll fight
it together!
Sorry, but
count me out.
(surprised breath)
Sailor Moon?
I'm sorry, but I'm
sick of fighting!
Are you serious?
I'm sick of it!
It's all I ever
do!
How can you even
talk like that?
You're the Princess!
You say I'm the
Princess, but the
truth is, I don't
feel like one, and
I'm not even sure
I want to be one!
I'm Usagi, not
Serenity!
Usagi! Don't you
understand? You
have a mission!
I don't care about any
so-called mission! So
what if I had a previous
life?! It has nothing to
do with me right
now! Don't you get
it?! I'm tired of
risking our lives
fighting all
the time!
I keep thinking...
...What if all of
you end up just
like Mamoru?
I don't ever want
to see that happen!
I'm just so tired
of being sad!
How can you talk like
that?! Don't you know
what's at stake here?!
You're a coward, Usagi!
You're right!
I'm not strong
like you!
I'm sorry.
You crybaby! Mamoru
got hurt trying to
protect you! This is
how you pay him back?
I think Sailor Moon
just needs some time
to think about this.
But Artemis!
Give her a little
space, and I'm sure
the old Usagi will
return.
Until then, let's
be patient and
watch over her.
More importantly,
Luna, I found
the exit!
Great! We're not done
with our talk, but I
think we'd better get
out of here while we can.
Let's get going,
everybody.
(surprised gasp)
So you found
the exit, very
impressive.
Luna! Artemis! You
need to take cover
right now!
Okay, we
hear you!
You be careful,
Venus.
I'll try. You
three protect
the Princess!
Hold on! I'm
fighting with
you.
I appreciate that.
You're wasting
your time!
Don't underestimate us!
Supreme!
Thunder!
No way! He completely
absorbed my attack!
Hmph!
How about this?!
Crescent Beam!
It's no use. In this
dimension, he can
absorb every ounce of
energy we can summon
up to throw at him!
What are we
supposed to do?
Die!
Ahhh!
Arghh!
That's not enough
to defeat us!
Is that all you've
got, Kunzite?!
Not at all!
Take this!
Watch out!
(painful groans)
(gasp)
Look after our
Princess, Mercury.
(nervous breath)
Sailor Moon. You
need to accept
your destiny.
Be strong. You
can do this.
Stop wasting
my time.
Fire!
Soul!
You fool!
(scared gasp)
(forceful grunt)
(restrained groans)
Ahhh!
(gasp)
And now it's your
turn, Princess.
Not while I'm here.
Don't try to
interfere!
You're a stubborn
one.
(forceful grunt)
Ahhhh!
Mercury, are you
alright?! Hang
in there!
Sailor Moon, you
have to be brave.
Mercury...
Usagi...
(gasp)
Believe in
yourself.
Usagi...
You can do it!
Rei...Minako...
Mako...Ami...
I'll try!
Tuxedo Mask, please
help me! Give me
the strength!
Sailor Moon...
You're with me,
Tuxedo Mask.
Fight, Sailor Moon!
Hold it up! Raise
the Silver Crystal!
Right!
So you've chosen to
plunge into hell on
your own, is that
right, Princess?
That's fine with
me! I will now
have my revenge...
...for Zoisite's
death!
(attacking grunt)
Please!
Silver Crystal
give me strength!
What is this?!
Ahhhh!
Damn her! This is
bad! She's beginning
to learn how to use
the Silver Crystal!
Serenity!
Endymion. She haunts
you. You still cannot
forget about her.
But no matter how much
you love Serenity, it
is a love that can
never be.
Thank you so
much, Tuxedo
Mask.
You saved us!
(happy gasp)
Thank you,
Sailor Moon.
Does this mean
you're still
gonna fight
with us?
That's right.
I will.
That completes stage
one, wouldn't you
agree.
Yeah, you did
great, Usagi!
And the same goes
for all of you.
Remember, if we
continue working
together and do
our best, we can
overcome any
obstacle!
I know he's out there
somewhere, Tuxedo Mask,
I'm not going to give
up until I find you.
No, it can't be!
Ahem! A powerful new
enemy appears before
Usagi, who is still
trying to recover from
her emotional scar.
To her surprise, the
new enemy is Tuxedo
Mask! Poor Usagi!
What will become
of Sailor Moon?!
Luna, you're enjoying
this, aren't you?!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi's Confusion: Is
Tuxedo Mask Evil?"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.