Unforgivable! How
dare you corrupt an
innocent young man's
feelings!
As long as the moon
shines in the sky,
no evil deed will
go unnoticed!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights
for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you.
Hey! I'm Usagi
Tsukino!
You know me as the
Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, a fourth
Sailor Guardian has
appeared! She has a
heart of gold and
is super strong!
She is Makoto Kino,
also known as Sailor
Jupiter!
When the four Pretty
Guardians get together,
nothing can stop us!
(giggles)
Crushing on Ami:
The Boy Who Can See
The Future.
There are seven
Rainbow Crystals in
total. And we will
not be able to obtain
the Legendary Sliver
Crystal unless we
gather all seven.
I'm sure you're
already well
aware of this.
Yes.
At the moment, we
have one of them
in our possession.
Only one...
Because you failed
to bring me another
one. Instead you
allowed Tuxedo Mask
to take it.
I apologize,
my Queen.
Don't worry, Queen
Beryl. That's not
about to happen
again. I'm sure
he's about to go
after all the other
Rainbow Crystals.
The next time he
appears, we will
destroy him and
reclaim the Rainbow
Crystal that
he possesses.
That better happen
soon and don't forget,
I want the other
five crystals as well.
We need to have all
seven of those crystals
in our possession to
revive our Great Ruler!
Miss Mizuno!
Please wait up!
Oh, hi Ryo!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
Uh, I was, uh...
What is it?
Is something
wrong?
Oh no!
Look out!
(shocked breath)
Are you
all right?!
Did you
get hurt!
Ugh. Mom's gonna
be mad at me again.
Well she should be,
that's one awful
score you got there.
You have to study
a lot harder.
(chuckling)
You and me
both!
(laughing)
This sucks...
Who's this Ryo
Urawa? He got
a perfect score!
Ami came in
second?!
I can't believe
there's somebody
better!
Ami!
What a bummer,
huh?
Yeah, I was one
point short of a
perfect score. I
guess I'll need to
study even harder
next time.
Wow, I really
don't get her
sometimes...
Ryo Urawa, the guy
who got the perfect
score, is in the same
class as you, right?
Yeah! What makes it
even more impressive
is that he just
transferred to this
school. Oh,
hi Ryo!
Hm? Oh, uh...
Miss Mizuno.
Ohh!
Here. You should
try to relax and
not get so upset.
Good luck!
Miss Mizuno...
Just as I suspected,
you have a crush
on Ami!
That's an old article
about her when she
took first place in
the nation!
By the looks of it
you've had a major
crush on her forever,
haven't you?
It's not that at
all. All I'm trying
to do is study as
hard as I can so
eventually I can
be as smart as
she is.
And thanks to all
that extra studying,
now you've actually
beat her! Way to go!
Not true!
This time I just
happened to get
very lucky.
I don't even come
close to her level
of intelligence.
And what's more. How
I might feel about
her doesn't make a
bit of difference.
Huh?
Just forget it...
Have no fear! I'm
an expert when it
comes to solving
love problems!
Just let me
handle it!
Wait! Miss
Tsukino!
You should be
careful today,
whenever you're
near any water.
Huh? Water?
All done!
Ahh!
Guess I should've
mentioned that
sooner.
(crying)
That's cold!
Sorry about
that...
I'll leave it up
to you, Mamoru.
Where should we
go next?
Uhh...
Well...
I'm starting to
learn about my
past, little by
little. But there
are still so many
things I don't
know. Guess the
only way to pull
it all together
is to turn into
Tuxedo Mask and
find the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
Hey there,
I'm waiting!
Oh! I'm sorry.
What did you say?
You've been acting
weird lately. What's
going on? Has
something happened?
No. Same stuff as
always. Let's go.
(giggles)
Here! This is
for you!
I can...
keep this?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
Now you don't have
to carry around that
newspaper clipping!
Pretty cute,
huh?!
You don't often
see her making
that kind of face.
The Moon Stick
is reacting. I
wonder if this
boy could be...
I really love it.
Thanks so much for
giving it to me.
Oh, you don't have
to thank me! More
importantly, have
you thought about
when you're going
to tell Ami how
you feel?!
Hm... My mind was
made up from the
very moment I found
out I was transferring
to the same school as
Ami. I decided I'd tell
her when I measured up
to her academically.
Well, that means
you're good to
go any time.
Ah... Yeah,
but...
So, here's the
plan! Once Ami
is finished with
her cram school
today I'll get
her and bring
her to you!
Wait for us,
all right?
Take your time!
I'm not
ready, yet.
(evil chuckle)
So completely innocent
and naive. It's almost
difficult to believe
that he is one of the
Seven Great
Monsters.
Usagi...
There's something
I've been meaning
to tell you. But I
wanted to be sure
before I said
anything.
What is it?
(giggling)
Hey there, Ami!
Oh, hi, Usagi!
What brings
you here?
Well, I'd thought
I'd take you to
this awesome place
I just found!
Huh?
C'mon, Ami!
Let's go!
Hey!!
(giggling)
Welcome home.
I've been dying
to meet you.
So you must
be Zoisite!
S'cuse me?
Explain yourself!
How do you know
my name?
Ever since I was
little I've had the
power to know about
things before they
happen. Lately this
ability to see into
the future has been
growing stronger.
I'm now fully aware
of my true identity.
Even though I would
rather not be.
Ha ha ha! That
makes my job a
lot easier. Now,
transform into
your Great Monster
persona and kneel
before your master.
No I won't!
I would rather be
put to death right
this minute, than
become a slave...
...to a demon!
Zoi!
Ahh!
Now be a good
little boy and
accept your fate.
(painful grunts)
C'mon! Hurry up!
Wait, look
it's Zoisite!
(painful grunts)
Oh no, he's
attacking Ryo!
Both of you
transform
immediately!
Moon Prism Power
Make up!
Mercury Power!
Sailor Moon!
That's enough!
Zoisite!
As long as the moon
shines in the sky,
no evil deed will
go unnoticed!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who
fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am
Sailor
Mercury!
Let that
boy go!
How dare you
interfere!
Sailor Mercury,
take Ryo someplace
where he'll be safe!
Right!
I don't have the
time to play games
with you little girl.
Zoi!
Ahh!
Where'd he go?
Huh?!
We should be safe
for now, but how
are you feeling,Ryo?
Thank you so much
for saving my life.
Miss Mizuno.
(gasp)
He said my name.
How does he know
I'm Sailor Mercury.
How far did Mercury
go? There's no sign
of them anywhere!
Try using your
Moon Stick!
Trust me on this.
If you use the Moon
Stick, you should be
able to find Ryo and
Sailor Mercury
right away. It
will react to
their location.
What are you
talking about?
Ryo would have
to be a Rainbow
Crystal Monster
for that stick
to work!
Well, he is one!
What?!
If we don't hurry
Sailor Mercury is
gonna be in danger!
Are you sure?
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Ahh!
Huh?
What's he doing
with a photo of
me?
Not again...
I think you were
having a very
bad dream.
I wasn't dreaming.
I was seeing a
glimpse into the
future.
Huh?
I have a mysterious
power that allows
me to predict the
future. That's how
I was able to get
a perfect score on
the midterm exam.
What are you
talking about?
I know who you
really are, Miss
Mizuno...
I've looked up to
you for a long time.
And now, as much as
I've tried to deny
it, apparently
it's my fate to
fight you.
(giggle)
You don't believe
me, do you?
I don't. You seem
so sure about what
will happen later
on, but maybe you've
got it all wrong.
Like mistaking me
for this Miss
Mizuno...
All right then, it's
obvious you don't
understand what I'm
trying to say. But...
What?
When I do turn into
an evil monster.
Don't hesitate to
kill me immediately!
That's my future.
And it cannot
be changed.
You're wrong! The
future is something
you create yourself.
If you give into
negative thoughts,
nothing will change.
You can create any
fate you want, if
you just believe in
yourself enough to
know you can do it.
Hm.
You're right.
Thank you,
Sailor Mercury.
Oh my...
How touching...
Do you really think
you can escape from
the power of the
Dark Crystal?
Zoisite!
Ah. You're defending
him. I wonder if you'll
still be willing to do
that when you see him
in his true form.
Ahhh!
Ryo!
Watch closely, as
you are about to
see the emergence
of Bunboo, one of
the Seven Great
Monsters!
C'mon, Bunboo, get
her! I want you
to destroy that
Sailor Guardian!
Are you okay?!
Bunboo!
Ryo, is that you?
The future is
something you
create yourself.
(gasp)
Bunboo!
(painful grunt)
(gasp)
He still has
human emotions!
Fool!
Bunboo!
You will obey me!
Sailor Mercury is
your enemy!
Go! Take back
the Rainbow
Crystal that
belongs to us!
Bunboo!
Hey, Zoisite!
Unforgivable! How
dare you corrupt
an innocent young
man's feelings
for your own
selfish purposes!
I'm afraid you've
got the wrong
idea about him.
That boy's true
form is the monster
you see now!
Unforgivable!
Absolutely
unforgivable!
Now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you.
Sailor Moon, wait!
Please use your Moon
Stick and turn Ryo
back into a
human first!
Got it!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Bun-boo!
I don't get it!
Why isn't it
working?!
It's no use! Ryo's
completely under
the control of their
evil power right now.
In order to turn him
back, you'll first
have to weaken his
energy levels.
Do it! We have
no other choice,
Sailor Moon.
When I do turn into
an evil monster.
Don't hesitate to
kill me immediately!
It'll be all right,
Ryo. We'll make sure
you return to normal
again.
Bunboo!
Ahhh!
Fire!
Soul!
Supreme!
Thunder!
We almost missed
all the action. It's
a good thing we made
it in time!
Yeah, that's
for sure.
Bubble!
Spray!
Bunboo...
Now, Sailor Moon!
Use your power to
restore Ryo back
into a human!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Ahhh!
Bunboo!
His monster energy
has weakened a lot!
Do it, Sailor Moon!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
(struggling breaths)
Refresh!
Ryo!
I'll get you
next time!
Talk to
me, Ryo.
Are you
all right?
You saved me...
So, the third Rainbow
Crystal is now in the
hands of the Sailor
Guardians. I shall
leave them alone
for tonight...
You're transferring
to another school
again? Why can't you
just stay here?
Well, it wasn't my
idea, but it can't
be helped. My dad
got a work transfer.
We were all
becoming friends.
It's just not fair!
Yeah, you're right.
Um, Miss Mizuno?
Ryo, just call me
Ami, all right?
Uh, Ami, I
better give this
photo back.
I'm gonna study hard
and when I'm able to
outscore you on my
own merits, then I'll
come back for it.
Here's a
different one...
I think this photo
is a better one for
you to remember me
by. I'd like you to
keep it.
Don't be so worried
about impressing me
with your grades.
You can come visit
me anytime, Ryo!
I'm so lucky! I've
been asked to become a
model for a painting!
Really? By who?
None other than the
famous Yumeni Yumeno!
That's amazing!
The only problem is,
I have to pose with
this guy who I really
don't like...
I guess you've gotta
take the good with
the bad!
Rei will strangle
you if she finds
out!
Don't say that!
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"The Painting of Love:
Usagi and Mamoru Get
Closer."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.