What in the world?!
A human got turned
into a monster! Now I
can't punish him!
I've never encountered
anything like this in
my entire career as
Sailor Moon! But this
is no time to worry
about that! What
the heck, I'm just
gonna do it!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
It may not look it,
but I'm actually a
superhero!
I use a special
brooch to transform
and fight evil! You
know me as...
...the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love
and for justice. I
am Sailor Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius,
Ami Mizuno, who's
Sailor Mercury!
And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic,
who's Sailor Mars.
Both of them seem
to have it a little
more together than
I do.
But, oh well,
guess I just
gotta do my best!
(giggles)
"Jupiter, the Powerful
Girl in Love."
Awaken, Great
Ruler...
To you, I offer
vital energy.
Hear my plea and
awaken once more.
Great Ruler of ours,
now is the time!
Arise! Oh
Great One!
(gasp)
So, It seems as if
the energy from the
humans has stirred me
from my long sleep.
Yes, Great
Ruler! What an
auspicious
moment.
How we have
waited for this
to happen!
But it is not enough.
I can feel myself
being drawn back into
a deep sleep...
Yes...
You must locate the
Legendary Silver
Crystal, at once!
Without that Silver
Crystal, it will be
impossible for me to
make my resurrection
complete!
We're searching for
it but it has not
yet been found!
When the Seven Great
Monsters are revived
together with the
Rainbow Crystals.
Only then will the
Legendary Silver
Crystal shine brightly
enough to be found!
Ahh! Of course!
Oh no! I'm late!
I'm so late!
Hey! Don't forget
your lunch!
Oh! Okay, thanks
Luna!
Ow! That hurt!
Sorry about that-!
You broke my leg!
I heard it snap
like a pretzel!
Hey! Whatcha
gonna do now?!
She said sorry!
Wha-?
I saw the whole
thing, boys.
She barely bumped
you. That's pretty
low, trying to con
an innocent girl.
What's that?!
How dare you!
No one ever
talks to us
like that.
(painful grunt)
Why you!
Oh wow!
Are you okay?
Uh, sure!
You take care.
A rose-shaped
earring...
So cool!
When the Seven Great
Monsters and the
Rainbow Crystals are
revived together,
then the Legendary
Silver Crystal will
be found!
I remember everything
about the Seven Great
Monsters. They were
the strongest of our
allies. But they
were sealed away
eons ago by our
enemy.
Your memory serves
you well. The legendary
Seven Great Monsters
were the most powerful
warriors of all!
Until that day when
we suffered a great
loss to our enemy!
Those cowards sealed
away the Seven Great
Monsters into separate
fragments of the
Legendary Silver Crystal
and then banished
them to Earth.
Those seven fragments
are known as the
Rainbow Crystals...
So what's become
of the Seven
Great Monsters?
They lost their memory
of once being monsters
and they have been
reborn as humans.
I see. So if we
remove these Rainbow
Crystals from the
reborn humans...
Will it lead us
to the Legendary
Silver Crystal?
Yes, but what's even
better is the Seven
Great Monsters will
also be reincarnated.
I've modified that
crystal to only react
to the presence of
the Rainbow Crystals.
Mmm. Thank you,
my queen.
Zoi!
Ahh. So there's a
Rainbow Crystal
inside him, huh?
(boys laughing)
Race ya there!
It's lunchtime!
Lunchtime! My
stomach's growling
like a big old bear!
It's that girl
with the rose
earring!
Hey Usagi!
(startled scream)
Don't startle me
like that!
That girl your
stalking is a
transfer student
who just joined
class six today!
Huh?
Her name's Makoto
Kino. And the word
is, that she's
incredibly strong!
Turns out that she was
kicked out of her last
school for fighting.
So if I were you I'd
keep you distance!
Sounds like you
should be careful
around that girl
or she might real-
Uh-uhhh
Agghh!
Wait!
Usagi!
Ohh wow! Look how
cute and yummy her
lunch and dessert
are!
Ah! And the bag of
hers is cute too!
That mixed rice ball
looks so good, I can
almost ta-
Who's there?!
Ah! Uh! Ha-ha-ha!
Why hello again!
Oh it's you! So
you go to school
here too, huh?
I do! I'm Usagi!
So, care to
join me?
Huh? Sure! Thanks
for helping me
this morning!
Oh, would you
like to have
some?
Huh?! Well
actually I'm
not really a
big eater!
Uh, what?
But since you
offered...
Yummy!
I'm sure glad you
came by. Y'know for
some reason everyone
at school here seems
to be afraid to
talk to me.
Well, Mako...
Uh, sorry, is
it okay if I
call you that?
Sure...
Mako, your mom packs
the best lunch I've
ever tasted!
Oh!
Actually, I made
all this myself.
Wha?! That's
amazing!
You've gotta teach
me how to make these!
Or you can make them
for me! Ha ha!
Just kidding!
What a natural,
Usagi can make
friends with
anyone!
So Mako, I was
wondering, why
aren't you wearing
our school uniform?
What I'm wearing
now suits me better.
Oh...
(giggling)
Aw! Looks like
Motoki's not
here today.
Oh yeah, who's
Motoki? Is he
your...
(embarrassed laugh)
...older brother
or cousin?
No, no, no.
Motoki is a
very special-uh?
Hey, Mako!
Usagi!
Huh?
Here you are!
What is it?
Luna says she's
concerned about that
girl over there...
Oh? You mean Mako?
Luna, you worry
too much...
Agh! How did I
lose that one?!
Uh, Mako?
Yeah?
Meet my other
friends. This is
Makoto Kino, she
just transferred
to my Middle
School today.
Hi there.
Oh-uh, hi!
So this is Ami,
who's the really
smart one. And Rei
mean one.
Wait-Did you say
I'm the mean one?
Sure did.
Didn't hear that-
You said I'm what?
You're the
mean one.
So tell me what
year, month, week,
day, hour, minute,
and second I was
ever mean
to you?!
You don't think
that you're being
mean to me right now!
How nice. You get
along so well.
No way!
As soon as we see
each other she
starts an argument
every time!
I do not!
You do so!
Well the more you
argue, the closer
you are.
Huh?!
(giggling)
That's a good
one, Makoto.
Oh...
Cute!
That's Luna. She
has a crescent bald
spot on her forehead
and we all think she's
really special.
She lives at my
place!
(giggling)
What's that?
(impressed chatter)
(gasps)
Heh!
Oh! Hi there,
Usagi.
Hey there, Yumi.
Did you just
see that?
Mmm-Hmm.
Everyone calls him
'Joe the Crane
Game Troll'.
Why is his nickname
'Crane Game Troll'?
'Cause he's a genius
at that crane game!
I've heard that every
single stuffed animal
he sets his sights
on, he gets! He's
got hundreds of 'em!
Wow, awesome.
Mako, isn't- Uh?
He's just like
him...
What're you
talking about?
My first love...
Hey! Hello? Hello?
Earth to Mako!
Wake up! Come back!
I wonder what's
gotten into her?
Huh?
I found you!
Ahh!
(giggling)
Who are you?!
This will only
take a moment.
Zoi!
Ah!
(painful grunts)
(painful scream)
Stop it!
Ahhhh!
Sailor Moon!
Please stop!
Ahhh!
Stop that!
Huh?
You shouldn't bully
people weaker than
yourself!
Damn it!
I'll make sure
you regret
interfering!
(punching grunts)
(giggling)
And just what
was that?
I'm not done yet!
Hmph, how barbaric.
Ahhh!
(throwing grunt)
You prehistoric
witch! You scarred
my precious face!
Mako!
W-what?! Oh no!
A fight!
Huh?!
Hey! Are you
okay?!
Are you all right?
Mako, what just
happened here?
Don't touch me!
Just mind your own
business! Leave
me alone!
But...
What's his problem?
We were just trying
to help him out!
Oh! Mako!
What's going
on here?!
I can sense it!
What?
I felt a super evil
aura from that guy
she fought,
Huh?
That means he might
be from the Dark
Kingdom!
You think so?!
Wait, then...
In that case Mako
and Joe are in
serious danger!
Usagi! Wait up!
You need to stop
following me!
I'm just afraid that
someone else is going
to come after you.
(annoyed sigh)
I can be your
bodyguard.
And just why would
anyone be after me
anyway?!
Uhh, maybe 'cause
you won way too much
of that crane game.
Yeah! Maybe the folks
at the game center
hired someone to hunt
you down and kill ya!
Heh! Not likely.
Hey! Would you
be able to teach
me how to win at
that crane game?
You could never
do it...
(painful gasp)
What's the
matter, Joe?
Welcome!
Joe!
I'd like to enjoy
my coffee alone,
thank you!
He's sure got
an attitude!
That's why I
like him.
You see...
He reminds me of
the guy who
broke my heart.
Oohh...
Now that is the
face of a girl
who's in love...
(painful grunts)
Really, you can go
on without me if
you're too tired.
Oh no!
Ha ha ha!
Uh!
He wants you to
go in! You see
that!
Uh! What do
I do?!
You gotta stop
talking and
get going!
Come on now...
Wait!
There's no waiting
for love! Now get
in there and good
luck!
Uh.. Were you?
Have a seat.
'Kay...
Don't get the
wrong idea.
Yeah?!
It's just too annoying
to see you standing
around outside just
watching me.
Umm...
I'm great at the
crane game 'cause
I've got this
supernatural power
I've kinda been
blessed with...
Supernatural
power?!
Ever since I was a
kid, I've had this
weird ability.
(gasp)
You understand now?
I've never met anybody
else who can do that.
That's why I know you
could never win
that crane game.
But wait, hold on.
Isn't that considered
cheating?
Cheating who?! I've
got this ability
and I'm putting it
to really good use.
Oh, I see.
Welcome.
Oh, I'll have a large
curry rice. No, on
second thought, Tea
with milk. Hm?!
Ahh!
Help me!
It's that
guy again!
You're crawling
away and leaving
Mako behind?!
I don't care about
her! She's the one
who decided to
follow me!
What's that?! You
think of yourself
as a man acting
this way?!
She's not my
responsibility!
Besides giant girls
like her really
aren't my type!
I knew it!
That guy's from
the Dark Kingdom!
Oh Mako! Are
you all right?!
Say something!
That's the second
time a guy I liked
said that about me.
Oh Mako...
I've had it!
(startled scream)
You don't have to
run away. After all,
you're one of us.
O-One of you?!
I'm taking your
Rainbow Crystal.
(painful screams)
Got it!
Hold it, you!
Sailor Moon!
(chuckling)
You're a little
too late, Sailor
Moon!
Just who are
you anyway?!
Allow me to
introduce myself.
I am one of the
Dark Kingdom's Four
Kings of Heaven,
Zoisite.
What?!
I think I'll let
Gamecen take care
of the rest of this!
He vanished!
Gamecen!
Whah! Joe turned
into a monster!
(attack growl)
Ahh!
(crying scream)
Game-cen!
And just what do
you think you're
trying to do to my
hero Sailor Moon?!
That sign!
E-nough!
Wow!
Gamecen!
Look out!
I... can't move!
Sailor Moon!
Hold on!
Wait!
Huh?!
Mako! You're a
Sailor Guardian!
You can talk?!
To help Sailor
Moon, hold this
transformation pen
and shout out:
Jupiter Power
Make Up!
Please! You must!
It's the only way
to save her!
Jupiter Power
Make Up!
Sailor Jupiter!
Wow! Mako
transformed!
Jupiter, my
guardian planet!
Bring forth a
storm! Summon the
clouds and bring
down your thunder!
Supreme!
Thunder!
Ga-ga-ga-
Gamecen!
Supreme Sundae?
All right, one
more blast!
No-don't!
That monster still
has a human heart!
Remember he used to
be a human being!
Then how are we
supposed to stop
him!
You have to turn
that monster back
into his original
form!
But how?!
What is this?!
The moon stick!
Now shout, "Moon
Healing Escalation!"
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Gaaaaame...
Refresh!
(relaxed sigh)
Mako, you are the
fourth Sailor
Guardian, Sailor
Jupiter!
Me? A Sailor
Guardian?
Sailor Moon, listen.
Now that we've found
all four Guardians,
you will lead the
team to find and
protect our
Princess!
Wait! I'm the
leader?!
Yes. The Moon Stick
you're holding
signifies your
position as leader.
Agh! Dang it!
Dang it! Dang
it! Aw c'mon!
Who needs boys?!
Why you! Uh?!
Ah! I lost!
Ugh! One
more time!
(nervous laughing)
Oh! Hey Usagi!
Oh! Hi there,
Motoki!
Hey, I heard Joe the
Crane Troll played
here yesterday.
Wish I coulda
seen that.
Ha ha. Oh, allow
me to introduce you
to my new best
friend, Makoto Kino.
Nice to meet you.
You're just exactly
like my former love
who broke my heart.
Huh?!
Just yesterday you
said that Crane Joe
was exactly like him!
Well, I just
meant his voice.
Huh?!
Oh, Mako. Give me
a break, will ya?!
Oh, brother...
What's wrong, Usagi?
You look worried...
It's Naru. She's
still depressed over
what happened with
Nephrite...
You need to cheer
her up in times
like this!
Yeah...Wait, I
know! People usually
feel better if they
eat good food!
Let's see, French,
Chinese, Ethnic.
Ooh, they all
sound so yummy!
Are you sure you're
doing this for Naru?
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"Restore Naru's Smile:
Usagi's Friendship"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.