This is unforgivable!
Completely unforgivable!
I'd never let anyone
get away with kidnapping
(cont'd)
young girls who dream
of finding love!
But until the day
when every family is
safe and love is a
universal truth...
I am Sailor Moon,
and in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen
year-old middle school
student.
I'm a bit of
a klutz...
And some people
might say I'm a
little emotional.
So, one day, this
strange cat named
Luna gave me a
special brooch
that transformed me
into a guardian in
a sailor uniform...
... and told me
I had to fight bad
guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
(Giggles)
The Cursed Bus:
Enter Mars, The
Guardian of Fire.
(Queen Beryl)
If these Sailor
Guardians find the
Legendary Silver
(cont'd)
Crystal before we do,
then they could
cause us some very
(cont'd)
serious problems.
We, the Dark Kingdom,
must be first to
acquire the crystal.
We will show no
mercy to anyone who
stands in our way.
Are you here to
tell me you still
haven't located it?
I'm afraid so,
Queen Beryl.
You have failed
several times
already, Jadeite.
But I will give
you a chance to
redeem yourself.
Go collect more
human energy for
our great ruler
and then eliminate
those two
troublesome
guardians.
Yes.
(Police Sirens)
Huh?
I wonder what
happened...
(Gasp)
Ami!
Oh! Usagi!
(Giggle)
Hi, Luna!
(Luna)
Ami!
Are you waiting
for the bus?
Yeah, I'm on
my way to cram
school.
Wait, you seriously
have to travel so far
that you need to take
a bus to get there?!
It's nothing. I'd
take a plane if it
meant going to a
good cram school!
And besides, now
that I'm a Guardian,
I need to study and
acquire as much
knowledge as I
possibly can so that
I can help Luna find the
missing moon princess.
Yes, that's right,
Ami! You're so
admirable! Unlike
someone else I know...
Ha ha ha!
Where is that
bus?!
(All)
Huh?
(Police Sirens)
Another police
car?
(Naru)
Hey,girls!
(Kuri)
Have you two
heard what happened
on this bus route?
(Usagai & Ami)
What?!
Yesterday evening
a little after six
p.m., a bus that
was full of passengers
just drove off and
then disappeared!
Wow! Really? That
sounds pretty cool!
No, it's not.
It's really
serious!
Do you guys know
the bus stop down
the road called
Sendai-Zaka-Ue?
Yeah! It's where
the five streets
meet, isn't it?
That's right.
Apparently nearly
fifty people got
on the bus there
yesterday and
no one's seen
them or the bus
since!
At first, the police
tried to keep it
secret because they
thought it might
be a mass kidnapping
or something.
But no demands were
made, so they made
it public and opened
up an investigation.
The cursed six
o'clock bus...
(Gasp)
Scary, right?
You know, there's
a Hikawa Shrine
right near Sendai-
Zaka, and the amulets
from there are known
for warding off evil.
So what do you say
we go down there and
get some?
Wait, I know that
place!
They say the Shrine
Maiden there has
strong spiritual
powers and can even
predict the future!
Oh, then we can
get our fortunes
told too!
Well let's head
over there!
Usagi, do you think
you could pick me
up an amulet?
Yeah, but why don't
you come with us?
Sorry, but I really
have to study today.
There's an important
practice test coming
up that I can't
miss. You know what
it's like when you
have to hit the books.
Please, please,
please, let him
notice that I
like him!
(Girls)
I can't believe I
did that. Guys!
Seriously!...
(Chuckle)
Go on, wish for even
more love!
Fill your hearts
with romantic energy!
It's coming...
Something sinister
is growing closer...
(Grandpa Hino)
Hi, there! What
a bunch of cuties!
Any of you interested
in working here?
Huh??
sorry, but we just
came here to buy
some of those love
amulets that you sell.
Hahuh ha!
Why, of course!
I was only kidding
you! Ha ha
It's five thirty.
You're just in time!
So, as usual, I'll
recite a special
prayer in order
to bring true love
into your life!
Here me, oh spirit
flame! Listen to me
proclaim! May their
hearts come ablaze
(cont'd)
with true love always!
Let joy in them imbued,
and may their wishes
(cont'd)
come true!
(Sigh)
There.
I'm guessing that
you girls have
come a long way.
But, before you leave,
you should draw a
fortune slip!
We sell ema plaques
for passing exams,
as well! Maybe you
should buy a couple!
Thanks for your
concern, but we
don't need that.
(Giggles)
Weird!
Here's another
group of cuties!
(All)
Huh?
Would any of you
like to work part
time here as Shrine
Maidens!
(All)
Uhh...
(Rei)
Grandpa!
Just stop hitting
on everyone,
would you?!
Oh!
Hi, Rei!
You know, people
around here are
starting to say
very unflattering
things about you!
(Chuckle)
Ahh! She's so
cool! And pretty!
(Usagi)
So she's a shrine
maiden! I wouldn't
mind doing that
(cont'd)
part time!
(Giggles)
(Girls)
What fun!
(Giggles)
I sense an evil
aura! Is it a
spirit?!
(All)
Uhh...
Trying to make
trouble at our
shrine, huh?
Forget it!
I won't let you!
Evil spirit!
Be exorcized!
(Gasps)
Usagi!
That isn't what
I expected to
happen.
(Jadeite)
Ms. Rei, I
brought some hand
towels and water.
Thanks. You can
leave them right
there.
Sure.
Wait, that man
looks familiar...
What a hunk!
(Meow!)
what! Huh! Where'd
he go?! Huh?!
Well, that sure
was a quick
recovery!
Is that guy
your older brother?
What?! Oh, no!
Ugh, this is all
Grandpa's fault!
(Laughs)
(Rei)
He's so overly
friendly with
everyone!
(cont'd)
He tries to make
friends with every
person who comes
(cont'd)
to visit the
shrine.
Grandpa hired that
guy and now he's
actually living here
with us!
Uhh..
You're grandpa is
interesting...
Listen, Usagai,
I'm very sorry
for what happened
earlier.
It's no big
deal! I mean
uhh--
Things have been
really weird
lately.
For one, my sixth
sense and prophesies
used to be spot on,
but not anymore.
Huh?!
Prophesies? Wait,
could this girl
be the princess
that we've been
(cont'd)
looking for?
Huh?
You there!
Where's the person
in charge here!
My daughter came
here to buy one
of your amulets,
and she still hasn't
come back home!
I know your head
priest always has
a special prayer at
five thirty! You're
purposely sending
people onto that
cursed six o'clock bus!
Don't make wild
accusations!
Look, that ceremony's
been going on for a
long time! And the
police already
questioned us about
the bus's disappearance!
(cont'd)
If you want to file
a missing persons
report, talk to them!
My Grandfather has
nothing to do with
this! Now get out of
here!
(Gasp)
What nerve!
How rude!
(Rei)
You're the rude
one! Get out!
(Luna)
Usagi, something
strange is going
on. Our enemy is
(cont'd)
involved, I can feel
it. Call Ami. We need
to have a strategy
(cont'd)
meeting.
But Ami's busy!
A whole lot of
people have gone
missing! Just call
her and tell
her to get here
quickly!
All right,
already!
(Ami)
So, this is
Sendai-Zaka...
(Usagi)
Yeah.
Huh?
(Gasp)
Look at all
those people!
(Luna)
There all waiting
for the bus!
(Ami)
And they all have
amulets from Hikawa
Shine...
(Usagi)
I bet they went over
there 'cause they're all
in love with someone!
They should be busy
with high school
entrance exams!
Where do they
find the time
for all this?
Jeez.
But, don't you
want to fall in
love, too, Ami?
It's wonderful!
(Chuckle)
Usagi, both of us
are too young to
understand what love
truly is!
I really don't think
you should spend so
much energy on these
fantasies.
Oh, look!
(Ami)
There it is! That's
the six o'clock bus!
(Luna)
It just looks like
an ordinary bus!
(Ami)
You're right...
Okay, Usagi, get
on, quick!
But, uh...
Go on, go!
No! No way!
Come on!
I don't wanna!
And now, I
really don't!
Don't be like that,
Usagi. We have to
get on with the
others to investigate!
Be brave!
I can't!
I'm way to scared!
(Crying)
Oh no, it left!
(Luna)
Come on, Usagi!
You can't be
such a chicken!
I know! But
I-I-
(Crying)
Nothing we can do
now. We'll just have
to come back tomorrow.
I guess so...
Oh, look!
(Luna)
The bus!
Huh?
No way!
Could it be a
black hole? A
fourth-dimensional
rift?
Or a tear in the
magnetic field?
What is happening
here?!
(Deep chuckle)
Master Jadeite,
today's operation
was a big success.
(Jadeite)
The energy of girls
wishing for love is
very powerful.
( cont'd)
Drain it all from
them.
Sir!
Sailor Moon!
(Rei)
Here you go,
Phobos, Deimos.
(Usagi)
Rei!
Oh, hi,
Usagi!
Can I help you?
Yesterday's six
o'clock bus
disappeared, too!
I saw it with my
own eyes!
And you think my
Grandpa's involved
just like everyone
else does?!
Huh?!
The police keep
coming to question
us, and I'm sick
and tired of it!
You've got the
wrong idea, Rei!
I was just wondering
if you knew anything
that might help
us understand what
happened!
I don't!
I'm sorry if I'm
making you upset!
That's not what
I'm trying to do.
I just wanted
to be friends
with you!
Look, I don't care.
Just go.
Uh, okay. I'll
just come back
later. Bye!
What nerve! Who
does she think
she's kidding?!
I wonder if she
accidentally dropped
this...
(Girls)
Two love amulets,
please!
Sure, and what
colors can I get
for you?
Um, let's see.
(Girl)
Uh, which one?
(Rei)
Ever since he came
here, we've been
selling so many amulets.
(cont'd)
And more people have
been visiting, too.
(Girls)
I'm still deciding!
How bout a blue one!
Why would the buses
that go to the shrine
suddenly disappear?
What's the connection?!
Who is it?!
Who's out there?
It's only me. Your
meal is ready now,
miss.
Leave! You're
distracting me!
(Jadeite)
My apologies.
Those eerie, ice-cold
eyes of his...
Couldn't they be the
reason my prophecies
and divinations aren't
going well?
(Usagi)
Hey Luna, why'd
you leave that pen
with Rei?
(Luna)
I just wanna confirm
something that I've
been wondering about.
You wanna confirm
something?
Like what?
I'll explain it
later.
What's important right
now is that you get
on that six o'clock
bus today!
Yeah I know, but,
I, um...
(Luna)
You must conquer
your fear!
Hmm- I wonder what's
keeping Ami. She said
we'd get on the bus
together!
Ah! ú The bus!
Ah!
Ah! It's coming!
(Luna)
We have no choice.
We have to board
without her.
What! Wait, are
you kidding me?!
Okay, let's go!
Huh?
I changed my mind!
I'm scared!
(Luna)
Seriously
Usagi, get on!
(Usagi)
I don't wanna!
Stop this right now!
Hurry up!
(Deep Chuckle)
(Luna)
The bus is leaving,
come on!
(Usagi)
Please Luna, give me
a break, would you!
I'll never get
on that evil bus!
Okay!
Oh no, what now?
(Usagi)
Moon Power! Transform
me into a gorgeous
flight attendant!
There this will
help take some
of the fear away!
Uh, you know this
isn't an airplane,
right?
Hold that bus!
Wait for me!
(Usagi)
They're all!
What's all this?!
(Deep Chuckle)
As a flight attendant,
it's my sworn duty to
see that passengers
have a safe and
pleasant trip! So,
I won't let you take
over this bus!
Uh-Ahh!
Ahh!!
(Gasp)
I'm too late...
What's the origin
of this evil? What's
caused this misfortune
to befall us?
Rin! Pyo! To!
Sha! Kai! Jin!
Retsu! Zai!
Zen!
(Gasp)
So you're the cause
of this evil!
(Rei)
I should have known!
(Jadeite)
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
My trusted flames
have shown me
everything!
I know that you're
the root of the
evil here!
Reveal your true
self to me!
(Chuckle)
You fool! Now
you will join
the others!
What's happening?!
Ahh!
(Deep Chuckle)
(Crying)
Where am I?!
Usagi, just
calm down!
How can I?!
Look where we
are!
(Usagi)
Rei!
(Deep Chuckle)
(Luna)
It's a monster!
Usagi, you have
to transform into
Sailor Moon!
(Crying)
I'm so sick of
all this!
But I'll do it!
Yes! Your carefree
spirit and optimism
are your true
strengths!
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
I am the pretty
guardian who fights
for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
It's about time!
I've been expecting
you, guardian!
That mark!
Look!
Let Rei go! And
everyone else, too!
I won't let you
keep them trapped
here! So now, in
the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Ha! Your toy
can't defeat me!
But you fell
for my trick!
What?!
Rei, you aren't
hurt, are you?
No, I'm okay.
Rei, take out the
transformation pen!
Hold on!
Did that cat just
speak to me?!
I'll explain it
all later. Just
trust me.
Hurry up and take
out the pen that
you picked up earlier!
Uh.. this?
(Luna)
Use it to transform
into Sailor Mars,
the guardian of fire!
Now hold that pen
and call out, "Mars
Power Make Up!"
Uhh-Ahh!
(Usagi)
Hurry up!
I don't have a
clue what's happening,
but I'll give it a shot!
Mars Power!
Make up!
I don't believe
it! She's also
a guardian?!
(Gasp)
What is this?!
What's happened
to me?
AHH!
I don't know what's
going on, but you'll
pay for your evil
deeds, monster!
Fire!
Soul!
Ahh!
Eeee!
Huh?
(Usagi)
What's happening?
(Luna)
Oh, no! Rei's attack
is causing the dimensional
portal to close!
(cont'd)
We have to get
out of here, fast!
Yeah, but how?!
(Luna)
No idea!
Ahh!
What are we
gonna do?!
Usagi, Luna, everyone!
Please be safe!
( Luna)
Ahh! It's closing!
(Rei)
What's that?
Is Ami doing
that?!
I'm not sure, but
it's possible. She
might be trying to
show us the way
out of here!
I think you're
right!
Quickly, run toward
the point where that
light is coming from!
Hey there!
You girls need
a ride?
Hop on!
Ah! Tuxedo Mask!
You're here!
Wow, he's
really cool!
(Usagi)
Check it out!
(Luna)
Let's go,
you two!
(Usagi)
Right!
Oh!
Nice work, Ami!
(Giggle)
(Jadeite)
So, another
guardian has
appeared?
It seems you'll
make a worthy
opponent!
But I will crush
you next time
without fail!
Luna!
Ami!
Thank you!
You did a great
job, Usagi!
Until we meet
again...
(Rei)
Wait, where's
Tuxedo Mask?
(All girls)
Aww...
Wait a minute!
Don't tell me
you're falling for
Tuxedo Mask!
What?! Don't be
ridiculous! I only
wanted to thank him
for helping us save
the passengers! And
besides, you're the
one who has feelings
for him!
Isn't that right?
Wake up, honey.
Sometimes those
feelings are only
one-sided.
What's "one-
sided" mean?
It can't be!
No, not that!
(Crying)
(Usagi)
Luna, did you
hear the news?!
(Luna)
What news?
(Usagi)
People have gone
missing from the Dream
Land amusement park.
(cont'd)
Think a monster's
behind it?
(Luna)
You just want an
excuse to go play
there, don't you?
(Usagi)
No! I want to
investigate!
(Luna)
Investigate
what?
(Usagi)
Um, the roller-
coaster, the Ferris
wheel, the merry
(cont'd)
go round!
(Luna)
You're just in
it for the rides!
Next time on Sailor
Moon, "Usagi vs Rei:
Nightmare In Dream
Land."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is
a messenger of love.