What?! They're trying
to bring back the Seven
Great Monsters, after
all the trouble we went
through to turn them
back into humans? If
they want to recycle
something, then try
recycling cans! They
can't recycle people!
It's absolutely
unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
(tired sigh)
Huh?
Who's there?
(evil chuckle)
I've been looking for
you, Miss Nishimura.
But, maybe you'd prefer
I call you Rikokeida,
which is your true
given name as one of
the Seven Great
Monsters.
What are you
talking about?
Come on! Do not
resist. Join us
once again.
(painful grunts)
Four down, three
more to go...
"I Won't Run Away From
Love Anymore: Ami
Versus Mamoru."
Hello. This is Ami.
Hey Ami, it's
me. Ryo Urawa.
Oh! Hi, Ryo. It's
good to hear from
you!
Ami, are you
anywhere near
a TV?
Yep. I've got one
right in front of me.
You need to turn
it on. Right now!
(gasp)
The woman that you're
looking at is Miss
Yumemi Yumeno. She's
the fifth of former
Seven Great Monsters
to go missing.
W-What are you
saying, Ryo?
I'm saying the next
target could be me...
...or your friend Rei's
grandfather. You have
to believe me. I used
my precognitive powers
to figure it out.
Where are you? If
you're here in town,
I can come protect
you right now.
No! You need to stay
away from me so you
won't be in danger.
You should go
and protect Rei's
grandfather instead.
Don't worry, I can
handle things on
my own.
You must stop the Dark
Kingdom's plans at all
costs, or terrible
things will happen. Go!
Ryo?! Ryo!
It's better this way.
I wish I had Ami and
the others help. But I
can't become dependent
on them again, I need
to be able to take
care of myself.
Hold on. Wasn't that?
This is Makoto.
Mako, something's
come up! Meet us at
the Hikawa Shrine
right away!
Got it. Mm-hmm
Queen Beryl, I'm curious
about what Endymion is
doing. Why is he trying
to retransform the
humans into the Seven
Great Monsters right now.
(evil chuckle)
Well, as you know,
each one of them was
purified by the Moon
Stick and returned
to human form.
However, by using our
Dark Energy and the
power of the Dark
Crystal, we can turn
them back into
monsters again.
But why go through all
that trouble? They were
defeated by the Sailor
Guardians, which makes
them useless.
Ha! Well, here's
what you don't know.
Once the seven are
together, they will
combine as one to
become the largest
and most powerful
monster ever to
be seen.
Ahhhh!
Ahhh!
And when that happens,
we will finally be able
to put an end to the
Sailor Guardians, once
and for all!
Something I've been
striving to do. So why
would you assign this
important task to
Endymion and
not to me?!
Are you questioning
my decision, Kunzite?
Is there a problem?
No, Ma'am, no
problem, but...
Then hold off on
your judgment and
let's watch and see
how Endymion does.
Hmph. Fine.
So tell me, Ami. Is
your friend Ryo's
precognitive power
really accurate?
Yes, it's extremely
accurate.
Hey. You'd better
believe that if the
Dark Kingdom is
rounding up the
Seven Great Monsters,
that can only mean one
thing. They're planning
something awful.
Okay, Ami, let's
go. Come on.
Huh? Where are
we going?
I thought it was
obvious! We have to
go look for Ryo and
give him protection!
But we don't even know
if he's in town or where
to begin to look for him.
I saw him. I know he's
in the neighborhood. We
just have to walk around.
We'll run into him.
You guys better keep an
eye on Rei's Grandpa.
Wahhhh!
What is it? What's
the matter, Usagi?
I feel so sorry
for the hero of
this manga!
Hey! You should ask
permission before
you read my manga!
What's the big
deal? You weren't
reading it.
And now I can't
because you're
crying all over
it!
They're at it again.
And this won't be
the last time either.
(disappointed sighs)
I'm close. He must
be somewhere right
around here.
Ryo Urawa, I presume?
And you're Endymion
from the Dark Kingdom?
I see your precognitive
skills prepared you for
my arrival. That's very
impressive, Mr. Urawa.
So you know what's
next. What your
immediate future
holds for you?
I do. I've been there
before. You plan on
drawing me into the
Dark Crystal.
That's very good. Now
don't resist. Come with
me and we'll get this
over quickly.
Sorry, but I'm afraid
I can't accommodate you.
You see, someone once
told me that my future
is something that I
create for myself.
So what does
that mean?
It means, I'm not
going to give up!
(painful grunt)
Murderer!
Help me!
Back off!
No! It's not true!
Get out of here!
Let's go back. I
feel sorry for Ryo,
but there's not much
we can do for him at
this point. It's
probably too late.
You just feel sorry
for him? I always
thought Ryo was your
boyfriend, Ami.
No way, he's not
my boyfriend. He's
just a friend of mine.
Eh-uhh, are you really
sure about that Ami,
that you're not just
in denial?
Well, uh...
Ami, I hope you
haven't forgotten
that Ryo is in love
with you!
Yeah, I know that.
But we have an
important mission
that takes priority
over everything
else. I can't allow
myself to return
his feelings.
That'll leave you
with nothing! Only
regret for the rest
of your life!
Even Sailor Guardians
are entitled to fall
in love.
Or at least go on a
date with a boy they
really care about.
You're just
running away,
Ami!
That's why you want
to go back now. It's
another excuse to keep
yourself from getting
attached to him.
You're afraid to
fall in love.
Admit it, you're just
not being honest with
yourself.
Th-that's not true.
(gasp)
There he is!
Listen, I completely
understand why you'd
hesitate to get
involved. It can be
difficult. A-Ami,
where are you going?
Hey, come back!
I wasn't finished!
I just saw him!
What? You saw Ryo?
Yeah...
Let's go!
Ami...
I-I mean Sailor
Mercury!
How's it going?
You all right?
Don't worry, we're
here. So you'll be
safe now.
(amused laugh)
Oh, how reassuring
to know that.
(determined grunt)
Huh? Mamoru?!
Mamoru? Recently
someone else also
called me by that
name...
...But all of you
are wrong!
My name is Endymion!
Sailor Moon!
Sailor Mercury, take
Ryo away from here.
I'll handle this.
No, I'm fighting
with you!
What are you talking
about? Right now
protecting Ryo is
our top priority!
But...
Go, now!
Okay!
This way, Ryo!
Mamoru. No.
Endymion!
I really don't want
to have to fight you.
But since I must,
I won't hold back.
I promise you!
That's fine by me.
But are you sure you
can handle me all by
yourself?
I'll give it
everything I've
got!
Supreme!
Thunder!
Hah! I'm so scared!
This is Sailor Mercury!
Ryo is safe! He's with
me right now!
Good work,
Sailor Mercury!
But right now Sailor
Jupiter is fighting
Mamoru alone to buy us
some time to get away!
Did she say Mamoru?
Will Sailor Jupiter
be all right fighting
him by herself?
Not sure, but we
need Sailor Moon
right away!
The Moon Stick might
be our only hope to
return Mamoru to
the way he was!
Get up, Usagi!
Uhh, all right.
Let's go! C'mon,
Luna.
Uhh, point me in the
right direction, 'cause
I don't know where I'm
going.
(fighting grunts)
What's the matter?
Have you worn yourself
out already?
I'm not done
quite yet!
I admire your fighting
spirit. But I don't
have time to play games
with you all day.
Let me show you
what a real attack
should look like.
(fighting grunts)
Ahhh! Yahh!
(terrified scream)
Hah-ha.
Just as I thought.
You're way out of
your league. Look me
up when you're an even
match. Maybe I'll
come out to play!
Damn you!
Sailor Mercury...
Huh?
Do me a favor.
Look!
C'mon! Run this way!
I'm freezing and I
don't think this
cold is good for
my complexion!
You've gotta run
faster! That'll make
your complexion nice
and rosy!
Oh, yeah, that's
easy for you to
say!
Ahhh!
Wahh! That hurt!
What happened,
Usagi!
Sailor Jupiter,
you're all right!
Thank goodness, we
got here in time.
But you didn't. Luna,
by any chance did
Endymion pass this
way?
I don't think so.
Damn it!
Where'd he go?
Ryo, what's up?
Why did you wanna
come in here?
Sorry, it's just I've
always dreamed about
going to an amusement
park with you.
That's really sweet.
Now I have no regrets.
My dream's been fulfilled.
But it would be best if
we split up right away.
We can't. There's no
telling when the Dark
Kingdom will be coming
after you again.
I'm prepared to give
up my life to fight
them!
I want you to be free
of me, to fulfill your
own mission!
My life is no big
loss. I wasn't human
to begin with. But if
giving my life can
save the world, then
I've accomplished
something.
I believe we're two
of a kind, always
running away from
something. Something
we truly want.
Huh?!
That's what a friend
of mine told me. She
said I was in denial
and that I should just
be more honest
with myself.
Uh... but, Ami.
Sacrificing yourself,
is certainly noble.
But be honest, wouldn't
you really rather keep
on living as a human
being instead?
Seems like you've
forgotten about the
people who will be
very sad if you die.
(surprised breath)
It's time that we
stop running away.
No matter what the
obstacle is, let's
tackle it head-on!
Those are all truly
admirable thoughts,
Sailor Mercury.
What is it that
you want.
Look at that!
Huh?!
C'mon. Let's
check it out!
Right!
Listen, Mamoru. I'm
not going to hesitate,
even a moment, to fight
you anymore!
Prepare yourself!
I look forward to it.
I was planning on
waiting until the
other Sailor Guardians
were drawn here by the
light of the ferris
wheel, but I take it
you don't need them
to fight me.
Bubble!
Spray!
(startled gasp)
Hold on. I have one
piece of business to
take care of, before
I fight you.
(grunt)
(painful grunt)
(gasp)
Oh no!
Ryo!
(painful grunts)
Ami!
(evil laugh)
Thanks for waiting.
You horrible monster!
How could you!
I don't care if the
Dark Kingdom forced
you to do this!
I'll make you
pay for what
you've done!
Douse yourself in
water, and repent!
Hmph! If you're hoping
to bring your boyfriend
back here. You'll have
to destroy this, the
Dark Crystal.
But of course, that
means you'll have to
defeat me first to
get your hands on it.
So let's fight!
(surprised gasp)
Hah. I just want you
to know that, because
I respect you, I won't
hold back.
I know I don't
stand a chance.
But I have to try.
Bubble Spray!
Again? Is that
all you've got?
Why, you deceptive brat!
No more deceptive
than you! Now I have
a mission I need to
get done first, as well!
(angry growl)
(delighted sigh)
You're all right!
Yeah, and you Sailor
Mercury, look much
more confident than
you did earlier.
Thanks. I really
owe it all to you,
Sailor Jupiter.
Hey! Looks like you
single-handedly
crushed the Dark
Kingdom's plan!
Sailor Moon. Listen.
Right now you've got
to turn Tuxedo Mask
back to normal!
Not if I get rid
of the three of
you first!
From now on...
When you're in the
mood to recycle, only
recycle cans! Don't
try to recycle people
who are living peaceful
lives. It's unforgivable!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
Supreme!
Thunder!
Bubble!
Spray!
(painful screaming)
Now, Sailor Moon!
You've gotta be
quick!
Jeez, I know that!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
No!
(painful grunts)
It looks like it's
working to a degree,
but he needs more.
Increase the energy,
Sailor Moon.
(forceful grunts)
(painful groans)
Refresh!
You did it! You
brought the real
Mamoru back!
Thank goodness!
(exhausted sighs)
Great job,
Sailor Moon!
Huh?!
He vanished!
But how?
It must be the
work of the Dark
Kingdom.
Oh no!
As I feared, Endymion
hadn't lost his past
memories, after all we
had done to ensure it.
So there's more work
to do. We need to
infuse him with the
energy of our Great
Ruler. And this time
we'll turn him into
a loyal servant of the
Dark Kingdom forever!
(people chatter)
Let's come here
again, all right?
(gasp)
Sure!
(giggle)
We can't let
this happen!
If Ami's side-tracked
from her important
mission because of her
interest in this new
relationship,
who's gonna keep
us together?
Isn't that supposed
to be your job, Usagi?
Uh...
I think you're
jealous of those
two. Isn't that
right?
You're jealous, too!
Oh, come on guys,
just cool it. Let's
be happy for them
and let them be!
Minako's crush is a
handsome boy from
England!
Nice, very nice!
Hey, don't forget!
You have Mamoru!
Yep! That's right!
There was this one
time when, underneath
the gentle moonlight,
Mamoru and I
shared a...
(giggle)
What did you
share exactly?
I'm too embarrassed
to say it!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Sailor Venus's Past:
Minako's Tragic Love."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.