A powerful evil energy is
about to be unleashed into
the world. And we're the
only ones who can stop it.
Oh sacred light of the
Moon, give us the strength
to succeed in this fight.
Sailor Jupiter, Mercury,
Venus, Mars! No matter
what happens, we'll
always be together!
The dark spots on the sun
continue to spread at an
unusual pace. Earthquakes,
volcanic eruptions,
hurricanes and other
catastrophes believed to be
caused by this phenomenon,
continue to occur throughout
the world. The National
Weather Bureau is calling
this an unprecedented
atmospheric event and has
released a statement
saying they-
We will have to
act quickly!
"Death of the Sailor
Guardians: The Tragic
Final Battle."
Dinner's ready, hope
you're all really hungry!
Tonight's menu features
my very special curry!
We're thrilled you made
such an effort to make
us dinner, Usagi!
Oh Dad, you make it
sound like this is
such a big deal!
Well it is! Shall
we dig in, everyone?
Is it really edible?
Don't be rude. Maybe
it doesn't look great,
but the taste will
blow you away!
Uh, Is something
the matter, Usagi?
What's wrong??
It's hot!
See, I knew it.
Is everyone ready?
Yeah. Let's do this.
Well, there's no
turning back now.
Hey, uh, Rei!
Hm?
Do did you at least
give Yuichiro a kiss
before leaving home?
And just why'd you
bring that up?
I just thought, what if
something bad happens,
you'd have regrets.
Nothing bad is gonna
happen to us!
Ow! You don't have to
yell at me like that!
I was just concerned
about you!
Just mind your
own business!
Usagi, let's stop all
this thinking about
'what if?'
I agree, when this is
all over I intend to get
out there and experience
all the love I can.
Really, Mako? I guess
all of you are right.
Sorry.,,
Love, huh?
I'd like that.
Oh?
Hm?
Ohh?
All right, that's enough
talking girls. It's time!
Let's go everyone!
Transform!
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Jupiter Power!
Venus Power!
Make Up!
All of you need to get
to the D-Point in the
Arctic Circle at once!
But how?!
By putting all of your
powers together and
teleporting yourselves.
Since we're both injured,
we'd only get in your way.
So we're going to stay
here. But you girls can
handle this, right?
If you Sailor Guardians
combine all of your powers,
there's no doubt you will
defeat Queen Beryl!
Sailor Teleport!
Good luck, girls.
Please, come back
to us safely.
Yi-Yi-Yikes!
It's freezing!
How come all of you
aren't shivering in
this cold?!
Pull yourself together
and you won't feel the
cold!
Speak for yourself!
You have more body fat!
We're not off to a
great start, are we?
Huh?
Hey, I found it! There's
a strong evil aura that's
coming from over in that
direction!
Ahh-Choo!
Very soon now, Queen
Metalia will be fully
resurrected. I'll make
sure of it!
Whoever thinks they can
eliminate these foolish
Guardians, step forward!
The DD Girls will
finish them! Leave
the task to us!
Wait!
Hm?
The evil aura's
getting much
stronger.
Here they come!
Tuxedo Mask...
It's Tuxedo Mask!
Wait! It could
be a trap!
Isn't that obvious
by now...
But I...
C'mon! They're doing
this because they know
you'll run to him!
Let's see...
Help me Sailor
Moon, please...
Sailor Moon...
I can't! I've
gotta go help him!
No! Don't!
Control yourself!
But can't you see?!
He's suffering! I
have to help!
He needs me!
(shocked gasp)
Watch out, everybody!
That's a monster!
Huh?!
Ahhhh!
See? I told you so!
I didn't wanna
believe it!
(evil laughter)
Hey you monster! How
dare you trick me! You
guys are really mean for
trashing the pure love a
young girl can have for
someone special, even
though I was a little
stupid to fall for your
silly trick. Now you've
gone and made me really
angry! So I'm going to...
We get it.
So anyway...
Now, in the name
of the Moon. I'll
punish you!
(unimpressed laugh)
There's five of them?
You girls don't stand
a chance against us,
not while you're here
in the D-Point!
Sailor Moon, I
love you...
Hunh! What kind of idiot
would fall for the same
stupid trick twice?
Hey didn't you
hear what I said?
But he needs me!
What if this time it's
for real and he's not
actually some kind of
monster?!
Ahhhh!
See?!
Sorry!
I've had enough of this!
Back off!
(shocked gasp)
Motoki!
(gasp)
Ahhh!
(startled gasps)
Moon Tiara!
Fire!
It's not good! We'll
end up hitting Jupiter
as well!
Never mind me! You've
got to make your move
to go stop Queen Beryl!
(painful grunt)
(gasps)
(painful grunts)
Allow me to give you
girls a taste of what
real thunder feels like.
What?!
Go to hell!
Supreme Thunder!
That's enough
from you!
Die!
(painful scream)
(gasps)
Curse you!
(strained grunts)
(gasp)
Jupiter!
Hey girls...
I'm coming!
I'm not gonna
make it...
So, go, get her. Get
Queen Beryl. Hurry!
Leave me here.
No we won't! We
have to go back
there together!
Remember what you said
Mako? How when you get
back you're going to find
all the love you can!
You weren't lying
to us, were you?!
Just stay with us. Don't
give up. If you lied, Lord
Enma will pull your
tongue out!
There's no time for
crying. You must go...
Princess...
(gasp)
(shocked gasp)
No! Mako! You
can't die! Mako!
Sailor Moon!
There's nothing more
we can do here. We need
to go. Come on, Sailor
Moon.
Forget it! If stuff like
this is going to happen,
we should just give them
the Silver Crystal!
How can you even
say that?!
It's true. That's really
what we should've done
in the first place!
Queen Beryl!
Sailor Moon!
Stop it!
You can have the
Silver Crystal
right now!
Let go! That Crystal's
why Mako died!
We should just
give up!
Sorry I did that, but
listen. Don't let
Jupiter's death be
in vain...
They're coming!
Right!
No! You three need to
keep going. I'll hold
them off here.
But, Mercury...
You and Venus have more
firepower than I do, and
Sailor Moon needs all the
support you can give her!
Now go!
Wait Ami, you're not?
Don't be silly!
I'm not gonna die!
Do you promise!
Yeah.
Come and get me!
(gasp)
Ryo...
So now it's my turn
to see illusions of
someone special.
Huh?
Bubble!
Spray!
Ahhh!
It's actually an illusion,
but it possess the heat
of the real thing! The
illusion's source is that
jewel on her forehead!
The only way to stop
them, is to destroy
the source of this
illusion!
Bubble!
Spray!
Ahhh!
No you'll roast
like a pig!
I'm no pig!
How about a
baked potato?
Hah! Now die!
Ahhhh!
(exhausted sigh)
(evil chuckle)
Guess I won't be
using this again...
(attacking grunt)
Damn her! Now I
can't create my
illusions anymore!
(shocked gasp)
Ami is...
Ami is dead!
Why?! Why did she
choose to stay
behind!
Crying over everything
won't help us!
They're gonna keep
attacking us! They
won't stop!
But...But, I'd never
thought it'd turn out
like this.
(gasp)
Look out!
Ahhhh!
No! Minako!
Stop it! Now!
I'll give you the Silver
Crystal if you'll just
let Minako go!
If you do that I'll
never forgive you!
Ahhhh!
You Guardians are fools!
Begging for your teammate's
life. That Silver Crystal
will be ours, but only
after we kill every
last one of you!
Starting with this one!
Ahhhh!
Minako!
(painful screams)
Crescent!
Beam!
Ahhhh!
Minako!
You know what...
What?
I really had fun
arguing with you
all the time.
Wait! Why'd you
just say that?!
I thought I'd tell you
in case something bad
happens.
Stop it! This isn't
the time to be joking!
Wait!
I can handle the rest
of what needs to be
done here. I'll defeat
them and Queen Beryl
then I'll come home!
So please Rei, just
go home!
I don't want
you to die!
I appreciate your concern,
but I'm afraid I can't let
you do that. You need to
save your strength for the
bigger battle.
Besides, you've never
seen anyone come close
to beating me!
Give me two minutes,
then we'll go finish
Queen Beryl together!
Fire!
They're fast!
Ahhh!
Rei!
What happened?
Now you're mine!
(surprised gasp)
Ahhh!
She's alive!
Damn you!
(painful screams)
Well now, that leaves
just you, Princess.
Rei, no!
Now it's your turn!
I'm not done yet!
(shocked gasp)
Fire...
Soul!
Ahhhh!
Usagi, turns out you
were right about
Yuichiro, I...
Should've kissed him.
Too late now...
Mako...Ami...
Minako... Rei...
I get it. This is
a dream. A dream...
When I wake up, they'll
say "good morning" like
always. And Rei will call
me "silly Usagi" as usual.
Hey now. no
need for tears.
Be strong, Usagi.
Don't you ever
give up hope.
Now get up, Usagi!
Right!
We will always be
here with you.
You will...
Good! Now go!
That's right! I'm
not alone! I'm not
alone!
(evil chuckle)
Mamoru, please, stop!
It's me, Usagi!
I don't want to fight
you! Please remember!
Usagi, don't! If you
unleash the power of
the Silver Crystal,
you'll die!
Silver Crystal! My
feelings, everyone
else's feelings. Give me
the power to believe in
them even more!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi's Eternal Wish:
A Brand New Life."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.