[Usagi]
You know what's worse than
being rude and damaging
things that aren't yours?
People who think nothing of
other people's feelings,
that's what!
I am Sailor Moon, and
in the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino, and
I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a Cancer with blood type O.
My birthstone is a pearl,
and I'm a bit of a klutz.
Some people might say I'm
also a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange
cat named Luna appeared,
turned me into a Guardian
in a sailor uniform,
and told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggles]
Punishment Awaits: The House Of
Fortune Is The Monster Mansion.
Come on!
Hurry up!
Okay!
I hear that this
guy is really good!
Yeah, me, too.
He's even been on TV a
couple of times. So.
Oh no! Look at
this long line!
Hmf. Foolish humans.
[Queen Beryl]
What? You still have not found
the Legendary Silver Crystal?!
[ghostly voices]
No.
Then you must
search harder!
The great ruler needs
massive amounts of energy
and can't be kept waiting!
[ghostly voices]
As you command.
Jadeite.
Yes.
As I'm sure you've heard,
the Legendary Silver Crystal
has not been found.
So I want energy to be harvested
from humans instead.
Rest assured, I have
already taken care of it.
[alarm]
Mmmh...
Time to wake up!
Augh...
Oh, no you don't!
Ergh... I...
can't breathe...
How do you expect to succeed
in our mission lying down?!
[gasp]
Aww...
Good girl!
It's already past eight?!
Why didn't you wake
me up earlier, Luna?
Now I am totally
late for school!
[sigh]
Gurio Umino.
Here!
Kenji Ohta.
Takayuki Kamikawa.
Here.
Shhh!
Yuji Kimura.
Here.
Well, hello and
good morning to
you, Usagi!
Ghkk!
You go straight
to the hallway!
Why exactly are you
out here with me?
Oh, well, 'cause you know,
it's actually a little
difficult for me to
explain.
You're such
a weirdo.
Yeah.
[running]
So, what did you
want to talk about?
I want to go on a
date with Usagi!
She's my dream girl!
I want to exchange
diaries with her!
And talk to her parents
about our future together!
Huh?
Ha ha ha!
That's not gonna happen!
Guaah!
[giggles]
Sorry, but I just don't
think it'll work if you
ask her straight out.
So I should be
stealthy and go for
a surprise attack!
No, you silly. I say you
go and ask a fortuneteller
what you should do!
Well, in that case,
I already have the
answer.
Huh?
This "fortune telling game"
I have was based on an
idea of mine.
This says that Usagi and I
are supposed to get married
and live happily ever after!
[sigh]
See, it says
"Happy Couple!"
I'm not talking
about a game!
I'm mean going to a
real fortuneteller!
Oh. I see.
You know, House of Fortune
just opened in the Juban
District, and I've heard
that they're really good.
So why don't you go there
and give them a try?
Yeah!
[goofy giggles]
Huh?
What's going on?
There's usually a really
long line of people here.
[chuckle] You're right, but
now I have competition.
Huh?
"House of Fortune?"
It's so flashy!
What is that place?
Well, that is the new
"House of Fortune."
What? So do they do
fortune there as well?
Yes. And everyone wants to
go there because it's new.
Huh?
Well I want YOU to
read my fortune!
Why of course.
Hmm.
I can tell there's a boy
that likes you right now.
And it's someone you
see all the time.
A boy I see all
the time likes me?
Could it be him?!
[excited giggle]
Too bad, it looks like
he's not here yet.
Hmm...
[Motoki]
Hey, Usagi!
Whaa!
That's what I call
perfect timing!
I'm just about
to start work.
Hi, Motoki! What
a coincidence!
Hey, the Sailor V
game just came in!
Wanna be the first
one to give it a try?
Yeah!
Come on, come on,
come on, yeah,
come on, come on!
Aw, come on!
Die, die, die!
Yes! Ha ha ha!
Ohhh! Wha?
Aw... Game over!?
That's a pretty
hard game, isn't it?
Yeah, sure is!
I'll tell you what:
let me show you
some tricks.
Oh, no, let me--
It's on me.
Okay, now watch
me carefully.
See, once you get there,
you have to get that
special item.
See? Now I have it,
it'll give me the
power boost I need...
My heart's pounding
like crazy!
I'm in heaven!
[Motoki]
You got it? Then you
just keep shooting.
[dreamy]
Ahh...
Mmh.
Luna?! What are
you doing here?!
Oh! Luna?
That's her name, huh?
Yeah.
You know, I've seen her
around here a lot lately.
I wonder if she's a stray.
[growl]
Hrm!
Hey, what are you doing?
Cut it out!
All right! All right, already!
I'm going, I'm going!
Let go!
Well, see ya!
But you're still right in
the middle of your game!
I'll come again.
I'll be waiting.
Every time that I see
you, it always perks up
my whole day, Usagi!
[happy squeal]
[giggle]
Nice! Way to
ruin the moment!
I thought you were supposed to
go straight home after school?
Well, yes. I mean,
technically, I am.
You're not getting it.
You need to listen to me.
Your mission is of the
utmost importance!
[running]
Where are you going now?!
I'm going to go see that
fortuneteller again, about
my future with Motoki!
Huh!?
No! I'm too late.
Ah!
I should probably wait
to ask the guy who did
my fortune before,
but... I want to
know right away!
Just what are you up to, Usagi?
Uht! Nothing!
Never mind!
Wait, I know!
I'll tell my own fortune
to decide where to go!
Heads, I go to the
guy I saw before.
Tails, I go to the
House of Fortune!
(om kicking/flipping shoe
effort)
Hm?
Ow!
Uh, oh...
It's that stuck-up
guy again.
You need to watch where you're
throwing things, bun head!
Is that all
you can say?
Well, how about this:
why don't you try
acting more like a
lady for a change.
[angry]
Rgnnnn!
Thanks for the advice!
Bleeh!
Ahhg! And I was
so happy, too!
Hmm?
Who does he
think he is?!
Now, then.
[blows on cards]
Awesome!
Look deep into my eyes.
Ohh...
Ohh?
You have now become
a charming servant
of the devil.
And whatever whim pops into
your head, you can do it
without any fear at all.
I understand completely.
I can do whatever
I want to do.
[chuckle]
Soon I'll begin collecting
energy for my master.
[sinister chuckle]
Sailor Moon!
[Kenji]
Hey, Usagi!
Huh?
Dad! What are you
doing, shopping?
Yeah, I got home early
for a change, and
decided to help your mom
by running some errands.
Oh, Dad, that's
really sweet of you!
Well, Mom does take care of
everything around the house.
This is the least I can do.
Ah, I bet Motoki's
considerate like Dad is.
By the way, Usagi,
Huh?
What are you doing
out so late?
Come on, let's go home before
your Mom gets worried.
Sorry.
[Kenji]
Usagi, what's
with that cat?
It looks to me
like it's trying
to follow us home.
Oh, that's just
my friend.
Hmm. Okay, I guess
that's only
slightly strange.
Hmph.
Has Umino said
anything to you yet?
What do you mean?
About what?
That he likes you.
like, likes
you likes you.
Whaaa?!
[chuckle]
But he's so shy that
he can't bring
himself to tell you.
[Umino] [smooth]
Usagi, let's go on a date.
What's happened
to you?
Umino, you can't come
to school out of
uniform like that!
Who cares?
Usagi, let's get goin'.
Going where?
Wow, someone's gotten
a little overconfident
all of a sudden.
Umino! What is with
that outfit of yours?!
Heh!
Speak up! Is this
some kind of a joke?
Hmph.
Ahhh!
[Umino]
No, that was a joke!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[stunned]
Baww!
Oh, I'll never
live this down!
[Umino]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ngh!
That's quite enough
out of you!
He he ha ha ha ha ha!
Whoa!
Rrrgh!
[snicker]
What are you doing, Yuji?!
I think you'd better
learn to walk and talk
more quietly in class.
What did you say!?
[Umino]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What? Umino went to
the House of Fortune?
Yeah, I told him all
about it yesterday.
I think that Yuji went
over there, as well.
Hmmm.
[crash]
Huh?
Hey! What do you
think you're doing!
You're all in big trouble!
Yagh!
You think an incompetent
teacher like you can
boss us around?
Think again!
Yeah, let's
teach him!
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Ah ha ha ha ha.
Yes, keep causing trouble!
Ah, the rebellious
energy of youth.
[chuckle]
Mm hm hm, ha ha ha ha!
Hey, stop that!
What do you
think you're
doing?!
Hey, Usagi.
Stop saying my
name like that!
How about a kiss?
Wahhhh, I can't
stand you like this!
Wahhh! I can't stand you!
Waahhh!!
Come on, let's get
out of here, guys.
Waahhh!!!
I'm sensing some dark energy
coming from those kids.
It's okay,
they're gone now.
Phew, I feel better now.
Haugh.
Umino tried to kiss me?
What is he thinking,
acting like that?
You have to listen to me,
Usagi, something evil is
trying to stir up trouble.
So Umino and the others?
I'm sure that they're
being controlled.
I wonder if it has
anything to do with
that House of Fortune?
What?
Umino has been acting
really strange ever since
he went to that place.
Nice one!
Good job
figuring that out!
You could reward me with
more goodies like the
brooch you gave me!
I take back what
I just said!
Let's go!
Errm, am I gonna have
to fight again?
Sounds kinda scary.
Uh! Would you come on already!
Time to transform!
Go on!
Do I have to?
Yes, you have to!
[nervous]
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Hrrm! Okay!
Eeehehe! I kinda
forgot! I say what?
Just say,
"Moon Prism Power Make Up!"
Oh, right! That's it! Heh!
Moon Prism Power Make Up!
All of you have done an
excellent job so far.
Now go and tear up
the rest of this town!
Yeah!
Sounds like
fun to me!
[Sailor Moon]
You know what's worse than
being rude and damaging
things that aren't yours?
People who think nothing
of other people's
feelings, that's what!
[Balm]
Who's there?!
I am the pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Sailor... Moon?
And now, in the name of the
moon, I will punish you!
Yahh!
Huh?
Hey, that almost hit my face!
Hello, that's
because she was
trying to hit it!
Oh, yeah;
you're right.
[sinister laughter]
Go get her!
Raah!
Hu hu ha ha ha!
Oh no, not this again!
Raaa!
No!
Ehehhe!
Heeheheh!
That's it! If you
come any closer,
you're really gonna get it!
Haa! Heee! Hehehehe!
Ahhh!
Agh!
Aaahhhh!
Heeheehahaha...
[scared]
Mmmh...
Huh?
Huh?!
Someone else getting
in the way?!
Who is it now?!
Heh.
Tuxedo Mask!
Sweet!
No matter how bad things look,
you must never, ever give up!
Okay!
And now farewell!
Until we meet again!
Oh, thank you!
'Bye, Tuxedo Mask!
Haaaagh!
[gasp]
[growl]
Ooh, she's mad.
Come on, Sailor Moon, focus!
Use your tiara!
Oh, yeah! That's right!
Hraaaa!
Huh?
Haah...
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Yah!
Raahh!
Moon Tiara...
Action!
Waagh!
Augghhh!
So, Balm, you failed me.
[relieved sigh]
Haa! I did it!
Huhh?
See ya later, guys!
[Umino]
What?!
I lifted up Ms. Haruna's
skirt? Seriously?
Oh, no no no!
Plus, you also demanded
a kiss from Usagi.
Oh, and you broke a
window in one of the
teacher's offices.
Huh? Hey, where are
you going, Umino?
Augh, well, All that is left
in my life now is despair.
Good morning!
Guaah! Usagi!
Ahh!
Yesterday, I, Uh...
Listen, don't worry about it!
Yes! You're right.
I shouldn't worry
so much!
After all, you're
always okay when you
get a bad grade on a
test, aren't you?
I should be
more like you!
Augh! He has no idea
what I went through!
Ah! I'm late!
Ahh!
[Usagi]
Luna, have you heard about
the radio show that reads
people's love letters?
[Luna]
You sure love gossip,
don't you?
[Usagi]
I think I'm going
to write one, too!
[Luna]
That's fine, but who
are you writing it to?
[Usagi]
Well, let me think...
Hmm... [snoring]
[Luna]
Oh boy, she's hopeless.
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon. "The
Mysterious Sleeping Sickness:
Protect the Girls in Love"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.