(Usagi)
Unforgivable!
(cont'd)
You know what's so
unforgivable? Desecrating
a lovely white wedding
(cont'd)
dress. The eternal dream
of every young girl.
(cont'd)
I will not let you
get away with this!
(Cont'd)
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
moon. I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
It may not look it,
but I'm actually
a superhero!
I use a special brooch
to transform and fight
evil!
You know me as the
Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius, Ami
Mizuno. Who's Sailor
Mercury!
And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic,
who's Sailor Mars.
Both of them seem
to have it a little
more together than I
do.
But, oh well!
Guess, I just gotta
do my best!
(Giggles)
"A Girl's Dream: Usagi
Becomes A Bride!"
That's how to measure
darts for a dress.
(Sigh)
Heh!
Sure, I'll have another
pork bun.
(Naru)
I wonder what's wrong
with Ms. Akiyama. She's
so distracted!
(Yawns)
You're telling me! That
home economics class
was so boring, I can't
even wake up now
that it's over!
(Yawns)
Ms. Akiyama used to
be really passionate
about sewing, too!
I just don't know
what could have
happened to her!
Well, I can
answer that!
Why are you always
popping up and scaring
us all the time?!
Uh-oh. I actually found
out the cause of Ms.
Akiyama's strange
behavior.
I believe that it is
strongly connected
to her engagement.
Her engagement!
(Umino)
Yes, Ms. Higure Akiyama
is thirty-four years
old and still unmarried.
(Cont'd)
But she's strongly
determined to change
that. Her greatest desire
(cont'd)
is to marry her beloved
in a beautiful ceremony
while wearing a wedding
(cont'd)
dress that she
sewed herself.
(Fiance)
Higure! I know that
I'm only a short and
uninteresting businessman
(cont'd)
with no status and
no savings to his name
whatsoever.
I can't even give you
the grand wedding
reception you deserve.
But still, would you
please do me the
honor of becoming my
wife?
(Gasp)
Awe...
Yes!
Aw-ahh!
Well, it's not an
ideal situation,
but as long as they
love each other.
Give me the ideal
or nothing at all!
(Usagi)
I believe in
impossibly high
standards!
As long as they're
handsome, go for it!
Take a chance with them!
I, for one, plan to
get married by the age
of twenty-five!
Ugh!
She wants a handsome
guy! I'm doomed!
(Haruna Sakurada)
Ms. Akiyama!
Huh?
Oh, Ms. Sakurada!
What's wrong?
You seem distracted.
Oh, wait! I bet that
you were just thinking
about your fiance,
weren't you?!
Oh, don't be silly!
Wow! What beautiful
silk!
Oh, of course! Now
I remember! You were
planning on making a
hand-made dress for your
wedding ceremony,
right?
Yes, but I can't seem
to find any silk
that I like.
I've already picked
out the design that I
like, though.
Well, don't give up,
no matter what happens!
Finish that wonderful
dress of yours soon,
so that you can have
an amazing ceremony!
After all, I'm counting
on finding my future
husband at your wedding
reception. You know
what I mean?!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Okay, thanks.
I'll do my best!
Sure thing! I'm gonna
do my best, too!
(Giggles)
The stars see all; the
stars know all. Vega
in the Lyra constellation,
its tears fill the heavens.
It floats alone, unable
to traverse the galaxy.
By the light of Vega,
the person who will shine
the brightest and will
gain the most energy
is, Higure Akiyama!
And now, she will become
my next victim!
(People talking
and congratulating)
Gasp!
(Gasps)
What a beautiful
bride! I'm so
jealous!
That really is the
dream of every young
girl in love! I hope
it's me someday!
(Emcee)
No, this way!
(cont'd)
That's good. Now,
hurry up!
(Usagi)
Hm? What's this?
A handmade wedding
dress contest?
And the grand prize
is a lavish, all-
expense-paid wedding
reception?!
Wow! A lavish wedding
reception! I can just
picture it! And my groom
would be...
Ahh-
(Giggles)
(Gasps)
Tuxedo Mask!
And Motoki, too!
(Giggling)
Ahh! I've never
been so happy!
(Laughing)
Ugh, but I'm hopeless
when it comes to sewing!
I'll never be able to
make a dress!
(Rei)
Hold on!
An all-expense-paid
wedding reception?!
But what if you don't
have anyone-
I mean, what if you
and your fiance haven't
decided on a date?!
Please, try to remain
calm. The prizewinner can
choose to have the
ceremony held at
any time they want!
(Gasps from crowd)
All right!
(Chuckles)
I'd better hurry
up then, and make
my move!
Hi, Rei.
Ah! Usagi!
Whatcha doing?
Oh, nothing!
Ha-ha-ha!
Why are you here?
Hey, wait! Hold
on a second. Your
mom is a housewife,
isn't she?!
Yeah, but what does
that have to do
with it?
(Chuckle)
Uh, Usagi...
Heh, what is it?
(Usagi)
Hey don't push!
What's gotten into
you, Rei?
(Gasps)
There having a hand-
made dress contest?!
(Ikuko Tsukino)
Oh! So you're Rei, huh?
Yes!
Oh, boy!
I never expected Usagi
to be friends with a
girl as lovely as you
are!
Thanks! I may go to a
different school than
she does, but the two
of us are still
really good friends!
We're what?! Come on,
she just followed me
home!
Hey! That's supposed
to be my cake!
Usagi!
Ignore her. Here, have
some. Go ahead! Eat up!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
(Luna)
Usagi, what do you
think Rei's up to?
How should I know?!
Wow! There's really
nothing better than a
homemade cake!
You are quite the
talented chef, Ms.
Tsukino!
Oh, well...
Faker! Anyone can
tell it's from the cake
shop by the station!
Ow!
That hurt!
I'm so jealous of Usagi!
A wonderful mother
like you must be great
at all kinds of things,
like sewing for
instance!
Huh?!
Can I tell you a little
secret? I've always
dreamed of learning how to
sew from a talented
woman like you!
We could start with
something like a
wedding dress, maybe!
Huh?!
You want to learn
sewing from me?
(Chuckles)
(Forced Laughing)
Thanks for having me.
You know, you could've
told me sooner that
your mother is a
a total loss when
it comes to sewing!
Hold up! You only
came over here to see
if you could use my mom
to help you win that
wedding dress
contest, didn't you?!
(Mmmh!)
Ah! Why you little
cheater!
Unbelievable!
You should be spending
your time on training
to fight the next
monster, not wasting
it on entering some
silly contest, Rei!
You too, Usag-!
Ugh! Where did that
girl go?!
What?! A wedding dress
contest?
(Usagi)
Yeah!
So, anyway, Rei told
me she was going to
enter it, too! Doesn't
that make you so angry!
Not really, I don't
plan on getting married
anytime soon.
What?!
Listen, that isn't
the point here! Wearing
a beautiful dress is
every girl's dream!
Anyway, you're really
good at home economics,
right? Can you just
teach me how to sew?
Well, sure, if you
really want me to.
Yay! There is no way
I'm going to lose
to Rei!
Uh!
First you're going
to have to learn the
basics, and only once
you have them down,
will we actually
sew.
Aw, come on, Ami!
(People Yelling
and Fighting)
Hey! I had it first!
No, I did!
Let it go!
Ms. Sakurada?
Oh.
(Gasp)
This silk!
(Nephrite)
Beautiful.
Huh?
(Gasps)
How, beautiful.
Flawless.
Uh-'scuse me?
(Nephrite)
What wonderful
fabric,
This would be the
perfect material to
use in making a wedding
dress.
Ahh. I can imagine
you walking by the
water under a sky
filled with stars.
Each of them twinkling
in delight as a sign
of their blessing.
Here..
Best wishes.
Ah!
(Dreamy Sigh)
Sailor Moon!
(Naru)
An all-expense-paid
wedding reception?!
Wow, I had no idea!
Yeah! And that is
exactly why I've got
to enter this contest!
You see?
Now I get it. I
thought it was weird
that you'd want to go
to Ms. Akiyama's house.
And what makes you
can suddenly learn how
to sew when you've
never been able to
stay awake through
one of her classes?
I have to learn!
I don't know what
else to do!
But you know, making
a wedding dress isn't
easy even for people who
know how to sew well.
And you'll probably
just give up before
you're half way through.
I'll be fine,
all right!
(Usagi)
Remember, a woman's
faith can split
mountains.
(Naru)
Who says that?!
Well, maybe I said
it wrong.
(Laughs)
What's she up to
now?
Huh?
(Usagi)
Who's he?
(Naru)
That guy looks
totally out of place
with a bouquet.
He's kinda goofy-
looking, huh?
Ha! Yeah, but we
shouldn't say stuff
like that!
Huh?
(Usagi)
That's Ms. Akiyama's
place!
(Naru)
You mean?!
That's Ms. Akiyama's
fiance?!
Uh.. Higure?
Is something wrong,
sweetheart?
Why aren't you
answering my phone
calls?
Are you not feeling
well or something?
Uh, Higure?
Agh!
Huh?
Higure, is that
you?
Uh, I, Uh...
(Higure)
What the hell is
this?!
Now listen! Don't you
come near me until the
Juban Community Center's
dress contest is over!
If you do, I'm calling
off the engagement!
(Higure)
Got it?!
(Shivering)
My dress! My dress!
I've got to get back to
making my wedding dress!
I need to finish it
fast!
Higure?
(Naru)
No way! That was
Ms. Akiyama?!
(Usagi)
She mentioned the
contest...
(Gasp)
She's entering!
She's gonna be
tough competition!
Oh, no!
Not good!
That's your concern?
That teacher. Something
is not right about her.
What? Ms. Akiyama
from home economics
class?!
I definitely sense the
presence of a monster.
And she was acting really
strange.
You know, she hasn't
been to school in a
while, either.
(Luna)
Oh? Well, we bett-
Ahh!!
(Grandpa Hino)
Hey, come back here
Rei!
(cont'd)
Just what are you
planning to do with the
only wedding kimono I
(cont'd)
have to rent out
to customers?!
Ahh!
Ah!
Sorry!
Hmph! Here I thought
you were running off
to elope with someone!
Wha-Wait a minute,
you're not-
Hey! You know me
better than that!
Do you really believe
I'd wear that to enter
the handmade wedding
dress contest?!
Well in any case...
(Grandpa cont'd)
I will not allow a sacred
wedding kimono to be used in
some sacrilegious contest!
What's her grandpa
angry about, anyway?
Listen, young lady,
why don't you have your
wedding ceremony right
here at the shrine?
It'll be a lot less
expensive than that
Juban Community Center
would be!
Well, uh, I've got
no one to marry!
Ah ha! I'm single
too! Why don't you
and I get married?!
Ow-uh-he-hoh!
I am the pretty cat
burglar, Usagi
the Kid.
Ahh! This is perfect!
(Usagi's Mother)
Usagi!
You're not thinking of
taking my favorite
curtains, and trying
to turn them into
something else
entirely!
Like a wedding dress?
I'm sorry! I want to
buy dress fabric, but
my allowance won't cover
it! This was the only
other choice!
Please! Aww!
Fine, under one
condition.
I'll stop giving you an
allowance for the next
three months to pay for
the new curtains we'll
have to buy.
Ugh! No, anything
but that!
But that aside, you
only have a couple of
days left. Can you actually
make a dress in time?
But, I really want
that lavish wedding
reception!
I just can't give
up!
(Crying)
(Laughter)
(Emcee)
Thank you all for
coming today to
participate!
(cont'd)
This is going to
be a fabulous event!
Fabulous!
(Chuckles)
What a great success!
I'm so jealous, I
can hardly take it!
Just let it go,
Usagi! You did the
very best you could.
Plus, I bet you did
one thing better than
everyone else.
Poking your fingers
with the sewing needle!
(Crying)
(Ami)
Rei, come on!
Stop fighting!
We have to see if
anything suspicious is
going on!
Usagi, I want you to
go undercover as a
participant in the
contest!
Aww! Don't be so
mean! You know I don't
have a dress!
But you have your
transformation pen!
Oh, I forgot about
that!
(Sighs)
(Usagi)
Moon Power!
Transform me into a
super beautiful bride!
(Usagi)
I did it!
(Giggles)
Don't you think I
look pretty?
Ha! I should be
able to win this
whole contest!
Jealous...
(Luna)
Usagi!
You didn't make that
wedding dress, so it'll
be cheating!
It's just for cover
anyways.
Should've known.
(Gasps)
Ladies and gentleman!
(cont'd)
The Juban Community
Center's Hand-made
Wedding dress contest
(cont'd)
Is about to begin!
(Crowd Excitement)
So have you found
your teacher, yet?
No, I haven't seen
her anywhere!
Thank you very much!
First of all!
Huh? What's going
on?!
Ms. Akiyama?!
Amazing!
(Emcee)
Hey! You can't
interrupt the show
like this!
Just shut up!
(Sighs)
Yes, of course!
Now I see it!
You truly are the
ideal bride!
Please, won't you
marry me?!
Silence! Do you
really think someone
as lowly as you is
worthy of me?!
The greatest men in
every nation around the
world should be bowing
down before me
and they will do so,
once word of my
unsurpassed beauty spreads
far and wide!
And not only the men,
but the women as well
will kneel before me!
(Scared)
Ahh!
(Sinister Laughing)
(Tired Sighs)
(Cont'd Laughing)
Usagi! Don't look
into her eyes!
Huh? Hey! What are
you doing under my
dress, you pervert!
Now is really not the
time for this!
Her energy has peaked!
Come forth!
My monster, widow!
(Usagi)
Ms. Akiyama!
So you've revealed
yourself, monster!
Ha-ha!
(Usagi)
Why are these monsters
always so creepy!
Who the hell are you?
(Rei and Ami)
Stop right there!
Huh?!
(Usagi Whining)
A wedding dress is the
symbol of every girl's
dream!
And we'll never forgive
anyone who defiles that
white wedding dress!
Hey! No fair showing
off without me!
You! You're gonna pay
for ruining my chance
to win that lavish, all-
expense-paid reception!
Prepare to feel a
girl's wrath!
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Make up!
I am the pretty guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
I am Sailor Mercury!
And I, am Sailor Mars!
In the name of the
moon!
(All)
We'll punish you!
We'll see about that,
you brats!
Ah!
(Gasp)
(Rei)
Idiot!
(Sinister Laugh)
I'm going to weave you a
beautiful burial outfit made
from your lifeless body!
No! No! No!
Please!
Bubble!
Spray!
What is this?!
Fire!
Soul!
You all right?!
Get a hold of
yourself!
Sorry, I just can't
stand spiders!
Curses! Where are
you?!
Ahh!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Ah!!
(Crowd waking up)
Wh-what's this?
Where am I?
What happened?
(Crowd congratulating)
(Haruna Sakurada)
Ms. Akiyama, you look
so pretty!
(Usagi)
I can't believe he waited
for her even after all those
horrible things she said!
(Rei)
They say looks aren't
everything, but...
(Usagi)
Yeah, well, I still
prefer handsome guys!
Very mature, Usagi!
Mmm!
Do you guys know the
tradition that says
whoever catches the
bouquet is supposed to
be the one that gets
married next?
(Gasps)
What? Really!
(Ms. Akiyama)
All right, ladies!
Catch!
(Gasps)
Hey! It's mine!
Get off!
Huh?
Awh!!
(Usagi)
Hey, Luna!
Am I beautiful?
(Luna)
Not this again!
What now?!
(Usagi)
I was asked if I
wanted to be a model!
(Luna)
Well, they say, with
enough flattery, even a
pig can fly.
(cont'd)
But you have more
important things to do!
(Usagi)
I know but I need a
break once in a while!
(Luna)
You never stop taking
breaks!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi's A Model: The
Flash Of The Monster
Camera,"
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.