You monster! How dare you
dress up in a tuxedo just
to toy with an innocent
girl's feelings! I'm
never, ever, EVER going
to forgive you for this!
You hear me?!!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
Moon I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino! It
may not look it, but
I'm actually a
superhero!
I use a special brooch to
transform and fight evil!
You know me as...
...the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice. I am Sailor
Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius, Ami
Mizuno, who's Sailor
Mercury...!
...And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic, who's
Sailor Mars. Both of them
seem to have it a little
more together than I
do...
But, oh well, guess I
just gotta do my best!
[giggling]
"Usagi's Joy: A Love
Letter From Tuxedo Mask"
The stars see all, the
stars know all!
Hear me Regulus, ruler of
the southern skies! Oh
vast constellation of Leo
the Lion!
Show me a weakness
something I can use to
eliminate those Sailor
Guardians forever.
[grunting]
Tuxedo Mask!
Moon Tiara Action!
Fire...
.... Soul!!
Till we meet again,
Sailor Guardians.
[swooning]
My hero...
Aha! So, she has a
weakness for Tuxedo Mask!
Then that's how I'll
crush you!
Hello, Nephrite. Queen
Beryl would like to have
a word with you.
Nephrite, I'm told that
you are having trouble
gathering human energy
for our great ruler.
Is this true?
The universe wasn't
built in a day, my queen.
You'll watch your tongue!
Question my orders again
or fail to take care of
those
Sailor Guardians and
you'll soon find yourself
right alongside Jadeite
in the Eternal Sleep!
[trembling]
A sentence worse
than death.
I am Nephrite, proud
member of the Dark
Kingdom's Four Kings
of Heaven! And I will
succeed in my mission!
In fact, I now know just
how to deal with Sailor
Moon.
Sounds a lot like the
story we used to hear
from Jadeite.
What's your plan?
Queen Beryl, I promise
you that this time,
Sailor Moon will be dealt
with and eliminated.
[chuckling]
Very well, then.
I'm going to destroy her
with her own love! Ha ha
ha ha ha ha!!
Huh?
[gasping]
Aaaghh! No way--no way!!
I don't believe it!
It's from Tuxedo Mask!
My heart yearns for
you. Please come meet
me at the MS mall in
Shinjuku tomorrow night.
Ahhh! Yes!
Well, that's certainly
nice and all, but why
would Tuxedo Mask send a
love letter to you?
Oh, come on, Luna,
isn't it obvious?
[giggling]
He's in love with me!
Okay, let's say for a
second that your
delusions are real. How
does he know you're
Sailor Moon?
It's amazing!
That's just how powerful
his love for me is! His
heart can see into mine and
right through all my secrets!
There's nothing but truth
between true loves.
Well, just because Tuxedo
Mask is always helping us
doesn't mean we should
trust him.
Maybe he's on our side
and maybe not.
[kissing noises]
I can't wait!
No way! You're all
lying! I don't
believe it!
But it's true, Usagi.
We all got letters from
Tuxedo Mask.
I got one too!
Same here!
Me too!
Who is this Tuxedo
Mask anyway?
No clue!
I really wish we knew
which guy it's from.
It would be so great if
it was from him.
[laughing]
Come on, give
it back.
Now class I've heard
about the love letter
prank and I want you
girls to remember that
distractions like that
are enemy number one when
it comes to learning,
understand?
[agreeing]
And since we don't know
what kind of person sent
them, I want everyone to
avoid going
out alone at night.
Especially to the MS mall
in Shinjuku.
Understood?
Yeah!
Good answer!
Why didn't I get a love
letter, mister mysterious
Tuxedo Mask?! What am I,
chopped liver?!
There's something very
suspicious about this
love letter business,
Ami. Don't you think so?
You're right, we should
probably go talk to Rei
and see what she thinks
about it.
Huh? A lover letter from
Tuxedo Mask? What's
that about? Aagh!!
Apparently he sent one
out to every girl in
town.
Think it's some kind of
advertising?
It could be, but who
knows what's really
going on.
Huh?
[sighing]
Hey, hi Usagi!
[sighing and groaning]
Huh?
What's up? You look
kinda bummed out.
Sigh!
Ahh, I bet I know what's
goin' on here. The other
girls got a mysterious
love letter, but you
didn't get one.
Doesn't that sound
about right Motoki?
Yeah, that's gotta sting
a little!
No, that's not right! I
got a letter too, you
jerk!
[gasping]
Oh, well then why were
sighing just now?
Because it's just so
mean!
All this time, Tuxedo
Mask's been cheating
behind my back and now
he's even sending love
letters to other girls!
[sobbing]
Oh no, Rei! I didn't
know you were sick!
I woke up this morning
with a fever and a sore
throat.
It stinks, but I don't
think I'm in any shape to
go out, even if it is for
Tuxedo Mask.
[coughing]
Sorry.
There's no need to
apologize, Rei. Here, let
me go get you some ice.
All is in place.
Sailor Moon's love for
Tuxedo Mask will force
her to show up here tonight.
And when she does, it
will be her end!
Mr. Sanjoin?
Hm?
Hello there!
Sorry... you probably
don't remember me. I'm
Naru Osaka.
Sure, I remember you.
Are you shopping?
Uh-huh.
This is going to
sound weird but can
I ask you something?
Sure.
Mr. Sanjoin, I was
wondering if you're
Tuxedo Mask.
Tuxedo-!?
Course not, why would you
ask that?
I know, it's kind of
a strange question, but
it would be nice if
you were Tuxedo Mask.
Does she suspect it was
me who wrote the letters?
Impossible! But why else
would she ask that?!
The real question
is: Could she be Sailor
Moon?!
Just forget I asked I'm
not usually this
nervous.
So Naru.
Y-Yes?
Has anybody told you
you're the cutest girl
in school?
[swooning]
I mean it, I felt drawn
to you since the first
time we met. Hope you can
make it tonight.
Tonight?! Wait a minute!
It has to be him!
Has anybody told you
you're the cutest girl
in school?
I mean it, I felt drawn
to you since the first
time we met.
[swooning]
I feel the same
way, too.
This makes no sense.
Why would Tuxedo Mask
write love letters to a
whole bunch of other
girls and not just to
me?! I don't
get it!
Well I guess the only way
to figure this out is to
go to the mall and ask
him myself!
The first rule of getting
ready for a date...
Wear a clean pair of
underwear!
And wear a clean
dress to go with it!
The second rule of
getting ready for a
date...
Is to wear just the right
amount of perfume!
And the third rule
for getting ready...
Is to brush your teeth
and get rid of stinky
breath!
And now for the finishing
touch!
Just exactly the right
shade of lipstick!
Then get ready for
magical things to happen!
[laughing]
Oh, who am I kidding!
Ooh but what if it did,
what if it totally did?!
Huh?
Is anybody here?
It's me, Naru--are you
here Tuxedo Mask? Or
should I call you Mr.
Sanjoin?
Here I am!
[swooning]
I'm glad you came.
I know that voice!
I was right all along!
It's you, Mr. Sanjoin.
You recognize my voice?
I'd know your voice
anywhere! And no mask or
hat can hide your beautiful
face or hair!
Are you genuinely that in
love with this Masato
Sanjoin?
Yes, ever since this
afternoon, all I could
think of was you. I am
madly in love with you,
Mr. Sanjoin.
Enough of this charade!
Cut the acting and reveal
yourself!
I know who you really
are--you're Sailor
Moon!!
Huh?!
Sailor Moon!
Hmm, I just realized...
I really should've let
Ami and Rei know where I
was going tonight.
Where in the world are
you Usagi?
Yeah funny you should
ask. I'm actually in
Shinjuku right now.
[gasping]
That little sneak!--More
like she decided to have
a date with Tuxedo Mask
without us!!
[coughing]
Uhh, what's wrong,
Mr. Sanjoin?
Spare me your lies!
Just transform already!
I don't get what
you're saying.
But, you have to be
Sailor Moon! Why else
would you come to meet
me?!
For love.
[grunting]
Look at the energy
she's giving off!
Mr. Sanjoin.
Naru!!
But why? Why would Tuxedo
Mask do this to her?
Hold on! That's a fake!
That guy isn't Tuxedo
Mask!
Hang in there,
Naru!
Moon Prism Power Make
Up!!
[grunting]
Not again!
My head!
So this one didn't turn
out to be Sailor Moon, but
the energy I gained from
her was amazing.
Get your hands off of
Naru!
Huh? Who's there?!
How dare you dress up
in a tuxedo to toy with
an innocent girl's
feelings!
So you're here!
I am the Pretty
Guardian.
Who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
Moon I'll punish you!
How were you able to
figure out I wasn't the
real Tuxedo Mask?
A girl can always
recognize her true love!
Sailor Moon Kick!
So you want to play
rough? Here, I'll give
you back your little
friend!
Naru!
[growling]
[grunting]
Wait a minute!--You're
Masato Sanjoin!
No, I am Nephrite, one of
the Dark Kingdom's Four
Kings of Heaven!
Nephrite, huh?!
I came to destroy you
once and for all, Sailor
Moon and that's just what
I intend to do!
[gasping]
Hear me now Regulus, the
brightest of the southern
skies!
Give me your strength!
Ahhhh!
Devour this girl now,
Leo!
Aaghh!!--Oh no not that!!
[panting]
Ah!
Who did that?!
Uh!
You really thought I'd
let you get away with
using my name on all
those phony love letters
so you could draw out
Sailor Moon?
Not a chance!
Ohhh! Nothing's
better than the
real deal!
Damn it, Tuxedo
Mask!
Hyah!
I'll handle these
guys! Now, get going!
Right! There's nothing
I won't do for the real
you!
You fools! She thinks you
can save her from me?!
Bring it!
Whoa, what am I doing
leaving him all alone!?
Moon Tiara... Action!
[roaring]
No way! Why's it not
working?
Sailor Moon! Get into the
elevator!
Okay!
[roaring]
[panting]
Ha ha ha ha! They fell
for it completely!
I should have known!
What's wrong?!
Yes, it was a trap. Now,
what do you suppose is
gonna happen when this
elevator reaches the top?
Just tell us already!
Since you insist... the
elevator cable is going
to snap!
And you'll be
pulverized after
plummeting to the
basement of this building!
Waaaahhhhhh!
I'm too young to be
pulverized!
[sniffling]
Well, as long
as we're alone...
We need to find
a way out.
What's wrong with me? I
should be terrified right
now, but all I can think
of is how happy I am
being alone with Tuxedo
Mask.
Sailor Moon, listen...
[cooing]
Now what are you doing?
We need to focus here.
Huh?--Oh, right!!
Take my hand!
We've reached the top
floor! Get ready to jump!
'Kay.
[grunting]
[chuckling]
[laughing]
At last!
[groaning]
Can't hang on!
Don't give up, Sailor
Moon! I'll get us outta
this! In the meantime
just think about
something else to get
your mind off of it!
Okay!
Um... I know! Tell me why
you always come to my
rescue!
I don't know why, but
something inside of me
tells me to.
I've got a foothold so
climb up and onto my
back, now Sailor Moon.
[grunting]
I know why you save me.
I think you're in love
with me but you just
aren't ready to tell
me yet.
Ah! Oh, no. Did I
say that out loud?! I
was only kidding.
Sorry but I was
wondering...
[grunting]
Just who are you under
that mask?
Wait, don't tell me!
You're Motoki aren't
you?! Ha! There I go
again saying dumb stuff!
Sailor Moon...
Yeah?
This may sound strange...
But I have the feeling
that there was some kind
of connection between us
somewhere in the past.
It's there in the corner
of my mind, but I can't
remember what it was.
[grunting]
Ahh! I shouldn't
have had that other
pork bun!
Just stay calm!
Oh! Okay talk about
something else, got any
less dangerous hobbies?
Oh!! Why am I such an
idiot? I can't think of
any normal questions,
'cause I'm not a
normal girl!
[wailing]
Uh!
Tuxedo Mask!
You know better than to
go out on a mission
without telling us about
it Sailor Moon!
Sorry about that!
[coughing]
That was too close for
comfort!
Thanks for the
rescue, you two!
This is unbelievable.
I'm stuck with a nasty
cold while you get to
sneak out and flirt with
Tuxedo Mask! It's just
no fair!
Huh?! Well it's not
exactly like that...
Not now Sailor Mars.
Are you taking her side?!
You were just as mad as
me before!
Yes, but right now the
most important thing is
for us to get Naru here
to a hospital.
I wish you girls would
get along better!
Farewell for now!
Tuxedo Mask!
Why does he
always disappear?
If there's anything I
can't stand it's a girl
fight.
Queen Beryl, as you may
recall Nephrite swore to
defeat Sailor Moon. Yet
he failed once again.
You must sentence him to
the Eternal Sleep.
[grunting]
Ordinarily I would agree
and his sentence would be
swift and without mercy.
But this amazing energy
he stole earns him a
reprieve.
But My Queen!
This discussion is over!
You Zoisite, should
remember your place and
your own mission to bring
me the Silver Crystal!
[gasping]
[chuckling]
It all makes sense now...
Everyone becomes obsessed
with someone or something
at least once in their
lives, and focuses all
their energy on it...
Still I never would have
expected that girl Naru
to produce such
incredible energy.
She has truly
fallen in love with the
Masato Sanjoin persona
I've crafted.
The poor, pathetic
fool.
[laughing]
Wow, just look how
beautiful this place is!
The blue sky, the
sparkling ocean!
Don't forget you're here
for training.
Oh, I know, I know, I
know!
But what am I supposed to
do with all these gorgeous
men on the beach?!
Ugh! Why is our
hotel so dilapidated?
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"The Summer, The Beach,
Youth And Ghosts!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.