Dear Dark Kingdom, I'm
writing you today to
inform you that I,
Sailor Moon, am officially
quitting the Sailor
Guardians and like to
join your group. Yours
truly, Sailor Moon.
Ha! Now I can finally
have my revenge on Sailor
Mars for the way she
bullies me all the time!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish
you!
We've got you now,
Sailor Moon!
You might as well
give up, Sailor Moon!
No way!
Oh, really?
Then we've got
no choice!
This is it,
stupid girl.
Sailor Moon!
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
Fire!
Soul!
Ahhh!
Whoops! Guess
I overdid it.
"Usagi Abandoned: The
Falling Out of the
Sailor Guardians."
(shocked gasp)
Hmmm...
That was another unusual
burst of energy.
In these past few days,
there have been several
energy reactions similar
to that one.
I suspect it might have
something to do with
the Silver Crystal.
How so?
We should have an
answer shortly.
You there,
Oniwabandana?
Sir!
Oniwabandana, at
your service!
So have you figured out
what's the cause of the
unusual energy readings.
Ban Ban!
See for yourself!
What's this?
Ban Ban!
Oh!
Huh!
The source of that
unusual energy turned
out to be the Sailor
Guardians.
It's happening because
Sailor Moon had a
falling out with the
other Guardians and
they're fighting.
Ban Ban.
Is this true?
Sailor Moon and the
Guardians are at
odds with each other?
That's peculiar.
This could be a
trap...
Kunzite, what do
you make of this?
I'd like some
additional proof.
I agree.
Go back there
and watch them!
As you wish!
Ban ban.
Ban ban...
Who's there?!
(startled gasp)
Ahh! It's a monster!
I'll be taking
these jewels!
Ban ban!
Ahhh!
(terrified gasps)
Mom!
Ban ban!
Ahhhh!
Stop right there!
Sailor Moon!
Huh?!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Ban ban...
In the name of
the moon...
Move it!
Agh!
Huh?!
Hey! Why'd you
do that?!
Stop acting like
you're the only
cool one here!
Well, your kick
kinda flattened my
pretty face!
Looks like a big
improvement to me.
What was that?!
Look, no one
invited you!
You should butt out!
(furious grunt)
I'm the one who heard
about this crime first
anyway, so you can
take a seat!
Don't try stealing
our thunder, okay?
And don't talk about
me like I'm a thief!
Just shut up,
alright?!
You're standing
in my way!
You got in my
way first!
What's going on
here anyway?
(girls fighting)
I've had enough
of you!
Huh?!
Hey!
Oh no! Paparazzi!
Sailor Guardians fighting
each other at the scene
of a crime! This is going
to be a huge scoop!
Who are you?!
I'm a writer for
the Weekly Dokkiri!
Stop!
Cut it out now!
The Weekly Dokkiri?!
That's a photo magazine
that does sleazy stories
that aren't even true.
They print anything,
right?!
Pretty much! So what's
the cause of this fight
between you guys?
Huh?
Hold on! We get along!
There's no way that the
Pretty Guardians of
Justice would really
fight with each other.
We're a happy team of
heroes!
(nervous laugh)
Eh... Right?
Hmph!
I knew it!
Something's wrong!
Let me guess, you're
tired of dealing with
Sailor Moon messing up
all the time. Or is
there some boy
trouble going on?
This is stupid.
I'm going home.
Yeah, let's go!
Hey, wait! C'mon
you can tell me!
That sure was a
waste of my time.
What was that
all about?
Uh, hello?
Huh?
Oh, that's right!
Where'd that monster
go anyway?!
She got away while
you were busy fighting.
(sad sigh)
So, uh...
Yeah?
So could you
help me out?
Oh, wow! Sorry
about that!
Of course!
(nervous laughter)
And then the monster
was able to get away.
It was crazy.
Really?
But you know what the
weirdest part was?
Uh...what?
It seemed like Sailor
Moon was having an
argument with the
other Sailor Guardians.
(nervous laughter)
No way!
I don't know about the
other Guardians, but
Sailor Moon is cute,
kind and sweet. She's
not the type who
would fight or argue.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm...
Not her!
Say!
Hey, it's you!
Tell me more about
what you were just
talking about!
Oh no!
Oh, I should probably
introduce myself to
you, huh?
I'm Nana Asahina,
freelance writer.
Pleased to meet you!
Ohh...
Now then, you two seem
pretty close to Sailor
Moon. So what's the
deal with her?!
Huh?
I guess were close.
(nervous laugh)
Ah! So you said Sailor
Moon wouldn't fight or
argue? What exactly
makes you say that?
Uhh, Naru!
I...
One question! My sources
say Sailor Moon's saved
you lots of times, true?
Uhh, Usagi?
You were there last
night so you must've
talked with Sailor
Moon. Was she saying
anything bad about
the other Guardians?
Uh, we're kinda in
a rush here. Gotta go!
Well...
Hey, Usagi! Wait
up for me!
Just give me a call
when you can, okay?
There's someone who
doesn't know when
to quit!
Hmm...
(kicking grunt)
Hah!
What's the square
root of two?!
Take that!
Ow! Hey! That hurt
Mars! You kicked me
for real!
Yeah, because that's
kind of the whole point!
We're not playing games
here!
Now wait, hold it. I
felt like there was real
hate in that kick, Mars.
Huh?
Oh yeah? I know
what my butt felt.
Hold on! Don't play the
blame game! This whole
plan of us having a big
falling out with you was
your idea to begin with!
So don't go acting like
a whiny wimp! Okay?
I am not being a wimp!
It's absolutely up to
us. We must rescue Tuxedo
Mask from the evil clutches
of the Dark Kingdom!
That's exactly why we've
gotta make it look to
whoever's watching, that
we're really fighting,
Sailor Moon!
But you kicked my butt
so hard now there's a
crack in it.
That's enough!
Listen up! Unless it
really looks like we
mean it, they're sure
not gonna invite their
enemy, Sailor Moon,
to their hideout.
Got it?!
I know, that's
the plan...
Mars is right,
this plan of yours
is really dangerous,
Sailor Moon.
So you've gotta do
some serious acting to
make them buy this!
All right! I get
it already!
(worried sigh)
Hey Artemis, did you
happen to find out
anything about that
reporter who showed
up yesterday at
the jewelry store?
Yeah, there's something
very fishy about her.
Huh?
I knew it!
Look! She already
wrote the story!
Oh no! I look so
stupid in that
photo!
That's how you
always look, Usagi.
What did you say?!
Cut it out you two.
That girl came from
out of nowhere, and
she's already a very
successful reporter!
She's had big scoops
on every political and
entertainment story
out there. It's like
she already knows
where to go before
it even happens!
Could it be that
she's been turned
into a monster?
That's what I think.
All right!
The fact that a monster
is contacting us is good!
Oh yeah! That means this
great plan of mine must
be working!
It could be a
coincidence...
Ugh! You think so?
Well, then let's
get this show
on the road.
Usagi, your plan's
really risky, you
sure you wanna go
through with it?
Huh? Sure!
Why not?
Oh, it'll be fine!
I mean, why worry?
You know we've got
your back.
Do you want me to
go instead of you?
Why are you asking?
Huh?
I go and get myself beat
up training for this and
now you decide to just
take over as the leader?
Huh?!
Aren't you over
thinking this a
bit, Usagi?
Well if Rei wasn't
always so hard on me,
this'd be a lot easier.
Then just stop
messing up all
the time!
What was that?!
Self-fulfilling
prophecy...
(annoyed sighs)
It should be right
around here somewhere...
Oh! This is it!
Whoa!
What a sweet-looking
apartment building!
I sure I wish I lived
in such a nice place!
This is no time for
you to be admiring
her, Usagi! She
could be a monster!
Oh yeah! You're right!
(chuckle)
(good luck grunt)
(nervous laugh)
Well hello!
Uh, Sailor Moon dropped
by and she asked me to
give you this letter.
This is from
Sailor Moon?
(nervous gulp)
I have decided I don't
want to be the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice
anymore! I'm so sick
and tired of working
with those Sailor
Guardians.
I have a shocking
confession I want to
share with you, so meet
me at Juban Cemetery
tonight at eleven
p.m.
Wow! Thanks for the
letter, but why'd she
have you deliver it?
Uh, I dunno!
People have always
told me that I have a
reliable face for
delivering letters!
(nervous laugh)
What kind of
answer is that?
Well thanks to you,
I've got another great
story to report!
I'm glad I could
help you out!
(obnoxious laugh)
Hmm...
Sailor Moon!
Oniwabandana,
are you there?
Ban ban.
So how are things
proceeding?
(chuckle)
I see...
Sailor Moon's had a
change of heart and
she's definitely broken
away from the Guardians.
Ban ban.
Then I think it's
time I pay her a
little visit.
(evil chuckle)
It's time...
Thanks for your
letter.
(startled gasp)
Oh, you startled me!
Is it really true that
you want to leave the
other Sailor Guardians
forever?
That's right! I
don't even want to
ever see them again!
Hmm...
Really?
Yes, really.
You're sure
about that?
I'm definitely sure!
I'm done with them!
Good. In that
case.
Huh?!
Ban ban ban ban ban
ban ban ban ban ban
ban ban ban! Ban!
A monster!
Master Kunzite!
Huh?!
Kunzite!
Meeting you wasn't
part of what I agreed
to! I'm here to get
interviewed!
Ban ban! That
interview is off!
Wait?! Really?!
So I heard that you've
broken up with the
other guardians.
You know, if you join
us, you can see Endymion
any time that you like.
Stop being so ridiculous!
I'm the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice and I don't
plan on stopping!
Well, that's too bad.
Right now, Endymion
can't even move.
What?! What's
wrong with him?!
Hm! Who knows? One
thing's for sure,
seeing you would
help him.
(evil chuckle)
Perhaps asking you to
join our side isn't
realistic. But I'm sure
you'd like to pay
Endymion a visit,
wouldn't you?
You'll take me to him?
Of course I will,
but on one condition.
What is it?
Hand over the
Silver Crystal.
(shocked gasp)
If you pass up this
chance you'll never
see Endymion alive
again.
Tuxedo Mask must be
very sick. What
should I do?
What's you answer?
Ban ban.
Uh, umm...
Give it to us.
All right! I will!
But first, I want to
make sure Tuxedo Mask
is okay!
All right, it looks
like he fell for it.
Master Kunzite...
Hm?
Damn it. So this
really was a trap.
All right, then.
I'm ready, so why don't
we get going. If I never
see Sailor Mars and those
others again, that'll
be too soon!
Hmph. I like your
hate filled resolve.
(struggling grunts)
(shocked gasp)
Is that?
That's the entry
way to the Dark
Kingdom.
Huh?!
(scared whining)
That's sure one
creepy entrance.
Having second
thoughts?
I'm going, okay?! Man,
you are so mean, you're
just like Sailor Mars.
There she goes insulting
me! I'll show her who's
mean!
Now, now...
Hold on, Tuxedo
Mask. I'm coming
for you!
Ba-ban!
Hm?!
(shocked gasp)
Now, you will hand
over the Silver
Crystal. Ban ban.
No! I won't do it
until after I see
Tuxedo Mask.
Oh no, it's way
too late for that.
I guess you'll
die right here!
I'll take that Silver
Crystal from you after
you're dead. Ban ban.
No you won't, the
Silver Crystal isn't
even here!
What?!
She's in real trouble!
Let's save her!
Wait!
If we rescue her now,
this whole plan will
have been a complete
waste of time!
You're a fool!
Once you're gone,
there won't be anyone
left who can use the
Silver Crystal. And now
Sailor Moon, you've
dug your own grave.
Damn it!
Hold on! Just wait!
(evil chuckling)
Wait, now I get it!
They're using me as
bait to see if Sailor
Mars and the others
will come to
my rescue.
Please girls, don't
give in! Don't try
to save me!
(angry grunt)
Let's go!
Right!
Hmph!
No, not yet!
But she really
need our help
right now!
Move!
(shocked gasp)
So Mars, turns out
you really do hate
Sailor Moon, don't you?
Jupiter...
Wait, isn't that?!
I wouldn't hold on to
something this important
for someone that I
didn't care about!
You see? Mars
feels the same!
Sorry...
(painful scream)
(evil laugh)
Die, Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon, no!
(struggling grunt)
Please! Don't
come out!
(struggling grunts)
I've had enough!
Oh, so now they go!
Get away from her!
Ban ban?!
Hnnh!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
We're done
playing games!
Let her go!
No! Why'd you come?!
Fools! You think I
didn't see through this
stupid scheme of yours
a long time ago?!
Huh?
I-I don't care! Just
let Sailor Moon go,
you monster!
Raging Fire!
Soul!
Ahhh!
Supreme!
Crescent!
Thunder!
Beam!
(shocked gasps)
Next time you want to
trick me, you might try
practicing your acting
a bit more!
Ban ban!
(gasp)
Time for you to die!
(attacking grunt)
(attacking yell)
Sailor Moon! Catch!
It's over!
Ahhh!
You're done!
So give up!
Not quite yet!
Ban ban! Ban ban!
Ahhhh!
We will turn you
into mincemeat!
Ban ban!
No you won't!
Bubble!
Spray!
Huh? What is this?
I can't believe you saw
through this plan! After
all, I stayed up all night
coming up with it! I wanted
my plan to blossom like
a beautiful flower, not
make me look like a
blooming idiot!
Seriously?
Anyway!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
We'll see about that!
Zip it! Fire!
Soul!
Hot! Hot! Ow! Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Ow!
Hot! Hot! Ow! Ow!
Time to finish this!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
(painful grunts)
Refresh!
Hey, we did it!
Mm-hmm! Wait! Why'd all of
you have to come running
out?! I could've handled
this whole thing on my own!
Well, because you were
crying like a baby!
Just when was I
crying like a baby?!
Today at eleven thirty-
three PM and twenty
three seconds!
(angry growl)
You can't even be
nice when you are
trying to save my
life!
They never quit.
Yeah, but I wish
they would.
Hey!
So you two, there's a
rumor that the Sailor
Guardians are splitting
up, is there any truth
to that? Huh?!
Oh, c'mon! Enough!
There's nothing that
burns as hot as forbidden
love. No matter what stands
between them, their hearts
will always be as one.
Endymion, I remember
everything. The day of
that passionate kiss.
And our final moments
as we shared our
last breath.
To those of you thinking
this is just going to be
another silly episode,
you're in for a shock!
No kidding!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi's Awakening: A
Message from the Distant
Past."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.