Oh please, God!
Please! Can you help
mend a sweet young
girl's broken heart?
Zoisite! You committed
evil on sacred ground!
You're not gonna get
away with it!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
God. I'll punish you!
Hey! I'm Usagi
Tsukino!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice, I
am Sailor Moon!
And now a fourth
Sailor Guardian has
appeared! She has a
heart of gold and is
super strong!
She's Makoto Kino,
also known as
Sailor Jupiter!
When the four Pretty
Guardians get together,
nothing can stop us!
(giggles)
Restore Naru's Smile:
Usagi's Friendship
Please...
Hurry and find the
Silver Crystal.
I don't understand!
What is the
Silver Crystal?
And who are you?!
The Silver Crystal...
Find the Silver
Crystal and all
will become clear.
Find the Silver
Crystal and all
will become clear.
That dream again...
Who is that princess?
Am I Tuxedo Mask?
Silver Crystal...
If I find it, maybe
my questions will
be answered.
As of now, we have
obtained one of the
Rainbow Crystals.
So Zoisite, what is
your next move?
Well, The Dark Crystal
has just detected
another of the
Rainbow Crystals.
Zoi!
The next Rainbow
Crystal is inside
this man.
Good. Now
retrieve it.
Naru didn't come to
school again today.
Nephrite, we're
safe now...
I'm sorry...
Huh?
Don't think we'll
be having chocolate
parfait together.
(upset gasp)
Please stay!
No! You can't go!
You promised that
we would have a
chocolate parfait
together! You can't
just break a promise!
You can't!
(sobbing)
Nephrite!
Naru...
Hm? So you're going
to go visit Naru's
house?
Yep. I mean she
hasn't shown up at
school in well over
a week now. I guess
she really hasn't
gotten over
everything yet.
Huh?
You mean it's
something more
serious than
a cold?
Are you kidding
me? How can anyone
possibly be so dense.
Huh?
Nothing... Just
make sure to cheer
Naru up once we get
to her place, okay?
Whatever you say
Usagi! I am ready
and willing! You can
totally count on me!
I know it's rude to
just show up, but we
were wondering, you
know, how you're doing?
Yeah, I mean all this
time, I just assumed
you were gone because
of a really bad cold
or something...
Or did somebody just
break your heart?
Don't go there!
Hey! What did you
have to go and
do that for?
Think of another
subject to talk
about!
Huh?! Uhh... Did you
wanna go get some
chocolate parfaits
or something?
I cannot
believe you!
Usagi...
Huh?
Let's get out
of here...
(gasp)
Why don't we all
go out and get
something good
to eat!
You mean it?
(silly giggle)
A power that's
capable of
destroying the
planet?!
Yes. If the Silver
Crystal falls into
the wrong hands, it
could mean the end
of all life as
we know it!
Wow, now that's
a scary thought.
So, where exactly is
this Silver Crystal?
Well we're not really
sure where it is but...
We do know that
there are fragments
of it, called
Rainbow Crystals.
Rainbow Crystals?
Yes. The Rainbow
Crystals are pieces
of the Silver Crystal.
This all happened a
long, long time ago.
A group known as the
Seven Great Monsters
used to serve the
Dark Kingdom.
Someone was able to
seal these evil
monsters in the
fragments of the
Legendary Silver
Crystal.
Once they were inside
the Rainbow Crystals,
the evil monsters
became good and
descended down
here to the Earth.
Here, they were
reborn as humans
with the Crystals
deep inside of them.
And lived their
lives in peace.
But Zoisite is
trying to extract the
Rainbow Crystals from
those seven people.
If he obtains all
seven of the Rainbow
Crystals, not only
will he have awoken
these fearsome
monsters, but he
will have the Silver
Crystal in his grasp.
Thus our enemy will
have the power to
destroy our world.
Hmph!
Well as long as you
got me around, there's
no way that this villains
plan is gonna succeed!
Dang it! That was
just what I was
gonna say!
Luna, how do we
identify people who
have Rainbow Crystals
inside of them?
The Moon Stick I
gave Usagi reacts
to their presence.
Huh?!
If that's the case,
I'm totally against
leaving the Moon
Stick with Usagi.
Why?
It's useless in her
hands. She'll probably
try to use it as a
hammer or something.
Oh, that's
ridiculous!
Actually, she
might do something
like that...
Hey! I have faith
that Usagi can
handle it!
I know that Usagi is
unreliable and only
has the faintest
sense of duty.
But that's exactly why
I want her to be the
leader, so she can
gain some confidence.
Gain some
confidence?
Yes. It's my belief
that if she is given
responsibilities, she
will rise to
the challenge!
I don't think
that'll ever
happen.
Come on! Try and
have some faith
in her!
Please, accept
Usagi as your
leader!
Say what you will,
I'm still opposed!
I guess...
She deserves
a chance.
Ami...
(painful groan)
But, maybe we should
see how she does
before committing.
Yep.
Aww, I wish you
guys would believe
in her a little more.
To be fair...
I haven't known
her long enough
to decide.
That's it! If you
get to know Usagi
better, I know
you'll want to
give her a
chance, Mako!
Hey there!
Uh, hey Usagi!
We're in the middle
of an important
meeting, here. Do
you think you could
come by for
a bit?
Oh, sorry!
You actually caught
me on my way to
Chinatown with some
friends. The three
of us are going to
have the yummiest
meal ever together!
You see? She has
zero responsibility!
Uh... What's
the matter?
How come you two
are just standing
over here like this?
You do know that
Chinatown's right
over there.
And you brought lots
of money with you,
right Usagi?
There are so
many graves in
this cemetery.
But there's no
grave for Nephrite.
Naru...
Yes! Peking duck
sounds excellent!
They say there's
nothing as tasty
as Peking duck!
Oh, I'm so happy!
I've dreamed of
eating Peking duck
since I was
a child!
Oh? Maybe you'd like
me to cook you like
a Peking duck?!
I just want
to eat it...
Huh? Where'd
Naru go?
Hm?
Uh! N-Naru!
Pastor!
Hm?
I don't know
what to do!
Please sir, I
really need you
to tell me.
Someone has died.
Someone dear to me.
He was living with so
much pain in his heart.
And I- I just couldn't
save him from it.
Your feelings for
him are admirable.
I am certain that
his soul's at peace.
But...
But now that he's
gone forever, I'm
left with nothing!
I don't think
that's true.
Even now, you are
surrounded with love.
All you need to do
is turn around and
love will be there
for you.
Turn around?
Huh?!
Uh, who are you?!
What do we
have here?
(gasp)
You again?!
You're the guy
who attacked us!
What a coincidence...
...running into
you here.
Sailor Moon!
Naru!
Where on earth
could she have run
off to? Huh?
What is that?
Oh no! The stick's
picking up a signal!
Luna! What're you
doing here?
Never mind that!
Just take the stick
our of your bag,
quickly!
Right! No need
to yell at me!
That means the Stick
has just located one
of the seven Rainbow
Crystals!
Seven Rainbow
Crystals?
I'll explain
everything later!
There's a chance a
monster might appear
at the signal's source!
What?!
Call Mako on the
communicator!
Wait, you mean
Mako's in the
area too?!
The signal is coming
from the cemetery?
Got it!
I'll be right
there!
The signal is
getting stronger!
Hurry!
And just who
are you?
Wouldn't you rather
know more about
yourself than about
a stranger?
I'm just a
simple pastor.
(amused chuckle)
Is that what
you think?
Why don't we let
this Dark Crystal
reveal to the world
who you really are?
That crystal
belonged to
Nephrite!
Stop!
Let go!
Stop using that
for evil!
Oh no, it's
Naru!
You should wait
until Mako gets
here!
How do you expect
me to wait? Naru's
in danger!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
This violence
must stop!
How compassionate.
You really should
worry about yourself.
Hold it right
there!
Who's there?!
Sailor Moon!
Trying to commit evil
on sacred ground?
You won't get away
with it!
(amazed gasp)
In the name of
the Moon, I'll
punish you!
Heh! Well, look
who's here...
It's too late!
I'll be taking the
Rainbow Crystal!
Zoi!
Ahh!
(gasp)
Oh no!
That's it!
It's mine. Come
forth, Rainbow
Crystal!
Ahh!!
Leave him alone!
The Crystal's
getting away!
Pastor!
Where did it
go? Where's the
Crystal?
Pastor, you're
safe...
Wrong...
I am no pastor...
I have been reborn!
My name is Boxii!
No way...
(chuckles)
I hear the roaring
of the crowd as the
fans cheer me on!
(crowd cheering)
I'm the champion!
Wow!
Boxii, be a good
sport and knock out
Sailor Moon!
Hold on! I don't
know anything about
boxing!
Great! Let's fight
and see who's the
real champion!
Ehh, I told you
I don't box!
Come on!
No way!
I'm a champion!
Lovely punch!
Ahh!!
Sailor Moon!
Aww, come on,
hurry up Mako!
I, am the king
of kings.
Stop it!
Boxii, I'm begging
you! Please turn
back into the kind
pastor!
I've heard enough
of your yapping!
Naru!
Ahh!!
Umino!
I'm a champion!
Lovely punch!
Look out,
Sailor Moon!
(gasp)
(shocked gasp)
Thank you,
Tuxedo Mask!
Huh?!
Boxers are gentlemen!
They never hit beautiful
young ladies!
They embrace them
with tenderness!
Boxii! Knock out
that pathetic
nuisance, this
instance!
All right!
C'mon!
Lovely punch!
Ahh!!
(angry growl)
I'm a champion!
Triple Punch!
Child's play!
What's this?
Mako! Transform!
Got it!
Jupiter Power
Make up!
Sailor Jupiter!
Oh? A new
challenger!
(angry growl)
Jupiter, my
guardian planet!
Bring forth a storm!
Summon the clouds!
And bring down
your thunder!
Supreme
Thunder!
Ahh!
Do it!
Sailor Moon!
Right!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
(struggling grunts)
Refresh!
Do you believe in
God? I believe in
Him. Go forth, and
love your fellow man!
(laughter)
The Crystal!
I'll be taking the
Rainbow Crystal!
Farewell!
I promise I will
take it back from
you someday!
Sailor Moon! Go
get that Rainbow
Crystal back!
Tuxedo Mask
saved me...
(nervous laughter)
At last, I finally
understand who I
really am.
I have been Tuxedo
Mask all along.
There...
Thank you
very much!
Naru, but
that's...
Yeah, but it's fine.
Umino did get hurt
trying to save me
back there.
(nervous giggle)
Yeah...
Usagi...
I'm sorry that I
made you worry. I'll
be back at school
tomorrow.
Sounds good!
I'm sorry, Mako.
I was hoping you'd
see Usagi's good
side, but it looks
like it was
nothing but a
waste of your
time.
Well, I'll admit
that she does seem
to care a lot about
her friends.
That's true!
That music...
It's nice.
Where's it
from?
Oh...
You know...
Hey Luna, it looks
like Ami might have
a boyfriend!
Maybe so, but she's
still working hard
on her academics.
Compared to her
Usagi, you're just
so...
What are you implying,
Luna? I'm working very
hard to find romance!
It's the only thing
you're working on!
Next time on Sailor
Moon, "Crushing on Ami:
The Boy Who Can See
the Future"
The moonlight is
a messenger of love.