[Sailor Moon]
There's no way that I'd let
anyone get away with wasting
a girl's precious time!
I bet even the cuckoo in
a cuckoo clock is angry!
I am Sailor Moon, and
in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
[Usagi]
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
...and some people might
say I'm a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange cat
named Luna gave me a special
brooch that transformed me into
a guardian in a sailor uniform.
And told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggle]
Usagi's Disaster:
Beware of the
Clock of Confusion
[Queen Beryl]
What? You're telling me that a
second guardian has appeared?!
[Jadeite]
Yes, my queen.
I see.
Well, then. That's all the
more reason that you must
gather energy quickly for
our great ruler!
Of course, Queen Beryl, and I
already have an ingenious plan
in mind to do exactly that.
Oh?
Human energy can be
amplified by feelings
of anxiety.
For example, it increases
in situations when they
are pressed for time.
Therefore, by making it seem
th
at they're rushed and are
running out of time,
we can magnify their energy and
collect it more efficiently.
I like it!
Make it so at once.
Right!
Wow! There are so
many people here!
Is this really your
first time at a place
like this, Ami?
Yes, although I have
read about them.
That's sad! There's
more to life than
studying for exams!
Oh. Sorry.
Don't be sorry!
There's no need
to apologize!
Okay!
Today, we're gonna make up
for what you've missed out on!
We'll window shop until we drop!
Uh, okay!
Ta-da! [chuckle]
[chuckle]
Let's go
there next!
Okay!
Look, look, Ami!
[both giggling]
This one
looks good!
And I like
this one!
[both]
Yeah, right, like
we'd ever wear these!
Hmmm!
Waak! Waak! Waak!
[Usagi]
Whoaa!
This is so fun!
[giggling]
You find
anything
interesting?
Yeah, a whole
lot of stuff!
What kind of stuff do
you read for fun, Ami?
I'll show you
if you show me.
Uagh! there's
no pictures!
It's all pictures!
[Usagi]
Whew.
I'm getting tired!
[Ami]
Yeah!
Hey look, that
place is packed!
Sure is.
[Usagi]
Oh! It's a grand
opening sale!
[Ami]
Clocks and watches, huh?
Everything's fifty to
seventy percent off?!
Wow, that's a great deal!
We really should go and
check it out!
Well, I don't need a watch.
I got one from my mom
as a present.
What?! Where's your
adventurous spirit!
Shopping isn't just
about buying.
It's about having fun!
Welcome to
our store.
Please, feel free
to look around.
[Usagi]
Whoa! Look at those prices!
Are watches usually
this inexpensive?
No! They're having a special.
It's unbelievable!
Look at this weird one!
[giggle] That's so cute!
Sure is!
[Usagi]
No way! This one
looks just like Luna!
I think I might
have to buy it!
Maybe it will help me
get to school on time!
Ah, the cat clock.
Good eye. It's quite a bargain.
Yeah, it sure is!
Your prices
are so low!
Oop!
Ouch! They're practically
giving these clocks away and
I still can't afford one.
But if I'm late to class
again, I'm gonna set a
new school record!
Usagi, I can come by your house
in the morning to make sure
that you wake up on time.
Please don't cry.
Thanks, Ami!
You're the best!
I love you!
[Usagi]
I'm home!
[hammering]
Welcome back!
You're in for a treat!
I bought you something
really nice today!
Yeah?!
I'm so excited!
What?
I went shopping today with
Umino's and Naru's mothers,
and I picked this up. Here!
It's from that clock store!
Wow, you were there, too?
Yeah, they were
having a sale!
Umino's mom bought
seven clocks!
I want to go back
and get more myself!
Oh! Awesome!
Isn't it cute?
You're always
oversleeping, so,
Maybe this'll be able to get
you out of bed in the morning.
Thank you mom!
Luna's going to be so excited!
It looks just like her!
Oh please. That clock
doesn't resemble me one bit!
Come on, I'm much better
looking than that thing!
Okay! If you say so!
I just hope it keeps me
from oversleeping again!
I don't like the vibe
of that clock at all.
It's got a sinister
feel to me.
Okay, great! Good night!
Come on, Usagi!
Don't do that!
Unh! Do I really look as
sinister as that clock does?!
Huh?
Huh??
This cannot be good.
Coming!
Oh! Ami!
Good morning.
Is Usagi
still asleep?
No, she's
long gone!
Already?! But it's only
seven o'clock in the morning!
I know; she got a late start.
Her brother Shingo
was already on his
way before six!
Listen, you'd better hurry up,
or you'll be late, too!
Ahhh! I'm gonna be late!
See you later!
Have a nice day, honey!
Well, no time to waste!
Gotta start cleaning,
washing and doing laundry--
Oh, and then it'll be
time to get supper ready!
Why's everyone so late?!
[grumble]
That's it! I can't
just wait all day!
I'm gonna go call everyone!
Yeah, really! I can't just
sit around here, waiting!
Okay that's it, I'm gonna go
run laps around the school!
That's enough!
We'll have
self-study today!
It's eight o'clock, and so many
people are still not here!
I can't wait any longer!
I have four dates lined up for
today. I can't keep hanging
around here with you slowpokes.
I've got to go home and
get ready for all of them!
Class dismissed!
Then I'm going home, too!
There's nothing for me to
do now that I've finished
my entire lunch!
Yeah, good idea!
You know the old saying:
"Life is short, so grab the
first guy with glasses and a
blue school uniform you see!"
No one ever said
that but you!
Anyway, we can't waste
any more precious time
waiting around here!
Right! Let's go home!
Why are all these stores
opening up so early?
[Luna]
Ami!
Huh?
Thank goodness
I found you!
Of all the days for Usagi
to leave early, she may
have picked the worst one!
What's the matter?
What's the big
rush about?
This clock. Something's off
about it. You think you could
take a look at it for me?
Hm. All right, then.
Why don't we take a
quick look inside it?
Oh, hold on.
What's this thing?
In simple terms,
that is a supercomputer.
A very compact one.
It comes in handy
for calculations
or analyzing data.
Really?! I actually
get to keep this?!
Yeah. I was gonna give
it to Usagi, but I'm
not sure she'd get it.
I believe you'll be
able to make better
use of it, Ami.
Wow, thanks, Luna!
Now check that clock.
Right! Sure thing!
Ah!
[Luna]
You okay?!
[Ami]
What was that?!
Ami, look
inside here!
[Ami]
It's empty!
I knew it! This isn't
an ordinary clock!
I'll bet everyone who's been
acting so strangely just bought
a clock from that new store!
Sailor Moon!
Oh, no! I'm hurt!
I've gotta get to the
hospital right away!
Oh, no, I'm going to
miss my plane now!
That means I'll have
to run all the way
to Paris instead!
[Jadeite]
[chuckle] Yes, keep
rushing, humans.
Rush right to your deaths! And
the faster you scurry around,
the greater amounts of energy
we can extract from you!
If I'm able to gather up
all of this nervous energy,
I'm certain that our great ruler
will be most pleased.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No matter how far away the
humans get from this clock,
it will continue to harvest
all of their frenetic energy.
You really do
have quite a way
with time, Ramua!
Your magic has
undermined the humans
and their sense of time!
You have done an
excellent job with this.
What kind words.
I thank you, Master.
I'll leave the rest to you.
But be warned that this
disturbance may bring
those two guardians.
You would be wise
to use caution.
Yes, sir.
I'll handle it.
[traffic, honking]
Too slow! Too slow!
We're going too slow!
Hey! Why is
this bus going
so slowly?!
Just quiet down!
I'm as impatient as
you are to get going!
Well, then do
something about it!
I mean, you are
the driver, right?
Whoa!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?!
Whaa!
If the left lane's blocked,
I'll use the right!
[Usagi]
Whoaa!
I've driven a bus for ten years.
I'm a pro! Move it!
Hey!
Hehe! haha! hahaha!
I need to get off!
Stop this bus
immediately!
Sorry, this just
became an express!
We're not going to make
any stops until we reach
our final destination!
Shut up and
stop the bus!
Uaaahh!
It's no use.
No one's answering
at the school.
But if Usagi's not there,
then where do you think
she could have gone?!
I don't know.
This might be dangerous
with just the two of us.
Yeah, we really should
find Usagi first before
we do anything else.
[car crash]
Thanks for nothing!
I'm going home!
Oh, no! My poor bus!
- For crying out loud!
- Great! Now I'm late!
Just what were you
thinking, ya lunatic?!
I'm very busy! I don't
have time for this!
Usagi!
Oh! Hi, Ami!
[Usagi]
So this is the
monsters' hideout?
Usagi!
Not so loud!
You can't just stand out
there in the open like that!
The enemy
could spot us!
Ohh, What are we waiting for?
Didn't you say that clock
shop is suspicious?!
Let's just storm in
there right now and
finish this, Luna!
Usagi, you've been completely
bewitched by the monster's
spell! Can't you feel it?
I simply don't have time to
discuss that kind of thing!
I have a lot of things
to accomplish today!
First off, I have to get home,
then eat a pork bun,
after that, finish
playing my video game,
take a bath and then--
Oh no look what
time it is already!
Okay, Usagi,
calm down.
We get it.
Just try to hold on for a
moment, and we'll think of a
way to get inside. Right, Ami?
Well, I suppose that
we could try sneaking
in from the back.
But the enemy might
expect that and be
waiting for us.
Oh we'll go in
through the front!
The enemy's going
to attack us either
way so let's just hurry
up and transform!
Come on, Ami,
let's do this!
What?! Right now?!
[fast]
Here I go! Moon
Prism Power Make Up!
You, too, Ami! Hurry up!
Standing around thinking
won't get you anywhere!
Okay! Like they [always] say,
"Nothing ventured, nothing
gained," right?
But Ami! This is too fast!
Mercury Power Make Up!
All right!
Let's move in!
Ah! Wait!
Take this!
Moon Tiara Action!
Ahh!
Oofh!
Boy, this just
isn't my day.
Sailor Moon!
There's the door!
Right!
Now who's this?
I am the pretty guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
That's right!
I'm Sailor Mercury!
[Both]
We're here to
take you down!
Oh, ho! You two got
here very quickly.
As expected.
There's no way that I'd let
anyone get away with wasting
a girl's precious time!
I bet even the cuckoo in
a cuckoo clock is angry!
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Hmf. Really?
You were fools to enter my lair,
but now that you're here, this
is where you will die!
Sailor Moon, come and get me!
Oh, I will!
Ah, Sailor
Moon, wait!
No time to wait,
let's go!
Okay!
Good luck in there, you two.
I can't help you this time.
Where could she
have gone?!
Come on!
Be careful, Sailor Moon.
That monster has probably
set a trap here.
This is so
irritating!
You coward! What kind
of loser hides like
this! Just come out!
Heh heh heh. I'm waiting
just a little farther ahead.
Come and get me!
Oh, don't you worry!
I will get you!
Wait! You could be walking
into trouble, Usagi!
Hurry up, Mercury!
Coming!
She's not here!
Sailor Moon,
listen! Please!
If we run around blindly
like this, we're just
going to get lost!
I'm not worried!
Because I have you
with me, Mercury!
[sigh]
Hey! What is that?!
It's a supercomputer.
From Luna.
Wow, that's
totally awesome!
[Ramua]
What's the matter?
Can't quite catch up?
Be quiet! We're coming!
You just wait!
Huh?!
We'd already be
there if it weren't
for your cheating!
Oh, no!
Play fair!
Sailor Moon,
get back!
Boy, that
was scary!
I'll say! It appears
that time is very erratic
and unstable here.
It's able to speed up,
slow down, and even to
go backward!
You mean there are
rooms where we could
turn into old ladies?!
Uh...
I am Sailor Moon, the
shriveled-up guardian.
Mmh! Oh man! What a
terrifying thought!
Strange. No one's here.
[Sailor Moon]
What's taking so long?!
Give me one
more second.
Augghh!
[Sailor Mercury]
Just as I thought!
Oh, yeah?
There's a pattern to this
labyrinth, and I think
I can figure it out.
Great! So where can
we find the monster?!
I'm seventy-eight
percent certain that
she's... this way!
Come on,
let's go!
Yeah!
[chuckle]
You have done well to make
it this far, Sailor Moon.
But it's over!
You've reached
the end!
Wrong! You're the one
who's reached the end!
[weak]
Ah! Ahh...
I can't stand up!
What's happening to me?
[Ramua]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
The effects are finally
starting to show.
By now, Sailor Moon,
my clock has drained away
nearly all of your energy!
[gasp]
Her energy?!
Now take this!
My face!
Waaaaah!
Sailor Moon!
Back off!
Haaa!
Aagh!
Can't move!
[snickering] I have stopped
time entirely for you!
And now you will get to
watch in silence as I
make Sailor Moon suffer!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Sailor Moon!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[Sailor Moon]
Help!
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha!
Huh??
Ah! My energy's coming back!
The Energy!
it's escaping!
Ah! I can
move again!
Bubble...
...Spray!
Where are you?!
Damn it!
Are you okay,
Sailor Moon?
Thanks a lot, but
I'm all right now.
The monster's
right there!
Got it!
Moon Tiara Action!
Ahh! Ahhh!
Ah!
Usagi! Ami!
You're okay!
[chuckle]
Oh, boy, that was
totally exhausting!
I think I've had just about
all the excitement that I
can handle for one day!
Usagi! I have
huge news!
The bakery is offering
free cakes to whoever can
eat them the fastest!
What? No way!
We gotta hurry!
[giggle]
Ack!
Owowowowowow!
She's gonna be like
this for the rest of
her life, isn't she?
Yep! She sure is!
Waahhh!
[Usagi]
Luna! I made another friend!
Her name is Rei Hino!
[Luna]
What's she like?
[Usagi]
She's a super cool
shrine maiden!
[Luna]
The opposite of
someone I know.
[Usagi]
Plus they say she has
strong spiritual powers,
and can predict the future!
Maybe she can
tell me about my
future boyfriend!
[Luna]
Silence! Evil
thoughts,
be exorcized!
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"The Cursed Bus: Enter Mars,
The Guardian Of Fire"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.