[Sailor Moon]
You evil fiend!
How dare you place fake
glass slippers on the hearts
of young girls who dream of
becoming Cinderella!
I am Sailor Moon,
and in the name of the moon,
you will be punished!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
And some people might say
I'm a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange
cat named Luna appeared,
turned me into a guardian
in a sailor uniform,
And told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggle]
Usagi Learns Her Lesson:
Becoming a Star is Hard Work
[panting]
Oh, no! I'm gonna
be late again!
But if I run all the way
to school, then I'll be
too tired to study!
Huh?
[Usagi] [reading]
"Feeling exhausted?
Try this energy booster!"
If Mikan thinks
I should try it,
then maybe I will!
Oh, no! I'm so late!
Huh?
Dagh!
What was
that for?!
Get moving, slowpoke!
Oww, that really hurt!
But don't forget that's
what saved you from
being late to class!
You're welcome!
[Umino]
Ta-dah!
I finally got the
poster of Mikan
Shiratori I wanted!
Hold on, Umino, you didn't
just steal this from the
drugstore, did you?
No, of course not!
I just ordered it
over the Internet.
It's a series of
tubes that connects
people's computers!
Anyway I got a
whole bunch more,
so if you want one,
I could sell it
to you for cheap!
We're gonna
pass this time.
Did you know Mikan Shiratori
used to attend Juban Middle
School like us and is now
seventeen years old?
She has appeared in
eight commercials,
and each month she
makes two million yen!
Whoa! Two million?!
That's a lot!
I wonder how many pieces of
shortcake I could buy with that.
If I remember right,
Mikan was discovered
right here in town.
Boy, she sure
is lucky.
Yeah, I wish that I had
better luck so I could
get discovered, too!
Seriously!
Those talent scouts
must be blind if they
keep on ignoring us.
To be honest, it seems
more likely that they
ignored you because they
can see all too well.
What did you say?!
I believe that the next big star
from our school to follow in
Mikan's footsteps will be...
Uh?
Usagi Tsukino!
Hrrm.
Huh? Me?!
A star?!
Yeah!
Huzzah!
- Can I get your autograph?
- I've been waiting for hours!
- You're the best!
Here! Thanks for
your support!
[chuckle]
I can use this energy.
What?! You want to
sing together?!
Yeah, we'll charge
right into the
entertainment world!
Got it!
Let's do this!
Uh, no. Wrong.
What we really need to do
is promote ourselves
with a song,
and then we'll become even
bigger stars than Mikan is!
Stars?
That's right!
Well, then,
let's get to it,
already!
Now is really not
the time for this.
We'll become an
overnight sensation!
You mean just
like Cinderella?!
Yeah! Let's go!
♪ ♪
And a one!
And a two!
And a!
♪ Gomen-ne,
it's hard for
me to say. ♪
♪ Although it's easy to
say it in my dreams. ♪
♪ My thought circuit is
about to break down. ♪
♪ You know right now,
I want you with --
Enough with all that screeching!
Hey, what do you
mean, screeching?!
What a rude thing to say
to the stars of tomorrow!
Yeah, whatever!
Once more!
Second verse
this time.
Mm-hm!
♪ ♪
♪ The moon!--
light guides!!
Ugh!
♪ us to our
destination dear! ♪
♪ Time and again,
we'll find each other! ♪
Owww! You're so
clumsy, Usagi!
♪ Counting the--
I am!? You're
one to talk!
Always
blaming
others!
No, that's you!
Well, if this is how you're
gonna be, then I'll just have to
go become Cinderella on my own!
Then you can consider us
rivals, because I'm gonna be
your biggest competition.
[light growling]
[sigh]
[canned laughter]
Now that I said all
that to Naru, what am I
supposed to do next?!
[Television]
Act sorry!
Eh?
What a smart
monkey!
He sure is!
Hey Luna, I bet
you could do
tricks like that!
Mow.
That's it, Dad!
You're a genius!
Uh...
[giggle]
Don't be surprised if
you see a bunch of
paparazzi here soon!
Mroww!
Rowr!
Do you think that
she's running a fever?
She seems
okay to me.
Yeah, she's just
as weird as she's
ever been!
[Usagi]
Act sorry!
Hrrrh. I don't understand.
Why are we doing this, Usagi?
Just stop complaining!
Now let's try it again!
Act sorry!
Hrrhm.
[doorbell]
Hello! This is Gurio Umino.
Your daughter, Naru,
invited me to come over.
May I come in?
Just come in here! Quick!
Well, that's about
all I can do.
You actually look
pretty good in salmon.
I don't get it. Why do
you want me to dress
like this again?
I've gotta go
study some more.
Now, now. What you
really should be
studying is socializing!
What? Socializing?
Usagi told me that she'd find
you even more attractive
if you only showed more
interest in learning about
how people interact.
Usagi really said that?
Eee!
Okay! I'll
do anything!
Heeh...
A beauty and the beast
team just might get the
talent scouts' attention!
[yenta voice]
I feel like my whole life's
about to change! Thank you!
Oh, really?
[nervous laugh]
[humming tunelessly]
Aaahhh!!
Ahh! Ahh!
Someone!
Help me!
Please!
[chuckle]
You, there! And you, too!
Be like Mikan Shiratori!
Transform your life
like Cinderella!
Hello, everyone! How are you?
I'm Mikan Shiratori!
Tell me girls, have any
of you ever dreamed of
being a star?
No way!
Is that really Mikan?!
I'm pretty
sure it is!
Okay! All of you go sign up
for the Cinderella Caravan!
Okay.
I wanna be like
Cinderella!
[all]
I want to be like her,
I want to be like her.
[chuckle]
Hey, have you
guys heard about
the Cinderella
Caravan contest?
No, what's that?
[chuckle] Boy, aren't
you behind the times!
Rgh! I've been busy
with some other things,
thank you!
Anyway, it's a talent
search hoping to find the
next Mikan Shiratori.
Yeah, and Mikan has already
given it her full support,
so you know it's the
real deal!
Ah!
[chuckle] This is my chance!
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who's gonna
win this contest!
Isn't that
right, Umino?
[girly giggle]
You've got that
right, girlfriend!
[girls] [horrified]
Ahhh!
Don't do it now!
You'll give the
act away!
Practice
makes
perfect!
Huhh??
Everyone! What do
you want to become?!
A star!
What's this?!
Why aren't all you
kids in school?
Mikan, what's going on?!
Why did you cancel all
of your appearances!
You just can't
go doing that!
Starting today, all of you
are going to be big stars!
[both]
Stars...?
Stars!
[chuckle]
Handstand!
Watch this!
Those are some
great tricks!
[both]
We're gonna be stars!
Today's the day we get
to show off all the
progress we've made!
But I really
don't want to...
What?! You can't
back out now!
Look, I only went along
with this in the first
place because I thought you
needed a change of pace!
So you
understand!
But it has nothing
to do with that!
You're obsessed
with becoming a
big star!
No, that's not
true at all!
Yes, it is!
No!
Then prove it! Stop trying
to get into that silly
little Cinderella contest!
[whine]
You no longer have the
luxury of fooling around.
Don't you understand how
important your mission is?!
[whine]
Will you stop
this nonsense?
[sniffle]
Come on, Usagi,
let's just go home,
okay?
There's no
time for this!
[sobbing] Luna
you're so mean!
[cries]
Huh?! Aw...
She doesn't understand
anything about me or how
important my dreams are!
Hey!
[gasp]
Not that stupid
jerk again!
Well, well;
if it isn't
Miss Bun-Head.
Don't tell me you're
going to that stupid
Cinderella contest too.
Hmf.
And let me guess, you're
going to try to impress
them with a comedy
routine, is that right?
No of course not!
Are you kidding me?!
I'd never do that!
Just stop bothering me!
I've got to go!
Ugh, buy a
new outfit.
Sailor Moon!
I needed some bread,
and the grocer said it
was "under there."
Oh, yeah?
And a moment later,
they gave me these!
And why's that?
When they said
"under there,"
I said "under where?!"
You stars're on to
the next round!
[chuckle]
♪ This is the
miracle of romance ♪
Congratulations,
you advance!
You pass!
And you!
We did it!
Aw yeah, girl,
we sure did!
Those of you who are moving on
will be performing live at the
Shan Shan Plaza next Sunday.
And that's when
you'll become famous!
[dreamy sighs]
[evil chuckle]
Huh?! What's going on?!
You really
think so, huh?
Of course!
But how about this?
What happens if you
pluck all the feathers
off a bald eagle?
Nothing,
'cause it's
already bald!
Good morning,
Naru. Huh?
Eighty!
Uh?
So many autographs!
Eighty-one!
Okay, everyone, did you
all get your streamers?
Oh! Usagi!
Here's one
for you!
All right, guys!
We're going to have an
autograph session now!
But isn't it
time for class?
Hey we're working
on our acts here!
Stars don't
take stupid
classes!
Hey! Let's throw
the streamers!
[laughs]
[giggle]
Ough!
Careful! Don't injure a
star's face, or he won't
be a star anymore!
This is getting bizarre.
♪ Gomen-ne, it's hard
for me to say. ♪
♪ Although it's easy to
say it in my dreams. ♪
Don't you find this
a bit strange?
Yep.
And it's like this
all over town;
people are suddenly
neglecting their daily
responsibilities because they
think they're famous stars.
You think a Monster's
behind this?
Not sure, but they all went
to that Cinderella contest.
That means we could've
been in danger as well!
You should be
thanking me for
saving you!
Hmm, Of course, you
also might have blocked
my path to stardom.
You're still thinking
about that?!
[Naru]
Now, make sure that you come
to Shan Shan Plaza on Sunday
to see our big concert!
We still have tickets left,
but they're going fast!
Hold on!
Not cool!
The show in Shan Shan
Plaza is supposed to
be our big show!
Yeah!
[arguing]
They actually believe
they're famous.
Hrmh.
That's odd. There's
no audience here
to watch the show.
[Mikan]
Listen up!
Soon, all of your shows
are about to begin!
Can't you guys hear the
audience out there,
cheering for you?!
[excited, nervous gasps]
Okay, it's make
or break time!
Yeah!
[applause]
It's almost time!
This is so
exciting!
Let's do it,
Yumiko!
Right!
One-arm
handstand!
Check out this
full boat pose!
Heh heh. Time to start
taking your energy.
Soon I'll have a fresh batch
of energy for our great ruler!
Hm hm hm, ha ha ha ha!
Hey, Kuri, do you
know what a
house's favorite
type of plant is?
A wallflower!
Hup! Backflip! And that's
followed by a triple axel,
and then a triple spin!
What IS this?!
Very strange.
What's a cow's
favorite thing to do
when it has free time?
Watch mooo-vies!
So, you've seen
the truth.
Huaaaahhhh!
H-Her head!
Spinning! Ahhh!
Huh? Usagi!
Usagi! Come out!
[panting]
You have to transform
into Sailor Moon!
Do I really have to?
Naru and the others
are in danger!
Awwww...
Okay, let's go.
Moon Prism Power! Make Up!
[clapping]
This is the miracle of romance!
[faints]
Oh yeah!
[woozy]
We hope you've
enjoyed the show...
[fainting]
Uhhh...
[chuckles]
Huh?! What's happening?!
[Sailor Moon]
You evil fiend!
How dare you place fake
glass slippers on the hearts
of young girls who dream of
becoming Cinderella!
Ugh!
Who's there?!
I'm the pretty guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
moon, you will be punished!
What?!
So you're not Mikan!
You're a monster!
Yagh!
There's no escape!
Where'd you go?!
Luna, where are you?!
Ugh, where does that
talking cat go when I
need her the most?!
There you are!
Ah!
Aaahhh!
Huh?!
Ew, what is this?!
[struggling]
Blagh! Ngh! Agh!
[frightened gasps]
What is going on?!
[struggling grunts]
Oh, no! I can barely move!
I can't
breathe...
That's right,
it's all over!
[big gasp]
My glass prison!
Why you!!
All right, you're the star of
this show now, Sailor Moon!
Thank you,
Tuxedo Mask!
Good luck!
You're not
getting away!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Hm!
You'll pay for this!
Moon Tiara Action!
Huagh!
Daagh!
Whoa...
Hmm... Hey, what?!
How did I get here?!
Huhh?
What happened...?!
I don't know! Why
are we standing in
an empty theater?
No idea...
Uh?
Huh?
Oh, boy!
I'm exhausted.
Nothing good happens when
you get too obsessed.
Yeah, yeah.
No, think about
what you've done!
Act sorry!
[sigh]
[chuckle]
[Usagi]
I became friends with this
super smart girl today!
Her name is Ami Mizuno!
Once I get to know her
better, I bet she'll give
me a bunch of pointers on
how to ace all my exams!
[Luna]
That's so like
you, Usagi.
[Usagi]
What do you mean?
[Luna]
Never mind.
Just be careful!
I'm sensing a strange
energy from her.
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"Is the Girl Genius a Demon?
The Brainwashing
Cram School of Horror!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.