I'm so excited! We
haven't taken a family
trip for ages, and we're
going to a hot springs!
What?! Why is there a
monster here?! How dare
you interfere with our
family-time together!
You're gonna pay for
this, I promise! I am
Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
my Dad, I'll punish
you!
Rise and shine, Usagi.
It's a two-day holiday,
so you can focus on
your studies to become
a princess.
Usagi?
Oh my goodness,
that's unusual.
She's already up!
Where is everybody?
Hm?
Good morning, Luna!
The family's taking a
trip to a hot springs!
We'll be back by tomorrow
night, so watch the
house while we're gone,
okay? I'll bring back
some hot-spring manju
for you! Love, Usagi!
Usagi!
'The Legendary Lake Yokai:
The Bond of Usagi's Family!'
Gosh, you're such a
weirdo, Usagi. Why'd
you leave a note behind
for that cat? It's not
like she can read.
Trust me, I have my
reasons. He's getting
away, you gotta shoot!
It's been so long
since we've all
been on a trip
together!
I'm not too thrilled
about having to spend
a night in a rustic hot
springs inn, though.
Ahhhh! You're
awful at this!
Give it!
Give that back to me!
(fighting grunts)
(gasp)
It's gonna break!
(sigh of relief)
Ugh!
(chuckling)
Now why are you getting
so upset? Did some boy
you like give that to you?
Huh? Umm...
Yeah, something
like that.
What?! A boyfriend?!
(frightened screams)
Dad, what are
you doing?!
Honey, hold
the wheel!
Usagi, have you been
secretly dating someone?!
No! That's not what's
going on! I promise!
You need to keep
your eyes on the
road, dear!
Well, that's a
relief, anyway.
(chuckles)
For a minute, I
sure was nervous!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
(relieved sighs)
Wow! It's so pretty!
(giggle)
And it's so
peaceful here!
That's because
there's nothing
here.
Actually, there are
beautiful memories
here. This lake is
where your mom and
I first met, many
years ago.
Oh dear. That's
ancient history.
(gasp)
It's Mamoru's
music box.
Mamoru...
Usagi, it's
time to go.
Is something wrong,
sweetheart?
No, everything's
just fine, Mom.
Kunzite, is this the
lake where you detected the
abnormal energy reading?
Yes, my Queen. The energy
is very similar to that of
our monsters. There is a
slight difference, but it
is still very powerful.
I see. Endymion, I
want you to go check
it out immediately.
Yes.
Queen Beryl...
Hm?
He's been acting
strangely the past
few days. Do you
suppose he's beginning
to finally realize that
his memory has been
erased?
Unlikely. But we should
be cautious. I want you
to follow him, observe,
and then report back to me.
Yes, my queen.
By all measures, Endymion
is completely under our
control. I seriously
doubt he has any
suspicions about
his past.
(giggling)
This is incredible!
What a view!
Not too bad for a
rustic hot springs
inn, wouldn't you say?
Shingo, what's wrong?
Come over and join us.
You'll like it, believe
me! It really feels great!
No way! It's a
co-ed bath!
What are you so
embarrassed about,
son? There's no one
here but your family.
Hurry and come in,
before you catch cold!
Umm...
Hmm...
(sneaky giggle)
Chyaah!
(giggling)
Ha! I got you!
Oh yeah?!
Ahhh! Shingo,
give that back
right now!
Stop fooling
around, you two!
Oh, let them play.
If you don't give
that back, you'll
be sorry!
Really? Come
and get it!
Shingo!
This view's incredible!
I can see the valley
and the whole lake!
Huh?
Got it! You dropped
your guard!
There's someone on
the shore! Look!
Down there!
Huh? Really?
(gasp)
It can't be!
It is! It's Mamoru!
Agh! Wait, please!
Sis?
What's with her?
She's acting weirder
than usual.
(gasp)
Mamoru!
It's not him.
(gasp)
It's playing again.
The music box.
Huh?
(gasp)
Mamoru...
That melody. Why is
it resonating inside
my soul?
Please, Mamoru! It's
me, Usagi! Are you
really here?
Do you know me...
...at all?
Mamoru?
Usagi?
I don't know them.
Those names mean
nothing to me.
How can that be?!
Mamoru, it's me!
Please! Don't you
recognize me?
Usagi!
Mom...
(surprised gasp)
Mamoru...
Usagi, what's the
matter? Why did you
run off so suddenly?
Sorry about that.
It was nothing.
Oh. There's the Legend
of the Lovers. Is that
what you were looking at?
Huh?
What's that?
It's an ancient tale
about this lake. A
long, long time ago, a
young man fell in love
with an angel who had
descended from the
heavens.
Another woman who loved
the young man was angry
that he didn't return
her feelings. Consumed
by hate and jealousy,
this woman turned into
a monster, and began
attacking the villagers.
The angel and the young
man used the power of
their love to seal the
monster away in the lake.
But having used up all
their strength, the two
died, and ascended to
heaven.
It's the story of
their love for
each other.
Sealed away in
this lake.
Come on, let's go
back. You'll catch
cold.
(giggle)
'Kay, Mom!
You're such a baby.
Mmm...
Listen, Usagi. Promise
me something, if you
ever do fall in love.
Huh?
Promise that you'll
bring the boy over and
introduce him to your
father and myself, so
we can get to know him.
Yes. I promise.
I'll do that,
one day...
But it might
be a while.
A monster sealed
away in the lake.
I wonder if that could
be the source of the
unusual vibrations.
How perceptive. You
may very well have
uncovered the source of
this mysterious energy.
(growing growl)
Hear me, bitter soul
sealed in this lake.
Now, I command you
to return to life!
(sharp grunt)
Arise! Oh
ancient spirit!
(gasp)
Give him back!
(stunned gasp)
Sailor Moon!
Give him back!
(angry growl)
(amused chuckle)
Well now, Endymion. With
your endless curiosity,
you've raised a grudge
from the past.
What will you do?
(fierce scream)
(fierce yell)
Give him back!
(attack yell)
Wait! Where are
you going?
Huh?
Mamoru, you're
so near, yet...
Usagi, is something
the matter?
(startled gasp)
Oh! It's nothing!
I was admiring how
beautiful the moon is.
It's perfect tonight!
It is beautiful, now
that you mention it.
It's so pretty, it
just makes me wanna
cry.
I'm gonna go soak in
the hot springs and
watch the moon a
while before dinner!
If you'll excuse me!
She's a mystery. I'm
so confused. I mean,
there are times when
she seems like a
totally different
person.
Yeah...
I won't give up,
Mamoru. Even if you
have no memory of me.
I've got to find a
way to get through
to you!
Give him back!
What was that?
Huh?
No way! Who are you?!
Usagi! What on earth
is that thing?!
It's some kind of
horrible creature!
It's a monster!
Watch out everyone!
(attack roar)
Get down!
Give him back!
Ahhhh!
(frightened gasps)
Run for it!
(scared screams)
Look at the trees!
It must be some
kind of poison!
That's it! Now
I'm angry!
Hey you! What's your
big problem! You're
totally ruining our
family trip!
Go away! Leave
us alone!
Usagi, don't
confront her!
Agh! That's right!
Let your dad handle
this!
Hey! Stay away from
my family! You monster!
(scared whine)
(aggressive growls)
Ahhh!
Look out!
(struggling breaths)
Ahhh!
Dad!
Moon...
Honey, are you
all right?!
Look at this
tacky freak show!
Don't call him that!
He's a good guy...
...I think.
Back off, creature!
I'm not gonna let
you go and hurt
innocent people!
(growling)
Give him back!
Do you think you can
walk all right, dear?
Oh, my back!
I want to go and
help Tuxedo Mask,
but I can't transform
in front of my family!
Now's your chance!
Run for it!
(painful grunt)
Tuxedo Mask!
(angry growl)
Ahh!
Hold it right there!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
We are the Sailor
Guardians!
Wow! The Pretty Guardians
who fight for love and
justice!
Hey, that's my
catchphrase!
Give him back!
Bubble!
Spray!
(screaming)
Come on! Now's
our chance! The
inn is that way!
Stay together!
it's not that far!
Please be
careful, guys.
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
(angry yell)
Hey monster,
over here!
You can't just run
amok out here! You
have to pay for
threatening innocent
tourists and ruining
the Tsukino Family's
vacation!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
Tuxedo Mask. You
protected Usagi!
You're still the same
good person that I
love so much.
Ahhhhh!
(gasps)
Sailor Moon!
Crescent Beam!
Supreme!
Thunder!
(painful scream)
We got her!
(angry growl)
What?!
I don't understand,
why didn't our attacks
work on her?!
Alright, in that case!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
(painful scream)
That should do it!
(surprised gasp)
(angry growl)
Oh come on! That's
not fair! What kind
of monster is she?!
Wait. This evil aura.
That's no ordinary
monster. She's an
evil yokai, born from
years of strong
jealousy.
You're right about
that, Sailor Guardians.
The truth of the matter
is, I am the one to blame
for awakening this
ancient yokai. You
must stay out of this.
That makes sense,
except yokai are my
area of expertise.
Cleanse and dispel this
yokai with flames of
purification! Rin!
Pyo! To! Sha! Kai! Jin!
Retsu! Zai! Zen!
Ahh-Ahhhh! Evil
spirit! Be exorcised!
Fire!
Soul!
(painful scream)
Oh, wow!
Get her,
Sailor Moon!
Oh! Uh, right!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Ahhhhh!
Refresh!
She's going to heaven,
released at last from the
eons of torture brought
on by her jealousy.
She's beautiful!
Tuxedo Mask!
I was going to say
that you interfered
needlessly, but I'll
let it go this time.
Farewell!
Don't go!
Tuxedo Mask...
Well, Endymion. You
are an odd fellow.
Usagi! Where are you?!
Answer me! Hey sis!
Where are you?!
Usagi! Say
something!
Tell us you're
alright!
Come on, sis! What
if the monster got
her?
If I had known this
was gonna happen, I
would have let her
play with my game.
Okay, hand it over!
Usagi!
Mom! Dad!
Oh, you had us
so worried!
Sorry, Mom.
Dad risked his life to
protect me. Mom thinks
about me every minute.
And Shingo's a pain,
but I still love
him. It's great to
have a family.
Ah, this feels
so good.
You said it.
Where are you,
Tuxedo Mask?
Usagi...
Chin up. Everything
will work out.
Thanks, Mako.
But I'll be fine. When
I think about it, I have
all these great friends
who care about me!
I've been wondering
about something, though.
What brought all of you out
here in the first place?
Luna said that
you were here.
And of course...
...Not one of us
wanted you...
...to have all
the fun, Usagi!
(giggling)
Hey! I got water
up my nose!
You must've
deserved it!
Stop it!
You guys, I think
she got the message.
(giggling)
Usagi, we've got
trouble! Ryo Urawa
is in danger! It looks
like they're planning
to revive the Seven
Great Monsters!
What?! That's crazy!
Ami is protecting
him alone! Now
let's go!
But, I can't go
outside because it's
so cold! Take care of
things for me, will
you, Luna?
Thanks a lot!
Usagi!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"I Won't Run Away from
Love Anymore: Ami
versus Mamoru!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.