[Sailor Moon]
I'm really mad! How dare
you use people's love of
cute pets against them!
I won't let you get away with
treating people like this!
I am Sailor Moon, and
in the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a Cancer with blood type O.
My birthstone is a pearl,
and I'm a bit of a klutz.
Some people might say
I'm also a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange
cat named Luna appeared,
turned me into a Guardian
in a sailor uniform,
and told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggles]
[Usagi]
Scent of a Monster:
Chanela will Steal
Your Love!
[Usagi]
[nightmare grunts]
[frightened running]
Nooo! I'm scared! Help!
Huh?!
Aaahhh!
Tuxedo Mask!
You came!
You're my hero!
[dreamy]
Aahh!
Have no fear, I will
always be by your side
when you need me.
[dreamy]
Aahh...
[Shingo]
Hyaaahh!
Huh?
Wait! Tuxedo Mask!
Ohh...
[Shingo]
Huaaaagh!
Nnngh!
That stupid Shingo!
He totally
ruined my dream!
Why is there a
cat in my room?!
[yawn]
Meow?
Yaaagh!
Ngh! Stay away!
Hey! Stop--
Mmmf!
Usagi, get that cat
out of here right now!
That's right.
You're scared of cats.
I forgot.
Here!
Gahh! Stop it!
Okay!
But only if you promise
that you'll stop bothering
your incredibly smart and
beautiful big sister!
Breakfast!
Coming!
Augh, safe
at last!
And just what were you
two arguing about so
early in the morning?
Usagi, is that the
same black cat we
saw the other day?
Yup! Her name
is Luna.
She's perfect for Usagi.
They're both obnoxious.
Well, guess you'll be
spending more time together
now that she's decided she
wants to sleep in your room.
Pffft!
What?! You've got to be
kidding, I didn't say
she could sleep there!
Anyway, now that
everyone in the
house has met Luna,
we can let her
move in with us
for good, right?!
No. Way.
Yes way, yes way!
Yes! Way!
No way, no way, no way!
Yes way, yes way,
yes way!
YES WAY!
I vote one hundred
percent no!
I'm fine with keeping her.
What about you, honey?
Well, I think that we
should have the kids
work it out themselves.
[both]
Seriously!?
Why were you in
Shingo's room, anyway?
Well...
I've been so busy with work,
and I was exhausted.
I just went into
the wrong room,
It was an honest mistake!
Work?! Were you out
chasing mice or something?
Of course not!
Don't be ridiculous!
I was out looking
for the Moon Princess!
Moon... Pudding?
No, you idiot.
Anyway, see if you
can make Shingo
like you, okay?
See ya!
Goodbye! Oh and good luck!
[sigh]
[Luna]
Maybe this pet store'll
give me a clue of how to
get Shingo to like me.
Adorable!
Look! He's licking
my finger! How cute!
So that's how you do it!
Well, Jadeite, have you
devised a new strategy to
capture more human energy to
offer to our great ruler?
Yes, Queen Beryl.
The monster Iguara has
already made preparations.
The foolish humans constantly
remain at the mercy of all their
ridiculous wants and whims,
and by merely providing
a minor catalyst to
activate them,
we can cause all those
pathetic yearnings to spill
out as a mass of energy!
Yes, and once we do,
we'll be able to
capture all of it!
All for our
great ruler!
Very well, proceed.
but do so carefully,
understood?
Yes.
[school bell]
[Naru]
Seriously? Shingo really
doesn't like cats?
Mhm. When he was just a baby,
a cat from the neighborhood
bit him on the tip of his nose.
And ever since then, he hasn't
been able to get over his fear
of them.
Oh that's nothing!
When I was a toddler,
an alligator practically
swallowed me whole.
What?!
An alligator?!
Really?!
Yes, it was a curious
accident caused whenmy Mother
Forgot to close the latch
when she set it down.
Uh, close the latch to what?!
Umino, are you sure that
you aren't just talking
about an alligator handbag?
Maybe that was it!
Rrrh, Umino!
- Bye!
- Buhbye!
- Bye, see you tomorrow!
- See you later!
Mreow!
HYAAAAGHH!
Well, that didn't go well...
Uh, Shingo?
The cat...
Where's the cat?
[giggle] You're not really
an animal person, are you?
Uh...Oh, Mika!
I don't know; I might be okay
with another kind of pet.
just anything
except a cat!
Oh, yeah? Then I have the
perfect thing for you!
What?
There's a new pet shop that
just opened here in town.
Let's check
it out!
Uh, okay.
[Mika]
There it is.
It's called Perfume!
- Oh my goodness!
- Look at this!
- So cute!
Wow, it sure
smells good!
Yeah, it smells
like perfume!
[Mika]
Hey. I think it's coming
from these little guys.
Huuh?
Hi! Are you interested
in a Chanela?
A Chanela?
[chuckle] Yes!
Those animals are called
Chanelas, and each emits
a delightful perfume.
Every one of them
gives off a different
and unique scent.
Huh?
Ah!
I'm gonna buy
this Chanela.
I'd like to buy one, too.
But they must be expensive.
You can pay me
whatever you like!
Really?!
That's awesome!
[sinister chuckle]
[whine]
[yapping]
They smell
so good!
Yeah I know!
[whine]
As long as I have a
Chanela, there's nothing
else I'll ever need!
[sinister chuckle]
Ulp!
I see. So you couldn't
get him to like you.
You know, it isn't really
important for me to live
with you guys as a pet.
Huh??
It's not really like
you to give up as
easily as that, Luna!
You're always the one
lecturing me about how I need
to work harder at my mission.
Well, this is your
opportunity to
lead by example!
O-kay...
Oh, hey!
Brreow!
That's it, Luna!
Hrrmh!
Mrowwrr!
Ahh!
Starting today, this
Chanela is my pet;
my only pet!
So hurry up and get
rid of that cat!
[sniff]
Stop being so mean
to Luna, Shingo!
Wahhh!
Nnnghh!
Waaah!
It's okay.
I'm so sorry Shingo
did that to you!
[Ikuko]
Usagi, I've
made some tea!
Coming!
Mmh.
That new pet of yours
really does smell nice!
I know! And it's easy
to take care of, too!
A Chanela doesn't
need to be fed!
Wow, that's one
economical pet!
[mouth full]
And even I have to
admit that little
guy is pretty cute!
Well, why don't
you keep both Luna
and the Chanela?
I agree!
No way!
Never!
You're just
the cutest!
[Usagi]
Shingo! Hurry up
or you'll be late!
Shingo! Hey, are
you listening?
I'm staying home today.
Huh??
You and I will be
together forever!
Huh??
Sailor Moon!
What do you think
of my Chanela?
Isn't it great?
Eh. My Chanela
smells better.
Let me see...
No, it doesn't!
Wow! Those Chanelas
are really popular
right now, huh?
I know! They're huge!
Everyone has one!
But I really don't think
people should be bringing
their pets to school!
Oh! Ms. Haruna!
Hey guys! Hurry
up and hide them!
- Oh! She's coming!
- Ah!
- She's here!
Okay, let's get started.
Everyone open your
textbooks to page two
hundred and thirty-four.
[fidgeting]
Dagh! I gotta
see my pet now!
I can't wait
anymore!
- Driving me crazy!
- Can't wait!
- Wanna play with it!
Aw... So cute!
What's that!?
Give it to me please!
No way!
Stop! No!
[crash]
Ms. Haruna!
Are you all right?
I'm out of here!
Me, too!
Yeah!
Those girls sure were
acting strangely.
Yeah!
I mean, sure, Chanelas are
cute and all but there's
no need to go that far.
Come to think of it,
Just this morning...
Shingo was acting weird too!
I wonder if it's related
to those Chanelas.
Naru, do you happen to
know exactly where they're
selling those things?
I think everyone got them
from a place called Perfume.
Let's check it out!
Sorry, I have cram
school today.
Aw. Okay, I guess
I'll just have to
go alone.
Are you gonna be all
right by yourself?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Ugh, the things
that I do for my
numbskull brother!
Well, that's sisterly love!
So this is where
they're being sold.
Wait a second...
What if I become
like Shingo?!
Hey! Bunhead!
Ngh!
I know that voice...
[chuckle]
Ngh, Great. Why do
you keep showing
up wherever I go?!
It's annoying,
you know that!
And I could say the exact
same thing about you!
Ugh!
Don't tell me you've decided
to be like everybody else
and buy one of these pets?
Why not?
You don't seem like
the type of girl
who likes perfume.
Augh!
Just get lost!
Well, I'm inside.
Hello!
Welcome!
Look around!
Take your time!
Right. Thanks.
[chuckle]
I should have waited till
Naru could come with me.
Wow, they really are cute!
Usagi, don't be
fooled by that!
Luna?
Why, what's up?
There's something very
strange about this place.
Oh...
Really like what?
Awww!
Don't look in its eyes!
[dreamy]
Ahhh...
So cute...
Usagi!
Ahh!
I'm not surprised
even one little bit!
I knew that a beautiful
girl like you would
pick the prettiest pet!
Mmhm.
[giggle] So cute!
Usagi, you really ought
to take that back!
Don't come any closer,
or I'll give you a kick!
Usagi...
I can't stand you!
Dumb cat...
Hang in there.
Remember it's not Usagi's
fault she said that.
Beep beep! Coming through!
Out of the way!
Ah!
[crying]
Usagi, hold up!
Meow!
[giggle] Aw, what a
cute kitty! Thank you!
I can't leave
things like this!
Dagh! Ahh!
Mhh...
Huh?!
Oh, Thank
goodness.
Luna, what's going on?
What happened to me?!
I'm sorry, Luna!
I totally screwed up!
Never mind that!
I'm more worried
about Shingo!
Me, too!
All right, Shingo!
Hand over that
Chanela, right now!
No way!
Come on! Give it
to me, already!
I told you
give it to me!
Mmh!
[gasp]
I'm... sorry!
I'm not handing
my Chanela over
to anyone!
Agh!
Usagi, there's no time to
feel sorry for yourself,
we have to go after your
brother right away!
But I don't have any idea
where he could have gone!
I'm positive that he's gone
back to that pet shop!
Now quick, change
into Sailor Moon!
And let's go!
What do I do if I
come face to face
with a Chanela again?
Just get a grip, Usagi!
You have a very
important mission to
fulfill, remember?!
Mm.
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Now, listen! You are
to take these Chanelas
and distribute them
throughout the city!
Yeah!
[Sailor Moon]
I'm really mad!
How dare you use people's love
of cute pets against them!
Ugh! Who're you?!
I won't let you get away with
treating people like this!
I am the pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of
the moon, I'll punish you!
Damn you!
[roar]
[snarling]
Ew, gross!
[roar]
[snarling]
Ah!
Ya ha ha!
Shingo...!
Usually about now,
Tuxedo Mask shows up to
bail me out of trouble.
Yahh!
But I don't think
he's coming!
Stop depending
on other people!
[snarling]
Quickly! Use your
Moon Tiara Action!
But what about
Shingo?!
Okay, then just
shout Moon Tiara
Stardust instead!
Got it!
Moon Tiara Stardust!
Huh?
Ah! I didn't know I
could do that, too!
I'll get you!
Sailor Moon, this way!
Right!
Yahhh!
[frightened panting]
Huh!?
Ahh!
I can't...get out!
Don't give up!
Aim for the
base of that
monster's tail!
Moon Tiara Action!
Gyaahhh!
Phew!
Sailor V, wait!
Eee! Oh no!
Sailor V! Can I have
your autograph?
I'm a big fan
of yours!
I'm actually Sailor Moon,
you know!
What? Oh, okay.
Close enough, whatever.
will you please give
me your autograph?
Ehh, Listen, there's
something that I need you
to do for me, Shingo.
Huh? No way!
How do you know my name?!
I'm Sailor Moon.
I know everything!
Now, Shingo, what I'm asking
you to do is be nicer to
that black cat named Luna.
And if you do that, then
I'm certain that cat is
gonna bring you happiness.
Sure! If that's what
Sailor Moon wants!
[chuckle]
[meow]
How are you liking
that ham, Luna?
[pleased meow]
Well! This is much
more pleasant!
From now on, I guess that
we're a family of five!
[chuckle]
[sigh] I'm not sure if
this is any better.
[Usagi]
Oh! I love this song!
[Luna]
Oh! You like jazz now?!
[Usagi]
Of course! All grown-ups
like jazz, and I'm
practically grown-up!
Well, kinda. Okay, I
just want to fall in
love like grown-ups do!
[Luna]
That won't happen as long
as teachers make you
stand in the hallway!
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon:
Protect The Melody Of Love:
Usagi Plays Cupid!
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.