(Usagi)
Hello blue skies and
sunshine! It's the moment
we've all been waiting for!
(cont'd)
Summer break is
finally here!
(cont'd)
Wait, what's going on?!
Is someone trying to ruin
our vacation?
(cont'd)
And look! They're robbing
an innocent girl of her
future!
(cont'd)
That's just
unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
moon! I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
It may not look it, but
I'm actually a superhero!
I use a special brooch
to transform and fight
evil!
You know me as, the
Pretty Guardian who fights
for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius,
Ami Mizuno, who's
Sailor Mercury!
And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic, who's
Sailor Mars!
Both of them seem to
have it a little more
together than I do!
But, oh well. Guess
I just gotta do my
best!
(Giggles)
"The Summer, The Beach,
Youth, And Ghosts."
(Usagi)
Ah!
We made it!
We're finally here!
(All)
Wow!
(Usagi)
Look at the beach!
(Ami)
The sea breeze is
so refreshing!
(Rei)
Yeah, this place is
really nice!
It's too bad we
couldn't have brought
Naru along with us!
We are not here to have
fun, Usagi!
Remember, we're here
for a Sailor Guardian
summer training camp!
(Egh!)
Way to ruin the
moment, Luna!
Wow!
(Ami)
How far is the pension
house we're staying
at?
(Rei)
It's supposed to be
pretty close by.
So Rei, I'm expecting
this hotel to be a
really swanky resort!
Well, I think it is.
Really?!
It says here, "Blue
seas surround you as
yachts go gliding by!
From our luxurious
(cont'd)
pension house you can view
a beautiful sunset over our
gleaming private beach!
Our own private beach!
(Crowd Talking)
(Usagi)
Motoki, it's you!
(Giggles)
Huh?
(Usagi)
Tuxedo Mask!
Ah!! I can't wait!
This is it! This is
what I'm talking about!
Being young, at the beach
during summer break!
Huh?
Eh? Gah!
Hey, wait for me!
(Usagi Whining)
Are we there yet?
We're lost, aren't we?
That's because you
said it was definitely
this way!
Ugh! No, we're lost
because you didn't plan
ahead well enough!
Dummy!
What did you call
me?!
(Thunder Rolling)
Ahh!
Thunder! Looks like
it's really gonna
pour on us!
We better get going!
(Rei)
Right!
Ahh!
I'm really scared of
thunder!
Ahh!
(Luna)
Usagi!
(Ami)
What's wrong?!
Who's there?!
Oh!
Uh! Sorry I scared
you!
(All)
Huh?
Awe!
Now it's raining!
Uh, please, follow
me!
C'mon! Let's go!
(Usagi)
Okay...
(Lightning Strike)
(Usagi)
Ahh!
Make it stop!
I can't take it
anymore! I wanna
go home now!
Uh- That looks
creepy.
(Rei)
This is the place!
We've made it to the
pension.
(Usagi)
What?! We're staying
here?!
(Rei)
What's your problem?
This place looks
haunted.
Thank you, you
really helped us!
(Giggles)
We're absolutely
soaked.
Are your flowers okay?
Oh. yes!
That's good!
(Cowering)
Welcome!
Ah!
(Sakiko)
Hi.
(All Three)
Welcome back, Miss.
So, do you three ladies
have a reservation?
Yes, we do!
I'm Rei Hino, from
Tokyo.
We've been expecting
your arrival!
Eee-eee!
(All Three)
Come in!
Thanks.
(Ami)
Thank you for having
us.
Oh!
N-nice to meet you!
How long are you going
to keep making a scene
here?! It's embarrassing!
But, I, uh...
(Father)
Sakiko!
Ahh!
Calm down already!
Huh?
So just where were
you?! Get over here!
Uh, yes father.
Right away!
(Thunder)
Aw, I'm hungry.
And so exhausted!
(Luna)
Guess all that
screaming wore you
out.
Hey! You were
scared too!
Uh..
Seriously Luna, don't
you think the hotel
staff looked kinda
weird?
I mean, what if this
place really is haunted?
Maybe we should leave!
Ah!
Uh, yes?
Hello!
AHH!
What's wrong?
L-look behind you!
(Rei)
Huh?
Ah, there! It came on!
Sorry for bothering
you. It's time for
dinner now!
Jeez!
Usagi!
But I swear! She
popped in here out of
nowhere.
(Rei)
Now you're gonna
get it!
(Usagi)
No! Ami, help!
(Ami)
Not this time, Usagi!
You're on your own!
(Usagi)
But Ami!
(Rei)
No buts for you, bunhead!
(Usagi)
Hey, watch it!
(Father)
What a bunch of
noisy girls!
(Sakiko)
But they seemed like
very nice people.
Sakiko! Don't you go
getting involved with
such foolish girls?
Understand?!
Yes, I won't, Father.
(Everybody Eating)
Om!
Hm?
(Cook)
So, would you like
seconds?
Ahh!
No thanks, I'm already
full!
(Nervously Laughing)
(Cook)
Okay...
(Gasps)
Did you save some
room for dessert?
No, I didn't,
but thanks!
You stupid dummy!
What the heck made
you decide to pick this
place anyway?!
Duh, isn't it
obvious? It was
cheap.
Agh!
Even so, the food here
is tasty and I really
like the funny costumes
that they're wearing.
(Usagi)
You do?!
Nice to hear
that.
That's actually one
of the selling points
of this pension.
(Ghostly Moans)
(Usagi)
What now?!
There it goes,
again!
That wailing! It's
sounds so scary!
(Rei)
Must be the owner
crying.
No, that isn't me!
(Usagi)
Ah! Why do you keep
popping in out of
nowhere!
Hnh! Hey!
Ehh-Ehh!
Did you all see that?!
(Owner)
We-We didn't see
anything!
Hear that Luna, we
must've been imagining
things!
(Nervous Laughing)
Do you think it
was a monster?
No, I'm not sensing
that there's one
here.
However, I did sense
some kind of incredible
power.
Uh!
(Teeth chattering)
(Father)
Good girl. That's a
good girl. You're a
very good girl.
(cont'd)
Now sleep, go to
sleep.
That's right.
Good girl.
(Father)
Your eyes are heavy.
Now, sleep.
Yes, listen to my
voice. You will now
slowly open your eyes.
(cont'd)
Gradually, very
slowly.
(Deep Laughter)
Sailor Moon!
Yippee!
Check out those
great waves!
Hmm!
(Giggling)
Yay!
This feels great!
(Rei)
It's like that storm
never happened!
I know, this
weather's great!
But something's
missing...
I know, you're
right.
(Rei)
Well, this beach
certainly is private,
right?
(Usagi)
Yeah, so private
there's no one else
here but us.
Ships way offshore.
A flock of seagulls.
(Sigh)
Where are all the
yachts that glide
by?! And all the hot
boys?!
(Whines)
I hate this beach,
you hear me! I really
hate this beach!
So who wants to
play ball?!
(Groans)
Can I bury her in
the sand?
Wait! we never did
see that girl Sakiko
come out of her room
this morning.
Hey, you're right.
Wait! Hold on, Ami!
Did you bring some of
your textbooks here
with you?!
(Ami)
Mm-Hmm!
Aghh!
Hmph! Listen, Ami!
Youth is a precious
thing. You only get to
experience it once!
I know studying's
important, but I think
it's just as important
to have fun and make
some memories while
we're on this great
vacation!
But, I like
books.
Uh, Usagi said
something that makes
sense for once!
(Giggles)
Okay, you win!
Come on, let's go
have some fun!
Ha! Now that's
the spirit!
(Usagi)
Here goes!
(Laughing)
Ha!
Got it!
Catch!
Agh!
(Gasps)
Catch!
Agh!
Hey! Stop picking
on me!
(Giggling)
(Girls Playing)
I'll get you both!
You too, Luna!
(Girls Laughing)
Ah-ooo!
Oo-oo!
Aw! Nighttime's
here again.
I'm scared!
(Usagi)
Luna? You still there?
Luna!
For the tenth time!
Yes, I'm right here!
But I'm really
super scared!
Evil spirits, be
exorcised!
This should keep us
safe while were
having our dinner.
But, I'm pretty sure
that thing wasn't
a ghost.
It felt like it
was real and really
powerful.
(Cook)
Come on, let's do it
already!
If this is going to
start happening every
single day, I'm going to
go crazy!
We all know what we
have to do.
Yeah, but no matter
what, we can't let those
girls staying with us
know about it!
(All Three)
Right!
(Humming)
Oh!
(Ami)
Hi Sakiko!
Huh?
Oh, hello Ami!
Wow! You know my name?
But I never told it
to you.
Well, I was up here
all day and saw
you playing.
Rei's the pretty and
mature one, and
Usagi's the clumsy
one, and the cute little
cat is Luna, right?
(Echos from Rock
hitting the cliff)
And what about you?
Any close friends?
(Sakiko)
Uh-uh.
Well let's change
that!
You know, not so long
ago, I was a bit of a
loner. But now it's
different!
Huh?
See, I became friends
with Usagi. You should
become her friend, too!
(Chuckles)
She makes everyone
feel very happy!
Really? Are you sure?
Mm-Hmm!
(Happy Sigh)
(Father)
Sakiko!
(Gasps)
How many times have
I told you not to
talk to strangers?!
Uh! But Father, Wait!
(Ami)
W-Wait!
I'd suggest you girls
leave this place
right away!
That is unless you
want to see something
really terrifying.
Huh?
(Sakiko)
Father! That hurts,
please let go! I'm sorry.
Father!
(Sakiko)
But, Father!
Ami and her friends
are all really nice!
She even told me we
could all be good friends!
That's enough!
(Gasps)
(Father)
Sakiko, you possess
strong psychic powers
and I want you to gain
(cont'd)
full control of
that power!
(Sakiko)
But I can't do it!
It's too hard!
If you let me continue
to help you, you can
do it. I have found
a great way to draw
out your powers
is by using hypnosis.
Hm..
Are you trying to tell
me that you're going to
ignore your father who
knows what's best for you!
Uh...
But, father.
Now, just concentrate
on the coin, Sakiko.
(Father)
Concentrate...
Keep going deeper
and then you'll show
all those stupid people
who called our psychic
abilities fake that
you possess an
awesome power!
(Father cont'd)
Once you access your
superior psychic powers,
they will transform you
(cont'd)
into the world's
leading psychic!
(Deep Laughter)
(Ami)
Sakiko!
(Whining, Crying)
Hey, Ami, Rei!
Where did everybody
run off to?
(Crying)
(Chant)
Jibba, jabba, jibber,
joe, eeny, meeny, miney,
moe, getta, grabba, gotta
(Chant)
go, peda, meda, teeny,
toe, jibba, jabba,
jibber, joe.
Ah! What are they
doing?!
Oh no! Now you know?
Ah!
(Scared Ahh)
(Female Owner)
Hold on!
Ahh!
(Rei)
Usagi!
Aghh!
See! I told you!
They're ghosts!
Every one of them!
Calm down! These
people are normal
human beings!
(Usagi)
That can't be!
It is Usagi, but
what's more important
is that there's
an incredible force
being generated
in this place!
(All)
What?!
Something is coming!
(Gasps)
(Scared Gasps)
Ah!
Jibba, jabba,jibber,
joe, eeny, meeny,
miney, moe!
Now! Use your psychic
powers to create a
ghost! By now, this
should be an easy task
for you! And once
they see that, it'll
scare off those noisy
girls! Ha-ha-ha!
(Ami)
Stop that!
So, it's you again!
(Gasps)
(Father)
Amazing, Sakiko!
Good! Wonderfully done!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Go scare those girls
out of their wits!
Now we will get our
revenge on all those
(cont'd)
people who laughed
at us and said we
were fakes!
Ahh!-Ahh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's good!
It's perfect!
Gah! What?!
What are you doing?
(Gasps)
Huh?!
Whoa!
Eee-uh!
What's going on
here?
(Gasps)
Ugh!
Ahh!
A ghost!
Ugh!
Uhh. Sakiko!
This is all your
fault, Rei! Why did
you have to make
reservations here?!
This isn't the time
to be complaining
about that!
Usagi, Rei!
Transform!
(Ami)
We have to save
Sakiko's father!
(Father)
Sakiko!
(Crying)
Uh-uuh!
If we don't do
something now,
everyone will wind
up possessed!
Huh?!
All right!
I'll transform!
(Usagi)
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
(Ami)
Mercury Power!
Make up!
(Rei)
Mars Power!
Make up!
I am the Pretty Guardian,
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
I am Sailor Mercury!
I am Sailor Mars!
Meeny ghost! How dare
you ruin a hopeless
young girl's vacation!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon!
We'll punish you!
But I'm still really
scared!
(Father)
Sakiko! Stop it!
I said stop it!
Don't you recognize
your own father?!
Sakiko!
Come on, wake
up! You have to!
Sakiko!
No more! I can't
take it anymore!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Ahh!
Ahh!!
Please, Sakiko!
We need you!
You have to wake up!
Huh?
Oh! Sakiko!
Huh? Ami?
Ahh!
Hmph!
(Sakiko)
Father!
Sakiko! You have to
use your power and make
that ghost disappear!
But, it should've
disappeared completely
right after I woke up!
(Sakiko)
Why is it still
here?!
(Ami)
Look out!
Sailor Mercury!
Father!
Sakiko!
Quickly run away
from here! That ghost is
now beyond your control!
(Usagi)
What does he mean
by that?!
(Ami)
That ghost represents
Sakiko's repressed
feelings and desire to
(cont'd)
rebel against her
father. That feeling
was so strong inside
her that when it was
let out, she lost
control!
Agh!-Ah!
Hmph!
Are you okay?!
Go! Run away now!
No, father!
My daughter, you just
wanted to live a normal
life but instead I
forced you to do what
I wanted. I'm sorry!
Father!
(Gasps)
Sakiko, watch out!
Go away!
Oh!
(Gasps)
(Father)
Sakiko!
(Ami)
Are you okay?
I am...
Everyone, I want to
apologize for being
so single-minded and
only caring about
showing the world
Sakiko's powers.
I forced her to
train,
(cont'd)
even though I knew
I was going against her
will in developing
(cont'd)
her unique abilities.
I even started using
this hotel and the
patrons who stay here
as subjects to test
her power.
So then, what was
the staff doing
before?
(Rei)
They were probably just
trying to perform an
exorcism to get rid
(cont'd)
of the ghost.
I knew that!
(Giggles)
(Usagi)
Here it goes!
(Rei)
Got it!
Catch!
Agh!
Here!
Hey! Why am I always
the target here!
(Giggling)
Oh, so you thought
that was funny Sakiko?
(Usagi)
You're gonna get it
now!
(Bellhop)
Are you sure the ghosts
won't show up here
anymore?
I mean, we like working
here but we're pretty
timid. And ghosts and
monsters are what really
scare us the most!
Don't you worry.
You won't see them
here.
(Giggling)
(Father)
Ever again.
(Cont'd Giggling)
(Usagi)
Luna, guess what? We
get to visit an animation
studio!
(Luna)
Wow, look at all the
neat stuff and the pretty
ladies working there!
(Usagi)
I wanna be an animator
too and be a part of this
awesome business!
(Luna)
Yeah? I say go for it!
(Usagi)
Watch me! I'll become
the best!
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"Protect the Children's
Dreams: Friendship through
Anime."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.