Thank you everyone, for
giving me the courage
to never give up.
Evil being!
I am Princess Serenity!
In the name of the Moon,
I will now seal you away
forever!
So, this is the Dark
Kingdom's lair...
Ami...
Rei...
Mako...
Minako...
I'll do my best
until the very end.
"Usagi's Eternal Wish:
A Brand New Life."
So, you're finally
here...
I will personally seek
to it that you will go
straight to hell.
Huh?
Ah!
Ahhhh!
Welcome, Princess. You
did good to get this far.
I commend you for that.
You're Queen Beryl?
Yes. The one and
only, in the flesh.
Endymion.
Make yourself useful.
Kill the Princess.
As you wish.
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Useless.
Even with the Silver
Crystal, you're still
inexperienced as a
princess. You won't be
able to dispel Queen
Metalia's dark energy
from within Endymion's
body.
(evil laughter)
Stop you futile efforts
and hand over the Silver
Crystal like a good girl.
(forceful grunt)
(gasp)
Ah!
Sailor Moon...
(gasp)
Die!
(scared screams)
(painful screaming)
(evil laughter)
Ahhh!
Mamoru...
Hey, Bun-head.
Ahhhh!
Mamoru...
Ahhh!
(struggling breaths)
Ahhhh!
(evil laughter)
Very soon the entire sun
will be consumed by Darkness.
And finally, Queen Metalia
will be resurrected.
(struggling grunts)
You can stop that
now, Endymion.
Cut off the
Princess's head.
Now.
It's no use.
Once Queen Metalia is
resurrected and back
among us. She will have
the strength to unleash
the Silver Crystal's full
power, and she will fill
this world with Dark energy
forever!
Everything you and your
friends have fought to
protect, will become
meaningless!
(upset gasp)
Ahhhhh!
(struggling breaths)
(painful grunts)
We made sure the dark
energy seeped inside
every pore of Endymion's
body.
You'll need to come
up with more than
that to defeat him.
(painful grunts)
Please, stop.
Sailor Moon!
Stop it.
Ahhhh!
Die!
Stop this now!
Please, try to
remember. It's me,
Princess Serenity.
Long ago we pledged
our love to each other.
I am Serenity of the
Moon Kingdom.
Anybody who dares to
defy the Dark Kingdom
must die!
You've been poisoned by
bad energy that's made
you cruel. But kindness
still beats in your heart.
(conflicted grunts)
I don't want this.
Please don't force
me to fight you.
Please.
What?! What is that?!
(painful scream)
What happened?
Who am I?
I can't remember
anything!
I'm all alone!
No, you're not.
I'm here for you.
Huh?
You're not alone.
I'll always be
with you.
(surprised gasp)
Mamoru! No!
Usagi...
(surprised gasp)
Thank you.
Mamoru...
You're back!
You'll pay for
this Princess!
I cannot and will not
forgive you for once
again trying to take
Endymion away from me!
(attacking yell)
(throwing grunt)
(painful grunt)
Mamoru!
(painful whimpers)
Endymion!
Why must you protect
that little girl? If you
had chosen me, you'd now
be ruling as king of both
the Moon and the Earth!
What's happening?!
Mamoru! Don't die!
Why? Why is his rose
able to defeat me?
(painful grunt)
Is it his energy?
Is the power of Endymion's
love for that girl so strong
that it could destroy my
whole body?
(painful grunt)
I refuse...
I refuse to
believe that.
Please wake up.
Mamoru...
Leave now. Get out
of here quickly.
Huh?
Go back to being an
ordinary girl without
any worries.
Find yourself a
really cool boyfriend.
Nobody's cooler
than you, Mamoru.
(gasp)
Mamoru?
Mamoru!
(crying)
Sailor Moon!
(painful grunt)
Queen Metalia, I beg
of you, please grant
me your energy...
...with enough power to
crush that despicable girl!
Please Queen Metalia,
I will do anything!
As you wish...
The time has come to
instill hatred and greed
into all living creatures
in the universe.
Queen Beryl! Eliminate
all beings who attempt to
resist, and turn the world
into complete darkness!
Ah!
(painful screams)
I'm sorry, but I
can't kiss you.
Rei, Ami, Mako, Minako,
all of them died without
having a chance to kiss
the boys they liked.
Right now, nothing would
make me happier than
kissing you, but I can't
I'm sorry, Mamoru.
But I'm not going to
run away. I still have
something left to do.
Watch over me.
I'll do my best.
(evil chuckle)
At long last, all the
dark energy is mine!
I will now rule
the entire world!
(evil laugh)
You'e here, you
little irritant.
(chuckle)
I'll finish you
off, this time.
(attacking growl)
Princess!
Die!
(shocked gasp)
This is it. The
world is coming
to an end.
Queen Metalia's Dark
energy has been
unleashed upon us!
Wait! Luna!
Out of my way! I
have to go to the
D-Point now!
What for? It won't do
any good! There's nothing
more we're able to do!
Don't you think I
know that already?
But if we don't somehow
stop Usagi. She's going
to release the power
of the Silver Crystal!
And if she does that,
you know she'll die!
Like the way Queen
Serenity did!
I know that! But there's
no other way left to
save the world now!
Don't do it, Usagi!
You must not release
the power of the Silver
Crystal!
If you do, you'll
be gone forever!
(attacking yell)
Moon Healing!
(attacking grunt)
Escalation!
(angry yell)
(powerful grunt)
Tell me, why are you
so determined to
defeat me?
You dream of a lovely
future that will never
come to pass. One day,
you will realize that
this world is already
filled of ugliness and
filth!
You're wrong. I
believe in it! I
have faith!
Faith in what?
Everlasting love?
Indestructible
friendships?!
(amused laugh)
All of it! I believe
in this world...
...and the Guardians
who fought for it.
You're a fool! There's
nothing worthwhile in
this putrid world for
anyone to believe in!
(attacking roar)
(struggling grunts)
Silver Crystal!
Please give me strength!
I need everyone's
combined faith in love
to fight for the world
we believe in!
Love is no laughing
matter, but you get a
happy feeling from it.
(giggle)
Stop saying I'm in
love with him! I just
feel bad for Yuichiro
and that's all.
So what if he already
has a girlfriend? I
think it's worth
giving it a shot!
It's all right. All
that matters is that
Alan and Katarina are
happy.
My friends...
I won't be sealed
away by the Silver
Crystal, now that all
the Dark energy's mine!
(forceful grunt)
Everyone, give me
all your strength!
Please!
Right now!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Jupiter Power!
Venus Power!
Moon Prism Power!
(gasp)
What's that?!
(painful scream)
(horrified gasp)
Ahhhh!
Thank you, everyone.
When I wake up in the
morning, I feel the breeze
as it rustles the white
curtains in my bedroom.
My cuckoo clock tells
me it's seven a.m. Then
I hear my mom say, "C'mon
sleepy head, time to get
up or you'll be late!"
But it's so hard to wake
up. So I think to myself,
"Just three more minutes
and I'll get out of bed."
Of course, I'm late
for school every day.
Ms. Haruna makes me
stand out in the hall.
And all my tests are
covered with red marks.
On our way home from
school, we all stop for
some crepes, then go
check out the party dress
on display in the
store window.
It's those simple things
that made my life so
happy and fun.
I wish...
...I wish I could
go back...
...to being just
a normal girl.
Ahhhh!
(screaming)
I'm going to be
late again!
Bye!
It's a miracle!
Not only did the dark
spots on the sun disappear,
but all of the girls have
been reincarnated.
It's sad.
I feel sorry for them.
Every single memory they
had of being together is
completely gone now.
That's okay.
Hm?
They always have the
chance to become
good friends again.
You're right!
(whining)
I guess I should
have studied a
little bit more.
Oh I hate you,
you stupid test!
Watch where you're
throwin' things,
Bunhead.
Thirty percent?
Looks to me like you'd
better study harder next
time, Bunhead.
How rude!
Jerk in his purple
pleated pants!
What a strange kid.
(chuckle)
Admit it. He's cool!
And pretty good
looking, to boot.
No way! He's just
a stuck-up jerk!
That's what you say
now, but how knows? You
might've just met your
soul-mate back there.
Ugh! Give me a break!
I know exactly what my
dream guy will look like!
You have a dream guy?
Yep! In my dream he always
comes to my rescue. And
although I don't know what
he looks like yet, I know
nobody in the world
is cooler than he is.
Sailor Moon is all
pumped up as we go
into a new story arc!
We finally return to
our peaceful lives, when
powerful new enemies
suddenly appear!
Seriously?
It'll be full of thrills,
and full of laughs.
Guess we'll just have to
go as far as we can go!
In your case, you've
gone too far already!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Moon Returns: The
Mysterious Aliens Appear."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.