The ski resort is having
a contest and the girl
with the right athletic
ability and elegance
earns the title "Moon
Princess?" Cool! But
how will I have a
chance to win if I'm
trapped in the freezing
snow?! Either way, I'd
better get out of here
before I catch a cold!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish you.
"The Snow, the Mountains,
Friendship and Monsters."
Hey! Let's go up to
the snow! C'mon!
I'll be fun!
And it says right here
that this weekend,
they're having this
great Moon Princess
contest up at
the ski resort!
That seems like an
odd coincidence.
Yeah it's perfect! A
contest like this one
is tailor-made for me
to win, don't you think?
Let me see!
Wow! So the contest
winner gets to be
crowned Moon Princess
at night, in front of
a big crowd of
people?!
(happy sigh)
Mmm. I can already
see myself there!
So is that
a yes?!
I'm good with all of
this, but I'm wondering
what Luna and Artemis
will think about it.
There's no need to
worry about that,
I'll just tell them
we're all going up
to the mountains
to do some serious
training!
I'm kinda surprised
you'd actually suggest
telling them that.
Why? It's the truth.
It's more like
stretching the
truth, but I'm sure
they'll believe it
coming from you.
Great! That means
all of us can go!
But how're we gonna
find a hotel vacancy
on such short notice?
I think I could
help you out with
that, Rei!
Yuichiro?!
My folks own a place
up there that's big
enough for all of
you to stay!
Whoa! We would so
appreciate that!
Sure!
Well then it's all
set! I'll take this
weekend off and then
I'll just-
Hold on! So does
that mean that you're
coming too?
Oh, is that
a problem?
No, that'll be
fine. Right, Rei?
Like they say, you
never know when you
might meet
your destiny.
(awkward laugh)
You mean, "By chance,
a meeting could be
your destiny." Right?
I'm not sure either
of those quotes would
really apply in this
case.
(annoyed groan)
(nervous sigh)
(evil chuckle)
I know that they'll
fall for this. Because
these girls are quite
predictable.
Are you sure?
Hm?
I think you might
be underestimating
these Sailor Guardians.
What?!
Perhaps that's the
reason all of your
previous attempts
have failed, you
tend to regard your
enemy's abilities
too lightly.
(annoyed growl)
Know thy enemy,
know thy self.
I believe that that
is the first rule of
battle, isn't that
right?
Just what I expected
you to say. After all
Endymion, you've been
helping Sailor Moon
for so long...
I'm sure you know
everything about
those Guardians.
But, I know
them too!
I will do whatever
is required to
defeat everyone of
those girls.
For you, Zoisite.
Hm...
Wow! How pretty!
I can't believe
we're actually
here.
I feel bad leaving
Luna and Artemis
behind.
They'll be fine,
besides I'm sure they'd
rather be curled up
somewhere warm.
There's nothing like
relaxing on a nice
warm kotatsu, right
Artemis?
Huh?
Aww. He looks so
peaceful there.
Why would anyone want
to pass up being here
to go train in the
freezing cold? Well,
good for them.
Whoa!
My parents are at our
Swiss chalet right now.
So please, make yourselves
right at home.
This place
is so huge.
Say...Since you're
so filthy rich! Uh- I
mean so well-to-do,
Why are you wasting
your time training
at our shrine?
I train so I can
become a better
person.
Oh, uh, right!
Become a better person
my butt. He just wants
to spend all day smelling
your hair.
Please go away!
(embarrassed laugh)
Well, why are we
just sitting here?
Let's go skiing!
Yeah!
Wow! Oh wow! Look
at all this snow!
This is so awesome!
This is perfect
weather for skiing!
That's for sure!
Wait a sec, where'd
Rei and Yuichiro go
anyway?
This area's flat as
a pancake. Let's all
go further up the
mountain, okay?
Uh! No thank,
I'll pass.
Maybe you'd better
go on ahead with
Yuichiro.
We'll be over at
the beginners'
slope practicing.
Yeah, we'll
be fine!
Hold on, Usagi.
Weren't you planning
on getting in on the
Moon Princess Contest?
That's being held
way up there on
the mountain. Up
at the top.
Huh?
What?!
Besides being good
looking, you also
need to be a good
skier or you won't
have a chance of
being named the
Moon Princess.
Are you kidding?
What'll you
now? Drop out?
You know it's alright
if you quit, then I'll
be crowned Moon Princess!
Hey wait! I'll go!
After all, the real
Moon Princess should
win this thing!
Do you see anyone
that might be her?
No. Not yet.
Give it time. With
the monster power that
I've endowed upon you,
you should have no
trouble uncovering
Sailor Moon's true
identity.
Go on. Get to work.
Leave it to me,
Master Kunzite.
(evil chuckle)
Lo-Lo-look at that.
I-I sure hope this
isn't where I'm
s'posed to try
to ski...
Nah, this is nothing
compared to how steep
it is up at the top.
Huh! Ugh...
(pageant chatter)
All of these
ladies must be
crazy!
Welcome to all you lady
contestants! The Fourth
Annual Moon Princess
Contest will begin in
just a moment!
Tonight, our very
first princess is
here to help guide
you down the course.
Moonlight Slope's very
own ski instructor,
Miss Saeko Yamamoto!
And now here are
the contest rules.
Whichever of you
deemed by the judges
to be the fastest and
most graceful skier to
cross the finish line
of the Moonlight Course
will be crowned Moon
Princess.
Even though you'll be
racing in the dark,
the course is quite well
lit-so there's no danger.
(scared gulp)
Ready, set, start!
(scared whimper)
Wahh! Okay, that's
it! I quit!
Usagi, you can't fall
this far behind in
the race!
Ahhhh!
(screaming)
That's the way
to ski, Usagi!
You can do it
if you try!
(giggling)
(evil chuckle)
This ski course will
be their one way
ticket to hell. Hah!
Huh?
(leaping grunt)
(falling screams)
I thought I sensed an
evil aura just now!
Can't be! There's
no way a monster
would ever be up
here!
Ahh!
Huh?! Usagi!
Wahh! I can't
slow down!
(scared screaming)
Not bad, Usagi! But I'm
the one who's gonna
win this race!
(panic scream)
(screaming)
Hmm. Well it looks like
one of those two skiers
is the real Moon Princess,
Sailor Moon.
(screaming)
Hmph!
Sailor Moon!
Usagi! You've got to
slow down or you're
gonna get hurt!
Ahh! If I could I
would've done that
by now!
How are you supposed
to stop these things?!
Hah!
(panic scream)
(gasp)
Uh-Usagi! Start
skiing a lot faster.
But Rei! I've got no
control at all here!
Wait, that sure sounded
like an avalanche! That
must mean Rei's in trouble!
(panic scream)
Just keep going!
Time to get
serious! Hah!
Blizzar!
What's happening?!
Mommy!
Hey Rei! It's
me, Yuichiro!
Don't you worry
Rei! I'll save you!
You shall not pass!
I could swear I
just heard a
voice back there!
Very impressive,
princess! Now let's
see if you can escape
this!
Bliz! Bliz!
(screaming)
I gotcha!
Huh?
What should we do?
There's something
weird going on here.
Could this be the
work of a monster?
(struggling grunts)
Uh, Rei. Are
you all right?
No! Not
exactly! Now come
on! We need to climb
up this snowbank and
get out of here!
(struggling grunt)
That's not working.
Why don't we just
wait here for someone
to rescue us?
What if no one shows
up until after we've
been turned into
ski-sicles?!
You've got to
suck it up and
tough it out!
Hm?
Aww, I bet by now
someone else has
been crowned as
Moon Princess.
Probably. Thanks to
me saving a certain
someone, I missed
my chance!
Sorry...
Tuxedo Mask...
Oh, I'm sorry
Rei, I...
That used to be
Tuxedo Mask's right?
Uh-huh...
When I'm sad and I
listen to it, it
kinda helps to take
away my sadness.
Hmm...
Sorry! I didn't mean
to brag or anything.
I was just trying to
keep things positive.
Y'know trying to
change the mood
here...
I hope I didn't
hurt your feelings
by bringing him up.
There's no reason to
think that. It really
doesn't bother me
anymore.
Oh, but I thought.
Really, I'm totally
fine with the fact
that Mamoru. I mean
Tuxedo Mask, isn't
going to be my guy.
I mean let's face
it, he went and
risked his life to
save your life.
That proves he
really likes you!
Oh Rei...
But now hear me out
Usagi, if you don't
have a life filled
with happiness with
Mamoru. Count on
this, I'll punish
you!
(acknowledge laugh)
But speaking of
punishment, first
we've got to defeat
those Dark Kingdom
guys and bring
peace to the
world.
Yeah, you're right.
Whoa! That's right!
What was that about?
I just figured out that
with your Fire Soul, we
could probably get out
of here right now!
Whoa! That's right!
Hey, why didn't you
think of that sooner!
When it comes to
coming up with ideas
there's just no hope
for you!
I just came
up with one!
Okay you're right.
Let's transform!
Mars Power!
Is that you Rei?!
Huh?
It is you! Thank
goodness, you're
alive!
Oh, uh, Yuichiro!
This has gotta be
a miracle of love!
This is a safe way
out! C'mon, let's
go ladies!
Not so fast!
Wha?!
It's Miss Yamamoto?!
Ha ha ha! I
am Blizzar.
And I've been ordered
to eliminate Sailor
Moon!
I'm sure this is
the Dark Kingdom
at work!
They must've turned
her into a monster!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Prepare to die!
Whu-huh-wha?
You mean me?!
With your looks,
athletic ability
and your elegance,
you must be the
real Moon Princess!
Oh, so you think
that too, huh?
You're awfully
honest for a
monster.
What?! No way, y'mean
you really are Sailor
Moon?!
You've got it
all wrong!
Silence! My judgment
has never been wrong!
Blizzar!
I will protect Rei!
(shivering)
Uhhhh...
Poor Yuichiro!
Forget about him!
Now's our chance!
Transform!
You're even colder
than the snow is, Rei.
Hurry up and do it!
Okay! Moon
Prism Power
Make Up!
Mars Power
I don't believe this!
So you're both Sailor
Guardians?!
We can't forgive you
for trapping us in
this ice! Don't you
know that it's really
not good for young
ladies to let their
tummies get cold!
How dare you freeze
my Yuichiro into a
statue! You're gonna
pay for what you've
done, Monster!
Hmph!
In the name of
the Moon. I'll
punish you!
In the name
of Mars, I'll
chastise you!
Enough of your talk!
Blizzar!
(panic screams)
Fire!
Soul!
Time to finish you!
Huh?
Oh my god!
Tuxedo Mask!
Good evening,
Pretty Guardians.
Nice to see you.
Endymion?!
I'll handle these
girls once and
for all.
Blizzar, stand
aside and watch.
Prepare to die,
Sailor Moon!
(scared squeals)
Ahhh!
I won't miss
next time.
So what now?
Tuxedo Mask! Have
you really forgotten
who we are?!
You used to be on
our side, remember?
You've always fought
to protect Sailor
Moon! Because you
loved her so much!
He can't remember.
I'm begging you,
try to think back
to that time!
Huh?
Blizzar!
(gasps)
(evil laugh)
Huh?
Why'd you stop
me, Endymion?!
Sailor Moon!
Now's your
chance!
Right!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
(painful screams)
Refresh!
Hunh! My time is too
valuable to defeat you
fools right now! So,
farewell ladies.
We will meet again...
Tuxedo Mask, I will
find a way to get
you back, I promise.
You're such an
idiot, Yuichiro.
Always risking your
life to save me.
(chuckle)
Thank you.
Whu-huh?!
What am I doing here?
You finally woke up!
Oh thank goodness!
You're safe Rei!
Yeah. After you got hit
the Pretty Guardians showed
up and they rescued everyone
of us!
Oh I see, well I'm
sorry I wasn't up to
the job, but I did try.
Hey! What are you
talking about! You
acted so cool and
brave back there!
Huh?!
Didn't he, Rei?
(chuckle)
Yeah, you did!
Well I'm glad
to hear that!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
(laughing)
There you are!
Where have you
all been?!
You know we've been
worried sick about
you guys!
I'm just glad you're
safe! If it ends well,
all's well!
Uh, shouldn't that
be, "All's well that
ends well", Minako?
Hmph!
I had an awful time.
Usagi's such a klutz.
She almost got us
all killed.
What?! Aw, c'mon we
had fun! We had a chat
that strengthened our
friendship! Right?
Me? A fried of
yours?! We pigs
fly!
Wahh! Stop being
so mean, Rei!
The skating rink, where
people zoom around like
rays of light!
You're not doing much
zooming on your butt.
Such elegant
skating costumes!
A fancy costume won't
make you a good skater.
My performance has
you enchanted!
I'm just waiting
to see wipe out.
That's enough from
you! Leave me alone!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Paired with a Monster:
Mako the Ice Skating Queen."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.