[Sailor Moon]
What?! Someone's
using beautiful music
for an evil plot?!
And trying to take
away a grown-up's
right to find love??
That's unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon,
and now in the name of the moon,
I will punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
and some people might say
I'm a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange cat
named Luna gave me a special
brooch that transformed me into
a guardian in a sailor uniform.
and told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggle]
[Usagi]
Protect the Melody of Love:
Usagi Plays Cupid!
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
Ahh!
Ooohhh.
[Queen Beryl]
So, this music.
stole the energy
of that plant!
Exactly, Queen Beryl!
The music contains
subliminal ultrasonic
waves that siphoned
off its energy.
The humans who listen to
it will suffer the same
fate as this plant.
Interesting.
Proceed.
Yes, ma'am.
Kyurene!
Go plant the ultrasonic
waves from this tape
into the music that
humans listen to.
As you wish, sir.
♪ [Piano Jazz] ♪
Naru, this song's
great! Wow!
I know, right?
This one is my favorite.
Me, too! So this is jazz, huh?
I never thought I'd like it!
[Usagi]
You're so
mature, Naru!
Yup! If there's anything
you don't understand
about it, just ask me.
Uh, sure,
if you say so.
[Usagi]
Hmm.
Yusuke Amade, huh?
He's so cool!
I bet he's a
sophisticated
older man!
I'd sure love to
date him one day!
Egh, yeah, but what are
the chances of that?
And I'm not sure
he'd say yes.
This is it.
Today's the day I
tell her how I feel.
[sinister chuckle]
This tape will infect all
the audio recorded here,
just like a virus.
All the music they record
from now on will contain
energy-draining subliminal
ultrasonic waves!
[chuckle]
Ah!
Oh!
Ah! There it is!
I can't believe that
I almost forgot this!
Yusuke would have
been very upset!
Akiko?
Huh?
Mr. Amade's
downstairs right now.
He's in the lobby.
Okay, I'll
head down.
He didn't have to
come all the way down
here in the rain...
Ugh.
[Akiko]
Yusuke!
Huh?
Look at you! You're soaked!
Didn't you bring an
umbrella with you?!
I know, you were just caught
up in the moment, dreaming
up a new song, right?
Yeah. Kinda.
Here's your demo.
I think it's fantastic.
We should meet next week
to discuss recording it
for release.
Sure, uh.
Listen. Today is your
birthday, right?
It is!
I totally forgot!
Akiko!
We've got a big
problem with the mix!
What? Again?!
[sigh] Sorry, I have
to take care of this.
Sometimes they can't
find the "on" switch.
Here.
And take my umbrella!
It's the pink one. 'kay?
It's by the front door.
One more thing! See if
you can come up with a
great title by next week.
Make me proud!
If you'd paid more attention,
you would have seen it
already has a title.
"A Waltz for Akiko".
[sigh/chuckle]
[Usagi]
Ugh, all this rain is
just so depressing!
Well, April showers
bring May flowers,
right?
Well. Hope the flowers
appreciate it.
Meow!
All right, I'll see you
at school tomorrow!
Yep! 'Bye, 'bye!
NEW! SAILOR V: THE GAME
[Usagi]
Oh! The new Sailor V game!
Let's stop in for bit.
No way. You can't go into
an arcade at this hour!
You have school tomorrow!
What's the big deal?
I'll be quick!
Ugh...
Huh?
[running]
Watch out!
Huh?
Waugh!
Hm? [gasp]
[sobs]
My new clothes are
all soaked now!
Hey, you!
Grrr!
D'aahhhh!
Huh?
Help! Someone!
Please! Please, don't kill me!
Spare me! Please!
Uh, oh-kay?
What are you talking about?!
I'm not going to kill you!
What, seriously?!
Someone is really
after you?!
Yeah, and you probably
won't believe this.
I can barely believe
it myself, but...
What is it?
The thing that's
after me...
It's a monster!
A monster?!
Yeah.
Huh?
[squeaking bats]
[terrified]
Yaaaggh!
Ah! Augh!
[uneasy breath]
It must have been
a hallucination.
It had to be!
Heh heh. sorry to
bother you with it.
Anyway, I'll let you go.
Huh?!
I'm working a gig at
the jazz club just
down the street.
What? A jazz club?
Oh! I almost forgot!
For your dry cleaning.
I'm sorry, I don't have
any money on me right now.
But here, you can contact
me at this number later.
Okay... Yusuke Amade--
[gasp]
Wait, you're Yusuke Amade?!
See ya!
Uh--!
That was him!
The Yusuke Amade
from the CD that
Naru played for me!
Never mind that now, Usagi!
You heard him, there's a
monster that's after him!
We have to help him!
Right! Plus it's a great
chance to take a peek
into the grown-up world!
We can't leave him alone!
Come on!
Sometimes I wonder if
she really gets it.
[Jadeite]
You fool! You still haven't
gotten the tape back?!
My humblest apologies.
I was very close to
retrieving it, but
somehow he got away.
No more excuses!
Sorry, sir!
Enough. Make sure the plan
proceeds as scheduled!
If you're unable to
get the tape back,
The next plan will
be to deal with you.
Yes, sir!
Sailor Moon!
[Usagi]
So this is a jazz club, huh?
I really doubt they'll
let a young girl like
you go inside.
Oh? Is that so...?
[Usagi]
Moon Power! Turn me
into a hot musician!
[giggle]
So what do you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
Don't I look like
a grown-up now?
But, I really doubt
they'll let an old cat
like you go inside.
Buh?!
♪ [Piano Jazz] ♪
Well, there he is.
Hm?
Hey! Quit your squirming around!
You're just supposed to be
neckwear, remember?!
Have you decided what
you'd like to order?
Huh?
Umm...
A soda float!
Ahh!
Hmm?!
I'm very sorry, ma'am,
but I'm afraid that we
don't serve that here.
Oh. Okay.
Then water's good!
Aah!
[uneasy shudder]
For an old guy, he
really looks pretty good
when he plays the piano.
♪ [song finishes] ♪
[applauding]
Usagi, look!
Huh?
Aahh!
He's gone!
Oh! Hey Yusuke!
Need a ride? My car's warming
up in the garage, so meet me
down there in a bit.
I wrote that song
especially for her.
Maybe she's a little slow
on the uptake, but still...
[squeaking bats]
Huh?
Uwahh!
AAAHHHHH!
Luna! Did you
hear that?!
Let's go!
Right!
Hah.
Can't leave any witnesses.
Guess I'll have to kill you!
[Usagi]
Leave him alone!
Ahh!
Yusuke!
Are you all right?!
Ngh. She took it away.
My tape.
Tape?
"A Waltz for Akiko"?
[Luna]
Usagi, the monster is going to
use that tape for something
evil, I'm sure of it!
Waaagh!
[Usagi]
Uh, you think maybe you
could slow down a little?!
[shriek]
[Yusuke]
I won't let anyone have
that tape! No one!
Even if it is a monster!
Boy, you sure
are worked up!
That's because this isn't
just any demo tape!
I know! It's got the
song that you wrote
for Akiko on it!
Uh... How'd you
know that?!
Well, you may not know it
by looking at me, but I
really am quite grown up!
[exasperated]
Ugh...
And I was able
to figure it
out on my own!
It's just a crush.
It's ridiculous,
At my age.
Age doesn't
have anything
to do with it!
Even old guys like
you have a right
to fall in love!
Thank you.
I think.
[Yusuke]
Wait, why are you so
eager to help me chase
down a monster, anyway?
Because I am a
champion of justice!
Especially for those
who are in love!
Ah, youth.
It's wasted on the young.
[Usagi]
There! Right there!
Now the rain's stopped and the
clouds are gone, we can see her!
That's good!
Really? Are you sure it
landed on that building?
Yes, I'm positive!
This isn't good.
That's the place
where Akiko works!
What?!
[Kyurene]
[chuckle] That's
right. sleep now.
And when you awaken
and begin recording
music here once more,
every single track will
contain subliminal
ultrasonic waves.
Akiko!
Uh!
Mrowr!
Stop right there!
Ugh! Damn you!
Mrah?!
Give me the tape!
Hold on!
Huh?
That tape! That can't
be the demo I made!
Huh??
Give it to me now!
Yahh!
You okay?!
I just fell on my butt!
What do you think?!
[waking]
Uhh...
Aahhh!
Aah!
[frightened shivers]
If you value this woman's life,
then you'll hand the tape over
to me right now!
Akiko!
No fair!
Hurry it up!
Aggh!
Yusuke...
All right, then.
Here!
Ah!
Let go of her,
you monster!
Mrowwr!
Why, you!
It's all over now!
Just face it and give up!
Go, Usagi!
Mm!
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
Huh?!
I am the pretty Guardian,
Who fights for love
and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
I won't let you use beautiful
music for your evil plot!
I bet that Haydn,
the father of music,
would be really
mad, too!
Huh?!
But Bach's the
father of music!
Don't be a know-it-all;
you're making me look bad!
...Anyway,
And now, in the name of
the moon, I'll punish you!
Ha ha!
Haaa!
Waagh!
Whooaa!
Ha ha ha ha!
This is bad!
She's firing
ultrasonic waves!
And what're they?!
Oh, I get it!
It's a sound!
Die!
Yah!
Huaaahh!
Ha! How do you like
getting a double dose of
your own sound waves, huh?
Now finish her
off, Usagi!
Moon Tiara Action!
Yaaggghhh!!
[Akiko]
What were you thinking, Yusuke?!
What if you'd hurt your hand?
You might not've been able
to play the piano ever again!
Yes, I know that.
However, the truth is
if something bad were
ever to happen to you,
I would never be
able to play the
piano again, either.
What?
Yusuke...
Akiko's lucky to have
someone like Yusuke,
who'd do anything to
save the woman he loves.
[Naru]
Usagi, did you hear
what happened?!
Oh, it's just so horrible!
Yusuke Amade got married!
[Usagi]
Yeah, I heard about that.
Aw! It's so sad!
And I had such a huge
crush on him, too!
I know! He's such a sweet
guy, and so brave, too!
Wait, what?!
You talk like
you know him
or something!
Ha ha ha ha!
that's because I do!
Right, Yusuke?
[Usagi]
Give me your paw and
spin around, Luna!
[Luna]
I'm not your pet
dog, you know!
[Usagi]
I'm gonna become a huge star
once I win the talent show!
But I'll need more than
just my good looks.
[Luna]
You don't say.
[Usagi]
Do you like "Cutie Usagi"
as my stage name?
[Luna]
Oh, boy.
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi Learns Her Lesson:
Becoming a Star is Hard Work"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.