Endymion...Mother...
I remember everything.
Kunzite! We'll show you
that things don't always
work the way you planned!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name
of the moon!
We'll punish you!
Tuxedo Mask, tell
me where you are!
Wake up, Usagi!
It's urgent!
My dear Tuxedo
Mask, I love you!
Usagi!
This is important! Sailor
Venus and Artemis have
finally discovered the
entryway into the Dark
Kingdom's hideout!
What?! Are you serious?!
"Usagi's Awakening: A
Message from the
Distant Past."
This is the place,
everyone.
It looks that way.
Great work, Sailor
Venus.
C'mon!
What's this?
Let's check it out!
What's that energy?
(struggling grunts)
(evil chuckle)
I wish I could give you
a grand tour of the Dark
Kingdom, but at the present
time we're not quite ready
to welcome all of you.
But there's a fun place
I'd like to take you
to, instead.
Stop messing with us!
Supreme!
Thunder!
Sailor Moon! If you
willingly hand over the
Silver Crystal, I shall
spare your life!
Oh really, is that right?
Well if you tell me what
happened to Tuxedo Mask,
then maybe I won't have
to punish you.
Enough! I've had
it with all of you!
I'm sending you to
the Multi-Dimensional
Chaos World!
What's the Multi-
Dimensional Chaos World?
It might be prehistoric
Africa during the age
of the dinosaurs, or it
might be medieval Europe
during an era of war,
bloodshed and bubonic
plague.
Whoa! Those totally suck.
I don't want to go to
either of those worlds.
I'll pass!
(forceful grunt)
Ahhh!
Now I'll take the
Silver Crystal!
(reaching grunts)
No!
Ahhh!
Where am I?
What is this place?
This is what's left of
the Silver Millennium. In
the distant past, it was the
glorious land of the Gods.
Silver Millennium?
Who are you?
I am the incarnation of the
Moon Goddess Selene, here
to deliver you a message
from the distant past.
My name is Queen Serenity.
I am queen of the Silver
Millennium. And I am also
your mother.
What?! My mother?! How
could that be possible?
I don't understand what
you're saying.
I put Luna and Artemis
into cold sleep and then
awakened them so they
could watch over all of
you. I've been waiting
a very long time for
this moment.
(astonished gasp)
We are a race of long-
lived beings born on the
Moon. We protect the sacred
stone, the "Legendary Silver
Crystal", handed down in
the Moon's royal family.
Our mission is to watch
over the Earth and help
it advance. Try to
remember Serenity, open
your mind, and remember
the time when you were
a Moon Princess.
You would often spend
many happy hours gazing out
at the Earth, daydreaming
of what life would be like
being surrounded by the
wind and the trees of
the blue planet. And then,
one day you found love.
Princess Serenity!
(startled gasp)
Prince Endymion!
I apologize for
arriving so late.
I've been waiting
for you.
A terrible thing
has happened.
(gasp)
It seems that many of
my people have been
brainwashed by a woman
named Beryl.
Beryl?
This woman has been
possessed by an evil
energy called Metalia.
And as a result. She has
convinced many humans
that in order to live
longer lives, they must
take over the Moon.
Who's there?!
Huh?!
I'll see you
later at the ball!
Hurry back, Endymion.
What happened to
the others?!
Don't know. Looks like
we'll have to find the
hideout ourselves!
Where are we?!
It's the Arctic!
Princess...
Would you do
me the honor?
Why are you
wearing a mask?
A bitter war is about
to get underway any
day now...
between my people on
Earth and your people.
I will become your enemy.
It wouldn't be good for
either of us if people
knew I was here.
So please forgive
my disguise.
You?! My enemy?
Listen to me carefully.
Metalia is not human.
She is a being of pure
evil energy. And Beryl
is a sorceress. She is
using Metalia's power in
an attempt to conquer both
the Earth and the Moon.
Unless I do something,
the Moon Kingdom will
be destroyed.
I'm convinced the only
way to stop this war is
to eliminate Metalia, and
wipe out her evil energy.
That should put an
end to Beryl's plans.
I'm going to need you
to help, Serenity. Please
believe me, we don't have
any time to waste.
Yes.
Serenity...
I love you,
Endymion.
(attack yell)
It's terrible!
Everybody run for
your lives!
The people of Earth
are attacking us!
(attacking roar)
Bubble!
Spray!
Fire!
Soul!
Supreme!
Thunder!
Crescent!
Beam!
(shocked gasp)
(deathly screams)
(attacking yell)
(evil laughter)
From this day forth, I
shall rule both the
Earth and the Moon!
I will not tolerate
any opposition!
Beloved Queen Metalia,
at this very moment, our
own Dark Kingdom is born!
(triumphant laugh)
Sailor Moon!
(fearful gasp)
So you must be
Princess Serenity.
(scared gasp)
Say goodbye to
your pretty face!
Hah! Take this!
(painful yell)
What's this?
Now that I have your
attention, listen to me!
I will not let you lay
a finger on the Princess!
Endymion!
Why are you protecting
this girl? What loyalty
can you have for the Moon?
You are the Prince of the
Earth. Marry me and you
will be King of both the
Moon and the Earth!
No, Beryl. Don't you see
what's happened? Metalia's
evil energy has totally
consumed you!
Come to your senses!
Free your heart from
evil!
Silence you fool or
I will kill the both
of you!
(evil growl)
(painful scream)
Don't go, Endymion!
Serenity! Stay back!
Endymion, don't
leave me!
Get out of here!
Serenity!
(painful screams)
(scared gasps)
Serenity!
Princess Serenity!
(evil laugh)
She's dead! The Moon
Princess is dead!
(evil laughter)
Serenity...
Queen Serenity, don't!
If you release the Silver
Crystal's full power,
you will die!
My life doesn't matter.
Not when the peace of
the Moon and the Earth
is at stake.
Moon Healing
Escalation!
What?!
(painful roar)
Queen Metalia!
(painful screams)
Curse you, Queen
Serenity!
Don't give up.
You have to stay
strong, Artemis!
I'm alright. But what
about you, Luna. Are
you getting tired out?
Mm. I'm fine. I have
no intention of dying
until we find that
hideout!
Is that?!
We did it! At last we've
finally found the entry
portal to the Dark
Kingdom's hideout!
We have to tell
the others!
Sorry, but you're
way too late.
(fearful gasp)
Luna...
Artemis...
Yes?!
The Silver Crystal can
bring peace into the
world when used by
someone with a pure heart.
But, when it is used
by someone with an
evil heart,
it immediately becomes
a frightening weapon.
That's enough, please
don't talk anymore!
With the power of the
Silver Crystal, I was
able to seal away Metalia.
However, there's no telling
when she'll return
once again.
That's why I need to tell
you about the Moon Stick.
Only those with royal
blood are able to use it.
So in the future, if Metalia
is able to break free from
her suspended animation...
...Entrust this stick to
Princess Serenity, so that
she can protect the peace
of the world.
Yes.
Princess Serenity, and
all the other Sailor
Guardians as well, may
your future lives on
Earth be filled with
love, kindness and hope.
This is my final wish.
Live in peace
and happiness.
Queen Serenity!
(screaming)
Queen Serenity...
So that's
what happened.
It all makes
sense now.
Now we know why we
were chosen as Sailor
Guardians to protect
this planet.
Yes.
Thank you, mother.
Help!
(painful scream)
(startled gasp)
(attacking yell)
Ahhh!
Luna!
Artemis! No!
Sailor...
We're not going to
let you hurt them
anymore!
Sailor Moon, but how
did you?! I sent you
away to the Multi-
dimensional Chaos World!
Well too bad that
things didn't work
out the way you
planned.
But thanks to you,
we've regained
all our memories
of the past!
We'd like to
show you...
...how very
grateful we are!
Argh! Don't be condescending
to me, you presumptuous
dress-up dolls!
Return Tuxedo Mask. I
mean, Endymion. You have
no right to keep him!
(evil chuckle)
I'd be willing to let
him go if you'd just hand
over the Silver Crystal!
Hah!
(fearful gasp)
(attacking roar)
(attacking growl)
(painful screams)
Sailor Moon!
You're even more deranged
than I'd ever realized!
Unforgivable!
Hmph! It is you who are
deranged if you think your
silly attacks could possibly
work here in my world!
(attacking yell)
(painful screams)
We need to put our
powers together to
protect Sailor Moon!
Let's do it girls!
Venus Power!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Jupiter Power!
(attacking yell)
(painful grunts)
Stop it!
Even if you went out right
now and bought us the finest
haute-couture, trend-setting
designs as replacements.
I can't forgive you
for trying to shred
our Sailor Guardian
outfits!
In the name
of the moon...
I'll punish you!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
(startled gasp)
I am Kunzite! A proud
member of the Dark
Kingdom's Four Kings
of Heaven!
You can't make me
yell out 'Refresh'
ever!
(attacking yell)
What?!
(surprised grunt)
Impossible!
To be defeated by
my own weapon!
Oh, Zoisite!
Help guide me to the
world where your soul
is in limbo! I'm coming
my love!
Sailor Moon's power
is just incredible!
Even greater now.
Are you going to
be all right, Luna?
I'm okay, Usagi. I mean
Sailor Moon. No, you're
Serenity, aren't you?
The Dark Kingdom's
hideout is the D Point
located in the Arctic
Circle!
You're going to have
to hurry there before
the dark spots on the
sun spread!
There isn't
much time left.
Okay, we'll storm the
Dark Kingdom immediately!
Right, everybody!
Right!
Now, in the name
of the moon...
We'll punish you!
A powerful evil energy is
about to be resurrected!
The time for our final
battle is here!
Curse you impudent
girls! I will not let
you interfere with my
plans! Die!
Silver Crystal, please!
Please! Give us strength!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Death of the Sailor
Guardians: The Tragic
Final Battle."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.