[Sailor Moon]
Whether it's Einstein,
Hawking, or Newton,
gifted minds are here to better
mankind! I won't allow them to
fall into the hands of evil!
I am Sailor Moon, and
in the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
[Usagi]
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-old
middle school student.
I'm a Cancer with blood type O,
My birthstone is a pearl,
And I'm a bit of a klutz.
Some people might say I'm
also a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange
cat named Luna appeared,
turned me into a guardian
in a sailor uniform,
and told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggle]
[Usagi]
Is the Girl Genius a monster?
The Brainwashing
Cram School of Horror!
[Jadeite]
So many human
schoolchildren,
have been made completely
miserable because they're
forced to study.
Yes, I've heard that
parents desperate for
their children to succeed
can be even harder on
their kids than our
monsters would be.
That's right, my Queen.
Some parents will go to
almost unimaginable lengths
in order to get their children
into a top-rated university.
From pre-school to high school,
they'll stop at nothing to see
that their children get the
best education.
I see. And what happens
after they leave that
first-rate university?
Who knows?
But we can
use this.
Hmm. Proceed.
Yes, ma'am!
[Usagi] [hysterical]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[laughter]
Usagi!
Oh! Hey, mom!
You should look at this!
It's so funny!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[both laughing]
But now isn't the
time to be laughing!
The practice test you took.
Well? How did it go?
The results don't come
out until tomorrow.
But I wouldn't
worry about that!
[nervous]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Look, Usagi.
I don't ask for
much from you when
it comes to school.
Just please,
try not to
fail, okay?
Ghk-gk-gk!
Wahhhhh!
If there's a top of the class,
there has to be a bottom, too!
So I'm actually helping by
making those kids look good!
There's no one in the entire
world that suffers more...
than kids who get
scolded for bad grades!
Waahhhh!
Honestly, Usagi, you
sure do come up with
some bizarre arguments.
Your grades would make
anyone burst into tears.
[little whines]
Stop whining, Usagi.
Education is
important, you know.
Easy for you to say.
It must be nice
to be a cat.
What are you
talking about?
[sigh] I wish I were a
cat with nothing to do.
Give me a break. I have
all kinds of things to do;
I have a princess to locate!
Ack!
Hey! You're just
reading manga!
Hrmmh!
Hmm!
[sigh]
If only you could
share the passion
you have for manga
with something more
meaningful like helping
me find the Princess.
Awww, come on!
Your destiny's to
find the princess and
battle your foes.
Accept it!
Responsibilities
won't vanish because
you ignore them.
I never asked
for this!
And besides, when you
say "foes," what exactly
do you mean by that?
You know, evil monsters
not of this world.
Yeah, but what are they?
To tell the truth,
I don't know what
they are.
I just know they
need to be stopped.
Mmh.
[video game title]
Sailor V, the Game!
Codename Zer Zero Nine
One, this is Luna.
Passphrase: "The
rabbit on the moon is
pounding rice cakes."
[digital filter]
The moon's rice
cakes are sticky.
And they puff up
when you toast
them, as well.
Passphrase accepted.
Have you found the
princess?
Not yet, and
I don't have
any leads.
I see.
Sailor Moon is proving to
be much less reliable than
I expected her to be.
Now, now,
don't complain.
Sorry.
By the way, I've sensed
a new, mysterious
energy lately.
Hmmm.
It's coming
from her.
Hm. She might be a monster
sent by the enemy.
I agree.
Speed up your
investigation.
Right.
Ugh, Ami Mizuno got
the best grade again?!
That girl is a genius!
Well, as expected,
Ami Mizuno ranked first
in our whole school.
Actually, she's
number one in the
whole country!
Huh? The country??
And it's
rumored...
Aahh!
that when they measured
her IQ, it was discovered
to be over nine thousand!
Whoa. So she's like
a super-genius, then!
Mm-hmm!
For the last time,
Umino, stop
sneaking up on us!!
Dah!
Oh! There she is now!
Huh?
I hear that she's been
taking classes at the
Crystal Seminar.
Oh, isn't that the
new cram school they
built in Juban?
My mom says it costs
a whole lot of money
to go there.
Ami's mom is a
doctor, apparently.
Eh?
She's rich
enough to
afford it.
Yeah, but she
actually has a
scholarship there, so
she's going for free.
Just between us,
I don't really
like her.
She thinks she's all that
cause she's so smart.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, she
sure keeps
to herself.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
[giggling]
Hmmm.
Gyah!
[forced, nervous laughter]
Yep! It sure is.
I wish I were one
of the smart kids.
They have it so easy!
My mom is gonna kill
me for my grade.
Usagi! You're gonna have to
sign up for that cram school!
And pay for it yourself!
Ah...
Oh. isn't that her?
Uh?
Whaa??
Ah!
Kitty?
I can definitely sense
a mysterious energy.
[happy sound]
[gasp]
Focus!
[giggle] You're so soft!
If I didn't live in a
condo, I'd take you home.
I'd love to have a
cute cat like you!
[laugh]
Luna!
Mm?
Meow!
Sorry for that!
I hope she didn't
scare you too much!
[nervous laugh]
Is she your cat?
Yep!
When she dropped down
like that, I thought
she might be an angel!
Mm? What?
Luna an angel?
What a cute thing to say!
[Usagi]
You're Ami Mizuno from
Class Five, right?
I'm Usagi Tsukino
from Class One.
Nice to meet you!
[Ami]
You, too.
And this little
furball's named Luna.
Luna? That means
"moon" in some
languages, right?
Wow, you really
are a genius!
You're the very first
person who knew that
right away.
[giggle]
If we became friends, then
maybe she could help teach
me how to ace my tests!
[whisper]
Usagi!
Mm?
She might actually be
a monster sent by the
enemy. Be careful.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Don't be silly!
What's so
funny, Usagi?
[nervous laugh]
Nothing!
Nothing at all!
Hey, listen, Ami,
you want to go
play some video
games with me?
Okay, but I've
never played one.
Don't worry about
that. I can teach
you everything
you need to know!
This should help earn
me some brownie points!
He he he he he!
Oh, she's fine.
You're just imagining
things, Luna!
Nggh!
Yaahh!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Well the buttons are
clearly sticking today.
But that's how it's done.
Well why don't you
give it a try anyway?
It's really fun!
Okay. But it
looks hard.
Mm! Another smart
observation from the
genius! It is hard!
You'd be lucky to get
five hundred points
on your first try!
Hey, you're
pretty good!
Really?
Wow! Great!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Uhh...
[arcade goer]
Whoa!
Oh, wow.
[arcade goer]
Amazing, she got the
all-time high score!
Ah!
Hey, Usagi!
Glad you're here!
Oh! Hi!
Wow!
Incredible!
Yeah, it sure
is, huh?
Oh, boy. So much
for my great plan.
Huh?
Oh, no! Look
at the time!
[crowd]
Whaa?!
Sorry, gotta go.
I'll be late for
my cram school!
I'm so sorry! I didn't
realize that you had
to go to there today.
I go everyday.
Egh!
Everyday?!
Studying's the only
thing I'm good at, so
I have to do my best.
Well, see you later.
It was fun!
'Bye!
It's like she's living in
a whole different world.
Oh, there you are.
Motoki!
Listen.
Sure!
Anything for you.
I think that friend of
yours might have dropped
this on her way out.
[sigh]
That's really
all you wanted?
Huh?
Huh? Oh, nothing!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I can hold on to
this for her.
Huh.
[chuckle] Foolish humans.
Studying so very hard.
You'll give me all of
your mental energy!
Sailor Moon!
Oh, no, I don't have my disk!
I wonder if I dropped it.
Oh well, it's not like I
use it very often anyway!
Miss Mizuno?
[gasp]
Yes?!
Please make sure you're
using your crystal disk.
It'll help you study
more effectively.
Remember, you're on a
scholarship, so you must
keep your grades up.
Sure.
[chuckle] I'm
expecting great
things from you.
Uh...
[sigh] When I use that disk,
I get the worst headaches.
It's easier just to
learn on my own.
Oh. It says that if someone
uses this newly developed
"crystal disk" thing, they
can become a genius.
Is this the crystal disk
they're talking about?
You should be
careful, Usagi.
Huh? I'm just
returning her disk!
You worry too much.
Wait. You think you
can become a genius,
Bun Head?
You again?!
Would you please stop
creeping up on me?!
Whatever. But more
importantly, was that
cat just talking to you?
Eek!
Ee!
Mew!
That's impossible!
Everybody knows that
cats can't talk!
Don't be ridiculous!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
[panting]
Whew, that was close.
It would be bad if
he found out!
Uwah!
Huh?
I panicked and
forgot to give
this disk back!
Hrg! This is all that
stupid guy's fault!
Hold on, Usagi, let's
go to the school and
find a computer first!
Huh? What for?
I want to take a look
at what's on that disk.
You mean you think it's
something suspicious?
Look, I haven't had time to
learn about computers, so you'll
have to figure it out yourself!
[nervous laugh]
Ha ha ha! Of
course she can
use a computer!
Nowadays, everyone should
be able to use a computer.
Even you, Usagi.
Okay I get it.
[high pitched tone]
Ah ha! I knew it.
Oh, man, what is
that awful noise?!
Give us all your knowledge
and mental energy.
Offer it up to our great ruler!
And in doing so,
become our servant!
This is a program used
for brainwashing people!
No way!
Your friend really
is a monster!
[Usagi]
I still don't believe it.
But it's the truth, usagi.
Now come on, let's go!
Okay.
Moon Power! Make me look
like a doctor from the
university hospital!
Here goes nothing!
Everyone, step away
from your computers
right now!
[mindless moans]
[gasp]
What are you doing here?!
You can't just
interrupt everyone
while they're studying!
You really are an evil
monster, aren't you?!
Mm, I'm what now?
Don't play
dumb with me!
Quick! Transform
into Sailor Moon!
Moon Prism Power! Make Up!
Uh! No way...
Mf!
[gasp]
I am the master of knowledge,
and my name is Garoben!
And soon, I will gather all of
the mental energy generated
by this girl's genius brain
and then offer it up
to the great ruler!
Mwahahahahaha!
This means that Ami was
never a monster at all!
You hear that, you
suspicious cat?!
No kidding...
Let her go, you evil hag!
Gifted minds are here
to better mankind!
I won't allow them to fall
into the hands of evil!
I am the pretty guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
[chuckle] Your first question!
Hm?
is about the genius
Isaac Newton.
Answer me this: why do
apples fall from trees?
Seriously, that's the question?!
Don't ask me; go ask an apple!
You fail! That wrong
answer gets you this!
Wah!
Ha ha ha ha ha! Fool!
I know! A typhoon
knocked 'em down!
Gyah!
Luna!
Ugh! Come on! It's because
the Earth has gravity!
Fine! Because
Earth has gravity!
[little sobs]
Ugh. Now on to
question two.
Explain to me in fifty
words or less exactly
what gravity is!
Aw, come on,
that's impossible!
[zombie moans]
You'll be just like them
if you can't answer!
What?! No way!
I don't wanna be an
academic zombie!
Hmf. As for you.
Augh!
Offer up your genius
mental energy to me.
[struggling]
Huh?
It's not absorbing
her energy. But why?!
Wait, I know what must have
happened! You stopped using the
crystal disk, didn't you?
I did! Studying should be done
on your own. Using the disk
was like cheating. You jerk!
Curse your impudence!
Huh?! Hmm? And
what is this?
Huh?! That mark!
Oh! The strange energy
that I sensed was because
she's a Sailor Guardian!
Hah! No problem.
I'll just take
your entire brain!
Unh!
Heh. Prepare yourself!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[sinister laughter]
[Luna]
Ami!
Huh?
Here!
Quickly, shout out the words
"Mercury Power! Make Up!"
Mercury Power! Make Up!
Well, I guess that I was right
after all! Ami is the second
guardian, Sailor Mercury!
Ami?!
Haaa!
Use your Bubble
Spray attack! Now!
Bubble...
Spray!
Huh? What's happening!?
What's this!
Where did she go?
I'm so cold!
[shivering]
Huh?
Ooh! Damn it!
Huh?!
There you are!
[Sailor Mercury]
You fell for it!
Ah! Oh no!
Sailor Moon!
Now's your chance!
Right!
Huh?!
Moon Tiara Action!
Ahhh!
[waking moans]
Is everyone okay?
Am I?
That's right! You're the
second pretty guardian, and
your name is Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Mercury?
That's awesome!
[chuckle]
[Luna]
I'm sorry for mistaking
you for a monster.
[Ami]
Oh, it's okay.
[Usagi]
But I never guessed
you were one of us!
Things'll be better
than ever with you
here. Right, Luna?
That's
for sure!
Thank you!
[chuckle] Especially
when it comes to tests!
[Ami]
Usagi?
Yes?
I just wanted to say
again that it's been a
pleasure to meet you,
and I look forward to
fighting by your side.
I'm sure we'll
make a good team.
Uh, hehe! Uh,
I was gonna say
the same thing!
Ha ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha!
Oh wow. She's gonna be
better at this too.
What am I gonna do?
[Usagi]
Oh no! Time keeps
slipping away from me!
[Luna]
What's the matter, Usagi?
You seem really on edge lately.
[Usagi]
I just have way too much
to do! I can't waste any
second of the day!
Don't they say,
"Time is money, fall in
love while you can?"
[Luna]
Uh, not really.
[Usagi]
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi's Disaster: Beware of
the Clock of Confusion!"
The Moonlight is a
messenger of love.