Minako's boyfriend is
a handsome chap from
London. But what's
this?! A pretty lady
named Katarina likes
him too! It's a love
triangle! How awful!
Those Dark Kingdom
creeps are trying to
break the heart of a
young girl that's in
love. But I won't
stand by and let
that happen! I
am Sailor Moon!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
"Sailor Venus's Past:
Minako's Tragic Love"
Hmm, let's see...
Nothing here...
Not here either.
(sigh)
I wonder if...
Huh?
Sorry we're a
little late!
(whining)
I'm worn out!
So how'd it go?
Not one of the dumpling
places we checked out
had anything like an
entrance coming from
the Dark Kingdom.
Too bad. We've had
no luck either.
Somehow they continue
to keep sending Monsters
here one after another
from the Dark Kingdom.
There has to be an
entrance or portal
somewhere.
How'd things go
for you, Rei?
I've had no
hits at all.
We haven't found
anything that leads
to their lair.
I guess that
leaves Minako.
I'm so tired!
Usagi! Everyone here's
doing their best to help
out. Just suck it up!
I'm also starving!
When do we eat?!
Wait, didn't you
just eat a big meal
at the dumpling shop?
The three plates of
sweet dumplings and
two bowls of anmitsu
jelly were tasty!
But that was just
a snack! I'm hungry
again!
Hey everyone,
we're back!
How'd it go?
Not so great. We checked
every bathhouse in Tokyo,
but not one of them panned
out.
Well, thanks
anyway.
In that case, I
guess we'll call
it a night.
Sounds good.
I could use
some sleep.
Oh my gosh!
What's that?!
It can't be!
This has happened before!
Whaddya mean
before?
Those dark spots are
moving in the exact same
way they moved eons ago,
when the Moon Kingdom
was destroyed!
What?!
Once those dark spots
cover the entire sun,
then I will awaken
from my eternal sleep.
And that time
rapidly approaches.
All that's left is to
retrieve the Silver
Crystal, then at last
the world will be ours.
Good news. We will
have the Silver
Crystal shortly.
What?
I have found someone
who knows Sailor V's
human identity.
You have?
Yes, she is a police
officer in England who
works with Interpol.
What's even better is
this woman once thought
of Sailor V as if she
were her little sister.
That's good.
Now find a way to use
Sailor V's connection
with the Sailor Guardians
to eliminate them all.
Yes.
That noise.
What's going
on?
I can feel it. This
man possesses the same
energy wavelengths as
I do. Endymion, you
shall become my
successor!
(painful grunts)
(scared gasp)
What's the matter?
It was Tuxedo
Mask again...
So you had another
nightmare?
I feel for what
you're going
through.
But if all you do is
worry, you'll wind up
sick. You need to make
sure that you're eating
and sleeping enough.
Mm-hmm.
Well at least I'm
pretty sure that I'm
eating enough.
Mmm, great, now
I don't have to
worry.
(giggle)
Seeing the moonlight
sure makes these
dumplings taste
delicious!
Now I'm happy!
Ahhh!
Sorry, Usagi!
(choking grunts)
So Artemis,
what's going on?
There's big trouble!
It's Minako, she's
disappeared!
(choking grunts)
A little
help here.
Maybe she went out
to try to find the
entryway to the
Dark Kingdom?
Waaatter!
If she had, we
would've gone
together.
Water!
Any idea where
she could've gone?
Just one. She got a
call from this woman
named Katarina. Maybe
that phone call had
something to do with
her disappearance.
Ahh! I finally
got it down!
Nice job.
Minako...
Or should I say,
Sailor V. I was so
happily surprised
when I heard that
you were alive.
Why didn't you call
me and let me know
you were okay?
(emotional grunt)
I was so proud when
I heard that you're
active as Sailor V.
Thank you.
Well I want to help
you. So then, you're
a member of the Sailor
Guardians?
I'd sure like to
meet them.
Katarina. How's
Alan doing?
Oh, he's doing fine.
See? We took
this recently.
(sad sigh)
I know Alan misses
you, too.
Oh Katarina, I see
you still wear that
necklace I gave you
so long ago.
Why of course, I
treasure it. It was
such a special birthday
gift. Anyway I really
do want to help you.
And I'd love to meet
the Sailor Guardians
as well.
Katarina, you're
like the big sister
I never had.
And I know meeting the
Guardians is something
you'd enjoy. But I don't
want to expose you to
that kind of danger!
I'm so glad I saw
you. I must go.
Goodbye Katarina!
Minako wait!
Come back!
Master Kunzite...
It doesn't appear
that pushing her
any further will
work.
Let's turn you into
the monster Papillon,
so you can attack her!
Ahh!
Hah!
Papillon!
Alan...
Minako...
Alan!
A butterfly
in winter?
Damn!
You have died once!
It would've been much
better if you had
stayed dead!
A monster!
All right!
Venus Power!
Make Up!
What?! Minako's
really Sailor
Venus?!
Crescent Beam!
That won't work!
Huh?!
I know everything
about your techniques,
Sailor Venus. Now have
a taste of mine!
Ahhhh!
You see, I know
all your weaknesses!
Ahhahh!
That necklace.
Katarina, is that
you? But why?
(painful screams)
Now tell me the
identity of the
other Guardians!
Please don't do
this, Katarina.
Sailor Venus!
(shocked gasp)
Oh no! That monster
seems really strong!
(angry growl)
Over there! We'll
use that boat to
escape!
What?!
What are you thinking,
Luna?! I don't have the
slightest clue about how
to drive a boat!
Then just turn
yourself into a
real sailor!
Oh! That's right!
Okay!
Moon Power! Turn me
into a cute, seafaring
sailor!
(attacking growls)
(struggling screams)
Now's our chance!
Let's get out of
here!
Hm!
So how'd you figure
out where to find me?
Well we searched every
hotel's database for
one that had a guest
named Katarina.
That's how we found
out she was staying
at the Harborview
Hill Hotel.
Where'd she go?
I'll get her!
So hey, what now?
Ahhh!
No! She's found us!
Sailor Moon!
I'm gonna give this
boat everything it's
got!
Looks like
we got away!
Nice job, Usagi.
Thanks.
(giggle)
You can count on
me! Oh...
Hey Usagi! Steer the
boat toward that big
deserted ship that's
anchored over there!
Hm?
Aye, aye, Luna!
Ahh! I made it!
Now let's get
moving!
Says the cat that
rode the whole way
up on my head!
Everyone, we
have to hide!
They're here
somewhere!
It sure looks like
there's no one on
board.
Still we all need
to be careful and
stay alert. By now
that monster knows
that we escaped
to this ship.
Sailor Venus, how
does that monster
know so much about
you? What's your
connection with
this Katarina
person?
Hey Luna! Maybe she
doesn't really wanna
talk about it right
now.
No...
Huh?
It's okay...
The whole thing
happened just
six months ago.
I found myself in London,
I was following up on
information that there
was a Dark Kingdom monster
somewhere in England.
That's when I met a
young man named Alan,
and I fell in love.
Soon after that...
I somehow found
myself at a crime
scene.
Huh?
(evil laugh)
(shocked gasp)
(crying)
(painful screaming)
Huh?
Ahhhh!
That was amazing!
She's amazing!
Thanks!
(giggling)
From that moment on,
Katarina and I became
the best of friends.
She gave me good
advice, and helped
me with my studies.
We saw the sights
together, always
having fun.
I loved her like she
was a big sister. And
she always cared, and
looked after me as if
I was her little
sister.
Katarina! Alan!
C'mon you two!
Of course, I introduced
her to Alan. The three
of us always had fun
together.
Then one day
something happened.
Hm?
(shocked gasp)
Ahhhh!
Minako!
(painful wincing)
Huh?
Alan!
Alan! Minako was
in there! She's...
She's what?!
What happened?!
Don't worry.
I'm here.
I'll always be
here for you.
That's when I discovered
the real truth. I had
never realized that Alan
and Katarina were actually
in love...
I decided to leave and
disappeared from their
lives. I thought that
remaining dead to them
would probably be the
best thing for their
happiness.
So that's why you
returned to Japan.
You decided to forget
those sad memories by
devoting yourself to
fighting evil.
No!
Huh?
That's so unfair!
I'm so sad for you!
Thanks, Usagi.
Hm?!
So were those tears
of yours, tears of
joy? Brought on by
the thought of me
killing you?
Don't worry, I'll
make sure this
becomes the sight
of your graves!
I'm in a really bad
mood right now. If I
were you, I'd get out!
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
I see, so you are
Sailor Moon, huh?
At this point, I
don't care if you
do know who I am!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish
you!
Just what are you
blabbering about?!
Haah!
I refuse to run away
today! I won't let you
get away with trying to
break the heart of a
young girl that's
in love!
Die!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Ahhahh!
Ahhh!
Stop! Please
don't hurt her!
Huh?
It's my fault! I'm
the real reason she
was turned into a
monster!
Katarina knew that I
was a Sailor Guardian.
That's why the Dark
Kingdom used her to
do their bidding.
She's not to blame
for all this!
But you loved her like
a big sister and then
she betrayed you!
Please save her
for me!
How can you want to
be nice to her?! She
stole the guy that
you loved!
He chose her!
She's the person
Alan fell in love
with.
Agh...
Please help her.
All right!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Refresh!
Katarina!
Minako...
I'm sorry...
I had no idea about
your feelings for him.
I thought you were still
just a child. Forgive me.
So what's going on?
What happened to
Minako?
It looks like
she's sad.
Yeah, we should probably
go over there and try to
cheer her up or something.
It's better if
we just leave
her alone.
Huh?!
She'll be fine.
Minako is a lot
more mature than
any of us.
This is how
it should be.
He chose you,
Katarina.
As long as you're
both happy, that's
what counts. That's
what matters.
That's what matters.
I've had it!
What's wrong, Usagi?
Everyone keeps calling
me names like dummy,
klutz and stupid!
Well, at least
they're honest.
Right? That's what
I- Uh! Luna, how
could you?!
Hey! Honesty is
the best policy!
Cat thinks she's
so smart!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Usagi Abandoned: The
Falling Out of the
Sailor Guardians."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.