I don't believe it!
That jerk was Tuxedo
Mask all along?! And
now he's fighting
Zoisite right in front
of me. Ahh! Just what
the heck is going on
here?! Never mind,
what's important right
now is for me to fight
evil!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish
you.
Zoisite decided to
disguise himself as
me so he could lure
Tuxedo Mask into a
trap! When we tried
to stop him, another
member of the Dark
Kingdom named Kunzite
appeared and sealed us
inside a barrier! Then
that bad guy Zoisite
succeeded in wounding
Tuxedo Mask, leaving
us in serious trouble!
Just when all of us
thought our luck had
really run out, Sailor
Venus, the fifth
Guardian, surprised
everyone by showing
up and saving us! I
wonder if she could
be the Moon Princess
we're looking for?
"The Shining Silver
Crystal: The Moon
Princess Appears"
Sailor V, I mean
Sailor Venus...
Wait a minute,
could you be the
Moon Princess?
I'm not. But like all
of you, I'm a Guardian
dedicated to protecting
the princess.
I don't believe it!
My hero Sailor V is
right here in front
of me!
It's really nice
to meet you, all
of you.
Nice to meet you!
Hi there!
Glad to have
you here.
This is great!
While it is nice that
all of you finally met,
I need you to realize
we're in the middle of
an important
investigation here.
We'll share the
details with you
tomorrow night
when we meet at
the Hikawa Shrine.
See you later, Luna.
Right Artemis,
see you then!
Bye everyone! Later!
Well, there
she goes.
She sure doesn't
waste any time.
Yeah, and
she's so cool!
Queen Beryl...
Why did you order
us to retreat from
battle?
We were so close to
getting the Rainbow
Crystals and finishing
off Tuxedo Mask!
Orders have been
given from the
Great Ruler.
And what are
those orders?
You are not to kill
Tuxedo Mask. Instead,
you will bring him to
me alive.
But why do that?!
I don't need to
explain myself
to you!
Understood.
Damn it!
Why couldn't I protect
her?! I failed her!
Sailor Moon...
You have a very
lovely place...
How did you
find me?!
Actually finding you
was quite an easy
task! Once I learned
your true identity.
(chuckle)
Mamoru...
So what do
you want?
Hm! Well, now that
we know each other,
I think the timing's
right for us to get
things settled
once and for all.
Go on, I'm
listening.
Good.
We both want possession of
those Rainbow Crystals,
so I suggest a battle
between us with the
winner taking all.
How's that sound?
Hmph! Sounds fair,
I accept your
challenge, Zoisite.
Nice. That's a good
boy. Now as for where,
how about that wonderful
structure in the bay
area, the Starlight
Tower?
Yeah, that'll work.
Very well, the
Starlight Tower
it is. I'll see
you there today
at 5 o'clock,
until then Mamoru.
All right Ms. Haruna,
bye now! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's just great!
Ms. Haruna goes and
gives me detention
on a day when I've
got everybody waiting
for me! I can already
hear what Rei's going
to say to me...
You're such a worthless
blockhead! You're a
dimwit!
Hey, I know
those pants.
(painful grunts)
Hey there! How
ya doin' guy?!
What's wrong?
Oh hey, Bun-head.
You're sure cheerful
today...
Well excuse me then!
It just so happens
that I'm a cheerful
person all of the time!
(chuckle)
I hope you'll always
be that way. Take
care, okay?
Huh?
Whoa. What's with
him? He isn't acting
like himself.
(gasp)
Blood? How'd
that get there?!
Wait a sec...
Could he be hurt
in some way?
Ahhh!
Bun-head?!
What was
that about?!
You startled me.
What are you up to?
I dunno, I just got
really worried about
you, so I decided to
follow you.
Worried about me?
I know that you're
hurt! You need to go
see a doctor before
it gets even worse!
Hmph. Look, that's
none of your business.
Well, maybe
not, but...
So just bug off!
Well you didn't
have to be so
rude about it!
Hey wait! We
need to have
a talk!
(annoyed sigh)
It's show time.
(startled grunt)
Zoisite!
Oh no, what's
happening?!
Huh?!
It's all red!
You idiot! Why did
you follow me?!
I'm sorry!
Usagi always shows up
late, but this is way
too late.
I called her but
she's not at home.
She wasn't at
school, either.
Something's wrong.
She's not answering
her communicator
either.
I don't have a
good feeling
about this.
Me either, let's
split up and find
her.
She's at the
Starlight Tower.
Huh?!
Who are you?
Who are we? Have you
already forgotten us?
Artemis! Then
you must be...
...Sailor Venus?
Yes, my real name
is Minako Aino.
Based on what we've
been able to figure,
the enemy's involved
in some activity at
the Starlight Tower.
The fact that we
can't reach Usagi's
communicator proves
it. She must of
somehow figured out
the enemy's plan and
gone after them alone,
at Starlight Tower.
If Usagi were as
good as you say,
my job sure would
be much easier.
C'mon. We've got to
help her by getting
to the Starlight
Tower!
Right!
Welcome...
I'll place the Rainbow
Crystals that I have
right here. Now, let's
see yours.
Before I do that,
you need to let
this girl go.
Only if you put your
crystals with mine,
first.
Fine!
(hysterical laughter)
What's so funny?
You are, I'm laughing
at how foolish you
actually are!
Kunzite!
Now all the Rainbow
Crystals are ours!
You-You lied to me!
Ah-ah, better stay where
you are Mamoru, or your
cute friend will be
turned into ashes.
Zoisite, you
handle to rest.
Sure...
Uh, Zoisite?! Why's
Mamoru fighting
Zoisite?
Ugh! How dare you do
this to my face, you
worm. I'll get you yet!
Mamoru Chiba! If
you want to get the
Rainbow Crystals back,
come to the top floor
observation deck!
The Rainbow Crystals?
What would Mamoru want
with the Rainbow Crystals?
Ahh, allow me to
give you an icy
cold taste of fear.
Watch out!
Ahhh!
Keep running!
His shoulder's hurt!
Tuxedo Mask got his
shoulder hurt yesterday
too. No, it couldn't be!
(gasp)
I can't take anymore
of this! It's making
me crazy!
We've gotta get
to that elevator!
Sailor Moon!
Oh c'mon!
Open! Open!
Whew! We're
safe now!
I wouldn't
count on it.
Huh?
Ew, gross!
What is all
this?!
It's no use,
we're trapped in
this thing...
So this is the
Starlight Tower,
huh?
Wow, that's one
huge building.
(gasp)
Usagi and Mamoru
are both trapped
in the elevator!
What?!
They're trapped
up there?!
Not good! All the
doors are sealed
shut!
You mean there's no
way to get inside?
What now?
Jupiter, my guardian
planet! Bring forth a
storm! Summon the
clouds! And bring
down your thunder!
Supreme!
Thunder!
We'll force our
way in! C'mon!
Uh, right!
Hmph! Pesky ants.
We now possess all the
Rainbow Crystals and
we've got Mamoru as
well. If we can destroy
the Sailor Guardians
while they're here...
(chuckle)
That would be our
revenge for that
cut cheek of yours.
This elevator sure
is taking its time.
Feels like we've been
in here for days.
Say, I was wondering
why do you want those
crystals? Oh! Sorry!
I understand if you
don't want to talk
about it.
It's got to do
with my past.
If I have all those
Rainbow Crystals,
they'll help me find
the Legendary Silver
Crystal. Then I can
figure out my past
once and for all.
He even knows about
the Silver Crystal?!
When I was six, my
parents and I were in
a bad car accident
and I lost them.
I'm sorry, but neither
of the parents survived.
But miraculously, their
only son, Mamoru, did
manage to pull
through.
Who am I?
I dunno.
I can't remember
what happened to
me, I can't remember
anything!
I've never been
able to remember
what happened.
Since then, I've
been having the
same dream over
and over.
The Silver Crystal.
Find the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
I want to have my
memories back. And
I know the Silver
Crystal will help.
I don't know why
I told you all
of that.
You know what? Before
I used to think you
were the worst person
in the whole wide world.
Hm?!
But not anymore...
Now you're the
second worst.
(chuckle)
Thank you.
Huh?!
Tuxedo Mask? No, he
can't be him! That's
just impossible!
Yes, Sailor Guardians.
This will be the perfect
place for you to die.
Huh?!
What's going on?!
Sailor Venus!
Why'd it stop?
(evil chuckle)
Goodbye, you two.
What's that?!
What should I do?!
If I transform into
Sailor Moon now,
he'll know who I am!
But if I don't,
we're both going
to die!
I guess I've got
no other choice!
Moon Prism Power
Make up!
(gasp)
Huh?!
Sailor Moon?!
Mm-hm!
I'll report to Queen
Beryl that Mamoru
Chiba perished in
an accident.
You call that
an accident?!
Well here's what I
think! You're going
to pay big time for
all the suffering
you've caused,
especially for trying
to kill us with your
dirty tricks!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
Hmph! Well Sailor
Moon, I'll get rid
of you and Tuxedo
Mask!
What are you saying?
What do you mean
Tuxedo Mask? He's
not even here!
Yes I am!
It can't be?!
(gasp)
Uh, no way!
Looks to me like
you'd better study
harder next time,
Bun-head.
Sailor Moon, crying
isn't going to solve
any of your problems.
Your little Miss
Bun-head, here, is
getting all puffy
because she's being
ignored by you!
Tonight, it's you
who saved me.
If you keep on eating
like that, then you
might just turn into
a pork bun.
Farewell, Sailor Moon!
You really are
Tuxedo Mask.
You were very brave
today, Sailor Moon.
Now you can leave
the rest to me.
You can't! I know
you're hurt!
Please! Get out
of here quickly!
Sailor Moon, I
will protect you.
Oh Tuxedo Mask...
Playtime is over,
children. Now we will
finally settle this,
Tuxedo Mask.
Very well, but first
you must promise me that
you'll leave Sailor
Moon out of all this.
Why of course. We'll do
this fair and square.
(evil chuckle)
All fair and square.
Die!
(fearful gasp)
(painful grunt)
(shocked gasp)
No! Don't die!
Are you all right,
Sailor Moon?
Stop looking like
you're about to cry.
I'm so glad that
you're safe.
Tuxedo Mask!
We're too late.
No! Not Tuxedo Mask!
Tuxedo Mask.
Hm?
Wha?!
(surprised gasp)
The Silver Crystal!
It is! The Legendary
Silver Crystal!
Sailor Moon!
Wha-What's
going on?
It's her! The
Moon Princess!
She has awakened.
Why do these bad things
have to happen one after
another? Now, because of
me, Mamoru is...
C'mon Usagi!
I can't take it anymore!
I don't want to see people
I care about getting hurt
because of me!
Usagi, pull yourself
together! You're the
princess. You have to
accept your destiny
and fight!
Luna...
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Returning Memory:
Usagi and Mamoru's Past"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.