Sometimes girls just
can't help falling in
love, even when their
intuition tells them it's
wrong. And they'll stand
by their love, no matter
how tough things get.
When a girl is on the
path of true love, I
won't let anyone get in
her way!
I am Sailor Moon...
...and in the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino! It
may not look it, but
I'm actually a
superhero!
I use a special brooch to
transform and fight evil!
You know me as...
...the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice. I am Sailor
Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius, Ami
Mizuno, who's Sailor
Mercury...!
...And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic, who's
Sailor Mars. Both of them
seem to have it a little
more together than I
do...
But, oh well, guess I
just gotta do my best!
[giggling]
Naru's Tears: Nephrite
Dies For Love
I hate to see you so sad like
this. Naru, I think it would
be best if you just forget
about him.
I can't.
Uh!
Even if he is a bad
person..I still love him.
Hm. What a dilemma...
Usagi... You have someone
you like, right?
Uh, me? Well.. Yeah, of
course!
So then, you should
understand exactly how
I'm feeling now.
Mm.
I don't understand...
Why did the Dark Crystal
react to Naru Osaka's
energy?
Is it the energy of her
love for me?
I won't let anyone
hurt Mr. Sanjoin!
[giggling]
Because I love him...I
love him with all my
heart.
Mmph! What nonsense.
Now that I think about
it, Sailor Moon knew that
girl quite well.
Which means Naru Osaka
most likely knows who
Sailor Moon really is.
[chuckling]
Watch out, Sailor Moon.
As I thought. So that's
the Dark Crystal, which
can determine where the
Silver Crystal's located.
Hmm...
The Dark Crystal is
reacting again...
...to the same girl.
Huh? I wonder if it's
possible that the Silver
Crystal could be inside
the body of a human...
It's not there.
I'm not getting a
reading. She doesn't
carry the crystal.
[gasping]
Mr. Sanjoin?
No. The man you know as
Masato Sanjoin does not
exist.
My real name
is Nephrite.
Uh--
I can't lie to you any
longer.
Huh?
Stay right where you are
and listen...
All right.
You are a wonderful
girl...
...And thanks to you, for
the very first time, I've
learned what love
actually is.
This emotion doesn't
exist in the evil
organization that
I work for.
In my world, we betray
our allies. We kill each
other for personal gain.
I thought that was just
how life was. I never
expected it to be any
more than that.
But your love has
opened my eyes.
It's truly changed me.
I'm now thinking of
joining Sailor Moon
and her friends to fight
the evil organization.
That's why I need you
to tell me all you know
of Sailor Moon and how
to find her.
I really don't know
anything. I'm sorry.
Don't you believe me?
It's not that! I do
believe you!
I really do! But I just
don't know anything...
about her... honest.
I see... That's
unfortunate.
[gasping]
Please wait!
I want to help you,
Nephrite.
Now to watch and
wait. If she does know
Sailor Moon's identity,
then she'll contact
her sooner or later.
My, my.
So, what do we have here?
It seems he's fallen in
love with a human girl.
Master Zoisite...
Were you listening? You
heard what Nephrite said?
Heh, what a fool.
Let's take him out,
now.
Now hold on a second.
Remember Nephrite is a
powerful warrior.
We need a plan in
place before we
pursue him.
Let's begin by taking
that girl hostage, and
using her to lure him
out.
As you wish.
What should I do? I
wanna help him, but I
really don't know how
to find Sailor Moon.
Usagi! You have a phone
call.
Okay. Who could be
calling at this hour?
It's the middle of the
night.
[yawning]
Hello? Usagi speaking.
Mm?
Is anyone there?
Usagi...Sorry to bother
you this late...
Naru! What--
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do.
I'm so confused. You're
the only one I can talk
to about this.
So tell me, what
happened?
It's about Mr. Sanjoin.
He just came by right now.
And asked where he
could find Sailor Moon.
[gasping]
He was in such a hurry,
it seemed like he was in
trouble.
I feel so powerless,
there's nothing I could
do to help him.
Do you have any
idea where he is now?
[crying]
Naru, are you crying?
I'm fine. I shouldn't
have gotten you out of
bed. Just forget it.
But, Naru....
I'm all right now. Just
talking to you has calmed
me down. Thanks for
listening, Usagi.
You sure you're
okay?
Usagi...
Nephrite is keeping close
tabs on Naru, so he must
be up to something.
Come on, Usagi, pick
up the pace, we need
to hurry!
I don't have four legs
like you!
I'm going
on ahead!
All right,
be careful!
Whoa! What's
going on?!
Oh, I get it! A
monster's behind this!
You don't scare me!
All right where are you?
Show yourself! Come out!
Fine! That's it!
Moon Prism Power Make Up!
[chuckling]
Looks like my little
trick worked.
What?!
[gasping]
It's Nephrite!
So, Sailor Moon is
actually Usagi Tsukino!
Seeing is believing.
Oh no!
[chuckling]
Listen, please don't
tell anyone that I'm
Sailor Moon!
Let's just keep this
between you and me!
Please, I'm begging you!
But you've no reason
to hide your identity,
now.
I don't see things
quite the same way as
you! C'mon, pretty
please...!
No use worrying. You
won't be leaving here
alive.
[screaming]
I don't wanna die!
Somebody... help me.
Now, to end your life
once and for all!
Hm?
The beautiful Sailor Moon
will never suffer defeat
at the hands of evil.
Not while I'm
around.
Tuxedo Mask!
My hero!
Mm.
Mm!
[chuckling]
No! Get away!
Nephrite, help!
That voice...
What's wrong, Nephrite?
Seems I have other
matters to attend to.
I can attack you anytime
I want, now that I know
your true identity,
Sailor Moon.
So watch
your back!
What am I gonna do?
Luna's gonna be so
mad at me!
You're a smart girl,
I'm sure you'll figure
something out.
Farewell, Sailor Moon.
Thank you for coming to
save me.
I'm too late! I have
to inform the Sailor
Guardians immediately!
They want the Dark
Crystal in exchange for
Naru Osaka. This has got
to be the work of Zoisite.
What a fool. Why on earth
would I care what happens
to that girl?
Sailor Moon!
Nephrite better
get here quick.
Do you honestly think
he's going to come rescue
this human?
Hmph! Well,
if he doesn't, I guess
we'll be forced to
eliminate her.
The poor thing. She
looks so frightened.
[chuckling]
Hm?
[gasping]
Nephrite, you came!
Die!
Ha!
[grunting]
Did we get him?!
[gasping]
[grunting]
I've got a message
for you to deliver to
Zoisite. I'm not giving
up the Dark Crystal.
[panting]
Thank you, Nephrite...
for coming to save me.
Don't thank me. If you
didn't know me, this
wouldn't have happened.
In fact, I don't
even know why I
saved you.
Besides, I haven't
been honest. I've lied
to you this whole time.
And knowing myself,
I may continue to lie
to you.
That's okay with me.
As long as you always
remain by my side... I
can live with the lying.
[gasping]
Oh no! You've been
injured!
It's all right.
It's not all right.
This happened to you
because of me.
We have to hide from
those women, before they
find us again.
Come on,
follow me.
You'll need to take off
your jacket.
All right.
[grunting]
On 3rd Avenue, there's
this little place that
serves the best chocolate
parfait.
Chocolate
parfait?
Yeah, you like it?
Uh--sure, why
wouldn't I?
That's a lie...
Mm?!
A sweet lie to make
me believe that we have
something in common.
[grunting]
Thank you, Naru.
Anyway, I was wondering
if you'd like to go there
with me sometime.
I know it's kind of a
silly idea, but I've
dreamed of going there
with you.
To share a chocolate
parfait together.
Sounds good.
Let's do it.
You mean it?
You think I'm
lying to you.
Mm-mm.
I can't wait!
Oh, but will your evil
organization give you
a day off? Like, maybe
this Sunday?
Hm?
[chuckling]
Wow, I've never
seen you laugh like that.
[giggling]
How strange, what
brought that on?
Now I can't seem
to stop laughing.
[grunting]
[struggling]
Heh-ha!
[grunting]
[gasping]
What have you
done to him?!
You let your guard
down. Those thorns will
drain your energy until
you meet your death.
[giggling]
A fitting end
for a traitor.
If you don't want us
to kill the girl, too,
then hand over the Dark
Crystal.
You can have it.
Get out of here, now!
No!
Run away!
I won't!
[sobbing]
Go, you idiot!
[grunting]
No!
[struggling]
Fool. Do you really think
a pathetic human like you
could pull out those thorns?
[struggling]
Give it up! You have
to get out of here!
[struggling]
Just leave me.
You've done enough.
[struggling]
[gasping]
Impossible!
Nephrite, don't die!
Hold on, please!
[struggling]
[grunting]
I'm going to finish
both of you!
[gasping]
Now, die!
[trembling]
Huh?
Are you all
right, Naru?
[grunting]
[gasping]
Nephrite?!
Well done, you three.
The plan worked. The
Dark Crystal is ours.
I'm sure he wants to
die with the girl he
loves, but we can't wait.
Give him a good beating
to finish him off.
Damn you, Zoisite.
[shaking]
[chuckling]
This should be fun.
[grunting]
Run!
No...
Stop right there!
Hm?
How dare you mess with
two people who are in
love! That's truly
despicable!
The Sailor Guardians!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Douse yourself in
water and repent!
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
All right, we'll
deal with you, first!
Die!
[screaming]
[trembling]
Bubble...
...Spray!
Now's our chance!
What?!
Where'd they go?!
Fire!
Moon Tiara!
Soul!
...Action!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Nephrite, we're
safe now.
Sailor Moon...
Yes?
It looks like your
true identity will
remain a secret
after all.
[grunting]
[gasping]
No! Don't die!
[struggling]
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Don't think... we'll
be having... chocolate
parfait together.
[whimpering]
Please stay.
[grunting]
Looks like I've continued
to like to you until the
very end. Forgive me.
[crying]
No...
[struggling]
Thank you for being
part of my life.
[crying]
Nephrite, please
wake up.
[sobbing]
No, no! You can't go!
You promised that we
would have a chocolate
parfait together!
You can't just break
a promise! You can't!
[sobbing]
No!!!!
[crying]
Nephrite!
Luna! This is
my new friend, Makoto
Kino! But you can just
call her Mako!
She's so bi-i-g!...
She saved me when I
ran into some bad
guys. She's super-
strong!
You're a superhero!
How can you let someone
save you like that?
But the guy
Mako likes is being
targeted by a monster!
You're saying a new
enemy has appeared?!
Next time on
Sailor Moon, "Jupiter,
the Powerful Girl in
Love."
The moonlight
is a messenger of love.