What?! Motoki has
a girlfriend?!
Back off, Zoisite!
Anyone who gets in
the way of love
deserves to be
stomped into the
ground by a horse!
Oh, you have nothing
to do with it?
Well, I don't care!
Sailor Moon is
looking for a
boyfriend!
Hey! I'm Usagi
Tsukino!
You know me as the
Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
This job's not easy
by the way. We have
to find and protect
the Legendary Silver
Crystal before the
bad guys get it.
But in order to do
that, we need to
find the seven
Rainbow Crystals
and the people
holding them.
Pretty crazy, huh?
But now there are
four of us Sailor
Guardians, so I think
everything's gonna
work out just fine.
(giggles)
Total Chaos: The
Messy Love Rectangle.
For today, there's
only a ten percent
chance of rain in
the forecast.
Oh brother!
You can never
trust those
weather
forecasters!
I'd certainly call
this more than a
ten percent chance
of rain!
Darn it! Why don't
you watch where
you're going?!
Sorry...
If sorry resolved
things, we wouldn't
need police!
That voice...
Is that you,
Motoki?
Here, let me
help you up.
Thanks...
I'm sorry about that.
I had a lot of things
on my mind. I wasn't
watching.
You don't have an
umbrella. You're
going to get soaking
wet in this downpour.
Why not share mine
until it lets up?
His voice just
reminds me so much
of my former love.
Oh, if only we can
stay like this
forever!
Mako?
Huh?
Let's go.
Oh.. Uh...
Yeah!
I heard you're
a fabulous cook.
Is that true?
I guess...
That's cool. One
of these days
you'll have to make
me something.
I'd love to,
anytime!
I could clean your
place too! I'm
really good at it!
That would be
a huge help!
Here! Write down
your address and
phone number, and
list your favorite
foods as well!
Done. Mako,
you sure are
interesting.
(giggle)
Yeah, I get
that a lot.
Ah, I see hayashi
rice is your
favorite.
I wish the rain
hadn't stopped.
Huh?
(nervous laugh)
Sorry, Mako. I
have to drop by
the school for a
little while.
Sure, no
problem...
But I'm gonna come
over to your place
this Sunday and make
hayashi rice for you!
Gotta go!
Buh-Bye!
Uhh...
Looks like you and
that cute girl are
quite friendly.
Reika!
Mamoru was talking
about somebody having
a new girlfriend. I
guess he meant you.
Oh! Give me
a break.
(chuckle)
I'm just kidding.
I know. So, seeing
how you're dressed,
it appears you're
about to cancel
our date again.
I'm so sorry. I'm
going to be working
really late.
No worries. But
more importantly,
have you reached a
decision yet?
No, I'm still
working on it.
Take your time.
It's going to
affect the rest
of you're life,
so you want to
make sure you've
made the right
decision.
You're so sweet.
Thank you.
(gasp)
Hey you two!
What's up?
Oh, Mamoru! We
didn't see you
there!
(chuckle)
Sorry, gotta run!
Mamoru, can you do me
a favor and take my guy
out for some coffee?
I'll call you
later!
(sigh)
Something's
bothering you.
What's up?
It's Reika...
There's a possibility
she'll be going to
Africa to pursue her
research study.
Africa? What
kind of research
would require her
to move there?
It's pretty impressive
stuff! She's going to
be exploring the area
where all life on
earth supposedly
originated.
So now what's
the plan?
Not sure. She
can't make up
her mind yet.
I'm not talking
about her. What
do you want?!
Well, I want to tell
her to stay here with
me. But, I just can't
be that selfish and
get in the way
of her future.
That's so
like you.
Hey, by the way,
are you a big fan
of hayashi rice?
Sure, why do
you ask?
Because Mako said
she was gonna come
over to my place on
Sunday to make a
whole batch of it.
Why don't you come
by for a taste?
Mako? But she's
Usagi's friend.
I'm sure you're
aware that Usagi
has eyes for
you. Right?
Sure, but both
of them are
pretty cute.
But a minute ago
we were talking
about Reika. I got
the impression
you were hung
up on her.
I'm not about to
hook up with a
middle-school girl.
Hi there, sweetie!
They're cute but
you've got me all
wrong. I think of
Mako and Usagi as
being little
sisters to me.
Little
Sisters,
huh?
Oh, brother!
Motoki is in for
a rude awakening!
(chuckle)
Who's there?
Hey, good morning,
Motoki! It's Makoto
Kino. I'm here!
Just a-
Just a minute!
Hey Mako, what
brings you here?
Stand clear,
I'm coming in!
Uh, the place
is a mess.
No problem! Guys
don't clean up
a lot. Or in your
case... not at all.
And this is
pretty bad.
(attack yell)
Let's do this!
Huh?! Let's do
what now?
You know what!
Clean up this big
mess, of course!
Now, if I don't
do this in thirty
minutes, I'll be
late for school.
So, let's go!
Who's this girl
with you?
Oh her? Well,
that's Reika.
I'm guessing she's
not your sister.
No...
Ah! She must be
your girlfriend,
right?
Uh...
Yeah...
Ahhhhh!
It's unusual to
see you looking
so sad, Mako.
What's going on?
A depressed face
will give you
wrinkles!
Ha! Ha! Someone
broke your heart
again. Am I
right?
You picked the wrong
day to mess with me.
It was just
a joke.
Don't stress out.
Think of me as your
personal Cupid. I'm
here to fix it and
make it right!
I think it would
be a better idea
to work on your own
love issues first.
Luna!
Still maybe I can
help. Tell me the
name of the person
who broke your heart.
Motoki...
Ahhhh!
Do you really have
to be so shocked?
Yes, of course I
do. I can't believe
it. This is so
upsetting.
Because I'm...
I'm in love with
Motoki too!
What?! You
like him too?
How could you
do this? How
could you?!
But, I thought you
were in love with
Tuxedo Mask?
Yes, I love him
too! I've fallen in
love with them both!
Well, you have
to choose one!
Both of you stop and
think about it for a
moment. The guy gets
to choose too, it's
not a one-way
street.
Aha!
Oh boy, now
what?
If Mako had her heart
broken by Motoki,
that can really only
mean one thing.
Motoki has chosen
someone else to be
his girlfriend!
And that someone he
has chosen must be...
...cute
little me!
Wrong! It's
someone named
Reika.
What?! How can
that be?!
I can't take
it anymore...
Don't give up
so easily!
So what if he already
has a girlfriend. Even
if we get rejected, it's
worth giving it a shot.
But Mako...
Crying isn't going
to get you anywhere.
You're right! We're
Pretty Guardians
after all!
And if we don't
fight...
There's no
tomorrow!
Why do I get the
feeling there's no
tomorrow, no matter
what?
Let's do this!
And whoever wins,
no hard feelings,
right?
Yeah!
So, let's decide the
order of who goes
first by height.
This isn't exactly
gym class, you know!
Hey! What are you
girls up to.
Something we don't
need you for!
Bun-head and Bigfoot
together. Let me guess,
you're here to confess
you're love to Motoki.
Forget about him.
I'm saying this
for your own good.
What we're doing here
happens to be none
of your business!
Yeah, get lost!
I'm telling you the
truth. Motoki only
thinks of you as cute
little sisters to him
and really nothing
more than that.
Little sisters?
You're lying!
No, I'm not. If you
don't believe me, why
don't you go ask him
yourself, Bun-head?
I don't need you to
tell me what to do!
And I'm not Bun-head,
I'm Usagi Tsukino.
Get that into
your thick skull!
You walking
fashion disaster!
Whatever!
Motoki, where
are you?
Oh. Hey, Usagi.
Motoki's not here.
He's off 'til
tomorrow.
(annoyed sigh)
Do you know Motoki
already has a
girlfriend?
Yeah, so what?
Man, I'm way out of
touch on how middle-
schoolers think
these days.
Huh. But maybe, if
she decides to leave
to study abroad, you
might still have a
fighting chance.
What?! She's
going away?!
Give me details!
When is she
leaving?!
I shouldn't
have said
anything.
Guess I got
carried away!
Are next target is
this young lady.
A student at the
Azabu Institute of
Technology.
And she's quite
lovely too...
You're cruel,
Kunzite. How can
you suggest she is
more lovely than me?
Underneath she
is just an
ugly monster!
Shh! I'm kidding.
Don't let envy ruin
your beautiful face.
Look at me.
Go away!
This rose can't
compare with the
beauty I see in
your face.
Thank you,
my dear.
In return, I will
bring you the
Rainbow Crystal.
Sailor Moon!
I've come here to
encourage Reika
to study abroad.
But now that I'm
here. What can I
possibly say to her.
Tomorrow, let's
try raising the
temperature of the
specimen a bit more.
Yes, that would
be interesting.
See you tomorrow.
Right. Good
night.
That's her...
Excuse me.
Can we talk?
Oh, you were with
Motoki the other
day...
What did you want
to talk to me
about?
Are you planning
on going away
to study, Reika?
My! News travels
fast. Did Motoki
tell you that?
Please don't
avoid the
subject.
I don't know.
Huh?
I can't decide.
There's a professor
I'd like to learn
from and work with
in Africa, but I'm
having trouble
bringing myself to
leave Motoki...
But, if he tries
to stop me...
You'd better start
now and get your
priorities straight!
If you'd give it
all up for Motoki,
then I don't think
you're very serious
about your
profession!
You need to choose
one path! Study
abroad or love!
You can't have
it both ways.
I only came here
to convince her
to go to Africa!
The weight of this
bag is the weight
of my love. Heavy!
We take a
right here.
You know the way
pretty well, Mako.
I'll finally be in
Motoki's apartment.
How I've dreamed
of this!
Hello, Motoki.
Usagi, you look
amazing in that
apron.
Will you accept
my proposal to
become my bride?
It's rather
sudden...
Give me your
answer...
I just... I'm
not sure if I'm
ready to settle
down yet.
But for you, of
course I will.
Usagi...
Stop!
Well, at least we
know that's never
ever gonna happen.
Hey! Thanks for
dropping by,
you two!
C'mon in!
Wow! It's as tidy
as I'd imagined
it'd be!
Good-looking guys
keep their places
so neat!
(gasp)
An unfinished
cup of coffee.
Oh, Motoki's
manly scent!
Remember why
we're here.
Usagi...
I have to prepare
myself. I'm not
emotionally ready.
Aha! You're amazing,
Usagi. You prepare
yourself to get in
the zone emotionally,
even for cooking!
Huh?!
Let's get
started.
All right, let's
do this! Uh, what
do I do?
First, peel
the carrots.
I'm not really
a good peeler.
Then you can
dice up all
the onions.
I can't. They
make my eyes
water!
Then cook up
the rice.
I don't know how
to do that! I'm
taking a pass!
Some co-cook you
turned out to be!
I'm sorry!
Hello?
Reika!
Motoki...
I know it's taken
me a while, but I've
finally made up my mind
about going to Africa.
What? I couldn't
here what you said.
I've made my
decision. I want
to see you tonight.
Okay, I'll come
as soon as I can.
What?!
Girls, I'm very
sorry to have to
do this to you...
Well, don't keep
her waiting.
Hurry back!
You were
listening?
That was
dumb.
Could you watch
the place while
I'm away?
Thanks!
Ow! I just cut
my finger!
(sigh)
He's still not
back yet.
No wonder I haven't
seen them for hours.
They're still here!
Oh no! There
must be a Rainbow
Crystal close by!
Luna, is that you?
You both need
to transform now!
Great! First Motoki
leaves, and now
this! I've had it!
Yeah, who does he
think he is, leaving
two pretty girls
here alone to watch
his house! That's
no way to treat us!
Usagi...
I'm kidding!
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
Jupiter Power!
(giggle)
How very brave
of you.
But it's a wasted
effort. Now move
aside.
Ahh!!
What a
barbarian...
Zoi!
(gasp)
Ahhh!
Oh, how sweet!
You monster!
Well now, it takes
one to know one.
You're a monster
yourself. And I
mean the real you.
One of the Seven
Great Monsters.
I'm one of the
Seven Great
Monsters?
(chuckle)
That's correct.
Now pay close
attention.
Look into the
crystal...
Ahh!
I am Rikokeida!
No! We're
too late!
Is that really
Reika?!
Sailor Moon,
Sailor Jupiter,
you need to be
very careful!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights
for love and for
justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
Today we're not...
...the same as
usual!
We're ten thousand
volts of heartbreak-
power, looking for
a boyfriend!
Not you too, Mako...
In the name of
the moon...
I'll punish you!
Girls without
boyfriends are
pathetic!
Oh, yeah, well
it's your fault
for messing up
our chances!
Take this!
Watch out!
(chuckle)
The fifth Rainbow
Crystal belongs
to me.
Hey!
You're forever
butting in where
you're not wanted!
I'm not about to
let you have the
Rainbow Crystals.
Oh! It's my guy,
Tuxedo Mask!
Hey, aren't you
forgetting about
your guy, Motoki?
That's a little
complicated. Right
now I'm into Tuxedo
Mask!
Take that!
And that!
Ew, gross!
What are they?!
The foundation of all
life, including you,
originated from these
single-celled organisms.
Huh?!
So says the
single-celled
brain.
Jupiter, my guardian
planet, bring forth
a storm! Summon the
clouds and bring
down your thunder!
Supreme...
...Thunder!
Big Flask!
Ah!
She's collecting
my lightning!
(laughing)
C'mon let's go!
That was
too close!
She used the
lightning from
my Supreme Thunder
to attack us!
You dodged that one,
but there's still a
lot of lightning
power left!
Sailor Jupiter, do
something or we're
both gonna be fried!
I'm going to enjoy
destroying the
two of you.
Bubble...
...Spray!
What?!
Mercury!
And Mars!
Luckily we got
here in time.
It took us forever
to find you two.
Fire...
...Soul!
Show some respect
for your lab
equipment!
Stop wasting
resources meant
for good!
Shut up and take
her out already.
Mmm! You're
not the boss!
Hmph! Well, you've
been too boy-crazy
to be the boss.
Boy-crazy?!
Just do it
already!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Refresh!
Ha! Looks like
your monsters
been defeated!
It seems I've lost
as well. You may
take the Rainbow
Crystal.
(giggle)
Huh?
You're so naive that
you'd really believe
I'd give you the
Rainbow Crystal?!
Sooner or later,
I'll get you for
this, Zoisite!
Motoki!
Reika!
Passengers who have
not yet checked-in
for Flight Six-Fifty-
Eight to San Francisco,
please hurry to
the terminal.
Reika, I really don't
want to say goodbye
to you.
I know. I promise
to write you.
And I'll be waiting
for you to come back.
Motoki...
Well, I'd
better go...
Take care...
(crying whines)
So sad! Maybe we
should forget about
Motoki. Whaddya
think?
I think Reika will
meet someone special
in Africa and she'll
never be back!
You do not!
So you've
dropped out!
Good!
What I didn't
say that!
Motoki is
all mine!
That's just
wishful thinking!
Wishful thinking
is thinking you
can cook!
Nooo!
(crying)
What's wrong,
Usagi?
It's-It's Rei! She
said we're not
gonna be friends
anymore!
I'll be okay. I'm
sure she was just
a little on edge
because of her
Grandpa when she
said that.
Oh! Gramps,
turn back into
a good guy!
Next time on Sailor
Moon, "Grandpa Loses
Control: Rei in Danger"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.