(Usagi)
It's not fair that
you're only targeting
the energy of couples
(cont'd)
that are in love!
I mean, don't you
feel sorry for leaving
(cont'd)
out the girls
without boyfriends?!
I am Sailor Moon,
and in the name of the
moon. I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino,
and I'm a fourteen-year-
old middle school
student!
I'm a bit of a
klutz...
...and some people
might say I'm a
little emotional.
So on day, this strange
cat named Luna gave me
a special brooch that
transformed me into
a guardian in a
sailor uniform, and
told me I have to
fight bad guys!
Boy does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
(Giggles)
"I Want a Boyfriend:
The Luxury Cruise
Ship is a Trap!"
Moon Tiara!
Action!
That girl's become
quite the nuisance.
(Chuckle)
Huh?
Who would've guessed
that one little girl
could make so much
trouble for the
great Jadeite.
What is it, Tetiz?
It's been a while,
and yet you still
remembered my name. I
feel very honored, sir.
(Grunt)
So tell me, what
business does Queen
Beryl's subordinate
have in a place like
this, anyway?
You haven't changed,
have you?
Your response is
always so cold every
time that I come to
express my love for you.
I'm afraid I have no
time to deal with
you little delusions.
Go back the way
you came.
Oh, don't be like
that. I came here
today to offer you my
service, Master Jadeite.
I've come up with
a perfect way to
gather energy for
our great ruler...
What did you say?!
Ah ha! I see that
I've finally caught
your attention...
(Chuckle)
Then come closer.
I call this plan
Operation Romantic
Cruise...
(Tetiz as spokeswoman)
A night on the open
sea...
(cont'd)
Together in your own
little world, just
the two of you.
(cont'd)
The perfect time to
rekindle that old spark
or fan a new flame.
(cont'd)
On a romantic cruise
for lovers.
(cont'd)
Our maiden voyage
begins tomorrow. Let
your dreams come true.
(Sigh)
I wanna go, too!
Oh, just imagine
sailing away by the
light of the moon.
I know, but I heard
that tickets have been
completely sold out
for a month!
(Umino)
Looking at those
romantic cruises, huh?
They do seem nice!
(Chuckle)
A luxury liner with
room for six hundred
and sixty six
passengers.
(cont'd)
Supposedly the view
of the stars as the
ship travels from Tokyo
(cont'd)
to Yokohama is enough
to make any man and
woman fall in love!
Well now you've just
gone and made me
seasick. Thanks a lot.
Hold on, Usagi.
You mean you wanted
to go on that cruise
for real?!
I see. Oh boy,
this is very
unfortunate.
Umino, are you
saying?!
That you have
tickets?!
I did, but I'm
afraid that I don't
have them anymore,
because I gave them
both to my neighbor.
(Usagi)
How could you pass
up something so
incredible?!
Well, I'm still a
minor. I can't go
without a legal
guardian.
And besides that,
did you see when it
sails? It's way past
my curfew!
(Sad sighs)
That's probably the
most responsible thing
I've ever heard you say.
Actually, come to
think of it, the
lottery in the shopping
district was giving
two tickets out
as the grand prize.
Ah!
I'm gonna get it
this time, I know
it!
Aw, I lost again!
Here's a packet of
tissues as a
consolation prize!
Oh, this is so
frustrating!
(Rei)
Usagi?
(Usagi)
Oh, hi!
Rei, you won't
believe this! I've
played this lottery
(cont'd)
ten times so I can
go on this cruise,
and I haven't won!
(Rei)
Two tickets? I don't
get it. Why would you
even want those?
C'mon, wouldn't you
want to go on it
too?
Course not!
We're Guardians,
Usagi! We don't have
time to waste on useless
nonsense like this!
Hmph!
I'd like to give
it a try.
Sure, you got it.
Huh?!
Whoa! She's intense!
Scary!
Hah!
Huh?
(Clerk)
Congratulations!
You just won the grand
prize, two tickets for
a romantic cruise!
Yeah! Sweet!
I won!
(Giggles)
Uh, Rei? What happened
to not wanting to
waste time on useless
nonsense like this?
(Yawns)
(Usagi)
Come on! You said you
weren't even interested
in those tickets before!
(Rei)
I still don't see
why I should give
them to you.
Hmm...
Wait, I know!
Let's go together!
It'll be lots of
fun!
You're supposed to
go with a boyfriend,
you know!
Yeah, and do you
have one?
Shut up!
Ha! I knew you
didn't have anyone
to bring!
Unlike you, I can
easily get a date
for the cruise.
That's enough you
too! Cut it out,
already!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's just their
usual silly fight.
Ami! Rei is being
really mean to me
right now!
Ami, perfect timing.
C'mere!
Huh, what is it?
(Rei)
Just get over here,
will ya?
Ugh! Ah!
Ugh! You'll never
get a boyfriend in
time!
Hey! I'm not done
talking to you!
(Rei)
But I'm done
with you!
(Ami)
Huh? You want me
to go with you?
(Rei)
Yeah, here!
But Usagi, it seemed
like she really
wanted to go.
No way! Can you
imagine that dork
in a romantic setting?
(Ami)
But, I...
(Rei)
You can do nautical
research, it'll be
a learning experience.
C'mon!
And maybe, I can
find a hot boyfriend
just like Tuxedo Mask!
Ha! I knew it!
She really doesn't
have a boyfriend!
(Rei)
Ami, let's just go
together, all right?
Please, please, please?
Well, 'kay.
Does she honestly
think I'm gonna stay
home while they go
on that cruise?
Fat chance!
Ugh, I wish she'd
devote this much energy
to her actual mission.
(People chattering)
Okay, let's get
onboard!
How do you plan on
doing that, Usagi?
What are you talking
about?! Situations
like these, are why
I have this!
What?!
You can't, Usagi!
That's only supposed to
be used to fight for good!
Don't be so serious,
Luna!
(Usagi)
Moon Power!
Transform me into
a beautiful photographer!
Now, let's get you
inside of this case,
Luna!
(Luna)
I don't wanna go-!
(Chuckle)
Captain Jadeite, all
of our young victims are
climbing aboard by
the dozens! Looks
like the plan's
going well!
I'm impressed, Tetiz.
It's hard to believe
that this is actually
just a broken-down
old ship that's been
enchanted with your
seawater magic.
Yes, but you should
know this isn't all
my magic is capable of.
(Jadeite)
Let the flowers of
your love blossom,
all you human fools!
Captain, we're all
ready to cast off
and get underway now.
Good, let's depart.
Ay'ey!
(Rei)
Uhh.. Why did I
decide to wear heels?
This is ridiculous!
You know, I've been
looking around, and
it seems like we're
the only two girls
that are here all
by themselves.
You're right.
I knew this was some
kind of love boat, but
I didn't think it
would be all couples!
I thought there might
be some single guys
here!
(Giggles)
Guess we won't be
finding boyfriends!
(Luna)
Where are we?
The engine room.
Can't be. The engine
room of a ship this big
wouldn't be anywhere
near this quiet.
Well, maybe it's
just idling now.
I don't think so.
It looks to me like
we're moving at full
speed.
Boy, you sure worry
a lot. Maybe they've
just have some kind
of state-of-the-art
silent engine
installed. Anyway,
I wonder where Rei
and Ami went.
(Jadeite)
What are you
doing here?!
Sailor Moon!
You're a reporter,
huh? Well, I'm sorry,
but you're in a
restricted area.
Oh my, what a
cute guy!
What's this intense
evil aura that
I'm sensing?!
(Jadeite)
It's dangerous
here.
(Usagi)
Oh, sorry! I got
separated from my
crew when I came
(cont'd)
onboard, and
I got lost.
Oh, I see. You've
got a bit of a
problem, huh?
I know! We can
go look for my
friends together!
Uh..okay.
Something about this
woman bothers me.
He would make a
wonderful future
boyfriend!
I just came up with
a really great idea!
Oh? What is it?
(Rei)
Since there are so
many couples here,
there are bound to
(cont'd)
be at least a few
of them who are
fighting, right?
(Ami)
What are you getting
at?
If we can find some
guys who've been
freshly dumped by
their girlfriends,
then we can grab
them on the rebound!
(Ami Sighs)
I should've just stayed
home and memorized the
dictionary.
(Jadeite)
I'd like to make an
announcement to the
whole ship that you
(cont'd)
got separated from
your friends.
But I'm afraid that if I
do so, it would ruin the
beautifully romantic
mood that the other
guests are enjoying.
Yeah, you do have
a good point.
Besides, I'm perfectly
happy just being
with you!
What is this odd
feeling I'm having?!
(Jadeite)
Why do I feel the
need to be so cautious
around this girl?
(Usagi)
Oh! He can't take
his eyes off me!
(Tetiz)
Captain...
Excuse me.
It's nearly time.
I see. Pardon me.
I have to go now.
Oh, that's too
bad.
Ah! We were just
getting to the good
part!
Usagi! We have a
situation! This ship
is full of evil energy!
Huh?!
The time is near.
Yes, the energy of love
from all the couples
onboard has almost
reached its peak now!
(Tetiz)
And when it does we'll
collect the energy
from over six hundred
(cont'd)
passengers at once!
So, do you agree
that my plan is a
good one?
If it works you'll
have my praise, but
not sooner.
I'm ninety-nine percent
certain it will work.
And if it does succeed,
then I believe you
ought to start paying
a little more attention
to me, Master Jadeite.
(Jadeite)
I'll consider it...
What are they saying?
I can't hear?
Whatever it is, I'm
sure he's a monster.
But he's my future
boyfriend!
Come on! Honestly,
Usagi?!
Ah!
(Usagi)
Oh no, they're
gone!
I bet they're up
to something just
terrible, too!
Um, listen, Rei.
Do you think you
could eat a little
quieter?
Don't tell me
what to do!
(Mouth full)
I've got to take
advantage of this
trip somehow!
Who needs boyfriends?!
(Announcer)
Attention, everyone!
Please gather in
the reception hall.
(cont'd)
We've prepared a
wonderful show for you,
and it's about to begin!
Hey, you think we
should go to that?
Oh yes!
Anything to get you
away from the food!
She just said the
reception hall!
Maybe we'll find
the monsters there!
(People Chattering)
Thank you all for
coming.
Now cuddle up as you
watch the most romantic
show in the whole world!
(Chuckle)
(cont'd)
(Laughs)
What a trick!
This is a pretty
elaborate effect!
Rei, is that-
It's definitely a
monster.
This ship is like a
maze! Which way is
the reception hall?!
(Laughs)
All of you will
continue your romantic
dreams, in hell!
(Deep Chuckle)
That's Jadeite.
Hm? Who are you?!
Heh. You've made a
big mistake, Tetiz.
You're only stealing
energy from couples.
(Jadeite cont'd)
But your plan doesn't
have any effect on girls
who don't have true
romantic partners.
Why did you two come
if you don't have
boyfriends?!
Hey, shut up!
We could have boyfriends
if we really wanted
them!
Hmm, I doubt it!
Show these girls the
door!
Ahh!
Gotcha!
Why did I wear
heels?
We can't transform out
in the open, in front
of everyone.
(Rei)
We're in trouble.
Ha! It's useless to
struggle.
Master Jadeite,
I may have made a
minor miscalculation
in my plan,
(Tetiz cont'd)
But we've still
managed to collect
plenty of Human Energy.
(Tetiz cont'd)
I believe that Queen
Beryl will be very
pleased with us.
(Jadeite)
Agreed.
(Luna)
Here it is, Usagi!
(Usagi)
I see it!
Moon Prism Power
Make up!
(Usagi)
Stop!
It's Sailor Moon!
(Usagi)
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights
for love and for justice!
(Cont'd)
I am Sailor Moon!
(Tetiz)
Just how did you get
on board?!
How dare you target
couples and go after
the energy that their
love creates!
Love is precious!
Some girls can't even
find boyfriends! It's
so sad!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
So you're Sailor
Moon?!
I will destroy you!
Ah!
Whoa!
(Luna)
Be very careful now,
Sailor Moon! It looks
like that monster
(cont'd)
has the power to
control seawater!
Take this!
Ah!
(Chuckle)
Excellent job, Tetiz.
(Rei)
Fire Soul!
We've gotta hurry,
Sailor Mars!
Damn right! No one
makes fun of me for
not having a boyfriend,
and gets away with it!
Die!
Bubble!
Spray!
Agh! Damn it!
Fire!
Soul!
(Ami)
Finish her,
Sailor Moon!
(Usagi)
Okay!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
(Gasp)
Ah!
(Groans)
(Chuckle)
Well, well, I
underestimated you
girls, but then, you've
gotten a lot more
skilled since the
last time we met.
It's the end of the
line, Jadeite!
We're not letting you
get away with this!
Both of you, don't
let your guard down!
Ha! Insolent.
This ends now!
Huh?! Why did he
disappear?!
(Rei)
Did he run away?!
I don't know.
(Jadeite)
Uh?! Q-Queen Beryl!
You used my precious
monster Tetiz without
my permission, and
thanks to your
incompetence, she's
now been killed!
Y-You're mistaken!
This was Tetiz's idea
right from the very
start!
I'll hear your excuses
at the palace. Better
choose your words
carefully.
You've already caused
enough trouble.
Yes.
Damn it!
I'll get you for
this, Sailor Moon!
Aw, this is just
plain awful!
No love connection
for us!
Well, I'm not just
gonna give up!
The next time there's
a cruise like this,
I'm gonna have a
boyfriend to take
on it with me!
Yeah! And I'll be
right behind you!
Not if you keep on
dressing like that...
(Usagi)
Jean jackets are
making a comeback
you know!
(Luna)
Those two are never
going to learn, are
they?
Think I'll just stick
to studying for now.
(Luna)
Oh, boy!
(Usagi)
Oh, no! Jadeite has
declared war on us!
(Luna)
We can't let him
win, Usagi!
(Usagi)
Right! We have to
stop him at any cost
to make this world
(cont'd)
a safer place!
(Luna)
That's the spirit!
(Usagi)
Now, with that said.
Rei, Ami, do your
best!
(Luna)
Oh, Usagi...
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Girls Unite: The End of
Jadeite."
(Usagi)
Hey, that rhymes!
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.