[Usagi]
Preying on poor young
girls that have dreams
of becoming fit
is just about the most
evil thing you can do.
It's unforgiveable!
I am Sailor Moon, and in
the name of the moon,
you will be punished!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino, and
I'm a fourteen-year-old
middleschool student.
I'm a Cancer with blood type O.
My birthstone is a pearl,
and, I'm a bit of a klutz.
Some people might say
I'm also a little emotional.
So, one day, this strange
cat named Luna appeared,
turned me into a Guardian
in a sailor uniform,
and told me I had
to fight bad guys!
Boy, does that ever
make me nervous!
But I'm sure it'll
all work out fine!
[giggle]
[Usagi]
"Learn How to be
Skinny From Usagi!"
[pleased]
Mmm!
[stretching]
[Usagi]
Yaaahhh!!
Huh?!
[Usagi]
Aww oh, no! I've put on weight!
I'm so out of shape!
[crying]
It's okay! People look
better with a little
meat on their bones.
Especially when
they're young.
Daddy's right,
hon.
Know what your real
problem is, Usagi?
You eat way too much!
You could probably
stand to get more
exercise, too.
And she does spend
more time eating
than studying!
[all]
That's why you've
gained weight!
Ouch! You don't have to
be so harsh... [crying]
[Luna]
There's no point in crying.
Just try to cut back on what
you eat, that's all!
Okay.
And it couldn't hurt to get
a little more exercise.
Mm-hmm.
Uh? What's
that, Luna?
[chuckle] It's you
in six months!
What?!
That's not funny, Luna!
I'm gonna get you!
[Luna]
Yaaahh!
[school bell]
Hmm? Where's
your lunch?
Ulp!
Oh, well, uh...
[Umino]
Usagi!
Huh?
Sounds to me like you forgot
to bring your lunch today!
Here!
Have mine!
It's delicious!
No thank you.
I see! So you're on
a diet now, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Me, too.
I know you how feel.
It's really hard to
stay fit.
[all]
Oh, is it?
Usagi, why don't
you try swimming?
It's a good way
to stay fit.
Mmhh...
That won't work.
She's no good at it.
Too bad.
I've tried things like
fasting and eating
pineapples to lose weight.
But none of those fad diets
ever last for very long.
[all]
Oh, they don't?
I think that the best diet
is falling in love, because
then you want to look good!
Have you ever been
in love before?
No...
[all]
No kidding.
That's right...
Hey, wait, what do
you mean by that?!
Listen, you're just
born the way you are,
and there's nothing
you can do about that.
You know, you of all
people are one to talk!
What?!
Grrr!
Auhh!
Actually,
speaking of
which,
did you notice that
Ms. Haruna is looking
really fit lately?
How'd she do it?
Dunno!
Good morning, everyone!
[giggles]
She doesn't look
much different than
she did before.
You can't tell with that
dress on, but here,
have a look at this.
Here's a "before" picture.
And here's "after" she
started working out.
Oh, wow!
And it took her
only two days!
Uh, Umino, how'd you
get these pictures?!
Well, that's a
trade secret.
Oh, yeah?
Yes?
Just tell us how
you got the photos!
Er!
Spill it!
Uh!
Tell us!
Yahhh!
- Hey! Come back here!
Where are you going??
- Hold it, Umino!
Pheww!
I shouldn't have
opened my big mouth...
Found you!
Guaaah! Okay,
I admit it!
I followed Ms. Haruna and
took both those pictures
with my very own camera!
I don't care
about that stuff!
I just want to know the
name of the gym where
she goes to work out!
Huh? Oh...
[Usagi]
Shapelin! This is it!
Miss Haruna's gym!
[Naru]
I don't know,
looks pretty expensive.
Hey, look! Isn't that
Rie Goto, the actress?!
She's so pretty!
Exercise hard, and you
can be in great shape!
And in just a few days,
you'll be beautiful, too!
[Rie Goto]
We can all get into
shape together!
And you don't have to spend a
fortune, because at Shapelin,
we're currently
offering a free trial!
Ah! Free trial?!
Can't get any
cheaper than that!
[in unison]
Let's do it! Come on!
[sinister chuckle]
More fools enter our lair.
There's no such thing
as a free lunch, girls.
[giggle] Good thing we
brought our gym clothes!
Time to get
in shape!
[all girls]
Ahh!
Welcome to Shapelin.
Are you new members?
[gasps of awe]
He's cute!
I love his
glasses!
I'm one of the instructors
at this gym.
Oh, uh, we should tell
you that this is our
first time here.
Great! Just come this way.
Mmmm!
Hnngh!
Mmmhh!
Mh!
C'mon, let's
see two more!
Awww!
[panting]
Good! But now let's
pick up the pace.
What?! Aahh...
Keep it up! Push yourselves
to be fit, and all of you
will end up gorgeous!
[panting]
Where's Usagi?
Huh? Um, rowing
machine, I think.
Now don't slack off!
You want to be
beautiful, don't you?
I can already tell you
have so much potential.
Right! Beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful!
I'm going to keep
working out till I
become beautiful!
[panting]
All right!
That's enough for today!
[relieved sighs]
You worked really hard!
So as a reward, come
step into the Shape Ray,
the pride of our gym.
[in unison, out of breath]
The... Shape Ray?
Whassat?
[Usagi]
Oh, my muscles!
I never knew it was
possible to be so tired!
[relaxing sigh]
It is tough getting fit!
Ah, I'm so hungry.
Step in
here.
Uhhh...
Keep in mind that a mere five
minutes in the Shape Ray,
and you'll be the fittest
that you've ever been in
your entire life!
That's it! I bet that's
how Ms. Haruna got that
fit in just one day.
I'm going in!
Yeah!
I will, too!
Heh.
Ah, the young and
succulent energy of girls.
[chuckle]
Jadeite!
Yes. I'm here,
Queen Beryl.
Jadeite, report!
No need to worry.
We are continuing to
gather a large amount
of human energy for
our great ruler.
I see. Then proceed as planned.
Right! These foolish women
are determined to lose
weight no matter what,
so I'm sure that
this plan will be a
complete success.
I... feel so...
So tired...
Isn't that a small price
for how attractive you
all will become?
Yeah!
It is.
Totally!
And if you come
back tomorrow,
you'll become
even more stunning.
[Exhausted]
Okay.
[chuckle]
It's so strong, the energy of
these girls who'd shorten their
lives for their "ideal" body.
[chuckle]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Sailor Moon!
[Usagi]
I still can't believe that Naru
and the rest of the girls just
left me behind at that gym!
Boy, some friends they
turned out to be!
[sigh] So hungry.
Ah!
Oh, wait!
Huh? Uh...
[practically drooling]
Eeeheehee!
Those are some
yummy-looking
pork buns!
Er... Eh...
Mom! A scary girl tried
to take my pork buns!
I've been dazzled
by pork buns.
How pathetic!
I just can't stop
thinking about food!
[sigh] It must be nice to
be Sailor V who's so perfect she
never needs to diet or exercise!
[Motoki]
Watch out!
Usagi! You almost
fell down!
Oh, Motoki!
Are you sick
or something?
Maybe.
You want to go
to a hospital?
I'd much rather
go to a restaurant.
Huh?!
I haven't eaten a single
thing since yesterday!
So hungry.
Ah! This feels like a
dream, but it's not!
Motoki is actually
holding me for real!
Usagi? Usagi, are
you all right?
Motoki...
Yes, I think so!
Good, just stay strong.
And hopefully the energy
of love will help you to
recover quickly.
The energy of love?
That's right.
My love for you.
Motoki...
Yes, Usagi?
Oh, I'm so glad to be alive!
Just hang in
there, okay?
Ah! this must be the warmth
of the energy of love!
Huh?
[embarrassed chuckle]
I... um...
Well, I'm glad you're
feeling better!
But what did you mean when
you said that you hadn't
eaten since yesterday?
Ah! Umm...
Don't tell me you did so
poorly on a test that your
mother refused to feed you for
a day or something like that!
Of course not;
it's nothing like that!
I just thought that I'd go
on a little diet, that's all!
A diet?!
Ha ha ha ha!
What is it?!
What's so funny?!
Sorry! I don't mean to
laugh, it's just that I
don't know where you got the
idea that you need to diet!
If anything, you could
stand to gain some weight!
Huh?
Personally, I find
curvy people to be
much more attractive.
I mean, I can't understand
why a girl would want to be
nothing but skin and bones.
What? Really?
Yeah!
Wow, you're the best!
So good! Nothing's
better than a pork bun!
I'm still young,
after all.
I can carry a little
extra weight!
What do we
have here?
Now, would you call that
cannibalism, a bunhead
eating a pork bun?
Just leave me alone!
Why do you care what
I eat, anyway?!
If you keep eating like
that, you just might
turn into a pork bun.
Oh, shut up!
What a catch!
Thanks for this!
Plus it means one less
for you to eat, bunhead.
That jerk and his
dumb glasses!
He does kinda have
a point, though.
Huh?
If you keep eating like
that, then you're just
going to have to work
even harder to stay fit!
Luna!
I don't really care what
anybody else has to say.
Motoki told me that I'm
pretty just the way I am.
But I wonder if you
might be getting all
this wrong, Usagi.
How so?
He said that he prefers
girls that aren't just
skin and bones,
but you can go
too far the other
way, too, y'know?
Mmff!
But never mind that!
There's a bigger problem!
Oh no, you're right!
Let's see,
One, two, three, four...
I ate six pork buns today!
I mean Ms. Haruna has been
acting really strange lately,
and she looks like she's
wasting away to nothing!
Oh, boy. Six?!
That means...
Ah! No way!
And it isn't
only Ms. Haruna!
A lot of the girls who went
to work out at Shapelin
have become far too thin!
Something is going on
down there at that gym!
Hey, are you
listening?
Then it's gotta
be Shapelin!
Yes!
Shapelin is the only thing
that can save me from turning
into a total nightmare!
Wait! Usagi! That's
not what I was saying!
Oh, boy.
Hm?
Huh?
Must get fit,
must get fit,
must get fit!
Ugh, that girl is hopeless;
I can't watch this anymore!
Hold on!
Is that?
It is! It's Ms. Haruna!
She really is skin and bones.
Hm, I wonder where
she's going?
Hmm.
I already don't like
the looks of this.
Huh?
Wait, what is that?
Ha ha ha ha!
This young woman's energy
is nearly all gone.
We'll finish
draining her today.
And after that, she'll
just grow weak and die.
[gasp] Oh, no!
Usagi!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
[meow]
I'm gonna get you for that!
All right, where are you, Luna?!
Come out!
Usagi, Ms. Haruna's
in trouble!
Forget her!
You're going down!
Haaa!
Hss!
Wuagh!
Get... get off of me!
Just quit yowling and
listen to me closely!
And if you give me any
grief, then your face
is gonna pay the price!
[whimper]
If we don't hurry,
Ms. Haruna could
really die,
so you have to turn into
Sailor Moon right away
and save her, Usagi.
What? Just like that?
But it's so sudden!
Shut up and just do it!
[whimper]
Okay, okay! I get it!
[sob]
Actually, I don't
get it at all!
Moon Prism Power Make Up!
[terrified moans]
Hm. Just a little more
until we reach our goal!
Release Ms. Haruna
at once!
Huh?!
Preying on the dreams of
girls who want to be fit!
You're an unforgivable
enemy of all women!
Heh. So it's you again?
You bet it is!
I am the pretty guardian,
Who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
moon, you will be punished!
Heh! You impudent brat!
Take care of her!
[chuckle]
Raaagh!
Raaghaha!
Ahh!
Oh no, they have
me surrounded!
[menacing chuckles]
Go ahead and
finish her off!
Luna! Help me,
do something, quickly!
Sailor Moon, they're being
controlled by the headbands
that they're wearing!
If you can destroy those,
then you'll be safe!
No! I'm too scared!
Stay strong! Remember,
if you fight you might
lose weight!
Wait, what did
you just say?
I said that if you
fight these guys, it'll
help you get in shape!
Ah! Really?!
Then I'll do it!
Raaagh!
Sweat once,
and get fit!
Sweat twice,
get even more fit!
Sweat three times,
and I can do anything!
Never mess with a girl's
will to get into shape!
Now!
Moon Tiara Action!
Ogh!
Uagh!
Bye, boys!
Been fun!
[in unison]
Hold on. What are we doing
down here?! Man, that's weird!
Mmm-mm!
Wow, that really
was a good workout!
Jadeite, you have done very
well to gather this much
human energy for our ruler.
I'd say you can call your
plan mostly a success.
Yes. Thank you very much,
Queen Beryl.
And next time, I'll
get that Sailor Moon!
Mmmm!
So nice...
Usagi, I put out
a towel for you!
Thanks, mom!
So is Ms. Haruna
feeling all better now?
Yeah! She just took a
week off school to rest,
but she's back now!
Wow, what
an ordeal!
You know, mom, I really
don't think that you should
go on a diet, either!
Yes, you have to be
careful about that.
Usagi, too.
Seems like Usagi's
back to normal.
[Usagi]
Huwaaaa!?
See?
Oh, no!
I've gained weight!
Come on!
But I just got all
of that exercise!
Why me?!?
[Usagi]
A new pet called a Chanela
is becoming very popular.
And I can see why!
They're so cute!
[Luna]
But not as cute as me.
[Usagi]
Yyyyeah...
[Luna]
What?! Anyone can see
my beauty and charm!
I'm precious!
[Usagi]
Whatever, Luna. At least
a Chanela wouldn't yell
at me all the time!
[Luna]
Well, excuse me!
[Usagi]
Scent Of A Monster:
Chanela Will Steal
Your Love.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.