You're kidding! A seminar
on how to become a Princess?
It sounds like it was made
for me! They teach you
refined conversation and
dignified manners! And at
the end, there's even a
grand ball! But wouldn't
you know it! There's evil
lurking in the pretty flower
garden! In the name of all
the elegant young ladies...
...I shall punish you!
Let's become a Princess:
Usagi's Bizarre Training!
(panic scream)
I'm gonna be
late for school!
Oh boy, being a
Princess hasn't
changed anything.
Hey! Good
Morning, Naru!
Morning!
Hmmh. You overslept,
too, didn't you?
Speak for yourself.
I was finishing my
homework.
What?! We had
homework?!
Of course, weren't
you paying attention?
There was science, math,
English, social studies..
Oh, and that
Japanese report!
And of course,
the embroidery
for home ec.
I'm so screwed.
Wow! What a cool-
looking guy! Who is
he?
Uhh...
Okay...
What's with them?
Huh? You mean
you don't know?
Mm-mm.
Those are some of the
girls who are attending
the Princess Seminar at
the Rose Mansion.
Oh yeah, now I remember.
That's the place where
Countess Rose lives.
She's the lady who
recently moved here
from England, right?
Yup! From what I heard,
she's supposed to be a
famous aristocrat. And
she's and expert on
manners and the social
graces. Wealthy parents
send their daughters to
her to learn
how to act
like a princess.
You can take a
class for that?
Apparently. She teaches
them the basics of
elegance and culture.
Hmmm...
Ahhhhhh!
We're gonna
be late!
Alright, class. Your
homework, as you will
recall, was to translate
page 53 of your textbook.
I present to you,
Princess Serenity!
She's so beautiful!
So elegant, and
so refined!
She is truly a
princess like
no other!
You're breathtaking,
Princess. May I have
this dance?
Young lady, did you
get your homework
done?!
Silence! How dare you
address a Princess
in that way?!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Forgive me, Princess!
(laughing)
Just kidding!
(giggling)
Miss Tsukino...
Wake up,
right now!
How dare you address
a Princess in that way.
(embarrassed gasp)
You seem to be
babbling. Did you
forget your homework
again?
Uhh, guess I did.
Sorry about that,
again...
Go stand in the hall!
Wahhhh!
Mmm. Yeah, this is
becoming a really
big problem.
I've got to take my
responsibilities as
a Princess much
more seriously!
Very good!
I'm glad you finally
realized that!
Well of course, silly!
If I don't, I won't be
able to dance with Tuxedo
Mask at the ball!
She's hopeless.
Endymion...
You shall assist
Kunzite with the
task of defeating
Sailor Moon and
recovering the
Silver Crystal.
I refuse. I don't team
up with anyone. I will
work on my own.
That's fine with me.
I will do the same.
Whatever gets
the job done.
I expect one or both
of you to bring me
Sailor Moon's corpse
and the Silver Crystal,
as soon as possible.
Yes. I already have
a plan in motion.
(evil chuckle)
Excellent.
Codename Zero-Zero-
Nine-One, this is Luna.
Passphrase: "The rabbit
on the moon is pounding
rice cakes. Over.
The moon's rice
cakes are sticky.
And they puff up
when you toast
them, as well.
What is it, Luna?
Well, sir. Usagi just
isn't serious about
being a princess, and
I don't know what to
do to get her
mind right!
That is a difficult
problem, and you need
to...uhh. Oops! I-oh..
(embarrassed laugh)
A-Artemis...
(embarrassed laughter)
Well, I guess the
secret's out. The
communicator's been
acting very weird today.
(awkward laughter)
You mean to tell me
that you're the one
who's been bossing me
around this whole time!
Uhh, yeah...
And why didn't
you let me know?!
You never asked! And
as time went on, it
got more awkward and...
(embarrassed sigh)
Now then...
Today, young ladies, I
shall read you a poem
by Francis Hineck.
As I sank deeply into
the darkness, my beloved
sent me a golden arrow.
I confess, I am perplexed
by the sweet poison covering
the arrowhead. I realize as
I sit here, that I am a
prisoner of love.
Hmm. Looks like
they're having
a party.
Ahhhhh!
What is it, Usagi?
They're eating
cheesecake from
Charmont! I want
it!
Are you serious?
(cough)
Excuse me, but if you
have business here,
young lady, please
us the front door.
(panic screams)
And how may I help you?
Well, uh, to be
perfectly honest,
I was kinda thinking
about attending the
Princess Seminar!
Unfortunately, the
seminar is by invitation
only, through current
members.
Invitation, you say?
Well...I got an
invitation from this
prominent lady!
Meow?
We don't accept
invitations from
felines.
(amused chuckle)
What an imaginative
young lady!
I think an invitation
from a cat would be
fine this time.
But madam...
You're so
understanding.
In my opinion, it will be
amusing to have a unique
person around. However,
there is one condition.
Uhh! Condition,
you say?! If it
has to do with,
tea ceremony, flower
arrangement, cooking,
sewing, cleaning, even
putting on a kimono.
I'm afraid I cannot
do any of those things!
Is that alright?!
If not, I understand.
(amused giggle)
How wonderful to
be so unskilled!
(hurt groan)
Edward, if
you would.
Ma'am.
Take this.
Huh?
Strange as it seems,
the Countess really
enjoys playing Frisbee.
So, if you attend the
Princess Seminar,
you'll have to be
adept at it.
Alright! I've actually
gotten pretty good at
this sort of thing!
There!
(amazed gasp)
Good!
That was splendid!
You may attend my
Princess Seminar,
young lady.
Ahhh!
Woo-Hoo!
Wow. So Usagi really
went to the Rose Mansion
to become a princess?
I bet she just
gives up in a
day.
Maybe, but it is good
that she's taken the
initiative to try and
learn the basics.
I just hope this course
will turn her into a
proper princes.
But really, what would
she have to do to become
a proper princess?
Huh?
I mean, what's wrong
with the way Usagi is
right now?
Many things, actually.
The bottom line is, she
has to behave like a
princess in every respect.
Why is that?
(frustrated groan)
Well, among other things.
Only a proper princess
would be able to activate
the true power of the
Silver Crystal!
Hey! Why don't we
join Usagi at this
princess seminar?
Good idea!
We don't need
five princesses.
(playful chatter)
Let me show you
how it's done.
Here!
(scared gasp)
(giggling)
If this is all it takes
to be a princess, no
problem at all!
Is everything
proceeding to your
satisfaction, Master
Kunzite?
(evil chuckle)
Sailor Moon has a
special technique,
Moon Tiara Action,
which is similar
to that game, but
she's also very
clumsy.
In other words, the
clumsy girl who knows
how to play that game
well, but who still
cannot pass the
Princess Seminar,
is Sailor Moon,
correct?
(affirmative grunt)
But that still leaves
one important question.
Will someone with her
amount of experience,
fall for our trap?
She will.
Sailor Moon's that
kind of girl, my dear.
Here you go!
Sailor Moon!
This dress is so tight
and uncomfortable!
I don't know how
these girls put
up with it.
(ecstatic gasp)
Alright, everyone,
let us dine.
Good deal!
I'm starving!
(loud slurping)
That's not correct,
miss. Try not to
slurp.
O-okay.
(quiet slurping)
Unacceptable.
Try again.
Once again! You
can't make those
noises!
Wahhh! This is crazy!
How can eating be
this hard?!
A princess's way
of speaking is of
utmost importance.
And let me emphasize
that polite speech
is essential. At all
times, one must be
sophisticated, elegant,
and to the point. This-
This is so boring!
It's just like school!
Um...
For example, what do
you say when you're
offering a guest a
cup of coffee?
Huh? Well, let's see.
Would you be so kind
as to please partake
of some coffee? Uh...
It's free!
(giggling)
I appreciate your
concern, but there's
no need to emphasize
that the coffee you're
offering is free. In
this case, a simple
'Please have some
coffee' will suffice.
Huh? Oh boy.
Gracefully, ladies.
One, two, three...
That's it. Follow
the music.
This is the final
session of the
Princess Seminar.
If I come by and tap
you on your shoulder,
you have graduated.
(uncomfortable grunts)
Ahhhhh!
(giggle)
Sorry about that!
This is impossible!
It's the hardest thing
I've ever tried to do!
Well, this isn't
surprising...
Hey! What are you
guys doing here?
We can't let you
have all the fun!
(chuckling)
Why are you
on the floor?
After all, every single
person has at least
one redeeming feature!
(awkward grunts)
Everyone has things
they struggle with.
(awkward laughing)
(painful screams)
I'm not very good
when it comes to
dancing!
This is not going
well. I wonder...
Maybe I'm not cut
out to be a princess.
You pass,
my dear.
You passed.
You pass, as well.
Young ladies, if I
tapped your shoulder,
proceed to the other
room, and I will give
you your graduation
certificates.
(giggle)
(annoyed groan)
We flunked!
This is kinda creepy.
These statues look
way too real.
It's because they are.
As a matter of fact,
all the dolls in this
room, at one time, were
actual young women.
What did you just say?
(evil laughter)
(shocked gasps)
She's a monster!
Hello. I am...
...Shakokai! Welcome
to graduation.
(scared screams)
(evil laughter)
(gasps)
Hey! What was that?
Did you hear someone
screaming in there?
Something must have
happened to Ami and
the others!
We'd better
check it out!
(frightened scream)
(evil chuckle)
A monster!
What in the-?!
Run!
Ahhh!
(horrified gasp)
That is so gross!
You three are the only
girls who failed to pass
my Princess Seminar.
According to what I
know to be true that
means one of you must
be Sailor Moon. So,
which one of you
is it?
What makes you
say that?
I was told that Sailor
Moon is clumsy, stupid,
lazy, and unrefined. And
there's no way a girl like
that could ever pass
the Princes Seminar.
That kinda
makes sense!
Damn, that was
really good
thinking!
Will you two stop
agreeing with her!
Whose side are you
on, anyway?!
And now to turn you
all into dolls!
Ahhhh!
Look out!
Get off of me!
I can't see!
Agh!
Now!
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
Mars Power!
Venus Power!
Make Up!
I said, get off!
So irritating!
Where did those
girls go?!
You can't flunk
Sailor Moon without
consequences!
Huh?
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Mars!
I am Sailor Venus!
In the name of
the Moon...
...We'll punish you!
You're certainly
welcome to try, but
first, let me give
you all something!
(attack yell)
Ahhhh!
I'll burn that up!
Fire!
Soul!
(evil laughter)
Crescent
Beam!
Our Crescent Beam
and Fire Soul are
having absolutely
no effect!
I don't think my
Moon Tiara Action's
gonna slow her down,
either!
(evil chuckle)
You're all going
to make exquisite
wax dolls!
We'll pass, thanks!
I like playing with
dolls, but I don't
want to turn into one!
(gasp)
That rose!
Could it be?!
Excellent work,
Shakokai!
Master Endymion!
It's Tuxedo Mask,
everyone! He's come
here to save us!
Not so sure
about that.
Sailor Moon, hand
over the Silver
Crystal.
If you do it now,
I shall spare your
life.
But, that's going
against Master
Kunzite's orders!
Sailor Moon, will
you give it to me?
You're kidding,
right, Tuxedo Mask?
You don't mean that?
You have to snap
out of it, Sailor
Moon.
This Tuxedo Mask
isn't anything like
the one you used to
know!
Come on!
Endymion!
Step back, do
not interfere!
What are you
talking about?
I was the one who put
this plan in motion.
And I want you to stay
out of it.
Ha ha. I've come here
for one thing. To
retrieve the Silver
Crystal. So bug off.
I beg your pardon?
So, what is it I
am supposed to be
doing?
KIll Sailor Moon!
No, the Silver
Crystal comes
first.
Don't listen to this
dressed up fool.
Sailor Moons comes
first!
Silver Crystal!
Shouldn't you be off
serving appetizers
somewhere?!
Oh brother! This is
ridiculous! Whose
orders am I supposed
to be following?
Ta-da!
Did you say something
about orders? Does that
mean you're the one who
ordered this cup of
coffee?
I'm sorry. I don't
recall doing so, but
that sounds lovely.
Now's my chance!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Refresh!
Oh my goodness! She
was Countess Rose!
I had no idea!
Now it's you turn
Tuxedo Mask! I'll use
my powers to change
you back to normal!
Moon Healing-!
(gasp)
Sailor Moon...
You can hold onto
the Silver Crystal
until the next time
we meet.
(evil chuckle)
Farewell!
What's happened,
Tuxedo Mask?
(confused sighs)
What happened?
Tuxedo Mask...
Ahhhhh!
Hey, what happened
to your Princess
training?
Oh that? I've got
that covered!
Really? How so?
I'm gonna become my
own kind of princess,
on my own terms! Mm-Hm!
Gotta go! Later!
She's never gonna
make my life easy,
is she?
Ahh-Ahhh!
Luna, we're
going skiing!
What in the world
are you talking
about?
There's a Moon Princess
Contest coming up! If I
don't enter, who will?
Don't you know how
much I hate the
cold?!
Oh come on, get over
it! You'll get to see
how good I look in
my ski outfit!
Do you even know
how to ski?
Uhhh...
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"The Snow, the Mountains,
Friendship and Monsters!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.