[Usagi]
The Crybaby: Usagi's
Beautiful Transformation.
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino.
I'm fourteen years old,
and go to Juban
Middle School.
I'm a bit of a klutz, and
sometimes get teased for
being a little emotional.
Usagi! It's after
eight o'clock!
Mmm... Mmh...
[gasp]
Augh!
Not again!
Whaa!
Why didn't you wake me up
sooner, Mom?! I'm late now!
I did try several
times, dear.
And each time you just
told me to go away.
I don't
remember that!
Usagi!
What?
I'm in a hurry!
I know, but don't
you need your lunch?
Mh. Thanks, Mom.
See ya later!
[yawn] Why does morning have
to come so early? I'm so sleepy!
[boys laughing]
Hmm?
[cat mrowling]
Ah! Hey!
Stop that!
Huh? Yahh!
Hmph. Little meanies.
Poor thing.
You okay?
Mrowr...
Seriously? They put
a bandage on you?!
Meow! Mewmeowr!
You want me to
take it off? Okay.
But it does look
pretty cute on you.
Meow?
Weird, a bald spot!
Uh!
[nervous]
Eh... heh heh heh!
[nervous shuddering]
[bells]
Yagh! Oh no, that's the bell!
I am so late for school!
Usagi Tsukino!
You're late again!
Not fair! It's not my fault
if all the other kids always
get to school on time.
[stomach growl]
Oog, and I'm
hungry, too!
Well, guess I have to make
up for skipping breakfast.
Time to dig in!
Miss Tsukino!
What are
you doing?
This kind of
attitude is exactly
why you're failing!
Gah! Thirty percent?!
That's right!
Wow, I can't believe
you did that, Usagi.
You seriously need to
learn some self-control!
Naru, you're my best friend!
You know I don't have that
kind of self-control!
Besides, I'm a growing girl!
I can't help it!
Hrrrmh.
Hey, how'd you end up
doing on your test, Usagi?
[Usagi]
Hi, Umino...
Can't you tell just
by looking at her
that she's upset?
Not that she
failed any worse
than usual.
Hey!
[gasp] I didn't
mean that!
Sorry.
Don't be sad, I slacked off
a little this time, too, so
I only got a ninety five.
[chuckles]
Oh well,
it's just
a test.
You're such
a jerk.
Hrn...
O-oh!
Hey, by the way!
Did you hear Sailor V
made another appearance
again the other night?
Hm? What?
Sailor V?
Yeah! I heard that she caught
a jewelry thief this time!
Wow, that's amazing!
I know!
Who is Sailor V, anyway?
Don't act impressed if you don't
know what I'm talking about!
Yeah, in case you haven't heard,
Sailor V is a costumed crime
fighter who's been fighting
evil in this part of town!
Sai...
..lor...
V!
And rumor has it that she's
part of the elite police
special investigation unit.
Huh. There's really
someone like that
out there?
Wow, that's pretty cool.
Jewelry is just
so beautiful.
I can totally understand
why someone would want
to steal some of it.
Yeah! I agree. I would love
to have a diamond ring.
[Naru]
I want ruby earrings.
Ooh me too! I'd love
a pair of them!
So sparkly!
I just remembered!
A sale started
yesterday at our
jewelry store!
Do you wanna
come with me and
check it out?
Of course I do! Yeah!
There are rings and earrings
that even we can afford!
Really?! I'm so there!
We'll meet there
after school, 'kay?
Yeah! I'll come
by for sure.
Oh, I wish school
was already over!
[uncomfortable chuckling]
See you.
Have we been able to make any
progress in locating the
legendary Silver Crystal yet?
[ghostly voices]
No.
We must always keep in mind
that the great ruler still
remains in dire need of a
massive amount of Energy.
We will find the Silver
Crystal at any cost.
But until then, we'll
provide our master with
human energy instead.
[Jadeite]
Queen Beryl.
Hm?
Allow me, Jadeite,
the honor of this
mission.
Even as we speak, my Monster
Morga is preparing to gather
human energy for the ruler.
She will not fail.
Then I'll leave it up to you.
Go now, Jadeite.
Yes, ma'am.
[crowd talking]
[gushing about the jewelry]
- Oooh!
- Beautiful!
- So cute!
There's so
many people!
Thank you all for
coming in today!
Well, welcome
to our store!
Please feel free to try
on anything you like,
My Mom's really getting
into this whole sale thing.
Maybe she's trying
to be more business
oriented.
We have the finest jewels!
Remember, everything here
is on sale!
[sinister]
Hmm.
Foolish humans.
Take the jewelry, and
give all your energy
to the great ruler!
[sinister chuckle]
Energy is being collected
from the clueless humans
who are drawn to the
sparkle of those jewels.
I'm sure that Queen Beryl
will be very pleased.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Continue, Morga!
Keep collecting
everyone's energy!
Gladly.
[Naru]
Mom.
Oh!
Oh, hi! I'm glad
you came, Naru.
I brought a friend
from school with me.
Hi, Naru's mom!
Oh, it's so nice of
you to visit my store!
It's a bit crowded now,
but please take your
time and look around.
Okay!
And because you're Naru's
friend, I'll even give
you an extra discount!
You really mean that?!
All right, score!
If you like diamonds,
how about this one?
It costs five
hundred thousand!
Five hundred
thousand!
Hefty price tag, huh?
But I'll give it to you
for thirty thousand!
[Both]
Five hundred thousand
for thirty thousand?!
I'll buy it!
- Wait a minute! I'll buy it.
- No, I want it!
- I heard it first!
This is totally
unbelievable!
Five hundred thousand for
only thirty thousand!
I really
want it!
You could always
ask your dad for
the money, right?
Yeah, but since I just
failed my English test...
Oh! That's right.
And my allowance is gone.
I spent it all. [sigh]
Hey, well, there's
always next time,
you know?
If only I had studied
a little more.
Hrrm. Oh, I hate you I
hate you, you stupid test!
Watch where you're
throwing things,
bunhead.
Huh?!
Oh, sorry!
Thirty percent?!
Huaaagh!
Looks to me like you'd
better study harder
next time, bunhead.
Hmf! Well, that's none
of your business!
Nyaa!
Stupid jerk and his
purple pleated pants!
What a weirdo.
[video arcade beeps and boops]
Huh?! They already made
Sailor V into a video game?!
Hmm.
[sigh] it must be so
cool to be Sailor V!
She doesn't have any tests
to worry about, and I bet
taking down all those bad
guys feels super awesome.
Compared to all that,
I'm nothing.
[sigh]
I can't believe that
I have to bring this
stupid test home!
Waahh!!
[sniffs]
Usagi Tsukino, at
last I've found you!
Sailor Moon!
[Usagi]
Hey! I'm home!
Oh, you're back!
You're sure late
getting home today.
Uh, yeah,
a little bit.
Oh, by the way, I bumped into
Umino earlier, and he said you
got your test back already.
What?!
He said he got a
ninety-five on his.
Oh, really?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Good for him.
Darn you, Umino...
I'm so gonna get
you for this.
So? What did you get
on your test, Usagi?
D'ooh!
Oh! Well, uh...
Actually, the
thing is... Uh...
Can I see it?
Okay.
Rrrgh! Usagi!
Yeah?
Stop bringing home
grades like this!
Go outside and think
about what you've done!
Waah!
But, Mom!
I don't want
to hear it!
Ow!
Hey, you're
in the way!
So what huge mistake
did Mom kick you out
for this time?
I sure wish I had a
sister who wasn't a
total loser.
D'ooh! How dare you
talk to me like that!
Bleaah!
That's it! Sailor V kick!
Ooogh!
Wahh! Come on, Mom!
Let me in already!
Uhn, that's strange,
I'm starting to feel
dizzy...
[woozy]
Oohhh... I feel weak...
What's happening?!
Everyone seems to
be getting sick
all of a sudden.
Should we call
an ambulance?!
Hello? Mom?
[chuckle]
Yes, this should be
enough Energy for now.
What do you mean?
[chuckle]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
[horrified gasp]
Unhh... Thank goodness,
she finally let me in.
I'm completely exhausted
from all of that.
Why do moms always get
so upset over grades anyway?
I don't feel like
doing my homework now.
I think I'll take
a quick nap.
[yawn]
Uh?
Huh?
Yah! The cat with
the bald spot!
Uh, it's not a bald spot.
Don't be rude.
Ahh!
You can talk?! No way!
How can a cat talk?!
Ahem!
Usagi, my name is Luna.
And you can't imagine
how long I've been
looking for you.
Eeee...
First things first. I wanted to
say thank you for saving me from
those kids earlier today.
Not to mention taking
that bandage off.
With it on, I can't talk, and
it dulls my sensory powers.
I thought I was
done for when those
kids put it on.
But because of that,
it led me to you!
[chuckle]
Good night!
What are you doing?!
This isn't some kind
of dream, you know!
Rrrg, Come on, stop
playing around!
Okay, then let me prove
to you it's not a dream!
Hmm?
A little gift from me,
just for you.
Wow! For me?
It's so beautiful!
Usagi, I need you
to listen to me.
Awesome, thank
you so much!
I need you to
listen to me!
Strange things
are happening
in this city.
Even the police
can't handle
what's going on!
A dangerous enemy
has appeared.
You're the one who can
defeat this enemy.
You're the Guardian that's
been chosen for this mission!
But there's more
than just that.
You also have to find
the other Guardians
and our princess!
Wow, really?
How cool!
Heee!
You don't actually
believe a single word
I'm saying, do you?
Oh, sure!
Of course I
believe you!
[not convinced]
Great. just repeat the words
I'm about to say, all right?
"Moon Prism Power, Make Up!"
Right!
Moon Prism Power, Make Up!
Huh?
No way!
What's going on?!
I don't believe it,
I transformed!
What is this?! What is
all of this about?!
Tell me!
[over radio]
Help! Please!
Someone, please help me!
Hmm?
No! Mom, stop!
That's Naru!
How am I hearing this?
Do you believe
me now?
I still don't know what's
going on, but I could hear
that Naru's in big trouble!
Usagi, you have
become Sailor Moon!
Now, go quickly!
Go and help your friend!
Hm?
Hee?
[Naru]
Help! Help please!
I... can't breathe...
Stop, Mom!
What are you doing?!
[chuckle] Im not your mother,
you pathetic little girl!
[screams]
Ha ha!
Huaaagh!
I've locked your mother
up in the basement.
And after I'm done
killing you, I'm going
to go kill her, too
and then send the
both of you to the
world of the dead.
[Usagi]
Get away from Naru!
Huh?!
And who might
you be?
Me?! I'm uh... Oh yeah!
I am the pretty Guardian,
Who fights for love
and for justice,
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
moon, I will punish you!
You're Sailor what? Hmph!
Are those stupid catch-phrases
supposed to scare me?
Now arise, all of you
vassals who have given your
energy to the great ruler!
Awaken and
attack her!
Oh no... Now what am
I supposed to do!?
Wuuhhh!
Yagh!
Yah!
Ahh!
Huh?
Yaah!
Ah! I'm bleeding.
This is bad!
What do you think
you're doing,
Sailor Moon!
You have to fight back!
You've got to attack and
defeat that monster!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
I can't.
I don't wanna fight,
I'm too scared!
How did I get
myself into this?!
Ahh! I wanna
go home now!
Time to finish you!
Ah!
Ahhhh!
Who are you?
I am known as Tuxedo Mask!
Sailor Moon, you have
to remember that crying
isn't going to solve
any of your problems!
Yeah, maybe not,
but I can't help it!
Wahhhh!
[amplified]
Now's your chance!
Throw your tiara at her and
yell, "Moon Tiara Action!"
But why would I want to do that?
What's going to happen?
Just hurry up and do it!
Moon Tiara...
Action!
Augghh!
[gasp] No way!
Morga. You failed me,
you fool.
Oohh...
[Tuxedo Mask]
Well done,
Sailor Moon.
I won't soon forget what
happened here tonight.
Ahh...
He's right.
You did really
well, Sailor Moon.
He's so cute!
[Naru]
I had this incredible
dream last night.
A superhero named
Sailor Moon showed
up to save me from
a hideous monster.
She was so cool!
Are you serious?
I had the exact
same dream!
Yeah, me too!
Wow! How weird!
Hey, Usagi.
Isn't that weird?
Are you even
listening?
Please be quiet, you guys.
I'm so incredibly tired.
I just want to sleep
a little longer, okay?
[yawn]
Nighty-night!
Hey Luna, want me to read your
fortune?
Quit fooling around, Usagi!
Don't forget, you're on a
mission!
Don't worry! I'm doing my job as
a superhero.
Oh, really?
By the way, I heard that people
who went to that Fortune Teller
are acting weird. What do you
think?
Sounds suspicious. Let's go!
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"Punishment Awaits: The House Of
Fortune Is The Monster Mansion"
Punishment Awaits: The House Of
Fortune Is The Monster Mansion
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.