Wow, these paintings by
Yumemi Yumeno are so
beautiful, but why do they
make me feel so nostalgic?
Wait!-That pure-hearted
girl possesses a Rainbow
Crystal?! We've gotta
do something!
Okay, here
goes nothing!
I am Sailor Moon! And in
the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
Hey! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice.
I am Sailor
Moon!
This job's not
easy, by the way.
We have to find and
protect the Legendary
Silver Crystal before the
bad guys get it. But in
order to do that, we need
to find the seven Rainbow
Crystals and the people
holding them!
Pretty crazy, huh? But
now there are four of us
Sailor Guardians, so I
think everything's
gonna work out just fine.
[giggling]
"The Painting of Love:
Usagi and Mamoru Get
Closer"
Of the seven Rainbow
Crystals... Two are in
the hands of those Sailor
Guardians and Tuxedo Mask
while we only possess one
of them.
And as for our allies,
the Seven Great Monsters,
three of them have
already been defeated.
Do you have anything to
say for yourself,
Zoisite?
Yes! Queen Beryl-please
allow me just a little
more time.
This young lady is our
next target.
I promise to
obtain the Rainbow
Crystal she has by
whatever means necessary.
But should you fail...
you know what will happen
to you?
Yes, my Queen.
Yup, it's autumn all
right. Seems like there
are folks in love
everywhere.
Oh Tuxedo Mask, tell
me. Are you a friend
or a foe?
There is one thing we
do know, that he is after
the precious Silver Crystal.
So that means we
should consider him
an enemy.
No! That can't be
right!
I don't know the real
identity of the guy
I'm in love with
and then there's
all those scary
monsters!
They keep popping up all
the time! Why does this
stuff keep happening to
me?!
Sorry I'm late,
Usagi.
Naru! So what is it you
wanted to show me,
anyway?!
You're just gonna have
to wait to find out!
Come on!
Okay, but I'm
starving! Can we get
something to eat?
[screaming]
That was way too
close. Seriously.
[chatting]
Wow! They're great!
Aren't they?! That's
why Yumemi Yumeno's
paintings have become all
the rage now.
This place is packed,
mostly with couples.
You know why? Because her
artwork is known as the
paintings of love!
Oh, Umino!
I agree! They say if
you have one of Yumemi's
paintings,
Your own wishes of
love will be granted!
Um-hm!-Um-hm!
Then I'm buying a poster
of hers!
Wow look at that! It's
one of Yumemi's self
portraits.
Oh! She's beautiful!
She definitely looks like
a person who would create
fantasy art.
Actually what she really
looks like is a mystery
because she's never, ever
been seen in public.
Well then, maybe in
reality she's super
ugly.
Did you really just say
that?!
[giggling]
This isn't good. I
can't paint without the
right inspiration.
But I've heard Yumemi
hasn't produced any new
paintings in a while.
Yeah, rumor is she's in a
creative slump and has
gone into hiding.
I'm right here.
That sucks.
Yeah, no kidding.
[fake laughing]
[giggling]
Huh?!
What is it,
Usagi?
Wow, this picture.
It's like I've seen
it somewhere before.
Huh? This painting
reminds me of...
Please find the Silver
Crystal.
It's like that dream
I always have.
Hey! Hey, come on,
let's go!
[grunting]
Sorry!
My glasses,
where'd they--
Hey. Are you all right,
Miss?
Yeah... wait. You're
him! It's you!
Huh?
Hey!
Isn't that guy out there
a friend of Motoki?
Yeah, that jerk!
He's cheating on Rei!
Oh, this is gonna be fun!
Sorry Naru, I'll see you
later, 'kay?
Hey wait!
Oh, Umino, make sure
that you walk Naru
home!
And grab a poster
for me, will ya?
Okay-You can count on me!
Can you believe her?
How about that? An
unexpected turn of events
has left me all alone
with Naru.
In the past I would've
been sad if Usagi decided
to suddenly run off and
leave me behind.
Now it just feels like
I've fallen in love yet
again!
Umino, I can
hear you.
Please, help me.
Help you what? If you
want something you better
speak up, lady.
Um--- I want
you to be my model.
Oooo! Busted! Wait
'til I tell Rei
about this.
You've got this all
wrong, Usagi.
And just how's that?
You're the one holding
hands with this girl!
Huh?!! What luck!
Huh? What
is it?
You're perfect! Now
I can start my next
painting!
[sighing]
Please say you'll
model for me, oh,
please!
Huh?! Model for you?!
Well, come in!
Right this way!
Wow! What
pretty flowers!
Thank you!
Well, uh--
Make yourselves
comfortable while I go
make some coffee.
Look I know I let you
talk me into coming here,
but I really can't spend
my whole day doing this
thing.
Oh, yeah, whatever. Like
you have better things to
do, you loser.
Hmph!
This looks like Yumemi
Yumeno's artwork!
[gasping]
Wait! Are you Yumemi
Yumeno?
Mmm.
I'm not what you
expected, right?
People think someone really
beautiful should paint
paintings like these.
That's why I made my
self-portraits look
pretty. But please, keep
this all a secret, okay?
So then no one knows what
you look like? Not even
your own friends know
who you really are?
That's a big
secret!
I don't have
any friends.
But I'm used
to it, now.
Besides, as long I can
keep working on my
paintings, that's good
enough for me.
All right, then.
Let's get you two
ready.
Usagi, could you sit
here?
What?! You want me to be
in a painting with this
jerk?!
You should
be so lucky.
Ohhhhhh!
I can't be a part
of this. I'm out of
here.
Please don't go.
I can explain.
I have a hard time
imagining it all without
having models to help me.
And lately, there's
been no one who matches
what I see.
I promise it'll be just
for today... Please?
Oh, all right.
Oh my gosh!
If Rei ever saw this,
she'd kill me!
But hey, he does look
pretty handsome.
Oh, geez. What am I
thinking here?!
Stop it, Usagi!
Tuxedo Mask is the
only one I love!
Owie-that hurt.
Just what are you doing?
Uh! None of
your business!
Hmph!
Heh.
Now! Let's get started!
I feel this one could be
a masterpiece!
Oh boy! It's hopeless!
Where could Usagi have
run off to anyway?
Is that me?!
Unbelievable!
Can't we get this
over with?
You know the only real
reason I'm still sitting
here is because this
coffee's so good.
[sticking tongue out]
I'm so impressed. How are
you able to draw such
wonderful pictures?
Whenever I start my
drawing, I always make a
wish in my heart.
I wish for the people who
see my artwork to let it
make them happy.
And for all of them to
be able to find their
true love.
Wow! That explains why
they're called paintings
of love, it all makes
sense, now.
You're such a kind
person, it's sad you
don't have any friends.
That can't be helped. My
fans think Yumemi is this
incredible beauty. But if
people found out I'm
her, it would shatter
their dreams, and make
them sad.
It's not true!
I say those who can't
make themselves happy,
can never make others
happy either.
[gasping]
That was so mean! Oh!
This picture's lovely!
Ugh, you are always
so full of yourself!
I mean, just take a
look at this picture,
isn't it beautiful?!
[gasping]
What?! Wha--what
is it?!
This shows a woman giving
her lover a present as a
token of her love.
It's strange, but whenever
I draw this couple,
I always end up feeling
very sad, for some odd
reason.
I feel it too. This
drawing stirs my emotions
and makes my heart ache.
A token of
her love.
[chuckling]
Yumemi Yumeno.
I'll turn you back into a
monster very soon.
[chuckling]
Sailor Moon!
Boy, that was so fun and
your homemade cookies
were really tasty.
I'm sorry for keeping
you so late.
Maybe you would've
preferred to have Mamoru
escort you home instead.
Are you kidding?!
He's the biggest
jerk ever!
Oh, look! It's Yumemi
Yumeno's art!
It's beautiful. Anyone
who creates art like this
must be gorgeous!
Hey, Yumemi, don't let
it bother you, okay?
You're kind, you're able
to draw beautiful pictures
and on top of that,
you back such
amazing cookies!
And in my book, that
makes you a wonderful
person.
Usagi...
Cheer up, okay?
Goodnight! Nice
meeting you!
In my book, you're
a wonderful person.
[giggling]
Yeah! I gave her some
good advice!...
I hope what I told her
makes Yumemi feel better
about herself.
Finally!-Usagi!
Hey! It's my Moon
Stick!
You dropped it in the
park. Listen, Usagi. If
you don't really want it,
I can easily find
someone else to
take it.
No! Of course I want it.
I was just preoccupied at
the time thinking about
Tuxedo Mask!
Well, it sure looks
like you're over that,
now.
I guess I am.
I guess that's a good
thing. You don't tend
to worry about things
for too long.
Deep down inside,
you're just a simple
girl.
Hmph!
Great, so you think
I'm a simple fool!
Gee, thanks, Luna!
Uh-oh. I was only
trying to be honest
with her. Maybe too
honest.
[panting]
Stupid Luna.
The reason girls like
me worry about things
is because we're not
simple!
[beeping]
Huh?!
I think that sound
came from Yumemi's
house!
Time to give me the
Rainbow Crystal and turn
back into a monster!
He's gorgeous! But
scary! Who are you
anyway?!
Zoi.
[screaming]
Good-now wake up, Veena!
[chuckling]
[gasping]
I can't believe
Yumemi was a monster!
Uh! No way!
[chuckling]
I'm afraid! No, I can't
be afraid of her! Oh,
boy--
Girls! A fourth Great
Monster has appeared!
Hm??!
I need you here right
away!
Right!
Now, Moon Prism
Power Make Up!
[chuckling]
That went well!
Hold it right there,
Zoisite!
What?!
Huh!
I won't let you take
Yumemi away! Trying to
destroy her dreams is
unforgivable!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice! I am
Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Hmph! Don't you ever
get tired of making that
same old speech? Veena,
destroy her.
[chuckling]
[trembling]
Hah!
[gasping]
Excellent Veena! Go
on-play with her some
more!
Ow-That hurt!
[chuckling]
Hah!
[gasping]
Oh! Thanks Tuxedo Mask!
[grunting]
Are you retreating
already? Not this time!
Go, Tuxedo Mask, go!
Hmm!
Yumemi, please stop this!
I beg you!
Try to remember your kind
heart! Yumemi!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Fire Soul!
You're here!
Sailor Moon! Great job
so far! We're here to
help!
[chuckling]
Huh?!
[grunting]
Bubble... Spray!
[straining]
Hey, go easy on her.
She's actually a really
nice person inside. Be
right back!
Huh?!
Now hand over the Rainbow
Crystal, Zoisite.
Never!
Zoi!
[grunting]
This should finish you!
[gasping]
Moon Tiara Action!
Hnh? Sailor Moon!
[grunting]
Are you okay?!
Tonight, it's you
who saved me.
Really? Uh!
♪
I suppose that this
pendant is yours,
isn't it?
Princess.
♪
What?! Does that mean
you know the princess?
We've actually been
looking for her for
quite a while now.
I don't know where she
is, but since it is your
mission to locate her, you
should hold onto this.
You mean it? Thank
you so much.
Uh, there is one other
thing. The Rainbow Crystal
that you took... could I
have that back, please?
No. I cannot turn
that over to you.
You see, all of the
Rainbow Crystals are
very important to me.
And if I see an opening
to steal a Rainbow Crystal
that you already possess,
I will.
What?! Then you're
really our enemy after
all!
When it comes to the
Rainbow Crystals, you may
be right. Farewell!
Why, Tuxedo Mask?
Oh no! I totally forgot
about Yumemi!
Supreme... Thunder!
[struggling]
Wait! Jupiter, that's
enough! Please stop it.
[groaning]
You're right, Sailor
Moon. She does look
pretty weak.
Sailor Moon, now's your
chance!
Right Luna!
Moon Healing Escalation!
[groaning]
Refresh!
[struggling]
Huh?
Oh-Usagi!
Hi Yumemi!
I'm surprised you invited
us-I thought you didn't
want people knowing what
you looked like.
[chuckling]
I've decided to stop
hiding from everyone.
It's beautiful!
I'd say it looks pretty
good considering who the
model was...
Ugh, would it kill
you to be nice once
in a while?
Oh, hey!
Huh?
All of my self-portraits
will look like this from
now on.
Thanks to you I've
found the courage to be
honest about myself and
what I look like, so now
I feel good sharing the
real me with everyone!
I'm so glad, Yumemi!
Autumn... the
season of longing.
A time when you want to
be with the one you
love.
There's no time for
that, you've got an
important mission!
Maybe a walk in a park
together or see a
movie...
Come back to reality!
Tuxedo Mask...
Motoki...
You know Motoki has a
girlfriend.
What?!
"Next time on Sailor Moon,
Total Chaos: The Messy
Love Rectangle"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.