(Usagi)
Remember! A student
should not be having
improper relationships
(cont'd)
with the opposite gender!
Especially when they're
older than you!
(cont'd)
And turning a beautiful
park into a place for evil
is absolutely unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
Hi! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
It may not look it,
but I'm actually a
superhero!
I use a special brooch
to transform and fight
evil!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights
for love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
I'm friends with the
kindhearted genius, Ami
Mizuno, who's Sailor
Mercury!
And Rei Hino, the
hotheaded psychic, who's
Sailor Mars.
Both of them seem to
have it a little more
together than I do.
But, oh well, guess
I just gotta do my
best!
(Giggles)
"Usagi's Panic: Rei's
First Date"
(Rei)
Oh, it's nice and
quiet here.
(Usagi)
Yeah, this is the
perfect place for a
date!
(Ami)
I'm glad you like
it.
(Rei)
I'm kind of suprrised
that you know of a
place like this, Ami.
(Ami)
Really? Well, sometimes I
come here to read before
I go to cram school.
(Ami)
Hi, Mr. Kokurtitsu!
Huh? Oh! Ami!
(Both)
Huh?
(Usagi)
Wow!
You're in charge of
taking care of this whole
enormous park all by
yourself?
Yes, but I won't be
for much longer.
What?
The person who owns this
land has sold the park
to a developer.
(Mr. Kokuritusu)
They plan to build a
large business complex
here.
(Sigh)
That's such a shame.
Especially for all the
wildlife. Where will
they go when this place
is destroyed?
(Mr. Kokuritsu)
It's a big problem.
That's too bad, this
is such a nice park.
(Mr. Kokuritsu)
Well, nothing we can
do about it now.
If this place is
closing, then I better
find a date and enjoy
it while I still can!
(Sigh)
Where are all the
girls? I can't find
anybody today.
Huh?!
Ahh!
(Mamoru Chiba)
Are you all right?
(Meow)
It doesn't look like
your injured.
(Usagi)
Hey!
Agh!
(Usagi)
What are you doing
to Luna?!
(Mamoru)
You need to take better
care of your cat!
(Mamoru)
She almost got hit
by a truck, bun-head!
She is none of your
business!
Luna isn't just some
ordianry cat, you know!
She's really special!
(Rei)
Stop it, Usagi!
(Ami)
Yeah, we should be
thanking him for saving
Luna!
(Luna meows)
(Usagi)
Why are you taking his
side?!
(Motoki)
Oh, hey!
What's up, man?
Oh, hey, Motoki!
(Usagi)
Motoki..You..
You know this guy?
(Motoki)
Sure! We go to the
same college.
You're a college
student?!
The stars see all, the
stars know all. Celestial
orbs, grant me your
mystical power.
Albireo, also called
Beta Cygni, is the
brightest it's been in
over a century.
The person whose energy
is increased the most
because of Albireo is
this man!
(Chuckle)
Once his energy has
reached its peak, I
shall take it all!
What?! I'm gonna
play again!
(Ami)
Should you really be
wasting your money
like this?
(Usagi)
You're right! Give me
a quarter!
Ah, so that Mamoru
guy is living all by
himself, huh?
Yeah, he has a very
expensive condo.
His family is rich!
And he goes to the same
college as you, right?
He must be smart! Isn't it
a tought school to get into?
Yeah, I guess it is.
But listen, Rei, why do
you want to know so much
about him, anyway?
Oh, no particular
reason!
Mamoru Chiba, he'd
be the perfect boyfriend
for me!
(Chuckles)
(Rei)
I've made up my
mind!
(Rei)
I'm gonna go on a
date with Mamoru in that
park before it closes.
Uh-Ah!
Not yet! Ami, give
me another quarter!
Uh, hey, are you
okay there, Rei?
(Rei)
No, not really!
There must be some way
to save this natural
habitat before it's gone.
(Kokuritsu)
Why can't you save
it?
Hey, who are you?
Why are you here?!
Humans have stopped
respecting the
environment almost
entirely.
You must show these
arrogant people...
...the fury that
Mother Nature
possesses.
Why, me?
Because...
(Kokuritsu)
...it's your duty.
Hear me, my monster.
Take control of this
man's hat and absorb
his energy!
(Heavy Breathing)
You must show these
arrogant people. The
fury that Mother Nature
possess!
Because it's your
duty!
Ah-Ahh!
(Men Yelling)
What's going on?!
Get out of here!
Hurry!
Using my monster's
power, you can control
animals and insects
however you please.
(Nephrite)
And the more you use
that power, the more
your energy will grow!
(Deep Laughter)
According to what
Motoki said, this is
the route Mamoru takes
home after school.
Ah!
Oops! I'm sorry!
I guess I wasn't
looking where I was
going!
Oh, no. It's fine.
I'm the one who
should've been more
careful.
(Mamoru)
Why don't I make it
up to you by buying
you a cup of coffee?
Sure, that's wonderful!
I love coffee!
That's great!
Yeah, that's the
plan!
(Giggles)
I'll create my chance
by bumping into him
on purpose!
(Luna)
Usagi, you're going
to gain weight again.
(Usagi)
Don't worry, it's
organic!
(Luna)
Hey, it's Rei!
Hm? Huh?
(Usagi)
You're right!
I wonder what she's
up to.
(Giggles)
Here he comes!
Now! Here goes!
Ah!
Oh!
Gah!
Are you all right?!
I have no idea what
she's doing over
there, but she's sure
being clumsy!
Clumsy? Look who's
talking!
Yeah, I think I'm
okay.
Oh, all right! Great!
Have a nice day!
Wait!
Huh?
Hold on. Aren't you
friends with that
bun-head girl?
Yes! My name's Rei
Hino. We met the other
day at Dream Land.
Oh! You didn't get
hurt back there at all,
did you?
No, not a bit.
But, uh...
I'm sorry about all
this. Let me make it
up to you by buying
you some coffee.
What are you sorry
about?
Oh! For uh...
For putting my head
in the way of your
foot!
Huh?!
(Mamoru)
Well, I guess that
I could join you.
(Gasp)
Really?! That's great!
(Mamoru)
Yay...
Everything's working
out just perfect.
Huh?!
(Usagi)
What does he think he's
doing with Rei?! I'd say
that he needs to find
(cont'd)
someone his own age,
don't you?!
You know, Usagi. I
don't think that Mamoru
is as bad a person as
you think he is.
What do you mean?!
It's obviously an
improper relationship!
Even my student
handbook says
something like this
is unacceptable!
Anyway, Rei could
be in danger!
Let's follow them!
Come on!
Ah- I really don't
like where this is
headed.
Sailor Moon!
(Rei)
Um...
Huh?
Would you like
some sugar?
(Mamoru)
Oh, I'll pass.
Of course! I
should have known!
(Rei)
Yeah, sugar is
totally gross!
I wanna go in to
hear what they're
talking about! Ugh!
I wish I had some money!
It's your fault for
wasting your allowance
on ice cream!
I know!
(Usagi)
I'll transform into
a waitress!
You can't do that!
Why not?
You know why! It's only
meant to be used for
good!
So, I'll be a good
waitress!
(Gurio Umino)
Usagi!
(Gasps)
What are you doing
down here?
Umino...
Hey, Umino! Hi! Say,
do you have any money
on you?
Um, yeah.
Then how would you
like to go on a date
with me, right now?
(Umino)
Really?! I mean, yes!
Yes, yes!
I can't watch this.
So, Mamoru,
Do you have any more
free time today?
'Cause there's this
great place that I know.
Would you like to
go see it with me?
Okay. Yeah, sure,
why not?
Really?!
It's going just as
I planned!
I can't hear them
from here, either!
Ah!
(Luna)
Hey, Ami!
Huh?
(Giggles)
Luna!
Huh? What's the
matter? You seem like
you're feeling sad.
Yeah...
(Park Rep)
Well...
(cont'd)
The construction company
that was doing the job
at the park has quit.
At this point, it looks
like we'll keep the
park the way it is.
And so, we would like for
you to continue taking
care of it, as usual.
Hmm...
(Luna)
What?! The park
manager said that?
Yeah, he's never
been so strict before.
From now on, you
can't just come to
the park whenever you
want!
You don't deserve the
gifts that Mother
Nature has to offer!
I wonder what
happened to him.
Ugh! I'm tired of
this unreliable
construction company.
(Sighs)
Do they really expect
me to believe that insects
and animals attacked them?
Ahh!
Ah-Ah-Ahh!
What's happening?
I won't come near
this park ever again!
Ah! I'm sorry!
(Luna)
Those squirrels are
filled with evil energy!
(Ami)
Huh?!
This has to be the
work of the Dark
Kingdom!
Oh, no! Did they
get to Mr. Kokuritsu
too?!
(Mamoru)
Wow! I never knew
this town had a park
like this!
(Rei)
Yeah, but it's gonna
be torn down soon. Which
is really unfortunate.
(Mamoru)
What?
They're gonna turn
it into an office
complex instead.
(Sigh)
Sorry to hear that.
(Mamoru)
It's such a nice park,
so full of natural
beauty.
Yeah, exactly! You
think so, too?
Yes, I believe that
people have a duty to
take much better care
of Mother Nature.
Mamoru.
(Usagi)
Oh! What could they
be talking about
out there?!
I'm going have to find
a way to get closer
if I want to hear them!
Usagi, you're very
bold to bring me
to this place.
I mean, we're still
kids, you know? We
should take it slow.
But then again.
I suppose just one
smooch wouldn't hurt!
Usagi? Wh-What about
the smooching?!
Huh?!
(Ami)
Usagi!
(Usagi)
Ami! Luna! I didn't
know you were here!
Let me guess, you
guys also came to check
up on those two, right?
Stop talking nonsense!
This is serious!
Listen, Usagi!
Something seriously
bad has been happening
here in the park!
What?! What's going
on?!
(Mr. Kokuritsu)
You again?!
(Gasps)
(Ami)
Mr. Kokuritsu!
All you ungrateful
humans!
(Mr. Kokuritsu)
You've abused the gifts
Mother Nature has given
you!
The only way to make
up for it is with
you deaths!
(Nephrite)
His energy has
reached its peak!
Now, Petasos! Do it!
Ah!
(Sinister Lauging)
A monster!
Hear me, all you animals
in this park! Attack
the humans!
Ahh!
Unforgivable!
Mercury Power!
Make up!
(Luna)
Don't just stand
there, Usagi!
I know, all right!
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
(Gasps)
(Painful Grunts)
Mamoru?! What is it?
What's wrong?
(Rei)
What's going on?!
Look out!
(Chuckling)
Ah!
What's happening?!
Help! Ah!
Bubble!
Spray!
Uhh..
We've stopped your
animal attack, and now
we're gonna stop you!
Wow! Sailor Mercury
is all fired up!
Hm! In that case!
Hand flower!
Look out!
Ah!
Sailor Moon! No!
Heh! Petasos Rope!
Huh? Ah!
(Mamoru)
Hey.
Are you all right?
(Rei)
Yeah, I'm okay.
How about you?
Heh. Just a little
wet, that's all.
That was crazy!
(Rei)
What an intense
evil aura!
Mamaru, you stay here.
I have to go do
something!
(Struggling)
Sailor Mercury!
No!
Uh..
Hm. I'll get rid
of you first!
Ah!
Can't lose!
I have to save Mr.
Kokuritsu!
Huh?
(Rei)
Fire Soul!
Ah!
(Screams)
You okay?!
(Usagi)
I'd be beter if you
didn't try to set me
on fire!
Is that how you talk
to someone who just
saved you?!
(Usagi)
Uhh...
Oh, so she's the one
who interrupted my
date!
You'll pay for
exploiting Mr.
Kokuritsu's kindness!
Yeah, and for turning
a beautiful park into
a place for evil!
(Both)
And now, in the name
of the moon..
(Both)
We'll punish you!
Aw! Hey, you stole
my catchphrase!
Hm. Enough of you
impudent humans!
I'll kill you all!
Ah!
Agh!
(Gasps)
Thanks,Tuxedo Mask!
It's up to you now,
Sailor Moon!
Got it!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
Agh!
Ah-Ah-Ahh!
(Struggling Breaths)
'Till we meet again,
Sailor Guardians.
(Dreamy Sighs)
My hero!
(Mr. Kokuritsu)
Ami, I don't remember.
What happened to me?
It's all right.
Don't worry now.
You were just having
a bad dream.
Good grief, what a
horrible experience.
Mamoru! Are you sure
you should be up
and about?!
Yeah. Pretty sure
I'm doing okay.
Hey, you know what I
think? I bet Mamoru
is secretly Tuxedo Mask!
There is no way an
annoying guy like him
could be Tuxedo Mask!
Huh?!
What's that?!
Who's this Tuxedo Mask?
Oh, don't worry about
it! He's no one, really!
(Rei)
I know I'm right!
Mamoru has to be Tuxedo
Mask!
Oh! Usagi!
Uh! Umino...
(Umino)
I've been looking
for you!
Well, since I found
you, let's finish our
date!
AH!-Uh..
(Rei Chuckles)
(Mamoru)
Oh...
(Usagi)
Umino! Stop making
stuff up!
What are you talking
about, Usagi? You're
the one who asked me
out!
Don't you remember
that?!
Uoh, so that's your
type, huh?
No, it's not like
that!
(Usagi)
You guys have it
all wrong!
(Usagi)
It's every girl's dream
to have the perfect
wedding.
(Luna)
Daydreaming again?
(Usagi)
How romantic to be married
under the wedding bell
at a quaint chapel.
(Luna)
Uh huh...
(Usagi)
I'd be so happy in a
beautiful white wedding
dress.
(Luna)
Uh-huh...
(Usagi)
And of course, you
can't forget the kiss!
(Luna)
Ah! Too much
information!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"A Girl's Dream: Usagi
Becomes A Bride."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.