You dare to turn a
kid's hero like Redman
into an evil monster
and force him to use
Lake Akan's famous
Marimo algae balls
as a weapon against
innocent people?!
I bet the Hokkaido
Sightseeing Association
didn't give you permission
to do that, did they?!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Hey! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
This job's not easy
by the way...
We have to find and
protect the Legendary
Silver Crystal before
the bad guys get it.
But in order to do that,
we need to find the Seven
Rainbow Crystals and
the people holding them!
Pretty crazy, huh?
But now there are four
of us Sailor Guardians,
so I think everything's
gonna work out
just fine.
(giggling)
"Umino's Resolve:
I'll protect Naru"
Huh?
Codename Zero-Zero-
Nine-One. This is
Luna. Passphrase:
"The rabbit on the
moon is pounding
rice cakes", please
respond ASAP.
The moon's rice
cakes are sticky.
And they puff up
when you toast
them, as well.
So then, how are the
Sailor Guardians doing?
One of them still
has issues with
responsibility, but
the others are really
doing very well
indeed!
The day when all
five Guardians come
together is near.
What you mean that?!
Yes. Therefore, now
is the time for you
to explain everything
to them.
You're sure
about that?
We know that the
Dark Kingdom has
been growing more
and more restless.
We have to prepare
the Sailor Guardians.
They need to know what
they're fighting for.
I understand.
The time has finally
come to tell them.
(yawning)
Why would Luna want
to meet with us so
late at night?
Huh?
It's good that
you're all here.
Has another monster
appeared?
I don't want
to scare you!
Whaa! But you
just did!
Listen carefully
to what I'm about
to tell you.
Huh?
I was sent here
all the way from
the Moon to help
guide you!
What?!
The Moon?!
Why?!
No way!
So then why did you
come to Earth, Luna?
I came here to
awaken each of
you.
I dunno. This
story just gets
weirder.
True, but if Luna
says that she came
here from the moon.
I believe her.
Thanks a lot for
that, Ami.
The Princess you've
been searching for
carries the royal
bloodline of the
Moon Kingdom.
The Moon
Kingdom?
Royal bloodline?
There's really a
kingdom somewhere
on the Moon? Now
that sounds more
like a fairytale.
You four girls are
destined to meet
that Princess and
very soon you'll
take on the important
duty of protecting her!
And time is of
the essence!
Hey Luna, I just
have one question-
Is there really a
rabbit on the moon
that pounds
rice cakes?
Oh, come on!
Well?
Look at them.
They're truly
lovely.
And yet, their
true beauty will
be revealed only
when all seven
Rainbow Crystals
come together.
Don't you agree?
I'll get those last
three crystals. Then
we'll see their beauty
shine, won't we, Kunzite?
We certainly will.
(happy sigh)
Once we've collected
all of the Rainbow
Crystals, the Legendary
Silver Crystal will
be in our grasp.
Possessing the Silver
Crystal will surely
please our Queen.
Imagine how delighted
Queen Beryl will be.
What?!
But what about me?
Ooh, that
looks good!
Umino, you wanna
trade a fried shrimp
of yours for some
of my sweet peppers?
Sure Naru, if you'd
like it, have one!
Hey thanks!
(wolf whistle)
You two sure look
cute together.
So, are the two
of you going out?
Does it look
that way?
Hhah-ha-ha.
Whoa! Umino and
I are not together.
We're not dating.
He and I are
just friends.
Oh... We're
friends...
Just friends,
huh?
Y'know Umino's a
really nice guy...
And he's smart and
always helps me
with my schoolwork.
I like him, but there's
just something missing.
You know what I mean?
If you wanna win
Naru over, be
pushy! Pushy!
Pushy!
Yeah? But how
should I do that?
Then I, with all my
experience in love,
will have to instruct
you on how to do it!
We're gonna have to
transform you into
a super cool guy!
A super cool guy,
huh? Like who?
Like who?! Why
like Tuxedo Mask!
So Tuxedo Mask
is super cool?
Tuxedo Mask is the
coolest guy ever!
Aha! I see! So if I
transform myself into
Tuxedo Mask, then I
could be Naru's
boyfriend?!
Well uh, that's not
what I meant. I meant
using Tuxedo Mask as
a role model might-
Okay! From now on,
I'm going to be just
like Tuxedo Mask!
Mmm-Hmm!
From now on, call me
"Tuxedo Umino Mask!"
Do you get the
feeling someone's
following us?
Huh?
Ahhhh!
Fifi! Be a good
doggie and stop
barking!
Don't fear!
I'm here!
Tuxedo Umino Mask
is on the scene!
How dare you bare
your fangs at Naru!
What're you
trying to do!
How rude!
Aww! Did that
weird boy scare
you sweetie!
Umino, what're
you doing?
(chuckling)
I'm no longer
Umino!
I'm Tuxedo Umino
Mask! Defender of
love and justice!
Farewell!
What's with him?
(nervous laughter)
Hey, wanna stop
in for a bit!
Sure!
You mustn't! Stopping
here on your way home
is wrong! Before you
know it, your whole
allowance will be
gone! And if you
insist on going in,
you'll have to do
it by going over
my live body! Hm!
All right then!
Ahh! My spleen!
Excuse us!
Tuxedo Umino Mask
may die, but love
and justice will
live on!
What's Umino
trying to do
anyway?
(nervous giggles)
I have no clue!
Hey! How's
it going?
Hi Motoki!
Oh yeah! I got two
free tickets to a
show, ya wanna go?
Free tickets!
For two?!
I don't believe
it! He's asking
me out!
Me on a movie
date with Motoki!
It's a dream come
true!
Yeah, I'm way too
old to go see the
Redman Show at the
amusement park.
The Redman Show?!
Oh! Guess you girls
are too old for that
show too, aren't ya?
(nervous laughter)
Ah!
We'll take them!
Huh? You want
to go to it?
You should go
together with
Umino!
Huh?!
I'd be happy to!
I just don't feel
up to going.
He-he! Umino's doing
his very best in his
own way. C'mon at least
give him a chance!
She doesn't care
about me. I might as
well just forget it.
Okay, okay, fine.
I'll go with him.
But you owe me one.
(excited giggle)
Oh yeah!
All right then! Ah!
Tuxedo Umino Mask
is back in action!
(sad sigh)
There, there.
New power.
Come forth!
I've improved what
the Dark Crystal
is capable of.
With it, we can
turn human beings
into monsters.
(evil chuckle)
My dear Kunzite,
Soon I will collect
the remaining Rainbow
Crystals from Sailor
Moon and the others.
(chuckles)
To lure Sailor Moon
to me, I will turn
Naru Osaka into a
monster and she will
do my bidding.
(door bell ringing)
Yes. Who is it?
Tuxedo Mask!
He's good! He's
already seen through
my plan! Looks like
I'll have to pay the
girl a visit
another time.
Gah!
What was that I just
saw?! Wowie! It's a
good thing I was here
to protect Naru.
Hello? Who's
out there?
It's Tuxedo
Umino Mask!
What's with you?!
Don't you know it's
almost midnight!
Well, we didn't decide
what time to meet
tomorrow, so I thought
I'd just stop by to-
Uh?! Naru!
Hey, what time should
I be at the amusement
park to meet you?!
Naru?!
Ten? Eleven? Twelve-
thirty?! What time?
Hey!
Let's meet
at twelve.
Then twelve it is.
That means we can
have lunch together.
And Tuxedo Umino
Mask will bring you
lots of your favorite
deep fried shrimp, okay?
Okay?!
Hello...
Sailor Moon!
So Usagi, now that
you know more about
your mission, what
are you doing to
find the Princess?
You weren't even
listening to me,
were you?
No, I heard you!
Really! But I just
couldn't sleep if I
didn't know where my
best friend's love
life is going! You
know what I mean?
Agh, you need to
work on what's
really important.
Why'd you follow me
to the amusement
park anyway?
As a wise messenger
from the Moon, I'm
concerned what actions
a certain foolish
Guardian might take.
Know what I mean?
Ah! There
they are!
Hey, Usagi!
Wait up!
Hi-ya!
Rawr!
Redman is here!
Hee-yuh!
Ahhh!
Redman Leg Attack!
I'm glad you didn't
come wearing that
funny costume today,
Umino.
(nervous giggle)
Why would I?
But just in case
I brought it.
Don't worry Naru,
if you need to be
protected it's in
my pack.
(nervous laugh)
Redman Punch!
(crowd cheering)
Dark Crystal,
transform that
girl into a
monster.
(laughing)
Hunh?!
Victory is mine!
Ooh!
(growling)
He transformed
into a monster!
Now it's monster
versus monster!
The monster Akan
is born!
Monster?!
Oh no, looks like my
crystal's transforming
beam hit the wrong
person!
(fighting growls)
This wasn't in
the script!
Have some algae
balls from Lake
Akan!
Ahh!
You too!
Hey what're you
doing?! Quit it!
Oh!
Luna, what's
going on?
This must be the
Dark Kingdom's
doing!
Naru!
(scared gasp)
Time for some marimo
algae from Lake Akan!
Move! C'mon
Naru! Run!
Usagi!
Get back here!
Stop that!
(gasps)
Umino!
I, Tuxedo Umino Mask
will protect Naru!
Eat fried shrimp!
Hnh...
Umino! Don't
do this!
Take that!
And now take this!
Ahhh!
Umino!
Ugh. Tuxedo Umino
Mask will keep on
protecting Naru!
I will keep her
safe even if it
costs me my life!
Umino...
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
Ahhhh!
(painful grunts)
Umino!
Naru...
Get away...
Quickly...
Leave him alone!
Ahh!
Someone help us!
How dare you use a
natural treasure
like marimo algae
as a weapon!
I bet the Hokkaido
Sightseeing Association
didn't say you could use
that algae, now did they?
Akan!
Listen up,
monster!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights
for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the
name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
(evil giggling)
Nice you could show up
on such short notice.
Zoisite!
I've been wanting to
see you Sailor Moon.
I have this very special
favor to ask of you...
And what's that?!
I demand that you
give me the Rainbow
Crystal that you have.
There's no way I'm
giving it to you!
Well if you refuse,
you're going to let
the people encased
in these algae
balls suffocate.
Huh?!
It's too bad, because
I don't think these
people are going to be
able to breathe for
too much longer.
(struggling grunts)
(struggling breaths)
How could you!
Now, hand over that
Rainbow Crystal!
You heard me,
hand it over!
Now!
Oh all right!
It's yours.
Good girl...
(painful grunt)
Not you again!
Ah! Tuxedo Mask!
I can't allow
you to have that
Rainbow Crystal,
Zoisite!
Silence!
(growling)
Akan!
Ahh!
Zoi!
It's Tuxedo Umino
Mask, he's trying
to...
Moon Tiara!
Action!
This might hurt
a little bit!
Ak-kanan!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Ahhh!
Refresh!
(relaxed sigh)
(exhausted groans)
Wow! She managed to
defeat the monster
all by herself!
Oh no!
The Rainbow Crystal!
What?!
Thanks for helping
me out with this
Rainbow Crystal.
Hey! Hold on!
You give that
back!
Ta-ta!
Curse you Zoisite!
Aww! The Rainbow
Crystal's gone!
Whatever it takes.
I will get that
Rainbow Crystal back.
Thank you so
much Tuxedo
Mask!
Don't thank me.
Once I finally
recover that
crystal, I'll be
keeping it.
Huh?!
Until we meet
again, farewell!
(people cheering)
Hi-ya!
(growls)
Redman is back!
Heh-yah!
Was that stuff
before part of
the show?
I dunno, but
it sure was
awesome!
Redman Leg
Attack!
Thank you so much
Umino, you were
really cool today.
Just call me
Tuxedo Umino
Mask.
Tuxedo Umino Mask.
(excited giggles)
Ugh, Usagi?
Having that Rainbow
Crystal stolen from
us was a real setback.
Hey, are you
listening to me?!
I'm so confused...
Why would Tuxedo
Mask say that?
Once I finally Recover
that Crystal, I'll be
keeping it...
Usagi, we've got real
trouble! A Sailor
Moon impostor has
shown up!
What?! He-he-he!
Well if an impostor
has shown up, then
that means I must
be super famous!
Oh c'mon! What're
you talking about?
You need to get out
there and stop her!
But what if she's
actually on of us?
Hey wait, that's
Sailor V!
Next time on Sailor Moon:
"Enter Venus, the Last
Sailor Guardian."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.