Autumn is the season of
love for all living
creatures. Earthworms
crickets, heck even Rei
falls in love! And I
won't forgive those
who try to ruin the
love between people,
or animals for
that matter!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the protection of
animals everywhere.
I'll punish you!
Hey! I'm Usagi Tsukino!
You know me as the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
This job's not
easy by the way!
We have to find and
protect the Legendary
Silver Crystal before
the bad guys get it!
But in order to do that
we need to find the Seven
Rainbow Crystals and the
people holding them!
Pretty crazy, huh?
But now there are
four of us Sailor
Guardians, so I
think everything's
gonna work out
just fine!
(giggling)
"Loved and Chased:
Luna's Worst Day Ever"
(Luna screaming)
Huh?
(bossy growl)
(confused meow)
Eeh...
(scared meows)
(disgusted gasp)
Rhett Butler,
where are you?!
There you are!
I was so worried!
Ahh-h!
Isn't my idea of
what a 'Rhett Butler'
would look like.
Oh, my...
I never would've
guessed that our
last target would be
a cute little girl.
But she's got the
Seventh Rainbow
Crystal.
And this one will
be easy to get.
Sounds like you had
one hectic morning.
Tell me about it.
I don't want anything
more to do with stray
cats, their turf wars
or whatever else
they're doing!
We're here!
Sorry to keep
you waiting!
Hey, where's Rei?
Ah... Um... She
mentioned something
about going on a date
because it's Sunday.
Hi! It's Mamoru...
(gasp)
Hi, it's Rei!
How's it going?
...I'm not home at
the moment. Please
leave a message
after the beep.
Okay...
Hi, Mamoru! This is
Rei! I found this
wonderful little shop
that has an unusual
cake called Tiramisu,
I mean it may not be
that unusual, but
I've never tasted it.
Anyway, I was
wondering if you
would like to go
there with me...
The Seventh Rainbow
Crystal. I'm going
to get my hands on it.
So what are you
doing there, Ami?
I'm trying to track
down the Seventh
Rainbow Crystal.
Huh? That's odd, my
Moon Stick isn't
reacting one bit.
The Moon Stick works
when we're close to
it, so we'll use the
computer to calculate
its location. We've
gathered the data,
but putting it in
takes so long!
(whining groan)
All done!
You've finished
inputting the data,
huh?
According to this,
the Seventh Rainbow
Crystal is right there!
Wow!
Hmmm...
So you think the
Rainbow Crystal is
somewhere around
that house?
If the data's
right, it should
be.
Hm?
Oh brother! Just
my luck! That
cat lives here!
Let's go.
C'mon!
You go on. I
think I'm just
gonna hang back.
Huh? But
what for?
I've got stuff
go do.
Your stuff can
wait. This is a
very important
mission, Luna.
Try to remember what
your duties are!
Stop being so rude!
I've never looked
that ugly in my
life!
It's all right.
We'll do fine!
There are times when
even Luna doesn't want
to go on missions.
I guess I'll have
to accept that.
Wait for us right
here so we can
find you!
Don't move even
an inch!
Yeah, yeah.
Frankly, I wish Usagi
would always show
such initiative.
Hm?
Uh?
(aggressive meows)
Uhh...!!
Ahh!!
Yes?
Hi! Sorry to
bother you.
Is your mother or
your father home?
No, they're not.
They won't be home
until tonight.
(gasp)
I know. My Stick's
reacting.
Could that little
girl be a monster?
Stop! Come
back here!
Rhett Butler!
Please stop!
Rhett Butler?
(evil chuckling)
(fearful scream)
(angry meows)
Ahh!
(surprised meows)
(nervous meows)
Meow?
Ahhh!
Wo-oh-oh!
Meow!
Ahhhh!
Meow!!
(chuckle)
Now then. It's time
for me to take the
Rainbow Crystal.
Huh?!
What's going on?
Why isn't the
Rainbow Crystal
appearing?!
(gasp)
It was right in front
of my eyes. That ugly
fat cat is the monster!
How could I have
been so careless?!
The final Great
Monster was reborn
as an animal, not
a human!
Stop right there!
Now that we've
arrived, you won't
be getting your way
Zoisite!
We won't let you
turn that child
into a monster!
In the name of
the moon, I'll
punish you!
Hah!
Zoi!
(scream)
Bubble...
Sailor Moon,
you're in my way!
I can't help it!
I'm done here.
I don't have time
to play these games
with you.
You're not getting
away! Now, supreme...
H-Hey wait!
We'll all be
electrocuted!
Uhhh...
It smells really
rotten down here!
Why does that ugly
fat cat have to hang
out in such a stinky
place? This is exactly
why I hate non-
human monsters!
O-Oh no!
This might be the
greatest challenge
that I'll ever have
to face!
Sailor Moon!
I wonder where Luna
went. It's been a
while since we saw
her.
I told her not
to move but did
she listen?! No!
She's abandoned
us in the middle
of an important
mission!
Luna would never
do anything like
that!
I'm worried that
something might
have happened to
her!
Oh?
Ahh! This little
girl has a copy
of the Sailor V
video game! Look!
Oh, Usagi.
We should stay on
alert. We don't know
when Zoisite will try
to come after her again.
I still can't believe
that this little girl
has a Rainbow Crystal.
(Usagi yelling)
Which means, she'll
turn into a monster.
(chuckling)
It's so close!
That ugly fat cat is
quite near by, now.
It feels warm.
Huh?
(screaming)
It's a moving
wall of rats!
I wonder where
Mamoru went? I was
sure we were getting
together today.
This isn't how I
wanted to spend my
Sunday afternoon.
Rei!
Huh?
Yuichiro?!
Hey, you! Looks like
you have today off,
too, am I right?
Yeah. I'm just sort
of hanging out. Would
you like to have a
cup of tea with me?
Well, I'm not
sure. I may have
other plans.
Oh, yeah, what was
I thinking, springing
this on you last
minute. A beautiful
girl like you is
probably all
booked up.
Huh?! Yeah...
I guess...
Ah! Got it! Oh
well then. Have
a nice day!
Huh?! Uh-h...
Oh wow, he sure took
off in a big hurry.
He's just gone with
the wind. See ya!
Aww, I don't see
an exit anywhere!
Ugh! Well we're sure
going nowhere. If
you had just stayed
away...
(gasp)
W-What happened to
you? Your leg is
hurt!
Did you injure it
when you leapt down
from that high wall
to rescue me?
Come to think of
it, you risked your
life two times to
help me...
Does that mean you
like me or something?
What a purr-
dicament!
Huh?!
Th-that's!
It's Zoisite!
I've found him! The
Seventh Great Monster!
What?! You have the
Rainbow Crystal that
we're all looking for?!
Quickly! Go through
that hole! He won't
be able to get in!
You won't get
away from me!
Ahhh!
Go-go-go-go!
Huh?
Ahh!
I'm taking the
Rainbow Crystal!
Nothing will stop me!
(fearful screams)
Ahhh!
Faster!
Look! There's
the exit!
(wishful sigh)
I should have said
yes to Yuichiro. Then
at least I could say
I had a date.
It's Luna! I didn't
know she had a
boyfriend. She's
pretty sly.
Huh?
Ahhh! What's
going on?!
Oh!
I should have noticed
this sooner!
The Moon Stick isn't
reacting! There's no
reaction at all!
But that means...
She has nothing
to do with the
Rainbow Crystal.
So then, why did the
Moon Stick react when
we arrived here earlier?
(gasps)
You don't think?!
It has to be that the
stick was reacting
to the cat!
(screams)
Game over!!
Faster! Run
Faster!
Ahhh!
Ow!
(scared whines)
What looked like a
disaster has turned
into my good fortune.
And in the end,
everything has
worked out to my
advantage!
Fire Soul!
(luna screaming)
Sailor Mars, the
Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and
for justice is here...
...to save the day!
I won't let you get
in the way of their
beautiful cat love!
You've got it
all wrong!!
The flames of love
are burning!
The flames of
justice are
burning!
I can't forgive those
who get in the way
of love...
...between people and
all living creatures!
So in the name of
Mars. I'll chastise
you!
Ha! You little fool!
Zoi!
(nervous gasp)
You should try
getting a grasp of
the situation before
you show off!
This time I'm getting
the Rainbow Crystal
for sure.
(screaming meow)
(gasps)
Oh no! Rhett Butler!
(scared gasps)
(growl)
Rhett Butler!
Is that you?!
Now get rid of them,
Great Monster!
They don't have any
back-up. It's a
piece of cake!
(painful whine)
I'll be taking the
final Rainbow Crystal.
Farewell!
Curse you!
Tuxedo Mask, you
thief! Come b-b-back
with my Rainbow
Crystal!
Oh no! It looks
like he's headed
into town!
Stop!
Luna!
Stop-stop-stop-stop-
stop! Please don't
move! Just stay still!
My friends will come
to help you soon,
I promise!
(vicious growl)
(screaming)
Luna!
(gasp)
Y-you saved me
again...
It'll be all right.
Usagi'll be here
soon and turn you
back to normal.
I knew it! Those
two are madly in
love!
Bubble!
Spray!
Oh no! You ruined
the moment!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sorry we're late!
Yeah, you'd better
be! What took you
so long to get here?
Sorry, I got a little
distracted by some
video game noise.
Me too, and it's
really not because
Usagi was playing
all those games.
Right! Usagi was
just trying to
have some fun!
Uh... You know,
you girls aren't
really helping me
a whole lot.
Hey! Enough already!
You need to get
serious!
Right!
(growls)
Moon Healing
Escalation!
Meow-fresh!
Oh, thank
goodness!
(giggling)
Oh, I was so worried
about you. Did you
miss me, Rhett Butler?
She's so happy to
have her kitty back!
Now, are you sure
you don't want to
say goodbye to your
boyfriend, Luna?
Get out! You and
that cat were
lovers, Luna?!
Woah! How'd you
come up with
that idea?!
Whoo-hoo! Luna's
hot, and love is
bitten!
(annoyed groan)
Even Usagi's making
fun of me! I don't
appreciate being the
victim of idle gossip.
Ooh... Give me
a break.
A new hero makes
an appearance on
Sailor Moon!
Everyone already
knows who he is,
but he's dressed
in a tuxedo and
wears a black
cape!
And like the wind,
he appears out of
nowhere to protect and
fight just for Naru!
Everyone...
Meet...
...Tuxedo Umino
Mask!
Next time on Sailor Moon,
"Umino's Resolve: I'll
Protect Naru"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.