[HOLO] So this is
the port town of Pazzio!
It looks like they have
delicious things to eat!
[LAWRENCE] Hey.
[HOLO] What?
I don't understand
why you don't have
to hide your face.
Are you implying something?
Nothing, it's just
if you've been
in that village for
hundreds of years,
shouldn't there be a legend
about you turning into a girl?
At certain times Holo
will appear in the village
in the form of a
pretty young woman.
And she is always seen
as a mid adolescent.
A lovely figure,
she has long flowing hair
as well as wolf ears and
a beautiful dark brown tail
with a splash of
white at the end.
In return for the
keeping of her secret,
she promises to make
the village's harvest
rich next year.
[LAWRENCE]
Sounds like you.
Even if I did
reveal everything,
they would only be as
skeptical as you were.
Unless I show
my ears and tail,
they will have no idea.
No, I suppose not.
They will not notice...
After all, they do
not remember me anymore.
[LAWRENCE]
And for both of our sakes,
I hope you're
right about that.
[HOLO] I am sure
it will be fine.
Oh!
This town is exactly what
I was hoping it would be.
[LAWRENCE]
Do you see those apples...
they look pretty
good don't they?
[HOLO]
They do!
Oh, they smell
absolutely wonderful.
Yes, they do.
Actually, an old
acquaintance of mine
dealt in apple futures.
He put more than half
of his assets towards it.
I don't know where
those apples were from,
but his investment
would've probably
more than doubled by now.
I should've gone
that route, too.
Yes.
I am sorry you did not.
[LAWRENCE] Well, you know,
the risk was high.
If I were him,
I'd'a used a vessel.
What? A vessel?
Yeah, I mean
if it got wrecked
you could end up
losing everything,
including your life.
But if all went well,
you could stand to make
an extraordinary profit.
You okay?
Well...
So what you do is
you rent a vessel.
The shipment size
is decided based
upon the amount
of money paid.
[HOLO]
Apples... Apples...
Oh please? Can I?
Oh, so that's
what you want.
Go buy as many
as you want with this.
Who buys that
many apples?
You are the one
who told me
to buy as many
as I wanted.
Maybe you just don't
have enough self-control.
Remember you're going to have
to earn these meals.
You tricked me.
You were only
pretending
not to notice I wanted them.
Well, were you or not?
I have to admit it
feels kind of nice
to know what people
are thinking sometimes.
Those are mine!
Hey! It was my money!
I am Holo the Wise Wolf.
I can earn this
money back quickly.
Which is a good thing.
Because I had originally
planned on using
that silver coin to cover
our room and board.
[LAWRENCE] How could
you eat that much?
[HOLO] Apples are
the devils fruit.
They are full of a rich and
sweet temptation from hell.
If you're such a wise wolf,
why don't you
have more control?
You might lose
things due to appetite,
but it is not as if holding
back is beneficial.
Our client today is in
the big building right there.
[HOLO] Their entrance
is rather large,
but, if you are comparing
the size of the whole structure,
I am sure there must
be bigger buildings.
[LAWRENCE] They're the third
largest trading company.
But, it's actually only a branch
of an even larger
trading company
who is based out of a
country in the far south.
Because they're
new to this area,
they have a tendency to pay
a higher price when
they're buying things.
But more importantly...
[HOLO] They receive
various information
from their other branches
as well as their
main store, correct?
And since they run their
business across borders...
It is possible they
would hear of a change
in the currency market, also.
Exactly.
I'm going to ask them
if they have
heard anything
about what Zheren
said to us.
Maybe confirm it.
[INFO CLERK] Welcome
to Milone Trading.
I've been here before.
I sold wheat to you
about three years ago.
Today I was hoping you
would buy some fur from me.
Yes. Yes.
I'm sure that will be fine.
[ASSESSOR] For using
our service today,
we thank you very much.
Your name is
Craft Lawrence, isn't it?
[LAWRENCE]
Yes, it is.
I am honored that
you remembered me.
[ASSESSOR]
We're honored you came back.
They told me you were here
because you wanted us
to purchase some of your fur.
[LAWRENCE]
That's right.
There are a total of seventy.
[ASSESSOR] Nice.
These are very good marten furs.
With all the different crops
having rich harvests this year,
we haven't had that
many of them come in.
I'm sure all the
farmers were too busy
working the land
to go hunting.
Yet, look at how many
I've brought for you.
Yes...
Now, let's see, you said
there are seventy of them?
Yes. That's right.
Then, since we have
done business before,
how does this sound:
132 coins.
132? Which coin?
Trenni silver coins.
Furs like these come
once every few years...
Maybe even
once in a decade.
I'd like you to take a
look at their fine gloss
that survived intact the cold
rain we had on our way here.
The gloss is very nice.
The coat, too.
[LAWRENCE] They are
also uniformly excellent
which is hard to come by.
Personally, I am
hoping to keep
a good relationship
with your company.
Of course, our company
definitely feels the same way.
Well then if we take
our future friendship
into account,
how about 140?
Yes... 40
Excuse me
just a minute.
Yes.
I do not know the market.
How good is that price?
It's pretty good.
So, can I assume
that we have a deal?
140 Trenni silver coins?
Is that indeed
what you said?
Ah, yes... Yes, it is.
140 Trenni silver coins.
That is correct.
I gather you
are surely
a very exceptional
merchant.
Yes.
And that
has to be why
you pretended
not to notice.
We cannot afford to
underestimate you.
Oh.
Ma'am I apologize,
but I am not entirely
certain what you mean.
I'm sorry...
Lawrence why are you
being so mean to him?
That wasn't my intent...
Why don't you tell him then?
Please sir, take one.
Now, I would like
for you to smell it.
What do you smell?
This scent...
It smells like fruit to me.
Precisely.
Were you aware
that the forests
are also full of
fruits this year?
These furs belonged
to martens
who resided in such
forests until recently.
Since they could eat
their fill of
this sweet fruit
'tis only natural
that they should
smell as sweet.
Yes, I smell it.
When they were
flaying their skins,
it took two
grown men to do it
and even then
the task was difficult
because the
martens' muscles
were so incredibly firm.
You may see.
Go ahead,
give it a good tug.
Harder!
It is strong.
Just like that
of a fierce animal.
It is warm as is
the sunshine in spring.
If you were to hold it
over you during rain
It would repel the
water and protect you.
Imagine for a moment there
is one piece of clothing
which smells this sweet.
Only one such piece
for sale amongst so many
that make you
wrinkle your nose
from their
oppressive scent.
There is no question
that it would sell
for an
exorbitant price.
Now... knowing this,
what kind of price
would you be willing to pay?
[ASSESSOR] 200.
200 Trenni silver coins.
200.
How about three
Trenni silver coins
per one piece of fur?
That is 210.
I, well...
Lawrence?
Are there other companies?
Oh... No.
No, that's fair.
We will take
them for 210 coins.
Oh, well of course,
if you insist.
[HOLO and LAWRENCE]
Cheers!
Wine is definitely the best!
What is wrong?
You should drink.
It is my treat
after all.
Tell me...
Have you ever worked
as a merchant before?
Oh no...
I am sorry if
I hurt your pride.
I did not mean to do so.
There was a merchant
who passed
by the village
a long time ago.
I was using his method.
So do not worry,
it was not something
I could
accomplish on my own.
Relax, your pride can
remain free and clear.
You know what, I never
really noticed it though...
Not at all.
I rolled up and slept in
those furs last night,
but I don't remember
smelling anything.
Well, you
would not have...
It was because of
the apples I had purchased.
You lied to him.
It was his own
fault anyway.
Oh, do not groan.
After all I am sure he is
happy to learn this method.
Am I right?
Yeah, probably.
If you only get upset
when you are tricked,
you will not go very far.
A professional would
get impressed and think,
"Perhaps I could
sell it that way, too."
By the way,
did you accomplish
what you had set out to do?
More or less.
Unfortunately, it seems
they haven't heard
any stories about a country
that will be reissuing
their silver coins.
Well, there might be a
trick to Zheren's story,
but as long as I gain...
I guess that's all
that really matters.
[ZHEREN] And now,
here's to our reunion.
Cheers!
I'm amazed!
You are both drinking
very good alcohol...
I guess this means
you must've done
well with the furs.
Yeah.
Congratulations!
This means my share
is going to increase, too!
Enough of that... C'mon.
Yeah?
You will sell me
the information
as to which silver coins
will be revalued.
And in return
you want a share
of the profit I make
as your payment.
That the right idea?
Yeah.
Is the story about the silver
coin's revaluation true?
I'm not...
well okay this is actually
something I'm guessing at
based on a little
bit of information
I got in the mining
town where I lived.
I mean, if you ask me,
I'm pretty sure you
can trust it, but...
There's no absolute in
business though right?
If you would have told me
that you had no doubts at all,
I would've turned
you down immediately.
So, what's your
share going to be?
Oh yeah...
10 silver coins
for the information.
Trenni coins.
Plus, I'd like
to have 10 percent
of your total profit.
That's rather modest,
don'tcha think?
True.
The problem is, if you fail
I won't be able
to do anything about it.
In exchange for
keeping my share small,
I don't want you to hold
me responsible if
you happen to lose.
I mean, I'd return
the 10 silver coins
for bad information of course.
Right.
That sounds good
enough to me.
This is just great.
Now, do you think we could
go see a notary public,
say first thing
tomorrow morning?
Of course.
That makes perfect sense.
To our profit then.
Cheers!
[HOLO]
Farum silver coin!
No. That one's a
fake Marinne silver coin.
But I thought that
was this one over here.
It's a later version
Bishop Radeon silver coin.
Don't worry.
You'll learn more
as you use them.
I think we should continue
after you sober up.
No! One more time!
If you insist...
Now then I'll
start from here
so try to
listen carefully.
Trenni silver coin.
Philing silver coin.
Lute silver coin.
Fake Marinne silver coin.
Farum silver coin.
Bald King Ranbalt silver coin.
Mitzfing Cathedral silver coin.
Fake Mitzfing
Cathedral silver coin.
Saint Mitzfing silver coin.
And this one...
I am finished. Goodnight.
Good choice.
You are a wise wolf.
I do not understand why
there are so many
of those coins.
How confusing
and just stupid.
New countries emerge
and others fall.
In addition,
provincial power holders
and church authorities
issue them out
for no particular reason.
On top of that you have to
add in all the counterfeiting.
The Lute silver
coins actually
used to be called
Fake Trenni silver coins.
Did you fall asleep?
From the very beginning,
you've given me
good information.
So, thanks.
No, I should
be thanking you.
All right.
I guess I better get going now.
Right.
Yeah! Go... make a killing!
And you stay
beautiful, ma'am.
Even when that boy
leaves is he ever noisy.
So this is the silver
coin in question.
Yes.
It is a pretty trustworthy
currency in this area.
Trustworthy?
There are hundreds of
different currencies.
And the amount of
gold or silver in them
changes around
all the time.
I see.
The face value of the
currency is actually higher
than the value of the gold
or silver within the coins.
So if you don't trust it,
you can't use
it for business.
I understand, I think.
All right then, have you
yet learned anything
with the information
you received on this coin?
Not really...
But I have a better idea
what might be going on.
Are you alright?
Yes. I would like
to eat that please.
What?
[HOLO] Now then,
what do you think
might be going
on with the coins?
Do you remember
which one this is?
Philing silver coin.
That's right.
The silver purity
of this coin is high,
so it's very popular
in the market right now.
It's right up there
with Trenni silver coins.
It seems to me it does
not matter what the era,
the currencies reflect
countries' power.
Correct.
If the market's conquered
by foreign currencies,
they might as well
have lost a war.
So, in order to
defeat their rivals,
they will increase
their silver purity.
Yeah.
Which means
it's possible Zheren
might be telling us
the truth after all.
Well, my ears are not
exactly omnipotent.
What?
Did you think I would
get upset with you?
Yes, I did.
The only thing
that might upset me
is you assuming
something like that.
All right. Where
are we going now?
One of my acquaintances
is a money dealer.
A money dealer?
Realistically, a person can't
tell the purity of currency
just by looking at it.
The reason why a coin's
popularity goes up or down
is because people are sensitive
to a change in purity.
To the extent they consider a
little change a big one.
So when the currency
has a big change,
there's always
an indication.
You don't have to memorize it.
Not right now at any rate.
But don't worry,
I can keep explaining it.
In other words, if
the currency creator
wants to make a major
increase in purity
he first increases the
purity a small amount
in order to measure
peoples expectations.
And judging by their reaction
he will wait until the right
time to make the big increase.
Yeah, you pretty
much got it.
[WEIZ] Lawrence!
Hey, Weiz.
Long time no see!
Okay...
Hello.
What's your name?
My name?
Oh.
My name is Holo.
Oh, beautiful!
Lawrence...
So have you slept with her yet?
No, of course I haven't!
Then you won't mind if I do.
It's a pleasure, my dear.
What is happening?
I have some business to
discuss with you Weiz.
Do you have a Trenni silver coin
that has been issued recently?
Not possible.
We handle them every day
and still can't tell.
What about melting it
down to check it?
Absurd.
There's no way I can do that.
Would you mind if I took
a little peek at it?
Of course; sure.
You appear to
be very naughty.
Give me just a moment, please.
Holo, come on now-you
can't tell them apart.
I've heard among highly
experienced dealers,
a handful can tell
by doing that.
But really I think
it's just a myth.
Whaddaya got?
I cannot tell.
No, I suppose you couldn't tell.
Don't worry
about it though.
He is a very
interesting man.
He is an incomparable womanizer.
Really?
So, go ahead and tell
me about the purity...
increased or not?
What makes you think I know
anything about the coins purity.
I saw your ear move a little.
Perceptive.
Although, I was a bit surprised
you didn't mention
it back there.
Well, I was thanking you.
What?
Come on now...
Tell the truth.
You were a little jealous.
It was a thank you for that...
Do not get upset though,
men are all jealous idiots.
And women are stupid too
to feel happy about it.
It's true, there are
idiots everywhere.
Come on.
What was the purity?
Oh yes that.
Well it was not by much,
but the newer the coin was
the duller the sound became.
Really...
so duller...
the purity must
be decreasing then.
Maybe Zheren
lied to us after all.
Making a profit with
decreasing currency
is really a waiting game.
If you buy back when
the value goes down,
there will be a difference.
When the market price
eventually catches back up,
that's where you profit but
it doesn't happen overnight.
I just don't see how Zheren
can expect to gain
any money this way.
Yes.
I think you might
have been tricked.
You really think so?
I really think so.
Okay.
So you think I was swindled out
of my money then, is that it?
In the worst case
he gets nothing.
That is all.
Even when the value of
the silver coin goes down
and you lose, all
he has to do is return
the money he originally
received from you.
But on the other hand,
the value could go up too.
Then he would receive
a share of the profits.
He has the chance
to make money
without paying anything
or risking a loss.
Well I'll be...
Humans are rather
smart, are they not?
Yes. They are.
Lawrence?
Is a decrease in purity
something abnormal
or is it more commonplace?
Common.
But they try to be careful
to make sure it stays
at the same level.
Yes.
And this, it is a deal
about silver purity
which appeared out of nowhere.
Coincidence or not...?
Curious nonetheless.
When hunting prey, we
sometimes climb the trees.
From that point of view,
we can see our prey's
unexpected hiding places.
In this way, we look at
things from a different angle.
What do you mean?
What angle?
Think about it for a minute...
What if it is not the young
man who is doing the scheming?
He did not necessarily
have to earn his profit
from that person in a
direct manner, either.
For example, someone might
have offered him money
to simply propose a
suspicious deal to you
and he was paid with
the money you gave him.
Yes! That's the deal.
This is more than a simple
trick to make me believe
I'm profiting from some coins.
I suppose the new angle worked.
Let's go!
Hey!
Where are we going this time?
Milone Trading Company.
Next episode...
Wolf and Her Helpless Partner.