[SHOP OWNER] I said no!
Now get out!
Please help; I'll take
anything you can give me!
Thank you for your kindness.
[INN OWNER]
Well you're back early.
I'm sorry.
Holo... I...
I could only manage
3 Lumiones on my own.
I'm 44 Lumiones short,
but there's not much
I can do about it now.
I thought maybe
I could gamble with it
and see what happened,
but you'd probably have
better luck than I would.
I suppose at this point
it doesn't make
a difference, though.
I can afford to risk it.
I'm sure that adding
3 Lumiones back to my debt
probably can't hurt
me anymore, right?
You idiot!
Get back up here already!
[INN OWNER] Will you
make a decision please?
Sorry... uh...
I dropped this bag out
of the window up there.
Yeah right. I'm sure you did.
You are an idiot!
I'm sorry.
Stop saying sorry!
Do you know
what you're sorry for?
What would you do if I had
run off with all your money?
I think that I would've
been okay with it...
After all, I won't be able
to help you anymore anyway.
Perhaps you
could use it to travel.
Use it to travel?
Why can't you just
be angry with me?
It's all my fault!
Correct? It's my fault.
Otherwise I know they
would have helped you!
This is all my fault!
I'm not angry with you,
because you only
came along to help...
I could never blame
you for that--
Again, you are an idiot!
Holo!
You are terribly good-natured.
What do you mean?
You are wrong about me!
I went with you out
of my own selfishness.
It backfired, so you could
be angry about it if you want.
But, instead,
you apologize to me
for simply brushing
up against my hand.
You should
not feel sorry.
But I do feel sorry...
I thought I had
done something
that I could
never take back.
I thought you would never
be able to forgive me.
I will do all that I can
to make things right again.
But, I realize it
still may never be enough.
Lawrence?
Will you answer
something for me?
Why is it that you
have such a good nature?
I just cannot
understand it.
My personality?
I don't know.
You really are rather dense.
Did you just tell me
your personality?
An imbecile would
have charmed me
and said I was
special or something.
Even if it was a lie!
Okay I'm sorry!
I'm confused about
what you want, though.
There are times you
want to hear something.
It does not matter
if it is a lie or not
but you will eventually want
to hit a person in his face
if he takes too
long to say it!
Guess where I stand?
Um the hitting?
Unbelievable. I simply
cannot believe you.
I am sure you find it
inappropriate to tell me
how you feel because
of our situation.
I'm appalled at
myself, actually.
I would still enjoy hearing
you say it to me though.
Shall we try it again?
Tell me...
Why is it you have
such a good nature?
Because you are
very special to me, Holo.
Oh my goodness,
what are we doing right now?
Wait, you're the one who
told me I had to tell you that.
Well, it was good
practice for you, was it not?
But you realize...
From now on you
should just try to upset me.
Although I do very much
appreciate your consideration.
Do you not agree that
we get so much more
accomplished faster
when we just argue about it.
Agreed, yes.
So how much exactly do you
have in this little leather bag?
I have 3 and 2/7 Lumiones.
Then there are still
43 and 5/7 left of the debt?
I have an idea,
do you want to hear it?
What idea?
Now do not get
your expectations up...
But I think it might work.
Seriously, what is it?
Well then...
This approach is
out of the ordinary...
Which means, what I
have in mind right now
they will
never see coming.
What is it?
[birds tweeting]
Do not worry.
I am right here.
Yeah.
You've already
obtained my money?
I heard you had something
important to discuss?
You really want me to
take that road this time?
[PRIEST] The road
is a bit rough, yes.
But I know
you can do it.
I have faith in God,
and I believe He
will protect you
again as He has before.
You're right.
But haven't you heard
about all the mercenaries
terrorizing and murdering
people along that route?
[PRIEST] Remember faith is
what keeps you eternally safe.
You must trust in
God to protect you.
I will.
You are indeed
quite an extraordinary
shepherd my Nora...
The Church and I
are proud of your steadfast
commitment to our lord.
Smuggling?
Are you serious?
Do I look like I'm joking?
How dare you waste my time.
I realize there have probably
been many people who've
tried a smuggling method
similar to this before.
And I'm sure
they were all caught.
At least you're
not completely ignorant.
Those on the verge
of bankruptcy
have a tendency
to misunderstand
a reckless plan
as a perfect one.
You must think
that I'm new at this.
But what if...
What if you could entrust
the gold smuggling
to a dependable
highly skilled person?
If the person
is that skilled,
he'd be making
enough money
without taking the trouble
to smuggle gold, wouldn't he?
Your theory is empty.
What would you say if
I told you I knew someone
who was very skilled but who
didn't make very much money?
I would say...
I don't believe
you in the least.
Who could that be?
Highly skilled and
currently working
in this town,
but poorly paid...
and even more importantly
they're in need of money.
What's more...
This person is,
shall we say,
dissatisfied with
their employer...
To say they're unhappy
would be an understatement.
Their employer is the church.
Now clearly, smuggling
gold is an action
that directly
opposes its rulings.
If we imply this is
not simply an opportunity
to make money but a
small yet calculated
revenge on the church,
this person will
definitely want to be involved.
And, trust me, there's virtually
no possibility of betrayal.
Once I tell you
who this person is
I think you'll understand their
position a little better.
If what you say is true,
why don't you carry out
this scheme on your own?
You must want
something from me
otherwise why
tell me your plans
knowing you will
have to share the profit.
Repayment of my
debt is due today...
As soon as
the sun goes down
I'll be arrested
by the trading house.
Unfortunately this is all the
money I have on me right now.
I want you to accept
this as collateral.
You see...
I'd like you to hold off on
the collection of my debt...
and I also want you to provide
me with the necessary funds
to purchase the gold
we'll be smuggling.
Excuse me?
Do you believe now is
the best time to be hesitating?
What do you mean?
Holo?
Interesting...
I heard someone
taking off just now.
My ears are especially
sensitive...
I can even hear whispering...
For example, the people
downstairs
are planning a strategy
for running away.
Oh, another one left now...
As it stands I do not see
how this trading house
can last more than
a couple of days.
Please stop it!
So Lemerio, what
do you think?
I assume you have the
appropriate channels
we can use to sell
the smuggled gold
and you can trust me
with that knowledge
as well as my promise to make
the conditions of
the deal favorable to you.
I need an answer.
All right I'll do it...
You have a deal.
Good, may God overlook
us in this endeavor.
Get Liebert here, now.
[SUBORDINATE A] Yes sir.
I think now it must be
my turn, am I right?
I don't know what you mean.
You cannot possibly believe
a good-natured person
like you could deceive
that little girl.
There are actually a few
innocent people in this world
who simply like
good-natured men you know.
You think you
understand females so well...
You do not.
Listen to me, okay?
Come on, you cornered him...
Now, it's my turn.
I need to talk to her myself.
Remember, I'm the one
who was blinded by greed
and ended up getting
products whose value
had collapsed
in the market.
If I have you talk to her
just because I don't want to
then I'm pretty
much hopeless.
Oh well...
I was hoping I could
get you further and further
into debt with me,
then you would owe.
Whoa, yeah that
was close then.
[church bells chiming]
Hello, Nora!
Oh, Lawrence!
Hi Holo!
Well, who
would've guessed it!
We happened to run
in to you right here
in front of the church...
The only explanation has
to be divine intervention.
Even I won't fall
for that story.
Well...
I think that might be
because you've been drinking
too much holy
wine at communion.
I don't really
drink alcohol very much...
that includes the wine
as a sacrament too.
What's the the truth?
Right...
I came here to
request your service.
Really?!
Is that so?
We can't really talk
about it in the open
so why don't we go to
a street stall instead?
Okay.
Here's to our reunion!
Now then,
you told me this before
but can you really
go to Lamtra?
Yes, that's right.
I can go there.
But can you go there
with sheep as well?
If there's not too
many of them I can.
All right then this
time I'm gonna ask you
to do something different...
Your pay... 20.
I'm not talking about
a worthless bond either.
I'll give you
20 gold Lumiones.
Watch it!
I'm sorry.
Um, did you say
20... Lumiones?
That's what I said...
But there is a risk
so the payment
will be contingent
upon our success.
If we fail
it'll be nothing.
I see.
What I'll need
you to do is walk
to Lamtra
with your sheep
and then just bring
them back safely,
that's basically what it is.
So, I'm not really
asking for anything
more than for you
to just be a good shepherd.
I imagine this job
must be very dangerous.
Otherwise you wouldn't
be paying me so much.
I won't deny that.
In fact because of it I
won't insist that you join me.
I want you to take a minute
and think about this.
The fee to join the Association
is 1 Lumione at the most, right?
If you have 20,
you can rent a house
and work without
having to worry
about your
immediate living expenses.
You'll probably be able to
purchase a trusteeship, too.
At that point, you
will be the proud
owner of
Nora's Clothing Store.
I'm wondering something...
Were you wanting to
join the tailors association
in this particular town?
No, actually I had
always planned
on moving
somewhere different.
I see...
But the size of this town
is at least appealing right?
Just think Nora...
It would be
difficult to move
to a town with
no contacts...
Then again, I guess you
wouldn't want anything
to do with the church in
this town if possible either.
No, you have it wrong.
Nora it seems to me
the church does not at all
appreciate the effort
you go through
to protect the sheep
they entrust you with.
In fact,
the better you are
the more they suspect you
of using pagan witchcraft.
You know that I'm correct.
As a test they
send you into areas
other shepherds
wouldn't go near...
And even though
you know it's not true
they tell you
the safe territories
all have been
claimed already.
I'm willing to
bet they'll keep
on sending you
into danger too.
until you're attacked.
They want you
to be attacked
by wolves or mercenaries
they don't care.
And they'll
keep sending you out
because they want
to prove you're a pagan.
I've seen it happen before.
If you ask me,
the church here is
worse than the devil!
We figured that we
could make a little money,
and then we can
leave this town.
But only after we make
sure the church suffers!
You know we're the only
ones you can count on.
I really believe we can
help each other, Nora.
This is your way out.
What do you think?
Tell me, what
are you planning?
We're going
to smuggle gold.
What...?
Smuggle gold?
I don't understand.
What do you
think I can do?
You can help
us pass through
this town's
strict inspection
because the gold will be hidden
within your sheep's bellies.
Can I...
Would you mind
telling me the whole plan?
In any town
influenced by the church,
gold fetches
an exorbitant price.
So the most
convenient place to make
a wholesale purchase
of gold would be
a pagan village
such as Lamtra...
but...
If we want to take the
safest route from Lamtra,
we'd have to take
the main road...
one which is
entirely too busy...
On top of that,
the area has been
another shepherd's
territory for a long time.
But if its me, I won't
arouse any suspicion
even if I decide to
go on a quiet road
which very
few people take...
And of course
I would decide on a road
that is the shortest distance
between here and Lamtra.
Exactly... Nora...
You've been treated very
poorly by this town's church...
This plan is a great chance
for you to get back at them
for being so cruel to you.
After all, the biggest
source of their funds
is the import
and export of gold...
along with
so-called donations.
However, if they
were to find out,
we'd be severely punished...
and regardless we'll
have to leave this town
for our own safety after
the work is completed...
Now you understand...
That's why the
compensation is so high.
[church bells chiming]
All right Lawrence
I will do this for you.
I look forward
to working with you.
Likewise.
Um?
What's wrong Nora?
Nothing...
I just wanted you to know
I wouldn't have taken
this offer from anyone else.
I only said yes because...
because it was you.
Are you not happy now?
Things turned out well,
did they not?
But is the end worth it?
Of course it is.
The gamble's not
worth our lives...
If what we're focusing on
here is our financial gain
then we might
as well call it fraud.
If you sign an unfavorable
contract, you're the fool.
That rule is common
sense if you're a merchant...
But what about the person
we're working with this time...
She's a poor shepherd girl
who doesn't know
her left from her right.
It is true that little girl's
smile at least looked innocent.
Seriously...
You are more than
hopelessly good natured.
That little shepherd
girl is not
a mere sheep you
understand...
she exists for more
than to be hunted.
No, in fact she is
a rather bold sheep
who decided on her own to
jump into a pit of wild animals.
Consider this...
She might just be
a completely different animal
who is hiding in sheep's skin...
I do not wish to admit this...
but she is a shepherd
that even I acknowledged.
You are not so bad after all,
but please try not
to be so gullible!
Well at this point
it doesn't matter,
we have a job to focus on now...
Hopefully we'll end up
the ones laughing.
Is that so?
Because I believe the
idea of the two of us
chuckling all by ourselves
is the most appealßing.
I don't
necessarily disagree...
But I'll be
far more relieved
once we can all
laugh together.
You really are
terribly good natured.
You don't like it?
You are silly.
[LIEBERT] Master you've
gotta be kidding me!
Are we really going
through with this?
We're going
through with it...
We have no choice.
Did you hear me Liebert?
Next episode:
Wolf and a Group of Youngsters