[LAWRENCE] Well, the smoked
mutton was unexpectedly tender.
Don't you think?
And I'm sorry, I guess
we ended up drinking
more than I had wanted to.
We didn't really exchange
that much information did we?
[ZHEREN] Yeah, you know
I guess we didn't, did we.
I keep getting distracted
by your wife's conversation.
I'm fascinated
by what she says.
[LAWRENCE] She loves to chatter
about nothing, it seems.
[ZHEREN] Even so...
I think she's
absolutely incredible.
You're a lucky man.
[ZHEREN]
Thanks again.
You two have been
great. Bye, take care!
[LAWRENCE]
Sure.
[ASSESSOR] Sounds good.
Now that I know what this
Zheren person looks like,
I can find out more
about him for you.
[LAWRENCE] I'd really
appreciate it.
But to be perfectly
honest, this is unusual.
I'm surprised to see it
happening after only one day.
We were a little cautious
at the beginning,
but after hearing
all the details,
it doesn't seem to be
just a simple fraud.
In order to get a large
amount of silver coins
whose value is
going to decrease,
someone is enlisting
people to persuade
several merchants to
purchase silver coins
by telling them a
somewhat believable story
about the value increasing.
However, since their
value is going to decrease,
the merchants will want to
get rid of them pretty quickly.
I can only assume
at that point...
this mystery person
will buy them all at once.
And any merchants sure
aren't going to tell anybody.
After all, they don't want
to hurt their reputations.
I'm starting to get a good idea
about how you can make
an enormous profit
using silver coins whose
value is decreasing.
However, it does come
with a fairly significant risk.
I have to admit, I'm pretty
intrigued by this whole thing.
I'm glad to hear it.
Well, everything is
a learning experience...
And that includes the
sale of those marten furs.
[HOLO] Do you think
we will make it in time?
Even if your
assumption is correct,
Milone Trading is
going to have to
do something about
this situation quickly.
Otherwise the plan to outwit
Zheren shall end in failure.
[LAWRENCE]
I'm sure it will be fine.
In order for this
to be successful,
especially in a foreign land,
they have to be
able to investigate
a person's background...
and do it quickly.
[HOLO laughing]
What's so funny?
Oh, it's nothing...
I was just remembering
the old days.
Why?
Because of me?
He was leaning back
in his chair as well
and had a terrible fall.
I tried to warn him,
but he refused to listen to me.
I will never forget
the look on his face!
[LAWRENCE] Sounds like
a fun person to be around.
[HOLO] Yes...
He was quite a fool,
but still extremely cheerful.
For some reason he
was never surprised
when he saw my wolf form.
I imagined some
called him strange.
But he was a very nice man.
He was the first
person to treat me
as if I was like
everybody else.
I liked him.
He was from Pasloei.
Is he the one
who asked you
to make the village's
wheat ripen well?
[HOLO] Yes.
Oh, what a fool he was.
I found him to
be a good friend.
What's wrong?
I believe I need to tell
you something important.
I just had it, but now
I cannot remember what it was...
What are you talking about?
[HOLO] I do not remember,
but I think it is important.
If it's that important,
don't worry, you'll remember.
I imagine so.
He was her friend... huh.
My name is Marlheit,
branch manager.
You can count on us.
We have no problems
with this deal.
What about Zheren?
Does that mean you were able
to find out who
he was working for?
Yes. It appears he was working
for the Medio Trading Company.
The Medio Trading Company?
I don't understand.
I mean, yes, it's true
they're the number one
crop dealer in Pazzio
and they do have a lot of
shipment vessels, but still...
You're correct.
It would seem to be
impossible for them to carry out
what you suspect
all by themselves...
It's more than likely
there is a nobleman
behind this whole thing.
We have yet to
identify that person.
But no matter
who they may be,
if we move first
as you suggest,
we can make it
work in our favor.
Then why don't we discuss
what our shares are going to be?
You appear perhaps
too happy, today, I think.
Yeah, but just think about it.
There could be at least
300,000 Trenni silver coins...
Maybe even 400,000
and if Myloan gives me
10 percent of their profit...
That's 2,000 for me and
enough to open my shop!
I am glad things appear
to be going so well for you.
I wanted you to stay at the inn
if your hangover was that bad.
I was worried.
I did not want for you
to get sweet-talked.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what I sai--
You're going to be fine...
The inn is right around
the corner, alright.
Just a few more steps
and we'll be there.
All right.
[LAWRENCE yawning]
You drew your shop!
Do not be frightened.
How long you've been there?
I never even heard you.
I think you are
a very talented artist.
Well I don't think so,
but thank you.
Are you wanting to open
this shop of yours soon?
If this thing with
Milone Trading goes through...
[LAWRENCE]
I guess, yeah...
it's pretty much a done deal.
[HOLO]
I see.
There isn't a
single merchant I know
whose dream isn't
to own their own shop.
I guess I'm not any different.
If you have your own store,
you can become
a member of that town.
It's different
than being a peddler.
You can make close friends,
and it'll be easier
to find a wife.
Speaking of which,
I wonder how Chloe
is doing right now.
I can't imagine
what she would say
if I opened my own shop.
Who knows, she might
even bite her tongue.
I would be
at a loss, though.
What do you mean?
Once you open this store,
you are not very
likely to leave there,
am I right?
I would be forced to
either continue traveling
all alone or find
myself a new partner.
Yes, but you are wise,
and don't forget about
the money you earned
from the marten furs.
Trust me, you'll be fine
traveling by yourself.
I do not want to.
I will not bind you...
But I am tired
of being alone...
You know?
Holo, I don't mind
coming along with you
until you get back
up to the north.
Even if I do get the money
it's not like I'll be able
to open my shop right away.
Do you mean this?
Of course, why would I lie?
Now why're you
making that face?
I told you I was
gonna go with you.
This isn't like you.
I always have the same dream.
Dream?
When I wake up,
everyone is gone.
Yue, Inty...
Paro Muri...
I cannot find
them anywhere.
We can live for
a hundred years.
I thought I could leave.
I left on a journey,
fully believing
I would see them again.
But I cannot find them.
I cannot find them anywhere.
I never imagined...
I thought I would be
able to see them again.
And now...
I am afraid...
I do not want to
wake from my dream
and discover I am all alone.
I am tired of being alone...
I do not want to be cold...
I do not want...
to be lonely.
I am so embarrassed.
This dream is very common
among peddlers, too.
Goodness...
Your tears have made
your face all sticky...
Give me a second.
Here.
That is your drawing.
I've drawn a ton of them.
Besides, it's
not like the deal
has gone through yet
I need to be careful...
Don't wanna get
overly optimistic.
Thank you.
I suppose I am in your debt.
Oh, I am so tired.
Are you not going
to go to sleep yet?
I suppose I should...
I can save the candle.
You think like a merchant
every second of the day.
[LAWRENCE] What the...
What are you doing?
[HOLO] That is not a very
romantic thing to say.
I cannot breathe.
Hold on. Have your
eyes adjusted yet?
What are you...
It was important
after all.
I finally remembered what
I'd wanted to tell you.
There are people
outside the door.
And I do not sense
they are well meaning.
I'd be willing to bet
it's Medio Trading.
And we are on
the second floor.
Luckily no one will
be waiting outside.
Come on.
We should go now.
You should probably
just take advantage
of this situation
and look at my body
under the moonlight,
do you not think?
[banging on door]
[HOLO]
We shall run!
We do not have
time for the wagon.
Killing the horse would not
serve their purpose anyway.
We can retrieve him
when things calm down.
[LAWRENCE]
Right.
[HOLO]
Here take this!
Keep it with you
just in case!
[LAWRENCE]
Why is it hot?
[HOLO] Because it is
the wheat in which I dwell.
[THUG A] They're headed
to Milone Trading!
[THUG B] Don't let
them get inside!
[LAWRENCE] Holo, when
we're done with this,
I think we should
go shopping.
[HOLO] What are you
saying to me right now?
I'll buy you
a comb and a hat!
What are you up to?
Nothing.
You just happen to
have beautiful hair.
I think I would much rather
have a comb for my tail.
Good idea.
We should get one...
Hang on,
we're almost there.
[THUG A]
Did you find them?
[THUG B]
No!
[THUG A] They should be
around here somewhere.
We've got backup coming.
We're going to
completely surround them.
[THUG B]
Yes, sir!
This is not looking
terribly good for us.
Do you think we
should split up then?
That is a good thought.
But I think
I have a better idea.
What is it?
I will go out onto the street
and attract their attention...
In the meantime...
No, you can't.
I won't let you.
Listen...
If we split up without a plan
you will be the one caught.
Do not forget, I am a wolf
and not so easy to capture.
If I am left alone, how can I
negotiate with Milone Trading?
You have already handed
over your plan to them.
What if they abandon us?
We are left with no choice
but for you to
threaten to betray them.
No, I can't do it.
Don't you understand?
If Medio Trading sees
your ears and your tail
they will take you
immediately to the church.
They shall not capture me.
But even if they did,
I can keep my ears
and tail hidden
if it is for
a day or two.
After all, I know
you will soon arrive
to rescue me anyway.
You don't understand!
Listen!
You want to open
this shop, correct?
Remember, I owe you.
This is simply my way
to paying back the debt.
Don't be ridiculous.
If you get caught,
they'll kill you!
A debt is not
the same as your life.
Loneliness is a disease
that can lead to death.
They might as well
be the same thing.
Please don't!
I will always
believe in you.
[THUG A] That way...!
We found them!
They're on Roita Street.
[THUG B] Where are they?
[THUG C] There's
only one of 'em.
There's supposed to be two!
[THUG A] There he is!
My name is Lawrence!
Help me!
I was here this afternoon!
[THUG A] I hear him!
[THUG A] Hold it!
Hand him over to us, now!
[BOSS] That's enough.
Let me make myself
perfectly clear to you.
This is the Great Marquis
Milone's Milone Trading Company
which is authorized
by the Grand Duke Raondeal
of the Duchy of Raondeal!
This gate belongs
to the Marquis
and anyone who is
on these premises
is considered a
personal guest to him.
And any guest
of the Marquis
is also under the
care and protection
of the Grand Duke of Raondeal.
Understand this:
You're wrong if you think
you're striking
a simple property.
You might as well be striking
the pedestal of the Grand Duke.
[whistle]
[THUG A] Withdraw for now.
It's rather late for
this kind of disturbance.
Now, why don't you
tell us what's going on.
You saved my life just now.
And I do apologize
for disturbing everyone.
No problem.
But you shouldn't
be thanking us;
you should thank the Marquis.
So tell me, who
were those guys anyway?
In all likelihood,
those men were
working for Medio Trading.
I think so too.
Somehow, they figured out
I brought a deal to you...
And they wanted to stop it.
They wanted to stop it?
It's possible they caught
the woman who
was traveling with me.
Can you help her?
Is there anything
you can do?
After hearing all
the commotion earlier,
some of our men
went to investigate.
They reported back to me
they had seen a young woman
being taken away by force.
Do you think
it might be her?
It has to be.
That was probably Holo.
She acted as my decoy
so I could come here.
Let me ask you:
Why do you think
they captured her?
What would
they want her for?
Like I said...!
They didn't want
us to work with you.
They wanted to get us out
of Medio Trading's way.
Then let me ask you this:
do you find it at all strange?
What are you
talking about?
Please calm down Lawrence.
There is something
else is going on.
It's not that simple.
I don't understand.
Think about it
for just a minute.
What would they gain by
taking you two hostage?
It doesn't make any sense;
it'd have no effect on us.
What?
We've now started collecting
the Trenni silver coins
so what would
be the point?
They're already too late.
It would only
be worth taking
the two of you hostage
if you had asked us
to simply
collect the coins
without having told us
what kind of moneymaking
idea it was.
But we do know the deal.
We know what is happening.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yet still, if
the rest were true,
I can't see a
store acting on it.
Can you?
No, I... I can't.
Yes.
I hate to say this,
but we already have all
the necessary information.
Whatever happens
to the two of you
is really no longer
our concern.
Believe me,
I am sorry...
But we already
have invested
quite a bit
of money into this.
I have to compare
the extraordinary profit
from this deal with
a grudge from a merchant
who we might see
every three years.
Again, I am very sorry,
but I'm going to have
to chose
the company's profit.
However, everyone here
in Milone would like you...
I can't
believe this.
Calm down and think!
Look, I can tell
your companion
must be very
important to you.
But you cannot allow that
to go to your head right now.
Might as well put
the cart before the horse.
You're right.
I apologize.
No need. I don't
imagine I would be able
to keep my
composure either.
Not if my wife was
in the same situation.
Still though,
this is strange.
Medio Trading would
also know full well
what our decision would be
in regards to helping you two.
That's true...
Of course they'd know.
And yet they
went after you,
knowing it still wouldn't
give them any leverage.
Why would they
want the two of you
if they weren't going
to get anything out of it?
Do you have any idea
why they'd want you?
No, none what-so-ever.
I don't know.
In all truth, the profit
margin we're looking at
could be enormous.
I'd like to insure this
plan is going to succeed.
Yes, I'm sure
you would.
If you can think of anything,
no matter how trivial,
I'm asking you
to please let me know.
Lawrence!
If you have an idea...
Tell me what it is.
[knocking door]
Excuse me, sir.
Yes, what is it?
We received a letter.
It was thrown
over the fence.
I think it has something to do
with what is going on right now.
It's to the wolf...
and the forest
where the wolf lives.
Please give it to me.
You can have it back;
I just want to read it first.
Be my guest.
I appreciate it.
"We have the wolf.
The door of the church
is always open...
Keep the doors closed
with those in the house
so the wolf does not come in."
They have the girl who was
with me; her name is Holo.
She is an incarnation
of the wolf
who is known
to bring a rich harvest.
It is you.
Next episode:
Wolf and Lovers Quarrel.