[birds chirping]
How many have
you eaten so far?
17... maybe 18.
Probably at least 19.
How many are left?
Why do you even care?
I just wanted to know.
You already know.
I want to hear you say it.
81.
Really? 8.
I said 81!
I heard.
Would you like for me
to finish them right now?
Will that make you happy?
I don't know; I don't
think you can do it.
I can!
I am Holo the Wise Wolf
so you shut up!
Ya know, you don't
have to be so stubborn.
I am not being stubborn.
You sure about that?
Yes, I am sure.
Are you sure that you're sure?
I am sure, that I am sure!
Because you don't
sound very sure to me.
Just you watch and you
will find how sure I am!
Honestly, I sure
am tired of them.
That's what I figured.
Even if they are your favorite,
you ate 20 of them yesterday,
on top of what you ate today.
So what.
I will eat every one
of them right now, watch!
Don't get so upset...
I'm sure you're
tired of raw apples,
but there are plenty of other
ways to eat them, you know.
What other ways?
You had better not
be teasing; this is not a joke.
What are you talking about?
Baking apples, I have never
heard of such a thing.
I had no idea
there were still people
that have never
tasted apple pie.
Well, I have not, but it
sounds like an excellent idea.
It is!
They bake it in an oven.
That way the apples become
surprisingly tender.
It's like they're rotting...
well, the texture's like that,
the flavor's actually amazing.
Oh?
I guess you can
think of it like this,
you know how things are really
tasty right before they go bad?
Well, for whatever reason,
when you bake an apple
it tastes like that.
It becomes sweet
and tender and warm
and it's all
at the same time.
But I'm sure after
your little binge,
sweet things is starting
to get boring.
So how about this instead...
Would you rather have
salt-seasoned meat
for dinner or fish?
Meat!
What happened to
the girl who looked
as if she couldn't stand
to eat another bite?
Meat is a completely
different story.
Let's go!
Okay...
Finish the apples, though...
Seriously.
You do not have to worry.
After what you just told me,
I am positive I can
finish them all, thank you!
Well, I guess we can go then...
Ready?
Of course!
I have been waiting
out here forever.
Why are you being so slow?
Why are you
being so difficult?
Because you like me this way.
[LAWRENCE]
Uh... well...?
[HOLO]
What?
It's just that...
Well you kind of
look like a nun.
[LAWRENCE]
All I see is a nun...
From every angle. Nun.
[HOLO]
Yes.
It is quite convenient for
travelling, would you agree?
I guess.
I fail to understand
how it makes a difference
whether I wear
this simple cloth.
The human world
is strange, as always.
But I suppose, if
you think about it,
even a wolf
will sometimes
like to wear sheep's
clothing, am I right?
True enough.
Although, if one were to wear
the fur of a rabbit instead
I believe you would
be caught rather easily.
Then I guess I should
probably carry some apples
with me just in case
I end up getting caught.
And I had very nearly forgotten
about those stupid apples.
[HOLO and LAWRENCE laughing]
[LAWRENCE]
However...
[HOLO]
What?
In your particular case...
looking too much like a nun
could actually be problematic.
What do you mean?
Well, it doesn't
matter what happens,
nuns do not drink
during the day.
Oh really? Well then
I must be an outstanding nun.
And, a nun would never
say something like that.
I humbly beg your
pardon, kind sir.
But really though,
when we head north
there are places
where you looking
like a nun will
definitely cause trouble.
Trouble...?
Well, what do you
suggest we do about it?
You'll have to change clothes...
I'm thinking it'll be safer
if you at least wear something
similar to what the girls
in town like to wear.
The food will
not taste as good
if we know we have
to run errands afterwards,
so what do you
say we go ahead
and purchase something
before we eat?
Really? Yeah,
that'd be great.
I was afraid I was going
to have to convince you.
Were you worried
I would insist
upon eating
and drinking first?
You should know
me better by now.
I am not that
drawn to food.
No, not food.
I see...
Then you were being
considerate after all.
I should probably
take you up on it.
Your exaggerated reason behind
purchasing me a new outfit,
or did you really think
that I would not notice?
For your sake,
I shall not hold back
and will allow you
to purchase new clothes for me.
The winter is fast approaching
and it will be getting cold.
That's very big of you.
Thanks.
Oh, no!
Oh no?
Is something the matter?
I don't have money.
I don't believe you.
No. I didn't
mean that way.
I meant I don't
have any change.
I simply do
not understand.
Why can you not
use that money?
Well technically
I could
but they wouldn't
like it very much.
Using gold coins to buy
clothes is kind of like
using a sledgehammer
to kill a fly.
I see.
I didn't realize
the gold coins
were so much higher
in value than the silver ones.
They are.
For example,
a current Lumione gold coin
is equivalent
to 35 Trenni silver coins.
If you live modestly,
you can last 7 days
on 1 silver coin.
And, gold is
35 times that.
Wow, it is a big
difference, then...
But...
This robe cost 2 gold
coins... exactly...
That is what they
said at the store.
Are you sure you
do not buy clothes
with gold coins
and apples with silver?
If that were the case,
most of the townspeople
would be naked.
The clothing shop owner
who sold it to you
was probably just
worried about whether
he'd really
get paid for it.
Oh.
I did not realize
it was so expensive.
Well obviously...
So for the next ones,
why don't you pick out
something a little cheaper.
Cheaper!
I am Holo the Wise Wolf.
If I am caught
in cheap clothing
it will ruin my good name.
You know they say
if one is truly pretty
she'll look good no
matter what she wears.
Now I need to
make some change.
Oh, exchanging money!
Then we shall have to
go to that bridge, right?
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
And walk fast
while you are at it...
I need to have a drink,
and I need one soon.
[WEIZ] Let's see...
For Lumione, it's gonna
be 34 Trenni silver coins
to stay current
with the going rate.
And the transaction fee?
It's 10 Lute silver coins,
or I'll take
30 Trie copper coins.
Lute silver it is.
Agreed, we'll
go with the Lute.
All right then.
Now don't forget
to be careful.
If you drop
anything it will end up
belonging to the person
who picks it up first.
Weiz?
Yes?
Try to remember
that I'm the customer.
Just leave the coin
over there somewhere;
can't you see
I'm kinda busy?
Well, when you tear away
yourself away from her,
do you think you
can help me?
What did I say?
It is more important
to me to make sure
this delightful girl does not
drop any of her silver coins.
Isn't that right?
Yes, and thank you!
But, can I ask
you a question?
Anything
in the world.
Do you not think there
might be a few too many
of these silver coins
for my hand to hold?
But my dear Holo,
that's exactly what
my hands are here for.
Oh...
Perhaps you
should not, though.
Your precious hands
will be occupied.
Oh, no.
I'd gladly
sacrifice my hands
to prevent any unfortunate
loss of silver coins from yours.
In fact, such sacrifice
could only bring me joy.
Yes, joy!
And do you know why
that is, my darling?
Because then
maybe you could see
that the passion in my heart
is so great that my hands--
no-- not even my
arms could contain it!
All right!
Have you forgotten
the basics of money dealing?
Silver gets a bag.
Gold gets a box.
And if money is
to be held in hand
it should be
crude copper, right?
Fine.
Keeping a wonderful girl
like that to yourself
is an act that
can only defy God!
Haven't you ever
heard the expression,
"Share the bread
you've been given with others."
You want me to share her?
Remember, there's no bargaining
when it comes to money dealing.
If I hand her over
it's all or nothing.
If you take her,
the debt she owes me
would transfer
over to you as well.
And I, of course,
would want to be paid
in full immediately.
I could never
do something as cruel
as put a price
on you, Love.
What a horrible
thing to say;
you are nothing more
than a crooked merchant!
I want you
to please understand,
the scales of my heart
will always be swaying
back and forth.
But there is something
you should know,
I shall never
lean to one side
or the other due to
the weight of gold coins.
Oh, Holo!
Of course you wouldn't.
You dare touch swaying
scales with your hand?
You must be a very
disreputable person indeed.
Oh, my darling.
Well, we should
be going now.
Hey, Lawrence,
I was wondering...
What?
You came all the way here just
to exchange that gold coin.
Are you buying anything?
I am.
I hear every
day things are getting
more and more
expensive best to buy now.
See ya.
Tell me,
do money dealers work
even after it
has become dark?
No.
It's pretty common
knowledge that money dealers
who trade after dark
are less than honest dealers.
I am not a crook,
so I refuse to work after dark.
I would like Weitz
to accompany us,
if you do not mind.
We're buying her clothes
and then we'll go get dinner.
If you feel like it, you can
meet us at the bar later.
Oh yeah, definitely.
I'm assuming the usual place?
Of course.
It's always best to get drunk
where you're comfortable.
See you there then!
As soon as I finish up here
I'll see both of you at the bar!
How fun.
That was certainly amusing,
do you not agree?
Hilarious, but you
had better watch yourself
with that one.
What do you mean?
He'll follow you around.
But I am already
followed around by you.
He is different though,
in that he knows
he is playing a game.
It is more fun
to tease you though,
and I enjoy
speaking to a smart male
every once in awhile.
Come on now Lawrence,
please do not be so serious.
We both realize that
this is only a game.
Although I have to admit
I am a little embarrassed.
It is just, that Weiz
fellow is such a smooth talker,
which is unlike
you completely.
But I know
from past experience,
there is nothing
more unreliable
than the words coming
out of peoples' mouths.
You live in
the business world.
You must know what I mean.
Yeah, I'm fairly certain
I would lie about anything
if it meant
I could make a profit.
Your lies do not
work on me though.
If you say so. Shall we
go buy your clothes then?
Lawrence!
You failed
to grab the happiness
which has been
handed to you twice now.
If you fail to grab
it one more time,
the tail of happiness
might just run away
and you shall
never find it again.
Wait...
I have no idea what
you're talking about...
Holo! What do you mean?
[CLOTHING SHOP OWNER]
That one is 40 Lute coins.
Which is a pretty
fair price for that piece.
It is expensive.
We're actually planning
to head north soon,
so if could you
find us something
suitably thick and cheap
for two people
that'd be great.
What can you afford?
Two Trenni silver coins.
I think I can help.
Two tops and bottoms,
plus two blankets...
How will these work for you?
I think those should work
just fine, thank you very much.
As you can see,
I'm a peddler myself,
I've managed
to get in good
with the local Milone Trading
branch while I've been here.
Oh! Milone Trading?
Yeah, so it looks as
though I'll be travelling
to this town several
times a year from now on.
Oh, is that right?
Then why don't you go ahead
and take this coat as well,
and I'll just go and
grab you another blanket.
Of course
these have been fumigated.
They are guaranteed to be bug
free for 2 more years at least.
I am sorry, but I thought we
came here to buy me clothes.
We did.
But then...
do I have to wear those?
If you think you can stay
warm wearing just that robe,
then no, you don't
have to wear them.
If you are upset about me
spending some of your money
without asking, you can
just tell me you are angry,
For I am Holo
the Wise Wolf.
I have a good brain as
well as a pleasing appearance.
But I have a good nose too,
and wearing that will
make my nostrils curl.
Well, maybe this is your
chance to learn some humility.
Trust me, your personality
would benefit from it.
Don't be upset. I'll show
you what's behind the trick.
Mister, I wanna
ask you something.
Yes?
Do you have anything nice
that a woman would want to wear?
Something for a woman?
Preferably something warm
for those northern towns...
And in the lady's
size if you have it.
Give me just a second,
I've the perfect thing.
How about this?
I bought it from
a merchant family
when they were
updating their wardrobe.
I think it is far
too extravagant for me.
Well then what
are you looking for?
I would like something
a little simpler
and easier to change into.
Right.
Let me see what I can find.
Excuse me? What about that?
Pardon?
Oh, yes, of course!
I'm not surprised
this caught your eye.
This is an excellent piece
that has been worn by a noble.
Look at this...
The ends are stitched very
carefully so they won't tear...
And, pay careful attention to
this walnut button.
Can you see the detail?
You simply will not
beat this quality.
You are a very good merchant.
Oh and notice this
specially made sling,
if you wear this
around your shoulders,
you won't be able to help
catching the eyes
of people in town.
I smell rabbit.
Well don't eat it.
I would like these!
So how much are they?
For the two
of them together?
10 Trenni silver coins...
No... Make it 9 instead.
No, no, wait.
How about 8 silver
coins so I can
show my respect
to this lovely lady's beauty.
That's a deal.
What if this lovely lady
were willing to try
on this lovely merchandise
and show it off,
would you then make it 7?
Okay, sure.
You can have them for 7.
Oh, thank you!
Excuse me a minute.
How do I look?
Just wonderful!
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you paid
20 coins for it!
So, were the
clothes not expensive?
No, 7 silver coins for that
quality is a really good buy.
Did you know you'd be able
to knock the price down?
If I had picked the kind
of clothes you are carrying...
I know we could
have purchased them
for 1/10 the
price of this.
I had actually expected
it to cost a lot more,
so don't worry
about it, okay?
However, if you feel
that bad about it,
try not drinking
anything tonight.
You'd save up 7 coins
pretty quick.
I do not drink that much!
[HOLO and LAWRENCE laughing]
Anyway, your little tactics
for knocking down prices
are kind of dirty.
No matter how good
the merchant is,
he has no way around that.
So, it is hardly my fault
all men are idiots.
What do you plan on doing
with those things you purchased?
You do not intend to
take them to the bar do you?
No. That was
not my intention.
We are not headed to the inn
either, are we?
That is because I'm not taking
them to the inn.
I'll sell these as is to another
clothing shop.
We've still got some
time before winter hits,
we can buy them again
when we get further north.
Sell them? Really?
Yeah. There's no
use in keeping them
if we're not
using them, right?
Yes, that is true.
But will you be able to sell
them at a high price?
I'm not sure.
I guess selling them for the
same price will be difficult.
I'll probably
lose some on the deal.
You sell even when
you know you will lose?
You haven't figured it out?
Hold on... I need a minute
to think this over.
Would you like me
to explain the trick?
I am not
asking for your help
but if you would like to tell
me I will not stop you.
Understood. It's nothing
special, and, plus,
you did a better
job than me anyway.
This bundle of clothes
cost 2 silver coins...
Let's say, for
example, I sold these
to another shop
for 1 silver coin.
I'd lose 1 silver coin.
Go on.
Well then,
you have to pay attention
to something
else altogether.
What else altogether?
Look...
No matter who sees your robe
they are going
to be able to tell
it is very
good quality, right?
I guess so.
I'm sure you can
imagine people who normally
wear this kind of quality
wouldn't visit a shop like that.
So, the shop owner wanted
to have a good relationship
with me because I was with you.
Now, this being the case,
what would you
do if you were him?
I would sell
things cheap
so it would leave
you with a good impression.
That's correct...
And after you did that,
then what would you do?
He reduced the price
a little on these...
but he reduced it quite
a bit for your clothes.
I am a customer who
willingly paid 2 silver coins
for clothes that
are basically rags.
But, there's a big
difference in the price
of these versus
the price of your clothes.
So tell me, what is
the significance there.
If we take
into consideration
the total balance
we really saved a lot.
Exactly right!
That hurt!
You did that to him and
yet you call me the tricky one?!
Which means...
you had to go and hit me?
That's right!
Although I am
surprised you came up
with such a method anyway.
I like to call it
having business sense.
Still...
The way you
handled that merchant
was a lot better
than I could have done.
Naturally.
Because your
shallow cleverness
is no match for my scheming.
Yeah, so you say.
Oh? Is that a challenge?
Because if you are confident,
you should probably
show me your skills
in the bar
where we are headed.
Show them in the bar?
You can pay as high a price
as possible to purchase me!
Sure, of course I will...
But I'll insist
on paying in apples.
You are not playing
very nice to mention apples.
They will get a little
sweeter if you bake them.
I think jealousy heats
you up a little bit.
Males burned with jealousy
are too sweet to eat.
Then what about you?
What? Are you saying
you want to give it a try?
I'll think about it.
You caught
the happiness that time.
Next Episode:
Wolf and Virtuous Scales.