[JACOB] There's only one reason
you'd come here so early,
you must be doing
serious business today.
Do you need
a certificate?
[LAWRENCE]
Yes, please.
I hope you'll end up
becoming a merchant
whose name alone
will make people flinch!
Yeah, so do I.
Oh, and, uh, by the
way, is there anyone
with the trading
house that might
want to go to Lamtra?
Oh no, say it isn't so.
Tell me you didn't fall
for that shepherd girl.
It's not like that.
Well, she is the only one
who comes back
safe from that area.
I don't need to tell you
how the church
feels about her, do I?
If you don't
want to be dragged
into a damned
complicated mess,
stay away from her.
Although, when
you think about it,
that fairy girl Nora
is definitely your type.
No she is not.
So do you want
the recipients
name on
the certificate or not?
On it.
Go ahead and make it
out to Lemerio Trading.
Are you saying you
already have a buyer?
Did you purchase
this on credit?
Yeah, is that a problem?
I guess you'll find out.
What do you mean?
Did they drop
the price or something?
Now don't worry about it.
It's you so
I'm sure everything
will turn
out just fine.
Okay.
Either way, you need to
wait to spend your money
on women until later.
You go through
all that trouble,
and then it's
gone in no time.
If I didn't get anything
in return, I wouldn't invest.
Look who's turning
into a hot shot.
Here's the certificate.
Thank you very much.
Alright I'm off,
wish me luck.
Holo, sorry to
keep you waiting.
They were quite sweet
They told me I was just like
a pretty little snowdrop.
Yeah well those kinds of guys
are like starving dogs.
They're preying on
what they think is weak.
Well I'm not weak.
Plus I have you
to rescue me anyway.
Am I not right?
Yeah I guess if
I felt like it.
Although, the
only one doing
any rescuing
recently has been me.
Now then,
I have no idea
what it is you are
expecting in return.
I would still like for you
to invest in me, though.
You heard that?
I did not know
you liked blondes.
So you like her
gangly appearance?
Or is it that she's
having such a hard time?
Or are you just
in to shepherds?
Hold on a sec!
Jacob was being funny,
that's how he is!
I mean it's not like--
Not like what?
Well, it's true
that Nora is very pretty.
And it's also true that
I well I like
talking to her.
But that's all
It's not like
that'll end up
making me not
like you anymore.
Please don't get
all sensitive, okay?
Okay.
I was just
trying to tease you
a little bit
that is all.
However, I never thought
I would hear
that from you.
Thank you
I'm so glad.
Holo...
But!
Men will say anything
to get their way.
That may be true
with other men
But I'm a merchant
my word is my bond.
I have heard
knights sometimes
leave their
shields and swords
in the hands of others
to show their sincerity.
What would you do,
as a merchant?
All right then
to show my sincerity
I'll buy you honey
pickled peaches.
What did you say
you would buy for me?
You know, everything
doesn't have to be
a game all
the time with you!
You are the
one who told me
to ask you in
a cute way, silly.
No I wanted you
to just ask me
Not play games.
But I was cute,
was I not?
I was only trying to
make things more exciting.
They were starting
to get rather boring,
do you not agree?
Please do not be upset
with me Lawrence.
It is true
that I felt happy.
Does that not matter
to you at all?
Okay fine, I get it.
I get it, I'm not upset.
Are you happy now?
We should not
get separated so
I think we
should hold hands.
All right wouldn't
want that to happen.
Running a business can get
pretty scary, am I right?
One must be
intelligent to make money
yet if allowed
to go to their head
one can also fall victim
to their own schemes.
Then, they
will end up selling
the arms at half price,
just like Latparon Trading.
But we're
smarter than that.
By transporting arms
without investing anything,
like we've done,
we can make a lot of money.
The sooner the better.
Really?
That is all well and good,
but I do not like being in debt
it makes me feel
uncomfortable.
Do you mean
buying on credit?
Yes.
You bought
100 Lumiones worth
of weapons at
half the price.
But technically you borrowed
that money from him right?
Yeah.
I'll sell them at full
price to Lemerio Trading,
and that difference
will take care of my debt.
You see, they'll buy
them at the wholesale price,
which is two
times what I paid,
so I'll end up
making twice as much.
I know you don't
like it but come on
you have to
admit it's worth it.
Yes well I suppose.
It seems that this place
should be run by a monk.
If that were the case
we would have
heard a prayer or two.
I'm curious, can you hear
anything besides the sound
of you eating my meat pie?
Your sarcasm is appreciated
but if you actually want
an answer I can tell you
I do hear what sounds
like people inside.
Are you serious?
Yes, but it is a
dangerous atmosphere.
Well, it is not a fun
atmosphere at least.
Hesitating isn't
gonna get me anywhere.
I mean I'm not gonna make
any money unless I go in.
Like meat pies are not
nutritious unless you eat them.
That is my
meat pie you know.
Oh, you should have
said something sooner.
Here.
Is it a holiday
or something today?
Why isn't anyone here?
It's not the Sabbath yet.
Yeah well it's complicated.
Did you get into town today?
Oh no. We got
here a few days ago.
I had things to do.
Oh, okay
Well, you look like
someone important.
I'm not.
I guess I'll be
on my way then
We'll come back tomorrow.
In that case I'm sure
to see you next time.
'Til then, Craft Lawrence!
I knew it had to be you.
These must be the weapons
from Latporon Trading, right?
How did you know that?
A post-horse messenger
came here from Poroson.
Latporon Trading just
transferred a debt to us.
They transferred your debt.
They did what?
What is going on?
Sorry to tell you but your
friend's business has failed.
Now he's just like us.
What do you mean?
The arms market
collapsed a while ago.
Your weapons are
worth almost nothing.
Latporon let him borrow
money towards worthless stock
and then transferred
the rights to our company.
Pretty much, all he's got
in that cart is a huge debt.
Your friend is bankrupt lady.
Lawrence...
He tricked me!
We both make our living on
these kinds of arrangements.
You understand that right?
Of course I do Lemerio.
We are merchants after all.
You obtained exactly
100 hundred Lumiones
worth of weaponry
at Latparon Trading.
Out of that purchase,
47 and 3/4 Lumiones
have been applied to your
credit with a payment deadline.
I would appreciate
being paid promptly.
Otherwise I will insist
your debt be assumed
by Lohen Merchant Association
of which you are a member.
I see.
Your deadline will be
the day after tomorrow.
I can give you
2 days, but no more.
You will need to pay back
the 47 and 3/4 Lumiones
in full by then.
Have I made myself
perfectly clear?
You have and I will
sell those weapons somehow.
Thank you so very
much for your time.
I'll see you in
two days then.
Good.
I'll get you your money.
Let me give you a little
information just in case
Our street stalls can be easily
found around the town exits
in case something should happen.
Feel free to stop by at
any time if you need us.
Thank you for your offer,
but I'm sure I'll be fine.
I hope the rest of your
day today is profitable.
The feeling is mutual
May God's grace be with you.
Sorry 'bout that.
[HOLO]
Hey so?
[LAWRENCE]
What?
To be more precise,
what happened back there?
everything back
there is garbage.
Oh I was hoping
I had misheard.
You did not.
I'm gonna end up
being bankrupt.
Should we run?
The information network
among merchants
might as well be Gods.
No matter where we went
I'd be found in no time
if I was doing business.
So I would never be able
to be a merchant again.
Some are going
to take it for granted
but an animal once
wounded will not always die.
Will you let this
wound overtake you?
No, absolutely not!
What I'll do is find that
money one way or another
and throw it right
back in their face.
I've still got some
time to start over.
I am Holo the Wise Wolf
And I am sure I will
be of some help to you.
Yeah, actually saving
on your food alone
would be a really big help--
I have told you
I will earn my food.
I was just kidding.
Very funny.
But I promise you,
if you need it,
I will help you escape
Even if I have to use
the power of wheat.
You promised me
you would take me
to my home in the north.
I could not take it if you
stumbled in a place like this.
I know and I will
keep that promise I will.
If it comes down to it,
I might really need your help.
Of course you will!
Well then, I need to
stop by the trading house.
So you can just wait at the inn.
Do I look like an
ungrateful wolf to you?
Do I look as if I wish to
relax and groom myself
at the inn while
you are in trouble?
I never said that!
Answer me!
Holo of course not
But it's really not the point.
Then what is
your point exactly.
The trading house is
like a hometown for me
And if I take a woman there,
they'll tease us and
make a big deal out of it.
Then you can
explain the situation.
And how would you
like me to do that?
If they report
you to the church
it's not gonna
make anything easier.
So why do you not
tell them we are
in love or
married or something?
Okay then,
you can come with me.
After all, you're certainly
wittier than I could ever be.
Yes count on me.
And I think, I'll tell
them you're an associate.
Just don't say anything
you don't have to.
And one more thing,
their welcome
is a little rough.
Do not worry about me.
Okay.
First I need to ask you,
who is this lovely girl
you brought with you today?
We've been
travelling together
for business reasons.
That the truth?
Milone Trading in Pazzio
offered 140 Trenni silver coins
for some furs I had,
but she got them to go higher.
They ended up paying 210.
What?
I told you, if I'm
going to invest in a girl...
You'll get
something back I see.
I know your type well.
But luckily the
scriptures also tell us
not to open a mysterious
box carelessly.
Which is quite wise.
Now, lets get to it.
So, I have a general
idea of what happened.
One of the Lemerio
Trading employees
came by earlier
to inquire about us
assuming the debt
they have with you.
The gist is you failed because
you simply got too greedy.
Is that right?
Basically.
Then it's quite simple.
The association
is most likely going
to have to assume
your bad debt.
Which means you will have
to repay us on your own.
If you had fallen victim
to fraud, been robbed,
or were sick or injured
things would be different.
We could have helped
you with your debt then,
but we cannot help you
with your own greed.
If God cannot
help you then it seems
the only one who
can is this young girl.
I'm well aware.
I am sorry.
Unfortunately I can't
show you any mercy.
I stand by the rules
no matter what,
which is the reason
I'm in this position.
My concern is
the entire association.
I understand.
If someone else
was being given
special treatment I
know I'd get upset as well.
Loans between
association members
are not allowed either.
Yes I know.
The debt repayment
is in 2 days, right?.
The pressure is on Emilio too,
due to their failed
investment in arms.
They'll probably want
to collect immediately.
Which means your failure
will become public knowledge
the day after tomorrow
and I will be forced to
physically restrain you.
Do you understand the severity
of what I'm telling you?
Yes I understand.
Unless I can collect
47 gold Lumiones,
I won't have a tomorrow.
No, you will still
have a tomorrow.
You will definitely
have one,
but this one will be cold.
It will be dark and
it will be very difficult.
If we're looking
at a 47 Lumione debt,
you can
probably repay that
if you row a long
distance trade ship
for about ten years.
You could also
dig holes in a mine,
but that's if you're lucky
and actually stay alive.
No one could be that lucky.
I know this is hard.
And I know it
doesn't mean much
but I don't
want you to die.
Sins get punished.
At the end of the day I still
have to do the right thing.
Yes I know.
Do the best you can
in these next few days.
If you need me I'll
assist you in any way I can.
I have faith in
you Lawrence. Go!
Take this time you have
to do as much as possible.
Thank you for
being so kind.
I don't know how,
but I'll make
this money
within 2 days.
There are
always loopholes
when it comes
to business.
And I'm sure
that some of them
can only be seen
when you're cornered.
Do you have any
more questions for me?
Anything else
I can help you with?
No we don't. Thank you.
No wait!
I need a clever
line to give them.
Something to
say when I throw
the money back
in their face.
Keep talking like
that and you'll be fine!
Good luck kid.
47 Lumiones in 2 days.
So, what are
you going to do?
Repay my debt
with a debt I guess.
Can you turn to anyone?
Well I'm not
known for running
my business irresponsibly.
I don't know
anyone in particular
who would loan me
a large sum of money.
But there are several
who might be willing
to help me out with
a little here and there.
If there are 47 of them you
will have the money in no time.
Exactly!
[MERCHANT A]
Lawrence!
It's been awhile, hasn't it?
[MERCHANT A] You have
any money making ideas?
Well actually.
No problem!
There are plenty of others.
[MERCHANT B] Unfortunately,
we're too busy right now.
I'm sorry.
[MERCHANT C] Hopefully
the prices for wheat and meat
will also rise towards
the end of the year.
Oh well,
moving on I guess
How did it go?
There's still
the next person.
Yes, of course!
[MERCHANT D] We are
actually right in the middle
of inventory right now.
[MERCHANT E ]
I'm sorry, but we can't.
Okay. So?
Damn it! Why?!
Why did I have to
make such a stupid deal?
I'm an idiot!
Lawrence?
It's nothing, I've
still got the next one.
[church bells chiming]
What about this place?
No, that won't work.
Hey, wait! Wait for me!
What is it?
Please forgive me,
but I cannot walk as
freely as you in this form.
You're right I'm sorry.
[MERCHANT F]
It's been too long, Lawrence.
Yes it's been awhile
and I know that we haven't
done business in some time,
but I have a huge
favor to ask you.
I've heard that you've been
begging for loans all
over the place.
Is it because of
the collapse
in the arms market?
It is.
I made an
optimistic projection
which turned
out to be off.
Optimistic projection?
Well, that
was part of it.
What could you do?
A market collapse
couldn't possibly
be predicted by
anybody but God.
It would be unfair
to blame only yourself.
My friend,
you have helped
make me money
plenty of times,
so I thought I would
be able to help you
if you ever ended
up in trouble.
Really?
But your attitude
is not that
of one who is living
an honest life under God
as well as being
sincere to others,
especially your friends!
Wait! What?
What do you mean?
Don't mock me Lawrence!
If you're really that desperate
for money from everyone
then how can you afford to still
walk around with a woman?
[YOUNG COACHMAN] Idiot!
[YOUNG COACHMAN] You're in the
middle of the street,
what are you doing?!
I don't get it.
Why is this happening
Why now?
Wait! Lawrence!
Are you okay?
Let's go
to the inn.
You're so pale.
Please.
It's your fault!
I'm sorry.
I will be at the inn.
Next episode: Wolf and
the Biggest Secret Scheme