[birds chirping]
[HOLO] No one knows when
the people of this village
began to say "the wolf
is running" to describe
the ripe wheat
swaying in the wind.
Whene'er the wind lays
flat the ears of wheat,
they become
"trampled by the wolf"...
And should a poor
harvest befall,
the crops are
"eaten by the wolf"...
In the beginning,
there was nothing...
There was only warmth...
And then, a promise was made.
[birds chirping]
[crickets chirping]
The cycle of encounters
and farewells continued,
with favour.
Until, one day,
humans came to achieve
abundance on their own.
And there was no
need to be faithful
to their promise anymore.
[LAWRENCE] I bet you're
getting just as tired
of these country roads
as I am.
Right?
[CAVALIER]
A peddler?
[LAWRENCE]
I am, yes.
Actually, I'm
returning from
a small
mountain village
half a day east of here.
Lucky for me,
they ended up
buying my salt.
Really?
Is that it?
No.
These are all furs.
Yeah, that's just
a bundle of wheat.
It's the kind which can
sustain either hot or cold.
What's going on?
Everyone seems a little
over cautious.
Not really.
We've been told
a village in the west
is holding a pagan festival.
Pagan festival?
Yeah.
[CAVALIER]
It's a disgrace.
They refuse to believe
in the one true God.
You'd think
the Holy Father
would use his
power over them.
If it were me,
they'd be crushed.
But it looks like
he won't do anything.
I don't know,
maybe he just pities
the filthy
and scheming.
Pagans, huh...?
So the people of
Pasloei are pagans.
[Farmer A laughing]
[FARMER A] Who would
have guessed it?
I can't believe
the new method
led to such a
rich harvest!
[FARMER B] Can't
thank the Earl enough.
[FARMER C] Well, we couldn't
just keep counting on the wolf.
[FARMER D] Hey,
don't insult her.
She's supposed to
be a god, remember?
Oh! Hey Lawrence!
[LAWRENCE]
Hello!
It's been awhile,
hasn't it.
Well, you came
at the right time.
Our harvest festival
starts tomorrow.
Tomorrow...?
I'm getting the impression
it's already started, right?
[laughing]
You're right,
We started early.
Care to join?
Hey now...!
He didn't do any work,
so why does he
get to join us?
You didn't do
any work either!
You wouldn't by chance
know where I could
find Chloe would you?
Chloe...?
Oh, I see.
That's how it is.
Not at all.
She's a fellow merchant,
so I like to have a drink
with her every once in awhile.
We like to talk work.
I have bad news for you.
They'll be the last ones this
year to finish harvesting...
So Chloe will have to become
Holo for the festival.
Look everyone;
I can see her hiding
from us in the wheat!
Who'll be the lucky
one to catch the wolf?
Who's it going to be?
Chloe!
Lawrence!
When'd you get here?
You better watch out,
Holo is gonna get away!
Finally, the last bundle!
Come on now;
don't keep all
the wheat for yourself.
You better be careful,
or Holo will escape!
Who's gonna
be the lucky one
to catch the wolf?
It's Chloe!
[howling]
Holo the Wolf has appeared!
Catch her!
She's heading over there!
Lawrence, help us!
Don't let her get away!
It's been awhile,
so tonight is
gonna be your treat.
What do you mean
"tonight is my treat"?
You're going to be
locked up in
there for a week.
Thanks to you,
we were finally able
to find some
new customers.
I'm sure Chloe's
a help to you now...
She has a talent
for this business.
Yes.
She is our
price negotiator...
This village is not
the same as it used to be.
Oh...
Those are
Trenni silver coins...
I haven't seen them
in this area before.
Yes, I know.
We are bidding
a farewell to the old,
rusty Lute silver coins.
I suppose you will soon
rival big towns like Pazzio.
Well, not yet.
But when we do,
it will be thanks to our
new lord, Earl Ehrendott.
We will never have to
pray to that wolf again.
Fortunately,
we can now overcome
the drought and
the wind all by ourselves
Forget about
Trenni silver coins.
I'd like to fill our village
with Lumione gold coins.
And when you do,
I hope you continue
to use my services.
After all, an outsider
would just be a nuisance.
On the other hand,
filling the village with
Lumione gold is a stretch.
Time for bed...
Finally.
What... a girl?
Hey...!
Hey you!
Get up now!
What are you doing
in my wagon anyway?
I said get up!
Are those... ears.
A tail?
[howling]
[HOLO] Wow, what
a beautiful moon.
You there...
Do you perchance
have alcohol?
No, I don't
have any!
Who are you?
Why not?
Well, then do
you carry any food?
Oh, no.
What a waste.
Demon...
Are you possessed
by the devil?
Ungrateful beast.
How dare you direct
your blade at me.
What? Ungrateful.
[HOLO]
Oh, an oversight?
You are not from
the village, perhaps?
My apologies...
You may wield away.
My name is Holo.
This is the first
time in a long while
I have
taken this form...
I believe it to be
working out finely.
Holo?
Yes. Nice name,
is it not?
Amazing...
I have heard
of someone else
who is referred to
by that name.
Really? How unusual.
I have never known another
Holo besides myself.
From where
is this person?
[LAWRENCE] It is
the name of a god
a village nearby has
known for generations.
Don't tell me you happen
to be the same god?
I have been named a god
and bound to this region
for quite a long time now.
I am not so grand...
Not as a god.
I am Holo, and Holo
is all that I am.
A meager, lost,
delirious woman
who must have been locked
deep inside of her house
ever since she
was a tiny infant.
You are thinking
something like that?
I was born in a land
from the far north.
North?
Yes, they have a short
summer and a long winter.
My home is in
the forest of Yoitz.
It is a world of silver
where everything sparkles.
You are a traveling peddler,
are you not?
Take me with you, then.
But why me?
Because I am a good
judge of character.
And because I do not believe
you are at all
the type of person
who would deny me
this kind of request.
Stay away!
I am not
that generous.
Please be
kinder to me.
I believe you
are adorable.
[HOLO sneezes]
I do not
hate this form,
but I find it too
cold for my liking.
Holo!
If you really are
"Holo the Wise Wolf"
I want you
to prove it to me!
Does that mean you wish
to see me in my wolf form?
That's right.
I do not want to.
What?
But why not?
I should ask you why!
Well...
Because if you're a human,
I'll turn you over
to the authorities.
A person
possessed by the devil
needs to be saved.
But I might
reconsider turning you in
if you are indeed Holo,
god of rich harvests.
After all, it's
possible you might
end up bringing me
some luck, as well.
Then you
insist upon this?
Yes, please.
One more time
shall I ask...
Do you insist upon
seeing this no matter what.
No matter what.
An incarnation
cannot change
her form without
a compensation.
And In order for
me to change
I'll need the blood
of a human.
Either that or
a bit of wheat.
By all means,
the wheat.
Hey, are
you all right?
[whimpering]
Once again, I apologize
for coming
back so suddenly.
Not a problem.
I'm headed to the festival,
but make yourself at home.
[knocking on door]
Who's there?
[CHLOE] Holo.
[LAWRENCE] Holo?
[growling]
You didn't bother showing up,
so I've come to you.
What are you doing?
Aren't you supposed
to stay locked up?
Come on, it's not
like there's a real Holo
that's gonna get mad.
Let's go.
Just where are we going?
[CHLOE] You're treating
me, remember?
Did you go to Sauschbasch
before you came here?
You smell differently
than you did last time...
You always did
have a good nose.
Each place you visit
has a scent.
I guess it's only natural
for it to stick to you.
And your features are
different than before...
You seem to be
more confident.
Thank you.
Things are going well for me.
You should watch out.
I might end up taking
your place soon.
Well...
When you do, please
make use of my services.
That's rude...
You don't really
think I will, do you?
Why not...?
This is good alcohol.
Fine.
Who's being rude now?
If you believe in me so much,
then I've got
a proposal for you.
If it works out,
you'll be able to
open your own shop.
You might even be
able to get married.
Very funny, Chloe.
I'm not being funny.
I've heard them talking
about a big business deal.
I'm telling you;
we could make a killing here.
Lawrence?
You're becoming more
and more like your father.
When it came to
dealing with business,
he definitely shared
in your enthusiasm.
It's not just enthusiasm.
Otherwise, I would
never have brought it up.
Is that so?
Well, just talking big business
can be intimidating.
But I find it hard to believe
you'd need me to talk.
No.
I want to work
with you specifically
because I respect you.
Don't you know?
I carry everything you have
ever taught me in my heart.
he only reason I'm where I
am today is because of you.
It's always been you.
Sounds risky.
Risky. Risky.
You're still young Chloe.
It sounds to me like this
is an all or nothing deal.
Before you get involved
I think you should
have more experience.
Your choice...
but this could've
been an opportunity
to make a profit together.
How about I bring you
a less risky deal next time.
I wouldn't mind
working with you on that.
And here I am...
I've grown up and you
never even noticed.
It's just your judgment
as a merchant
needs some growth.
Don't underestimate me.
You'll regret it one day.
That might be good for me.
But I'll try not to do it.
Is it a woman?
You seem as if you're
distracted by something.
I was wondering
what it could be.
Oh.
I wonder what it would be
like if Holo became my partner.
Holo?
Do you mean me?
No, I'm talking
about the real Holo.
For God's sake...
Please don't tell me
you believe in that myth.
You think it's just a myth?
Yes, I do.
Just a myth, huh?
Just a myth.
I wonder if she
ever feels heartbroken.
Are you talking about Holo?
Yes-if she is real.
No. That's impossible...
Why would a god
feel heartbroken?
I don't know.
There's no way
she really exists.
Who does not exist exactly?
Holo!
Do not be surprised.
Who did you expect?
Where have you been hiding?
Around this time of year...
I am in the harvested wheat.
Usually, I cannot leave there.
otherwise people would see me.
But there is one exception.
An exception?
If perchance there
is another harvested wheat
within a close proximity to
the wheat where I am hiding,
I can then move to that wheat.
In other words...
Without the bushel in your cart
I could never have escaped.
I am in your debt.
I'm sorry...
You graciously showed
me your true form
and all I did was
act like an idiot.
Is that why you disappeared?
A long time ago...
A young man from this
village approached me.
He asked me to help
their wheat to ripen well.
The promise made
I have kept ever since.
However, a rich harvest places
strain upon the land.
I had to allow it to
rest from time to time.
The villagers
called me impulsive.
They believed I had
broken my vow.
Now, it appears no one
needs me any longer.
Yet even when they
still had need of me...
Whenever anyone saw me...
they trembled with fear
and ran as far as they could.
And, so I was alone.
I never wished for that...
I never meant to
frighten you, either.
All right, suppose
I accept your story as it is.
You are a very skeptical man.
Do you have a place to go?
I wish to return to the north.
Lawrence!
All clear... You
can come out now.
I have to admit
it was not easy
to tie my shoelaces
inside of this thing.
Woe is me.
I can imagine it would be...
Shoelaces?
Hey...
Those are mine.
Yes...
And how do I look?
Those are my best clothes.
I spent ten years
collecting them.
They are very fine...
Quite wonderfully tailored.
So you...
are not such a bad
merchant after all.
I can still refuse
to take you with me.
I do not think
you would, though.
Don't underestimate.
I would never...
Now, as for your
name, what is it?
Lawrence.
My name is Craft Lawrence.
Well, Lawrence...
I will make certain
a stirring legend about you
shall be passed down
among the people for all time.
No thank you...
I don't need a legend...
But I will need you to
pay for your own meals.
It's not like this
is an easy business.
I am not the sort
who would insist upon living
off the charity of others.
I am Holo the Wise Wolf...
And I am a very proud wolf.
At any rate...
This is rather small...
Thank you.
But, I am sure it helps
to keep out the cold.
Next episode:
Wolf and Distant Past.