[LAWRENCE]
I hate to repeat myself,
but I can't help to think
our running into each other
must have been
divine intervention.
If it hadn't been
for you, Nora,
I wouldn't be wearing this
tipsy smile at the moment,
so thank you,
I appreciate it.
You're welcome,
Lawrence.
And I'm also very
grateful to you.
I'm so glad
we got to meet.
Me too.
But, really, I should...
No, I should...
You shouldn't.
I was the one
who asked you to help
me out with that crazy
gold smuggling business.
And to be
perfectly honest,
I'm still kind of
shocked you actually
went through
with the whole thing.
I am too.
I never even imagined
I could do something like that.
It's funny...
I am strange, aren't I?
I had been
thinking I would have
to do something
radical one day.
I always knew I could
not be dependent
on the church forever.
You helped me break
away from them,
and that is why
I'm so thankful.
I'm not as great
as you think I am.
Merchants have a tendency
to be egotistical.
So do shepherds,
for that matter.
It's true.
[LAWRENCE] You are drinking,
aren't you, Holo?
Your presence does not
mean I cannot drink alone.
[NORA] I do wish you would
join us in our conversation.
Hold on... Are you
already drunk?
Me?
A wise wolf who can
consume an entire lake?
'Tis impossible on
such a small amount.
All right.
It sounds like our friend
might just prefer
to be left alone.
After I drink
a bit more,
I shall join
your conversation.
So until that time...
[NORA] Of course.
We'll wait.
[LAWRENCE] Now, what were
we talking about?
The food is here!
[NORA] Wow.
It looks so good!
Thank you very much.
Do you want
some too, Holo?
You said you would
leave me alone,
and that is
all that I want.
Right. So sorry.
Where were we?
Let me see, I think
we were debating
who was more thankful.
Right, but what
was before that?
Oh! Yes, it was about
sheep and rock salt.
Ah, of course, that's it!
Now then, I had
no idea that sheep
could find rock salt.
Yes. It's rather surprising
how much they
enjoy it, actually...
For example, if you
rub salt lightly on a rock,
they will
continue to lick it
well after the salt is gone.
Then I wonder if
that old story is true.
What story do you mean?
I've heard there's
a town east of here
that uses a particular type
of torture involving sheep.
I never imagined it
could be true before now.
Torture involving sheep?
Yes, it's pretty funny,
believe it or not.
Basically, what they do
is tie up their criminals
and rub a bunch of salt
on the bottoms of their feet.
Rub salt on their feet?
That man will never
cease being an idiot.
Oh, excuse me...
What happened after they
rubbed them with salt?
Well wouldn't the sheep
lick the salt off?
They would.
They say at first,
the criminals laugh
uncontrollably because
they're being tickled.
[CRIMINALS laughing]
No, stop, no,
please don't, no, no no.
Yes, it is very unusual.
Especially when
you take into account
the sheep won't
stop licking once
they taste the salt on
the criminal's guilty feet.
What do you
think happens then?
Gee, I don't really know.
The criminal would be
reformed through laughter
and spread nothing but joy
to all of those around him.
They lived
happily ever after.
Is that story true?
I might have just
made up that last part.
You're so silly.
The first part of it
was true, though.
I mean, who knows what must
go on in the minds of sheep?
Well, now that
you mention it,
whenever I eat dried meat,
I usually get salt
all over my hands.
They're very good sheep,
but how do I put this...
They get too
carried away sometimes.
It can be frightening.
Luckily, you have
an obedient knight
waiting to rescue you.
Yes, but Enek
sometimes works so hard,
he forgets who's
supposed to be in charge.
[ENEK barking]
I was only joking.
[HOLO growling]
You know, Nora, your Enek
is exceptionally well trained.
Which I'm sure
is completely due
to you being such
an exceptional shepherd.
Oh, you're sweet.
What's wrong?
You are drunk, aren't you?
I am not drunk.
Sure you're not...
What am I gonna
do with you?
It is not possible
for me to be drunk
on 3 cups of alcohol, is it?
Are you okay?
[HOLO] I cannot help
but think of being alone
in the wheat fields
for so long
hundreds of years
until recently.
The days passed by peacefully.
Yesterday was no
different from today.
And, tomorrow
was no different
from the day after that.
Time seemed only to move
forward a few times a year.
There was the annual
harvest festival,
the 2 sowing festivals,
the festival
to pray for no rain,
and the festival
to pray for no wind.
The remaining time
was a cluster of boredom.
Ordinary day after ordinary
day with no celebrations.
Once, I even watched a tiny
sapling grow into a huge tree.
Compared to that,
while travelling,
every day is
a new experience.
I feel reborn each morning.
The time spent with
my travelling peddler
has only been
a few short months,
but it has been
the equivalent
of several decades.
We would have a clamorous
argument in the morning
but reconcile by
lunch where I would
tease him by
making him clean
the breadcrumbs
from my mouth.
We would have yet another
fight over dinner at dusk
and quietly discuss
the following day's
affairs in the evening.
I have had several
experiences
travelling and
living with others.
However, I cannot seem
to remember them
for some reason.
I suppose I am too busy
wondering what my partner
was doing yesterday.
What he was like last night,
and what he will
be like tomorrow.
I used to cry when I was
exhausted and
thinking of home.
But now, each day is
so full and wonderful...
I do not find myself
feeling sad any longer.
I cannot even pretend
I am not having a good time.
In fact, I am
rather concerned
I might be
having too much fun.
Heavy... Why am I at the inn?
Sorry.
No. That cannot
have happened.
No. It was just a nightmare.
I refuse to believe it!
I wonder why I...
Of course, I was
thrown off guard.
It was his stupid face.
When I do not like things,
I get angry.
I laugh when
they are funny.
To show him
that side of me
is unbecoming
of the wise wolf.
How can I live with myself
for behaving in such
a ridiculous manner?
This is my preferred form.
I can swiftly respond
to enemies' attacks
when I am as a wolf.
[HOLO laughing]
He cannot help but
expose himself as a fool.
He is as if a silly cat.
Perhaps I should
be defenseless
and insensitive like him
in order to survive in
this obtuse human world.
Why is he not here?
To think, he is not at my side
at a critical time
such as this... useless.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Why am I reacting this way?
[knocking]
Finally, you have
come back to me.
Why didn't you tell me
that you weren't
feeling well?
Um, well I...
You're not a child.
Don't tell me you didn't
notice until you fainted.
Thank god we were here.
What would we have done
if this happened to you
while we were travelling?
I know you may find
it hard to understand,
but if you fall
sick in a forest
or wasteland,
you could die.
You scared the hell
out of me, you know.
I am sorry.
How are you feeling now?
Any better?
I am fine.
I believe the exhaustion
has caught up with me.
So...
It's not a special
disease or anything?
Do not worry.
Oh, good... Thank God.
I feel like
I can breathe now.
You are good
at overreacting.
Yeah, thanks...
I guess once I started
thinking about everything
and what might have
caused you to be sick,
I, thought... never mind.
Tell me.
You thought what?
I... I thought it might be
because I gave you those onions.
I am not a dog, you know.
Yeah, I know.
You're Holo the Wise Wolf.
It is a shame I did not
get the chance to enjoy
the food and alcohol
from the festival, though.
Did you forget
I'm a merchant?
I'm on top of it,
I asked them
to wrap up
the leftovers for you.
Did you really?
Yes, I did.
Do you want them now?
Of course!
I knew you'd say that;
let me check...
Feels like you
still have a fever.
You were exhausted,
weren't you?
It is all your fault.
What?!
Your fingers are hard,
like a wolf's nose,
and it is very
confusing for me.
When wolves rub
their noses together,
to humans
that would mean...
I cannot say it.
Why not?
What's wrong?
Nothing is wrong!
Forget it!
Well, anyway, you're going
to have to wait on your food.
Try and get some rest.
Lawrence!
You are so warm.
[knocking]
Holo, are you up?
Can you not see me?
How are you feeling?
No, I cannot.
Now I can tell...
You look as pale as a spoiled
princess from a rich family.
Thank you. I am hungry.
Well, there's a bit
of good news...
I'll see if I can get
you porridge or something.
I am thirsty as well...
Did you bring me water?
No. Since you had
a fever last night,
I got you hard cider.
Are you serious?!
Um, Holo?
Hey, are you okay?
If only you were
half as quiet normally
as you are now.
You would get upset
if I never spoke,
sleeping in
the cart all day.
Well, it wouldn't be fair if
I were the only one awake.
If I did not speak up,
you would take advantage
and eat more than
me during meals.
I'm a good deal
bigger than you.
That's just natural.
So in order to compete,
shall I pretend to
be bigger than you?
What's wrong?
It tastes odd.
Right.
I diluted it some.
You did what?!
I thought my nose had
decided to stop working.
Diluted hard cider,
is good for a fever.
What?
Oh, come on...
You really
didn't know that?
I am Holo the Wise Wolf...
I know there are things
in this world I do not know,
and that makes me wise.
Sickness happens
when the balance
inside your body
breaks down.
It's like the ebb
and flow of the tide.
And when an imbalance occurs,
you can cure it
by simply adjusting
the balance between
the four humours.
Did you just say humours?
Correct!
There's hot,
there's cold,
there's dry,
and there's moisture.
If you say so.
All of these can
be adjusted with food.
Since you come
down with a fever,
you'd want to make sure
and eat something cold.
Cold like... apples!
I would thoroughly
enjoy eating a raw apple.
No, that won't work.
Apples are cold,
but they're also dry.
When you're
not feeling well,
you're actually dry,
so you need to
consume moisture
to balance yourself out.
The best source would be
to have something to drink.
Usually, if you
drink alcohol,
you'll feel better.
But, strong
alcohol is hot,
so we need to
lighten it up a bit.
So, what am
I allowed to eat
in order to be
balanced, then?
Well, if you have a fever
from accumulated fatigue
you need to cool
yourself down first.
Your body is
probably dehydrated,
so you need
to rehydrate it.
However, moisture
has a cooling effect,
and if you get too cold
You become gloomy...
It's true...
Now, knowing all this,
what would you say
to wheat porridge
cooked in sheep's milk
with apple pieces
and goat cheese on top?
That sounds delicious!
Yes! I want that!
Are you sure?
You seem completely
recovered right now.
I am dizzy.
Will you please hurry up?
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Do not forget
the goat cheese!
Lawrence!
[knocking]
Can you get up yet?
I cannot.
If I ever get sick,
I expect you to take
really good care
of me in return, deal?
Sure, I hope you will not
mind the Yoitz approach.
I can't promise anything.
Do not worry, I have
a very sensitive nose
and I would do
something about it
long before
you got like this.
Yeah, I am sorry
I didn't notice earlier.
But, for future reference,
I would like
for you to tell me.
I guess I'm just slow.
I can't really help it.
I believe that it would take
a while for you to realize
I was ill even if
I were on my deathbed.
What?
Forget I said anything.
Where is my food?!
If you can eat this,
you'll be fine.
Just give yourself
another day or so.
Ahh... Okay.
Once we leave this town,
we'll be back on
the wagon for a while.
I am sorry.
Don't be.
Focus on getting better.
I gave up on travelling
with any urgency
once I picked you up.
And remember, they say
after a big storm
comes the calm.
I gained back my reputation,
and things already seem
a whole lot better
than they were before.
When I think about it,
the prospect of staying
a few more days
could be a good thing.
I actually wouldn't mind
doing a little exploring
while we're here.
Please wait!
'Tis just...
The inn is...
it is far too quiet.
I suppose it is.
At any rate, it's probably
time we had a discussion
about what to
have for dinner
due to a certain
glutton I know.
Oh, that is
a good idea!
So have you
given any thought
to what you
might want to eat?
Although I'd like to
stay and keep you company,
I won't be able
to make you anything
if I don't get to the market
before it closes.
Keep in mind,
you need to stay
away from the heavy stuff.
Meat?
No. It has to
be either porridge
or soup with
bread dipped in it.
Then I want the dish
I ate earlier...
Sheep's milk, yes?
The flavor and the sweet
scent were so wonderful.
I would like that.
Ah, you want
sheep's milk again?
Is there a problem?
It goes bad quickly,
so the price of decent milk
goes up in the afternoon.
You want it to be
fresh, don't you?
I do!
All right.
I'll see if Nora
can find some.
She isn't a shepherd
for nothing.
She's really good
at finding a-- Uhh...
Um...
If we ask Nora,
we'll be able to get
you some good milk.
Or you could use
the power of money,
and then you would not need
her precious help at all.
Yes...
You might be right
about that, but still.
But still what?!
Can I ask why you insist
on hating Nora so much?
What...? What did you say?
I'm just wondering.
I mean, obviously
something happened
between you and shepherds.
I understand you don't like
her because you're a wolf.
But you don't
have to be so openly
hostile towards her,
do you?
There's an exception
to every rule.
I wish you could see
how kind she really is.
You know, I...
What is it?
Okay, fine, I am sorry.
So you'll
give her a chance?
Ugh, how shall I put this...
Whatever...
You cannot help
how you are.
I expect the milk
to be good.
Nora just wanted to
see how you were doing.
Are you feeling
any better now?
I am suffering from
a little bit of fatigue.
That is all.
However, I would like
to talk with someone.
I am curious; may I ask
you something, Nora?
What? Oh, sure.
I just hope I know
the right answer for you.
What do you think
is the greatest
trick to leading sheep?
I would say that
it's having a big heart.
It's getting windy
out there, huh?
I believe you are right.
Sheep are often convinced
they are too clever
for their own good.
Are you ladies
getting along?
Um... of course.
We are sharing
a little secret.
Really?
Next episode:
Wolf and the Inadvertent Rift