So... She's a wolf?
If that's the case,
then this is a warning
from Medio Trading.
They're telling you
not to do anything
until the deal is completed.
Unless you want your
companion taken to the church.
But still...
how can we know
they won't take her
to the church
afterwards anyway?
And let's not forget,
we've already
invested a great deal
in devaluing
Trenni silver coins.
If we back off now
we'll lose all of it.
Then we need to
be aggressive!
Suppose we rescue
your companion
and agree to
provide her shelter...
If we are
reported to the church
there will be no more
options available.
Like obedient sheep,
we'll simply have
to do what we're told.
As long as she stays in
this town we can't hide her.
Then I'll get her out
of the town and we'll run!
Unless you're extremely
lucky, you'll be caught.
She'll only
end up being taken
to another town and
reported to the church there.
Once that happens
there's nothing we can do.
What if we take into account
the profit
they're going to make
we might still be able
to solve this thing with money.
If only we had a trump card
we could counter with.
There is one way.
We'll report that Medio Trading
has your companion
with them before they do.
Which would redirect
focus on to them.
But if we choose
to sacrifice your friend,
I'm sure you would
be less than supportive.
You might even
take the initiative
and testify against us.
[LAWRENCE]
You can count on it.
But what's the benefit
in having the silver coins?
There must be some
sort of privilege
obtained from
the King of Trenni right?
According to our
investigation
the royal family's purse
strings are increasingly tight.
They'd have to be...
The royal family is
trying to temporarily gather
and melt the silver coins
currently in circulation.
The idea is that if
10 of their silver coins
can be made into
13 by reducing the purity,
they've made a profit.
For now they can
generate the funds needed,
but at the same time,
the country loses credibility.
You ask me,
the long-term disadvantage
is far greater than the
temporary increase in funds.
Yet they've taken it upon
themselves to do it anyway.
The Trenni Kingdom must be
in severe financial difficulty.
Which means...
that depending
upon the agreement...
you could get
plenty out of them...
It's amazing...
We're talking minting rights,
the rights to set tariff rates,
manage complete
markets, anything...
That's exactly right.
Then I think
I might have an idea.
Before Medio
Trading reports her...
complete your negotiations
on the Trenni silvers coins.
Use that profit as the trump
card to bargain with them
But selling privilege for
Holo may not be worth it to you.
You mean we have them
buy the privilege back?
If we make them
think buying it
is more profitable
than shutting you down...
I'm willing to bet
that they'll go ahead and pay.
Don't forget they
have their own trump card
that could send every
single one of us to the stake.
Not true.
If Trenni gets in trouble
with the church
the country can't win.
The Trenni Kingdom
wouldn't want their public
to know they were
connected with you...
not a company
sent to the stake.
If we received any unwanted
attention from the church...
the King would suffer because
of his interaction with us.
Medio Trading would
never make an accusation
that would only anger
the King in return.
I see... But still,
they won't be able
to back off of this quietly.
They'd be forced to
take you down with them.
So we hand over
the privilege in exchange
for reasonable compensation
and releasing your companion.
Yes. Exactly.
Well it's fine
methodology...
However, we still
have one major problem.
That's where you're wrong.
As far as I can tell,
Medio Trading hasn't
gathered that many coins yet.
Based on?
Based on...
If they'd already
had enough silver coins...
they wouldn't
have just taken Holo,
they'd have gone
directly to the church.
But they didn't.
They just tried
to block our move instead...
Hardly seems to me like
they're confident in their plan.
This deal takes
advantage of the King.
I can't imagine they've
made a big show
of purchasing coins.
What about you?
It seems I have a plan,
but what are you going to do?
I'll get Holo back...
We can stay on the run until
you finish the negotiations.
That's reckless.
We may eventually get caught,
but I think I can
buy us some extra time.
In the meantime,
gather as many silver coins
as you can and finish the deal.
I can't do it.
So then do you
intend to report Holo?
If that happens
I will testify against you.
All we need is a little help.
We can manage for
at least a day or two...
You have to remember,
I'm running with the
incarnation of a wolf beside me.
Even if she ends
up getting captured...
Humans are no match for her,
not if she's using
her natural abilities.
Trust me on this.
Let me ask you a question,
How much time will you need
to gather enough
coins to talk to the King?
If we leave by horse
for Trenni Castle right now
we'll get there by sunset.
And then if the
deal's made on the spot
we could be back by morning.
Right now?
But you haven't
even figured out
how many silver coins you're
going to need to collect yet.
We'll simply work
it out based on an estimate.
And when it comes
time for delivery
we'll have
it all for them.
Okay...
But do you think
you'll be able
to negotiate
with the King on the spot?
I certainly
don't want to brag...
but if we want to we can
make any deal on the spot.
So then, you have to tell me,
do you know where
they're hiding Holo?
We are Milone
Trading after all.
Our employees
are attacked at night.
Our shops are set on fire.
These are everyday
things for us.
Our emergency measures
have to be and are perfect.
Although we do have one rival.
The church.
That is correct.
They visit more
countries and cities
than we could or
would want to visit.
So, they are
surprisingly well prepared
for emergencies themselves.
If the church decides to make
a concerted effort to find her,
she'll have no choice
but to confine herself
instead of
carelessly running away.
Under normal circumstances,
I would have preferred
to negotiate after finding out
who's behind Medio Trading.
We could find out
who's behind their financing
and take it from them...
it really is a shame
we don't know that benefactor.
I wouldn't even
know where to start.
Be careful.
I'm sure you'll be successful.
I'll try to live up
to your expectations.
Oh, the passwords...
Pireon and Numai...
remember them.
We're using two gold coins?
What else would we use?
[LAWRENCE]
Once I'm underground,
I go forward while
touching the wall on the right.
Is that it?
[MILONE EMPLOYEE A] Yes.
When you get to
the end of the passage,
just stay there and wait.
And the warehouse above that
is where they're
holding Holo.
So I stay there until
the market's opening bell rings
and that's when your people
will go in and save her.
[MILONE EMPLOYEE A]
If all goes well...
someone will be there
to open the cover above you
and lower your companion.
After that,
and listen very carefully,
if you hear the word
"Rahe" wait for my colleague.
If you hear "perouso"
then escape with her
via the planned
path immediately.
Rahe and perouso...
Periods of economic
boom or decline.
We like to keep it simple.
Clearly.
Okay, it's almost time.
[COACHMAN A] You idiot!
Watch where you're going!
[YOUNG MAN]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Go...
It's now or never.
I had no idea
they'd be this prepared.
I've often heard that churches
dig underground passages
for espionage and tax evasion
while at the same time making
it look to the general public
as if they're digging graves.
This is it.
[MEDIO EMPLOYEE A]
Come on out...
I've orders to move you.
It's happening now.
God, I hope they
can get her out okay.
Damn it...!
Why can't I stop shaking?!
What's taking so long?
Come on!
[MILONE EMPLOYEE B]
Rahe.
[MEDIO EMPLOYEE A]
Rahe!
Numai!
[MEDIO EMPLOYEE A]
Pireon.
Holo!
So I have to take this with me
so they think it was a burglary?
Come on! Let's go!
I cannot until you
get out of my way.
Please move!
Do not just stand there.
Here, these are for you...
Take them and try moving.
[FEMALE A]
Yes?
[MILONE EMPLOYEE A]
Pireon.
Numai!
[MILONE EMPLOYEE A]
Looks like everything went well.
Surprises are a part
of this business right?
Are we leaving him?
He'll come up
at another location...
Plus someone has to
get rid of that ladder.
After that I'm sure
he'll wanna leave town
since he's giving
the information
he has on
Medio to Marlheit.
Thank you for everything.
I hope you two make it.
Yeah, so do I.
I'm glad you're okay.
You were glad
I'm okay...? Really.
Yeah.
Say my name then!
Holo...! Holo!
Call me Holo, the Wise Wolf!
Wise... Yes.
And you would do
well to remember it...
I can name everyone who
has ever embarrassed me...
and now I have to add
one more to that list.
You are probably
wondering what name
to which I am referring.
'Tis your name!
Lawrence?
What were you
doing all that time?
I expected you
to come and rescue me!
Yes, and I did.
I know!
But you should still...
You were supposed to
have come for me much sooner.
I cannot talk;
I am too angry.
Holo... What happened?
You are a male...
It should have
been natural for you
to come and
rescue me immediately.
I thought I would
be down there forever...
You have no idea
how humiliating that was!
But you are okay?
Am I right?
I'm glad you're okay.
As long as you have
that wheat I shall not die...
There is no need to be worried.
I am pretty, so human males
have been known to fall for me.
Some would
be wise to remember
I am too strong for a human.
I am a wolf you know.
I did warn them...
"Touch me and I will
tear your thing off."
And can you believe
not one of them did?
Good for you.
I was fine.
Until that...
person appeared.
You may well
be surprised by who it is.
I know I was.
Who was it then?
Chloe.
The one from Pasloe.
Before I escaped, she told
me that young man, Zheren,
was the one
who gave her my name.
[LAWRENCE]
What did she say?
[CHLOE] I really thought
it was just an old story.
She was not kind.
An incarnation of the wolf
who lives on
the village's wheat fields
and can freely control whether
the harvest is rich or poor.
It is funny.
I do not know how many years
have passed since
I began living there.
It could be one year
for each hair on my tail.
I am Holo the Wise Wolf.
In order to have
rich harvests more often,
I sometimes made a poor
harvest to recover the fields.
It was always
under my supervision.
Yet, even with
those poor harvests,
I am sure their village
was a much better place
to grow wheat than other lands.
It is true
the villagers treated me
as if I were a god
of rich harvests.
But they did not
do so out of respect.
They simply wanted
to keep me there...
The one who
harvests the last
gets captured by everyone
and has to pretend
to be me, correct?
Do you have any idea
what that woman said to me?
She said... once she
heard my name from Zheren...
she hoped it might
be true... I was... I was...
And I was happy
when she told me this.
However, she was
hardly finished with me.
Didn't you know,
the days of us spending our time
appeasing you
are over now.
We no longer
need to be nervous
about your
impulsiveness.
And when we turn you
over to the church...
we will finally bid farewell
to a god who does not care.
I felt... I felt...
such shame!
You know...
I think you're
looking at it the wrong way.
If you want
to go back up north...
You're going to have
to leave the land eventually.
So it doesn't upset
them to see you leave...
Don't you see there's
a kind of freedom in that?
You're not bound
to the land anymore...
But at the same time
we're not leaving for nothing.
Because I-- no, we are
both of us merchants...
And I'll promise
you one thing...
We will not laugh
until we get the money,
and we will not cry
until we go bankrupt.
And guess what?
We are going to laugh.
Thank you.
However, I have
had few conversations
in the past several
hundred years...
So I've become
emotionally delicate.
It may be true that I have
cried in front
of you twice now.
But I would have cried
even if it was not you.
Do you understand
what I am saying?
That I'm your favorite?
Wrong.
If it makes you feel
better I'm taking care
of you
for the money.
Our job is to keep running
until Milone contacts us.
You can't keep crying
at the drop of a hat.
Although if you did
I'd still be there...
if only for the money...
So even if
it was someone else
that was doing the crying,
I'd have--
Stop it... That isn't fair.
I am the favorite.
[COACHMAN A]
Hey you two, we've arrived.
I certainly hope you've
come to an understanding.
Yeah...
I know the person
who's behind Medio Trading...
His name is Earl Ehrendott.
The merchant that's
been dealing wheat
in the Earl's territory
is the one who's collecting
the silver coins
in a large quantity.
Please pass this
information along to Marlheit.
I'll tell him myself.
No surprise...
Seems those who bring
money-making ideas
are always a little different.
You mean my ears?
Watching you two reminds
me of the old days...
I used to be a peddler too.
You better be careful...
Or you might just end
up with someone like her.
Really...?
Well the coach's seat
is too big for one person...
I'll have to start
praying for your luck.
Maybe if I had
"ended up" with him
I would not be in such a mess.
Not fair... I just won't talk.
I think you're
developing a crush on me.
All right, you are pretty cute.
I'll give you that much.
I'm glad.
And for a kid,
you're pretty cute yourself.
Geez.
Next episode:
Wolf and Silent Farewell.