[raining]
[LAWRENCE grimacing]
[LAWRENCE panting]
[HOLO] I was hoping this
would be a more moving reunion.
But you look just terrible.
Lemerio betrayed us...
This is the only
thing I could protect.
Seriously, you are
such an idiot.
Your face is
swollen from being hit...
You are covered in mud...
And your wrists
are even burnt.
Even in this
pathetic state,
you were still careful
and folded my robe to
keep it from getting wet.
You are terribly
good-natured!
Lawrence...
I might be forced
to kill humans.
Holo...
I had a plan
to carry out
this scheme
as quickly as possible.
I wanted it to go back
to just us travelling alone.
It is the reason
I did not argue
with that arrogant youth.
I managed the situation
with maturity.
Did you have to
bow before them?
I did.
Forget about it.
I made the decision
to do so.
And yet...
This is how
we are rewarded?!
I return to find you
in this abused state!
I cannot bear
to see you suffer!
[HOLO] We will go see
Lemerio immediately.
A price must be paid
for what he has done to us!
[LAWRENCE]
No, wait!
We have to find Liebert
and the others first!
And as soon as possible!
If a reason exists
that will convince me,
tell me now.
They are planning
to kill Nora.
That little girl does
have a partner as well.
I am sure she will be fine
even without our help.
It may be true
she has a partner,
but there's only so much
a sheepdog can do, Holo!
She needs you!
What could I do?
You could help!
You can take care of
a hundred men in no time.
Of course I can,
but only in my wolf form!
So?
That little girl
is a shepherd, right?
You have to do it Holo.
We can't let them kill her.
You don't want to see someone
murdered anymore than I do.
I would be willing to show
my appreciation, as well.
Really?
As long as you don't
say you want Nora's life,
I'll do everything I can
to fulfill your wish.
Come on...
You're the only one
that can save her!
Holo?!
I should probably
take off my clothes.
It would be such a pain
to make new ones.
I'll take that as a yes.
I still have one
condition though:
It does not
matter who they are,
I will not be
able to guarantee
their safety if they
begin to aggravate me.
You will accept
this before I can act.
Yes, I understand.
Although, I still
have faith in you.
When did you become
such a smooth talker?
Honestly...
My companion is nothing
more than trouble.
I am sorry...
Did you have
something to say?
Yeah...
You've got an amazing tail.
Well, that was
rather bland,
but most appreciated.
Now then,
I need you
to close your eyes
for a minute.
Go ahead, get on.
It is all right if you need
to hold on to my hair.
Do not worry, if you fall
I will carry you in my mouth.
I'm not gonna let go!
[LAWRENCE screaming]
[HOLO]
Lawrence?
[LAWRENCE]
What is it?
It is...
um...
I just want
you to know
I do not like shepherds
even a little.
Good!
I'm relieved to hear it!
Remember, Nora's
going to have to quit
working as a shepherd
whether this job
succeeds or not!
I have decided on
what I want!
What?!
The finest honey-pickled
peaches money can buy!
Come on Hol--
[LAWRENCE screaming]
[NORA]
No! Lawrence and Holo!
[MERCHANT A] When we found them,
they were beyond recognition.
Their bodies laid
over one another.
[LIEBERT]
Nora!
Excuse me...
I think I'm okay now.
[LIEBERT] While it
really is regrettable...
We must
remember we're alive
and we should
do our very best
to carry on
in their memory.
[HOLO] Hey! I need to know
if you're prepared for this!
[LAWRENCE]
What?
We are very near to them.
We've already caught up?
We have.
I can't see them!
Damn it...
There are at
least 20 people
and they appear
to be heavily armed.
Are you serious?
It does not matter.
Leave it to me!
Once I jump over them,
I shall drop low.
I want you to
get off of me then.
[HOLO howling]
I want you to stay here.
Protect the shepherd
and the sheep!
Nora! She's still alive!
Take the shepherd
and get out of here! Run!
Shepherd!
Do your job!
Enek!
[ENEK and HOLO growling]
[LAWRENCE]
Oh no!
This is bound
to aggravate Holo.
[LIEBERT]
Listen to me!
I will pay you 300 Lumiones
if you protect me!
Oh God... no!
[LAWRENCE panting]
Enek, go!
[ENEK barking]
[NORA]
Enek!
No... wait!
[LIEBERT screaming]
[LAWRENCE]
Nora!
Is that you?
I can't believe it...
Lawrence, you
aren't a ghost are you?
[ENEK growling]
[LAWRENCE] Do you want
to know a secret?
That wolf is actually Holo.
[NORA]
Holo?
[LAWRENCE] So you didn't
kill him after all.
[HOLO]I thought about swallowing
him once and for all,
but gold would probably
not sit well with my stomach.
[LAWRENCE]
Understandable.
This is it.
[LIEBERT] What the
hell is going on?!
I hope you bastards
don't think
you'll get away
with this!
[LAWRENCE] Hello, Liebert.
How's it goin?
Please!
I wasn't the one
who betrayed you!
It wasn't me...
I swear... it wasn't me!
This wolf is a proxy sent
by the Almighty God, you know.
She is not going
to believe your lies.
[LIEBERT]
No! No! No! No!
The payment you demanded
was too much for us!
If we paid as much
as you wanted,
we wouldn't have
had any money left
after paying off
our own deb.!
It was Lemerio's idea!
It's not my fault!
You understand,
you're a merchant like me!
I'm nothing like you.
I hope you can excuse
all this commotion.
Oh... No problem.
By now I'm sure
you've realized
Lemerio Trading
has betrayed us.
I also heard them talking
about their plans to kill you.
I did think something seemed
strange but I never imagined...
[HOLO] Well, are we going to
run with the gold now or what?
I'm not really sure...
If we don't smuggle
the gold to Lubinheigen
the exchange rate
for what Liebert purchased
is still worth
600 gold Lumiones.
If we simply
forget about Lemerio,
we could split it with
each other and live happily
without having
to work for a long time.
On the other hand,
if we didn't get
the funds from Lemerio
in the first place,
we wouldn't be in
the position to keep this gold.
If we run with
the money now, their company,
including all
of their employees,
will end up bankrupt
and out of business.
And then...
What then?
Holo!
I'm just trying to make
sure that we can still
live with ourselves
at the end of the day!
If we get revenge on
them for betraying us,
there'll only be another
revenge waiting!
[HOLO]
I'll take care of it.
You can't tell me you're
going to kill everyone involved!
It won't feel good
to buy bread tomorrow
with money that's
been stained with blood.
You have to believe me,
there's more than
just one option here!
Now is our
opportunity to choose
the road that will
lead us into tomorrow!
Holo...
Don't act like
you don't care;
if it wasn't for you
I would have frozen to death.
And I appreciate you agreeing
to my request
more than you know.
Listen...
[HOLO]
Enough already!
Do what you want!
I really do have the most
troublesome companion.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What? Oh that's fine.
So tell me what you
think about this idea...
[crickets chirping]
Tell me the truth,
Lawrence.
The truth?
Yes, please.
I would like
to hear it from you.
What are you talking about?
Do not play dumb with me.
I know you are not quite
the saint you pretend to be.
I want you to be
the one to decide
whether or not we go ahead
and take this gold
into Lubinheigen.
And I won't mind
at all if you think
we should just
divide the 600 Lumiones.
Oh...
But then, if we
take it in to town.
well... I could
turn it into 6,000.
6,000?!
Yes.
And with that
much we could
keep Lemerio Trading
from going under.
Since you seem to
know everything already,
I might as well tell you...
The amount of gold
was too little.
Really?
Yeah...
There's no way that bag
has 600 Lumiones in it...
There's 100 at best.
If we split it up,
and if you repaid your debt,
there wouldn't be any left.
So, unless we smuggle it,
we won't make any money.
Apparently they were starting
to get desperate...
The most they could come up
with was 100 Lumiones.
That's only a sixth
of what we asked for.
If they smuggled this,
it would increase to 1,000,
which would
barely get them by.
Then again, it's not
as if they would have had
to split the proceeds
with us had their plan worked.
Perhaps it was all
they could afford...
Either way, Lemerio Trading
knew they could not
pay us from
the very beginning.
Actually, I bet
it's the very reason
they decided to go along
with our little scheme.
Yes, I understand
it all now, however--
Don't tell me there's more.
It was not
necessary to speak
to that little girl
the way you did.
What... do you
think I overdid it?
You did not have to shoulder
the burden all alone.
There is more I would like
to say, but we are out of time.
Get on.
You do have to go
see Lemerio, correct?
You're going to come in
with me though, right?
I have no interest
in business dealings.
Are you angry with me?
If you don't hold on,
I will throw you off.
[LEMERIO]
What?! 500?!
[LAWRENCE]
That's right...
Once we succeed
with the smuggling...
Do you think
you would be able
to buy it from us
at 500 gold Lumiones?
N-No!
That's impossible!
There's no way we can afford
that in our current state!
I'm not talking cash here.
All you would have to do
is draw up a bond of debt
and then you would simply
pay installments
over the next 10 years.
Didn't you hear me,..
500 is too much!
Interesting...
You're someone who
founded a trading company
that can secure
a fairly lucrative
loading place in this town.
Seems to me
500 in 10 years
would be a small price
to pay for you.
Wait, what
are you doing?
Your man Liebert was
full of information.
I suppose you could run away
with this insignificant
amount of money...
But it might be
in your best interest
to simply accept our demand
and rebuild your company.
You can put the Lohen Merchant
Association as the loaner.
Association?!
Well, you can always
lie to an individual,
but if you end up
betraying an association
you'll never work
as a merchant again.
[JACOB] I thought
I'd seen the last of you!
You scared the hell out of
me you stupid son-of-a-gun.
[LAWRENCE]
Jacob, I can't breathe!
[JACOB] Inspirational,
what a good son.
You're so devoted!
[JACOB crying]
[JACOB]
With this, you'll be able
to convert
your 10-year-loan
into cash immediately
and still break off
relations with Lemerio.
How the hell did
you manage this?
[LAWRENCE] It was
just a gold dealing...
Although I can't
talk about it too loud...
For now, I'll buy this
for 30 Lumiones...
Once the deal goes through,
I'll go ahead and
give you another 100.
A hundred?!
It's extra for such
a joyous occasion!
Thank you, Jacob.
If I have that much,
I'll be able to repay
what I owe to people
when I go apologize to them.
[JACOB laughing]
Nah. I can't
believe it Lawrence,
you've turned out to be quite
an impressive peddler.
Now, once the
assessment is finished,
we'll drink until we drop!
Well, it's just
my companion...
She's waiting.
You are late.
I'm sorry!
Now, did you have something
you wanted to ask me?
Two somethings.
Two somethings?
Firstly...
How much do you trust
that little shepherd girl?
It doesn't matter,
even if Nora ran with the gold
we'd be able to catch her.
I guess I don't
trust her to the extent
that I gave her
the gold with that in mind.
Well, that
is that, then.
What was your
other question?
I promise I'll answer
no matter what you ask.
Remember, I'm the one who
owes you now so please ask away.
I just wante...
I think I need
to get some air.
Do you... remember?
[HOLO] I have been
wondering...
Whose name did
you call when I faced
the dog and
the little shepherd girl?
I was so angry at the time,
I could not hear you.
However, I could
still see you though
so I know you must have called
at least one of our names.
That's what's been
weighing on your mind?
No, not really...
Like I said, I had just
been wondering about it.
I called your name, Holo.
Did you just lie to me?
Yeah, I kinda did...
To be honest, I don't
remember what I said.
On the other hand...
On the other hand?
Given the situation,
I'm almost positive
I would have
called out your name.
I didn't really
have any time to waste.
I imagine
I must've unconsciously
chosen to call your name.
Yes.
That makes sense because--
Lawrence, hold on!
Okay. You may
finish explaining.
Well it's because...
It's because your name is
a little shorter than hers is.
On top of that, even if
I had said Nora quickly,
you'd know for sure, right?
I mean come on,
the name Holo
goes so fast in
that split second
you wouldn't have
heard me if you were angry.
So there,
don't you think
that's a pretty
good explanation?
Not one bit!
Are you seriously telling
me you only called my name
because it was
a little shorter?!
What upsets me
more than anything
is that you
actually think this way!
Idiot!
Oh! I wish you just told me
you had called her name!
Moron!
What is wrong with you?
Try again.
But this is your last chance.
Lawrence, please
just say one name.
[clocktower ringing]
[HOLO and LAWRENCE
unable to hear each other]
[LAWRENCE]
Holo.
Yeah I like that name
better after all.
Idiot.
[LAWRENCE chuckling]
[HOLO] Oh yes, well,
I should clear up
the false accusation for him.
[NORA]
Wha--?
Your companion was
never in love with me.
He just knew
what I was, that is all.
So you knew who she was then?
You have a very good partner.
Trust me, this one here is
more trouble than he is worth.
Oh really?
Well then, I wish the both
of you much happiness.