Che Dio vi benedica
il vostro cammino...
La pace sia con voi.
Thank you very much, sir.
Oh no, thank you very much.
And now I must
thank you again.
Well then...
Wait.
[NORA]
I was just wondering,
where did you hear
about this road?
[LAWRENCE] A bar in
Poroson a few days ago.
Didn't they tell you
about wolves out here?
Yes, they certainly did,
but we decided to risk it.
We're in a bit of a hurry.
I understand.
Um, is something the matter?
Oh... no... It's just...
Go ahead...
Please don't hold
yourself back on my account.
Okay then...
Do you think you
might want to hire me?
I am a shepherd.
And, yes, part of
my job is raising sheep,
but I also have
to protect them.
I can drive wolves away.
I'm very good at it.
If you hire me,
I can protect you
from the wolves on this road.
What do you think?
Enek, go.
[ENEK barking]
[SHEEP baaing]
Give me just a second.
Let me go talk to my partner.
Her skills?
Yes, she can help us.
You heard what
she said, right?
I think it might be worth it.
Yes, but you
already have me.
I know, and I realize
you should be enough...
but I never even
considered that a shepherd
could be used to protect
us from wolves, did you?
It could help me with
some business ventures, too.
It appears as though
human males do not mind
having several females around.
First of all,
don't wolves run in packs?
And second of all,
you're prettier than
her and you know it.
Oh fine.
I guess I can accept
that explanation.
So, you think
she's any good?
She ranks among the highly
skilled, most likely.
Think you could
be more specific?
I could hunt her sheep
without a problem.
But, I imagine she could
handle ordinary wolves easily,
even if they all
attacked at once.
[LAWRENCE]
Why is that?
[HOLO] She is quite the
expert at handling her dog.
A troublesome shepherd
and a clever dog
always work well together.
'Tis true in her
case at least...
Judging by her voice,
she seems young.
I am concerned about how
good she is yet to become.
Perhaps I might want
to take care of her now...
Please don't.
Thank you though.
Oh, Lawrence?
You do not really
plan to hire her, do you?
That's what
I'm thinking, yeah.
If you do hire her
we will be forced
to travel together for
a while, am I not correct?
Well yes.
Well, I find
that disconcerting.
We'll only be
traveling together
for two days, that's all.
Yes and I find
that disconcerting.
Right...
You'll be fine,
just be patient.
What could I possibly
need to be patient for?
Well you know...
it'll be two whole days
before we can be alone again...
But if you can't bear it...
I do not mind, but it
might cause problems for you.
If we were to
carelessly travel with others.
What happens if they
are to find out about me?
Oh... I understand now...
Would you rather
I said something like this?
I want to travel with you...
all by myself!
Idiot.
Holo.
Seriously.
Well, she will
probably not find out
if it is
only for two days.
You may do
as you please.
I'm sorry to
keep you waiting.
No, that's fine.
How does 40 Tries to get
us to Lubinheigen sound?
And, I'll pay you extra
if you keep us
from getting harmed
should wolves
happen to attack.
Is that too low?
No! Thank you very much!
No, thank you.
I'm sorry, I completely
forgot to ask your name.
Oh... of course.
I'm sorry too.
I'm... I'm Nora Arendt.
Enek.
Have you been working
as a shepherd for long?
Oh no. It's been
about four years.
I only became a shepherdess
after I took in my Enek.
That's surprising...
What did you do before?
I lived in a convent
annex and worked there.
We sheltered the poor
and helped take care of them.
I see.
I enjoyed my
time at the shelter,
but I always wanted
to have a job on my own.
I'm really lucky
to have found my Enek.
He's probably a reward
for your kindness.
Yes...
I'm sure it must have been
God that brought him to me
and for that
I am very grateful.
When I first met him,
he was filthy and
covered in wounds.
Attacked by wolves?
No...
I think it must've
been mercenaries...
The poor thing was
cowering under a small cliff
not far from the annex
when I first saw him.
Really?
You know...
I never imagined
I'd have a shepherd as a guard
No?
Shepherds don't normally
guard people, right?
No... I guess...
I thought
we could talk.
I can understand.
Also, I had always
wanted to become a tailor.
But to do it I knew
I needed to have money.
They have association
fees and things like that.
So you know, you'll
probably make more money
guarding merchants
than you will caring for sheep.
I imagine your territory
as a shepherd
is always up for debate.
Definitely...
It seems the safe places
are already claimed
by the time I get there.
The only area left was
the one with all the wolves?
Yes.
I have a feeling
they can be a pain.
Ow!
On top of that they're
cunning and underhanded.
They may be able to hear us
so it's best not to
talk bad about them.
You're right.
Once again, I am very sorry
for making you stop so early.
No...
Don't be.
I understand completely;
shepherds have to go to
sleep before the sunsets.
Thank you.
Enek and I have to watch
over the whole flock
throughout the night.
You know I always
think the same thing
when I look
at all of them.
"I wonder what kind of clothing
their wool will become."
Your shepherding skills are
really quite impressive Nora.
You're talented.
Oh no... Not me.
With your skill,
they should allow you to care
for a lot more
sheep than this.
I consider the ones
I have blessing enough.
I don't think I would
be able to handle any more.
I don't think your
employer is very smart.
Why don't you find
someone who appreciates you?
I could never though.
It's not possible.
Sorry...
I'm a merchant after all
so I tend to
think about things
only in terms
of profit and loss.
Lawrence?
Yeah?
Could you tell me,
do people usually change
their employers a lot?
Well it's normal to find
someone else to work for
if you don't like
how you're being treated.
I didn't know that.
Nora, don't you
work for the church?
What?
It's just a guess,
but I have feeling it's true.
I do, yes...
The priest at the church
entrusted the sheep to me.
He's actually
been very considerate.
You can ignore
what I said earlier...
You may not
get the best pay,
but as long as God
doesn't abandon us,
the church is not
going to go anywhere.
You won't ever have to
worry about losing your job
as a shepherd
and you'll never go hungry.
I guess you're right.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
And, as far as I know,
God doesn't have any rules
against doing a little
work on the side.
Tell you what,
when I get to Lubinheigen
I'll have a talk
with some of my friends
who are merchants.
I'll see if any of them
need a dependable guard, okay?
You'd really do that
for me Lawrence? Thank you!
She does not have
a job that's easy.
Well I do have to care
for my tail every day.
Oh wait., you're
talking about her aren't you.
Her name's
Nora by the way.
Hey!
You said it was okay.
I mean that is why
I asked you first!
Now I cannot even
groom my tail in peace.
But you were
just doing it.
Yes, until I had
to listen to the two of you.
Are you kidding?
I suppose you seemed to
be having a nice little chat.
You mean with Nora?
Unless you were speaking
to her dog or the sheep.
She said she wanted
someone to talk to;
I'm not gonna
turn her down Holo.
More importantly,
I haven't talked
to a normal
girl in awhile.
And you never noticed
that the little shepherd girl
did not actually
wish to speak with you?
That's okay, too.
I mean if it was love at
first sight I wouldn't be able
to experience
the joy of gradually
having her fall for me.
Whatcha think?
I'm pretty smooth, right?
No. No you are not.
You are not smooth at all.
Thanks so much
for that. Geez.
You happy now?
Yes.
Actually I am rather
amused at the moment.
So thank you.
As long as you're
not in a bad mood anymore,
that's all that matters.
I am not.
I do not remember
why I was angry.
I shall take it as
a gift from shepherd girl.
This is it.
Good morning to you, sir.
[GUARD] Well,
good morning to you miss.
May I have a pass?
Thank you.
Thank you
very much, sir.
I really
appreciate your help.
You know at
an official checkpoint
it would have taken
me at least 10 times longer
than that to get
this pass. Thanks!
Don't thank me,
it's all part of
my employment
with the church.
All right, here's the
40 Tries I promised you.
Wait, these 2 silver
coins will exchange
for about 45 Tries.
An investment
from a greedy merchant.
How?
If I have a good connection
with a skilled shepherd
you never know
I might just come
across an unexpected
money-making idea
in wool trading.
Well then thank you again.
We'll be at the trading house
of the Lohen
Merchant Association
for the next few days.
If you plan
to go back out
across the fields again,
please let me know.
I may be able to introduce
you to some merchants
from town who are
in need of a guard.
Yes of course I will.
Just in case let me
ask you something,
the road we took,
is that the only road
you'll be able to
work on as a guard?
No.
I can also go to Kastrata,
Poroson, and Lamtra.
Lamtra...
You mean that Lamtra?
Of course.
And not the roundabout
official route either?
Oh no, I take the shortcut
that goes through the forest.
Are you serious?
Even knights are
afraid of that forest.
As long as I'm
with Enek I'm fine.
Oh, in that
case you'll have
a much better chance
of finding a customer.
I hope that
you're right Lawrence.
Well, I have to go this way
for the livestock entrance.
Okay. We've almost made it.
Now all we're gonna have
to do is get through customs
and then head over to Lemerio
trading to sell these weapons.
Hold on.
We still have to buy
honey pickled peaches.
All right... let's go.
I do not
appreciate being ignored.
Now listen to me,
if they don't have them,
you're just gonna have to
deal with it and they might not.
So you say.
You can't get mad
at me if they don't.
So you say.
I'm not kidding!
[HOLO]
What is that gate?
[LAWRENCE] It's there
to keep enemies
from getting in
during a battle.
And they use those holes
for pouring out
boiling hot oil.
[HOLO] This town has
a disturbingly solid defense.
[CUSTOMS OFFICER]
Your pass please?
So you're coming
from Poroson.
What are you bringing?
Oh, yes I am
bringing 20 sets of arms.
Weapons? From Poroson?
That's right.
I bought them wholesale
from Latparon Trading.
Is that okay?
All right you're good.
So, are you paying
tax with cash or goods?
Oh, with goods please.
That's a wise decision...
Give the people on
your left 2 sets of arms.
It must be unusual then
to make a wholesale
purchase from Poroson.
Well, as a matter
of fact, no it's not...
It's actually
pretty common.
Oh.
Here are my papers.
[TAX COLLECTOR]
You can go.
I think public officials
have to be unpleasant
no matter where you go.
Did you not notice?
It appeared the last
one we encountered
was silently
laughing at us.
He most likely
became jealous
after seeing that pile of
arms and thought to himself
"You are a mere merchant,
do not get to have an ego
just because you
made a little money."
Well that's okay...
we still entered the
town without any problems.
So you wanna leave
the wagon at the inn
and head straight
to the street vendors?
[WOMAN] Peace be
with you, Father.
[PRIEST]
Good morning to you.
[CHURCHMAN] And God
will always find a way for us.
So good!
Could I have a refill please?
[BAR OWNER]
Okay another beer it is.
You're a pretty strong lady.
Oh but barkeep,
I am just getting started.
You've been had
by an expensive girl, sir.
But I gotta say
she is pretty.
I know and
she'd be perfect
if she just
didn't have that tail.
I like this place,
the alcohol is good
and the town is lively.
Be careful of
that liveliness;
you can't let
your guard down.
No matter what,
don't mess around
with knights or
mercenaries okay?
If you do, we'll
be in big trouble.
Here you go ma'am.
Thank you!
Much appreciated!
So, where are
we going now?
The trading house.
Holo, you have stuff
all over your face.
Will you stop?! Come on.
I have a question.
Is there any
point in me going
to that trading
house with you?
No, but I think it's too
dangerous to leave you alone.
Because of how
attractive I am, right?
I didn't mean
it that way.
We'll be in trouble
if you get drunk
and show off
your ears and tail.
If that should happen,
which it won't,
but if it did,
I shall take you into
my mouth and run out of town
as quickly as possible...
the fence is low,
I could do it.
If I am correct there
are stories like this
about a knight
and a young woman
in fairy tales
is there not?
The ones where
a knight rescues
a captured young
woman in his arms?
Yes. I shall do that.
I'm sure you see it
as a lovely picture
but for some reason
me inside a wolf's mouth
doesn't seem too romantic.
Would you rather
I took you upon my back
and raced through
a field of lilies?
By the way...
What is this
trading house?
Running any business comes
with dangers and accidents
and you can't always trust
that someone's
going to protect you.
You know how
knights wear armor?
Well, we, merchants,
like to keep safe
by using connections
with each other.
We're headed to a
branch of an organization
that consists of merchants
from the same homeland.
As always, this place
brings back memories.
It looks like
buildings where I'm from.
It just feels like home.
It must be nice.
To be able to feel at
home in different places.
Do you think
you can manage
to wait here
a little while,
while I go inside?
Wait, I thought you
were going to take me in
and show me off
to all the people
from your hometown.
I'll be quick,
if you can behave yourself
I'll buy you some sweet
bread when we're done.
Do not treat
me like a child!
So you
don't want some?
I shall wait
'til you get back.
[JACOB]
You're a poor excuse
for a merchant
to come in here.
It's the
middle of the day!
If you don't
have an interest
in doing an
honest days work
then you might as
well become a thief, huh.
But a really good
merchant can make money
without even getting
dust on his shoes.
And he should only
dirty his fingertips
with a little black ink.
Running around in
the market all day long
is proof of a
third-rate merchant.
Isn't that right?
Look what
the cat dragged in.
You've turned into
a pretty smooth talker.
Welcome back son!
I've never understood why
you always call me your son.
Now, don't
act so special.
You know everyone in
the Lohen Merchant Association
is like a son
or daughter to me.
Plus, I do still have
the benefit of knowing
you wet your bed a lot
whenever you went camping.
I also know you stole
the proceeds from a sale
and went trembling
with some of your friends
to a house of ill repute.
Okay, that's enough,
thank you.
[YOUNG MERCHANT]
Have you seen a merchant
named Craft Lawrence
come through?
[LOADING MAN]
Forget your man Lawrence.
I haven't even seen a rat
around here for
the past few days
[YOUNG MERCHANT]
I see...
Next episode:
Wolf and the Swirling Plot