[LAWRENCE] What's wrong?
[HOLO] The air, I can feel
it beginning to shake.
[LAWRENCE] We should be
right underneath the market.
Do you think that might be it?
No, it is something else.
Hold on.
Water..
I can hear it splashing.
What direction?
Ahead of us...
We need to run.
Does this passage
not fork anywhere?
Not the way we were headed,
but there are a series
of side roads up ahead.
I do not think even
I could keep us
from getting lost in here.
What is it?
Even if we run
they will catch up...
It seems they have
released the dogs.
The dogs?
Their voices sound stupid.
You should cover your
ears now. Trust me.
[howling]
[PURSUER B]
What the hell was that?
I could really
use some apples.
Once we're out of here,
I'll get you some.
How did they find
out where we were?
They most likely
didn't know we were here.
They probably
came underground
and found us by accident.
Otherwise we would've
been attacked already.
[PURSUER E] Milone Trading
betrayed you both!
Give up now!
[PURSUER E]
There's no use running from us!
Is that true?
Did they betray us?
If so, we were sold
for a high price.
After all,
they could shut down
Milone's branch
if they had you.
Really?
It must have been
high indeed.
They're just formally
greeting us...
Don't worry, it's a lie.
Let's turn here.
[PURSUER G] Hey...
Hey, I found them!
Where?
[PURSUER B] There they are!
That way!
Do you know
where we are going?
Yes! Of course!
We'll make the next right!
No!
Sorry but...
we're in a hurry.
Lawrence! No!
[PURSUER A] Father, I ask
you to forgive me of my sins.
Before you
ask forgiveness,
you should try
repenting how you live!
Damn it.
He stabbed me.
[HOLO]
Lawrence!
Thank goodness.
I... I could
not wake you up.
I'm alright.
I'm only resting,
that's all.
Please stay strong...
We are almost there.
Uh-where?
Did you not listen
to what I was saying?!
I told you I smelled light,
and asked if there was
a place that led above.
That's right...
yeah... I remember.
What's this?
A bandage.
Do not tell me you
forgot about that already!
Well, I am alright.
Don't worry.
We are getting close!
Now we should
find an exit
just at the other end
of this passageway.
Look!
Oh no...
An old well.
Lawrence...
I am sorry; I did
not foresee this.
[PURSUER B]
There they are!
[PURSUER WALLA] Hey!
We found them!
Stay back.
No. Wait.
Stop it. You cannot!
I don't have a choice.
You cannot!
Even if I were not Holo the
Wise Wolf, I could tell this!
From the description
they gave me,
I thought it
might be you...
I was hoping it
would not be, though.
It's a shame.
The one behind Medio Trading
is Earl Ehrendott, isn't it?
He is trading in wheat.
Pasloe's harvest.
And when you deal with wheat,
you can request payment
in any silver coin you prefer.
On top of that,
the privilege of eliminating
the wheat tariff
would be more than a blessing
to Medio Trading, the Earl,
and the Pasloe villagers.
You are the one
personally acquainted
with the merchants who
come specifically for wheat.
And more deals
are carried out
after the harvest festival
than any other time.
The village mayor is putting
you in charge
of the entire thing.
It's been you all along.
Well, I think we
should catch up later.
We don't have time now.
Don't be so cold.
After all, I barely got to see
you while I was in the village.
Lucky for you,
you found someone else
to occupy your time.
Give her to us, Lawrence.
We're going to turn her in
to the church and bid farewell
to the days of Holo the Wise
and Faithless Wolf.
Once we give her over to them,
we can shut down Milone Trading.
Additionally, if we can
use the King's privilege
to eliminate the tariff,
our wheat will produce
an enormous profit for us.
And it will be the same for the
merchants who handle our wheat.
Lawrence...
You chose to purchase
wheat from our village
while we were still
suffering under that tariff.
I want you to know I still
appreciate everything you did.
We would certainly give
you preferential treatment
if you continued to
do business with us.
Lawrence...
This is our opportunity...
We could open that shop...
You and I.
Think of the profit
we could make together.
Come with me.
With you?
Opening a shop has been
my dream for a long time.
Yes, I know.
But, what kind of
a merchant would I be
if I couldn't keep
a simple promise?
I'm not sure what I did to
deserve this turn of events...
But I just happened
to meet a strange wolf.
She wants to
return to the north.
And I made a contract
to accompany her.
I cannot break
that contract.
I gave my word.
Yes...
I did not want to
say goodbye to you.
Such is a merchant's
life, is it not?
You can kill the
man.
Just make sure you
capture the girl alive.
I'm not dead yet.
Holo!
Get the knife!
That is enough!
This might hurt a little.
Wha--?
You must bear it.
[PURSUER WALLA] Is she?
She's sucking his blood!
Oh my God!
No!
Stop hesitating,
she is simply a girl
who is possessed
by the Devil!
Look away...
I do not want you
to see me like this.
[HOLO growling]
All gods are the same.
Unfair.
You're cruel.
Every one of you.
Holo, please don't!
Wait, Holo!
Holo!
You... You tore all
of my good clothes!
Do you know how
much those cost?!
I don't care if
you're a god or not!
You'll have
to pay for them!
You may have earned
50 silver coins...
But that's not going to
be nearly enough at all!
Don't you try and
get out of it either!
I will follow you!
Holo...!
I will follow you all
the way to the north!
Holo!
It's nice to
see you're awake.
Your injury isn't causing
you too much pain, I hope?
Oh, no it's...
It's fine; thanks.
I would like to apologize
to you, Lawrence.
We miscalculated
the situation.
Oh, thank you,
but I don't think anyone
could've seen that coming.
We were very fortunate
all the commotion
occurred
underground, though.
If people had
witnessed her true form,
they would have probably thrown
our headquarters into the fire.
You saw her true form?
I did.
I received a report
from my employees
stating that they had found
you, but that a giant wolf
had refused to hand you over
to anyone other than myself.
So where is she then...
where did she go?
Once we
brought you here...
she left without telling
us where she was going.
Without even
saying goodbye.
Well, did
everything at least
go as planned
with the King?
We were successful,
of course,
and acquired the privilege
before Medio Trading
could ask for it.
You've got to
be kidding me.
We collected
307,112 coins and...
It seems the King
will devaluate the silver
coins rather dramatically.
He said he will give us cash
worth 350,000 silver coins
to be paid at
the time of delivery.
350,000?
And, according to the
contract we made with you,
your share is to be 5
percent of our profit...
That is correct,
isn't it?
Yeah, that
was the deal.
Please,
look this over.
What is this?
You will receive
120 silver coins,
which is 5 percent
of our profit.
That's all...?
I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
There's a delivery cost for
the coins we collected.
Then, the tariff that
comes along with it...
not to mention the handling
fee for the contract itself.
I never would
have believed
it would cost this much
just to handle a contract.
Blame his Government
Contractor for that.
Since they were also
giving us the privilege,
they were trying to
get back their losses
from purchasing
the silver coins...
We weren't expecting
this to happen...
It is an
unfortunate result.
I guess when it
comes to business
you can't be
prepared for everything.
However...
The unexpected
can be good as well.
Medio really
wanted that privilege.
Wait... What?
Remember, they were collecting
the same silver coins we were.
They knew the silver coins
would eventually be devalued,
so, in the end,
they were going to be
stuck with quite
a bit of debt...
I imagine they
were fairly determined
to turn a profit
no matter what.
So, when we
spoke with them,
they suggested
an amount
that we were willing
to accept on the spot.
It's 1,000 coins...
Yes, congratulations.
Would you like to receive
it in silver coins...
or if you'd like,
we could arrange
for some of it to
be given in product.
Pepper. Pepper.
It's light and
easy to carry.
And its price
is about to go up.
People buy more
meat in winter
so naturally they'll
buy more pepper as well.
What's so
funny about that?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You reminded me of
a play I read recently.
What're you
talking about?
It's actually a religious
play the church uses
to preach rules to
trading companies.
In it, the Devil appears
to a very wealthy merchant
and says to him, "Bring me
the most delicious human
in this land, or I shall
eat you instead."
Because he doesn't
wish to perish,
he brings young maids
and a fat male servant,
but the Devil
does not accept them.
He searches all over town
for delicious looking people,
until he finally finds a boy
who smells of honey and milk.
He presents this boy
to the Devil immediately,
but the
boy says to the Devil,
"The most delicious
human in the entire world
is right in
front of you.
Look, do you not see how
delicious this merchant must be?
He's seasoned his fat soul
with the spices
that made his fortune."
So, when you
asked for pepper,
I saw an image of you getting
fat and eaten by the Devil.
Well, the sooner my soul
can be seasoned
with spices, the better.
Yes. Definitely.
And I'll pray for luck.
Naturally, I want you to
know our company would like
to maintain the relationship
we've built with you.
Thank you.
I would as well.
Good, good,
I'm happy to hear it.
Lawrence, this is an invoice.
It has your name on it.
I don't remember purchasing
any of these products.
Where can I find
the unloading area?
Ah, well, go down the hallway
and take a right at the end.
Thank you!
Watch out!
Sorry!
A robe...
A silk waist sash...
A new pair of traveling shoes...
A tortoiseshell comb...
And last...
Plenty, of, apples!
[MILONE CLERK] Your total
is 140 silver coins.
Holo!
'Scuse me...!
I cannot have you coming
all the way the north to
collect, you understand.
Geez.
I shall not go home
'til I pay off my debt.
You've got a deal.
Spice and Wolf,
seems fitting enough to me.
Next episode...
Wolf and a Tail of Happiness.