- "RYOMOU, FORGIVE ME."
- ( doorbell rings )
- HMM?
- MOU-CHAN.
- SONSAKU AND SONKEN.
WHAT BRINGS THE TWO OF YOU
HERE TODAY?
- UM, I DID--
I WANTED TO INVITE
YOU AND MISS RYOFU
OUT TO DO SOMETHING FUN TODAY.
BIG SISTER HAKUFU AND I,
WE THOUGHT WE
COULD HAVE--
- HAVE EITHER OF YOU SEEN RYOFU?
- ( both gasp )
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
TO FU-CHIN?
- SHE'S GONE.
- SHE LEFT A NOTE?
- ARE YOU SURE SHE WOULDN'T MIND
THAT WE'RE READING THIS TOO?
"OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS,
I'VE HAD FUN WITH MY FRIENDS
AND CREATED WONDERFUL
NEW MEMORIES..."
- Housen: "...BUT SOMETHING
WAS STILL MISSING.
WITHOUT THE MEMORIES
OF THE PERSON I USED TO BE,
A PART OF ME FEELS EMPTY.
NOT KNOWING IS HURTING ME.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO LEAVE.
I NEED TO FIND MY PAST."
- WHOA!
- CAREFUL.
- ( sighs )
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- UH, YEAH.
- HE HAS A SACRED BEAD.
- HUH?
- WHERE DO YOU THINK FU-CHIN
MIGHT HAVE GONE?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- MOU-CHAN!
AREN'T YOU WORRIED
ABOUT FU-CHIN?
- IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
- RYOFU MADE THE DECISION
TO LEAVE ON HER OWN.
AND BESIDES, OUR WORRYING
WON'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
- I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT STILL I THINK WE--
- THEN STOP TALKING ABOUT
IT ALREADY. LET HER GO.
- BUT MO-CHAN--
- QUIT YOUR WHINING.
- ( whimpering )
- WHERE DID YOU GO
TO FIND YOURSELF, RYOFU?
- ( door opens )
- OH!
SON-- SONSAKU!
- LIAR.  I HEARD YOU.
- WHAT?  WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
- JUST NOW, I HEARD YOU SAY,
"WHERE DID YOU GO
TO FIND YOURSELF?" TO FU-CHIN.
- YOU-- YOU WERE EAVESDROPPING
ON ME WHILE I'M ON THE TOILET?
- ( laughs )
ADMIT IT--
YOU ARE WORRIED AFTER ALL.
- ARGH!
- AH!
- ( punching sounds )
- MOU-- MOU-CHAN.
SINCE IT'S OBVIOUS
YOU ARE WORRIED ABOUT FU-CHIN,
WE SHOULD GO OUT AND FIND HER.
- NO THANKS.
- LET'S GO.
- NO.
- COME ON, MO-CHAN.
- I TOLD YOU I'M NOT GOING.
- AND I SAY YES YOU ARE.
NOW GET UP!
- HYAH!
- AHH! MOU-CHAN,
YOU'RE BREAKING MY ARM!
STOP IT.  I GIVE.  I GIVE!
- I'M A FIGHTER?
- YES.
- I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND,
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE SEEM TO BE
PICKING FIGHTS WITH ME
BECAUSE OF
THIS "SACRED BEAD" THING.
HEY, ARE YOU A FIGHTER TOO?
YOU ARE.
SO WHAT'S BEING A FIGHTER
ALL ABOUT THEN?
- NO IDEA.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T REMEMBER.
I HAVE AMNESIA.
- HEY, YOU HAVE AMNESIA?
SO DO I!  I DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING EITHER.
THOUGH I WAS ABLE TO FIND OUT
MY NAME.
LUCKY FOR ME, ONE OF THOSE BOZOS
WHO PICKED A FIGHT WITH ME
KEPT YELLING IT AT
THE TOP OF HIS LUNGS.
- OH.
- I'M GENJYO KAKOUTON.
AND YOU ARE?
- I'M RYOFU.
- OUCH.  THAT REALLY HURTS.
MOU-CHAN WAS SERIOUSLY ANGRY
WITH ME THIS TIME.
STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE THREW US OUT.
- ( giggles )
- IT'S ALL FU-CHIN'S FAULT.
IF ONLY SHE WROTE
WHERE SHE WENT.
- I MIGHT KNOW.
- YOU HAVE AN IDEA
WHERE SHE MIGHT BE?
- BIG BROTHER KOUKIN
SAID SOMETHING
WHEN HE FIRST RECOGNIZED HER.
- I KNOW THAT UNIFORM.
IT'S RAKUYO.
- IT MIGHT NOT BE
THE BIGGEST CLUE,
BUT AT LEAST IT'S SOMETHING
WE HAVE TO GO ON.
IF NOTHING ELSE,
IT'S A PLACE TO START.
- THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
LET'S GO!
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE IS RAKUYO HIGH?
- UM, WELL--
- Kakouton: RAKUYO HIGH SCHOOL.
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS
WHERE YOU WENT TO SCHOOL?
- PRETTY SURE.
- CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- WHAT?
- DOES THE NAME MOTOKOU
MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
- MOTOKOU?  NO.
- I FIGURED.
- WAS HE A STUDENT
AT RAKUYO HIGH SCHOOL?
- HE WAS MY FRIEND.
I COULDN'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHAT MY OWN NAME WAS,
BUT I REMEMBERED HIS NAME--
MOTOKOU SOUSOU.
GUESS HE MUST'VE BEEN SOMEONE
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
- I ENVY YOU.
- HUH?
- I CAN'T REMEMBER
ANYONE IMPORTANT TO ME.
- SHOULD WE CALL BIG BROTHER
KOUKIN AND ASK HIM WHERE IT IS?
- OKAY.
- Ryomou:
I KNOW HOW TO GET THERE.
- HUH?
- SO YOU'LL HELP?!
THANK YOU, MOU-CHAN!
YOU'RE SO NICE--
- STOP!  YOU'VE BEEN
WAY TOO TOUCHY FEELY LATELY.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
- ( garbled protesting )
- CALM DOWN.
LET'S HEAD TO RAKUYO.
- ( both gasp )
- Ryomou: THE SCHOOL'S
FIGHTING FACTION FELL APART
AFTER ITS LEADER,
CHUEI TOUTAKU, DIED.
BY NOW, THE ENTIRE CAMPUS HAS
PROBABLY BEEN LONG ABANDONED.
- WOW.
THIS PLACE IS A WRECK.
HUH?  WAIT.
HOLD UP.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU USED TO GO TO SCHOOL HERE?
- I DON'T KNOW. THAT'S WHY
I WANT TO CHECK IT OUT.
- AH. THEN I'LL
KEEP YOU COMPANY.
- WHY?
- YOU AND I ARE BOTH FIGHTERS
WHO HAVE LOST OUR MEMORIES.
MAYBE THIS IS A COINCIDENCE,
MAYBE IT'S NOT. BUT I THINK
SOMETHING IN YOUR PAST
MIGHT HOLD THE KEY TO MY OWN.
- Girl: IT IS AS YOU PREDICTED.
SHE CAME TO US
OF HER OWN FREE WILL.
- I KNEW SHE WOULD COME.
OTHERWISE I WOULDN'T HAVE RISKED
LETTING MOU-CHAN SEE ME.
SHE ASKED ME A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
- BUT WHO IS THAT MAN
ACCOMPANYING HER?
- HIM?
I'LL HAVE KAKOUEN
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- Housen:
NOTHING FEELS FAMILIAR.
I'M NOT CERTAIN OF ANYTHING.
DID I REALLY GO TO SCHOOL HERE?
WHAT IF I'M NEVER ABLE
TO GET MY MEMORIES BACK?
- Saji: I KNOW WHERE YOUR
MEMORIES ARE HIDING.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHO AM I?  AFTER ALL
THAT'S PASSED BETWEEN US,
IT HURTS WHEN YOU ACT
LIKE I'M A STRANGER.
I KNOW EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW ABOUT YOU,
AND THEN SOME.
I KNOW WHAT MAKES YOU TICK,
HOW TO PUSH YOUR DEEPEST,
MOST SENSITIVE BUTTONS.
AND YOU KNOW ME TOO,
INSIDE AND OUT.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I KNOW YOU BECAUSE
YOU USED TO BE MY GIRLFRIEND.
- ( gasps )
- ( humming )
- WHAT'S THAT YOU'RE HUMMING?
- IT'S A POP SONG.
- YOU'RE INTO POP MUSIC THEN.
I'D NEVER GUESS THAT.
- HE'S NOT WEARING
A SACRED BEAD.
HEY, MAN!
WHAT'RE YOU, A FIGHTER?
- DOES IT MATTER?
- HOW DO I KNOW
YOU'RE TELLING THE TRUTH?
WAS SHE REALLY YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
- HA!
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH?
- SHUT UP.
- WELL, IF YOU
WON'T LISTEN TO ME,
THEN PERHAPS
YOU'LL BELIEVE HER.
SHE USED TO BE
ACQUAINTED WITH YOU.
ASK HER ANYTHING.
- YOU KNEW ME BEFORE?
TELL ME, WHO AM I?
- YOU'RE GENJYO KAKOUTON
FROM KYOSHO ACADEMY,
THAT'S WHO.
- KYOSHO ACADEMY?
WAS THAT MY SCHOOL?
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- YOU SAID
I USED TO BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
SO WE BROKE UP?
- YEAH. THOUGH WE WEREN'T
EXACTLY IN WHAT YOU'D CALL
A TYPICAL RELATIONSHIP.
EACH OF US HAD AN ULTERIOR
MOTIVE WHEN IT STARTED.
WE BOTH USED EACH OTHER
KNOWINGLY.
- USED EACH OTHER?
- IT MAY HAVE BEEN EXPLOITATIVE,
BUT I THINK WE BOTH STILL HAD
A LOT OF FUN ALONG THE WAY.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
LOOKS LIKE
YOU FORGOT EVERYTHING.
BUT NOT TO WORRY.
THAT ACTUALLY
SUITS MY PURPOSES A BIT BETTER.
AS LONG AS SHE'S WITH ME--
- SHE?
- MOU-CHAN DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT US?
- RYOMOU?
- SHE'S MY RESPONSIBILITY.
I'M GOING TO MAKE HER
INTO A REAL WOMAN.
- CAREFUL NOW.
- Kakouton! HEY!
JUST TELL ME
WHO THE HELL THIS WOMAN IS.
- MYOSAI KAKOUEN.
SHE'S YOUR FRIEND.
- SOMETHING DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
- KAKOUTON, COME WITH ME.
- STOP! DON'T TALK
LIKE YOU KNOW WHO I AM.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- YO, EYE-PATCH BOY.
YOU SHOULD DO AS KAKOUEN SAYS
AND RETURN WITH HER
TO KYOSHO ACADEMY.
MOUTOKU SOUSOU WILL BE THERE.
DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE HIM?
- WAIT.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
- HA!
- STOP!  BASTARD!
UH?  WHAT THE--
HEY, LET GO!
- YOU WILL COME TO KYOSHO.
- HEY! I TOLD YOU ALREADY,
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE WITH--
( grunts )
WELL, AT LEAST NOW I KNOW.
YOU GUYS
ARE NO FRIENDS OF MINE!
WHAT THE--
- IT'S UNFAIR TO USE A WEAPON
ON AN UNARMED PERSON.
IT'S UNFAIR TO USE A KNIFE
ON AN UNARMED PERSON!
- DO I KNOW YOU?
- ( sighs ) WHAT'RE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, TON-CHAN?
IT'S ME, HAKUFU.
WE USED TO PRACTICE FIGHTING
AND BASICS
AND DO A BUNCH OF OTHER STUPID
STUFF THAT FRIENDS DO TOGETHER.
DID YOU FORGET?
- STUPID?
HA! YOU WROTE YOUR NAME
ON YOUR SACRED BEAD.
HOW STUPID!
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
AND DON'T CALL ME STUPID.
- HMM.
"HA-KU-FU SON-SA-KU."
I REMEMBER!
YOU'RE HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- WHAT?  OF COURSE I AM.
WHY'RE YOU BEING SO FORMAL?
- SORRY.
I'VE FORGOTTEN ALMOST EVERY
SINGLE THING ABOUT MY LIFE.
EXCEPT THERE'S ONE THING
I DO REMEMBER.
- WHAT?
- THAT HAKUFU SONSAKU IS STUPID.
- HEY!  DON'T CALL ME STUPID.
I ESPECIALLY DON'T WANT YOU
CALLING ME STUPID.
I'M INSULTED.
I SHOULD STOP BEING YOUR FRIEND.
- YOU'RE MY FRIEND?
THAT MAKES SENSE.
I REMEMBER SOMETHING ELSE.
- YOU AND ME, WE'RE BOTH
ON THE SAME SIDE.
- MM-HMM!
- Hakufu: SONSAKU!
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
- MOU-CHAN, CHUBO.
- Saji: HOW NICE TO
SEE ALL OF YOU.
- HUH?
- SAJI?
- Sonken: LOOK, HE
HAS MISS RYOFU!
- COME BACK!
I HAVE QUESTIONS FOR YOU SAJI.
YOU CAN'T HIDE.
- MISS RYOMOU.
- ( grunts )
- TON-CHAN.
COME THIS WAY.
- BRING HER OVER HERE TO ME.
- ( both panting )
- DID WE FINALLY LOSE HER?
- HYAH!
- HOLD ON!
WOULD YOU MIND STOPPING?
IF I RUIN ANOTHER UNIFORM,
MY MAMA WILL KILL ME.
- OH NO, YOU DON'T!
( grunting )
- HYAH!
- OOH!
- LEAVE HER TO ME, TON-CHAN.
YOU GET OUTTA HERE AND--
- LIKE HELL I WILL!
- HUH?
- WHAT KIND OF A GUY
WOULD I BE
IF I KEEP ALLOWING A GIRL
TO SAVE MY ASS ALL THE TIME?
ROUND TWO.
- ( gasps )
RYOFU.
COME ON, WAKE UP.
- ( grunts )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHERE'S SAJI?
- WHO'S SAJI?
- HE'S THE GUY WHO BROUGHT
YOU HERE. DID HE HURT YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I CAME TO THIS PLACE
LOOKING FOR MY PAST,
AND SOMEHOW I ENDED UP HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
- YOU DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED?
- MMM.
I DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
- ( grunts )
- OH! HE'S TOAST.
- YIELD. DO AS I SAY.
I TOLD YOU ALREADY!
YOU ARE MY ENEMY.
AND I DON'T CARE
WHAT THAT SNOOTY BASTARD SAID--
THAT IF I WANTED TO
SEE MOUTOKU AGAIN,
I'D HAVE TO GO WITH YOU?
WELL YOU'RE NOT USING HIM
JUST TO GET AT ME!
DON'T EVEN TRY TO USE HIM
AS SORT OF BARGAINING CHIP
TO MAKE ME DO WHAT YOU WANT!
- TON-CHAN, NO!
THOSE TOOLS ARE
YOUR MOST PRECIOUS POSSESSIONS!
- HUH?
BASEBALL HAS THE GROUNDS.
JUDO HAS THE DOJO.
SO WHERE'S THE SACRED PLACE
FOR STREET FIGHTERS?
- WHAT?
ARE YOU GIVING ME A RIDDLE?
I'M VERY BAD AT THOSE THINGS
'CAUSE I'M KIND OF STUPID,
YA KNOW?
- THE STREET IS A VERY
SACRED PLACE FOR ALL OF US.
DO YOU THINK IT'S OKAY
TO JUST LEAVE
AFTER YOU'VE MESSED IT ALL UP?
( grunting )
I REMEMBER NOW.
THE MOST IMPORTANT RULE
OF BATTLE!
AND THAT RULE IS--
HYAH!
--BASICS!
KAKOUEN,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
MIXED UP WITH
THAT SNOOTY SON OF A BITCH?
BUT IF HE'S RIGHT,
AND MOUTOKU IS REALLY WAITING
AT KYOSHO ACADEMY,
THEN I WILL GO TO VISIT HIM.
BUT ON MY OWN TERMS,
WHEN I'M GOOD AND READY.
HUH?
THANKS TO YOU,
MY MIND IS CLEAR
AND I KNOW NOW WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
- HUH?
- OKAY.
FIRST, APPLY THE PUTTY.
MAKE SURE YOU GET IT
INTO ALL THE CRACKS.
NEXT STEP-- YOU GOTTA SMOOTH
ALL OF IT OUT WITH YOUR TROWEL.
THEN MAKE SURE
YOU SAND DOWN THE EXCESS AND...
FINISHED!
- YUP, TON-CHAN'S
STILL A COMPLETE MORON.
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
- HUH?
- LOOK AT WHAT I HAPPENED UPON.
- MOU-CHAN!  FU-CHIN!
( giggles )
- SEE YA.
- TON-CHAN.
YOU'RE LEAVING SO SOON?
- I NEED TO GET TO KYOSHO.
I'M SURE THE REST OF THE
ANSWERS I SEEK ARE ALL
WAITING FOR ME THERE.
( stomach growls )
- Sonken: SUN TZU TEACHES...
- HUH?
- ...MORNING IS KEEN,
AFTERNOON FLAGS,
AND EVENING FADES.
- WHAT?
- PEOPLE ARE FULL OF ENERGY WHEN
THEY WAKE UP IN THE MORNING,
THEN IN THE AFTERNOON
THEY TIRE,
AND IN THE EVENING
THEY SEEK REST
TO REPLENISH THEMSELVES.
WHY NOT SHARE A MEAL WITH US
BEFORE YOU HEAD OUT ON YOUR WAY?
- THAT WAS DELICIOUS.
THANKS.
- DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE MY MAMA?
- WHAT?
- BIG SISTER, WHAT WOULD HE
WANT TO SEE OUR MOTHER FOR?
- WHY WOULDN'T HE
WANT TO SEE HER?
HE IS HER BOYFRIEND, AFTER ALL.
- OH!  HUH?
MMM.
MOTHER HAS A BOYFRIEND?
- Goei: A-CHOO!
- ( objects rustling )
- OH, I DROPPED EVERYTHING.
- Koukin:
ARE YOU OKAY, AUNT GOEI?
YOU'RE NOT FEELING SICK,
ARE YOU?
- NO, I'M NOT SICK.
SOMEONE'S JUST TALKING
ABOUT ME BEHIND MY BACK AGAIN.
MAYBE IT'S THAT YOUNG MAN
I MET!
OR THAT MANAGER
OF THE DRUG STORE
BY THE STATION
WHO'S SO WONDERFULLY MANLY.
OH, I BET HE'S MADLY IN LOVE
WITH ME AND WANTS TO PROPOSE!
- YOU DON'T SAY.
- MMM!
YUMMY.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- DO YOU THINK THAT--
DOES FU-CHIN SEEM HAPPIER
THAN SHE DID BEFORE THIS?
- YOU ALSO NOTICED HER CHANGE?
- YOU GUYS.
WERE YOU TALKING ABOUT ME?
SO CUTE.
- ( theme music playing )
- Kakouton: SAY, SONSAKU,
YOUR MOM AND ME,
WE'RE NOT REALLY DATING
LIKE BOYFRIEND AND GIRLFRIEND,
ARE WE?
- Hakufu: OH, SURE YOU ARE.
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU TWO ARE SO IN LOVE.
MAMA IS EVEN CARRYING YOUR BABY.
- WHAT?!
SHE'S CARRYING MY--
YOU'RE LYING!
I DON'T REMEMBER DOING THAT.
IMPOSSIBLE!
I'M NOT EVEN INTO COUGARS.
- Sonken: PLEASE CALM DOWN.
AFTER ALL, SUN TZU SAID,
YOU SHOULD REAP WHAT YOU SOW
AND TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
- Hakufu:
HEY, HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND.
I DON'T THINK SUN TZU
EVER SAID THAT.