- YOU HAVE SOME SKILL.
IT'S A GREAT HONOR
FACING A FIGHTER LIKE YOU.
HOWEVER, DON'T THINK
FOR A SECOND I INTEND TO LOSE.
AAH!
- ( both gasping )
- Koukin:
AT THAT POINT IN TIME,
WE STILL LIVED
IN DAYS OF PEACE,
AND HADN'T
YET REALIZED ANYTHING.
US FIGHTERS
HAD INHERITED SPIRITS--
SPIRITS OF ANCIENT HEROES,
HAILING FROM THE THREE KINGDOMS,
CHINA'S AGE OF RIVAL WARLORDS.
- Goei: KOUKIN, DEAR.
- YEAH?
- YOUR BREAKFAST IS READY.
WOULD YOU BE A DARLING
AND GRAB MY IDIOT DAUGHTER?
I THINK SHE'S SOAKED IN THE TUB
LONG ENOUGH.
- LITTLE DID WE KNOW
THAT THE SPIRITS
IN OUR SACRED BEADS--
THESE HEROES--
WERE PREORDAINED TO ONCE AGAIN
DRAW US
INTO A BATTLE OF DESTINY.
- HEY!  YOU BASTARD!
- HUH?
HAKUFU!
HAKUFU,
WHAT'S WRONG NOW?
- ( panting )
- OH. ( giggles )
OH, KOUKIN.
GOOD MORNING.
- HURRY UP, HAKUFU.
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF GETTING UP EARLY
IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO TAKE FOREVER IN THE BATHROOM?
NOW THANKS TO YOUR EPISODE
IN THE TUB,
WE'RE RUNNING EVEN LATER
THAN USUAL.
- HEY, IT'S NOT MY FAULT
THAT GUY HAD THE NERVE
TO FEEL ME UP 100 TIMES
WHILE I WAS IN THERE.
- 100?  WHAT GUY?
- THE CENTIPEDE, OF COURSE.
EVEN I KNOW THOSE CREEPY
LITTLE GUYS HAVE 100 LEGS.
- 100 LEGS?
YOU KNOW THAT'S JUST A MYTH,
RIGHT?
- GOOD MORNING, MISS SONSAKU.
- I HOPE YOUR MORNING IS WELL,
LEADER.
- All:
GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING!
- Koukin: HAKUFU,
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND,
IS NOW NANYO ACADEMY'S LEADER.
- 9,998.
9,999...
- I'M IMPRESSED
YOU'VE KEPT THAT UP, GAKU-CHAN.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'M ONE OF NANYO'S BIG FOUR.
I CANNOT AFFORD
TO NEGLECT MY DAILY TRAINING.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME,
SONSAKU?
- OH, NOT REALLY,
THANKS!
IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M ONE OF THE BIG FOUR.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
WELL, SHUYU'S
RIGHT OVER THERE.
HMM?
- I WASN'T TALKING
ABOUT KOUKIN.
MOU-CHAN!
- ( gasps )
YOU CAN'T JUST SNEAK UP
BEHIND ME LIKE THAT.
- YOU SCARED ME.
UH, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOUR FACE IS ALL RED.
AH, I KNOW-- YOU WERE
JUST THINKING ABOUT SAJI.
- WHO, ME?
LIKE I'D CARE
ABOUT THAT BIG STUPID IDIOT.
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
I DON'T THINK I'VE SEEN SAJI
AROUND AT ALL LATELY.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
IT'S LIKE THAT IDIOT
DOESN'T EVEN CARE
ABOUT BEING
ONE OF THE BIG FOUR.
- DO YOU THINK SOMETHING
COULD HAVE HAPPENED TO HIM?
- PROBABLY JUST FOOLING AROUND
WITH SOME OTHER GIRL.
- OTHER GIRL?
- BY THE WAY, SHUYU,
ANY ACTIVITY FROM KYOSHO?
- NO.
APART FROM FROM THE FACT
THEIR LEADER,
SOUSOU MOUTOKU,
IS STILL MISSING,
THERE'S NOTHING STRANGE
TO REPORT.
- MOU-CHAN.
- IS THERE ANY NEWS ON SEITO?
THERE ISN'T REALLY
A LOT GOING ON THERE EITHER.
ALL I'VE HEARD
ARE A FEW RUMORS
SAYING THAT KAN'U UNCHO
WILL BE RETURNING SOON.
- HMM?
- I SEE.
SO KAN'U WENT OFF TO TRAIN
FOR A WHILE.  MAKES SENSE.
- YEAH.
- MOU-CHAN, MOU-CHAN, MOU-CHAN.
- SHE LEFT SEITO
WITH HER FRIENDS.
- I CAN'T SAY
THAT I'M NOT JEALOUS.
IT REALLY SHOWS
THAT RYUUBI GENTOKU
HAS GROWN QUITE NICELY
INTO BEING THEIR LEADER.
AND BY COMPARISON,
NANYO'S LEADER
IS NOTHING BUT A--
( grunts )
MOU-CHAN!
YOU'VE GOTTEN EVEN BIGGER,
HAVEN'T YOU?
JUST LOOK AT HOW THEY BOUNCE!
( laughs )
- NO, NOT THERE!
KNOCK IT OFF,
YOU STUPID PERVERT.
- AGH!  I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CALLED ME STUPID!
- SO WHAT IF I DID?
YOU ARE STUPID.
- AGH!
YOU SAID IT AGAIN.
WHOEVER SAYS "STUPID" FIRST
IS REALLY STUPID.
- SONSAKU, CAN YOU PLEASE
HAVE ENOUGH DIGNITY
TO BEHAVE MORE LIKE A LEADER?
- HUH?
- LEADERS HAVE A DUTY.
THEY MUST SET THEMSELVES APART,
BE AN IDEAL THEIR FIGHTERS
CAN ASPIRE TO.
- PERSPIRE TO?
- Both: ASPIRE!
- JUST BE AN EXAMPLE
FOR ONCE.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE, MOU-CHAN,
YOU HAVE A LOT MORE WORK
THAN ME.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- THINK ABOUT IT.
I ALWAYS WORK SO HARD
TRYING TO FIND YOU
ALL THOSE PART-TIME JOBS.
- AH!
OH, NO.
ARGH!
WHY, YOU!
- AH!  SORRY 'BOUT THAT.
- AND EVERY TIME,
YOU GOT FIRED, DIDN'T YOU?
- Y-YEAH, SO WHAT?
I DON'T EVEN GET WHY I HAVE
TO WORK IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- COME ON,
WE HAVE TO SAVE SOME MONEY
TO GO ON
THE OVERSEAS BATTLE TOUR.
- YOU MEAN YOU'RE REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT DOING THAT?
- OF COURSE I AM!
I EVEN WROTE IT
AS "MEANS BUSINESS"
AND PRONOUNCE IT
LIKE THE WORD "EARNEST."
SO, DON'T YOU GET FIRED
FROM THE NEXT JOB YOU GET.
- LOOK, I'M NOT CUT OUT
FOR THE SERVICE INDUSTRY, OKAY?
- IT'S AN IMPERIAL ORDER,
GOT IT?
- THERE- THERE AREN'T
ANY ORDERS LIKE THAT.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYWAY.
ONLY A LEADER IS ALLOWED
TO GIVE IMPERIAL ORDER.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DOES THAT MEAN I'M BEHAVING
MORE LIKE A LEADER?
- HUH?
TOLD YA!  THAT WAS EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- HOLD ON, NO!
- I'M THE LEADER.  GO!
- ( both sigh )
- CUT IT OUT.
- ( door opens )
- KAN'U, WELCOME BACK.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
- GE-- GENTOKU.
- CONGRATULATIONS
ON ALL YOUR TRAINING.
I MISSED YOU...
- ( panting )
- ...SO VERY MUCH.
- ( both giggling )
- GENTOKU.
- KAN'U.
KAN'U?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- NO. I WAS JUST THINKING THAT I
NEEDED TO PAY A VISIT TO
YOKOHAMA SO I CAN PRAY.
I STILL NEED TO REPORT
MY TRAINING AT KANTEIBYO.
GENTOKU,
WOULD YOU COME WITH ME?
- YES.
I'D BE HAPPY TO JOIN YOU.
AH, AND AS LONG
AS WE'RE DOWN THERE,
WE CAN GO TO CHINATOWN
FOR LUNCH.
DOWN THERE, WE CAN GO
TO CHINATOWN FOR LUNCH.
- ( gasping )
- CHINESE FOOD?
I WANT TO HAVE SOME TOO.
- KOUMEI,
IF YOU WANT CHINESE FOOD,
TOMORROW I'LL BUY SWEET 'N'
CHILI SHRIMP, OR WHATEVER.
- IF ALL OF US
ARE GOING TO CHINATOWN,
I WON'T REST UNTIL I'VE HAD
MY FILL OF CHINESE BUNS!
- CHINESE BUNS?
- OH, YOU MEAN YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY ARE, GENTOKU?
- YEAH.
- WELL THAT SETTLES IT, KAN'U.
GENTOKU HAS TO FIND
SOME CHINESE BUNS AND EAT THEM.
- Koumei: ME TOO.
I'VE NEVER HAD
THOSE BUNS BEFORE EITHER.
- Ryuubi: YOU TOO, KOUMEI?
IN THAT CASE,
WE ALL HAVE TO GO
EAT SOME CHINESE BUNS.
IT'S OKAY, RIGHT, KAN'U?
- IF-- IF YOU SAY SO,
GENTOKU.
- YAY.
WE ALL GET TO GO OUT TOGETHER.
I CAN'T WAIT!
- Koumei: I CAN'T WAIT EITHER.
- Ekitoku: SAME HERE!
- I AM GRATEFUL
TO HAVE RETURNED SAFELY.
PLEASE CONTINUE TO WATCH OVER
THE WELFARE OF SEITO ACADEMY.
- Ekitoku: EVERYTHING HERE
LOOKS SO FREAKIN' TASTY.
- OOH,
THIS LOOKS REALLY GOOD TOO.
- HEY, YOU THREE,
WE'RE AT A SACRED TEMPLE
RIGHT NOW.
- OH, KAN'U, ARE YOU DONE
WITH YOUR VISIT YET?
COME ON, HURRY UP
SO WE CAN GET SOME BUNS ALREADY!
- Ryuubi: LET'S GO.
- Sonsaku: WELCOME!
- MISS SONSAKU?
- RYU-CHAN?
AH!
- HAKUFU, JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?  HUH?
THE SEITO GIRLS.
- HEY, WHAT'RE THE TWO OF YOU
DOING IN CHINATOWN?
- Ryuubi: SO YOU'RE BOTH
WORKING HERE PART-TIME
TO HELP RAISE FUNDS
FOR YOUR CLUB?
- YEP. WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING
ON THE OVERSEAS BATTLE TOUR.
FACING OFF AGAINST FOREIGN
POWERHOUSES ACROSS
THE SEA IN BATTLE-- SO STOKED!
- THAT DOES SOUND
LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
KAN'U, DO YOU THINK
WE CAN TRY THAT TOO?
- I WON'T DENY
THAT IT DOES SOUND INTERESTING.
- Ryuubi: MISS SONSAKU.
- HUH?
- HERE.
IF YOU TAKE THE TIME
TO SIT DOWN
AND DEVOTE YOURSELF TO ENRICHING
YOUR MIND THROUGH READING,
YOU WON'T HAVE TO TRAVEL
ALL THE WAY OVERSEAS
TO ENJOY THE THRILL
OF A GOOD BATTLE.
- READING, HUH?
- MMM.
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
READING IS IMPORTANT.
- THANK YOU ALL FOR WAITING.
HAKUFU, THIS IS NO TIME
TO BE DAWDLING AROUND.
GET BACK TO WORK, OKAY?
- ROGER THAT, SIR.
WELL, TAKE YOUR TIME,
YOU GUYS.
- All: THANKS FOR THE FOOD!
- Ryuubi:
ARE THESE THE CHINESE BUNS?
- Ekitoku: YEP!
FEEL FREE TO DIG RIGHT IN.
- MMM!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, GENTOKU?
PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
- YES!
THEY'RE AMAZING.
- YOU SEE?
BE SURE TO THANK KAN'U
FOR LETTING US
VISIT THE SHRINE WITH HER.
- RIGHT.  THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BRINGING US, KAN'U.
- EKITOKU,
YOU'RE MY FAVORITE PERSON
IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
- HUH?
- GENTOKU,
I WANT TO HAVE SOME TOO.
- OH, KOUMEI,
YOU'RE SO SPOILED.
HERE.
OPEN UP AND SAY "AH."
- AHH.
- HOW DOES IT TASTE, KOUMEI?
- IT'S SO GOOD.
- KAN'U,
NOW OPEN WIDE FOR ME, OKAY?
- AH.
- Ekitoku: KAN'U?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- IT-- IT'S NOTHING AT ALL.
( clears throat )
GEN-- GENTOKU.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
KAN'U?
- IT'S MY CHOPSTICKS.
I DON'T THINK THEY'LL REACH
THE BUNS FROM HERE.
SO WOULD YOU--
WOULD YOU MIND
FEEDING ONE TO ME?
- SURE!
- OH, WAIT,
I CAN GET ONE FOR YOU.
- NO.
- HERE YOU GO, KAN'U.
- EKITOKU, YOU'RE THE WORST
PERSON IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
- HUH?
- ( crashing )
- AH!
HA!
WAIT UP, WAIT UP, WAIT UP!
- THAT'S IT.
THAT JUST MIGHT DO IT.
- HUH?
OH, KAN'U, WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO WITH YOU?
- Sonsaku:
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
- MMM!
OH, THAT'S SO GOOD.
- HAKUFU SONSAKU,
WHY ARE YOU EVEN HERE?
- I JUST FINISHED MY SHIFT
FOR THE DAY, SO I THOUGHT
IT'D BE FUN TO HAVE A SEAT
AND JOIN YOU GUYS.
- SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I TRIED TO STOP HER.
- WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU,
MISS SONSAKU.
AFTER ALL,
WHEN IT COMES TO MEALS,
THE MORE THE MERRIER, RIGHT?
- YOU'RE TOTALLY RIGHT,
RYU-CHAN.
IT'S LIKE OUR BRAINS
ARE THE SAME.
HIT ME AGAIN.
AHH!
- ALL RIGHT, IF YOU INSIST.
- ARGH!
- WH-- WHAT?
- Ryuubi: IT'S SO COLD.
KAN'U, WHY DID YOU POUND
THE TABLE LIKE THA--
AH-CHOO!
- I'M SORRY, GENTOKU.
- RYU-CHAN!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, MISS SONSAKU?
- YOU HAVE TO HURRY UP
AND CHANGE YOUR CLOTHES
OR YOU'LL CATCH A COLD.
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE TICKLING ME.
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF HER.
- HUH?
- YOU HEARD ME.
STOP BUTTING IN,
YOU PATHETIC NANYO.
- PATHETIC NANYO?
NANYO AND SEITO HAVE
NOTHING TO DO WITH
WHAT'S GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
- THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG.
SEITO HAS ITS OWN WAY
OF DOING THINGS AROUND HERE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHY ARE YOU SO ANGRY
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- NO MORE TALK!
- OH!
- HUH?
- ALL RIGHT,
NOW YOU'VE DONE IT!
IF I GO HOME WITH MY UNIFORM
ALL TORN UP LIKE THIS,
MY MOM'S GONNA KILL ME.
DAMN YOU!
- WATCH OUT!
- HUH?
HUH?
- I'M SORRY,
YOU AREN'T HURT, ARE YOU?
- SHIRYU!
- SHIRYU CHOU'UN.
- ( rumbling )
HUH?
- ( all screaming )
- WELL, KAN'U, I BELIEVE
YOU CAN TAKE IT FROM HERE.
NOW THAT I'M PRESENT,
WE CAN MAKE SURE OUR LEADER
IS PROTECTED.
- Koukin:
OUR FIGHTERS' SPIRITS,
WHO HAD FALLEN
INTO THE GRAND DREAM,
HAVE YET TO FIND PEACE
AND STILL WISH TO HAVE US SEEK
OUT BATTLES ON THEIR BEHALF.
- ( both grunting )
- SUN TZU TEACHES...
- All: HUH?
- ..."THE ART OF WAR IS OF
VITAL IMPORTANCE TO THE STATE,
A MATTER OF LIFE AND DEATH,
AND IT MUST BE STUDIED."
- HUH?
- SUN TZU.
HE WROTE THAT
IN HIS FOREWORD.
- A FIGHTER?
- Sonken: YOUNG LADIES
SHOULD NOT BE SO BRAZEN
TO BE EXPOSING THEIR SKIN
OR THEIR UNDERWEAR
IN THE PRESENCE OF OTHERS.
- HUH?
- I HATE TO TROUBLE YOU, BUT MAY
I PLEASE ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- OH.  OF COURSE
YOU MOST CERTAINLY MAY.
- I HAVE COME HERE
WITH THE UNDERSTANDING
THAT MY SISTER
MAY BE HERE AS WELL.
- YOUR SISTER?
- SHE IS KNOWN
AS THE "LITTLE CONQUEROR",
AND IS THE CURRENT LEADER
OF NANYO ACADEMY.
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE MENTIONED EARLIER
THAT MY NAME IS CHUUBO SONKEN.
- Both: CHUUBO?
- Both: SONKEN?
- WELL NOW, THAT'S THE NAME
OF THE BLUE-EYED CHILD OF KOTO,
SIBLING
OF THE LITTLE CONQUEROR.
- WAIT A SECOND, HAKUFU.
SHE'S YOUR--
- HUH?
- HAKUFU?
MIGHT YOU BE THE HAKUFU SONSAKU
I'VE LOOKED FOR?
- THAT I JUST MIGHT BE.
WHAT?
- IT IS MY PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
ACTUALLY,
I'M YOUR YOUNGER SISTER.
MY NAME IS CHUUBO SONKEN.
- OH, RIGHT.
I WASN'T SURE
WHO YOU MEANT BY SISTER,
BUT YOU PROBABLY DON'T MEAN ME.
NO WAY!
I HAVE A YOUNGER SISTER?!
- ( drawer closes )
- Kada: THERE, ALL DONE.
HERE, PUT THIS ON.
THERE'S A CHARM
WOVEN INTO THE BACK OF THE GAUZE
THAT'LL HELP KEEP THAT DRAGON
OF YOURS UNDER CONTROL.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
DR. KADA.
- EVER SINCE THE FIGHT
WITH SOUSOU,
HAKUFU SONSAKU'S DRAGON
AND GENTOKU'S RYUUBI'S DRAGON
HAVE BOTH BEEN DORMANT.
RYOMOU, IT SEEMS YOURS,
AT LEAST, STILL REMAINS.
- I WILL GO TO MY GRAVE WITH
THE DRAGON DWELLING WITHIN ME.
THAT IS THE DESTINY
I AM FOREVER CURSED WITH.
AS LONG AS I REMAIN LIVING,
THE DRAGON
WILL ALSO CONTINUE ON LIVING.
- ( cellphone chiming )
- ( door opens )
- SAJI.
WHY DID YOU GO OFF AND DISAPPEAR
WITHOUT SAYING ANYTHING TO ME?
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO GO OFF
AND DO EVERYTHING ON YOUR OWN?
WAIT, HOLD ON.
SAJI!
AH!
MY BODY WON'T LISTEN TO ME.
IT CAN'T BE THE DRAGON.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sonsaku:
HEY, SO IS IT REALLY TRUE
THAT YOU'RE MY YOUNGER SISTER?
- YES, I CAN HONESTLY SAY
I AM THE YOUNGER SISTER
OF HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- HMM, WHAT THEN?
DOES THAT MEAN DAD
USED FOOL AROUND WITH
A BUNCH OF STRANGE WOMEN?
HANG ON A SECOND.
I CAN'T SEE HIM
DOING THAT AT ALL.
YOU DON'T MEAN MAMA
FOUND SOME CRAZY HOTTIE
SHE KEPT FROM PAPA, DO YOU?
TCH, THAT OVER-THE-HILL CROCK!
- UM, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
OVER-THE-HILL CROCK?