- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Goei: YES, I UNDERSTAND.
THANK YOU FOR GOING OUT OF
YOUR WAY TO HELP ME WITH THIS.
I APPRECIATE IT.
WHAT?  HOW'S HAKUFU?
OH, SHE'S DOING FINE.
THANKS AGAIN.
YOU TAKE CARE TOO.
HUH?
YOU'RE UP EARLY
THIS MORNING.
IS ANYTHING THE MATTER,
HAKUFU?
- I'VE JUST HAD
THIS BAD FEELING
ABOUT MOU-CHAN EVER SINCE
LAST NIGHT'S STORM.
I COULDN'T GET TO SLEEP.
I JUST TOSSED AND TURNED.
- NOW THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
WORRYING ABOUT
ONE OF HER FIGHTERS
LIKE A PROPER LEADER SHOULD.
ON THAT FRONT, I HAVE
SOME GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
- GOOD NEWS?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
- I JUST LEARNED THAT
RYOMOU WENT TO THE MOUNTAINS
TO GET A LITTLE TRAINING
AND DO SOME SELF-REFLECTION.
WHAT'S MORE, I HEARD SHE'LL
BE COMING BACK VERY SOON.
- HUH?
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT MOU-CHAN?
- I HAVE A FRIEND
WHO LIVES ON THE MOUNTAIN
WHERE SHE WENT TO
BRUSH UP ON HER TECHNIQUE.
BUT THAT'S NOT IMPORTANT NOW.
PUT YOUR MIND TO REST
AND GET READY FOR SCHOOL
ON THE DOUBLE.
- AYE-AYE, CAPTAIN.
THANK YOU, MOM!
MORNING BATH,
HERE I COME.
- ( chuckles )
THAT GIRL SURE DOES
LOVE THE WATER.
OH, NO.  I FORGOT.
- ( grunts )
BYE-BYE.
GERONIMO!
( screams )
OW.
- Chuubo:
I'M SORRY, BIG SISTER.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
CHUUBO.
AUNT GOEI ASKED YOU
TO DRAIN THE TUB TO CLEAN IT.
BESIDES, THERE'S A WORD
FOR PEOPLE WHO DON'T BOTHER
TO CHECK THE POOL
OR TUB FOR WATER
BEFORE JUMPING INTO IT.
"STUPID."
- HEY, THAT WAS MEAN.
YOU'RE ALWAYS CALLING ME
THAT LATELY.
AND IT'S LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
GIVING ME THE COLD SHOULDER
EVER SINCE CHUUBO CAME.
( gasps )
OHH.
ARE YOU TWO--?
- ( gasps )
- NO, THERE'S NOTHING.
- BIG SISTER, IS THAT
WHO I THINK IT IS?
LOOK UP THERE.
- OH?
( giggles )
FU-CHIN!
- WHERE DID SHE COME FROM?
WASN'T SHE SUPPOSED TO BE
OFF WITH RYOMOU SOMEWHERE?
- BIG BROTHER KOUKIN?
- WHAT IS IT, CHUUBO?
TELL ME.
- IT'S RYOFU.
SOMETHING'S SCARING ME.
( sighs )
- FU-CHIN!  COME ON.
WAIT UP.
- I HOPE YOU'RE WRONG.
- ( sighs )
OHH?
- LOOKING FOR SOMEONE?
- ( laughs )
I FOUND YOU!
- ( gasps )
- ( giggles )
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY
TO SEE YOU.
- YOU ARE HAPPY?
- MM-HMM.
I WAS SO WORRIED
ABOUT MOU-CHAN
THAT I COULDN'T
SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
BUT NOW THAT I FOUND YOU,
I FEEL MUCH BETTER.
- YOU FEEL BETTER
BECAUSE OF ME?
- OF COURSE I DO.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I CAN
TALK TO ABOUT THESE THINGS.
FU-CHIN, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE MOU-CHAN IS?
- I DON'T KNOW WHERE
RYOMOU IS NOW.
DON'T YOU HAVE A BETTER
IDEA WHERE SHE MIGHT BE?
WHERE DOES SHE GO AND SPEND
MOST OF HER TIME?
- UMM... WHERE DOES SHE GO?
I KNOW, THE DOCTOR!
DR. KADA KNOWS EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW ABOUT MOU-CHAN.
COME ON.  LET'S GO.
AW, MAN!
OF ALL THE TIMES FOR THE DOCTOR
TO BE OUT OF THE CLINIC.
( sighs )
- DON'T GET SO DOWN.
I'M SURE SHE'LL SHOW UP
AGAIN AT SOME POINT.
- RIGHT.
WE JUST HAVE TO GO LOOK
FOR HER SOMEWHERE ELSE.
HEY, MOU-CHAN.
- ( screams, crying )
- ( screams )
I'M SO SORRY!
LET'S TRY HERE.
MOU-CHAN LOVES
FIGHTING GAMES.
SHE TOTALLY KICKS ASS
AT COMBOS.
COME ON, COME ON.
WHY WON'T YOU DIE ALREADY?
TAKE THAT, AND THIS.
POWER MOVE!
GO GO GO GO,
GOTCHA!
ALL RIGHT!
WAIT, WHAT AM I DOING?
SHE'S NOT IN THE GAME.
SHE ISN'T ANYWHERE.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO,
FU-CHIN?
- RYOMOU'S A BIG GIRL.
I'M SURE SHE CAN
TAKE CARE OF HERSELF.
WHY ARE YOU SO WORRIED?
WHAT'S SHE TO YOU?
- HUH?
WHAT DOES MOU-CHAN
MEAN TO ME?
HMM.
UM, THAT'S HARD TO
PUT INTO WORDS.
THE FIRST TIME WE MET,
SHE CHOKED ME
AND KNOCKED ME
UNCONSCIOUS.
SHE GETS ANGRY AT ALMOST
EVERYTHING I SAY.
AND UNLIKE ME,
SHE'S REALLY SMART AND SERIOUS.
THOUGH SHE'S NOT SO GOOD
AT KEEPING PART-TIME JOBS.
SOMETIMES I CATCH HER
ALL BY HERSELF
JUST STARING WITH THIS
LONELY LOOK ON HER FACE.
I GET REALLY WORRIED
WHEN SHE DOES THAT.
BUT MOU-CHAN DOESN'T
TALK MUCH AT ALL,
LET ALONE WHEN SOMETHING'S
TROUBLING HER.
I KNOW I'M TOO DUMB TO HELP,
BUT IF THERE WAS
SOMETHING I COULD DO
TO CHEER HER UP
EVEN A LITTLE,
I'D BE HAPPY.
- IF I MAY ASK,
DO YOU THINK YOU LOVE RYOMOU?
- MM.  ABSOLUTELY.
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
- Ryofu: YOU LOVE HER
BECAUSE SHE'S YOUR FRIEND?
- SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
MOU-CHAN IS, FU-CHIN IS,
KOUKIN IS, CHUUBO IS,
RYU-CHAN IS, KAN-CHAN IS,
AND TON-CHAN IS.
THEY'RE ALL MY BEST FRIENDS,
AND I LOVE THEM.
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
I MIGHT KNOW WHERE SHE IS.
- HUH?
REALLY, YOU DO?
- Ryofu: YES.
I'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
- Hakufu:
NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
MAMA DID SAY SOMETHING ABOUT
MOU-CHAN GOING TO THE MOUNTAINS.
SO SHE'S STILL UP THERE
DOING HER MEDITATION
AND TRAINING STUFF.
THAT'S WHERE SHE IS,
FU-CHIN, RIGHT?
THIS IS WHERE
SHE CAME TO TRAIN?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
RYOMOU IS THIS WAY.
- OHH?
( gasps )
WAIT!
I'M COMING WITH YOU, FU-CHIN.
HUH?  OH.
FU-CHIN!
WHOA, THIS PLACE IS A MESS.
FU-CHIN?
OH.
( gasps )
MOU-CHAN!
WHAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
WHO DID THIS TO MOU-CHAN?
WHY WOULD ANYONE
WANT TO HURT HER?
- YOU ARE SO STUPID.
YOU AND RYOMOU BOTH.
- HUH?
- YOU STILL HAVEN'T FIGURED
IT OUT YET, HAVE YOU?
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS TRUE FRIENDSHIP.
IT'S ALL A BIG LIE.
PEOPLE JUST USE EACH OTHER.
IT'S USELESS PRETENSE,
AND I INTEND TO DESTROY IT.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T NORMALLY
TALK LIKE THAT.
( gasps )
- MISS RYOFU AND I WENT
INTO THE HAUNTED HOUSE,
AND THEN SHE...
I WAS LYING DOWN
AND SHE TOUCHED ME.
- Rikuson: BUT REGARDLESS,
SHE'S NOT HERSELF.
SOMEONE IS MANIPULATING HER.
- SHE'S POSSESSED TOO?
BY WHO?
- CAN YOU TELL US ANYTHING,
RIKUSON?
IT'S GENPOU SAJI.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT FU-CHIN.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN FU-CHIN
THIS WHOLE TIME.
- CORRECT.
( chuckles )
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN WITH
HOUSEN RYOFU AT ALL TODAY.
- ( gasps )
HUH?
YOU'RE THAT GIRL I HELPED.
WHY DID YOU RUN AWAY
FROM MY HOUSE?
I WAS WORRIED.
- YOU MADE ME SO HAPPY.
NO ONE HAS EVER BEEN
NICE TO ME BEFORE.
- ( gasps )
- AND YOU WERE WARM
IN A WAY THAT I'VE NEVER FELT.
AND I WANT THAT
ALL FOR MYSELF.
- WHAT?  WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- RYOMOU CANNOT HAVE YOU.
YOU'RE MINE, AND I WANT
WHAT'S INSIDE YOU.
NO ONE ELSE CAN HAVE YOU
EXCEPT ME.
- I DON'T GET IT.
NONE OF THIS IS
MAKING ANY SENSE.
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
I... CAN'T MOVE.
- FROM NOW ON,
I AM THE ONLY PERSON
THAT EXISTS FOR YOU.
I, AND I ALONE.
- ( shivers )
- Saji: FORGIVE ME, RYOFU.
ALL OF THIS HAPPENED
BECAUSE OF ME.
BECAUSE I LOVED YOU.
AND BECAUSE SHE COULD
SEE MY FEELINGS FOR YOU
BRANDED ON MY SOUL.
WHEN YOU REAPPEARED
IN THIS WORLD,
I COULD HARDLY
BELIEVE MY EYES,
AND SO I MADE
MY DEAL WITH THE DEVIL.
NOW FIGHTERS EVERYWHERE
ARE SUFFERING THE WRATH
OF THE NECROMANCER,
THE REAL GENPOU SAJI.
HER CURSE IS INFECTING THEM.
HER VENGEANCE
AND HATRED SPREADS.
PERHAPS I SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED TO SHISONZUI
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
ALL I CAN DO NOW
IS WAIT FOR THAT DESTINY
TO PLAY ITSELF OUT.
DAMN IT.
ANY WAY THIS ENDS,
SOMEONE WON'T
COME OUT OF IT ALIVE.
- ( cellphone ringing )
- IT'S NO USE.
SHE'S NOT ANSWERING HER PHONE.
- WHERE COULD BIG SISTER
HAKUFU HAVE GONE?
SHE ISN'T ANYWHERE.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING ABOUT IT.
I REALLY HOPE
THAT I'M WRONG.
- OH.
- HUH?
( gasps )
HAKUFU!
- BIG SISTER,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- WHY HAVEN'T YOU
CALLED US ALL DAY?
WE WERE WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
- OH, YOU WERE WORRIED?
SO SORRY YOU
TROUBLED YOURSELVES.
BUT IF I'M SO WEAK THAT INFERIOR
FIGHTERS WORRY ABOUT ME,
I GUESS MY DAYS AS
THE LITTLE CONQUEROR
ARE AT AN END.
- WHAT?  WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, HAKUFU?
- BIG BROTHER,
THAT'S NOT OUR BIG SISTER.
I KNOW IT.
- BEING A LEADER
IS NOTHING BUT DOING
A WHOLE BUNCH OF CRAP
TO PROTECT MY
WEAK UNDERLINGS.
I'VE GROWN TIRED OF IT.
WHY DON'T YOU FIND
SOMEONE ELSE WHO GIVES A SHIT?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE
THAT BONEHEADED GORILLA,
GAKU-CHAN,
TAKE OVER FOR ME?
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- ( sighs )
SUN TZU TEACHES US
"ATTACK THE ENEMY
BEFORE HE CAN ATTACK YOU."
- HUH?
- THE ART OF WAR IS TO
ATTACK AN ENEMY'S PLAN
BEFORE HE CAN
PUT IT INTO ACTION
AND USE IT AGAINST YOU.
IT WOULD APPEAR
THAT IN THIS BATTLE
THE ENEMY'S STRATEGY IS TO
LOOK LIKE BIG SISTER HAKUFU
IN ORDER TO CONFUSE US.
- HAKUFU IS NOT REALLY HAKUFU.
- OH?  SO...
YOU FOUND ME OUT.
YOU CAN TELL.
I SEE.
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU HAS BEEN
POSSESSED AND TAKEN OVER
JUST LIKE MISS RYUUBI WAS.
BY GENPOU SAJI!
- TRY AND STOP ME THEN,
KOUKIN.
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting )
- ( grunting continues )
- HAKUFU,
RESIST THE MIND CONTROL.
- KOUKIN...
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
IT'S ME, KOUKIN.
YOUR HAKUFU.
- ( gasps )
- MY KOUKIN.
- BE CAREFUL,
BIG BROTHER!
- ( gasps )
WERE YOU PLANNING
TO KISS ME
AND GET CONTROL
OVER ME TOO?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
TOO BAD.
IF YOU HADN'T STOPPED ME,
KOUKIN,
YOU WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
THE CHANCE TO TASTE HER.
- HOW DARE YOU.
IS THIS FUN FOR YOU?
WHAT KIND OF
TWISTED PERSON ARE YOU
THAT YOU'RE ENJOYING THIS?
- TWISTED, AM I?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M A HORRIBLE FREAK SHOW.
WHEN I MANIPULATE
HAPPY AND FUN-LOVING PEOPLE
INTO STATES OF
DISCORD AND MISERY,
I DO RATHER ENJOY IT.
- WHERE IS IT?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH
THE REAL HAKUFU'S SOUL?!
- HMM.
ALL THOSE WHO ARE
UNDER MY CONTROL
SLEEP IN A DARK WORLD
FROM WHICH THERE IS NO WAKING.
YOU CAN CALL OUT TO HER
UNTIL YOU LOSE YOUR VOICE.
BUT HAKUFU SONSAKU'S SOUL
WILL NEVER BE COMING BACK.
- BIG BROTHER,
PLEASE LISTEN.
GENPOU SAJI WANTS TO
TEAR US APART.
YOU MUST SHOW HER
HOW STRONG OUR FRIENDSHIP IS.
- ( grunting )
- HA!
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( laughs )
( gasps )
- CHUUBO!
GET AWAY FROM HERE.
YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR HER.
- NO, BIG BROTHER.
I AM NOT GOING
TO RUN AWAY.
I MAY NOT HAVE
A FIGHTER'S STRENGTH
LIKE YOURS OR
BIG SISTER HAKUFU'S,
BUT I AM STILL
YOUR YOUNGER SISTER.
I AM CHUUBO SONKEN,
AND I WILL PROTECT
MY BIG BROTHER OR DIE.
- ( laughing )
THAT'S BIG TALK FOR SUCH
A PATHETIC LITTLE GIRL.
AS YOU WISH.
- ( screams )
( gasps )
- THERE.
THAT WASN'T EVEN CLOSE TO
THE FULL EXTENT OF MY POWER,
AND YET YOU STILL
COULDN'T GET NEAR ME.
YOU'RE FAR TOO WEAK
TO PROTECT ANYONE.
- IF I AM WEAK,
THEN YOU ARE EVEN WEAKER.
- ( gasps )
- GENPOU SAJI,
YOURS IS A PITIFUL SOUL.
THE ONLY WAY YOU KNOW HOW TO
COMMUNICATE WITH OTHER PEOPLE
IS BY HURTING THEM.
- ( grunts )
- YOU FEAR PEOPLE.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT YOUR FEAR,
THAT MADE THE PEOPLE
AROUND YOU AFRAID TOO.
- ( gasps )
SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
HA!
( screams )
( panting )
I SUFFERED!
EVERYBODY TREATED ME
LIKE AN OUTCAST.
THEY SHUNNED
AND AVOIDED ME
AND TURNED ME INTO
A PARIAH.
THAT'S WHY
I MADE THEM SUFFER.
THEY HAD TO SUFFER
LIKE I DID.
YOU'RE AFRAID OF ME TOO,
AREN'T YOU?
GO!  HURRY UP AND RUN AWAY
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
- NO, CHUUBO.
STAY DOWN.
- I WON'T LEAVE.
I'LL FIGHT.
I'LL FIGHT
TO SAVE MY BIG BROTHER.
AND I'LL FIGHT
FOR THE SAKE OF MY
BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
- WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I WON'T RUN AWAY.
SHE NEEDS ME.
- ( gasps )
STAY AWAY!
- ( screams )
BIG SISTER HAKUFU...
CAN YOU SEE ME,
SISTER?
CAN YOU HEAR MY VOICE?
PLEASE WAKE UP.
- ( gasps )
- WE NEED OUR HAKUFU BACK
WHO IS HAPPY AND KIND.
PLEASE, BIG SISTER.
COME BACK TO ME!
- ( gasps )
- ( crying )
- ( sobbing )
( sighs )
- Koukin: HAKUFU!
- WAKE UP.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
- CHUUBO.
- ( chuckling )
- YOU'RE BACK.
THANK GOODNESS.
YOU HAD US SCARED.
- WELCOME BACK,
BIG SISTER.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
- I HEARD YOUR VOICE,
CHUUBO.
I HEARD YOU
CALLING OUT TO ME.
BUT SHE...
HAD CONTROL OF ME.
THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD DO.
I FELT SO HELPLESS.
HER SOUL IN ME
WAS FRIGHTENING.
AND SHE WAS SO
TERRIBLY SAD.
I-- I'M SORRY.
LOOK AT YOU TWO.
YOU'RE BOTH BRUISED
AND BEATEN UP.
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF ME.
( sobbing )
- HEY, CALM DOWN.
THERE'S NO NEED FOR
THE WATER WORKS.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY NOW.
- ( sobbing continues )
- Koukin: LOOK AT YOU.
YOUR FACE IS ALL DIRTY.
HOLD STILL.
- THANKS FOR THE HELP,
KOUKIN.
( gasps )
KOUKIN!  OH, NO,
YOU'RE BLEEDING!
- ( gasps, grunts )
- FIRST, LET'S WIPE IT OFF AND
CLEAN THE WOUND A LITTLE BIT.
NEXT, WE NEED SOMETHING
TO USE AS A BANDAGE.
THERE.  ALL DONE.
- OH.
THAT'S BETTER.
THANK YOU.
CHUUBO?
- HUH?
- I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
- HONESTLY,
EVER SINCE
THE FIRST DAY YOU CAME
I DIDN'T REALLY BELIEVE
THAT YOU AND HAKUFU
WERE TRUE SISTERS
OR EVEN RELATED.
BUT AFTER SEEING
WHAT YOU DID,
I'M SORRY
I EVER DOUBTED YOU.
- UH?
- BRINGING HAKUFU
BACK LIKE THAT,
I CAN SEE THERE WAS A BOND.
YOU TWO REALLY ARE SISTERS.
- ( gasps )
- Hakufu: KOUKIN,
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
WITH CHUUBO?
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU,
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN,
I HAVE A SECRET,
AND I KNEW ONE DAY
I WOULD HAVE TO TELL
WHAT THE TRUTH IS.
I'M NOT WHO
YOU THINK I AM.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chuubo:
BIG SISTER HAKUFU,
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN,
WHEN I SUDDENLY
DROPPED INTO YOUR LIVES
AND ANNOUNCED THAT I WAS
YOUR YOUNGER SISTER,
YOU WELCOMED ME AND TREATED ME
WITH KINDNESS AND AFFECTION.
I WAS SO GRATEFUL
AND HAPPY.
I LOVED BEING
PART OF YOUR FAMILY.
THAT'S WHY...
I CANNOT CONTINUE
TO LIE TO YOU ANY LONGER.
I'VE BEEN HIDING SOMETHING
FROM YOU THIS WHOLE TIME.
THE TRUTH IS...