- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HOW'D YOU FIGURE OUT
THAT I WAS UP HERE?
- YOU DISAPPEARED WITHOUT
A WORD TO ANYONE.
NOT THAT I HAVEN'T DONE
A BIT OF THAT TOO.
AT FIRST, I HAD NO IDEA
WHERE YOU COULD HAVE GONE.
BUT THEN SAJI SUGGESTED
YOU MIGHT HAVE JUST GONE
TO GET AWAY FROM IT ALL.
- I KNEW IT.
- HUH?
- YOU DID SPEAK TO HIM.
THAT DAY AT RAKUYO
YOU MET SAJI.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED?
- MM.
I DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
- YOU LIED TO ME THAT DAY.
AND THEN AT
THE AMUSEMENT PARK...
I SAW YOU LEAVE WITH HIM.
YOU AND SAJI WERE IN CAHOOTS
FROM THE BEGINNING,
WEREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE BEEN LYING
THE WHOLE TIME.
- NO, IT WASN'T
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
IT'S TRUE THAT SAJI AND I
HAVE BEEN MEETING EACH OTHER
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
HE ASKED ME TO LIE A LITTLE,
BUT KEEPING IT A SECRET WAS
MY CHOICE.
I SWEAR.
I JUST DIDN'T WANNA HURT YOU.
- YOU DIDN'T WANNA HURT ME?
- I FIGURED OUT YOU HAVE
FEELINGS FOR SAJI.
AND HE TOLD ME YOU TWO
USED TO DATE.
IT WAS SO HARD FOR YOU
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT HIM,
BECAUSE YOU WERE AFRAID HE AND I
MIGHT GET BACK TOGETHER.
SAJI ASKED ME
NOT TO TELL YOU
THAT HE AND I HAD BEEN
MEETING UP.
HE DIDN'T WANT YOU TO GET
THE WRONG IDEA.
I PROMISE.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
EVEN IF MY MEMORY DOES
FULLY RETURN,
WE WON'T GO BACK
TO BEING A COUPLE.
HE SAID YOU'RE
VERY SPECIAL TO HIM.
AND I CAN TELL HE'LL NEVER HAVE
EYES FOR ANYONE ELSE BUT YOU.
- YEAH, THEN WHY IS
THAT BASTARD
ALWAYS RUNNING OFF
AND DISAPPEARING ON ME?
- SAJI IS WORKING TO UNRAVEL THE
MYSTERY OF HOW I'M STILL ALIVE
AND WHY I CAN'T REMEMBER.
HE SAYS HE CAN'T SEE YOU
UNTIL IT'S SOLVED.
SAJI THOUGHT THAT SAFER.
- BASTARD.
HE COULD HAVE
AT LEAST CALLED ME.
- ( giggles )
- WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING ABOUT?
- ISN'T THAT A TYPICAL GUY,
THOUGH?
SINCE THEY CAN'T JUST
PICK UP THE PHONE.
MEN SUCK AT COMMUNICATING.
BUT A GUY'S FLAWS DON'T MATTER
WHEN YOU'RE IN LOVE, DO THEY?
- UH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
- DON'T DENY IT.
SAJI REALLY CARES
FOR YOU TOO.
HE JUST DOESN'T SAY IT BECAUSE
HE'S NOT THAT KIND OF GUY.
I TOLD HIM NOT TO WASTE
HIS TIME FIGURING THINGS OUT.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
MY PAST ANYMORE.
- BUT YOUR MEMORIES--
- AREN'T IMPORTANT.
THE PAST IS THE PAST.
WHAT MATTERS IS
WHAT'S HERE AND NOW.
EVER SINCE I MET YOU,
THE TIME WE'VE SPENT TOGETHER
AS FRIENDS
HAS MEANT SO MUCH TO ME.
- FRIENDS?
- WHEN I WENT BACK
TO RAKUYO ACADEMY
AND SAW THE RUINS
IT HAD BECOME,
IT MADE ME REALIZE SOMETHING.
THAT PLACE WAS DARK AND COLD.
I WAS AFRAID THERE.
BUT WHEN I'M WITH YOU...
I FEEL WARM AND ACCEPTED,
LIKE THE DARKNESS IN MY PAST
NO LONGER HOLDS ME PRISONER,
AND I AM SET FREE.
THAT'S WHY...
- WHY WHAT?
- THE LAST THING
I WOULD EVER WANT IS TO COME
BETWEEN YOU AND SAJI.
AND IF I'M DOING THAT
JUST BY BEING HERE,
THEN I THINK I KNOW
WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
I LOVE YOU, RYOMOU.
AND I CAN'T BEAR
AT THE THOUGHT OF YOU HATING ME
ANYMORE THAN YOU ALREADY DO.
THAT'S WHY I'M GOING TO LEAVE.
AND YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
SEE ME AGAIN.
GOOD-BYE, MY FRIEND.
- WAIT!
I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO.
- DOES THAT MEAN
YOU TRUST ME AGAIN?!
OH!
( giggles )
- WAIT.  NO.  STOP.
- YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
I PROMISE
I'LL NEVER HIDE ANYTHING
FROM YOU AGAIN.
- ( giggles )
- Koukin:
IT WAS MISS RYOFU'S DOING?
- UH-HUH.
THAT'S WHAT RYUU-CHAN SAID.
- ( Ryuubi sobbing )
- Hakufu:
IT'LL BE OKAY, RYUU-CHAN.
PLEASE STOP CRYING.
DON'T WORRY.
THEIR WOUNDS AREN'T
LIFE-THREATENING.
- BUT--
- CALM DOWN.
HOW DID IT START?
- THE OTHER DAY,
MISS RYOFU INVITED
KAN'U AND ME TO GO
TO THE AMUSEMENT PARK.
MISS RYOFU AND I
WENT INTO THE HAUNTED HOUSE.
AND THEN SHE--
- AND THEN SHE WHAT?
- ( sobbing )
IT'S TOO HORRIBLE!
- DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I WASN'T THERE.
- I WAS LYING DOWN
AND SHE TOUCHED ME.
SOMETHING HAPPENED.
AND THEN SHE TOOK OVER.
AND ALL OF THIS IS
ALL MY FAULT!
( screams )
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
SHE WAS POSSESSED.
( gasps )
- WELL, I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER.
- ( gasps )
- HUH?  ARE YOU OKAY?
UH, YEAH, I'M FINE.
BUT WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET GOING.
- ( gasps )
CHUBO WAS DEFINITELY
ACTING STRANGELY
WHEN WE LAST SAW RYOFU.
DID SHE SENSE SOMETHING?
WHAT HAD HER SO SCARED?
- KOUKIN!
LET'S GO FIND FUU-CHIN!
- YES, BUT--
- DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME.
- All: HUH?
- Hakufu: RIKU-CHAN.
- Sonken:
MR. GAKUSHU, WHO IS THAT?
- HAKUGEN RIKUSON,
OUR ACADEMY'S STRATEGIST.
- HOUSEN RYOFU LEFT
RYOMOU'S PLACE A WHILE AGO.
SHE'S NOT EVEN IN TOWN.
BUT REGARDLESS,
SHE'S NOT HERSELF.
SOMEONE IS MANIPULATING HER.
- SHE'S POSSESSED TOO?
BY WHO?
- CAN YOU TELL US ANYTHING,
RIKUSON?
- IT'S GENPOU SAJI.
- HE'S DOING THIS?!
BUT WHY?!
- THE PERSON YOU KNOW
AS SAJI IS SAJI,
BUT HE'S ALSO NOT SAJI.
- HUH?
- Gakushu: THE GUY'S REAL
NAME IS SHISHI OUIN.
GENPOU SAJI WAS AN ALIAS
USED TO GET CLOSE TO
AND DEFEAT TOUTAKU.
- UH, I'M SORRY.
COULD YOU TRY PUTTING THAT
A DIFFERENT WAY?
'CAUSE I REALLY DIDN'T GET IT.
- THERE ARE TWO PEOPLE
NAMED GENPOU SAJI.
THERE'S THE ONE WE KNOW
AND THE OTHER WE DON'T.
IS THAT RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- ( distant siren blaring )
- Shisonzui: YOUNG MASTER.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- DON'T PUT THAT ON.
- SHISONZUI.
- IT'S TOO SOON TO WEAR
THAT SACRED BEAD.
DON'T RETURN TO BEING OUIN
JUST YET.
- BUT BOTH TOUTAKU AND RYOFU
OF RAKUYO ACADEMY ARE DEAD.
WHAT REASON IS THERE
TO CONTINUE LIVING MY LIFE
AS MY ASSUMED IDENTITY?
- DESTINY.
AFTER SHISHI OUIN OF
THE THREE KINGDOMS
DEFEATED HIS ENEMY TOUTAKU,
HE FELL VICTIM TO
A HORRIBLE FATE.
TRAITORS FROM WITHIN
HIS OWN COMMAND
ROSE UP AND KILLED HIM.
- Past Ouin: I AM OUIN!
- THAT PRECISELY WHY
I MUST RETURN
TO BEING SHISHI OUIN.
I MUST ACCOMPLISH
WHAT HE COULD NOT.
LIVE WHERE HE DIED.
- AND YOU CAN.
BUT NOT YET.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU ASSUMED
THE GUISE OF GENPOU SAJI,
YOU TOOK ON MORE THAN
JUST A NAME.
- MEANING WHAT?
- GENPOU SAJI HAD HIS OWN PART
TO PLAY IN THAT ERA.
HE FORETOLD SOUSOU'S DEATH,
THEN CONJURED AN
ARMY OF CORPSES.
- Past Saji:
WHEN CLAY MICE
CHASE GOLDEN TIGERS...
GUAN YU WILL LIVE NO MORE.
- ( screams, groans )
- ARE YOU SAYING THAT BEFORE
I CAN BE OUIN AGAIN,
I MUST FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO RAISE THE DEAD?
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
ONE DAY, THE REAL REINCARNATION
OF GENPOU SAJI
WILL INHERIT THE SACRED BEAD
AND WITH IT HIS FATE.
HE WILL COME TO KANTO.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
YOU MUST SEEK OUT
THIS MAGICIAN...
AND DESTROY HIM
OR SUFFER HIS DESTINY.
- DAMN IT!
K.O.'d AGAIN?
- WELL WELL WELL...
THE MIGHTY MOU-CHAN, INVINCIBLE
MASTER OF JOINT LOCKS,
GETS HER ASS
HANDED TO HER AGAIN.
- HEY, LAY OFF.
I'M JUST NOT IN THE ZONE TODAY.
I CAN BEAT THIS ONE.
- YEAH, SURE YOU CAN.
COME ON,
LET'S DO SOMETHING ELSE.
THIS LOOKS FUN.
HOW ABOUT SOME PICTURES?
- UH... NO.
I COULDN'T.
IT'S JUST TOO EMBARRASSING.
- YOU THINK IT'S SILLY?
- NO.
THAT'S NOT IT.
- OKAY, WE'LL DO SOMETHING ELSE.
CHANGE YOUR MIND?
COME ON, YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
WHY SO SERIOUS?
GIVE US A SMILE.
- STOP THAT!
HUH?  OH!
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- HEY!  WHEN DID I TELL YOU
IT WAS ALL RIGHT
TO STICK THIS
TO MY CELLPHONE?!
- AHH, YOU REALLY
DON'T LIKE IT?
- UH, WELL, NOBODY SAID
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- OKAY, I'LL PEEL IT OFF THEN.
- LEAVE IT!
IT'S FINE.
ANYHOW...
TODAY WAS NICE.
- HMM?
I DIDN'T QUITE CATCH THAT.
MIND SAYING IT ONE MORE TIME?
- JERK!  SHUT UP!
FINE!
I HAD FUN TODAY, ALL RIGHT?
BYE, SAJI!
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- LATER, MOU-CHAN.
- I FOUND YOU.
- HERE AT LAST.
GENPOU SAJI.
MOUTOKU SOUSOU IS GONE.
SO WHAT REASON DO YOU HAVE
TO MATERIALIZE HERE NOW?
- SHIMEI RYOMOU.
I WANT THE DRAGON THAT IS
LYING DORMANT INSIDE OF HER.
- ( exhales )
WHAT DO YOU WANT
WITH HER DRAGON?
- LOOK AT ME.
- I HAD NEVER SEEN
SUCH SAD EYES.
LONELINESS, DESPAIR,
RESENTMENT.
THOSE PITIABLE EYES THAT NEVER
EVEN GLIMPSED ANYTHING ELSE.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS?
I'M NOT GOING TO HELP YOU.
- OH, BUT YOU ARE GOING TO
HELP ME ACHIEVE MY DESIRES.
I AM CERTAIN OF IT.
- OH, REALLY?
SCREW YOU,
YOU HACK FORTUNE TELLER.
YOUR CRYSTAL BALL IS WRONG.
- I CAN RETURN SOMETHING
THAT YOU LOST,
A PART OF YOUR PAST
THAT WAS QUITE DEAR TO YOU.
- A PART OF MY PAST?
- THIS CAN'T... BE POSSIBLE.
HOUSEN RYOFU.
IS THIS REAL?
CAN YOU ACTUALLY BRING
A PERSON BACK TO LIFE?
RYOFU!
IT'S ME!
IT'S SAJI!
I'M RIGHT HERE.
- I WAS ABLE TO RESTORE HER,
BUT SHE IS STILL NOT WHOLE...
YET.
HER MEMORIES DID NOT
RETURN WITH HER.
THAT WILL REQUIRE
A BIT MORE TIME.
- HEY!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( both grunting )
- HUH!
- HAS HER MEMORY BEEN RESTORED?
- NOT COMPLETELY.
MUCH IS STILL MISSING.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY IS SHE FIGHTING?
- RYOFU IS A FIGHTER.
HE INSTINCTS SENSED
ANOTHER NEARBY
AND TOOK CONTROL OF HER.
- LIKE A REFLEX?
RYOFU, PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
- A FIGHTER'S INSTINCT IS
FRIGHTENINGLY POWERFUL.
FOR MOST, THE INSTINCT IS
FIGHT OR FLIGHT,
BUT SHE HAS NO CHOICE
EXCEPT TO FIGHT
UNTIL SHE GETS
HER MEMORY BACK,
OR THE BATTLES KILL HER.
- THEN I'LL FIND HER MEMORY.
- HOW WILL YOU DO THAT?
- BY USING RYOMOU.
- SHIMEI RYOMOU?
- RYOFU ONCE ENTRUSTED MOU-CHAN
WITH HER DEEPEST SECRET.
JUST HER.
WITHOUT HER MEMORIES,
RYOFU IS LITTLE MORE
THAN AN EMPTY SHELL.
RYOMOU WOULD NEVER JUST
LEAVE HER LIKE THIS.
- AND YOU THINK SHE CAN
UNLOCK RYOFU'S PAST?
- YES.
AT LEAST IT'S POSSIBLE.
RYOFU AND RYOMOU...
ARE BOTH FIGHTERS.
UNFORTUNATELY...
RYOFU'S MEMORIES
DIDN'T SEEM TO BE COMING BACK.
I TRIED AGAIN.
I TOOK A DANGEROUS RISK
AND WENT TO SEE HER.
I EVEN TOLD HER OUTRIGHT
THAT WE HAD BEEN LOVERS ONCE.
BUT IT WAS USELESS.
TO RYOFU, THE MEMORIES OF
HER PAST LIFE AS A FIGHTER
WERE THE BARS OF A CAGE
THAT HAD IMPRISONED HER.
AND DEEP DOWN,
ALL HER SOUL HAD EVER WANTED
WAS TO BE FREE.
- ( children playing )
- ( girl giggling )
- HEY!
WHAT'S SO FUNNY, FREAK SHOW?
- ( laughs ) I BET SHE WAS ABOUT
TO EAT THAT STUPID BUTTERFLY.
- SHE HAS TO EAT BUGS
'CAUSE SHE'S CREEPY.
- ( boys laughing )
- ( gasps )
- GO ON, EAT IT.
- ( boys laughing )
- NOT HUNGRY?
BUT I CAUGHT IT
JUST FOR YOU.
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
IF YOU DON'T WANT IT...
( grunts )
- ( cries )
- ( boys laughing )
- Girl #1: ISN'T THAT THE FREAK
WITH ALL THOSE WEIRD POWERS?
- Girl #2: I HEAR THAT WEIRDO
MADE BAD THINGS
HAPPEN TO AN OLDER KID.
- ( grunts )
- IT-- IT'S HERE.
IT'S LOOKING AT US.
- LEAVE US ALONE.
- A MONSTER!  LET'S GET IT.
- WAIT, DON'T DO IT.
- THAT HURT.
- Boy #1: GO AWAY!
- Boy #2:
STOP BREATHING OUR AIR!
- Boy #3: YOU'RE DISGUSTING!
- Boy #1:
YOU MAKE ME SICK!
- Boy #3: NICE SHOT!
- Boy #2: BEAT IT ALREADY!
SCRAM!
WHA-- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
AAH!
- Boy #1: STOP IT!
- ( blows landing )
- Boy #3: MY ARM!
IT'S MOVING BY ITSELF!
- Girl #1:
MY BODY WON'T LET ME RUN AWAY!
- ( children screaming, crying )
- Girl #3:
STOP IT!  PLEASE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- ( gasping )
OUIN.
DON'T LEAVE ME BY MYSELF.
STAY BY MY SIDE, OUIN.
PROMISE YOU'LL HELP ME
GET WHAT I WANT.
- OKAY.
- ( crying )
- AND THAT'S HER.
THE REAL GENPOU SAJI,
THE NECROMANCER.
- SO, YOU'RE SAYING THAT
THE REAL SAJI
FIRST POSSESSED FUU-CHIN,
THEN USED HER TO PUT A SPELL
ON RYUU-CHAN,
SO SHE COULD GO BACK
TO SATO ACADEMY
AND MAKE EVERYONE THERE FIGHT?
- YEP, IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU FINALLY GOT IT.
- AHEM.
I UNDERSTAND.
THAT MEANS THE REAL BAD GUY IS
THAT WITCH GIRL SAJI, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- I'M GONNA GO THERE!
- UM, BIG SISTER?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING TO GO?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
TO SEE SAJI,
THE NECROPHILIAC.
SHE CAN'T BE ALLOWED
TO CONTINUE.
SHE MUST BE STOPPED.
- Rikuson: DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE TO FIND HER?
- BUT RIKU-CHAN,
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
- OF COURSE I DON'T.
I'M NOT PSYCHIC.
- Hakufu: WHY NOT?
- Rikuson: HEY.
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD
IT WAS TO GET EVEN
THIS MUCH INFORMATION?
- CHUBO.
- ( rain falling )
- HUH?
IT'S RAINING.
- ( door opens )
- RYOFU?
- Ryofu: EVEN IF MY MEMORY
DOES FULLY RETURN,
WE WON'T GO BACK
TO BEING A COUPLE.
HE SAID YOU'RE VERY SPECIAL
TO HIM.
AND I CAN TELL HE'LL NEVER
HAVE EYES FOR ANYONE ELSE,
BUT YOU.
THE PAST IS THE PAST.
WHAT MATTERS IS
WHAT'S HERE AND NOW.
EVER SINCE I MET YOU,
THE TIME WE'VE SPENT TOGETHER
AS FRIENDS
HAS MEANT SO MUCH TO ME.
DOES THAT MEAN
YOU TRUST ME AGAIN?!
( giggles )
- ( gasps )
SAJI.
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
LIAR!
( grunts, shouts )
- RAGE.
THAT IS THE SOURCE
OF THE DRAGON'S POWER.
- RYOFU, YOU HAVE
DOUBLE-CROSSED AND DECEIVED ME.
BUT I REMEMBER
WHAT YOU TOLD ME ONCE
EVEN IF YOU DO NOT.
- THE SACRED BEADS
LOCK US INTO A HISTORY
WE MUST REPEAT.
BUT I FOUGHT AGAINST IT.
AND THOUGH IT COST ME DEARLY,
I SUCCEEDED.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I CHANGED MY FATE.
MY DEATH IS MY CHOICE.
- I, TOO...
CAN ALTER MY DESTINY.
IT'S MY CHOICE!
AND I CHOOSE...
TO KILL YOU!
AAH!
- HOW DARE YOU?
YOU DISGUST ME, RYOMOU.
- ( groans )
( crying )
( screaming )
- MOU-CHAN?
- ( thunder rumbles )
- ( continues crying )
- SHIMEI RYOMOU...
YOUR FATE WILL NEVER BE
YOUR OWN CHOICE.
THAT IS YOUR DESTINY
BECAUSE OF WHO YOU ARE.
YOU ARE THE FIGHTER
WITH THE DRAGON.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- MISS RIKUSON,
PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM CHUBO SONKEN.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE SONSAKU
HAS A LITTLE SISTER LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE COURTEOUS
AND POLITE.
WHILE SONSAKU, ON THE OTHER
HAND, IS LAZY, STUPID, SELFISH--
BASICALLY AN ALL-AROUND
TERRIBLE LEADER.
- Hakufu: WHAT DID
YOU SAY?! HEY, MISSY!
WHICH ONE OF US IS
THE MAIN CHARACTER HERE?
- Chubo: BIG SISTER, I THINK
MISS RIKUSON IS JUST UPSET
THAT SHE HASN'T SHOWN UP
UNTIL THIS LATE IN THE SERIES.