- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( water trickling )
- AHH.
THAT WAS A NICE BATH.
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
- EKITOKU.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE NOT LATE
FOR PRACTICE TOMORROW MORNING.
- CRAP, I FORGOT.  I'D BETTER
HURRY UP AND GET TO SLEEP
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU LATER.
- YES, I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW MORNING.
- Gentoku: EKITOKU.
- HUH?
WHAT'S UP, GENTOKU?
WHAT, DID YOU HAVE A BAD DREAM
AND WET YOURSELF IN BED?
- ( chuckles ) DON'T BE SILLY.
OF COURSE I DIDN'T.
- HUH?  HUH?
- HAS ANYONE TOLD YOU HOW NICE
YOU SMELL AFTER A BATH?
- HEY, GENTOKU,
QUIT FOOLING AROUND ALREADY.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
ARGH!
HANG ON.  WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I DON'T KNOW WHEN YOU STARTED
GETTING INTO THIS SORT OF THING,
BUT CUT IT OUT.
- ( chuckles )
- Gentoku:
HUH?  EKITOKU'S MISSING?
- RIGHT.  I HAVEN'T SEEN HER
SINCE LAST NIGHT,
WHICH MEANS SHE'S MISSED
BOTH PRACTICE AND CLASSES.
- IT COULD BE NOTHING.
MAYBE SHE HAD AN UPSET STOMACH
AND IS RESTING IN HER ROOM.
- I'VE LOOKED.
BUT WHEN I GOT THERE,
THERE WAS NO SIGN OF HER.
- LEADER, LOOKS LIKE THE BUS
IS GONNA BE HERE REALLY SOON.
- OKAY.
- GENTOKU,
WHERE ARE YOU PLANNING
ON GOING AT THIS HOUR?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"AT THIS HOUR"?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S LATE.
WE ONLY JUST FINISHED CLASS
FOR THE DAY, SO I THOUGHT
IT'D BE FUN TO GO TO THE CITY
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
( giggles )
- GENTOKU, AREN'T YOU EVEN
THE LEAST BIT WORRIED
THAT EKITOKU'S GONE MISSING?
- DON'T BE SUCH A WORRYWART.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD.
- DON'T YOU REALIZE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE LEADER
OF SEITO ACADEMY?
- YES, YES, OF COURSE
I REALIZE THAT.
KAN'U, YOU NEED TO LEARN
TO STOP WORRYING SO MUCH
ABOUT EVERYONE ELSE, AND TRY TO
HAVE SOME FUN FOR A CHANGE.
READY?
- I CAN'T WAIT.
SAY, YOU HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO CHECK OUT THE NEW SHOP,
RIGHT?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
WHAT KIND IS IT?
- ( snoring )
- MR. KOUCHUU.
MR. KOUCHUU.
- THAT VOICE--
IT SOUNDS LIKE OUR LEADER.
- MM.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN SENSE
MY PRESENCE.
SO STRANGE THINGS
DO HAPPEN.
- WHAT IS IT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- HAVE YOU SEEN KOUCHUU?
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
HE HAD A CHANCE TO SWEEP UP
THE COURTYARD THIS MORNING.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- WELL, ACTUALLY NO ONE'S SEEN
EKITOKU AROUND EITHER.
- EKITOKU TOO?
- AND--
- AND WHAT?
- GENTOKU SEEMS DIFFERENT
SINCE YESTERDAY.
- YOU MUST HAVE FAITH
IN HER.
SUSPICION CAN ONLY
MAKE ONE BLIND.
BUT IF YOU HOLD ONTO FAITH,
YOU CAN BE MADE TO SEE AGAIN.
- YOU ARE GENTOKU RYUUBI'S
SUBORDINATE.
IF YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
IN YOUR OWN LEADER,
WHO ELSE
CAN YOU BELIEVE IN?
- RIGHT.
I MUST HAVE FAITH.
- ( laughing )
OH, WHY DON'T YOU JUST FORGET
ABOUT THE READING ASSIGNMENT?
WE SHOULD JUST GO OUT
AND HAVE FUN.
AFTER ALL,
WE'RE ONLY IN HIGH SCHOOL.
SO WE SHOULDN'T BE
WASTING OUR YOUTH.
IF WE KEEP STICKING AROUND
THE MOUNTAINS LIKE THIS,
WE'LL TURN INTO OLD HAGS
BEFORE WE EVEN REALIZE IT.
OKAY THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
OH, LOOK, IT'S YOU.
- G-- GENTOKU,
WHERE DO YOU PLAN ON GOING
SO LATE IN THE EVENING?
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
JUST WHERE DO YOU PLAN ON GOING
WHEN IT'S SO LATE
IN THE EVENING?
- HUH?  I--
I'M OUT HERE GUARDING YOU.
- YOU HAVE TOO MUCH
FREE TIME.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A BIT STIFLING
HAVING YOU BREATHE DOWN MY NECK
ALL THE TIME?
- EKITOKU AND KOUCHUU HAVE BOTH
DISAPPEARED ALREADY.
WHO KNOWS WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN
TO YOU NEXT?
- DON'T BE SO SILLY, KAN'U.
TAKE A LOOK.
EKITOKU AND MR. KOUCHUU
ARE RIGHT OVER THERE.
- EKITOKU, KOUCHUU,
WHERE HAVE YOU TWO BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
- KAN'U, YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
STOP BEING SO NEEDY
ALL THE TIME.  IF YOU KEEP
ACTING LIKE A STALKER,
GENTOKU WILL END UP
HATING YOU.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( laughs )
I'M JUST FOOLING AROUND.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE YOU REALLY GENTOKU?
- ( giggles )
- WAIT!
- DON'T THINK I'LL LET YOU
GET PAST ME.
- WAIT, GENTOKU.
GENTOKU!
- WHAT IS IT, GENTOKU?
- ( chuckles )
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE, LEADER?
- YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
- HUH?
- BASHOKU.
- GO TO NANYO.
- NANYO?  BUT MISS KOUMEI--
- GO.  TELL THEIR LEADER
HAKUFU SONSAKU
ABOUT EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED.
- MISS KOUMEI.
- KAN'U!
JUST TURN AROUND
AND FIGHT.
IT'S NO FUN IF YOU'RE
RUNNING AWAY THE WHOLE TIME.
- SOMETHING'S
DEFINITELY WRONG.
EKITOKU AND KOUCHUU
WOULD NEVER ATTACK ME.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT,
BUT I CAN'T LET THIS
SENSELESS BATTLE DRAG ON.
- KAN'U, OVER HERE.
- CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT
IN THE WORLD IS HAPPENING
TO SEITO ACADEMY?
- DO YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
- YES.
SHIRYU, NOT YOU TOO.
- OF COURSE
SHE'S WITH US.
DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF
INTO THINKING
THAT WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
AT SEITO THAT HATE YOU.
- ( Ryuubi giggles )
EVERYONE'S ON THE SAME PAGE.
- Kan'u: GENTOKU.
- EVERYONE EXCEPT YOU, KAN'U.
- ( clock chiming )
- Hakufu: HUH?
- ( mews )
- YOU'RE TELLING ME
MOU-CHAN IS ABSENT AGAIN?
- YES, AND IT LOOKS LIKE
HER CELLPHONE IS OFF TOO.
- OH, DARN IT.
AND I JUST FOUND
A PART-TIME JOB
THAT'D BE PERFECT FOR HER TOO.
- WHAT'S WRONG
WITH HER?
IS MISS RYOMOU
SICK OR SOMETHING?
- HUH?
I'M GONNA CHECK ON HER.
- WHAT ABOUT ALL YOUR
AFTERNOON CLASSES?
- I'M FAILING ANYWAY,
SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
- HAKUFU.
- HEY, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
- IS-- IS THIS
NANYO ACADEMY?
- YES, IT IS.
- I HAVE A MESSAGE
FOR THE LEADER--
HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- HUH?
- Hakufu: I'M GOING
TO SEITO ACADEMY.
- AND I'M COMING WITH YOU.
- I'M COMING TOO.
- NO, KOUKIN, I NEED YOU
TO FIND MOU-CHAN INSTEAD.
WHILE IT'S TRUE I AM
WORRIED ABOUT RYUU-CHAN,
I'M JUST AS CONCERNED
ABOUT MOU-CHAN'S SAFETY.
- HAKUFU.
I UNDERSTAND.
- BIG BROTHER KOUKIN,
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO GO WITH YOU
AND HELP FIND HER.
- RIGHT.
- ARE YOU SHIMEI RYOMOU?
- YES.
- THEN I HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU.
PLEASE COME WITH ME.
- Koukin: WHAT?
SHE HASN'T COME BACK?
- NOPE.  SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO THINK WHERE RYOMOU
COULD HAVE GONE.
- AND ABOUT HOW LONG
HAS SHE BEEN AWAY?
- WELL, I DON'T REALLY
REMEMBER.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH, YEAH, I'M FINE, BUT WE
SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING.
- HUH?  HANG ON.
WHAT'S WRONG, CHUBO?
CAN YOU LET US KNOW
WHEN RYOMOU GETS BACK?
- YEAH, SURE THING.
- SO WHAT WAS
THE PROBLEM, CHUBO?
ARE YOU FEELING SICK
OR SOMETHING?
- UH, OH, NO.  SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IT'S NOTHING.
- THAT GIRL...
- IT CAN'T BE.
- EVERYTHING OKAY?
SO WERE YOU FINALLY ABLE
TO FIND SHIMEI RYOMOU?
- CHOURYUU HAKKE CHOUSHIKI.
KYUUHOSOUSHU.
WE'LL STOP HERE
FOR NOW.
GO TO THE HOT SPRING NEARBY
AND CLEAN YOURSELF UP.
- MASTER CHOUSHOU,
I CAN KEEP GOING.
- MAYBE, BUT THE DARK CLOUDS
IN YOUR HEART
WILL NOT CLEAR SO EASILY.
RIGHT NOW I'M AFRAID
YOUR SPIRIT IS TOO OVERCOME
WITH DOUBT.
- YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY SURE SHE HAS
NO IDEA WHERE SHE WENT?
OKAY, WELL, THEN WHAT ABOUT
FUU-CHIN?
ALL RIGHT, KOUKIN.
I'LL SEE YOU.
- I TAKE IT
SHE WASN'T THERE?
- HUH-UH.
- THOUGHT SO.
- HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
- IT LOOKS LIKE
A BATTLE WAS FOUGHT.
- YEAH, BUT WHY
WAS IT FOUGHT?
- HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- Gakushu: UNCHO KAN'U?
- WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- ( Ryuubi chuckles )
LOOKS LIKE WE FOUND YOU, KAN'U.
- WHAT HAPPENED, RYUU-CHAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WAY UP THERE?
- HAKUFU SONSAKU?
- WHAT?
- WELL, LOOK
WHO WE HAVE HERE.
IF IT ISN'T THE GORILLA OF NANYO
AND ITS BOOBY-BOMBED LEADER.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?  WHY ARE
ALL OF YOUR CLOTHES TORN UP?
- WELL, MAYBE THIS'S WHY.
- SONSAKU.
- SHE DIDN'T EVEN REGRET
ATTACKING HIM.
SO DID THEY JUST HAVE
A FALLING OUT?
- THAT ISN'T IT.
- RYUU-CHAN,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT YOU'RE DOING RIGHT NOW
IS NOT LIKE YOU AT ALL.
RYUU-CHAN.  RYUU-CHAN.
RYUU-CHAN, RYUU-CHAN.
- GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- GENTOKU, YOU NEED
TO PUT AN END TO THIS.
- SHE'S RIGHT, RYUU-CHAN.
YOU WERE ALL
SUCH CLOSE FRIENDS.
NO MATTER
WHAT YOU DID
OR WHEN YOU DID IT,
YOU STUCK TOGETHER.
WAS THAT ALL
NOTHING BUT A BIG LIE?
- HAKUFU SONSAKU,
YOU SAY SUCH STUPID THINGS.
OUR FRIENDSHIP
WAS NEVER IN DOUBT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE TODAY
IS SOMETHING ELSE ALTOGETHER.
RIGHT?
WE MAY HAVE BEEN BORN
ON DIFFERENT DAYS,
BUT WHEN IT'S TIME
FOR THE TWO OF US TO DIE,
THROUGH OUR BONDS OF SISTERHOOD,
I VOW WE'LL DIE TOGETHER.
THIS VOW
CAN NEVER BE BROKEN.
GENTOKU, YOU ARE MERELY
BEING CONTROLLED
BY SOMEONE ELSE
RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE LEAVE
THE TWO OF US.
I WANT TO BE ALONE
WITH GENTOKU.
- YOU GOT IT.
I'LL TAKE ON THE SMALL FRIES.
- WHO'S A SMALL FRY?
- LOOKY HERE, YOU GUYS.
COME CHECK OUT THE FULL MOON.
- WHY, THAT BITCH.
- HOLD IT!
I'LL BE YOUR OPPONENT.
- FINE, GORILLA,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
- ( chuckles )
WELL, KAN'U,
IT SEEMS YOU'RE PREPARED
TO DIE HERE, DOESN'T IT?
- ONLY IF IT'S GENTOKU
WHO KILLS ME.
UNFORTUNATELY THE PERSON
STANDING BEFORE ME NOW
IS BOTH GENTOKU
AND NOT GENTOKU.
- TOO BAD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- GENTOKU, LISTEN.
PLEASE HEAR ME OUT.
THE THINGS I'M ABOUT TO SAY
TO YOU RIGHT NOW
ARE NOT LIES.
I SWEAR IT.
( grunting )
I, UNCHO KAN'U,
CONSIDER MYSELF TO BE
A BLESSED PERSON
BECAUSE I WAS ABLE
TO FIND MYSELF A BRAVE LEADER,
A LEADER WHO I'M MORE
THAN WILLING TO DIE FOR.
I'M GLAD-- I'M GLAD
YOU'RE THE KIND LEADER
WHO DESPISES VIOLENCE
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
IT IS BECAUSE OF
THAT REASON
THAT I AM SO WILLING
TO STAND BY YOU
AND BECOME YOUR SHIELD,
TO FIGHT FOR YOU.
I WAS BORN-- BORN TO FIGHT,
A FIGHTER FROM DAY ONE.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN PROUD
OF THAT FACT.
AND YET A PART OF ME
LONGS FOR PEACE.
THE TWO OF US
WERE SUPPOSED TO MEET.
THE TWO OF US WERE
DESTINED TO MEET.
MY HEART WILL ALWAYS,
NO MATTER WHAT--
GENTOKU...
IT WILL ALWAYS BE
WITH YOU.
- KAN'U!
- SO IS IT ALL OVER?
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.  PLEASE, KAN'U.
SOMEONE-- SOMEONE
TOOK CONTROL OF MY BODY
AND I-- AND I--
AND I--
( sobbing )
- GENTOKU.
I'M GLAD.
- ( crying )
- EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
- WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW IN THE WORLD CAN MY SPELL
HAVE BEEN BROKEN LIKE THAT?
- WHAT'S THIS?
ARE YOU CRYING?
- ( owl hooting )
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU.
- RYOFU?
- ( chuckles )
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Chou'un: DESPITE EVERYTHING
THAT HAD TRANSPIRED,
KAN'U NEVER LOST HER FAITH AND
CONTINUED TO PROTECT OUR LEADER.
I ADMIRE
HER LOYALTY.
- Ekitoku: BUT OF COURSE THAT'S
OUR ONE AND ONLY SISTER FOR YOU.
THE OATH OF THE PEACH
GARDEN AREN'T EMPTY WORDS.
EVEN I, EKITOKU,
WILL GO INTO ACTION
WHEN THE SITUATION
CALLS FOR IT.
- Kouchuu: EKITOKU, YOU NEED
TO STOP BULLYING THE LEADER
AND LEARN A LESSON OR TWO
FROM KAN'U ON LOYALTY.
- SHUT IT, JERK. I DON'T NEED
TO HEAR THAT FROM SOMEONE
WHO THINKS ABOUT
SQUEEZING BOOBIES ALL DAY.
- Kouchuu: WHAT
A THING TO SAY.