- THIS CHICK'S STRONG.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU,
YOU CRAZY BITCH?
- SHIMEI RYOMOU
OF NANYO JUNIOR HIGH.
- YOU'RE FROM
NANYO JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL?
THEN GIVE ENJYUTSU THIS!
- THAT DUMB MONKEY?
HE DIDN'T SEND ME.
I'M FIGHTING ON MY OWN.
- ( laughs )
- ON YOUR OWN?
OF YOUR OWN FREE WILL?
THAT'S A LOAD OF BULLSHIT!
( grunts )
- A LITTLE TOO CARELESS,
JUST LIKE ALWAYS.
EH, MOU-CHAN?
- I'M NOT CARELESS.
- DON'T DENY IT.
THERE'S NO NEED TO
BE SELF-CONSCIOUS.
- I THINK IT'S CUTE.
HERE.
YOU CAN HAVE THE REST.
I'LL TAKE OVER FROM HERE.
CLEANING UP IS A MAN'S JOB.
( humming )
WAIT!
SAJI?
- ( grunting )
- I DIDN'T NEED YOU.
- FINE, YOU DIDN'T.
BUT YOU'RE HAPPY TO
SEE ME ANYWAY, RIGHT?
- LET ME MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
HANG OUT WITH ME TONIGHT.
- WHAT?
- NEVER MIND.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
- ( laughs )
- Ryomou: HOUSEN RYOFU.
IT WAS AT THAT MOMENT.
THAT WAS THE DAY
I FIRST MET YOU.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHY HAVE YOU COME BACK?
- ( grunting )
DO-- DO I KNOW YOU?
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHO I AM?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- WHO AM I?
- WHA--
- ( bell tolling )
- YEAH!
HA!
FIRST ONE HERE.
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO RACE UP
HERE, BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
THE BENTO'S STILL GOOD.
- BUT YOU WOKE UP EARLY TODAY
AND WORKED SO HARD
TO MAKE THE MOST AMAZING SPECIAL
BENTO FOR ME TO EAT FOR LUNCH.
IT WOULD BE A
SHAME IF I COULDN'T
EAT IT AT OUR
SPECIAL PLACE.
- ( laughs )
IT WASN'T THAT MUCH TROUBLE.
JUST A BENTO.
BUT IT MAKES ME HAPPY
TO KNOW THAT YOU LIKE IT.
- IN THAT CASE,
DO YOU THINK THAT YOU COULD
MAKE ME LUNCH EVERY DAY?
- OF COURSE I CAN DO THAT.
I'D GLADLY DO ANYTHING
TO HELP MY BIG SISTER.
- ALL RIGHT!
- BUT IT'S JUST A PACKED LUNCH.
NOTHING WORTH
GETTING EXCITED ABOUT.
- BUT MOM SAYS MAKING LUNCH
IS A HASSLE.
SHE MAKES ME BUY IT
FROM THE CONVENIENCE STORE.
- A-CHEW!
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT SOMEONE IS
TALKING ABOUT ME BEHIND MY BACK.
PERHAPS IT'S THAT GUY
FROM THE COFFEE SHOP.
BUT THE MANAGER AT THE SUPER
MARKET IS QUITE HANDSOME TOO!
THAT BEING SAID,
MUCH AS I LIKE
OGLING THE MANAGER,
I HOPE CHUUBO DOESN'T KEEP
MAKING THOSE GIANT BENTOS.
I DON'T THINK WE CAN AFFORD IT.
- OKAY.
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
- ( crow squawking )
CAW!
- GIVE BACK THE MOST
AMAZING SPECIAL BENTO
CHUUBO MADE FOR ME!
COME BACK, YOU STUPID CROW.
WHEN I CATCH YOU, I'M GONNA
PULL OUT ALL YOUR FEATHERS!
- ARE YOU SURE BIG SISTER HAKUFU
WILL BE ALL RIGHT?
- HONESTLY, I'M MORE WORRIED
ABOUT THE CROW THAN HAKUFU.
- SHE'S ALWAYS SO FULL
OF ENERGY, ISN'T SHE?
- MR. GAKUSHU.
HOW NICE TO SEE YOU.
IS MISS RYOMOU COMING?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
SHE DIDN'T SHOW UP TODAY.
- Both: HUH?
- SORRY, I HAVE TO GO.
BYE.
- WAIT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, MOU-CHAN?
- SHE JUST RAN OFF.
I HOPE THAT NOTHING BAD
HAPPENED.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
YOU'RE HOSEN RYOFU.
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
YOU COULD POSSIBLY BE.
- HOSEN RYOFU.
IS THAT MY NAME?
- I DON'T BUY IT.
HOW COULD YOU
NOT REMEMBER ANYTHING?
HAVE YOU ALSO FORGOTTEN
THAT YOU'RE A FIGHTER?
- A FIGHTER?
WHAT IS THAT?
- THIS IS A SACRED BEAD,
THE MAGATAMA.
YOU HAVE ONE JUST LIKE IT.
IT'S PROOF
THAT SOMEONE IS A FIGHTER.
- THIS PROVES I'M A FIGHTER?
- BUT BACK THEN,
THAT WASN'T ALL YOU WERE.
SAJI IS LATE.
SHOULD WE WAIT FOR HIM?
- ( grunts )
- SAJI IS NOT HERE.
RIGHT NOW I'M THE ONE
WHO IS YOUR OPPONENT.
- ( grunting )
- YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
YOU'RE FIGHTING ME
AND NOT THE YOUNG MASTER.
I MAY BE STRONG,
BUT HE IS 10 TIMES STRONGER.
- ( door closes )
- SAJI CAN'T REALLY BE
MUCH STRONGER THAN THAT GUY,
CAN HE?
WHERE IS HE ANYWAY?
THIS PLACE IS SO HUGE, THOUGH.
LIKE A MANSION.
IS IT POSSIBLE HE GOT LOST
IN HIS OWN HOUSE?
( gasps )
- Housen: YOU CAN COME OUT NOW.
JEALOUS, ARE WE?
THERE'S REALLY NO NEED TO BE.
I HAVE NO SPECIAL PLACE
IN SAJI'S AFFECTIONS.
I'M JUST A PLAYTHING FOR HIM.
- WHAT?
- IT'S A GAME.
HE'S JUST GETTING CLOSE TO ME
SO THAT HE CAN GET THE CHANCE
TO DEFEAT TOUTAKU,
LEADER OF RAKUYA.
JUST THE MEANS TO AN END.
BUT YOU'RE JUST A CHILD,
MOU-CHAN.
YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND
ADULT RELATIONSHIPS LIKE THIS.
- YOU BITCH!
- ( coughing )
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
RYOFU,
YOU'RE COUGHING UP BLOOD.
- PLEASE, LISTEN TO ME,
RYOMOU.
PROMISE ME--
PROMISE YOU'LL DO SOMETHING
FOR ME.
- YOU ASKED ME FOR A FAVOR.
BUT LATER ON, YOU DIED.
- ( gasps )
- I WAS THERE.
I WATCHED YOU FIGHT YOUR LAST
DEADLY BATTLE WITH TOUTAKU.
YOU USED UP EVERY BIT OF YOUR
STRENGTH TO TRY AND DEFEAT HIM.
- IF I DIED,
THEN WHO AM I NOW?
- ( cell phone ringing )
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- Gakushu: THAT'S A FINE
HOW-DO-YA-DO
AFTER I'VE BEEN SO WORRIED.
WHAT'S UP?  WHERE ARE YOU?
- THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- COME ON, RYOMOU, IT'S ME.
- ( door closing )
- DAMN.
- RYOMOU, TALK TO ME.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
CAN YOU HEAR ME, RYOMOU?
- ( phone beeps off )
- WHERE ARE YOU?
WHY AREN'T YOU HERE?
WHY IS IT THAT YOU
ALWAYS SEEM TO DISAPPEAR
JUST WHEN I NEED YOU THE MOST?
( sighs ) SAJI.
YOU ASKED ME FOR A FAVOR.
BUT LATER ON YOU DIED.
- SHE CAN'T BE RIGHT
BECAUSE THAT MEANS...
I'M DEAD.
- Hakufu: COME BACK HERE,
YOU LITTLE BASTARD!
- CAW!
- AWW, YOU STUPID CROW!
STOP TAUNTING ME.
GIVE ME BACK MY BENTO!
YOU'RE JUST MAKING FUN OF ME,
AREN'T YOU?
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
LET YOU GET AWAY WITH THAT!
HA!
- A SACRED BEAD.
SHE'S ALSO A FIGHTER.
- CAW CAW!
- WHOA!  OH OH OH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LUCKY FOR ME YOU WERE HERE.
THIS IS A VERY IMPORTANT LUNCH.
- ( growling )
- WAS THAT YOUR TUMMY GROWLING?
WHY DON'T YOU
EAT LUNCH WITH ME?
- I CAN'T IMAGINE NOT
BEING ABLE TO REMEMBER
ANYTHING ABOUT YOURSELF.
I DIDN'T THINK
THAT WAS POSSIBLE.
THEN AGAIN, I FORGET
ALL KINDS OF THINGS
ALMOST AS SOON AS I LEARN THEM.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
PEOPLE'S FACES OR NAMES.
NO MATTER HOW HARD I TRY,
THEY DON'T STICK.
KOUKIN SCOLDS ME, BUT HE TRIES
TO HELP ME REMEMBER.
OH, I KNOW!
I AM A LITTLE STUPID.
MAYBE THAT'S THE
REASON I'M FORGETTING
THINGS ALL OF THE TIME.
( laughs )
YOU FINALLY SMILED.
YOU LOOKED SO DEPRESSED.
I WAS A WORRIED.
BUT THEN IT MIGHT BE HARD
TO SMILE IF YOU'RE HUNGRY.
HERE, PLEASE EAT ALL YOU WANT.
IT'S JUST US GIRLS AROUND,
SO WE CAN GO AHEAD
AND STUFF OURSELVES.
MAMA SAYS IT'S NOT LADY-LIKE
TO SCARF DOWN MY
FOOD IN MIXED COMPANY.
- ( laughs )
DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU
FOR SHARING YOUR FOOD.
- THAT HIT THE SPOT.
I'M STUFFED.
- Sonken: BIG SISTER HAKUFU!
- Koukin: HAKUFU!
- GREAT.
NOW KOUKIN AND CHUUBO ARE HERE.
- WE WERE LOOKING
ALL OVER THE PLACE FOR YOU.
- OH!
THE BENTO I MADE FOR YOU.
YOU ATE THE ENTIRE THING!
THAT'S SO WONDERFUL.
DID YOU LIKE ALL OF IT?
- YOU BET.
AND THIS GIRL HERE
HELPED ME EAT IT.
SO IT WAS JUST THE RIGHT AMOUNT.
- IS SHE A FRIEND?
I DON'T BELIEVE WE'VE MET.
- OH. WELL, WE MET AND BECAME
FRIENDS JUST NOW IN THE PARK.
- WE'RE FRIENDS NOW?
- BY THE WAY, I FORGOT
TO ASK YOU WHAT YOUR NAME IS.
WHAT'S WRONG, KOUKIN?
- I KNOW THAT UNIFORM.
IT'S RAKUYO.
AND YOU'RE A FIGHTER.
THAT MUST MEAN
YOU'RE HOUSEN RYOFU.
BUT WHAT AM I SAYING?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HOUSEN RYOFU IS LONG GONE.
SHE DIED IN A BATTLE
WITH TOUTAKU.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S TRUE THEN.
I REALLY AM A FIGHTER?
- SHE DOESN'T REMEMBER THAT.
SHE DOESN'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING ABOUT HERSELF.
- NO, I DON'T.
- YOU'RE HOUSEN RYOFU!
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
YOU COULD POSSIBLY BE.
- THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
APPARENTLY,
I AM THE FIGHTER HOUSEN RYOFU.
AND I'M SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD.
- Sonken: SUN TZU TEACHES,
"A KINGDOM ONCE DESTROYED
CAN NEVER RETURN TO BEING,
NOR CAN THE DEAD EVER
BE BROUGHT BACK TO THE LIVING.
ONCE A COUNTRY IS DESTROYED,
THAT COUNTRY AS IT WAS
NO LONGER EXISTS.
THEY MAY REBUILD ITSELF,
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME.
SO WHEN A PERSON DIES, THAT SAME
PERSON CAN NEVER COME BACK."
YOUR PRESENCE HERE
PROVES YOU'RE ALIVE.
YOU ARE ONLY YOURSELF.
THE PERSON YOU ARE RIGHT NOW.
- SO I'M HERE
AND THAT PROVES THAT I'M ALIVE?
- THAT'S RIGHT, FU-CHIN!
YOU'RE NOT DEAD AND NO ONE
CAN CLAIM THAT YOU ARE.
SO BE HAPPY.
LET'S GO!
- BIG SISTER, WAIT!
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING, HAKUFU?
- THE CLINIC.
I WANT DOCTOR KADA
TO HAVE A LOOK AT HER.
- ( banging )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
OWWIE.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- KARAOKE.
HALF OFF TODAY!
- HAKUFU, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- TIME FOR A CHANGE OF PLANS.
WE'RE ALL GOING TO KARAOKE.
- WELL, WE'RE SO LATE,
WE MIGHT AS WELL
JUST SKIP CLASS AND--
HEY, WAIT JUST A MINUTE HERE!
- BUT IT'S A SPECIAL SALE
JUST FOR TODAY.
EVERYTHING IS HALF OFF.
THAT MEANS WE CAN ALL SING
TWICE AS MANY SONGS.
- AND THE CLINIC?
YOU WANTED RYOFU
TO GO GET CHECKED OUT.
- WE CAN DO THAT LATER.
SINGING MIGHT HELP JOG
SOMETHING IN FU-CHIN'S MEMORY.
PLEASE, CAN WE GO?
- HMM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, CHUUBO?
- THAT DEPENDS, BIG BROTHER.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN TO ME
WHAT KARAOKE IS FIRST?
- All: WHAT?
- NO LUCK.
WHERE'D SHE GO TO?
- Woman:
YOU ARE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE?
- FORTUNE TELLER?
I HAVE NO MONEY.
AND EVEN IF I DID,
I DON'T BELIEVE IN GOD
AND ESPECIALLY NOT IN PSYCHICS
OR FORTUNE TELLERS.
- THE INDIVIDUAL YOU SEEK
IS LOCATED SOUTHEAST OF HERE.
SHE ISN'T ALL THAT FAR
FROM THIS VERY SPOT.
- WHAT?
SHE'S SOMEWHERE
SOUTHEAST OF HERE?
- LISTEN FOR HER SONG
AND FOLLOW THE SOUND.
- THERE'S NO WAY.
SHE CAN'T BE.
- ♪ AN EXTREME PARADISE
IS THE PLACE I DREAM OF ♪
♪ WORTH SO MUCH MORE TO ME
THAN TRUTH WAS ♪
♪ CRYING AND LAUGHING,
ENJOYING MY LIFE ♪
♪ EVERY DAY,
I'M SO LUCKY! ♪
♪ THOUGH I MAY JOKE... ♪
- OH, I GET IT.
WE KARAOKE IN HERE.
- WHY DON'T YOU SING SOMETHING,
CHUUBO?
- I- I COULDN'T SING! I'M NOT
A VERY GOOD SINGER AT ALL.
- I'M STARTING TO GET IT.
YOU'RE THE COMPLETE OPPOSITE
OF YOUR OLDER SISTER.
- BUT I WOULD TRY IT.
I THINK I COULD DO IT IF YOU
SANG WITH ME, BIG BROTHER.
- ♪ IF THIS FEELING
THAT WE SHARE ♪
♪ IS TRULY LOVE ♪
♪ THEN I KNOW IT WILL SHINE
FOREVER UP ABOVE ♪
♪ LIKE THE STARS... ♪
- HEY FU-CHIN,
ARE THERE ANY SONGS
THAT YOU REMEMBER?
IN THAT CASE, WHY DON'T YOU
SING A DUET WITH ME?
- HMM.
- HERE'S A GOOD ONE.
HOW ABOUT WE TRY SINGING THIS?
( humming )
- ( humming )
- WHAT'S THAT YOU'RE HUMMING?
- IT'S A POP SONG.
- YOU'RE INTO POP MUSIC THEN.
I'D NEVER GUESS THAT.
- ( both humming )
- ( Housen humming )
- YOU KNOW THIS SONG?
- YEAH.
WHO DID I SEE JUST NOW?
- SEE, MUSIC DOES HELP YOU
REMEMBER.
LET'S SING THEN AND
MAYBE IT WILL TRIGGER
EVEN MORE OF YOUR MEMORIES.
♪ AS THE SEASONS
COME AND GO ♪
♪ I STILL REMEMBER ♪
♪ THE SCENE WON'T DISAPPEAR ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ AS I LAY ALONE AT NIGHT ♪
♪ I TRY TO FALL ASLEEP ♪
♪ BUT SLUMBER NEVER COMES ♪
♪ AND MY SEARCH FOR WARMTH
CARRIES ON... ♪
- Housen: PROMISE ME. PROMISE
YOU'LL DO SOMETHING FOR ME.
- ♪ ...I TRY TO FORGET... ♪
- ( coughing )
- HEY, RYOFU?
- HYAH!
- YOU FUCKING BITCH!
- Housen: HEAVEN AND EARTH,
WHITE WOLF STRIKE!
- ( grunting )
- YOU WILL NEED
TO BECOME STRONGER.
IF YOU REMAIN A WEAKLING,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO COUNT ON YOU.
- COUNT ON ME?
TO DO WHAT?
- TO TAKE CARE OF SAJI.
- WHAT?
- TIME IS SHORT
AND I AM RUNNING OUT OF IT.
THERE'S STILL MORE TO DO
TO CHANGE HISTORY.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU CAN'T CONTINUE FIGHTING
IN YOUR CONDITION.
- WHY NOT?
- YOU'RE DYING!
- SUCH IS THE DESTINY
OF A FIGHTER.
NO, THAT'S NOT QUITE RIGHT.
THE SACRED BEADS LOCK US
INTO A HISTORY WE MUST REPEAT.
BUT I FOUGHT AGAINST IT,
AND THOUGH IT COST ME DEARLY,
I SUCCEEDED.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I CHANGED MY FATE.
MY DEATH IS MY CHOICE.
- YOU CHANGED YOUR FATE?
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU NOW.
TAKE CARE OF SAJI.
- ( all gasp )
- IT'S MOU-CHAN.
- HUH?
- WOW!
MOU-CHAN AND FU-CHIN ARE FRIENDS
ALREADY. THAT'S AWESOME!
- YOU LEFT THIS WORLD
TOO SOON, RYOFU.
GOD HAS BROUGHT YOU BACK
AND GIVEN YOU MORE TIME TO LIVE.
- GOD GAVE ME MORE TIME?
- YES.
AND YOU CAN DO ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO WITH IT.
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR CHOICE.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hakufu:
WOW, I SURE SANG A LOT TODAY.
AND KOUKIN AND CHUUBO'S DUET
WAS SO CUTE.
THEY LOOKED ABSOLUTELY ADORABLE,
THE PERFECT COUPLE.
- Sonken:
UH, UH, BIG SISTER HAKUFU?
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
- Koukin: YEAH,
HAKUFU, WHAT GIVES?
CHUUBO AND I DON'T LOOK
LIKE ANYTHING AT ALL.
- Hakufu: HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU TWO?
WHY ARE YOU TWO STARING
AT EACH OTHER?
OH, NOW YOU CLAM UP?
HMM.
THIS IS SUSPICIOUS.
VERY SUSPICIOUS.