- MMM!  SO REFRESHING.
MORNING BATHS ARE THE BEST.
- ( door opens )
- GOOD MORNING,
BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
DO YOU NEED HELP
WASHING YOUR BACK?
- Goei: KOUKIN!
- YES, AUNT GOEI?
- GO TELL HAKUFU SHE'S BEEN
IN THE TUB LONG ENOUGH
FOR ONE MORNING.
BREAKFAST IS ALMOST READY.
- SURE, AUNT GOEI.
I'LL GET HER.
- SHE'S COMING HOME WITH US?
- WHAT CHOICE DO WE HAVE?
MAMA JUST SAID TO
BE SURE TO BRING HER BACK
TO THE HOUSE. I DIDN'T ARGUE.
- I'M STILL NOT SURE
THAT I BUY IT.
HOW COULD YOU HAVE A SISTER?
- Goei: WELCOME HOME.
- AUNT GOEI.
- HI.
WE'RE HOME, MOM.
- OH, DEAR.
WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO WITH YOU?
YOU'VE GONE
AND TORN YOUR UNIFORM AGAIN.
- UH, THERE'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY LONG STORY BEHIND THIS,
OR MAYBE NOT.
- FINALLY.
HERE YOU ARE.
- Both: HUH?
- MY NAME IS CHUUBO SONKEN,
AND I'M 16.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
- I KNOW YOU ALREADY
MET, BUT WHY DON'T YOU
REINTRODUCE YOURSELVES?
- RIGHT!
I'M HAKUFU SONSAKU,
AND I'M 16 YEARS OLD.
- I'M KOUKIN SHUYU,
AND I'M 16 JUST LIKE YOU GUYS.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU,
MISS SONKEN.
- MISS SONKEN THEN?
THAT'S FINE.
- HUH?
THAT'S YOUR NAME?
- IT'S JUST THAT I HEARD
YOU AND BIG SISTER HAKUFU
HAD BEEN RAISED TOGETHER
LIKE BROTHER AND SISTER.
- YEAH, THAT'S CORRECT.
- IN THAT CASE,
IF YOU DON'T MIND,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
JUST CALL ME "CHUUBO"
THE WAY YOU CALL BIG SISTER
HAKUFU BY HER FIRST NAME?
IF I'M ASKING TOO MUCH,
THEN YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
- NO.
THAT'S NOT ASKING TOO MUCH.
I CAN DO THAT.
FROM NOW ON, YOU'RE CHUUBO.
- THANKS.
THAT REALLY MAKES US
FEEL LIKE FAMILY.
YOU'RE THE BEST, BIG BROTHER.
- UM...
DID YOU SAY BIG BROTHER?
- YES.
- THAT SOUNDS PRETTY COOL.
- AHEM!
HELLO.  MY NAME IS GOEI.
I'M YOUR MAMA,
AND I'M JUST 17 YEARS OLD.
- ( all laugh nervously )
- CHUUBO, HUH?
HAKUFU, AUNT GOEI SAYS YOU HAVE
TO GET OUT OF THE TUB NOW--
HUH?
- BIG BROTHER!
- AH!
- BIG BROTHER?!
- BREAKFAST TIME.
- HAKUFU, DON'T FORGET
TO CHEW YOUR FOOD THOROUGHLY.
- MORE, PLEASE, MAMA.
- MY IDIOT DAUGHTER--
ALWAYS TUNING ME OUT.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE EVER
GOING TO LISTEN TO A WORD I SAY.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KOUKIN?
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN A BITE
OF YOUR FOOD.
- I GUESS I'M JUST NOT HUNGRY.
- WAIT,
IT'S ALL MY FAULT ISN'T IT?
I'VE BEEN ALOOF AND DISTANT
ALL THROUGH BREAKFAST.
- NO, DON'T BLAME YOURSELF.
IT'S NOT YOU.
IT'S NOT YOU AT ALL.
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING
ALL TO PIECES OVER?
I THOUGHT YOU'RE USED
TO SEEING ME IN THE BUFF.
- WELL, SURE,
I'VE SEEN YOU NAKED.
- DID I JUST HEAR YOU RIGHT,
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN?
- OH, SURE.  THE TWO OF US
ARE ALWAYS NAKED TOGETHER.
EVER SINCE WE WERE LITTLE KIDS.
- HUH?
- HEY, WHEN YOU SAY IT LIKE
THAT, IT SOUNDS CREEPY.
TRY PUTTING IT
A DIFFERENT WAY.
- I GUESS WE'RE NOT NAKED
ALL THE TIME.
- YOU'RE NOT HELPING.
- THEN WE'RE ONLY NUDE
WHEN WE PLAY TOGETHER.
- NOW YOU'RE MAKING IT WORSE!
- Goei: THE PAPERWORK
FOR REGISTERING
CHUUBO AT NANYO ACADEMY
IS ALL FILLED OUT.
- OKAY.
I'LL DROP IT OFF.
UM, AUNT GOEI?
CHUUBO-- IS SHE REALLY
YOUR DAUGHTER TOO?
- STOP WORRYING.
DON'T SWEAT THE SMALL STUFF.
YOU'LL GET WRINKLES
ON YOUR FOREHEAD.
- OKAY.
- Chuubo: BIG BROTHER KOUKIN?
- KOUKIN,
WE'RE READY TO GO.
- GREAT.
NOW GET TO SCHOOL
AND STUDY HARD.
- LOOK OUT!
- OH!
- YOU HAVE TO WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING
OR YOU COULD GET HURT.
OH.
UM, I'M SORRY.
- UM, THANK YOU
FOR HELPING ME.
- HEY, YOU GUYS!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- Chuubo: RIGHT.
SORRY, I GOT A LITTLE
DISTRACTED.
- WHAT'S THAT?
YOUR FACE IS ALL RED AND YOU
SEEM TO BE SWEATING TOO.
KOUKIN, COME HERE.
I THINK SHE MIGHT BE SICK.
NOPE.  NO FEVER.
- THANKS, BUT I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYTHING WRONG WITH ME.
I'M PROBABLY JUST NERVOUS.
IT IS MY FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL,
AFTER ALL.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
IF ANYONE
TRIES TO MESS WITH YOU,
I'LL BEAT THEIR ASS SO BADLY
THAT THEY'LL SCREAM
LIKE A WEAK LITTLE GIRL.
- YOU--
YOU'LL BEAT THEIR ASS?
- ( laughs nervously )
- YOU'RE SONSAKU'S SISTER?
- THAT'S RIGHT, I AM.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU TOO.
INCIDENTALLY,
DO YOU LIKE SWEETS?
- GAKU-CHAN HERE
HAS A SUPER HUGE SWEET TOOTH.
- YOU HAVE A SWEET TOOTH?
THAT'S GREAT.
I DO TOO.
- AWESOME.
THEN YOU HAVE TO TRY
THE GREEN TEA MOCHI SUNDAE
THEY MAKE OUT AT CHOUKOU.
IT'S A LITTLE MOM &amp; POP SHOP
OUT PAST THE TRAIN STATION.
- SHE DOESN'T LOOK
ANYTHING LIKE YOU, SONSAKU.
- REALLY?
YOU DON'T THINK SO?
- LUCKY FOR HER.
- En'in: WELL WELL,
SO SONSAKU HAS A LITTLE SISTER.
YOU MAY NOT HAVE THE GIANT
BOOBY-BOMBS YOUR SISTER DOES,
BUT YOU'VE GOT PLENTY THERE
TO HAVE A SQUEEZE.
- Man: WE GET ENOUGH?
- HMM?
- PICS.
YOU WANT MORE?
- NAH, THAT'S GOOD.
- FRESH MEAT,
WE'RE GONNA EAT HER ALL UP.
JUST LIKE ALWAYS, RIGHT?
HEY!  WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- YOU REEK.
IT STINKS LIKE A
SWEATY GYM SOCK.
- YOU MEAN I SMELL?
- HMM. I'LL LET YOU TASTE HER.
BUT FIRST YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
EXACTLY WHAT I TELL YOU TO.
HAKUFU SONSAKU.
DON'T GO THINKING THAT YOU
CAN RULE THIS SCHOOL FOREVER.
- ( bell ringing )
- THAT'S REALLY WEIRD.
WHERE COULD SHE BE?
- BIG BROTHER?
- SORRY IT'S SO LATE TODAY.
- ( cat meows )
- BIG BROTHER KOUKIN?
- CHUUBO?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AND WHY ARE YOU
FEEDING THAT LITTLE KITTEN?
- WELL, YOU SEE--
- WHAT DO WE DO, KOUKIN?!
- Koukin: WHAT DO WE DO?
YOU'VE GONE
AND PICKED IT UP ALREADY.
- BUT, KOUKIN,
HOW CAN WE LEAVE HIM ALONE?
HE'S JUST
A HELPLESS TEENY-TINY KITTEN.
- UM, WELL, I GUESS HE IS.
- RIGHT.
SO HE'S COMING HOME WITH US.
- HUH?  NO WAY.
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
- WHY NOT?
- YOU'RE NOT CAPABLE
OF TAKING CARE OF A KITTEN
ALL BY YOURSELF, HAKUFU.
YOU CAN'T EVEN
KEEP YOUR OWN ROOM CLEAN.
- THAT HITS BELOW THE BELT.
OKAY, FINE.
I'LL KEEP HIM AT SCHOOL.
- WELL, IN THAT CASE,
WAIT A SEC.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
- WHY NOT?
- THEN, LET ME ASK YOU,
WILL YOU SEE THIS
ALL THE WAY THROUGH?
CAN YOU BE RESPONSIBLE?
- YES, I CAN BE.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I'M SURE.
- WILL YOU MAKE A PROMISE?
- I PROMISE.
CROSS MY HEART.
- AND YET,
WHERE IS HAKUFU NOW?  HMM.
- WHAT A KINDLY PERSON.
- HUH?
- MY BIG SISTER, HAKUFU.
NOT ONLY
IS SHE A STRONG FIGHTER,
BUT SHE HAS A SORT
OF TENDER-HEARTEDNESS.
THAT'S WHY EVERYONE
LIKES AND RESPECTS HER
SO MUCH AS A LEADER.
- THEY DO?
- SHE DIDN'T ACT BOTHERED
IN THE LEAST,
EVEN THOUGH I SHOWED UP
ALL OF A SUDDEN
AND BARGED INTO YOUR LIVES.
- YOU'RE NO BOTHER.
I SWEAR.
DON'T GO THINKING
THAT YOU ARE.
WE LIKE HAVING YOU
HOME WITH US, CHUUBO.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO STAY
AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
- BIG BROTHER.
- SORRY.
- ( cat meows )
- SORRY, KITTY.
- Hakufu: DAY AND DAY, WITH
NOTHING BUT MILK TO DRINK.
POOR KITTY'S
GOT TO BE SICK OF IT.
MY CAT IS GONNA EAT
AN OILY FISH!
- Man: HAVE YOU HEARD
THE LATEST
ABOUT THE SO-CALLED LEADER
OF THE BIG FOUR?
THEY SAY SHE'S BEEN
KEEPING A LITTLE KITTY CAT
OUT BEHIND THE GYM.
RUMOR HAS IT SHE'S TOO STUPID
TO TALK WITH NORMAL PEOPLE,
SO SHE TALKS
TO THE CAT INSTEAD.
- WHAT A WEIRDO.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH
SHE'S AN IDIOT,
BUT A CREEPY CAT-WHISPERER TOO?
IT'S LIKE SHE'S SUBHUMAN.
- MUST BE A REAL PAIN IN THE ASS
FOR THE BIG FOUR.
THEY'VE GOT TO DEAL WITH THAT
IDIOTIC BIMBO EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- I'LL BET SHE DOESN'T
GIVE A CRAP ABOUT ANY OF THEM.
TO HER,
THEY'RE JUST HUMAN SHIELDS.
- HER, A LEADER?
THAT'S A LOAD OF BULL
I KNOW I COULDN'T SWALLOW
EVEN IF YOU RAMMED IT
DOWN MY THROAT.
- All: THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
( laughing )
- HUH?
- WELL DONE, GENTLEMEN.
- SONSAKU?
- NO ONE'S SEEN HER
SINCE THIS AFTERNOON.
- IT'S NOT THAT UNUSUAL
FOR HER TO DISAPPEAR.
- YEAH, BUT WE'VE GOT
TO GO TO WORK TODAY.
- IT'S WORK?  OH.
- I HATE TO ASK, RYOMOU,
BUT WOULD YOU MIND
FILLING IN FOR HER?
JUST THIS ONCE, PLEASE?
- I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
I'M NOT RIGHT
FOR THAT TYPE OF THING.
- COULDN'T YOU TRY IT ONCE?
THE MAID UNIFORM
IS AWFULLY PRETTY.
IT WOULD LOOK GOOD ON YOU.
I THINK YOU'D LIKE IT
IF YOU GAVE IT A CHANCE.
- I SAID NO!
BYE, SHUYU.  LATER.
OH, I'LL SEE YOU LATER TOO,
SONKEN.
- SURE.
BYE, RYOMOU.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
BIG BROTHER,
I DON'T MEAN TO MEDDLE,
BUT IS THERE A WAY
I COULD BE OF HELP?
MAYBE I COULD
TAKE BIG SISTER'S SHIFT.
- En'in:
LOOKS LIKE SHE FELL FOR IT.
NOW FOR THE BAIT--
SUCH YOUNG, TASTY BAIT.
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU MOPING ABOUT?
- AH!
MO-- MOU-CHAN.
- ( laughs )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE MOPING FOR REAL.
THAT'S SO NOT LIKE YOU.
IT'S HYSTERICAL.
- WHAT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT'S NO USE, MOU-CHAN.
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M JUST SOME SILLY DITZ
AND THAT I'M TOO STUPID TO BE
THE LEADER OF THE BIG FOUR.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I SEE.
SO THERE ARE STILL
PATHETIC LOW LIFES AT SCHOOL
THAT SPEW RIDICULOUS
AND CRUEL LIES.
- THEY WEREN'T LIES.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
THEY WEREN'T.
AT LEAST NOT ALL OF THEM.
YOU ARE KINDA STUPID,
AND THAT'S A FACT.
- MMM.
- SONSAKU.
- YEAH?
- WHAT'S YOUR IDEA OF WHAT
A LEADER IS SUPPOSED TO BE?
- I DON'T THINK
I HAVE AN IDEA.
HA!
I AM KINDA DUMB.
- NO TWO LEADERS ARE EXACTLY THE
SAME. BUT ALL OF THEM
BEAR THE SAME RESPONSIBILITY
TO THEIR SUBJECTS,
THE SUBJECTS WHO PUT
ALL THEIR HOPES AND DREAMS
ON THE LEADER'S SHOULDERS.
- YOU MEAN THEY
DEPEND ON THE LEADER?
- THAT'S RIGHT. AND IT'S
A LEADER'S RESPONSIBILITY
TO DO ALL SHE CAN TO PROTECT
THOSE HOPES AND DREAMS
AND SOMETIMES
EVEN HELP THEM COME TRUE.
THAT'S WHAT
BEING A LEADER IS.
THERE AREN'T TOO MANY PEOPLE
WHO COULD HANDLE ALL OF THAT
WITHOUT COMPLETELY FALLING APART
UNDER THE PRESSURE.
AND YOU, SONSAKU,
ARE JUST STUPID ENOUGH
THAT NONE OF IT GETS TO YOU.
- STOP CALLING ME STUPID.
OH.
THANK YOU, MOU-CHAN!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING
THAT YOU JUST TOLD ME,
BUT IT CHEERED ME UP ANYWAY.
THANK YOU FOR BEING SUCH
A GOOD FRIEND TO ME, MOU-CHAN.
- THEN WE ARE FRIENDS.
HMM.
OH, I NEARLY FORGOT.
SHUYU IS LOOKING FOR YOU.
- DID HE SAY WHY?
- SOMETHING TO DO WITH WORK.
- OH, CRAP,
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT!
THANKS AGAIN, MOU-CHAN.
SEE YOU TOMORROW!
- ( dialing )
- GAKUSHU?  IT'S ME.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO ASK YOU ABOUT.
- ( panting )
OH, NO, I'M SO LATE,
I'M GONNA TOTALLY MISS MY SHIFT.
HUH?
- ( moaning )
- KOUKIN?
KOUKIN!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- HAKUFU.  I'M SORRY
I GOT CAUGHT OFF-GUARD.
THEY TOOK HER.
- ( laughing )
NOW THEN,
SHOULD WE GET STARTED?
- Koukin: WAIT, HAKUFU!
DON'T GO.
IT'S A TRAP!
- I HAVE TO GO IN THERE
EVEN IF IT'S A TRAP
BECAUSE I'M THE LEADER.
- ( cameras flashing )
- HUH?
WHERE AM I?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA UPLOAD IT
STRAIGHT TO THE BOSS'S WEBSITE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
ALL OVER THE NET.
- HUH?
WHO'S THIS BOSS WITH A NET?
- HIS NAME IS EN'IN.
HE LEADS THIS GANG.
- EN'IN WAS THE GANG'S
NUMBER-TWO FIGHTER
UNDER THE OLD BOSS, ENJYUTSU.
THERE WERE RUMORS
AFTER ENJYUTSU WAS KILLED
THAT HE WAS SCHEMING
TO BECOME THEIR NEW LEADER.
- OKAY, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH SHOTS
OF HER WITH THE UNIFORM ON.
NEXT UP, WHAT'S INSIDE.
- En'in: THAT'S ENOUGH FOR NOW.
- EN'IN!
- DID I GIVE YOU PERMISSION
TO DO MORE THAN TAKE PICTURES?
- NO.
WE'RE SORRY, BOSS.
- DOES THAT MEAN
YOU'RE MR. EN'IN?
- NO NEED TO BE SO FORMAL. I'D
PREFER YOU CALLED ME MASTER.
ARE YOU SCARED?
I REALLY LIKE IT
WHEN THEY'RE SCARED.
YOU SMELL SO DELICIOUS.
JUST LIKE A BIG PIECE
OF WARM CHERRY PIE.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR A TASTE.
- ( squealing )
- TIME FOR DESSERT.
- NO, DON'T!
PLEASE STOP!  PLEASE!
HELP ME.
SAVE ME, PLEASE, BIG SISTER.
BIG SISTER HAKUFU,
SAVE ME!
- DO YOU MIND? WE WERE IN
THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
YOU CAN'T JUST BARGE IN HERE
WITHOUT AN INVITATION.
YOU TWO
ARE BEING TERRIBLY IMPOLITE.
- I'M THE ONE YOU'VE GOT
A BEEF WITH, NOT HER.
LET HER GO.
- I'M AFRAID I CAN'T DO THAT--
NOT UNTIL YOU DO SOMETHING
FOR ME FIRST.
- WHAT?
- I WANT YOU TO ISSUE
AN IMPERIAL ORDER.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- ME.
I WANT YOU TO WRITE AN ORDER
DECLARING THAT YOU,
HAKUFU SONSAKU,
ARE STEPPING DOWN
AND NAMING ME, EN'IN,
THE NEW LEADER
OF NANYO ACADEMY.
- WHAT?
- AND IF I DON'T DO THIS?
- THEN I GUESS YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENS TO YOUR SISTER.
- IF YOU HARM EVEN A SINGLE HAIR
ON HER HEAD, YOU WILL PAY!
- SUN TZU TEACHES US
"TO BEWARE
WHEN BIRDS TAKE TO THE SKIES."
- HUH?
- BIRDS TAKING FLIGHT CAN OFTEN
BE EVIDENCE OF AN AMBUSH.
GET READY, HAKUFU!
- OF COURSE THERE'S AN AMBUSH.
DID YOU REALLY EXPECT SOMEONE
AS INTELLIGENT AS
I AM TO FIGHT FAIR?
IF YOU HONESTLY THOUGHT THAT I
WOULD FIGHT YOU ALL BY MYSELF,
THEN YOU'RE AN ABSOLUTE FOOL!
( laughs )
- HAKUFU.
- HE'S RIGHT, KOUKIN,
I AM A FOOL.
I MAY EVEN BE AN IDIOT,
BUT I'M NO COWARD.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE!
- INSULT ME NOW,
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
BECAUSE ONCE MY GANG
IS DONE WITH YOU,
YOU WON'T EVEN
BE ABLE TO TALK.
NOW, GENTLEMEN,
ATTACK HER!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- WE'RE SORRY, BOSS!
- WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
- WHAT DOES IT LOOK
LIKE HAPPENED?
- GAKUSHU,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THE BONDS THAT UNITE
THE BIG FOUR ARE STRONG.
YOU SHOULDN'T
UNDERESTIMATE THEM.
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN WIN NOW.
- FINE, I GIVE UP.
YOU WIN THIS ROUND.
BUT DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO GET OFF SCOT-FREE.
VICTORY HAS ITS PRICE
AND YOU ARE ABOUT TO PAY DEARLY.
YOU SHOULD HAVE GIVEN ME
WHAT I WANTED!
HYAH!
- AHH!
- Hakufu: MOU-CHAN!
- HE'S ALL YOURS, SONSAKU.
- WOW, MOU-CHAN,
YOU'RE THE BEST!
MY TURN.
- ER, AHH, I'M SCREWED.
- HOW DARE YOU TRY
TO HURT MY SISTER?
YOUR ASS IS MINE NOW, BITCH!
- ( En'in screaming )
- I'M SO SORRY THEY BEAT YOU UP,
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN.
- DON'T WORRY, I'LL BE FINE.
I'M JUST GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
- AND I ALSO WANT TO
THANK BIG SISTER HAKUFU.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
- Koukin: THERE'S
ONE LAST THING.
- OH?
- THERE'S SOMETHING HERE
I JUST CAN'T FIGURE OUT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THE FISH.
- OH NO, THAT'S THE FISH
I BOUGHT THIS AFTERNOON!
- IT'S YOURS?
- KOUKIN!
GIVE ME A HAND.
IT'S SO LONG AND SLIPPERY.
- FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE,
WHY DID YOU BUY AN OILY SALMON
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
IT'S FOR THE CAT.
AAH! I HAVEN'T BEEN TO CHECK
ON HIM OR FEED HIM ALL DAY.
- I WENT AND FED HIM SOME MILK
AT LUNCHTIME.
- REALLY?
OH, THANK YOU, KOUKIN.
- BIG SISTER HAKUFU, I HAVE
A FAVOR I WANT TO ASK YOU.
- WHAT IS IT?
- STARTING TOMORROW,
CAN I COME WITH YOU
WHEN YOU GO TO FEED AND
TAKE CARE OF THE LITTLE KITTEN?
- SURE YOU CAN.
COME ANYTIME.
THAT WOULD HELP ME
A LOT, CHUUBO.
- OH, MY GOSH, YOU JUST--
- JUST WHAT?
- YOU CALLED ME
BY MY FIRST NAME, CHUUBO.
YOU'VE NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE.
OH, I'M SO HAPPY!
- OKAY THEN.
- Gakushu: LET'S ALL GO
TO THAT LITTLE MOM AND POP SHOP
OUT BY THE TRAIN STATION.
- YOU REALLY LIKE THAT GREEN
TEA MOCHI SUNDAE, DON'T YOU?
- YEAH.
- COME WITH US, MOU-CHAN.
- I DON'T USUALLY LIKE
TO EAT SWEETS.
BUT I SUPPOSE--
SAJI?
SORRY, I HAVE TO GO.
- WAIT.
- BYE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, MOU-CHAN?
- ( grunts )
THE DRAGON STIRS.
I'VE LOST HIM.
HEY!
ARE YOU OKAY?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
IT'S HOUSEN RYOFU.
HOW IS SHE EVEN ALIVE?
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Gakushu: HEY, SONSAKU?
YOU KNOW THAT LITTLE KITTEN
YOU'RE KEEPING OUT
BEHIND THE GYM?
DO YOU THINK THAT MAYBE I COULD
COME AND PET IT SOMETIME?
- HUH?
GAKU-CHAN, IF
YOU TRIED TO PET IT,
THE POOR LITTLE THING
WOULD BE CRUSHED.
NO WAY!
- COME ON.
I PROMISE I'LL BE GENTLE.
JUST ONCE.
WILL YOU PLEASE LET ME PET IT
JUST ONE TIME?
- Sonken:
GAKUSHU, PLEASE CALM DOWN.
A FIGHTER NEEDS
TO STAY COMPOSED
SO HE CAN BE READY FOR ANYTHING.
- NO, I WANT TO PET IT!
I WANT TO PET THE KITTEN
RIGHT NOW.