- KAN'U, WE CAN'T
DO THIS HERE.
WHAT IF SOMEONE COMES?
THEY'LL SEE US.
- GENTOKU.
- ( moaning )
- WAIT.  NOT YET.
WAIT, KAN'U,
KISS ME FIRST.
- ( crow squawking )
- HUH?
HMM?
- HERE, KOUMEI.
- KOUMEI?
WHO INVITED HER?
- I DID.  I PROMISED KOUMEI
THAT I WOULD LEND HER THAT BOOK.
- WHAT?
GENTOKU!
I NEED TO KNOW HOW
YOU FEEL ABOUT ME.
I NEED TO KNOW RIGHT NOW.
- YOU'RE SCARING ME, KAN'U!
( crying )
- IT WAS A DREAM.
GENTOKU.
HUH?
- Girl: EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- UM, HI, MISS KAN'U, SIR.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
MY NAME IS SHUUSOU
AND I'M A FIRST-YEAR STUDENT
HERE. YOU'RE SO COOL.
AND I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED UP
TO YOU IN AWE.
PLEASE ACCEPT
THIS PRESENT FROM ME! AHH!
- DID YOU SEE?
I GAVE IT TO HER!
- AH-HA-HA!  MAN, YOU SURE
GOT A GIGANTIC HAUL TODAY.
I'M GOING TO GET FAT
FROM EATING ALL OF YOUR GOODIES.
KAN'U?
- EKITOKU?
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
- AH?  WELL, WHATEVER.
THE OLD MAN
IS LOOKING FOR YOU.
- YOU MEAN MASTER SUIKYOU?
- Ekitoku:
DOING SOME SPRING CLEANING?
- I MUST GO OUT
TO BUY MORE SAKE.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU TO GET ALL
OF THIS CLEANING DONE FOR ME.
HAVE FUN.
- THIS SUCKS!
OUR UNIFORMS ARE GOING
TO GET ALL COVERED IN DUST.
DON'T YOU HATE THAT?
ARGH!  KAN'U.
- OH.
WHERE IS MASTER SUIKYOU?
DID HE GO OUT SOMEWHERE?
- HUH?
KAN'U, YOU'VE BEEN ZONING OUT
A LOT LATELY.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE FEELING OKAY?
- ( honks )
- SEITO ACADEMY
ISN'T MUCH FURTHER.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- GREAT.
- YOU'RE REALLY SURE
IT'S OKAY TO GO THERE?
- DON'T FORGET WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME YOU SAW KAN'U.
- NO MORE TALK!
- DAMN YOU!
- THIS MEETING IS TO BOLSTER
GOODWILL AND FRIENDSHIP,
SO NOTHING LIKE THAT
IS GONNA HAPPEN TODAY.
DON'T WORRY.
- EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
- OH, AND I'M JUST SO EXCITED
TO GET TO MEET GENTOKU RYUUBI.
AND I LOVED HER IDEA
TO BRING LUNCH
BECAUSE FRIENDSHIP
GROWS BETTER ON A FULL STOMACH.
- IT SURE DOES!
- ( both chuckle )
- ( sighs )
IF THIS KEEPS UP,
ALL THESE LUNCHES,
THERE'LL BE NO MONEY
FOR ANYTHING ELSE.
I ALMOST FORGOT--
IT'S TIME
FOR MY BALLROOM DANCING LESSON.
THE TEACHER IS SO LEAN
AND MUSCULAR-- EXACTLY MY TYPE.
- ( rustling )
- WHOA!
PERFECT.  NOW I'VE GOT
EVEN MORE WORK TO DO!
OOH!  HOW PRETTY.
I BET THIS IS WORTH A BUCK
OR TWO.
( laughs )
HUH?
AHH!
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
- OH MY!
( whimpers )
- I'M EMBARRASSED.
- WHA--
UH, I'M SO SORRY, MISS.
PLEASE LET ME HELP YOU UP.
- OH!  PERVERT!
HOW COULD YOU THINK
I WOULD TOUCH YOUR HAND?
IF I DID, WE'D HAVE
TO GET MARRIED!
- WE WHAT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
EKITOKU?
- OH?
- WHAT'S WITH
THAT STUPID NECKLACE?
IT CLASHES WITH YOUR UNIFORM.
TAKE IT OFF.
- HOW RUDE OF YOU.
- WHAT?
- A LADY MUST SPEAK PROPER AND
GENTEEL LANGUAGE AT ALL TIMES.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
YOU'RE PLAYING AT.
COME ON.
- OW!
THAT HURTS.
LET GO!
- IT MUST BE THE NECKLACE.
- AH!
HUH?  THAT'S WEIRD.
HOW'D I END UP ON THE FLOOR?
- DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- NO.  DID I DO SOMETHING?
- ( both gasp )
- THIS THING IS EVIL.
- ACTUALLY, THAT IS
A HEART-REVEALING STONE.
- All: HUH?
- WHAT'S
A HEART-REVEALING STONE?
- IT IS A MAGICAL
STONE THAT REVEALS
THE TRUE NATURE OF
THOSE WHO TOUCH IT.
- All: WHAT?
- FOR THOSE WHO DARE
TO PUT ON THAT NECKLACE,
IT WILL BRING THEIR DEEPEST,
MOST HIDDEN DESIRES
TO THE SURFACE.
THEN THEIR INNER-MOST FEELINGS
WILL POSSESS THEM.
- THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
HUH?
- ( giggling )
- BOOB SQUEEZE!
- AAH!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!
- HEY, HEY, BABY!
DON'T PRETEND YOU DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU KNOW YOU WANT IT.
- Both: HUH?
- Kan'u: EKITOKU, LOOK.
- Ekitoku: HE PUT
THE NECKLACE ON!
- YO, CHOUPI!
MMM, GIRL, YOU FINE!
YOU SO HOT, YOU SIZZLE.
OOH, YOU MAKE ME BURN.
THAT'S RIGHT, GIRL,
I'M MELTING!
- SO THIS
IS KOUCHUU'S TRUE SELF?
- THAT'S WHAT IT SEEMS LIKE.
- HE'S JUST A PERVERTED PRIEST.
- YO!  HOW 'BOUT I GET
UP IN YO' GRILL,
SHOW YOU SOME A DEM FLY MOVES
I FAMOUS FOR?
- HEY, GET OFF!
- OH!
- SNAP OUT OF IT ALREADY,
YOU IDIOT!
- I'M BACK, BABY!
GETTING HIT BY YOU
IS LIKE FOREPLAY.
- YOU WANT ANOTHER RIGHT HOOK?
- MAYBE LATER.
- WHAT ARE YOU--
- HEY, KAN-CHAN.
CHOUPI BE ILLIN', BUT I CHILL!
SO HOW 'BOUT YOU, GIRL?
I KNOW YOU GOTTA WANNA TASTE
THE TALL DARK AND SWEET.
MMM!
OOH, HEY, BABY,
YOU GOT A ROCKIN' RACK ON YOU.
- AHH!
AH!
- ( grunts )
WHAT DID I DO?
- DROP DEAD, YOU PERVERT!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT.
HYAH!
- AHH!
- MAY HE REST IN PEACE.
- ( grunts )
I THINK THAT'S THE LAST ONE.
- GREAT!
TAKE FIVE.
- HUH?
- ( whimpering )
HERE.
THIS IS THE BOOK I PROMISED YOU.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
- Kan'u: GENTOKU, YOU REALLY
HAVE NO IDEA, DO YOU?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAN'U?
- IT'S NOTHING.
- Ekitoku: KAN'U HAS
BEEN SPACING OUT A LOT.
I'M WORRIED SHE MIGHT
BE SICK OR SOMETHING.
- REALLY?
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
HMM.
NOT HOT, NO FEVER.
- Koumei: GENTOKU?
- YES?
- LET'S GO.
- OKAY, I'M COMING.
- WAIT. YOU'RE GOING
SOMEWHERE WITH KOUMEI?
- THE WEATHER IS SO NICE.
SO I THOUGHT I'D TAKE HER
TO THAT SPOT IN THE MOUNTAINS
UNDER THE BIG TREE
WHERE I LIKE TO GO READ.
- YOU SURE DO LIKE READING.
- AND YOU SURE DO LIKE EATING,
CHOUHI. DO YOU WANNA GET FAT?
- MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
BOOK WORM,
OR I'LL KICK YOUR BUTT.
- OH, PLEASE MISS CHUBBY
PANTS, DON'T SPANK ME!
- I SAID KICK YOUR BUTT!
- OH!  KOUMEI, HELP!
- GET YOUR BUTT OVER HERE!
- ( giggling )
( squeals )
- OH!
DOES SHE LIKE HER
MORE THAN ME?
- LET'S GO, KOUMEI.
- Ekitoku: YOU'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE!
- I WANT TO KNOW.
I NEED TO KNOW.
I NEED TO KNOW HOW GENTOKU
REALLY FEELS ABOUT ME.
- Ekitoku: KAN'U?  HEY, KAN'U.
YOU REALLY ARE ACTING STRANGE
TODAY, KAN'U.
- NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
WANT TO GET LUNCH?
- SURE.
FOOD SOUNDS GOOD.
- Koumei: FOR THOSE WHO DARE
TO PUT ON THAT NECKLACE,
IT WILL BRING THEIR DEEPEST,
MOST HIDDEN DESIRES
TO THE SURFACE.
THEN THEIR INNER-MOST FEELINGS
WILL POSSESS THEM.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M NOT SURE IT'S SUCH
A GOOD IDEA TO LEAVE THE
HEART-REVEALING-STONE
NECKLACES HERE UNATTENDED.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
THOSE THINGS ARE TROUBLE.
IMAGINE WHAT COULD HAPPEN
IF THE WRONG PERSON PUT ONE ON.
- ( snoring )
- KOUCHUU, WAKE UP!
- YES, MA'AM.
- DON'T LET ANYONE NEAR
THOSE NECKLACES.
WE'RE GOING TO GRAB LUNCH.
- NO, WAIT.
- I'LL STAY AND GUARD
THE NECKLACES.
- REALLY?
SUIT YOURSELF.
- ( moans )
- HUH?
WAKE UP, KOUMEI.
YOU SHOULDN'T FALL ASLEEP HERE.
YOU COULD CATCH COLD THAT WAY.
KOUMEI, I CAN'T MOVE MY ARM.
( giggles )
I GUESS WE COULD STAY
LIKE THIS A WHILE LONGER.
YOU'RE SO CUTE, KOUMEI,
AND YOU SMELL SO SWEET,
LIKE A NEWBORN BABY.
- I WANT TO KNOW.
I HAVE TO KNOW.
I CAN'T GO ON UNLESS I KNOW.
- HMM.
- I HAVE TO KNOW.
I HAVE TO KNOW, I HAVE TO KNOW,
I HAVE TO KNOW NOW.
- OKAY! LET'S FIND OUT WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA TREAT ME TO!
- WHEN DID I SAY LUNCH
WOULD BE MY TREAT?
- YOU OWE ME, MISTER.
IT'S PAYBACK
FOR GROPING MY BOOBS EARLIER.
- Hakufu: HEY, GUYS!
- NANYO ACADEMY?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
- ( humming )
- GENTOKU RYUUBI BELONGS TO ME.
- OH.
YOU'RE AWAKE, KOUMEI?
- GENTOKU'S BOOBS ARE SO BIG.
- EH? AH, MAYBE YOU'RE
NOT SO AWAKE AFTER ALL.
- ( sighs )
- OH!  KAN'U, THAT YOU?
- HOW'D YOU KNOW IT WAS ME?
- I COULD SMELL YOU.
I'D KNOW THAT SCENT ANYWHERE.
- YOU SMELLED ME?
SHE COULD SMELL ME, SMELL ME,
SMELL ME!
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- I BROUGHT THIS.
- IT'S A PRESENT
FOR YOU, GENTOKU.
- FOR ME?
OH, KAN'U, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- ( swallows )
- AH... ( giggles )
DON'T STARE AT ME LIKE THAT.
IT EMBARRASSES ME.
- OH.  I'M SORRY.
- THIS NECKLACE IS SO SPARKLY.
IT'S REALLY PRETTY.
I LOVE IT.
- YEAH YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
NOW HURRY UP AND PUT IT ON.
- HUH?
OH, OKAY.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I'M FINE.  HOW ARE YOU?
- WAIT.
YOU'RE SURE YOU FEEL FINE?
YOU'RE NOT FEELING A HOT BURNING
DESIRE RISING IN YOUR LOINS?
- HMM. WELL, I DO
SUDDENLY HAVE A STRONG
BURNING DESIRE TO READ.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
COME ON. IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SAY TO ME NOW
THAT YOU HAVEN'T BEFORE?
- WELL, SOMETIMES I THINK
YOU CAN BE A BIT OVERBEARING.
- ( sighs )
SO I GUESS I HAVE MY ANSWER.
DEEP DOWN IN YOUR HEART
YOU DON'T REALLY LIKE ME.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I DO LIKE YOU.
- WHAT?
DID YOU MEAN THAT?
SAY IT ONCE AGAIN FOR ME,
PLEASE.
- OKAY, KAN'U--
I LIKE YOU.
I LIKE YOU, I LIKE YOU,
I LIKE LIKE LIKE LIKE YOU!
- ( bells tolling )
- CARO MIO!
- AND I LIKE KOUMEI TOO.
AND I LIKE EKITOKU
AND I LIKE SHIRYU TOO.
I JUST LIKE EVERYONE.
HUH?  ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
I KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU WEAR THE NECKLACE
FOR A WHILE, KAN'U?
IT'LL DEFINITELY
LOOK GOOD ON YOU.
- OH. STOP! DON'T, THAT'S--
- HUH?
- GENTOKU.
- UH, KAN'U?
- HEY!
LOOK, GUYS, WE'VE GOT GUESTS!
- HI.
- OH, MISS SONSAKU.
- Kan'u: HAKUFU SONSAKU.
DON'T INTERFERE AGAIN!
- KAN'U!
IF YOU'RE HERE,
THEN WHO'S GUARDING THE
NECKLACES? THE OLD MAN BACK?
( gasps ) THAT NECKLACE!
YOU'VE GOT IT ON.
IS IT AFFECTING YOU?
- ( grunts )
- OH!  KAN'U,
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?!
- THIS IS BAD.
- WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- Chou'un:
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
I HEARD OUR LEADER SCREAMING.
- Ekitoku: BECAUSE OF KAN'U.
SHE GRABBED RYUUBI AND RAN.
IT'S BECAUSE OF THAT
HEART-REVEALING-STONE
NECKLACE SHE'S GOT ON.
THAT'S JUST LIKE THE ONE
YOU'VE GOT ON.
WAIT! CHOU'UN!
- SHI-SAN!
- AH.
- Koumei: HER TRUE NATURE.
CHOU'UN.
THAT'S WHO SHE REALLY IS.
- OH!
THAT HURT.
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU, KAN'U?
( crying )
DO YOU WANT ME
TO CHANGE CLOTHES?
- REMEMBER THE TWO OF US MADE
THE OATH OF THE PEACH GARDEN?
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW
IS DESTINY!
- BUT KAN'U, WE'RE NOT SCHEDULED
FOR TRAINING RIGHT NOW.
- I'M GOING TO BREAK YOU IN.
NOW DON'T STRUGGLE.
- KAN'U?
SHIRYU!
OH, HELLO THERE.
ARE YOU AND KAN'U BOTH
GOING TO TRAIN ME TOGETHER?
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN HANDLE
YOU BOTH AT ONCE.
- WOW! THAT NECKLACE HAS SUCH
STRANGE AND MYSTERIOUS POWERS.
- THIS IS NO TIME FOR LESSONS
IN MYSTICISM.
IF THOSE TWO
REALLY GET INTO IT,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A MAJOR PROBLEM ON OUR HANDS.
- INDEED, ONE OF THEM
WILL SURELY DIE.
- ( all gasp )
- Ekitoku: KOUMEI,
DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
NOW, COME ON.  LET'S HURRY.
- KAN'U, I DON'T NORMALLY
MIND TRAINING WITH YOU,
BUT THIS SEEMS STRANGE.
- BE QUIET.
- THERE IS NO FORGIVENESS.
YOU HAVE DISRESPECTED
OUR LEADER AND MUST PAY.
- Ryuubi: DISRESPECTED?
- GENTOKU IS MINE.
IF YOU DO ANYTHING TO TRY
TO DRIVE A WEDGE BETWEEN US,
I SWEAR I WILL KILL YOU!
- KAN'U,
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HUH?
- I TOLD YOU NOW
TO BE QUIET.
- KAN'U!
- ( both gasping )
- WE'RE TOO LATE!
- I'VE GOT TO TRY
TO STOP THOSE TWO.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
- WHO YOU CALLIN' STUPID?
- WAIT.
BOTH OF YOU, STOP.
WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME SIDE.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR
YOU TWO TO BE FIGHTING.
- AH!
- ( all gasping )
- All: OH!
- Ekitoku:
MASTER SUIKYOU, YOU'RE BACK!
- AYE YAI YAI.
LOOK AT THIS MESS.
WELL, I'M NOT CLEANING IT UP.
- WHERE AM I?
- WHAT WAS I DOING?
- AH.
- GENTOKU?
- DON'T COME NEAR ME.
YOU'RE-- YOU'RE SCARY, KAN'U.
- AH!  DID I DO ALL THIS?
HOW COULD I?
I CANNOT BELIEVE I WAS SO
DISRESPECTFUL TO MY LEADER.
THERE IS BUT ONE REMEDY.
- NOW YOU LISTEN TO ME.
I DON'T CARE
IF YOU DISRESPECTED ME.
I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO TAKE YOUR OWN LIFE.
- AS SUN TZU TEACHES, "REGARD
YOUR SOLDIERS AS YOUR CHILDREN,
AND THEY WILL FOLLOW YOU
INTO THE DEEPEST VALLEYS."
- WHAT?
- TO A LEADER,
HIS SOLDIERS ARE LIKE HIS
FLESH-AND-BLOOD CHILDREN.
THAT'S WHY HIS SOLDIERS
ARE DEVOTED TO HIM
AND WILL FOLLOW HIM TO THE
ENDS OF THE EARTH AND BEYOND.
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS, RIGHT?
- YES.
- PLEASE LISTEN, KAN'U.
IF YOU WERE TO DIE,
NO ONE WOULD BE SADDER
ABOUT IT THAN ME.
- GENTOKU.
- AS YOUR LEADER, I CARE
ABOUT YOU AS WELL, SHIRYU.
AND I WON'T TOLERATE YOU
TWO FIGHTING.
NOW SOMEONE TELL ME
WHO STARTED IT.
- IT'S MY FAULT.
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
- ACTUALLY,
IT'S BECAUSE OF THIS.
APPARENTLY,
WHEN YOU PUT ON THIS NECKLACE,
YOU JUST FEEL LIKE FIGHTING
EVERYONE FOR NO REASON.
- HAKUFU SONSAKU, THAT IS--
- RIGHT?
- OH! THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S GOT ALL THESE WEIRD
MAGICAL POWERS AND STUFF.
- MAGICAL POWERS?
BUT THEN HOW COME NOTHING
HAPPENED TO ME WHEN I PUT IT ON?
- ( sighs )
- OH, I FORGOT. WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WE CAME TO HAVE LUNCH AND MAKE
PEACE BETWEEN OUR SCHOOLS.
- I THOUGHT WE DISCUSSED THIS.
DIDN'T WE AGREE TO HAVE THE
LUNCHEON A WEEK FROM TODAY?
- All: WHAT?!
- AH, IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, THIS SORT OF THING
IS BETTER EARLY THAN LATE.
LET'S ALL CELEBRATE,
TO NEW FRIENDS!
( evil laughter )
- Koukin: HAKUFU!
- UMM, RYOMOU?
I'M SORRY.
YOU WASTED YOUR WHOLE DAY
HERE AT THE CLINIC WITH ME.
I FEEL BAD
TAKING UP ALL OF YOUR TIME.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
EVEN IF WE DIDN'T
FIND ANYTHING NEW TODAY,
WE HAVE TO KEEP TRYING.
YOU CAN'T LIVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE
WITHOUT YOUR MEMORIES.
- THANKS FOR YOUR HELP,
RYOMOU.
- BUT ONCE SHE GETS
HER MEMORIES BACK,
IS SHE GOING TO BECOME
THE OLD HOUSEN RYOFU?
- ( door opens )
- Ryomou: WANT TO EAT
BEFORE WE HEAD BACK?
- Saji: MIGHT I OFFER TO TREAT
YOU TWO LADIES?
BEEN A WHILE,
MOU-CHAN.
HMM.
- SAJI.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
-I KNOW I BARGED IN ON YOU
ALL RATHER SUDDENLY, BIG SISTER.
I HOPE I HAVEN'T
BEEN A NUISANCE.
- Hakufu: OF COURSE NOT.
EVER SINCE YOU CAME,
EVERY DAY IS FUN.
I'M SO HAPPY
WHENEVER CHUUBO IS AROUND.
I JUST HOPE YOU'RE NOT
GETTING TIRED OR BORED OF US.
HMM.  HOW DO I KNOW
WHAT YOUR TRUE FEELINGS ARE?
I KNOW.
I'LL USE THIS NECKLACE!
- Ryuubi: NO, MISS SONSAKU,
YOU MUSTN'T.
OH, NO.
IT'S ALREADY ON HER!
MISS SONKEN?
MISS SONKEN!
- Hakufu: WHOA, CHUUBO,
IS THIS THE KIND OF
GIRL YOU REALLY ARE?