- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( insects chirping )
- Ryuubi: KAN'U.
- OH.
- YOU MUSTN'T DO THAT.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR YOU
TO BE SNEAKING OUT OF BED.
- SORRY. I JUST NEEDED TO GET
OUT AND GET SOME FRESH AIR.
- OH HEY, IT'S MY BOOK.
- OH THIS?
I JUST WANTED TO READ IT ONCE
MORE BEFORE RETURNING IT TO YOU.
- YOU CAN KEEP IT
IF YOU WANT.
- UH, YEAH, BUT WHEN
YOU GAVE THIS TO ME,
YOU WEREN'T YOURSELF.
- WELL, MAYBE-- MAYBE
IT IS TRUE THAT I WASN'T MYSELF
BACK WHEN I GAVE IT TO YOU.
BUT TO BE HONEST, I'D ALWAYS
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE REALLY NICE
IF YOU'D TAKEN THE
TIME TO READ IT.
- YOU DID?
- I MEAN, DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A WONDERFUL THING?
THE ABILITY TO GIVE A BOOK
YOU LOVE TO A PERSON YOU LOVE,
IN THE HOPES THAT
THEY MIGHT LOVE IT TOO?
- THE PERSON YOU LOVE?
- YES!
AND THEN WE CAN GROW
TO BECOME EVEN BETTER FRIENDS.
( soft gasp )
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN THINKING
THAT THE PERSON WHO WAS INSIDE
ME HAD FELT THE SAME EXACT WAY.
- THE SAME EXACT WAY?
- YES.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT SHE SEEMED SO SAD TO ME.
SO I WAS THINKING MAYBE
IT'S THAT SHE JUST WANTED
TO BE FRIENDS WITH SOMEBODY.
- HMM.
- ( both panting )
- ( screams )
- CHUBO!
( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
ENOUGH OF THIS GAME
OF CAT AND MOUSE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN GAME?
WHAT WE'VE HAD ENOUGH OF IS
ALL YOUR CRAZY MAGICAL POWERS!
JUST TURN BACK
TO YOUR NORMAL SELF!
- WHY WOULD I? I'VE NEVER FELT
BETTER IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
EVEN RIGHT NOW I CAN FEEL THIS
POWER COURSING THROUGH MY BODY.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF THE PAIN
FROM BEFORE HAD NEVER HAPPENED.
( laughs )
- WHAT POWER DO YOU MEAN?
FROM MOU-CHAN'S DRAGON?
- SPEAKING OF WHICH...
WHERE IS MISS RYOMOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT!
WHERE DID MOU-CHAN GO?!
- TURN AROUND, SHE'S
STANDING RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- HUH?!
- ( both gasp )
- LOOK.
I THINK RYOMOU WANTS TO PLAY
HER OWN GAME OF CAT AND MOUSE.
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- MOU-CHAN?
- ( yells )
- ( gasps ) BIG SISTER!
WAKE UP!
PLEASE YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP.
GET UP NOW!
- ( footsteps )
UH?
( grunts )
- YOU'RE FIGHTING THE WRONG
PERSON, SHIMEI RYOMOU.
LET'S SEE HOW MUCH STRONGER
YOU'VE REALLY BECOME.
CONSIDER FIGHTING ME
YOUR ULTIMATE
TEST OF STRENGTH.
- ( moans )
WHA-- WHAT THE...?
FUU-CHIN? HUH.
COULD IT BE?
- ( chuckles )
THAT LUNCH AT THE PARK
WAS DELICIOUS.
- AWESOME!
YOU'RE BACK, FUU-CHIN!
- LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT A FEW
MORE PROBLEMS ON OUR HANDS.
- YEAH YEAH, WE REALLY DO.
IT SEEMS LIKE SOMETHING'S
REALLY WRONG WITH MOU-CHAN.
- SO THAT'S IT.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
THAT SHE'S UNDER THE SAME
MIND-CONTROL SPELL THAT
GENPOU SAJI PUT ON ME BEFORE.
- MISS RYOMOU...
HUH?
( screams )
- CHUBO!
- BIG SISTER!
- JUST HURRY UP
AND GO AFTER HER.
SHE'S YOUR SISTER, RIGHT?
- RIGHT!
- COME ON! NO TIME FOR YOU
TO SIT AROUND STARING!
HURRY!
- RIGHT. I'M ON IT!
- ( thinking )
I WISH YOU LUCK.
IF ONLY I COULD HAVE SPENT
A BIT MORE TIME WITH YOU.
OKAY, HOW ABOUT THE TWO OF US
HAVE SOME FUN?
- WE'VE DECIDED WE'RE GOING
BACK TO KYOSHO.
LOOKS LIKE
MOUTOKU'S FINALLY BACK.
- ( rumbling )
- HUH?
OH NO!
- FROM DAY ONE I SUFFERED
HAVING BEEN BORN A NECROMANCER.
SUCH WAS THE DESTINY
I HAD TO BEAR.
FIGHTERS COULD
NEVER UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT IS I HAD
TO GO THROUGH.
LIKE THE MOST PRIMAL
OF SPECIES,
YOU SIMPLY FIGHT EACH
OTHER IN HOPES OF
SHOWING OFF YOUR STRENGTH.
AND IF THAT'S ALL IT TAKES,
I'LL HELP YOU CRUSH EACH OTHER,
UNTIL THERE'S NO ONE LEFT.
YES,
THIS IS THE TERRIBLE DESTINY
I WAS BURDENED WITH.
NOW WITH THE DRAGON'S
MAGNIFICENT POWER
I HAVE FINALLY BECOME
THE TRUE GENPOU SAJI.
AND WITH THIS POWER
I NO LONGER NEED
THE HELP OF ANYONE ELSE.
LOOKS LIKE I'VE CAUGHT
ANOTHER ONE.
I'LL BE WITH YOU
IN A MOMENT.
- HOW DARE YOU DO
THIS TO CHUBO.
- DON'T COME NEAR!
( yelps )
- YOU'D BETTER LET CHUBO
GO RIGHT NOW!
- LET HER GO?
NOT A CHANCE.
IF I DID THAT, THEN I'D HAVE
TO START ALL OVER AGAIN.
ATTACK!
- DAMN YOU!
LET HER GO!
TAKE THAT AND THAT!
AND THAT!
( gasps )
- ( screams )
- HAKUFU!
- GOOD JOB, BIG BROTHER!
NICE CATCH!
- ( groans )
- WAIT, IS THAT...
GENPOU SAJI?
- MM-MM. THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN SHE WAS TRANSFORMED
BY THE POWER
OF MOU-CHAN'S DRAGON.
- RYOMOU'S DRAGON?
NOW I UNDERSTAND
WHY GENPOU SAJI WENT THROUGH THE
TROUBLE OF KIDNAPPING RYOMOU.
- KOUKIN, WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN TO HER NOW?
- HER FUTURE DOESN'T
LOOK VERY GOOD.
IT IS SAID THE POWER
OF THE DRAGON WILL CONSUME
WHOMEVER IT INHABITS.
- THEN YOU'RE SAYING
GENPOU SAJI'S LIFE
IS IN DANGER?
- Chubo: THIS WON'T
SOLVE ANYTHING.
- Chubo: NONE OF THIS WILL
SOLVE ANYTHING FOR YOU.
- OH, BUT IT WILL.
I WASN'T BLUFFING WHEN
I TOLD YOU I'D GET RID
OF EVERY SINGLE FIGHTER
ON THIS EARTH.
- Chubo:
YOU POOR, POOR SOUL.
YOU'RE SO SCARRED BY THE PAINFUL
MEMORIES OF YOUR PAST.
THAT'S WHY YOU
DON'T EVEN REALIZE
THAT YOU'VE BECOME A PUPPET
TO YOUR HATEFUL FEELINGS!
YOU CAN'T CONTROL YOUR FATE.
- ( grunts )
- Chubo: ALL THE FIGHTERS
YOU CLAIM TO LOATHE...
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM
IS DOING THEIR BEST
TO BATTLE THEIR DESTINIES, TO
MAKE THEIR LIVES THEIR VERY OWN.
EVEN WITH THE DRAGON'S POWERS
AND ODDS STACKING AGAINST THEM,
I PROMISE YOU
THEIR NOBLE SPIRITS
WILL NOT SO EASILY
BE EXTINGUISHED.
- SHUT UP!
- ( gasps )
- I THINK I'VE BEEN LECTURED
ENOUGH BY THE LIKES OF YOU.
I'LL HAVE THE DRAGON DEVOUR
ALL THOSE SILLY FEELINGS.
ANY THOUGHTS OF SENTIMENTALITY
WILL BE GONE.
( chuckles )
( huffs )
- OH NO!
WE HAVE DO SOMETHING
TO HELP HER!
- I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
HAKUFU!
- RIGHT!
- WHY'RE YOU HOLDING BACK?
YOU SHOULD BE TERRIFIED.
IF YOU'RE AFRAID,
THEN YOU SHOULD BE SCREAMING.
- Chubo: IT'S YOU.
- ( gasps )
- YOU'VE LOST SIGHT
OF WHO YOU ARE
BECAUSE OF THE DRAGON'S POWER
AND ONE WHO'S LOST SIGHT
CAN'T KILL ME.
- ( grunts )
- CHUBO!
- VERY WELL THEN!
YOU LEAVE ME WITH NO CHOICE
BUT TO START WITH THOSE TWO!
- LET'S DO THIS!
- RIGHT!
- ( all yelp )
- HOLD ON.
WHAT HAPPENED JUST NOW?
- BUT HOW?
MY DRAGON, IT'S...
( moans )
IT HURTS. IT HURTS.
MY HEAD...
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HER?
- MAYBE...
DO YOU THINK IT'S THAT SHE
CAN'T USE HER MAGIC ANYMORE?
- OR PERHAPS SHE'S
JUST NO LONGER ABLE TO
CONTROL THE DRAGON ANYMORE.
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S IT.
THE EFFORT EXCEEDS
HER PHYSICAL CAPABILITIES.
- ( straining ) IT HURTS.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
( screams )
- ( gasps )
- ARE-- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THE DRAGON...
- HUH?
- THE POWER OF THE DRAGON,
I CAN'T FEEL IT ANYMORE.
IT'S COMPLETELY GONE.
IT CAN'T BE.
IT CAN'T BE!
( sobbing )
PLEASE DON'T LET IT BE
GONE FOREVER.
WITHOUT THAT POWER
I'LL BE LIKE BEFORE.
- NO, NOBODY HERE IS GOING
TO HURT YOU ANYMORE, OKAY?
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU DON'T NEED THE DRAGON'S
POWER TO FEEL SAFE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
YOU NEED IN LIFE.
- Hakufu: THAT'S RIGHT!
- Both: HUH?
- THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
YOU'LL EVER NEED
ARE FRIENDS LIKE...
US.
- YOU'D BE MY FRIEND?
- YEP.
I'M HAKUFU SONSAKU.
- AND I'M KOUKIN SHUYUU.
- MY NAME IS CHUBO SONKEN.
WHAT'S YOURS?
- MY NAME IS...
- DON'T YOU DARE INTERFERE!
GENPOU SAJI.
- THERE WE GO. WE FINALLY
HEARD YOU SAY YOUR OWN NAME.
- ( chuckles )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryofu: FOR ME, DEATH WAS
THE PRICE I HAD TO PAY.
BY MY OWN CHOICE
AND WITH MY OWN STRENGTH,
I DID MORE THAN MERELY
LIVE OUT MY PREDESTINED FATE.
I HAD A LIFE OF MY OWN!
AND SO CAN YOU!
DESPITE WHAT YOU THINK
YOU WANT OUT OF LIFE,
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU
TO GIVE UP NOW!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- ( singing continues )
- ( grunting )
- RYOMOU, LISTEN TO ME!
SINCE AS FAR BACK
AS I CAN REMEMBER
I FOUGHT MY DESTINY,
BELIEVING WITHOUT A
DOUBT I COULD CHANGE IT.
AND EVEN IF MY CHANCES
WERE LESS THAN 1%
IT WAS WORTH FIGHTING FOR!
BUT TIME PASSED
AND FEAR CREPT IN
AND I WONDERED,
"IS IT ALL WORTH IT?"
SOME PEOPLE MIGHT SAY
THAT I WASTED MY LIFE,
THAT I WAS TRYING TO
FIGHT AGAINST FORCES
MORE POWERFUL THAN
I COULD IMAGINE,
BUT I DON'T REGRET
ANY OF IT!
PROMISE YOU'LL NEVER
LET ANYONE CONTROL
WHAT YOU DO
WITH YOUR OWN LIFE.
- WHAT'RE YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO TELL ME?
- PROMISE YOU WILL LIVE
AS YOUR OWN HEART DESIRES,
LIVE YOUR OWN LIFE!
- RYOFU.
- MOU-CHAN! FUU-CHIN!
- ( chuckles )
SONSAKU...
I GUESS THIS IS IT.
- ( gasps )
FUU-CHIN.
- IT WAS A LOT OF FUN
BEING HERE WITH YOU.
- HUH?
- ( ragged breathing )
- SEE YA, RYOMOU.
- ( gasps )
PLEASE WAIT!
- Ryofu: GOODBYE.
- ( sobbing )
THAT DAMN FOOL.
WHY'D SHE HAVE TO DIE AGAIN?
I DIDN'T WANT HER TO GO!
- ( no dialogue )
- ( birds chirping )
- Ryofu's voice: THANK YOU.
- ( gasps )
( sobbing )
- Chubo: WELL, I GUESS
THIS IS GOODBYE.
- Hakufu: DO YOU
REALLY HAVE TO GO?
- YES.
I WANT TO STAY, BUT I
PROMISED MASTER CHOUSHOU.
- COME ON! CAN'T YOU SAY
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO?
UH?
- BIG SISTER...
- ( sighs )
( forced laugh )
SAT-CHAN!
- HUH?
- NOW IF ANYONE
EVER PICKS ON YOU,
THEN YOU COME AND TELL ME
RIGHT AWAY, YA HEAR?
I'LL BEAT THEIR ASS
TILL THEY SCREAM LIKE A GIRL.
- ( chuckling )
- Chubo: I WANT TO SAY
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
YOU'VE DONE FOR ME.
MANY THINGS HAPPENED
WHILE I WAS HERE,
- BUT EVERY DAY
WAS SO MUCH FUN. MM.
WELL, GOODBYE.
- Hakufu: NO.
IT'S NEVER BE GOODBYE WITH US.
IT'S "SEE YOU LATER."
YOU'RE ALWAYS SUCH
A SCATTERBRAIN, CHUBO.
- OH MY. I GUESS I REALLY
AM YOUR YOUNGER SISTER.
- RIGHT!
NO MATTER WHAT YOU'LL ALWAYS
BE MY PRECIOUS LITTLE SISTER.
AND THAT'S WHY...
- ( signing in Japanese )
- YOU CAN COME BACK TO VISIT US
ANYTIME YOU WANT!
- ( gasps )
YES!
- Koukin: AND SO ANOTHER CHAPTER
HAS ENDED.
WE'RE ALREADY DASHING ONWARD
IN SEARCH OF NEW TOMORROWS.
WE KEEP ON PUSHING FORWARD
THOUGH WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT LIES AHEAD.
BUT THAT DIDN'T MATTER.
THROUGH IT ALL,
RYOFU TAUGHT US THE IMPORTANCE
OF CARVING OUT
OUR OWN DESTINIES.
AND WHILE OUR FATES
MAY BE TIED TO SOULS
FROM 1800 YEARS IN THE PAST,
WE WILL LIVE OUR OWN LIVES
OF OUR OWN CHOOSING.
WE TAKE PRIDE IN WHO WE ARE
AND WHO WE MAY YET BECOME.
WE ARE FIGHTERS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( vocalizing )
- ( singing in Japanese )