- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY
IS THAT MY NAME
ISN'T CHUBO SONKEN.
- Hakufu and Koukin:
HUH?
- I'M NOT WHO YOU THINK I AM.
I'M NOT ACTUALLY EVEN
YOUR YOUNGER SISTER.
- Both: HUH?
- IT'S TIME YOU KNEW.
MY REAL NAME IS
ACTUALLY SHOUKYOU.
- WAIT.
YOU'RE SHOUKYOU?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KOUKIN?
- THAT MEANS
IF YOU'RE SHOUKYOU,
THEN I'M...
- YOUR DESTINY,
IT'S TRUE.
ONE DAY,
I AM DESTINED
TO BE WED TO MY BETROTHED,
KOUKIN SHUYUU.
- SO YOU TWO--
YOU'RE GOING TO--
WHOA!
IN THE FUTURE,
YOU'RE...
( gasps )
...MARRIED?!
IS WHAT SHE SAID TRUE,
KOUKIN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT MIGHT BE TRUE FOR
THE KOUKIN SHUYUU OF
THE THREE KINGDOMS BACK THEN,
BUT FOR ME HERE AND NOW?
I JUST DON'T--
- I TOTALLY GET IT!
I MEAN, I HAD NO IDEA THAT
YOU WERE INVOLVED
WITH THIS KIND OF PERSON.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I GUESS THERE'S HOPE
THAT ONE DAY
YOU MIGHT BECOME A MAN.
- HEY!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WAS ALWAYS
ACTING LIKE AN IMMATURE KID.
STUPID.
- COME ON!
THERE'S NO REASON TO BE
CALLING ME STUPID.
THE ONE WHO SAYS STUPID FIRST
IS REALLY STUPID.
- YOU KNOW,
SAYING STUPID THINGS LIKE THAT
MAKES PEOPLE CALL YOU STUPID.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?!
- STUPID!
- ( Shoukyou giggles )
- IT MEANS EXACTLY
WHAT YOU THINK IT MEANS.
AHEM.
SO, I GUESS
THE FIRST QUESTION IS:
WHY DID YOU FEEL YOU HAD TO
LIE TO US ABOUT YOUR REAL NAME?
- WELL...
- WHAT BROUGHT THIS UP,
SHOUKYOU?
- I HAVE BEEN DESTINED TO BECOME
THE WIFE OF KOUKIN SHUYUU
SINCE THE DAY I WAS BORN.
MY FUTURE HUSBAND IS OUT THERE.
ALL I WANT IS TO MEET THE MAN
I'M DESTINED TO MARRY.
IS THAT REALLY SO UNREASONABLE?
- OF COURSE NOT.
BUT THE TWO OF YOU ARE
STILL QUITE YOUNG.
SHUYUU IS NOT YET MATURE ENOUGH
FOR SUCH NEWS.
IF HE LEARNS
WHO YOU TRULY ARE,
IT IS QUITE LIKELY
TO FLUSTER HIM INTO FOOLISHNESS.
- EVEN SO, ALL I WANT IS
TO CATCH A GLIMPSE OF HIM,
AND MAYBE THE CHANCE TO SPEAK
WITH HIM FOR A BIT AS WELL.
- ( sighs )
FINE, WE'LL TRY.
I WILL GO TO HIS RESIDENCE,
AND SHALL HAVE A TALK
WITH HIS AUNT GOEI.
- REALLY, MASTER CHOUSHOU?
- REALLY.
HOWEVER,
FOR THIS TO HAPPEN,
YOU MUST NOT MEET SHUYUU
AS SHOUKYOU.
- AND THAT WAS IT.
I'M SORRY FOR LYING,
FOR DECEIVING BOTH OF YOU.
( sobs )
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE NOT MAD AT YOU.
IT'S JUST-- WHY DID YOU SUDDENLY
DECIDE TO TELL THE TRUTH?
( gasps )
- BECAUSE I REALIZE
THAT THERE'S SOMEONE
FAR MORE SUITABLE FOR YOU,
SOMEONE THAT YOU'RE
ALREADY CLOSE TO.
- HUH?  UH.
- HUH?
SOMEBODY CLOSE TO KOUKIN?
WHERE?  WHERE?
WHERE?!
WHERE COULD THIS PERSON BE?
- ( sighs )
- ( giggles )
MISS SONSAKU.
- HOLD ON!
WHAT'S WITH ALL THIS SUDDEN
MISS SONSAKU STUFF OUT OF YOU?
- UH...
-TO ME, YOU ARE AND
WILL ALWAYS BE CHUBO.
YOU ARE MY LITTLE SISTER
AND MY VERY DEAR FRIEND.
I NEED YOU TO KEEP CALLING ME
BIG SISTER HAKUFU
LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO,
OR OTHERWISE,
I'M GONNA GET
TOTALLY CONFUSED.
- SO YOU'RE...
STILL BIG SISTER HAKUFU?
- THAT GOES FOR ME TOO.
YOU'RE STILL CHUBO.
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
- THANK YOU,
BIG BROTHER KOUKIN.
- WELL, I BETTER GET GOING.
- GET GOING WHERE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WAIT.
YOU'RE NOT PLANNING TO--
- I AM.
I'M GOING TO RAKUYO
TO FIND THE REAL GENPOU SAJI.
AND I'LL FIND MOU-CHAN TOO.
- HAKUFU.
I'M COMING TOO.
- KOUKIN, YOU'RE HURT.
- I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
JUST KNOW...
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
I PROMISE.
- KOUKIN.
YOU'RE ACTING
REALLY STRANGE TODAY.
SO WEIRD.
- BIG SISTER,
I'M DEEPLY GRATEFUL
FOR EVERYTHING YOU'VE DONE
TO PROVE YOUR FRIENDSHIP
AND MAKE ME FEEL CARED FOR.
I KNOW THAT BOTH OF YOU CARE
FOR RYOMOU LIKE YOU CARE FOR ME,
AND I WANT THE CHANCE TO SHOW
THAT SHE IS DEAR TO ME AS WELL.
AND THAT'S WHY,
MUCH LIKE BIG BROTHER,
I'D LIKE YOU TO TAKE ME
ALONG TOO.
- NO WAY.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT IT'S DANGEROUS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- HUH?
- CHUBO, KOUKIN,
LET'S DO THIS!
TOGETHER WE'LL HAVE
THE STRENGTH OF 100!
- THANKS, BIG SISTER.
- ( deeply sighs )
WELL, SINCE YOU MADE UP
YOUR MIND,
I DON'T SUPPOSE
THERE'S ANY POINT IN ARGUING.
MY TWO SISTERS ARE
A PIECE OF WORK.
- ( both laugh )
- NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
CHUBO NOTICED THAT SOMETHING
WAS WRONG WITH RYOFU
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE DID.
- WHY ARE YOU GIVING US
THAT WEIRD LOOK?
- WHAT?  THERE WASN'T
ANY KIND OF LOOK.
- Hakufu: ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
LET'S GO DO THIS!
- TO ZHUGE LIANG I PRAY.
IF BY TENTON
I CAN MOVE THE CLOUDS.
FILLING THEM WITH WIND,
SO THAT THEY MIGHT FLY
ACROSS THE SKY.
IF BY CHITON I COULD BURROW
BENEATH THE MOUNTAINS
AND PASS THROUGH THE BOULDERS.
IF BY JINTON
I COULD ERASE MY PRESENCE
AND CHANGE MY FORM.
IF I COULD SEND MY SWORD
FLYING THROUGH THE AIR,
COMMANDING IT TO BRING ME
THE HEAD OF MY ENEMIES,
THEN I WOULD ASK
MY PRAYERS BE ANSWERED.
- ( all panting )
( gasping )
- TON-CHAN!
- SHE'S DANGEROUS!
STAY BACK!
- IS THAT MYOUSAI KAKOUEN?
- LOOKS LIKE HER.
BUT IT SURE DOESN'T
ACT LIKE HER.
- Koukin: SHE'S UNDER THE
INFLUENCE OF GENPOU SAJI.
- Kakouton: WHAT?
- THIS IS ALL GENPOU SAJI'S PLAN
TO DESTROY TRUST IN EACH OTHER.
SHE'S USING HER POWER
TO MANIPULATE OUR FRIENDS.
- I KNOW SAJI.
STUCK-UP, BLOND SON OF A BITCH.
- OH, NO, WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT THAT SAJI.
THIS IS A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
GIRL SAJI,
WHO'S, LIKE, ALL MAGICAL
AND STUFF.
SHE KIDNAPPED MOU-CHAN
AND MADE EVERYONE
AT SATO ACADEMY ACT CRAZY.
AND SHE EVEN POSSESSED ME!
- HUH?
- BUT MAYBE WE SHOULD
TAKE CARE OF HER FIRST.
- LET'S DO THIS!
( grunts )
- TON-CHAN!
- STAY BACK!
( straining )
I'M NOT SAYING
THIS IS THE BEST IDEA,
BUT THAT WITCH--
SHE PUT A SPELL ON MY FRIEND.
AND THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA
IGNORE A FRIEND WHO NEEDS ME.
EVEN IF I HAVE TO RISK
GETTING HURT TO DO SO.
NOW, AS FOR YOU GUYS,
DON'T YOU HAVE A FRIEND
WHO NEEDS YOUR HELP TOO?
- BUT--
- THEN GET MOVING!
BUT DO ME ONE FAVOR.
BEAT THE WITCH SAJI
RIGHT INTO THE GROUND!
- ( gasps )
IT'S ALL WRONG.
DESPITE EVERYTHING,
THEY'RE STILL TRYING TO
HELP EACH OTHER.
- HAKUFU, GO ON AHEAD.
I'LL STAY AND HELP
DEAL WITH THIS.
- KOUKIN.
RYOMOU'S WAITING FOR YOU.
- MM.
LET'S MOVE OUT, CHUBO.
- RIGHT.
BE CAREFUL, BIG BROTHER.
- YOU BE CAREFUL TOO.
- THANKS.
- KAKOUTON!
SO, LOOKS LIKE YOU COULD
USE SOME HELP.
- JUST WATCH YOUR BACK.
OR YOU'LL END UP
GETTING HURT AGAIN!
- ( crying )
I WILL NOT LOSE.
NOT TO ANYONE.
I CAN RELY ON MYSELF.
ONLY IN MYSELF.
MYSELF.
- HEY!  MOU-CHAN!
JUST CALL OUT IF YOU CAN
HEAR ME, MOU-CHAN!
WHERE ARE YOU, MOU-CHAN?!
- THEY'RE HERE.
- MISS RYOMOU!
( echoing )
- FROM THIS MOMENT FORTH,
YOU WILL BECOME A BEAST,
A VESSEL FOR MY RAGE.
IN MY NAME,
YOU WILL SAVAGE THEM ALL.
A BLOODTHIRSTY BEAST
UNTIL YOUR DYING BREATH.
FIGHTERS...
I WISH...
THEY'D ALL...
- Ryofu: JUST DIE.
- ( gasps )
FUU-CHIN!
- FUU-CHIN.
- BIG SISTER, MISS RYOFU IS
BEING CONTROLLED BY SAJI.
- THIS HOSEN RYOFU IS NOTHING
LIKE THE GIRL YOU KNEW.
SHE IS ANGER AND HATRED
INCARNATE,
A LONG DEAD SOUL
RAGING AGAINST HER FATE.
A BEAST THAT WILL
BRING NOTHING
BUT PAIN AND DEATH
TO YOU ALL.
( shouting )
- CHUBO, RUN!
HUH!
( grunts )
( gasps )
( groans )
AAH.
( screams )
- BIG SISTER!
- ( groaning )
FUU-CHIN.
AAH!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( wind gusts )
- ( both gasp )
- LOOK OUT!
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
- FUU-CHIN... WHY?
WHY?!
I DON'T WANNA FIGHT THIS WAY!
STOP IT!
- PLEASE, BIG SISTER,
YOU MUSTN'T DO THIS.
THE MORE YOU LASH OUT IN ANGER,
THE MORE POWERFUL THE ANGER
THAT'S CONTROLLING HER
SOUL IS GOING TO BECOME.
- CHUBO... HELP ME.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?!
I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M SUPPOSED TO STOP HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
- I WILL WATCH AS YOU BREAK
AND REND EACH OTHER.
ALL THE PAIN
THAT I HAVE SUFFERED,
I HAVE BARELY BEGUN
TO UNLEASH IT UPON YOU.
WE'VE JUST BEGUN.
( groaning )
- THE POWER YOU WIELD IS
BEGINNING TO TAKE ITS TOLL
ON YOUR FRAIL PHYSICAL FORM.
TO WIELD THE POWER
TO DESTROY OTHERS,
YOU MUST IN TURN,
DESTROY YOURSELF.
- WHAT OF IT?!
WHY EXACTLY SHOULD I CARE?!
SOON, THE POWER OF THE DRAGON
WILL BE MINE.
AND THEN--
AND THEN I'LL MAKE
THE FIGHTERS SUFFER.
ALL OF THEM.
I'LL MAKE THEM ALL DISAPPEAR.
YOU AND I,
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO WILL REMAIN.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
JUST YOU.
YOU, AND NO ONE ELSE LEFT.
- SO WHAT REASON DO YOU HAVE
TO MATERIALIZE HERE NOW?
- SHIMEI RYOMOU.
I WANT THE DRAGON THAT IS
LYING DORMANT INSIDE OF HER.
- IT IS THE DRAGON'S NATURE
TO CONSUME THE FIGHTER
IN WHICH ITS SPIRIT RESIDES.
THE CORRUPTING POWER
WOULD SPREAD MISFORTUNE
AND BREED DESTRUCTION.
BUT IF IT CAN BE CONTROLLED,
PERHAPS IT COULD BE THE PERFECT
WEAPON AGAINST GENPOU SAJI,
SEALING AWAY THE POWER FOREVER.
- Saji:
THE POWER OF THE DRAGON.
- WATCH ME, OUIN.
WATCH ME AS MY POWER
BRINGS CHAOS AND MISFORTUNE
TO THE FIGHTERS
WHO STAND AGAINST US.
- I THINK YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH,
GENPOU SAJI.
- ( gasps )
- WITH THE WEAKENED STATE
YOU'RE IN NOW,
THE DRAGON'S POWER
WOULD OVERWHELM YOU.
- WHY TELL ME THIS NOW?
- I SUPPOSE IT'S TIME TO BE
HONEST ABOUT A FEW THINGS.
I DIDN'T HELP YOU BECAUSE
I WANTED TO BRING RYOFU BACK.
I THOUGHT OF A WAY TO REMOVE
YOUR POWERS USING RYOMOU,
WHILE SIMULTANEOUSLY
PROTECTING RYOMOU FROM YOU.
- ( exhales )
- THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
WHY ARE YOU LYING TO ME?
YOU PUT ON AN ACT
IN ORDER TO ANGER RYOMOU
AND AWAKEN THE DRAGON.
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED
SINCE THEN,
YOU'RE SAYING IT WAS
ALL PART OF YOUR PLAN?
- YOU POSSESSED THE POWER TO
BRING RYOFU BACK TO LIFE.
I FEARED YOU MIGHT
DESTROY RYOMOU
IN ORDER TO
ACHIEVE YOUR GOALS.
THEREFORE, I PRETENDED
TO COOPERATE
TO STAY CLOSE TO YOU
AND ENSURE
YOU DIDN'T KILL HER.
- BUT YOU PROMISED ME!
YOU SAID
YOU WOULDN'T LEAVE ME!
YOU SAID YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
- THE SOUL OF GENPOU SAJI
BURNS INSIDE OF YOU.
TELL ME,
WHAT GOOD COULD POSSIBLY
COME FROM HURTING OTHERS?
IT'S FOOLISHNESS.
YOU CAN'T HOPE TO CONTROL
PEOPLE'S LIVES
OR THEIR SOULS.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'M GOING TO GO PROVE MY POINT.
- WAIT!
( gasps )
- AAH!
- BIG SISTER!
- AAH.
- NO, YOU HAVE TO
HANG IN THERE!
PLEASE GET UP!
- OH, I WOULDN'T WORRY.
SHE'S NOT GOING TO
GO DOWN THAT EASILY.
- UH...
- ( groaning )
- AAH!  HEY!
HANDS OFF, YOU PERVERT!
- HA!  IT'S FAKE SAJI!
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
- HEY, WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN HIDING?!
THE REST OF US HAVE BEEN HAVING
A REALLY ROUGH TIME, YOU KNOW?!
- THAT'S MY BAD.
SORRY ABOUT ALL THE TROUBLE.
- SO THIS IS MR. SAJI
FROM NANYO?
- THAT'S HIM.
- IF IT'S ALL THE SAME,
I DO KIND OF HAVE A REAL
SERIOUS FAVOR TO ASK OF YOU.
SAVE MOU-CHAN.
AND WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
SAVE THE OTHER ONE.
- WHICH OTHER ONE?
- GENPOU SAJI.
I'M PRETTY YOU'VE MET.
PLEASE, TRY TO WARM HER HEART--
MADE FROZEN BY A CRUEL
AND CURSED FATE.
- SO THAT'S WHO SHE WAS.
- I HAVE FAITH THAT
YOU'RE UP TO THE JOB.
- I'LL TRY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT FUU-CHIN?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT PROBLEM.
IT IS, AFTER ALL,
KIND OF MY MESS TO CLEAN UP.
- HEY, SAJI, YOUR HAIR!
- IT'S NOT SAJI ANYMORE.
MY NAME IS SHISHI OUIN!
- REMEMBER:
SUN TZU TEACHES,
"IF YOU KNOW THE ENEMY
AND YOU KNOW YOURSELF,
YOU NEED NOT FEAR
THE RESULT OF
A HUNDRED BATTLES."
- SO GET GOING,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- RIGHT, FAKE SAJI!
- GO, AND USE YOUR POWER
TO BRING FEELING BACK
INTO HER HEART.
DO WHAT I FAILED TO DO.
SAVE HER SOUL
THE WAY YOU ONCE SAVED MINE.
NOW THEN...
- ( grunts )
- SHUYUU!
- DAMN IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M DOING
MUCH BETTER HERE.
- KAKOUTON,
LISTEN NOW AND OBEY.
- ( groaning )
- Sousou: OH, TON...
- ( gasps )
- ...LOOKS LIKE YOU
FORGOT THE BASICS.
- ( exhales )
WHO SAID THAT?
( gasps )
- IT CAN'T BE.
- LOYAL ONE.
KAKOUEN,
DO YOU KNOW THE SOUND
OF MY VOICE?
- I DO.
- ( shouting )
( grunting )
- DO YOU REMEMBER IT, RYOFU?
DO YOU REMEMBER?
THE TIME WE SPENT TOGETHER?
- ( shouts, grunting )
- I WANT YOU TO KNOW
YOUR PAST AS A FIGHTER.
IF YOU BELIEVE ALL THE TIME
YOU SPENT CHANGING
THAT FATE WAS SO SHAMEFUL,
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU'RE A FIGHTER.
WE MET 'CAUSE WE'RE FIGHTERS.
AND WE LOVED EACH OTHER
AS FIGHTERS.
I THINK IT'S THE SAME
FOR YOU AND RYOMOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, RYOFU?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I WAS BORN
DESTINED TO BE A FIGHTER,
BUT THEN,
I FELL IN LOVE WITH YOU.
AND SOON AFTER REALIZED
I DIDN'T HAVE LONG TO LIVE.
SO I MADE A DECISION.
I CHOSE TO TRUST RYOMOU
TO LOVE YOU.
- WELCOME BACK, RYOFU.
- NO.  NO!
IT'S NOT FAIR.
WHY DOES EVERYBODY
ALWAYS ABANDON ME?
MY POWERS ARE NEARLY ABSOLUTE,
AND STILL IT ALWAYS
TURNS OUT LIKE THIS.
- YOUR POWERS...
SEEM TO BE MISSING
A VITAL PART.
THEY'RE MISSING
THE POWER OF LOVE.
WITH SAJI-- WHATEVER HAPPENED
BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU
DOESN'T MATTER.
NO.
WHAT DOES MATTER IS
HOW CLEAR IT IS IN HIS ACTIONS
THAT HE CARES DEEPLY FOR YOU.
- ( slightly gasps )
- EVERYTHING HE DID,
HE WASN'T TRYING TO
DESTROY YOU.
HE WAS TRYING TO
SAVE YOU.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT
HE CARED ABOUT ME?
- WHAT IS THIS?
IT CAN'T BE.
( gasps )
- ( shrieks )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M SCARED!
THE DRAGON!
( screams )
- WHAT?
- ( screaming )
- Hakufu:
MOU-CHAN!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HER?
- ( whimpering )
PLEASE, YOU HAVE TO HELP ME.
- IS THAT GENPOU SAJI?
- SONSAKU!
STAY AWAY!
THAT'S THING'S DANGEROUS!
( gasps )
- ( chuckling )
- Hakufu: MOU-CHAN!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koukin: WE ARE
FIGHTERS WHO MANIFEST
THE SOULS OF ANCIENT HEROES.
IS OUR PURPOSE MERELY
TO ENDLESSLY FIGHT,
AT THE MERCY
OF DESTINY'S WHIM?
IS THERE ANYBODY OUT THERE
WHO CAN PLEASE TELL US
WHAT IS THE PATH
THAT WE SHOULD FOLLOW?
WHAT WILL OUR FUTURE
HOLD FOR US?
FOR WHAT REASON
DO WE FIGHT?