- ( people screaming )
- Oda: THE WORLD
UNDER WARRIOR RULE.
I AM TRULY THE DEVIL KING,
COME FROM THE SIXTH HEAVEN.
FOR I OPEN THE LID
ON HELL ITSELF.
IMBECILES, PROSTRATE YOURSELVES.
- ( theme song playing )
- WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
WILL ODA'S UNPROVOKED
INVASIONS KNOW NO END?
AND NOW I AM GIVEN NEWS
OF HIS LATEST OUTRAGE,
THAT HE MARCHED HIS ARMY
INTO THE HOMELAND OF HIS
OWN WIFE, THE LADY NOHIME,
AND RAZED IT TO THE GROUND.
FOR THE SAKE OF PEACE IN OMI,
ECHIZEN, AND OWARI,
I HAD HOPED WE MIGHT SERVE
THE CAUSE OF JUSTICE TOGETHER,
THAT WE WERE AS ONE IN BOTH
INTENT AND PURITY OF HEART.
I HAD THOUGHT THE PROOF OF HIS
CHANGE WAS IN SENDING YOU,
HIS FLESH AND BLOOD SISTER,
TO BE MY BRIDE.
I HAD BELIEVED THE DEVIL KING
HAD REGAINED HIS HUMANITY.
OUR PLAN TO ESTABLISH AN ERA OF
HEALTH AND PROSPERITY
WAS THE REASON, I TURNED A
BLIND EYE TO HIS PAST MISDEEDS
AND CALLED ODA NOBUNAGA
BROTHER-IN-LAW.
- I APOLOGIZE, MY LORD NAGAMASA.
IT IS ALL MY FAULT.
- WHY DO YOU DO THAT?
YOU ARE ALWAYS SO MAUDLIN.
HOW MANY TIMES MUST I TELL YOU
TO STOP MISPLACING
BLAME UPON YOURSELF?
- I APOLOGIZE.
- YES, I'VE HEARD THAT
ENOUGH FOR ONE NIGHT.
- MY LORD HUSBAND.
- WHAT IS IT?
- NO MATTER WHAT ALL
OF THIS MIGHT MEAN,
REGARDLESS OF WHAT MAY HAPPEN,
DO NOT DEFY MY BROTHER.
PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU.
- TURN A DEAF EAR TO...
- THAT IS SOMETHING I CANNOT DO.
THOUGH HE IS MY BROTHER-IN-LAW,
I AM STILL THE SWORN ENEMY OF
ALL THOSE WHO WOULD COMMIT EVIL.
- THAT OUGHT TO MAKE
THIS PAINLESS.
- PARDON MY DROPPING IN SO LATE.
- WHO DARES TRESPASS HERE?
IF YOU KNOW YOU
COMMIT THIS EFFRONTERY
TOWARD AZAI
BIZEN-NO-KAMI NAGAMASA,
I SHALL SMITE YOUR EVIL
HEART WHERE YOU STAND.
- SHH, SARUTOBI SASUKE,
SANADA NINJA CORPS.
I FEEL BAD FOR INTRUDING ON
YOUR PRIVATE TIME TOGETHER.
WELL, I'D LIKE TO FEEL BAD.
BUT THE DEVIL KING LEAVES
LITTLE TIME FOR AFFECTION.
- THE TIGER OF KAI SENT YOU.
- I PRESUME YOU
KNOW WHY I'M HERE.
- ASK AS OFTEN AS YOU WISH
AND I SHALL ANSWER THE SAME.
AZAI WILL HAVE NO PART
IN ANY PLOT TO ENCIRCLE ODA.
ODA NOBUNAGA
AND I ARE BROTHERS-IN-LAW
BY VIRTUE OF MY MARRIAGE
TO HIS YOUNGER SISTER,
MY BELOVED ICHI.
MY POSITION SHOULD BE OBVIOUS.
- ENCIRCLE ODA?
- WE ARE AWARE OF LADY
O-ICHI'S FAMILY TIES. EVEN SO...
- ENOUGH OF YOUR PRATTLING.
ONCE I HAVE MADE A DECISION,
I NEVER GO BACK ON MY WORD.
NOW, TAKE YOUR LEAVE QUICKLY,
NINJA OF KAI.
- ODA IS MOVING ON ASAKURA.
- WHAT? IMPOSSIBLE. WE HAVE
A LONG-STANDING PACT
OF STRICT NON-AGGRESSION
WITH ASAKURA.
SURELY, HE WOULD NOT BREAK IT.
- NOBUNAGA IS LITERALLY
NOT HUMAN, HE'S...
- MIND YOUR TONGUE.
YOU WILL NOT
INSULT MY WIFE
WITH SUCH SLANDEROUS
ACCUSATIONS.
I SAY AGAIN. AZAI SHALL NOT
TAKE PART IN YOUR ALLIANCE.
TELL YOUR LORD SHINGEN,
MY DECISION IS FINAL.
- MY LORD.
- MY LORD HUSBAND.
- Sanada: YOUR LORDSHIP,
SANADA YUKIMURA,
AT YOUR HUMBLE SERVICE.
- Takeda: AH, ENTER.
- SIR.
( gasps )
- I AM A MESSENGER OF UESUGI,
MY NAME IS KASUGA, MY LORD.
- AH, SO YOU ARE KASUGA.
IT IS TRULY A PLEASURE,
I AM SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
- SASUKE HAS TOLD ME
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
- HUH?
- BY THE WAY, HAVE THE
TWO OF YOU SET A DATE
FOR THE WEDDING YET?
- A DATE FOR WHAT?
- YOUR LORDSHIP, IT IS A SHAME
I DO NOT SEE SASUKE AROUND.
- ( grunts )
HE HAS NO REASON TO BE.
SASUKE, MASTER SARUTOBI,
SASUKE AND I DO NOT SHARE
SUCH A RELATIONSHIP.
- SASUKE IS CURRENTLY
ON A MISSION MUCH LIKE YOURS.
- I SENT HIM TO VISIT TOKUGAWA
OF MIKAWA AND AZAI OF OMI.
- UH...
- WE HOPE FOR
A TEMPORARY ALLIANCE.
- AN ALLIANCE? SO, YOU ARE
PLANNING A UNITED FRONT
AGAINST THE DEVIL KING?
- PRECISELY, THIS LUDICROUS
"WORLD UNDER WARRIOR RULE"
NOBUNAGA DESIRES,
IS A WORLD RULED
BY FEAR AND CARNAGE.
WE MUST FIRST
PROTECT THIS WORLD
BEFORE WE DESTROY
EACH OTHER OVER IT.
YOU SEEM PUZZLED.
- SIR, WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT YOUR LORDSHIP,
GIVEN YOUR GREAT STRENGTH,
AND THE POWER OF THE
TAKEDA CAVALRY AT YOUR BACK,
I BELIEVE THAT WE ARE
MORE THAN A MATCH
FOR EVEN ODA'S FORCES.
- BUT WE WOULD NOT GO UNSCATHED.
ASSUMING WE DEFEAT ODA, WE WILL
HAVE SUFFERED GREAT CASUALTIES,
LEAVING US INDEFENSIBLE AGAINST
ANY OTHER ARMIES' ATTACKS.
- BUT WE WILL NEVER KNOW
UNLESS WE TRY.
- ( grunts )
- AM I NOT CONSTANTLY
TELLING YOU
TO EXPAND YOUR VIEW? BUFFOON!
- FORGIVE ME, YOUR LORDSHIP,
BUT OTHER THAN LORD KENSHIN,
THE GENERALS OF THE
OTHER LANDS SEEK ONLY
TO PROFIT FROM THE SIDELINES.
WOULD ANY OF THEM EVER
ANSWER YOUR CALL TO ARMS?
- ( grunts )
YOU CONTRADICT YOURSELF, BOY.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY TO ME?
"WE WILL NEVER KNOW
UNLESS WE TRY?"
HEED MY WORDS, YOUNG CUB.
BEFORE YOU ARE ABLE TO
CHARGE THE FOE IN FRONT OF YOU,
FIRST YOU MUST FIX YOUR EYE
UPON THE BROADER HORIZON.
- YES, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- IN TRUTH,
EVEN I HAD HALF GIVEN UP,
AS WE HAD NOT RECEIVED
A SINGLE FAVORABLE REPLY.
UNTIL ONE DAY, NOT LONG AGO,
WHEN I RECEIVED A LETTER.
- A LETTER? FROM WHOM, SIR?
- THE VAGABOND OF MAEDA.
PUTTING HIS WANDERLUST
TO GOOD USE,
HE IS SPENDING TIME
VISITING WITH GENERALS
OF NEIGHBORING LANDS.
THIS MAEDA KEIJI'S PLAN
FOR AN ALLIED ARMY,
WAS IN FACT EERILY
SIMILAR TO MY OWN.
ONCE I ASCERTAINED
THE SINCERITY OF HIS ACTIONS,
I DISPATCHED SASUKE
TO SPEAK WITH THE GENERALS
ON MY BEHALF ONCE AGAIN.
- KASUGA, YES?
- YES, SIR.
- PLEASE INFORM
YOUR LORD KENSHIN
THAT TAKEDA SHINGEN
READILY CONSENTS.
- SIR.
- WITH MAEDA KEIJI
SPURRING HIM TO ACTION,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
WILL LIKELY RUSH
THE ENEMY ON HIS OWN.
WE WILL USE HIM
AS OUR SPEARHEAD.
AND QUICKLY ADVANCE
TO REINFORCE HIM.
FOR THAT TO WORK,
I WOULD HAVE TOKUGAWA
JOIN US AND IDEALLY,
I WOULD HAVE AZAI
PIN ODA FROM BEHIND.
THOUGH CERTAINLY, IT WILL
REQUIRE A HEARTRENDING CHOICE
ON AZAI'S PART.
WHAT IS IT, YUKIMURA?
- YOUR LORDSHIP, I,
I AM MERELY FEELING A
RENEWED SENSE OF ADMIRATION
FOR THE DEPTH
OF YOUR FORETHOUGHT.
YOU FIGHT NOT ONLY FOR THE
GOOD OF KAI OR YOUR ARMY,
BUT FIRST AND
FOREMOST TO PROTECT
THIS LAND OF THE RISING SUN
FROM THE MENACE
OF THE DEVIL KING.
I AM HUMBLED THAT YOU
WOULD THINK TO ENTRUST ME
WITH SUCH MATTERS
OF GRAVE SECRECY,
ALONGSIDE THIS HONORED
ENVOY FROM ECHIGO.
- LISTEN WELL, YUKIMURA.
DO NOT DOUBT THE IMPORT
OF YOUR PRESENCE.
BE A MAN OF FAITH, EVER FORGING
UPWARD TO EVEN GREATER HEIGHTS.
- YOUR LORDSHIP, I SWEAR I SHALL
TAKE YOUR WORDS TO HEART.
- GOOD.
- THE TIGER OF KAI,
THIS IS WHO SO OCCUPIES MY
LORD KENSHIN'S THOUGHTS.
MY LORDS, I SHALL TAKE MY LEAVE.
- SARUTOBI SASUKE, REPORTING IN.
- WELCOME HOME.
- MY LORD, I RETURN IN SHAME.
I JUST COULDN'T GET
THROUGH TO THEM.
NEITHER AZAI NOR TOKUGAWA
WILL JOIN WITH US.
- THEN SURROUNDING THE DEVIL
KING IS NO LONGER AN OPTION.
- SO, SHE WAS HERE, THEN.
SHE COULD HAVE STUCK
AROUND A LITTLE WHILE.
- HER STORY WAS A BIT
DIFFERENT FROM YOURS.
- HMM?
- MISTRESS KASUGA DENIED
SHE WAS YOUR BETROTHED.
QUITE FERVENTLY.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE LADIES LIKE I DO, MASTER.
I'M SURE SHE WAS JUST
HIDING HER EMBARRASSMENT.
- THAT WAS EMBARRASSMENT, HUH?
Huh, I GUESS WOMEN REALLY
ARE COMPLICATED CREATURES.
- WE ARE ABOUT TO RUSH
INTO THE BATTLE OF OUR LIVES
AGAINST THE DEVIL KING.
THIS COULD'VE BEEN OUR LAST
CHANCE TO SEE EACH OTHER.
- SASUKE, DO NOT
SAY SUCH THINGS.
YOU MUST LIVE THROUGH
THIS AT ALL COSTS
AND BRING MISTRESS
KASUGA HAPPINESS.
- OH, I'LL BE FINE, WHEN IT'S
WORK, I TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
IT'S HER I'M MORE WORRIED ABOUT.
ANYWAY, MASTER.
JUST MAKE SURE IT'S YOU
WHO GETS THE DEVIL KING'S HEAD.
- RIGHT NOW, THAT'S THE ONLY
WAY I CAN REPAY HIS LORDSHIP.
HOWEVER...
THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME
IN MY LIFE,
THAT WHEN FACED
WITH A POWERFUL OPPONENT,
I DID NOT FEEL A BURNING
WITHIN MY HEART.
IN THE DEVIL KING, ODA NOBUNAGA,
ALL I FELT WAS UNFATHOMABLE
DARKNESS AND STAGNATION.
THERE IS ONE MAN
I TRULY WISH TO FIGHT.
- BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE.
- THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
AFTER THE DEVIL KING
HAS BEEN PUT DOWN,
I SWEAR WE SHALL
HAVE OUR DECISIVE BATTLE.
- IT SEEMS HE'S FOUND HIMSELF
QUITE THE ADMIRER.
- ONE-EYED DRAGON.
- WHAT'S UP, LADY-KILLER?
- UESUGI'S FORCE SHOULD BE
PASSING THROUGH SHINANO BY NOW,
MAKING THEIR WAY TO KAI.
- HUH. LOOKING FOR A REMATCH
OF KAWANAKAJIMA?
- NO, THEY'LL INVADE
OWARI ALONGSIDE TAKEDA
USING US AS THEIR SPEARHEAD.
- DON'T THINK POORLY OF ME.
EVEN IF I HADN'T SPURRED
YOU ON, YOU WOULD'VE...
- DON'T STRESS OUT. KOJURO
ALREADY SAW THROUGH ALL THAT.
THERE COULD BE A MILLION
OTHERS AT MY HEELS,
BUT I WILL TAKE THE
DEVIL KING'S HEAD.
- WAIT AND SEE.
- ( chuckles )
- THEN I SWEEP THROUGH
AND SEIZE THE REST
WITH TAKEDA AND
UESUGI RIGHT THERE,
I'LL CRUSH THEM FIRST.
- ( screams )
- KIND OF TOO BAD THOUGH,
I WANTED TO SAVE MY FUN
WITH HIM UNTIL THE END.
- ( horse neighing )
- ( gasps )
- TAKEDA'S NINJA SPOKE TRUE.
BROTHER-IN LAW,
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- MY HUSBAND, PLEASE...
- ICHI, YOU MUST FLEE AT ONCE.
THOUGH I DOUBT EVEN THE DEVIL
KING WOULD KILL HIS OWN SISTER,
I WON'T TAKE THAT CHANCE.
- Azai's soldier: READY.
- AKECHI MITSUHIDE?
- WELL, LORD AZAI NAGAMASA.
TOWARD WHAT FIELD OF
BATTLE MIGHT YOU BE HEADED?
- I LEAD MY TROOPS TO ECHIZEN,
IN PURSUIT OF AN ARMY
OF DARK INTENT,
WHO WISH HARM UPON
MY SWORN FRIEND, ASAKURA.
- AND WHERE, MASTER AKECHI,
MIGHT YOU BE HEADED?
- ( chuckles )
BY ALL APPEARANCES, IT WOULD
SEEM THIS "ARMY OF DARK INTENT"
YOU REFERENCE IS US.
- YOU WOULD BREAK A PACT
MADE BETWEEN WARRIORS
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING.
- I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO DEEM YOU TRUE EVIL.
- MY LORD, WAIT.
- ICHI, PLEASE. GO NOW.
AKECHI MITSUHIDE, LISTEN WELL,
FOR AZAI HEREBY DECLARES
OUR ALLIANCE VOID.
SOLDIERS OF JUSTICE,
FOLLOW ME TO VICTORY.
IN THE NAME OF PEACE,
LET US ERADICATE EVIL.
- IS THAT WISE? YOUR WIFE
IS LORD NOBUNAGA'S SISTER.
IF YOU WERE TO SEVER
THE BLOOD BOND,
WHO WOULD BE THE ONE TO GRIEVE?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ICHI? RUN.
- I CANNOT RUN, MY LORD.
- I'LL MAKE YOU A DEAL, AZAI.
YOU CAN ASK
THE DEVIL KING YOURSELF.
- Oda: NAGAMASA, TO WHAT
PURPOSE DO YOU STAND
IN MITSUHIDE'S PATH?
- MY ANSWER, LORD BROTHER,
IS A QUESTION FOR YOU.
WHY DO YOU BREAK THE
PACT YOU MADE WITH ME
AND SEEK TO DESTROY ASAKURA?
THE PROSPERITY THE
AZAI ENJOY TODAY,
IS OWED TO THE SUPPORT ASAKURA
HAS SHOWN US SINCE DAYS OF OLD.
AND YOU ARE A BLOOD RELATIVE
OF MY BELOVED WIFE.
BOUND BY HONOR TO BOTH,
MY HEART AS A WARRIOR,
NO AS A HUMAN BEING,
DEEMS YOU EVIL AND URGES ME
TO DRAW MY SWORD.
- THIS WAS, THIS WAS MY FAULT.
- YOU SIMPERING IMBECILE.
ALL RIGHT. ODA WILL
NOT ATTACK ASAKURA.
- THANK YOU. I AM GLAD YOU
RECONSIDERED, BROTHER-IN-LAW.
- YOU WILL DO IT FOR ME.
- ( gasps ) I'M SORRY, MY LORD,
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- MITSUHIDE.
- SIR.
- WHAT ARE YOU...
- DO NOT MOVE!
- DEAR BROTHER.
- LORD ODA, WHAT IS THIS?
- AZAI NAGAMASA, YOU WILL
DESTROY ASAKURA IN MY STEAD.
- WHAT? THIS IS INSANITY.
YOU INSULT ME WITH THREATS
OF UNSPEAKABLE HORROR.
OUR VOW OF BROTHERHOOD
IS MEANINGLESS.
I HAVE BUT ONE COURSE
AGAINST SUCH EVIL.
I AM SWORN TO DESTROY IT.
- I AM THE DEVIL KING
OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN,
I TRANSCEND HUMANITY.
ONLY DEATH AWAITS
THOSE WHO DEFY ME.
- FAREWELL, LORD NAGAMASA.
CAN YOU FORGIVE ME?
- ICHI! NO!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
- ( laughs ) SO MUCH
FOR THE "MAN OF JUSTICE."
- LORD NAGAMASA.
- LITTLE BROTHER,
I CAN BE FORGIVING.
BUT THERE WILL NOT BE
A SECOND TIME.
- IF YOU ABIDE THE
TERMS OF OUR NEW PACT,
WE SHALL RETURN THE
LADY O-ICHI TO YOU.
- IN TRUTH, IT IS YOU
WHOM I WOULD MOST
LIKE TO FACE THIS DAY.
- LIKEWISE.
THIS IS ALL OR NOTHING.
IN DISPELLING THE
THREAT OF THE DEVIL KING,
WE ENSURE A FUTURE FOR ALL.
LET US FIGHT FOR THE SAKE
OF A TIME WHEN ALL MAY CHOOSE
THEIR OWN PATH WITHOUT RESERVE.
- ( cheering )
- YOUNG CUB.
I SHALL BE COUNTING ON YOU.
- SIR, I WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
- Narrator: TAKEDA SHINGEN
CONTINUED TO SEND LETTERS
ASKING FOR THE DEFECTION
OF TOKUGAWA,
WHO WAS ALLIED WITH
ODA AND CHARGED
WITH WATCHING THE EASTERN LANDS.
IF IEYASU CAN BE CONVINCED,
AND USING DATE'S INDEPENDENT
ADVANCE AS THEIR SPEARHEAD,
THEIR MANEUVER AGAINST ODA
WILL BE ALL THE STRONGER.
HOWEVER, IF HE
DECLINES YET AGAIN,
THEY WILL NOT ONLY HAVE
TO STAVE OFF TOKUGAWA,
BUT ALSO PREVENT
HIM FROM SENDING
A DETACHMENT AGAINST DATE.
- Tokugawa: "WHILE I AM SORRY
TO TROUBLE YOU IN THIS WAY,
I ASK FOR YOUR AGREEMENT."
"BUT IF IT IS NOT TO BE..."
- ( grunts ) DAMN IT,
LORD SHINGEN.
YOU MUST KNOW
THE POSITION I AM IN.
YOU ARE FULLY AWARE
THAT I AM BOUND
BY AN ALLIANCE WITH ODA
AND CANNOT COMPLY.
WHY MUST YOU
CONSTANTLY BEDEVIL ME?
I ONCE SUFFERED A CRUSHING
DEFEAT BY TAKEDA'S HAND,
AND I WILL SOMEDAY
VINDICATE MY HONOR.
IF HE INTENDS TO
CHALLENGE ME BY FORCE,
TOKUGAWA IEYASU, GLADLY ACCEPTS.
- SO, ONE-EYED DRAGON,
WHO WAS THAT WARRIOR YOU
MENTIONED THE OTHER DAY?
- OOPS.
- AH.
- ONCE YOU'VE DEFEATED
THE DEVIL KING,
THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE
YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
- YEAH, YOU COULD SAY THAT.
- I COULD SEE YOUR HEART.
- HUH?
- THERE'S A LOOK ABOUT YOU
WHEN YOU THINK OF HIM.
- HUH?
- IT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A FIGHT AND A WAR.
- ( chuckles )
- MITSUHIDE.
- WHY IS YOUR ARMY
NOT AT YOUR BACK?
- DO YOU INTEND TO TRY
AND NEGOTIATE?
- INDEED. IT IS MY HOPE
I MAY CONVINCE ASAKURA
TO SURRENDER TO ODA
WITHOUT BLOODSHED.
- OR PERHAPS, YOU HOPE
TO SWAY HIM TO THE SIDE
OF THE EASTERN GENERALS,
WITH THEIR PATHETIC LITTLE PLOT.
SURELY, THEY INVITED YOU
TO JOIN THEM BUT KNOWING YOU,
I'M CERTAIN YOU MOST
OBSTINATELY REFUSED.
- NOR WILL I JOIN THEM NOW.
- AS THEIR SPEARHEAD,
OSHU'S ONE-EYED DRAGON AND
HIS ARMY ARE CLOSING IN FAST,
HOPING TO TAKE
THE DEVIL KING'S HEAD.
- ONE-EYED DRAGON?
- TOKUGAWA IS MOVING
TO HOLD BACK TAKEDA
AND UESUGI AT NAGASHINO.
IF DATE GETS PAST THEM,
IT WILL BE PROBLEMATIC.
AT THE MOMENT, I BELIEVE
THAT IS MORE PRESSING
THAN ASAKURA.
YOU MUST KNOW WHY I HAVE
REVEALED THIS ONLY TO YOU.
YOU MUST SHOW HONOR IN
BATTLE FOR LORD NOBUNAGA
TO ACCEPT A PEACEFUL
END WITH ASAKURA.
AND SHOULD HE NOT,
LADY O-ICHI'S LIFE WOULD
HANG IN THE BALANCE.
- HE WOULDN'T.
- I AM STRUCK BY YOUR UNDYING
FAITH IN THE CAUSE OF JUSTICE.
THAT SAID, THIS IS ABOUT
ALL I CAN DO FOR YOU.
- THEN I, AZAI NAGAMASA,
SHALL BE A SHIELD AND REPEL
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
BUT AFTER WHICH,
I DO INTEND TO RESUME
MY COURSE WITH ASAKURA.
- UNDERSTOOD. I SHALL
CONVEY YOUR MESSAGE.
- MY DEEPEST GRATITUDE.
- I AM GLAD THAT
IN SOME SMALL WAY,
I AM ABLE TO HELP YOU CARRY
OUT JUSTICE, AZAI NAGAMASA.
- Narrator: THE CURRENT
OF THESE TURBULENT TIMES
WAS ABOUT TO SHIFT IRREVOCABLY.
THOSE WHO WOULD CARVE
OUT THEIR OWN PATH.
THOSE BEING TOYED WITH.
THOSE RESIGNED ONLY TO FATE.
EACH OF THEIR DESTINIES
WOULD CROSS BLADES
IN A FIGHT FOR SUPREMACY.
- SOLDIERS OF JUSTICE, FALL IN.
PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
THE AZAI ARMY SHALL NOT REST
UNTIL THE ONE-EYED DRAGON,
DATE MASAMUNE, IS OBLITERATED!
- ( theme song playing )
- Tokugawa: FINALLY, NEXT
TIME WILL BE OUR TURN
IN THE SPOTLIGHT.
TADAKATSU, ATTACK CONFIGURATION.
ANNIHILATE THE ENEMY.