- Narrator: AFTER THE BATTLES AT
NAGASHINO AND SHITARAGAHARA,
THE INJURED DATE MASAMUNE AND
HIS ARMY HAD TAKEN SHELTER
WITH TAKEDA IN KAI, WHEN
TRAGEDY STRUCK WITHOUT WARNING.
THE VILLAIN OF THE WARRING
STATES, MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE,
TOOK DATE'S YOUNG
RETAINERS HOSTAGE.
AS RANSOM, HE DEMANDED
MASAMUNE'S SWORDS.
THE SIX DRAGON CLAWS.
AS WELL AS TAKEDA'S
FAMILY TREASURE.
THE ARMOR THAT NEEDS NO SHIELD.
KATAKURA KOJURO HEADED OFF ALONE
TO THE RUINS OF THE GREAT TEMPLE
WHERE MATSUNAGA AWAITS HIM.
WHILE SANADA YUKIMURA,
BURNING WITH RIGHTEOUS FURY,
RIDES HOT ON HIS HEELS.
- HAND THE RANSOM OVER TO US.
- THE HOSTAGES WILL
BE DELIVERED LATER.
- SINCE YOU'RE DREAMING,
LET ME PUT YOU TO SLEEP.
COME ON.
- ( grunting )
- THEY'RE NOT SO TOUGH.
LONG AS THEY'RE NOT
ACTING TOGETHER.
- THE DEATH GOD CORPS USES
ANY AND ALL MEANS.
- WE FINISH MATTERS
SWIFTLY AND QUIETLY.
- ( choking ) THAT'S...
- MESMERIZING INCENSE.
- NO NEED TO WORRY.
- YOUR ARMY IS NO
DIFFERENT FROM US.
- YOU CAN JUST REPLACE
WHAT YOU LOSE.
- LIKE HELL WE CAN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( Matsunaga laughing )
THIS IS GETTING
SURPRISINGLY INTERESTING.
I HEARD THE ONE EYED
DRAGON WAS WOUNDED,
TAKING SHELTER IN
THE LAND OF KAI.
I THOUGHT IT A
GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
DATE'S SIX DRAGON CLAWS
AND TAKEDA'S LEGENDARY ARMOR.
THESE ARE BOTH TREASURES
I HAVE LONG COVETED.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW MY GUESTS
WOULD BE DATE'S MEN.
THOUGH, IN RETROSPECT,
YOUR APPEARANCES SHOULD
HAVE GIVEN YOU AWAY.
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
- YOU CAN'T PICK A FIGHT WITH
OSHU AND JUST GET AWAY WITH IT.
- ( stomach rumbling )
- I'M HUNGRY.
- Matsunaga: I HEAR THE TIGER OF
KAI IS PROVIDING AID AND SHELTER
TO ALL THOSE
INJURED AT NAGASHINO.
BE THEY FRIEND OR FOE.
THAT WILL SOON BE REVEALED
FOR THE HYPOCRISY IT IS.
TO WILLINGLY GIVE UP THE ARMOR,
A FAMILY TREASURE,
FOR A CLAN WHO MAY WELL
BE YOUR ENEMY TOMORROW.
NO LORD OF ANY DOMAIN
WOULD DO SUCH A THING,
LET ALONE FOR MEN
AS EXPENDABLE AS YOU.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA KILL US,
JUST DO IT.
- DO YOUR WORST,
WE'RE NOT AFRAID TO DIE.
- ( laughs ) I WOULD. BUT IT
SEEMS THE DRAGON'S RIGHT EYE
HAS HASTENED HERE IN PLACE OF
YOUR POOR, CYCLOPTIC MASTER.
- ( gasping )
- Yoshinao: BOSS KATAKURA?
- Matsunaga: YOU SEE
WHAT I MEAN? INTERESTING.
IF I ADD DATE'S MOST TRUSTED
TACTICIAN TO MY COLLECTION,
EVEN TAKEDA, WHO MUST CERTAINLY
HAVE IGNORED YOUR PLIGHT,
WILL BE FORCED TO
INVOLVE HIMSELF.
AN UNENVIABLE POSITION,
ALL BECAUSE HE TOOK
PITY ON THE DATE
IN THE NAME OF A HASTY ALLIANCE.
- Samanosuke: BOSS KATAKURA
WOULD NEVER BE SO CARELESS.
BESIDES, OSHU HAS NEVER
FORMED AN ALLIANCE WITH ANYBODY.
- IT MAY AS WELL HAVE,
GIVEN RECENT EVENTS.
YOU MEN SEEM AWFULLY
FRIENDLY WITH THEM.
OR WAS THERE SOME OTHER REASON
YOU WERE GUARDING
THE KAI BORDER IN PLACE
OF TAKEDA'S OWN MEN?
- WE WERE REPAYING
THEIR HOSPITALITY.
- TAKEDA'S FOOD
WAS REALLY GOOD.
- TENSIONS WILL SURELY
RISE OVER WHETHER OR NOT
TO OFFER UP THE ARMOR IN
ADDITION TO THE DRAGON'S CLAWS.
BUT PERHAPS SUCH PETTY
SQUABBLES WILL BE PUT ASIDE
TO ADDRESS THE MORE LOOMING
THREAT, ODA NOBUNAGA.
A GRAND ALLIANCE FORMED
TO PROTECT THE LAND
THEY SO RECENTLY FOUGHT OVER.
FROM THE DEVIL KING,
WHO WOULD RAIN DEATH AND
DESTRUCTION ACROSS THE WORLD.
IT IS BUT A FARCE.
SHARING PLOYS AND STRATEGIES
MAY SEEM BENEFICIAL NOW.
BUT WHEN THE INEVITABLE CLASH
COMES BETWEEN DATE AND TAKEDA,
WHAT THEN?
YOU HAVE NO NEED
TO GRIEVE, GENTLEMEN,
FOR YOU HAVE PROVED
INVALUABLE IN SHOWING THEM
HOW FOOLISH THEY TRULY ARE.
THE SADLY FLEETING LIVES
YOU THREE WERE BLESSED WITH
WILL HAVE SERVED A PURPOSE.
REST EASY, NOW. WHEN DEATH
COMES, IT WILL END QUICKLY.
- ( horse whinnying )
- YOU PUSH YOUR HORSE ALMOST AS
HARD AS YOU PUSH YOURSELF.
UH, MASTER?
- GET SOME REST. GOOD WORK
ON THIS LONG JOURNEY.
- AND THE ARMOR THAT
NEEDS NO SHIELD?
- DO NOT WORRY ABOUT IT.
MASTER KATAKURA, MAY I
FIND YOU UNHARMED.
- ( both grunting )
- RUN AWAY, IT IS YOUR
MEANS TO SURVIVAL.
- CRY OUT LOUD, IT IS THE
BLOSSOM OF LIFE.
- ACCEPT YOUR FAILURE,
IT IS YOUR FINAL THOUGHT.
- ( grunting )
( groaning )
( gasping )
- ( yelling )
- ( gasping ) NO, I BREATHED IT.
- ALREADY? IT'S NOT SO BAD
AFTER YOU GET USED TO IT.
- HOW ARE YOU STILL STANDING?
- IF YOU COME AT ME,
YOU WILL DIE.
THAT WOULD RUIN OUR PLANS.
HOWEVER, THIS WILL
BE AN ENDING OF SORTS.
( yelling )
I WILL BRING YOU DOWN!
- THOSE ARE...
- THEY WERE THE MIYOSHI THREE.
- ( sniffing )
WELL, AT LEAST THEIR
CHEAP TRICKS DIDN'T WORK
AGAINST THE DRAGON'S RIGHT EYE.
- HE CAME ALL THIS WAY
BEARING THE RANSOM,
AND STILL THEY TRY TO KILL HIM.
- HE HAD TO HAVE BREATHED
IN A LOT OF THIS STUFF.
MATSUNAGA WILL HAVE HIM
AT A DISADVANTAGE.
- MASTER, WE SHOULD HURRY.
- RIGHT.
- ( breathing heavily )
( coughing )
DAMN, I INHALED TOO MUCH OF IT.
MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE!
- GOOD EVENING, I HAVE BEEN
AWAITING YOUR ARRIVAL.
I MUST SAY I HAD HOPED YOU WOULD
BE BROUGHT TO ME AS A CORPSE.
BUT I SEE YOU ARE NOT
TO BE UNDERESTIMATED.
- I, KATAKURA KOJURO,
AM NOT CALLED THE DRAGON'S
RIGHT EYE FOR NOTHING.
- BOSS KATAKURA.
- SO SORRY, BOSS,
WE WERE CARELESS.
- LISTEN, SIR,
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
WE'D LOVE TO BE RESCUED,
BUT BIG BOSS'S SWORDS ARE...
- Katakura: THIS WILL ALL BE
OVER SOON. DO NOT GIVE UP HOPE.
- THIS IS A SURPRISE,
THAT YOU ACTUALLY BROUGHT THE
SIX DRAGON'S CLAWS HERE?
- Katakura: I BELIEVE YOU MADE
YOUR DEMANDS CLEAR.
- Matsunaga: THE ONE EYED DRAGON
IS A RARE MAN INDEED.
THAT HE WOULD HAND OVER
HIS PRECIOUS SWORDS
TO SAVE THREE COMMON SOLDIERS.
- DO NOT PRESUME WE
ARE LIKE OTHER CLANS.
IN THE DATE ARMY THERE
ARE NO COMMON SOLDIERS.
- ( all gasping )
IF THE DAY COMES WHEN WE
ARE ABANDONED IN THE FIELD,
WE WILL BE READY FOR IT.
- I SEE. WHY THEN, WITH THE FATE
OF THE ENTIRE LAND IN JEOPARDY,
HAVE YOU LET YOURSELF BECOME
CAUGHT UP IN THIS TRIVIAL MATTER
AND COME ALL THIS WAY?
IF THERE WAS EVER A TIME
TO ABANDON THE RANK AND FILE,
I WOULD THINK NOW MIGHT BE IT.
- THAT'S EASY. THIS IS NOT
WHERE THEY WERE MEANT TO DIE.
WE FORMED THIS CLAN OF WARRIORS
IN RESPONSE TO THESE
VIOLENT TIMES.
I FULLY EXPECT US
TO SUFFER CASUALTIES.
HOWEVER, I WON'T LET
ONE MAN DIE IN VAIN.
THAT IS THE WAY OF THE DATE.
AND THE WILL OF LORD MASAMUNE.
- BOSS, YOU CAN'T.
- PLEASE, NO.
- ( grunts )
THEY'RE YOURS, FOR THE MOMENT!
- BOSS KATAKURA!
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
- THE SOUL OF DATE,
IN HIS HANDS?
- NOW THESE ARE
MY DEMANDS. FIGHT ME.
IF I WIN, YOU WILL RETURN BOTH
THE HOSTAGES AND THE SWORDS.
IF YOU CAN FIGHT.
- ( chuckling )
THIS SHOULD PROVE AMUSING,
BUT IT IS NOT ENOUGH.
- WHAT?
- AS YOU SAID, I WAS QUITE
CLEAR IN MY DEMANDS.
WITHOUT BOTH TREASURES,
I WILL NOT NEGOTIATE.
- THIS IS ALL THE DATE
CLAN HAS TO OFFER.
IF YOU WANT THE TIGER OF KAI'S
ARMOR, GO BARGAIN WITH HIM.
- ( scoffs ) AS I THOUGHT,
THOUGH TAKEDA BRIEFLY
WELCOMED YOU INTO HIS HOME,
HE WOULD NOT GO SO FAR AS TO
OFFER UP HIS PRIZED POSSESSION.
- Sanada: HOLD! HOLD, I SAY!
- ( gasps )
- IF YOU WANT TAKEDA'S
ARMOR, HERE IT IS.
- SANADA.
- MY NAME IS SANADA
GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
I COME AS PROXY TO HIS
LORDSHIP TAKEDA SHINGEN.
BEHOLD, THE ARMOR THAT
NEEDS NO SHIELD,
TREASURED ANTIQUITY
OF THE TAKEDA FAMILY.
I INVITE YOU, LORD MATSUNAGA,
TO VERIFY ITS AUTHENTICITY
FOR YOURSELF.
- I NEVER IMAGINED
BOTH TREASURES
WOULD COME TOGETHER SO EASILY.
BUT NOW THAT I HAVE THEM,
I BELIEVE IT'S THE END.
- KATAKURA!
- SASUKE!
- ( rumbling )
- ( screaming )
- ( laughing )
- ( gasping )
( groaning )
BASTARD.
- YOU TOOK QUITE A BEATING.
FOR A ONE EYED DRAGON,
I CANNOT IMAGINE ANY OPPONENT
MORE FORMIDABLE
THAN HIS OWN RIGHT EYE ATTACKING
ONLY ON HIS RIGHT SIDE.
- IT'S NOTHING TO LAUGH AT.
- BUT HE MADE SURE TO AVOID
DIRECT HITS
TO YOUR GUNSHOT WOUND.
A RARE AND TRUSTWORTHY
MAN INDEED.
- WHATEVER.
YOU SENT SANADA AFTER HIM,
I TAKE IT?
THE ARMOR THAT WAS HERE,
IT'S YOUR FAMILY'S
MOST PRIZED...
- IT IS NEEDED ELSEWHERE
RIGHT NOW.
A MAN WHO CAN DO SOMETHING,
YET CHOOSES TO DO NOTHING,
CAN NEVER BE A MAN
WHO ACHIEVES GREATNESS.
BEFORE LONG, WE'LL BID FAREWELL
TO THESE TURBULENT TIMES,
AND IT WILL BE YOU YOUNG MEN
WHO CARRY ON
AND DEFINE THE ERA TO COME.
- ( scoffs )
- HMM?
- YOU SAY THAT,
BUT YOU'RE THE KINDA GUY
WHO'S GONNA BE THROWING
HIS WEIGHT AROUND
FOREVER OR AM I WRONG?
- NO, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE ME, ALL RIGHT.
( laughing )
MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE
IS THE ONLY GENERAL
WHO HAS FACED ODA IN BATTLE,
AND BEEN ALLOWED TO CONTINUE
BREATHING AFTERWARDS.
THIS COULD MEAN
HE'S UNDER ODA'S COMMAND
AND THE DEVIL KING
ORDERED HIM TO CREATE
SOME SORT OF DIVERSION FOR US.
THAT SEEMS UNLIKELY, THOUGH.
- WHY YOU SAY THAT?
- MATSUNAGA DOES
NOT TAKE ORDERS.
- THEN WHY DID ODA
LET HIM LIVE?
- I COULD NOT SAY
FOR CERTAIN BUT,
PERHAPS, WHEN HE FOUND
A RARE CUCKOO BIRD,
HE FANCIED KEEPING IT IN A CAGE.
REST WELL FOR NOW,
ONE EYED DRAGON.
THE WORLD STILL HAS
GREAT NEED OF YOU.
- TAKEDA, OLD MAN,
I WILL PAY YOU BACK FOR THIS,
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
- AFTER WE DEFEAT
THE DEVIL KING
WE CAN FIGHT EACH OTHER
ALL THE WAY TO KYOTO.
I KNOW SOMEONE ELSE WHO
WISHES THAT AS WELL.
- ALL RIGHT.
- LIFE, DEATH.
ALL THINGS REPEAT THIS CYCLE
OF BEING BORN AND BEING BROKEN.
IF YOU KNOW THAT EVERYTHING
IS TEMPORARY,
DO NOT RESIST WHAT YOU DESIRE,
BUT TAKE IT, APPRECIATE IT.
AND IN THE END, DESTROY IT AS
FREELY AS YOU WISH.
- MATSUNAGA!
- YOU'RE FREE TO GO, BOY.
THE MEN YOU CAME TO SAVE
ARE NO LONGER.
FIGHTING ME WILL
DO YOU NO GOOD.
WELL, DON'T YOU LOOK TO
BE IN A FOUL MOOD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE SO UPSET.
I OBTAINED THAT
WHICH I DESIRED.
THAT IS REALLY ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
- DAMN YOU, MATSUNAGA.
NOW I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO
OPEN THE GATES OF HELL.
- KATAKURA!
- YOU CLEARLY FEEL A
NEED TO TAKE MY LIFE.
SO BE IT, TAKE IT AS
YOUR DESIRE DICTATES.
IT IS THE WORLD'S ONLY TRUTH.
- ( men yelling )
- ( grunting )
- NEVER BEFORE HAVE I FOUGHT
ANYONE LIKE THESE MEN.
I SENSE NOTHING EVEN RESEMBLING
FIGHTING SPIRIT IN THEM.
- THAT'S BECAUSE MATSUNAGA
IS PAYING THEM.
HE CAN'T POSSIBLY HAVE
ANY LOYAL RETAINERS.
- ( men yelling )
- MATSUNAGA, YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
A CHILD THROWING A TANTRUM.
IT'S TIME TO SEND YOU TO BED.
- I HATE TO RUIN YOUR MOMENT,
BUT HOW DO YOU POSSIBLY THINK
YOU CAN WIN IN YOUR CONDITION?
- ( coughing )
- THE INCENSE OF
AGONIZING DEATH.
A SECRET PREPARATION
I AM FOND OF.
IT GROWS QUITE LETHAL
WHEN COMBINED WITH THE POISON
YOU BREATHED EARLIER.
YOU TWO CANNOT WIN!
- KATAKURA!
- NOW THAT COULD'VE GONE BETTER.
- SASUKE!
- WERE YOU HURT?
- PLEASE, WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO HERE?
THOUGH, IT DID GET
A BIT DICEY.
- ( swords clanking )
- NEITHER THE DRAGON
NOR THE TIGER
CAN AFFORD TO HOLD THE TIPS
OF THEIR TAILS TOO DEAR.
AGAINST A DEVIL WHO
DEVOURS ALL IN HIS SIGHT,
THEY'LL FIND IT
DIFFICULT TO SURVIVE.
MUCH LESS SEIZE THIS COUNTRY
FROM HIS BLOODY TALONS.
EVEN AGAINST ME, A WITHERED,
GREEDY OLD HERMIT,
YOU HAVE NO CHANCE OF VICTORY.
- I AM SICK OF YOUR
POMPOUS RAMBLING.
- ( yelling )
- Sarutobi: MASTER KATAKURA!
- THAT SMOKE HAS THE ANTIDOTE,
BREATHE IN DEEP.
- ( inhaling deeply )
- YOU'RE MINE NOW, MATSUNAGA.
IN THE PITCH BLACK NIGHT,
A SINGLE RAY OF LIGHT!
- ( screaming )
- IT'S A SHAME,
BUT SOMEDAY YOU WILL FADE
FROM THIS WORLD AS WELL.
FOR IN THE END, WE ALL
RETURN TO NOTHING.
- Katakura: WE WILL NOT
JUST FADE AWAY.
THOUGH THERE'S NO WAY TO
KNOW HOW LONG IT MAY LAST.
WE WILL LEAVE OUR MARK
ON THIS WORLD.
- ( laughing )
- THERE IS NO TREASURE YOU CAN
TAKE WITH YOU TO NIRVANA.
- YOU NEEDN'T WORRY. THAT ISN'T
WHERE YOU GO FROM HERE.
BUT I'LL MEET YOU IN HELL.
- YES, YOU WILL.
A BRIEF FAREWELL THEN,
RIGHT EYE OF THE DRAGON!
- Katakura: I AM IN YOUR DEBT.
- NO, I AM AS DISAPPOINTED
AS YOU MUST BE.
- I'M SO SORRY.
IT WAS ALL I COULD DO TO GET OUT
OF THERE IN ONE PIECE MYSELF.
- Sanada: THOSE ARE...
- Sarutobi: MASTER KATAKURA!
- MATSUNAGA!
- DON'T YOU EVEN THINK
YOU CAN KILL US SO EASILY.
- YEAH. WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
- THE BIG BOSS' SWORDS?
YOU CAN'T HAVE 'EM.
- ( chuckles )
YOU GUYS.
- BOSS KATAKURA!
- WHERE IS THE BASTARD?
- AW, DON'T TELL US...
- IS IT OVER ALREADY?
- IT IS.
- ( all groaning )
- I'M STILL HUNGRY.
- OH, MAN.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
- BOSS KATAKURA,
WE'RE SO SORRY.
- WE'RE SO ASHAMED, SIR.
- YOU GUYS DID WELL.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
SAID IT, BOSS KATAKURA.
- THIS ISN'T THE PLACE WHERE
WE'RE MEANT TO DIE.
- NOT UNTIL THE BIG BOSS
CONQUERS THE WHOLE COUNTRY.
- YEAH, THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
- Magobei: THAT WAS
SO HARROWING.
I SWEAR, I THOUGHT
I'D WASTE AWAY.
- YOU WERE LOOKING AT ME
LIKE I WAS FRESH MEAT.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- ( all laughing )
- THERE'S THE REAL TREASURE.
- Oda: SO, MATSUNAGA
IS DEAD, YOU SAY.
- Nohime: REGARDLESS, IT WAS
ONLY BY YOUR INDULGENCE
THAT HE WAS PERMITTED TO
LIVE IN SECLUSION THIS LONG.
MY LORD KAZUSANOSUKE,
WHY DID YOU PERMIT HIM
TO LIVE FOR SO LONG?
- BECAUSE I FOUND HIM
INTERESTING.
OH, YES. WHAT HAS MITSUHIDE
GOTTEN UP TO?
- MY LORD,
HE HAS MADE ARRANGEMENTS TO
CRUSH THE ALLIANCE
OF THE EASTERN LANDS.
HE IS BEGINNING WITH MIKAWA.
- WELL, THIS WILL BE FUN.
- ( theme song playing )
- Uesugi: MY MOST
BEAUTIFUL BLADE.
PLEASE CONTINUE YOUR
GRACEFUL DANCE.
NEXT TIME AND FOR
ALL TIME TO COME.
MAY BISHAMONTEN'S DIVINE
PROVIDENCE BE WITH YOU,
MY SWEET,
AS WELL AS MY HEART.