- Narrator: AT THE BATTLE
AT NAGASHINO,
THE ODA ARMY FROM OWARI
DELIVERED A CRUSHING BLOW
TO THE EASTERN LANDS.
THE DEVIL KING THEN ADVANCED
HIS ARMY TO THE FAR SOUTHERN END
OF THE LAND OF
THE RISING SUN.
AND COMMENCED HIS INVASION
OF THE ISLAND OF KYUSHU.
- YE'VE ACCEPTED OUR SURRENDER,
BUT STILL YOU TRY AND MASSACRE
THE REST OF US?
NO, SIR. I WILL NOT ABIDE
YOUR BOORISH ACTIONS.
- YOU OLD FOOL,
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK I AM?
- I'LL HAVE TO SHOW YOU
THE STUBBORN PRIDE OF SATSUMA.
- THIS WAS INEVITABLE.
- ( grunting )
- ( gun firing )
- ( groaning )
WELL, ISN'T THIS A REAL
KICK IN THE TEETH.
I S'POSE I'LL HAVE TO LEAVE
THE REST TO THE YOUNG'UNS.
- MAY YOUR SOUL SCATTER
TO THE WINDS OF DESTRUCTION.
- Narrator:
HAVING GAINED A FOOTHOLD
ON THE SOUTHERN TIP OF KYUSHU,
THE ODA ARMY PROCEEDED NORTH.
DEFEATING FIRST HYUGA,
THEN HIGO AND SOON...
- THAT COULD NOT
HAVE BEEN EASIER.
BURN IT ALL TO THE GROUND!
- ( theme song playing )
- YOUR WOUND FROM NAGASHINO
SEEMS TO BE ON THE MEND.
- YEAH, I COULD GO AFTER THE
DEVIL KING'S HEAD AT ANY TIME.
- I'M RELIEVED YOUR INJURIES DID
NOT PROVE TO BE GRAVE.
- SURE, NO THANKS TO YOU.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, KOJURO?
WANNA GO ANOTHER ROUND?
- SIR, I WILL BE YOUR SPARRING
PARTNER WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
- LORD MASAMUNE...
- WHAT'S UP?
- ONCE YOU HAVE DEFEATED
THE DEVIL KING
AND SUCCEEDED IN SEIZING
THE COUNTRY,
I, KOJURO, AM PREPARED TO
FACE THE CONSEQUENCES.
- HUH?
- NO MATTER THE REASON,
I STILL TURNED MY
SWORD AGAINST YOU, SIR.
WHATEVER PUNISHMENT
YOU DEEM APPROPRIATE...
( gasps )
- MAN, YOU KEEP
SPEWIN' THAT CRAP,
I'M GONNA HAVE TO CHOP
YOU UP RIGHT HERE.
- YES, LORD MASAMUNE.
- Sanada: THIS IS...
WHAT BEAUTIFUL
CRAFTSMANSHIP, LORD.
I AM MOST GRATEFUL
FOR THIS BOON.
- BY THE WAY, YUKIMURA,
I'M MOST CURIOUS TO
HEAR YOUR THOUGHTS
WITH REGARDS TO
THE RECENT INCIDENT.
- SIR, FOLLOWING OUR BATTLE
AGAINST MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE,
I WAS REMINDED OF SOMETHING YOU
TELL ME AT EVERY OPPORTUNITY.
A WISE LESSON I LEARNED.
"PEOPLE ARE THE STONE WALLS.
PEOPLE ARE THE CASTLE."
IF I MAY BE SO BOLD, SIR.
IN A WORD,
PEOPLE ARE OUR
GREATEST TREASURE.
MASAMUNE CARES
ABOUT HIS RETAINERS,
AND, IN TURN,
MASTER KATAKURA AND THE OTHER
RETAINERS HAVE PLEDGED
THEIR VERY LIVES TO
THEIR LORD'S SERVICE.
SWEARING TO SURVIVE TOGETHER
UNTIL HE RULES THE LAND.
WHAT'S MORE, IF IT WILL LAY THE
FOUNDATION TO THAT END,
THEY ARE PREPARED TO
DIE AT ANY TIME.
IN THIS RESPECT, THEY ARE NO
DIFFERENT FROM THE TAKEDA.
WHAT WE CALL TREASURE
IS ONE AND THE SAME.
I WAS UNABLE TO BRING BACK
THE ARMOR THAT NEEDS NO SHIELD.
REGRETTABLE AS THAT IS,
YOU HAVE NOT REPRIMANDED ME
AND I THOUGHT THIS
MAY BE THE REASON.
- EXACTLY RIGHT.
- YOUR LORDSHIP.
- YUKIMURA.
ONCE WE'VE DEFEATED THE
DEVIL KING, WHAT WILL YOU DO?
- SIR, NO MATTER WHERE
THEY ARE BORN,
NO MATTER WHERE THEY ARE RAISED,
PEOPLE ARE PEOPLE,
JUST LIKE US.
I, YUKIMURA,
WILL SERVE UNDER YOU
AS YOU RULE THIS LAND
OF THE RISING SUN,
AND I SHALL WIELD THE
SPEAR YOU HAVE GIVEN ME
WITH ALL MY MIGHT,
SO A DAY MIGHT COME
WHEN ALL PEOPLE
FORM A STONE WALL TOGETHER.
- WELL SAID, YUKIMURA.
- THANK YOU, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- YOUR...
- Sarutobi: YOUR LORDSHIP.
TOKUGAWA IEYASU
HAS BEEN KILLED.
IT WAS AKECHI MITSUHIDE.
WHEN TOKUGAWA FORMALLY
BROKE HIS ALLIANCE WITH ODA,
AKECHI APPEARED AS
THE DEVIL KING'S PROXY
AND CUT DOWN THE UNARMED
TOKUGAWA WITHOUT HESITATION.
- ( screaming )
- TADA, KATSU...
- ( laughing )
- ( sighs )
- HUH?
- LORD IEYASU.
SUCH DISAPPOINTMENT
HIS LOYAL RETAINERS
MUST BE SUFFERING NOW.
SUCH HEARTACHE.
( crying )
- THEN THAT MEANS AKECHI
IS NOT TAKING PART
IN NOBUNAGA'S INVASION
OF KYUSHU.
- ACCORDING TO REPORTS,
IT'S NOT JUST HIM.
TWO OTHERS HAVE BEEN
CONSPICUOUS IN THEIR ABSENCE,
ODA'S WIFE, NOHIME AND
AN ARCHER NAMED RANMARU.
- WHILE THE BULK OF HIS
FORCES ATTACK KYUSHU,
IT IS POSSIBLE HE DISPATCHED
THOSE OTHER THREE
AS ASSASSINS AGAINST
US. AS OUR FORCES ARE STILL
RECOVERING AND REGROUPING
AFTER NAGASHINO.
- CRUSH THE EASTERN ALLIANCE.
AND TAKE US DOWN ONE BY ONE.
- IN THAT CASE, WHO'LL BE THEIR
NEXT TARGET, OLD MAN TAKEDA,
YOURS TRULY, OR, MAYBE...
- LORD KENSHIN.
I'VE SENT HIM WORD.
- HMM.
- NOT SINCE THE REPORT OF ODA'S
DEFEAT OF SHIMAZU OF SATSUMA,
HAS ANOTHER MESSENGER COME
FROM THE TAKEDA CAMP.
- I FEEL SO USELESS.
IF I WERE OUT THERE,
I COULD BE REPORTING BACK TO YOU
DAILY WITH NEWS OF THE WORLD.
- GIVEN THE TIGER OF
KAI'S EARNEST WARNING,
IT CANNOT BE HELPED
RIGHT NOW.
- SIR.
- ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
I HAVE BEEN GRANTED
THIS UNEXPECTED PRIVATE
TIME WITH YOU.
AND I AM FORCED TO
REALIZE JUST HOW HARD
I MUST HAVE DRIVEN
YOU IN THE PAST.
ONLY NOW THOUGH,
AFTER BEING WITH YOU
NIGHT AND DAY, DO I SEE IT.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME, KASUGA.
- DO NOT THINK THAT.
I HAVE DEVOTED MYSELF TO
YOUR SERVICE AND PROTECTION,
LORD KENSHIN.
IT IS MY SWORN DUTY.
EVEN NOW, IF YOU WOULD
BUT ORDER IT,
I WOULD MAKE HASTE TO
WHEREVER YOU WISHED.
PLEASE, MY LORD, MAKE USE OF
ME WHENEVER YOU HAVE NEED.
- THANK YOU, KASUGA.
TRULY, THIS IS HOW ONE
MIGHT IMAGINE UTOPIA.
- OH, YES.
SITTING HERE WITH YOU,
THESE VIOLENT TIMES AND THE
MENACE OF THE DEVIL KING,
SEEM LIKE DISTANT DREAMS.
- AS LONG AS YOU ARE BY MY SIDE,
NO MATTER WHERE WE ARE,
IT WILL BE A PLACE OF
CALM AND PEACE.
- SO CLEAR AND PURE.
- ( gasping )
- LIKE A FLOWER
OR A WILLOW.
YOU SHAME ALL NATURE.
- ( gasping )
- AT MY SIDE UNTIL
THE END OF TIME.
- ( moaning )
LORD KENSHIN,
I AM UNWORTHY OF SUCH WORDS.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- BY NOW, THE DEVIL KING
HAS MOST CERTAINLY DEFEATED
ALL OF THE SMALLEST
AND WEAKEST DOMAINS.
I IMAGINE HE HAS
BURNED THEM TO THE GROUND,
MAKING ALL OF KYUSHU HIS.
- ( gasps )
LORD KENSHIN!
WHO ARE YOU?
- TAKEDA ARMY. SANADA NINJA
CORPS, I SERVE SARUTOBI SASUKE.
MY NAME IS ISAGI.
- I DON'T KNOW YOU.
WHICH VILLAGE ARE YOU FROM?
- LORD KENSHIN,
A WORD IN PRIVATE.
- ANSWER MY QUESTION!
- KASUGA.
- YES, SIR.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, KASUGA?
- NO.
- DELIVER YOUR
MESSAGE THEN, NINJA.
- LORD TOKUGAWA IEYASU HAS
PASSED ON FROM THIS WORLD.
- ( lightening crackling )
- IS THAT SO?
RETALIATION FROM THE
ODA FACTION, I TAKE IT?
- IT IS AS YOU HAVE SURMISED.
AS SOON AS HE WAS OUTNUMBERED
IN THE BATTLE AT NAGASHINO,
HE BROKE THEIR ALLIANCE.
IT WAS RETRIBUTION
FOR HIS RASH ATTEMPT
TO JOIN FORCES WITH
YOU AND TAKEDA.
- NOW, MY LORD,
YOU WILL SUFFER THE SAME!
( gasps )
- LORD KENSHIN!
- A WOMAN WHO USES
WESTERN FIREARMS.
YOU ARE THE DEVIL
KING'S WIFE, KICHO.
- TRULY THE WAR GOD. IT SEEMS
YOU WILL NOT PERISH SO EASILY.
- ( grunting )
YOU'RE MINE!
- BE GONE. BEFORE MY SWORD
REACHES YOUR THROAT.
- FOR THOSE WHO WISH
ILL ON MY LORD HUSBAND,
THERE IS ONLY DARKNESS.
- WE CARRY OUT HEAVEN'S WILL
IN BISHAMONTEN'S NAME.
- A THOUSAND PARDONS.
( gasps )
- ( gun firing )
- ( grunting )
- ( metal clanking )
- YOU BITCH!
- LORD KENSHIN!
- DO NOT WORRY,
I AM FINE.
HOWEVER, I CANNOT BELIEVE
SHE CAME HERE ALONE.
- HA! I GOTCHA!
- ( grunting )
I PITY YOU, DEVIL SPAWN.
- CARELESS!
- LORD KENSHIN!
- ( gasping )
- UESUGI KENSHIN
HAS BEEN LAID LOW.
- KENSHIN, MY LORD.
- MY LORD...
- NO, NO!
- ( Sanada grunting )
- Sarutobi: MASTER.
I'M GONNA MAKE A QUICK
TRIP TO ECHIGO.
- DIDN'T YOU?
- YEAH, I'VE SENT THREE OF
MY MEN OVER THERE ALREADY.
BUT I'VE STILL GOT A BAD
FEELING ABOUT THE WHOLE THING.
- WELL, THEN,
YOU BE CAREFUL, SASUKE.
- YOU DO THE SAME, MASTER.
OR YOU WON'T BE READY FOR BATTLE
WHEN THE CRUCIAL MOMENT COMES.
- I KNOW.
- THIS AIR OF FINALITY, I HOPE
IT'S JUST THE MISERABLE WEATHER.
- MY LORD!
( panting )
- Takeda: WHAT?
THE DRAGON KING'S DIKE?
- THE WATER LEVEL IS RISING
BEFORE OUR EYES.
THE DIKE LOOKS READY TO
CRUMBLE ANY MOMENT.
IF WE DO NOT ACT QUICKLY,
THEN NEARBY VILLAGES
AND FIELDS WILL BE...
- HMM.
- Narrator: THE DRAGON KING'S
DIKE IS A LEVEE BEING BUILT
AT AN ELEVATED AREA
CALLED THE DRAGON KING'S NOSE,
WHERE THE MIDAGAWA AND
THE KAMANASHIGAWA MEET.
TAKEDA SHINGEN HAS SPENT
MANY YEARS ON ITS CONSTRUCTION.
IN ORDER TO PROTECT THE
VILLAGE OF KAI FROM FLOODING.
- ( Takeda urging horse )
WHOA! WHOA!
- GATHER EVERYONE
FROM THE VILLAGE.
- RIGHT!
- ( dike creaking )
- MY LORD!
- HOW GOES?
- IT SEEMS TO BE HOLDING
FOR NOW, BUT EVEN SO, MY LORD,
IT JUST SHOULD NOT BE POSSIBLE
FOR THE DIKE TO BE SO WEAK.
- I HATE TO THINK IT, SIR.
BUT SOME OF THE MEN ARE SAYING
IT MAY HAVE BEEN SABOTAGED.
- FOR NOW, WE MUST PREVENT
ITS COLLAPSE AT ALL COSTS.
- MY LORD!
- OVER HERE.
- HUH?
- ( grunting )
( yelling )
HURRY, MEN!
IT IS STILL NOT TOO LATE!
- MY LORD.
- FOLLOW OUR LORD'S EXAMPLE!
- OVER HERE!
COME ON!
- ( all grunting )
- ( chuckling )
- ( dike creaking )
- AKECHI MITSUHIDE!
( yelling )
IT SEEMS THE
FOOL OF OWARI TOLD YOU
TO USE ANY MEANS NECESSARY
TO ELIMINATE YOUR ENEMIES.
OR PERHAPS...
- ( laughing )
THOUGH IT DRANK OF
IEYASU'S BLOOD JUST RECENTLY,
MY BLADE, SAKURAMAI IS
THROBBING INCESSANTLY.
THE ONLY WAY FOR IT TO BE
APPEASED IS TO DEVOUR YOU.
WHAT IS WRONG, TIGER OF KAI?
PLEASE, ALLOW ME A SMALL
TASTE OF YOUR PUNISHMENT.
DEVASTATION SUCH THAT IT
WILL SHATTER BONE IN AN INSTANT.
IT SHOULD BE SIMPLE
TO DELIVER SUCH A BLOW
TO THE CROWN OF MY HEAD.
AH, OF COURSE.
IF YOU WERE TO
WIELD YOUR WEAPON NOW,
YOU MIGHT ANNIHILATE ME.
BUT YOU MAY WELL DESTROY
YOUR PRECIOUS DIKE,
WHICH YOU WENT TO SUCH
GREAT LENGTHS TO CONSTRUCT.
IN FACT, YOUR MIGHTY AXE
WOULD UNDOUBTEDLY LEAVE
NO TRACE OF IT.
( laughing )
HOWEVER,
NOW IS NOT THE TIME TO BE
CONCERNED BY SUCH THINGS, IS IT?
- Sanada: YOUR LORDSHIP,
FORGIVE MY LATE ARRIVAL.
WE HAVE BROUGHT MATERIALS
TO REINFORCE THE DIKE.
IS THAT...
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- YUKIMURA, YOU MUST
SAVE THE DIKE.
- BUT, SIR.
- DO IT, BOY.
IF IT COLLAPSES, THIS
ENTIRE AREA WILL BE DECIMATED.
THAT CANNOT HAPPEN.
- SIR!
- ( creaking )
- NOW'S OUR TIME
TO REPAY TAKEDA.
- SHOW 'EM HOW WE DO IT.
- All: YEAH!
( all grunting )
- MASAMUNE, LOOK.
- AKECHI, HERE? THE BASTARD.
- I MUST MOVE THIS
BATTLE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
BUT IT IS CLEAR
HE WILL NOT PURSUE ME,
AND WILL TAKE ANY CHANCE TO
DESTROY THE DIKE.
WHAT DO I DO?
( grunting )
- ( men exclaiming )
- DAMN IT!
- SHIT! NO!
- ( men screaming )
- MASTER YOSHINAO!
MASTER SAMANOSUKE!
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- ( laughing )
- ( groaning )
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- I WISH I HAD MORE
TIME TO SAVOR IT.
BUT THE SENSATION WAS
MOST EXQUISITE, TIGER OF KAI.
- AKECHI MITSUHIDE!
- SICK FREAK! YOU WILL NOT
BE WALKING AWAY FROM HERE.
- SO, YOU LIVE AFTER ALL,
ONE EYED DRAGON.
- ( theme song playing )
- Takeda: OF THE FIVE ELEMENTS,
NONE IS SUPERIOR OVER THE REST.
THE MOON WAXES AND WANES.
YUKIMURA, BE ALWAYS FLEXIBLE,
LIKE THE WATER,
WHILE YOUR SPIRIT BURNS
LIKE A FLAME.
RISE ABOVE AND SHOW
THE MAN YOU ARE.