- THIS BELONGS
TO MASTER KATAKURA.
- WHY THE LONG FACES,
DRAGON MAN?
- TOYOTOMI KIDNAPPED
MY SECOND-IN-COMMAND.
BUT NOW THIS BASTARD,
MATSUNAGA, HAS HIM.
NOTE SAYS HE'S WAITING
FOR ME UP AHEAD.
- WHAT, IS HE AFTER
YOUR SIX SWORDS AGAIN?
- Samanosuke:
HOW IS HE EVEN ALIVE?
- OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA,
THESE GUYS ARE WITH YOU FOR NOW.
ATTACK OSAKA LIKE YOU WANTED.
I'LL JOIN YOU
ONCE I TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- Soldiers: BIG BOSS!
- Yoshinao:
WHAT IF YOU NEED BACKUP?
- NOT SO FAST.
- WHAT'S UP?
- HE'S A SLY ONE,
THAT TREASURE-HUNGRY CUR.
- NO SHIT.
SO, YOU KNOW HIM THEN?
- OL' MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE.
SUFFICE IT TO SAY,
WE'VE EXCHANGED UNPLEASANTRIES
A TIME OR TWO OUR OWN SELVES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU COULD DO WORSE
THAN HAVE CHOSOKABE MOTOCHIKA
FIGHTING AT YOUR SHOULDER.
MARK ME, I AIN'T INSINUATING
YOU CAN'T TAKE HIM
BY YOUR LONESOME,
I'M JUST SAYING
IT'D BE QUICKER THIS WAY.
BESIDES, TOYOTOMI'S
GOT AN EYE TO THE HORIZON
FOR YOU AND YOURS.
BUT HE'S NOT SAVVY
TO THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA
BEING ALIVE AND KICKING.
LOOK, OUR TEAMING UP
LIKE THIS IS A RARE CHANCE
TO SURPRISE THAT GORILLA,
PUNCH A HOLE IN HIS DEFENSES.
I'D HATE FOR US TO GO
OUR SEPARATE WAYS
JUST 'CAUSE MATSUNAGA
REARED HIS UGLY HEAD.
SO WHAT SAY YOU, TOUGH GUY?
- ALRIGHT, YOU SOLD ME.
LET'S DO IT!
- Matsunaga:
ONE-EYED DRAGON OF OSHU,
YOU'LL SOON ARRIVE.
OF THAT, I HAVE NO DOUBT.
TO THINK THAT I WILL
SLAY THE DRAGON
WITH THE MOST
EPHEMERAL OF WEAPONS--
DECEPTION, WELL-PLAYED.
- ( theme music plays )
- NO USE, GUYS.
THEY'RE JUST TOO TOUGH!
EVERYBODY RUN FOR IT!
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
RETREAT!  RETREAT!
- GOOD WORK, MUSASHI.
NOW REEL THEM IN.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME
FOR AN UNCERTAIN SOUL.
- ALRIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S HAVE AT THEM!
- ( shouting )
- YOU LIKE THAT?
I CALL IT,
"MY SIGNATURE BAIT AND BASH!"
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
TAKE YOUR BEAT DOWN LIKE MEN!
COME ON, THEY'RE GETTING AWAY!
- THIS RETREAT PATTERN...
BEHIND THEM, THAT'S...
THE MORI ARMY!
- MUSASHI, COME BACK!
- THEY'RE BARELY WORTH
THE TROUBLE OF KILLING.
NOTHING BUT REMNANTS
AND WEAKLINGS.
USHER THEM ONWARD,
MY CHILDREN OF THE SUN!
- ( battle cries )
- Miyamoto:
THAT'S NOT FAIR,
YOU COPIED MY MOVE!
COME UP WITH YOUR OWN STRATEGY,
WHY DON'T YOU?!
- LORD SHIMAZU,
WE ARE AWAITING YOUR ORDERS.
- MORI CAME, JUST LIKE
I CALLED IT.
- LEAVE THEM ALONE!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?!
RAISING YOUR SWORD
AGAINST THE UNARMED,
YOU DARE TO CALL
YOURSELVES WARRIORS?!
- DON'T JUDGE ME!
DAMN IT!
I JUST WANT TO GO
BACK TO MY FARM!
- I WANT TO SEE
MY WIFE AGAIN!
- Takeda:
YUKIMURA,
OUR OPPONENTS ARE STILL MEN.
AS YOU WIELD YOUR SPEARS,
DO NOT EVER FORGET THAT.
- BUT YOUR LORDSHIP,
THAT IS ALL I CAN THINK OF.
MY OPPONENT'S HUMANITY
FILLS MY MIND
UNTIL THESE SPEARS
ARE NUMB IN MY GRASP.
I SHOULDN'T BE HAVING
THIS DILEMMA.
BUT INDECISION TAKES HOLD
OF MY SOUL AND I AM HELPLESS.
I STAND IN BATTLE
LIKE A MAN TRANSFIXED.
PLEASE, GUIDE ME, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- ( screams )
- MASTER YUKIMURA!
- AN ARMADA, YOU SAY?
STORMING THE BEACH?
BUT WHAT ABOUT LORD SHIMAZU?
HE'S ALL ALONE
ON THE SOUTHERN SHORE
RECUPERATING FROM HIS WOUNDS.
- COMPANY, EH?
LONG AS YOU'RE HERE,
MAY AS WELL GET TO KNOW YOU.
WELCOME TO SATSUMA!
COME AND GET ME, BOYS.
IF YOU AIN'T TOO YELLOW!
- LORD SHIMAZU!
SO THAT'S HIS
FAMOUS JIGEN STYLE.
THIS IS AS FAR INTO SATSUMA
AS YOU'RE GETTING!
- I THOUGHT TURNING
THEIR SIMPLEMINDED TACTICS
AGAINST THEM WOULD BE
MORE THAN SUFFICIENT.
BUT THIS RAGTAG BUNCH
KNOWS HOW TO FIGHT.
A SECOND TOYOTOMI DETACHMENT
IS SURELY EN ROUTE
FROM THE NORTHERN END
OF KYUSHU RIGHT NOW.
I'M SURE THEY HAVE ORDERS
TO CRUSH ALL THEY FIND HERE.
INCLUDING ME.
GO FORTH MY SACRIFICIAL PAWNS.
THE BLOOD YOU SHED THIS DAY
FUELS YOUR LORD'S ASCENDANCE.
- Bekunosuke: WHAT THE--
LOOKS LIKE HE STILL FIGHTS
AS DIRTY AS EVER!
- Soldier: HOLY...
- Chosokabe: TIME TO FLY,
YOU SONS-OF-BITCHES.
- BUT, WE CAN'T JUMP THAT!
- ONLY ONE WAY TO KNOW
FOR CERTAIN, RIGHT?
- DAMN STRAIGHT!
- LET'S TAKE HIM OUT.
ARE YOU READY?
- I WAS BORN READY, DRAGON MAN.
- YOU MUST BE MATSUNAGA.
THOSE BOYS OF MINE YOU KIDNAPPED
SAY YOU WERE A CRAPPY HOST.
- LONG TIME NO SEE, OLD MAN.
YOU DIDN'T REALLY THINK YOU WERE
SHUT OF ME, NOW DID YOU?
- IT SEEMS I'M IN LUCK.
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
AND THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA.
- WHERE THE HELL'S KOJURO?
- A THOUSAND PARDONS, BOY.
BUT THE RIGHT EYE OF THE DRAGON
ISN'T ACTUALLY HERE.
- ( screams )
- I APPLAUD YOUR DEDICATION.
- Takenaka: LORD MATSUNAGA
DEIGNED TO LEAVE KATAKURA HERE.
ONE OF THE DEAR BOY'S
PERSONAL EFFECTS
WAS ALL THE OLD TRICKSTER
REQUIRED.
A CONVENIENT DEVELOPMENT, THAT.
ONCE THE COUNTRY LAY
AT YOUR FEET,
I INTEND TO BRING KATAKURA
INTO OUR RANKS AS AN OFFICER,
THAT HE MAY HELP US
PRY OPEN THE WORLD.
UESUGI IS TRYING TO CONTAIN
OUR FORCE AT UTSUNOMIYA.
AND THE SUPPOSEDLY
NEUTRAL MAEDA CLAN
NOW DEFENDS KASUGAYAMA.
LORD MAEDA'S WIFE
USUALLY ACCOMPANIES HIM,
BUT SHE REMAINS IN KAGA.
FOR KEIJI'S SAKE,
ONE MIGHT ASSUME.
- THEY ARE NO THREAT TO US.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS THAT WE TAKE
OUR PLACE IN ODAWARA
BEFORE THE TAKEDA
MAKE THEIR MOVE.
- THOUGH THE TAKEDA
WILL NEVER MAKE IT THERE,
EVEN IF WE INVITED THEM IN,
BOTH THE TIGER
AND THE WAR GOD
WILL BE ATTACKED FROM THE REAR
BY THE ARMY WE'VE SECRETED AWAY
IN THE FAR NORTH.
I'LL HEAD TO HARIMA DIRECTLY.
AND RELIEVE THE MORI ARMY
OF THAT PIRATE FORTRESS
THEY'VE REBUILT.
THE SUN WILL BE SETTING
ON DEAR MOTONARI QUITE SOON.
WHETHER HE CONTINUES
TO FIGHT IN SATSUMA
OR HEADS BACK WITH NEWS
OF THE FORTRESS' COMPLETION,
HIS FATE HAS BEEN DECIDED.
WE'LL HAVE THE UNREST IN SATSUMA
QUELLED BY THE COMMANDER
OF THE ARMY WE DEPLOYED
TO THE NORTHERN END OF KYUSHU.
YOUR MIGHT ARMY
IS UNSTOPPABLE
THANKS TO THE MACHINATIONS
WE'VE SET INTO PLAY.
THE LAND WILL TREMBLE AT HOW WE
MAKE WAR UPON THEM, HIDEYOSHI.
- READY OUR FORCES FOR ODAWARA.
- HUH, THAT'S STRANGE.
IT'S GOT TO BE AROUND
HERE SOMEWHERE.
YUMEKICHI, DID YOU TAKE IT?
IF YOU GRABBED IT AS A PRANK
WHILE I WAS SLEEPING,
IT'S NOT FUNNY!
LOOK, THAT CHARM MEANS A LOT
TO ME, YUMEKICHI.
YOU KNOW THAT.
KASUGA, HEY.
- I CAME TO TELL YOU
IT'S HAPPENING NOW.
- WHAT?
- TOYOTOMI'S MAIN
FORCE IS ON THE MOVE.
HE MIGHT HAVE CAUGHT WIND
OF MY LORD KENSHIN'S MOVEMENTS.
AND INTEND TO OCCUPY ODAWARA
BEFORE TAKEDA SWOOPS IN.
- AND AFTER THAT,
HE'S GOING TO ROLL OVER
THE WHOLE KANTO PLAIN.
GUESS IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
I NEED A SMALL FAVOR,
TAKE CARE OF YUMEKICHI FOR ME
UNTIL I GET BACK, ALRIGHT?
- WHAT?
- SORRY, LITTLE BUDDY.
I'VE GOT TO GO THIS ONE ALONE.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
YUMEKICHI.
I'M COMING BACK, YOU KNOW?
CHEER UP, WHEN HAVE I
EVER TOLD YOU A LIE?
LOOK, I SOLEMNLY PINKY-SWEAR IT.
- Narrator: THE SUN SETS
UPON THE COAST OF SATSUMA,
WHERE THE DAY'S FIGHTING
ENDS IN A STANDOFF.
SHIMAZU YOSHIHIRO'S
UNEXPECTED ENTRY INTO THE FRAY
HAS THWARTED THE PINCER ATTACK
MORI'S NAVAL FORCES
HAD HOPED TO EXECUTE.
BEREFT OF A COMMANDER AFTER
MOTINARI'S ABRUPT DEPARTURE,
HIS SHIPS HAVE RETREATED
TO A SAFE DISTANCE FROM SHORE.
- Shimazu: YOU'VE DONE
REAL GOOD OUT THERE TODAY.
THEY'LL BE NEEDING BACKUP
AFTER THE DRUBBING WE GAVE THEM.
LET YOUR MEN TAKE TURNS GRABBING
SOME SHUT EYE WHILE THEY CAN.
- SIR!
- I'VE SEEN SOME
FINE SPEARWORK OUT OF YOU.
- SIR?
- YOU SHOWED ME
WHAT KAI'S TIGER CUB
IS REALLY MADE OF.
- WHAT YOU SAW WASN'T RESOLVE,
ONLY DESPERATION.
MY FOES' DEATHS
WEIGH HEAVILY ON ME.
MY BURDEN GROWS
WITH EVERY MAN I STRIKE DOWN.
- JUST 'CAUSE YOU END A MAN,
DON'T MEAN YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP
HIS HOPES AND DREAMS
IN YOUR RUCKSACK.
- BUT HOW DO YOU FIGURE, LORD?
IS IT CONCEITED OF ME?
- YOU'RE GOING ABOUT IT
ALL WRONG.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN HONING YOUR
SKILLS FOR ALL THIS TIME, HUH?
- PARDON?
- TO DISTINGUISH
YOURSELF IN BATTLE.
GOOD A PLACE TO START AS ANY.
BUT THEN WHAT?
IF I KNOW THE TIGER OF KAI
HALF AS WELL AS I THINK,
HE'S ASKED YOU ALREADY.
WHAT DRIVES YOU
TO PICK UP THEM SPEARS?
- MIYAMOTO MUSASHI...
- Shimazu: MIYAMOTO OVER
THERE, HE'S TENACIOUS, TOO.
LIKE A DOG WITH A BONE,
THAT ONE.
WANTS TO BE THE GREATEST FIGHTER
THAT EVER WAS,
LIVES AND BREATHES FOR IT.
NO DOUBT RATTLING AROUND
IN THAT HEAD OF HIS.
NEVER KNOWN HIM TO HESITATE.
BACK IN THE DAY, I FOUGHT
JUST TO BE FIGHTING,
FOOL THAT I WAS.
BUT NOW, WHEN I HEAVE UP
THIS DAMN HEAVY SWORD OF MINE,
I KNOW THAT I'M DOING IT
TO MAKE THIS A WORLD
WHERE THE YOUNG ONES CAN LIVE
WITH SOME HOPE IN THEIR HEARTS.
IN FACT, I RECKON ALL OF US
WHO HAVE A DUTY TO A DOMAIN
AND THE FOLKS WHO LIVE IN IT
FEEL THAT WAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIND YOURSELF,
MASTER YUKIMURA.
IT'S HARD AS HELL
TO FIGURE OUT RIGHT FROM WRONG
WHEN YOU'RE HOPPING
BACK AND FORTH
LIKE THE SAND'S TOO HOT
FOR YOUR FEET.
- IT'S ONLY WHEN YOU KEEP
YOUR EYE TO THE FUTURE,
THESE INJUSTICES BECOME JUST.
IT'S THE WAY OF THE TIMES.
- DECIDE IN HERE
WHAT YOU WANT OUT OF LIFE.
THE PATH WILL MAKE ITSELF CLEAR.
IN YOUR HEART OF HEARTS,
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW
UNCERTAINTY AGAIN.
- THE PEOPLE OF SATSUMA
ALL CAME HERE
AFTER BEING DRIVEN
FROM THEIR HOMES.
THIS PLACE IS THEIR LAST,
BEST CHANCE.
I FOUGHT WELL TODAY BECAUSE
I WANTED TO DEFEND THAT CHANCE.
YOURS IS A LAND OF CLEAR SKIES
AND DAZZLING SUNSHINE,
OF GENTLE WAVES
LAPPING THE SANDS.
I WANTED THIS PLACE
TO KNOW PEACE.
HE DID ASK, I FORGOT.
AFTER THE FINAL DEED OF VALOR,
ONCE THESE TURBULENT TIMES
HAS BEEN TAMED,
WHAT DO I WANT TO ACCOMPLISH?
WHAT FUTURE DO I WISH
FOR THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN?
LORD MASAMUNE, MORI MOTONARI,
TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI,
EVEN HIS LORDSHIP,
THE GREAT TIGER OF KAI,
WHEN THEY TAKE THE FIELD,
IT'S WITH GOALS AND IDEALS
UNSHAKABLY FIXED
IN THEIR HEARTS.
IT'S NOT THAT THEY NEVER WAVER,
THEY DO!
BUT WHEN THEY DO, THEY FIND
THE WILL TO OVERCOME IT.
IT'S NO WONDER I WAS UNABLE
TO BEST LORD MASAMUNE.
- GO AND STOP
THAT SUN-ADDLED PANSY MOTONARI.
HE'S HEADING BACK AROUND
TO FIGHT TOYOTOMI.
SO TAKE MY SOLDIERS WITH YOU,
IT OUGHT TO HELP MAKE UP
FOR THOSE WHO YOU LOST
AT ITSUKUSHIMA.
- BUT LORD SHIMAZU, THAT WOULD
LEAVE YOU DEFENSELESS.
- CALL THEM A PARTING GIFT.
NO NEED TO WORRY
ABOUT ME, YOUNG ONE.
I AIN'T FORGOTTEN
MY JIGEN TECHNIQUE.
AND I CAN STILL DEAL OUT
THE HURT.
- TRUE, BUT, SIR--
- SHARE A GOOD-BYE TOAST
WITH ME?
DON'T YOU LOSE THAT KIND HEART
YOU'VE GOT, YOU HEAR ME?
THOSE WHAT GOT THEM AGONIZE
OVER A LOT OF THINGS.
AND THEY MAKE THEIR FAIR SHARE
OF MISTAKES.
TAKES THEM FOREVER AND DAY
TO GET STRONG.
BUT ONCE THEY DO,
THEY'RE DAMN NEAR UNSTOPPABLE.
THEY'RE MEN JUST LIKE YOU,
WITH KIND HEARTS, I GUARANTEE.
NOW GET ON WITH YOU,
I KNOW YOU CAN BECOME
THE GREATEST WARRIOR
IN THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN.
- MANY THANKS, MILORD.
- KARMA HAS FAVORED US.
CRUSH ALL WHO OPPOSE US,
MY FORTRESS OF THE SUN!
BEHOLD, THE SUN BEGINS
ITS SKYWARD ASCENT.
- Toyotomi:
HANBEI.
- Takenaka:
WHAT IS IT, HIDEYOSHI?
- ONCE THE COUNTRY IS OURS,
I WANT YOU TO REST.
- WHAT?
- DID YOU THINK THAT I HAD
NOT NOTICED YOUR FATIGUE?
WITHOUT YOU, ALL MY PLANS
ARE FOR NAUGHT.
- YOU COULD OFFER ME THE WORLD,
I WOULDN'T TRADE IT
FOR THOSE FEW WORDS.
- ( coughing )
- Soldier 1:
MASTER TAKENAKA!
- Soldier 2: WHAT
HAPPENED? HE LOOKS TERRIBLE!
- Soldier 3:
CALL FOR THE DOCTOR,
AND NOTIFY LORD HIDEYOSHI.
- DON'T, THERE'S NO NEED
FOR THAT.
I'M JUST--
( coughing )
I'M JUST A LITTLE TIRED.
I'LL BE FINE.
YOU MEN HEAD FOR HARIMA
AS INSTRUCTED.
I'LL BE ALONG SHORTLY.
- BUT, MASTER--
- I AM GIVING YOU AN ORDER.
- ( all )
YES, SIR.
GRANT ME TIME.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
- Sarutobi:
SO, THIS IS WHERE WE STAND--
MORI'S ROLLING IN FROM THE WEST
WITH HIS FORTRESS.
HIDEYOSHI MUST BE HEADED
FOR ODAWARA LIKE WE THOUGHT.
THEY STARTED MOVING
AS SOON AS THEY CAUGHT WIND
OF WHAT UESUGI WAS UP TO.
THEY'RE FAST, I'LL GRANT
THEM THAT MUCH.
BUT THEY WOULDN'T DARE
LEAVE THE NORTH UNDEFENDED.
A HIDDEN ARMY IN OSHU, MAYBE,
OR PERHAPS FURTHER AWAY.
ARE THEY HEADING OUT
TO DEAL WITH THE THREAT
OF MORI'S FORTRESS?
INFORM OUR LORD TAKEDA
WITHOUT DELAY.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU, I
JUST HAVE TO DO SOMETHING FIRST.
MIGHT AS WELL CHECK IN
ON OUR MASTER SANADA'S
MOVEMENTS WHILE I'M AT IT.
- Kasuga:
TAKEDA'S NINJA CORPS...
NICE THAT THE NEW GLIDERS
DON'T BLOW UP.
- HEY, THERE
BEEN A WHILE, HASN'T IT?
- SARUTOBI SASUKE,
YOU SCARED ME TO DEATH!
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SO HIGH-STRUNG.
COME ON, YOU'RE A NINJA.
HEADING BACK TO ECHIGO
TO REPORT IN, I ASSUME?
- I SENT A MESSENGER, BUT I'VE
GOT A BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
THAT DETACHMENT OF TOYOTOMI'S
IS HEADING WEST.
- BUT NO TAKENAKA HANBEI
IN SIGHT.  YEAH, I KNOW.
- SO--
- SO, WHY ISN'T THE
TRUSTED LIEUTENANT
OUT THERE LEADING THE CHARGE?
- ONE OF THOSE WHISTLES,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- ONE OF WHAT?
- THOSE FLYING THINGS
YOUR NINJA JUST GLIDED PAST ON.
YOU FIXED THEM UP, I CAN TELL.
- OH, THOSE.  YEAH, RIGHT.
TECHNICALLY SPEAKING,
WE'RE NOT ALLIES RIGHT NOW.
SO WHY WOULD I GIVE YOU ONE?
KASUGA, YOU ARE SO NAIVE.
- I RISKED MY LIFE
AS YOUR UNWITTING GUINEA PIG
AND YOU--
- SHH!
TOYOTOMI'S PERSONAL SPY.
- WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHO COULD HAVE--
- THAT WAS--
- Chosokabe:
SO THAT'S HOW IT'S GOING TO BE.
TOYOTOMI'S MAIN FORCE,
HEADED FOR ODAWARA I'D WAGER.
- MEANING THAT BASTARD MATSUNAGA
WAS IN LEAGUE WITH HIM
ALL ALONG.
- WHO KNOWS, TEAMING UP MEANS
THAT GRASPING OCTOPUS
ONLY GETS HIS TENTACLES
ON HALF OF THE PRIZE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO HERE,
ONE-EYED DRAGON?
THAT OVERGROWN APE IS GOING
TO TAKE THE KANTO PLAIN.
- SERIOUS?
YOU'VE STILL GOT TO ASK?
CATCH HIM AND TAKE HIM DOWN.
- Narrator: AND NOW, THE
RIVAL WARLORDS MAKE HASTE
FOR THEIR FINAL BATTLEGROUNDS
ACROSS THE LAND.
AIMING FOR THE PINNACLE
OF THE ERA,
THE BLADES RISING UP IN CHAOS
HOWL TO ONE ANOTHER.
- YOU KNOW WHY I'M HERE,
TIME IS GROWING SHORT.
VERY SOON I SHALL HAVE
YOUR ANSWER OR YOUR LIFE.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sanada: PEACE IS MORE
THAN JUST MINDLESS TRANQUILITY.
I KNOW THAT NOW.
ONLY THOSE WHO CAN FACE
ANY AND ALL ADVERSITY
WITHOUT BUCKLING, AND WHO STOKE
THE FIRE IN THEIR HEARTS
WILL ACHIEVE ALL
THAT THEY DESIRE.
AT THE FINAL BATTLE, MY SPIRIT
WILL IGNITE ONCE AGAIN!