- HIDEYOSHI...
- YOU WILL SUFFER THE FATE
OF ALL THOSE WHO DEFY ME.
FOR THE SAKE OF MY FUTURE REIGN
OVER THIS COUNTRY,
I WILL MAKE AN EXAMPLE
OUT OF YOU AND TAKE YOUR HEAD!
IT APPEARS YOU'VE RISEN
ABOVE THE LITTLE SNAKE
WHO'S HISS WAS WORSE
THAN HIS BITE.
HOWEVER, EVEN IF YOU COULD
WIELD A HUNDRED SWORDS,
EVEN AT YOUR VERY BEST,
YOU ARE ULTIMATELY NOTHING
COMPARED TO ME.
- YEAH, YEAH, I GET YOU.
I DIDN'T EXPECT A PARTY
WITH A WET BLANKET
LIKE YOU TO BE FUN.
'CAUSE I REALLY DON'T LIKE YOU.
SO THE QUICKER I GET THIS
OVER WITH, THE BETTER!
- I SEE, SO HE ACTUALLY
SAID THAT, DID HE?
HE TOLD ME TO STAY PUT?
- SHOULD KENSHIN BE ATTACKED,
GO TO UTSUNOMIYA.
IF DATE IS THE TARGET...
- ...SEND REINFORCEMENTS
TO ODAWARA.
SHOULD THE MOBILE FORTRESS
APPEAR IN THE WEST,
IN THE HANDS OF MORI
OR POSSIBLY THE TOYOTOMI,
KNOW THAT I HAVE MET MY END
TRYING MY BEST TO STOP IT.
HOWEVER, I SHALL NOT ALLOW
MY DEPARTURE UPON THIS JOURNEY
TO BE OUR FINAL FAREWELL.
I SWEAR UPON THE SOULS
OF MASTER OYAMADA
AND ALL THE OTHERS I HAVE LOST,
I SHALL CARRY OUT
MY MISSION WITHOUT FAIL!
- I MOST HEARTILY UNDERSTAND.
SO, YUKIMURA HAS FINALLY FOUND
IT WITHIN HIMSELF
TO MAKE USE OF ME.
AT LAST, I HAVE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT.
BUT HONESTLY, TELLING ME
TO STAY PUT?
( laughing )
YUKIMURA, MY CUB,
ONE-EYED DRAGON,
USE THE STRENGTH OF YOUR YOUTH.
OVERCOME THIS ORDEAL.
ACCOMPLISH WHAT YOU
HAVE SET OUT TO DO.
- Soldier: LORD MORI,
THERE IS AN ARMY
WAITING FOR US UP AHEAD.
THEIR BANNERS INDICATE
THEY'RE FROM SATSUMA.
- DECIMATE THEM.
LIGHT IT UP!
WHAT?!
- I AM SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA
OF KAI!
LORD MORI MOTONARI,
IN THE INTEREST OF HIS LORDSHIP
TAKEDA SHINGEN,
THE TIGER OF KAI,
AND WITH WORDS OF ENLIGHTENMENT
FROM LORD SHIMAZU YOSHIHIRO
OF SATSUMA IN MY HEART,
I'VE COME TO STOP
YOUR INVASION OF OSAKA!
- I WAS WONDERING
WHO'S PAWN YOU MIGHT BE.
TAKEDA'S MAN WHO LET
HIS OWN PAWNS DIE
AT ITSUKUSHIMA,
WAS IT STRATEGY OR FAILURE?
I'M SURPRISED
YOU STILL DRAW BREATH.
- BOTH THE TOYOTOMI AND THE MORI
GIVE NO THOUGHT
TO THE FUTURE OF YOUR PEOPLE.
YOUR ONLY THOUGHT IS BETRAYAL!
YOU WILL GO NO FURTHER!
- YOUR ONLY SKILL
IS MAKING A NUISANCE
OF YOURSELF TO OTHERS.
BE GONE, I HAVE NO INTEREST
IN YOUR DRIVEL.
- Takenaka:
I SEE NOW,
IT IS CLEAR YOU AND I
ARE QUITE DIFFERENT.
THE WORDS WHICH ADORN YOUR SWORD
ARE NOT THE NOBLE VOW
OF A SECOND-IN-COMMAND.
THEY ARE A SUTRA, MEANT
TO SEAL AWAY THE BRUTALITY
BURIED DEEP WITHIN YOU.
- RECITE YOUR OWN SUTRAS,
TAKENAKA HANBEI.
THAT IS ALL THE TIME
I WILL GIVE YOU.
- AFTER ALL I'VE SEEN,
MY LIFE IS OF NO CONSEQUENCE.
BUT SADLY,
WHAT'S LEFT OF IT WILL NOT END
BY YOUR HAND.
- Toyotomi: ARE YOU NOW
AWARE OF WHAT YOU LACK,
ONE-EYED DRAGON?
IF THAT EYE CAN SEE
HOW THIS COUNTRY
WALKS DOWN THE PATH OF RUIN,
AT LEAST TRY TO STRIKE
A RETURN BLOW.
IF YOU WOULD HOWL, THEN HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO MATCH IT.
THE COUNTRY I GIVE SHAPE TO HAS
NO NEED OF THOSE WHO ARE WEAK.
THOSE WHO LACK STRENGTH,
I WILL SIMPLY CRUSH
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
- GIVE ME A BREAK,
IN A WORLD UNDER
YOUR FAT-ASS THUMB,
NO ONE COMES OUT THE WINNER.
- THE LAND MUST BE RULED
BY STRENGTH!
AND I AM THE STRONGEST ONE
THERE IS!
- ( all ): BOSS!
- THIS COUNTRY SUFFERS
A MALADY OF WEAKNESS.
AND I, MY TOYOTOMI ARMY,
WILL BE THE CURE!
- Ishida: YOU ARE UESUGI
KENSHIN, I PRESUME.
- INDEED I AM,
AND WHO MIGHT YOU BE?
- YOUR SLAYER, ISHIDA MITSUNARI.
UNDER LORD HIDEYOSHI'S
AUTHORITY,
I WILL TAKE YOU DOWN.
- DRIVEN AND PURE OF HEART.
SO MUCH SO IT PAINS ME.
- LORD KENSHIN!
- HOW SWIFT.
- ONCE WE'VE BEATEN
ALL OF THESE GUYS TO A PULP,
YOU'RE FIGHTING
WITH ME, POPS.  REMEMBER?
- OH, I KNOW.
THIS HERE'S NOTHING
BUT A WARM-UP.
YOU'VE DONE GOOD, BOY.
REST THERE FOR NOW-- BRING IT!
- Tokugawa: GLAD WE DIDN'T
HAVE TO STRIKE OUR ALLIES,
THE MORI, FROM BEHIND.
RIGHT THEN, LET'S FIGURE OUT
WHAT DIRECTION
LORD HIDEYOSHI'S PATH
IS HEADED IN NOW.
TOKUGAWA IEYASU,
TAKING THE FIELD!
- LISTEN WELL, MY PAWNS.
GIVE YOUR LIVES IF YOU MUST
BUT SLAY EVERY LAST ONE
OF OUR FOES!
- HE IS WILLING TO SACRIFICE
HIS OWN MEN.
NO MATTER HOW NOBLE THE CAUSE
ONE MAY SERVE,
THAT IS UNFORGIVABLE!
- Soldier:
MASTER YUKIMURA!
- NO!
- Mori:
THE FOOL,
SURELY HE DOES NOT HOPE TO STOP
THE PASSAGE OF THE SUN
WITH ONLY HIS TWO SPEARS.
A VAIN PLAN
IF EVER THERE WAS ONE.
- PERFECT SPEAR OF CONQUEST!
SANADA YUKIMURA HAS ARRIVED!
YOU SHALL NOT PASS!
BURN ABLAZE!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- THESE SPEARS ARE MY SOUL,
THEY WILL NOT BREAK!
DO NOT BREAK!
- HE IS THE ULTIMATE PAWN,
THE IDEAL SACRIFICE.
I WISH I COULD MAKE MY OWN MEN
LEARN FROM HIS EXAMPLE.
- MORI MOTONARI,
COME, LET US HAVE A FAIR FIGHT.
- YOU WILL DIE
MOST HORRIFICALLY,
LIKE THE PAWN YOU ARE.
OH, THREE STARS,
MY FAMILY CREST.
WITH RESPECT, I OFFER
IT UP TO THE SUN.
NO MERE PAWN CAN STOP ME!
ACTIVATE THE MORNING STAR
DEATH RAY!
- THE HEAT!
IT IS EXCRUCIATING!
- ALL GOES IN ACCORDANCE
WITH MY CALCULATIONS.
- Takenaka:
I HATE TO ADMIT THIS,
BUT I MUST FINALLY ACKNOWLEDGE
THAT DEAR MASAMUNE
IS A BORN DRAGON.
HIDEYOSHI IS STRONGER
THAN ANYONE OUT THERE,
BUT HIM--
I SENSE SOMETHING
UNFATHOMABLE IN THAT DRAGON.
SOMEDAY, HE IS CERTAIN
TO BECOME A FORCE
THAT WILL BRING HARM
TO THE TOYOTOMI.
- Sanada:
SOARING THE SKIES,
SCORCHING THE EARTH,
SANADA YUKIMURA
WILL NEVER STAND STILL!
- AMAZING!
THIS MAN BURNS SO FURIOUSLY,
HOTTER THAN EVEN
THE INCOMPARABLE SEARING
OF THE SUN ITSELF!
- MY SOUL'S LIGHT
SHALL NEVER BE EXTINGUISHED!
- MY CALCULATIONS,
HE HAS VOIDED THEM.
I SUFFER DEFEAT?  IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( cheering )
- Sanada:
LORD MASAMUNE,
IN SOME SMALL WAY
HAVE I BECOME MORE LIKE YOU?
PLEASE LIVE THROUGH THIS.
AND ONCE MORE, LET US--
ONCE MORE, LET US MEET
ON THE FIELD OF BATTLE.
- I'VE WANTED THIS CHANCE
TO HACK AWAY
AT EACH OTHER'S LIVES.
BUT IF YOU'RE LIFE
IS ALREADY NEARING ITS END,
YOU CANNOT DEFEAT ME.
BUT I GRANT YOU NO MERCY.
- AS IT SHOULD BE.
THERE WAS NEVER ANYONE
WHO COULD TAKE MY PLACE.
NEVER!
HIDEYOSHI...
- THE DRAGON WILL DEVOUR
EVEN THE GODS.
MY LORD MASAMUNE
WILL NEVER KNOW DEFEAT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DAYDREAMING
ABOUT OVER THERE?
INSTEAD OF STARING OFF
AT A PLACE
YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE FROM HERE,
TRY PAYING ATTENTION
TO WHAT'S RIGHT HERE
UNDER YOUR NOSE.
- AGAIN, YOU HOWL
RATHER THAN STRIKE.
CERTAINLY YOU HAVE
LEARNED YOUR LESSON,
AND HAVE BEGUN TO REGRET
BEING FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO DEFY A MIGHTY POWER
WITHOUT KNOWING YOUR PLACE.
YOU WANT THIS COUNTRY?
YOU KNOW NOTHING
OF THE BROADER PICTURE.
THAT IS THE KEY
TO YOUR DOWNFALL.
THS IS FINALLY THE END
OF ONE WHO LACKS STRENGTH.
DAMN IT!
FIRST THE PIRATE,
AND NOW YOU?!
WHY WILL YOU NOT DIE?
- YOUR LAVENDER LACKEY'S
TOO SCARED
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
YOU'RE JUST NOT AS STRONG
AS YOU THINK.
NO LIMIT!
IT HASN'T YET, BUT YOU
WON'T GET THIS COUNTRY
IF IT DOES KILL ME.
- ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU
WOULD UNIFY IT, THEN?
AT MOST, YOU ARE THE TOP APE
IN A PACK OF WILD GORILLAS.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
WITH THIS COUNTRY IF YOU HAD IT?
- DOESN'T MATTER, YOU WON'T BE
AROUND TO FIND OUT.
- PATHETIC FOOL!
- YEAH, THAT SONG'S
GETTING BORING.
LONG AS YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO PROTECT,
THOSE THINGS HAVE A WAY
OF WORKING THEMSELVES OUT.
YOU SEE?
- UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES
WILL I HAND THIS COUNTRY
TO THE LIKES OF YOU!
- BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE,
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
BLAST OFF!
I CAN FINALLY HEAD ON OUT
TO THE REAL PARTY.
THE ONE THAT'S BEEN ON HOLD,
THANKS TO YOU.
THE ONE I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
- Keiji:
HIDEYOSHI...
REMEMBER BACK WHEN?
WE ALWAYS USED TO ENJOY
THE BREEZE TOGETHER LIKE THIS.
IT'S LIKE WE'VE GONE BACK
TO THOSE DAYS, EH, HIDEYOSHI?
- TIME FLOWS AT QUITE
A LEISURELY PACE HERE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER STOPPED
AND ENJOYED THE BREEZE WITH YOU.
- Keiji:
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE THE THREE OF US
WERE TOGETHER AT ALL.
A REAL LONG TIME.
OH YEAH, HIDEYOSHI,
YOU USED TO LIKE GOING
TO SEE CHERRY BLOSSOMS, RIGHT?
WHEN SPRING COMES, WHY DON'T
YOU AND I HEAD AROUND AND--
- Toyotomi:
KEIJI,
NOT EVERYBODY GETS
TO LIVE FOREVER AS YOU SEEM TO.
IN ORDER TO LEAD ALL PEOPLE,
TO BUILD A TRULY STRONG NATION,
YOU CANNOT ALLOW ANYTHING
THAT COULD MAKE YOU WEAK.
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
DELIVERED THIS TO ME.
BUT I AM NO LONGER
WORTHY OF HAVING IT.
DO ME THE HONOR
OF HOLDING ON TO IT.
FOR HER, KEIJI.
- REALLY?
YOU STUBBORN, STUBBORN FOOL.
DAMN YOU.
- Narrator: THE TOYOTOMI
ARMY SOON FELL TO SHAMBLES.
THERE ONCE WAS A GENERAL,
WHO BELIEVED ONLY IN STRENGTH
AND PURSUED IT
WITH BLIND AMBITION.
AND HIS LOYAL STRATEGIST,
WHO BELIEVED
IN HIS LORD'S ASPIRATIONS.
WITH TRULY CRUSHING MIGHT,
THEY SOUGHT TO UNIFY
THE COUNTRY.
AND THEN TO FORGE RELATIONS
OUT IN THE WORLD AT LARGE.
AND NOW THAT ERA
HAD COME TO AN END.
NO ONE HAD YET LAID CLAIM
TO THE ENTIRETY
OF THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN.
AND UNTIL THE DAY BLADES
ONCE AGAIN ROSE UP IN CHAOS
TO FIGHT FOR IT, IT'S PEOPLE
GAVE THEMSELVES OVER
TO THE FLEETING PEACE THAT HAD
SPREAD ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
AND ONCE MORE,
THEY QUIETLY WAITED
FOR THE WAR CRY.
ASPIRING TO THE PINNACLE.
- WAIT, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING?  KIEJI?
- OH, JUST A QUICK JAUNT
OUT TO KYOTO.
BUT I MIGHT STRETCH IT
INTO A TRIP
TO MOTOCHIKA'S PLACE.
- BUT, YOU JUST GOT HERE.
- YOU ARE TO BECOME A WARRIOR
AND SUCCEED AS HEAD
OF THE MAEDA CLAN.
IN FACT, YOU JUST RECENTLY SAID
YOU WOULD DO SO.
- THAT DOESN'T
REALLY SOUND LIKE ME.
- ( groans )
- WELL, SEE YOU LATER!
-  KEIJI!
- HONESTLY, WHAT A CHILD
YOU ARE!
EVERYTIME I SEE A GLIMMER
OF MATURITY, YOU BLOW IT!
- MATSU, YOU KEEP
THAT DISAPPROVING LOOK
AND THOSE WRINKLES
WILL STAY THAT WAY!
- JUST A MINUTE, KEIJI.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
SOME THINGS YOU SIMPLY
DO NOT JOKE ABOUT!
MY LORD INUCHIYO,
THIS REALLY IS NOT A MATTER
TO BE LAUGHED AT.
I SAID GET BACK HERE, KEIJI!
- Takeda: THE WORLD IS
STILL FULL OF STRIFE.
THOUGH MANKIND MAY CEASE TO WAR,
PEOPLE WILL ALWAYS
CONTINUE TO STRUGGLE.
THOUGH A DAY MAY COME WHEN
YOU LAY YOUR SPEARS TO REST,
FOR AS LONG AS YOU LIVE,
WIELD THOSE SPEARS OF YOUR SOUL
FOR WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN.
- SIR, IN ORDER TO FORGE A WORLD
WHERE ALL MAY LIVE,
NOT FOR WAR AND STRIFE
BUT FOR THE SAKE OF HAPPINESS,
TO BUILD A WORLD
WE CAN BE TRULY PROUD OF,
IT IS MY PLEDGE, I, YUKIMURA,
SHALL ENDURE INJUSTICES,
OVERCOME TRIALS,
AND ACCEPT CONTRADITIONS
FROM NO PERSON BUT MYSELF.
UNTIL LASTING PEACE COMES,
I WILL LET MY SOUL BURN.
I WILL ACCOMPLISH
ALL THAT FATE ALLOWS ME TO
WITHOUT FAIL, MY LORD.
- ( chuckles )
PERHAPS MY GENERATION'S TIME
HAS PASSED.
( groans )
- ( gasps )
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- YOU THINK THAT I WOULD
UTTER SUCH FEEBLE WORDS?!
MY, HOW YOU'VE GROWN,
YUKIMURA.
- THANKS, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU KNOW,
SOMEONE'S BOUND
TO WANT TO THROW
A NEW PARTY SOON ENOUGH.
- IT CAN'T BE LONG UNTIL
WE LIVE IN A TIME OF WAR AGAIN.
WE MUST COMPLETE THE REBUILDING
OF OSHU BEFORE THEN.
- YEAH, LOOKS LIKE WE WON'T
HAVE ANY TIME TO BE BORED.
- PLUS, WE'VE ADDED QUITE A
SPIRITED BUNCH TO OUR ROSTER.
THEY SEEM PRETTY IMPATIENT
TO RAISE A WAR CRY.
- EXCELLENT.
WE'LL HAVE TO LET
THEM SEE THE COUNTRY
UNDER THE DRAGON'S RULE.
- SIR.
- AND ALONG THE WAY,
I'LL BE ENTRUSTING MY BACK
TO YOU AS ALWAYS, KOJURO.
YOU READY FOR IT?
- YOU NEED NOT EVEN ASK.
- THAT'S WHAT
I LIKE TO HEAR.
ARE YOU BOYS READY?!
- YEAH!
- Date: THEN HOLD
ONTO YOUR SOUL!
- YEAH!
- Date: COME ON THEN,
LET'S GET SERIOUS!
- Men: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S KEEP THIS PARTY COOL
AND SHOW 'EM
A REAL DRAGON'S MAJESTY.
- Men: YEAH!
- HERE WE GO!