- ( theme song playing )
- Keiji: COMING THROUGH, FOLKS!
( grunts )
- KEIJI.
- ( squeaks )
- Keiji: SORRY!
- KEI IS BACK!
- Man 1: KEIJI'S HERE!
- Man 2: BIG BROTHER KEIJI!
- Woman: IT'S KEI!
- ( gasps )
- Matsu: HOLD IT
RIGHT THERE, KEIJI!
- UP TO HIS USUAL
ANTICS AGAIN?
- ( laughing )
HE NEVER LEARNS, DOES HE?
- WELL, LADY MATSU
LOOKS JUST AS BEAUTIFUL AS EVER.
- KEI DOESN'T EVEN HOLD
A CANDLE TO LADY MAEDA.
- ( all laughing )
- MATSU, SIS, PUT THAT THING
AWAY BEFORE SOMEONE GETS HURT.
COME ADMIRE THE CHERRY
BLOSSOMS WITH ME.
THEY WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER.
( grunts )
- OH, COME NOW.
HOW MUCH TIME...
MUST YOU WASTE...
LOOKING AT FLOWERS...
UNTIL YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH?
- ( groans )
AH NUTS, WHAT A WASTE.
- I HOPED YOUR LONG ABSENCE
WOULD BRING YOU SOME
MATURITY, BUT NO.
LIFE IS STILL A GAME FOR YOU.
EVEN NOW, DRAWING A COLD BATH
FOR MY LORD HUSBAND!
YOUR RIDICULOUS BEHAVIOR
GOES TOO FAR, KEIJI!
- ( laughing ) HE'LL BE FINE.
TOSHI ALWAYS RUNS AROUND
HALF-NAKED ANYWAY,
RIGHT, YUMEKICHI?
- ( squeaks )
- STOP WITH THE FOOLING AROUND
AND DO SOMETHING THAT
HONORS THE MAEDA FAMILY NAME!
- Keiji: YEAH, OKAY! OW!
YOU KNOW I'M NOT ANY GOOD
AT THAT SORT OF THING.
- I HATE FEELING TIED DOWN.
- ARE YOU STILL USING THAT LINE?
- TOSHI'S BEING
GIVEN DOMAIN OVER
THE LAND OF KAGA SOON, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE REALLY HAS
THE TIME TO DEAL WITH
THE TROUBLES I'D CAUSE HIM HERE.
- IF YOU UNDERSTAND THAT,
DON'T CAUSE HIM TROUBLE.
HELP GUIDE
MY LORD INUCHIYO WITH...
( sighs ) MEN.
GO FORTH, JIROMARU!
- ( grunting )
- TAKE WING, TAROMARU!
- ( screeching )
- HE IS SO SKILLED. IF THE JERK
WOULD ONLY APPLY HIMSELF,
HE WOULD BE SUCH AN ASSET.
- MATSU. SIS!
- YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
- ( Toshiie sneezing )
- DESTROY, GOROMARU!
- NO, MATSU!
( sneezing )
MATSU, DON'T DO IT!
- MATSU, SIS...
- PLEASE, MY LORD INUCHIYO.
STAY OUT OF THIS.
- ( growling )
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- MY LORD, NO!
- NOT GOOD.
- ( screaming )
- ( loud thud )
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME. MY LORD
INUCHIYO, PLEASE BE ALL RIGHT.
- I SHOULD KNOW BETTER THAN
TO COME UNARMED. MY MISTAKE.
- LOOKS LIKE TOSHI'S
GOING TO MAKE IT.
THAT'S MY CUE. SO LONG, MATSU!
- KEIJI, STOP THIS INSTANT!
- ( sneezing )
- MY LORD INUCHIYO.
- DO ME A FAVOR, PLEASE.
JUST LET HIM GO.
FOR NOW LET HIM DO AS HE...
( sneezes )
- MY LORD, THAT COLD BATH
HAS DONE YOU IN.
ALLOW YOUR LOVING WIFE
TO MAKE A NICE WARM
RICE PORRIDGE FOR YOU.
- NO.
HERE IN THE WARMTH OF YOUR ARMS,
IT'S MORE THAN REMEDY ENOUGH.
SEE? MY SHIVER IS ALREADY GONE.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO.
- YOU ARE THE BEST COOK
IN THE WORLD, THOUGH.
I NEVER TURN DOWN YOUR YAM SOUP.
I EAT ONE BOWL, AND WHAM! THE
STRENGTH OF A THOUSAND MEN!
- OH, MY BELOVED HUSBAND.
YOU SPOIL ME SO.
- ( both laughing )
- AND SCENE.
- I SWEAR,
THAT'S JUST HOW IT HAPPENED.
- QUITE A BOND THEY SHARE.
LORD TOSHIIE AND LADY MATSU
ARE WHAT ALL MARRIED
COUPLES SHOULD ASPIRE TO.
- SO TRUE.
LOVE DOES CONQUER ALL
LIKE WITH TOSHI AND MATSU,
OR WITH YOU AND KASUGA.
IF ONLY EVERYONE WERE
SO CONSUMED WITH LOVE,
THERE'D BE NO WAR.
- MAEDA KEIJI,
THAT IS PURE NONSENSE!
I AM BY NO MEANS IN SUCH...
- AW, COME ON. IT'S NOTHING
TO BE EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
LIFE IS SHORT, MY GOOD PEOPLE,
FIND LOVE WHERE YOU CAN!
- HOW DARE YOU BE SO FORWARD?
- ( screams )
- KASUGA.
- SIR.
- COULD YOU PREPARE US
ANOTHER CUP?
- YES, MY LORD KENSHIN.
- SUCH BEAUTY. YOUR GRACEFUL
AND UNCLOUDED SPIRIT
REVEALS ITSELF IN
EVEN THE WAY YOU SIT.
- PLEASE, MY LORD...
- IF I GAZED UPON YOUR
FORM FOR ALL TIME,
I WOULD NEVER TIRE OF IT.
- ( moaning )
- KASUGA, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE SHINOBI?
YOUR FELLOW NINJA BACK HOME
MUST THINK YOU'RE ODD.
- ( squeaks )
- I HAVE NO FELLOW NINJA.
- REGARDING LORD TOSHIIE,
I IMAGINE HE IS TROUBLED BY ODA
NOBUNAGA'S ACTIONS OF LATE.
ALL THE MORE SO,
AS HE IS HAPPILY MARRIED.
ODA'S RECENT INVASION OF MINO
MUST HAVE GIVEN HIM PAUSE.
AND YOU THOUGHT
TO LIGHTEN HIS MOOD
IN WHAT LITTLE WAY YOU COULD.
HENCE, YOUR PRANK INVOLVING
THE COLD BATHWATER.
OR AM I WRONG?
PERHAPS IT WAS MERELY
FOR NOSTALGIA, A FINAL BOW?
- NOTHING SO COMMENDABLE,
I'M AFRAID.
- EITHER WAY, I AM DEEPLY
SADDENED TO THINK THE
WORLD HAS COME TO PASS, SUCH
THAT YOU FEEL COMPELLED TO ACT.
- THIS DEVIL KING.
I HEARD NOBUNAGA BURNED
MINO TO THE GROUND.
HIS OWN WIFE'S HOMELAND.
BUT EVEN SO, LADY NOHIME
CONTINUES TO STAND BY HIS SIDE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
SHE'S RIGHT IN THE HEAD.
I FEAR FOR TOSHI AND MATSU MOST.
- THE LAND OF OMI
MAY BE IN DANGER AS WELL.
- YEAH, I WENT TO AZAI
TO TELL HIM TO BE CAREFUL.
BUT HE GAVE ME SOME SPIEL ABOUT
THE EVILS OF NEEDLESS ADVICE
AND TURNED ME AWAY AT THE GATE.
- THOUGH HE TOOK DOWN
IMAGAWA YOSHIMOTO AT OKEHAZAMA,
ODA SHOWS NO INTENT
TO RULE SURUGA.
NOR DOES HE SEEM
TO SHOW INTEREST
IN ATTACKING THE EASTERN LANDS.
- HE'S HOPING WE'LL
TAKE EACH OTHER OUT.
- AND WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT
HE SWEEPS THROUGH WITH EASE.
- AS I THOUGHT.
SINCE YOU WERE IN A POSITION
TO OBSERVE ODA FIRSTHAND
AND CAME TO THE SAME
CONCLUSION, IT MUST BE SO.
BUT INSTEAD YOU INTEND
TO RALLY THE EASTERN GENERALS?
- ( laughs )
I GUESS NOTHING GETS BY YOU,
DOES IT, KENSHIN?
- IT IS NO EASY UNDERTAKING,
HOWEVER, IF ANY MAN IS
CAPABLE OF SUCH A FEAT,
IT COULD BE NO ONE BUT YOU.
- IT'S A FOOL'S ERRAND, I KNOW.
BUT THIS JUST DOESN'T
FEEL LIKE THE TIME
TO BE LOAFING ABOUT ANYMORE.
- HEY GUYS, SHIFT CHANGE...
- WAS A WHILE AGO, JERKS!
- WE WENT TO CHECK
ON HOW BIG BOSS-MAN'S DOING.
- YEAH, HOW WAS HE?
- SAME AS HE HAS BEEN.
DAY OR NIGHT, WHEN HE'S NOT
SWINGING HIS SWORD AROUND,
HE JUST STANDS THERE,
LOST IN HIS THOUGHTS.
THINK ABOUT IT WHEN'S THE LAST
TIME HE HELD A WAR COUNCIL?
- AND MASTER KATAKURA'S
BEEN SPENDING ALL HIS TIME
ON THE CROPS.
- Woman: GRANDMA!
- MASTER KATAKURA!
HERE, THE TEA IS READY, SIR!
- AH, GREAT TIMING.
- WE WENT RIDING ALL OVER
THE PLACE FOR NOTHING.
WE ENDED UP HANDING OVER ODAWARA
TO TAKEDA AND SURUGA TO ODA.
- NO WAY! BIG BOSS
AND BOSS KATAKURA
CAN'T BOTH HAVE
LOST THEIR DRIVE!
- ( all gasping )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( grunting )
- MASAMUNE.
- HELLO, THE CASTLE!
THE DELICACY OF OSHU,
ONE-EYED DRAGON!
- WHAT?
- YOUR LOVELY GUARDS AT THE GATE
TOLD ME I COULD FIND YOU HERE.
- IF YOU'RE HUNGRY,
I THINK YOU WANT THE TEA HOUSE.
- WELL, HE'S GOING TO BE
A TOUGH NUT TO CRACK.
THOUGH, I'D EXPECT NO LESS.
- WHAT BUSINESS DO YOU HAVE
WITH LORD MASAMUNE?
YOU ARE IN THE PRESENCE OF THE
BIG BOSS OF OSHU, AFTER ALL.
IT WOULD BE PROPER IF YOU'D
INTRODUCE YOURSELF FIRST.
- OH, SORRY.
MY NAME'S MAEDA KEIJI.
PLEASURE MAKING
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
THIS HERE'S YUMEKICHI.
- ( squeaks )
- WE HAVE NO NEED OF A STREET
PERFORMER HERE. MOVE ALONG.
- MY WORD, THIS PLACE IS
IN LACK OF A WOMAN'S TOUCH.
GETTING LOVE TO BLOOM HERE?
GOT TO BE ONE HELL OF A CHORE.
- ( squeaks )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF CARNIVAL YOU CAME FROM,
BUT YOU'RE WAY TOO HAPPY
FOR MY LIKING.
- Takeda: LEAVE THAT
RIGHT WHERE IT IS.
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
MAY I FORMALLY
CONGRATULATE YOU, SIR,
FOR YOUR DECISIVE TAKING
OF ODAWARA CASTLE!
- YES. THOUGH MERE
CIRCUMSTANCE LED US HERE,
THAT BASTARD DATE HAD US
DANCING TO HIS TUNE ALL ALONG.
- NO. "ALL WHO PROSPER
SHALL ONE DAY FALL!"
THIS DEFINES THAT PROVERB.
HOJO'S LANDS WERE FATED
TO BECOME TAKEDA'S.
LORDSHIP, YOUR GRACE IN
HONORING YOUR FALLEN ENEMY
AS A TRUE WARRIOR
ONLY PROVES IT.
AND THIS HUMBLE SERVANT
IS DEEPLY MOVED.
- YUKIMURA, WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF ODA NOBUNAGA?
- SIR, I SENSED SOMETHING
ODD ABOUT HIM.
I CANNOT QUITE DESCRIBE IT.
A MENACING, ALMOST OTHER
WORLDLY QUALITY,
AND AN OMINOUS AURA
THAT COULD NOT BE DISMISSED
AS SIMPLE BLOOD LUST.
EVEN SO, HE IS NO THREAT
TO YOU, YOUR LORDSHIP!
- TELL ME THEN, WHY DO YOU
SUPPOSE THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
OF OSHU HAS MADE
HIMSELF SCARCE OF LATE?
- WELL, SIR, I'D GUESS
HE IS REBUILDING HIS STRENGTH.
AFTER CONFRONTING THE DEVIL KING
OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN.
HE WOULD NOT BE LOOKING
FOR MORE BATTLES!
- ( grunting loudly )
DO YOU TRULY BELIEVE THAT?
SPEAK, YOUNG CUB!
- CERTAINLY, YOUR LORDSHIP,
YOU ARE NOT SAYING THE
ONE-EYED DRAGON KNOWS FEAR,
THAT HE IS AFRAID OF THOSE
WHO OPENLY SNATCHED
IMAGAWA'S HEAD FROM
HIM? THAT MAN HAS STRENGTH
AND RESOLVE THE LIKES OF
WHICH I HAVE NEVER SEEN!
IMPOSSIBLE! IF THAT IS INDEED
TRUE, I SEVERELY MISJUDGED HIM.
( screaming )
- TO NOT KNOW FEAR
IS SHEER FOLLY!
TO KNOW FEAR IS NECESSARY. IT IS
THE KEY TO PROPER STRATEGY!
- BUT, YOUR LORDSHIP,
TO BE AFRAID OF ONE'S ENEMIES...
- YUKIMURA, TO WHAT PURPOSE
DO YOU WIELD YOUR SPEAR
IN THESE TURBULENT TIMES?
WHY DO YOU FIGHT?
- TO BE OF SERVICE TO YOU,
YOUR LORDSHIP!
HUMBLY AND WITH
ALL MY HEART. AND AS SUCH,
I WISH FOR YOUR CONTINUED
CONQUEST OF THE COUNTRY,
UNTIL YOU RULE THIS LAND
OF THE RISING SUN!
- AND WHEN THAT HAS COME TO
PASS, WHAT WILL YOU DO THEN?
- YOUR LORDSHIP, I SHALL EVER
REMAIN BY YOUR SIDE!
I SHALL SPEND MY LIFE
IN YOUR HUMBLE...
- THERE WILL SOON COME A TIME
WHEN EVEN YOU UNDERSTAND.
- YOUR LORDSHIP?
- Date: WHAT? AN ALLIANCE?
- MY HOPE IS TO BRING GENERALS
TOGETHER IN A UNITED FRONT.
THEN PIT OURSELVES
AGAINST THE DEVIL KING OF OWARI.
- THAT'S ONE
I HAVEN'T HEARD BEFORE.
A STREET PERFORMER RIDING
REIN ON A BUNCH OF SAMURAI.
- UH, MASAMUNE?
- WHAT?
- THIS MAN, HE'S THE MAEDA
FAMILY'S WANDERING ROGUE.
- REALLY? THAT MAKES SENSE.
- NO WONDER I THOUGHT
YOUR PLAN WAS BEYOND CRAZY.
- YEAH, WELL,
CRAZY'S KIND OF MY THING.
POINT IS THE TIME
FOR SQUABBLING
OVER OUR PETTY
DIFFERENCES IS OVER.
IN ANY CONFLICT,
THE MORE IT ESCALATES,
THE HARDER IT BECOMES
FOR THOSE INVOLVED
TO SEE THINGS CLEARLY.
THAT IS ESPECIALLY TRUE IN WAR.
DATE OF OSHU, TAKEDA OF KAI,
UESUGI OF ECHIGO,
AND TOKUGAWA OF MIKAWA
WILL SECURE THE EASTERN FRONT.
THEN ASAKURA OF ECHIZEN,
AZAI OF OMI,
AND AS MANY OF THE WESTERN
GENERALS AS WE CAN GET,
WILL SURROUND ODA.
AND I'LL PITCH IN TOO,
WHEREVER I CAN.
- NOT ONE FOR BREVITY, ARE YOU?
ODA NOBU-NAGA.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
HE'S NOT JUST ANY OLD MAN.
- YOU'VE MET THE DEVIL KING?
THEN YOU UNDERSTAND!
A MAN OF YOUR SKILL...
- A MAN OF MY SKILL
ISN'T INTERESTED
IN SERVING UNDER SOMEONE ELSE.
- THIS ISN'T A MATTER
OF WHO SERVES WHOM!
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY HERE...
- SINCE IT'S CLEAR
YOU WON'T DROP IT...
MAKE ME SEE THINGS YOUR WAY.
- ( sighs )
I REALLY DID NOT COME HERE
LOOKING TO FIGHT WITH YOU.
BUT IF IT'S SOME
ONE-ON-ONE YOU WANT,
I HEAR YOU'VE GOT A GREAT
RED-LIGHT DISTRICT.
- SHUT UP!
- YOUR WAY, THEN,
ONE-EYED DRAGON.
- WHAT THE HELL'S THIS?
- I'VE HEARD MANY A TALE
OF YOUR DAUNTING ABILITIES.
FIGURE KEEPING IT SHEATHED
MAKES IT A FAIR FIGHT.
- YOU WON'T LIKE ME
WHEN I'M ANGRY.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SAYING
YOU WEREN'T ALREADY?
- KOJURO!
- AS ALWAYS, BOSS,
ENJOY YOURSELF.
- ( grunting )
- FIND LOVE
WHERE YOU CAN. DRIVEL.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN ECHIGO?
- IT'S OKAY. I'M JUST TRACKING
SOMEONE'S MOVEMENTS.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
TRAVELING VARIOUS LANDS,
MEETING UP WITH GENERALS.
- THAT MAEDA SCOUNDREL,
I ASSUME.
- AH, SO HE WAS HERE.
- AND HE IS NOT ANY LONGER.
- WHERE'D HE HEAD OFF TO? OSHU?
- NO CLUE.
- HMM...
- WHAT?
- I SEE, HE AND KENSHIN GOT
ALONG BETTER THAN YOU'D LIKE,
SO YOUR HEART BURNS
WITH FLAMES OF JEALOUSY!
- THAT IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS!
- CRAZY. NOW, THEN.
IT IS JUST AS MY LORD SUSPECTED.
HOW WILL YOU RESPOND,
ONE-EYED DRAGON?
- ( grunting )
- WHAT IS THE POINT OF RULING
IF YOU NEVER FIND HAPPINESS?
RATHER THAN BLEED OUT
ON A DISTANT BATTLEFIELD,
WOULDN'T YOU RATHER PERISH
IN THE ARMS OF A LOVED ONE?
I WOULD. THE THOUGHT OF
SEEING TOSHI AND MATSU
TORN APART BY WAR...
THAT IS MORE
THAN I CAN EVER BEAR!
I KNOW IT MUST SEEM TRIVIAL
TO SOMEONE LIKE YOU!
WHY RULE,
IF NOT TO MAKE A BETTER WORLD.
WHERE WE ARE FREE
TO LOVE AND FIGHT,
LAUGH AND CRY, FIND HAPPINESS!
A WORLD WORTH DYING FOR!
- ( grunting )
( screaming )
- ( groaning )
- SORRY, FLOWER BOY.
GO SELL IT SOMEPLACE ELSE.
- UH, UH...
AH, MAN, TOUGH NUT INDEED.
- I HAVE TO SAY, SIR,
I AM RELIEVED.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- AT OKEHAZAMA,
HOW YOU LOST YOUR COURAGE
WHEN FACING THE DEVIL KING.
- YOU ASS.
ENOUGH WITH THE SARCASM.
- LORD MASAMUNE, SURELY YOU
MUST HAVE NOTICED IT YOURSELF.
AT THAT MOMENT,
YOU KNEW YOU COULD NOT DIE.
THAT YOUR POSITION IS SUCH,
THAT YOU COULD SIMPLY
NOT AFFORD TO.
AND YOU CAME TO REALIZE THIS
WITH EVERY FIBER OF YOUR BEING.
YOU SAW A MAN WHO CARRIES
THE LIVES OF HIS PEOPLE
UPON HIS SHOULDERS,
THEIR PRIDE, THEIR FUTURE.
YOU SAW THE RULER OF A NATION.
I AM ASHAMED I DID
NOT NOTICE IT MYSELF.
NOT UNTIL THAT STRANGE
VAGABOND MADE ME REALIZE IT.
HOWEVER, SIR, KEIJI'S CHALLENGE
CANNOT GO UNANSWERED.
THE PEOPLE OF OSHU
AND ITS ENTIRE ARMY,
ARE PREPARED TO FOLLOW
WHATEVER DECISION YOU MAKE.
- KOJURO.
- AS AM I. SINCE OUR
FIRST CAMPAIGN,
I HAVE BEEN YOUR RIGHT EYE.
AND I ALWAYS WILL BE.
THOUGH, LATELY, IT FEELS LIKE
ALL I EVER DO ANYMORE
IS TELL YOU WHAT NOT TO DO.
- WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
SOMEONE HAS TO
MAKE A STAND EVENTUALLY.
NOT SOMEONE. ONLY ONE MAN CAN.
AND THAT'S ME.
I TRUST YOU'LL HAVE
MY BACK, KOJURO.
- SIR.
- Date: YOU BOYS READY?
- All: YEAH!
- TO OWARI!
WE FIND ODA AND TAKE HIS HEAD!
- All: LET'S RIDE!
- ALL RIGHT!
THEN LET'S MAKE SOME TRACKS!
- ( all cheering )
- TIME TO ROLL THE DICE
AND I'M ALL-IN WITH OSHU
TO TRY THE LUCK OF
THE WHOLE COUNTRY!
- ( theme song playing )
- Azai: GAZE WELL ON
MY VALIANT FORM!
IN THE NAME OF JUSTICE,
YOU MUST WITNESS
OUR NEXT INSTALLMENT!
THOSE WHO DO NOT
SHALL BE DEEMED EVIL.
AND I, AZAI NAGAMASA,
SHALL ERADICATE THEM!