- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- TOSHIIE, MATSU,
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
GOING TO WAR AGAINST KENSHIN?
HYAH!
- ( horse whinnies )
- Kasuga:
MY LORD KENSHIN,
THE MAEDA ARMY, LED BY LORD
TOSHIIE AND HIS WIFE MATSU
IS APPROACHING THE BORDER
OF OUR TERRITORIES.
THEIR NUMBERS AND CONFIGURATION
ARE AS WE ESTIMATED.
IT APPEARS THEY INTEND
TO BRING THEIR ENTIRE ARMY
TO BEAR AGAINST US,
INCLUDING THEIR ARQUEBUS CORPS.
- LORD TOSHIIE REMAINS
AS FORTHRIGHT AS EVER.
WHERE HAS KEIJI GONE?
- IT SEEMS HE IS RIDING OUT
TO MEET WITH THE MAEDA FORCES,
AND KNOWING WHAT I DO OF HIM,
I ASSUME KEIJI BELIEVES HE'S
ABLE TO CONVINCE THEM
TO HALT THEIR INVASION.
- HE WOULD TRY.
ALTHOUGH IT PAINS ME TO DO SO,
WE SHALL PROCEED.
- MILORD.
- MAY BISHAMONTEN'S DIVINE
PROTECTION GO WITH YOU.
- WHOA!
HYAH!
TOSHIIE, MATSU,
WAIT, LISTEN TO ME.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO,
IT'S KEIJI.
- WE WILL NOT BE
STOPPING, MATSU.
- WHAT?
- WE WILL PRESS ON.
- AS YOU WISH, MY LORD HUSBAND.
- TOSHIIE, MATSU, PLEASE STOP.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO WHAT I--
- TOSHIIE, MATSU!
SO MUCH FOR BEING RATIONAL.
- Kasuga: LEAVE IT
TO LORD KENSHIN FROM HERE.
- KASUGA.
- GO WHEREVER THIS ROAD
MAY TAKE YOU
WITNESSING THIS WAR WILL
ONLY BRING YOU MORE PAIN,
AND YOU WILL MOST CERTAINLY
ONLY BE IN OUR WAY.
BUT MY LORD WISHES TO ASSURE YOU
THAT HE WILL DO EVERYTHING
IN HIS POWER.
- LORD UESUGI KENSHIN,
WAR GOD OF ECHIGO, I PRESUME.
I AM LORD MAEDA TOSHIIE,
PROTECTOR OF THE LAND OF KAGA.
- AND I AM HIS WIFE
LADY MATSU.
- I'VE HEARD MUCH
ABOUT YOU BOTH.
- YOU HAVE ALWAYS SHOWN
MY NEPHEW KEIJI KINDNESS.
- MY LORD HUSBAND, THIS MAN
IS NOW OUR OPPONENT IN WAR.
- LORD UESUGI, SURELY YOU DO
NOT INTEND TO ENGAGE US
WITH SUCH A PALTRY FORCE
AT YOUR BACK.
I KNOW YOUR REPUTATION
AS A WAR GOD, BUT--
- THESE BLESSED FIELDS
OF ECHIGO,
I HAVE NO INTENTION OF STAINING
THEM WITH THE BLOOD OF WAR.
LORD TOSHIIE, LADY MATSU,
WITHDRAW IMMEDIATELY.
I HAVE DISPATCHED THE ENTIRETY
OF THE UESUGI ARMY TO KAGA.
- YOU FIEND.
- IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING THAT
YOUR CASTLE WILL FALL,
BUT IT IS ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE INNOCENTS BEGIN
TO SUFFER AS WELL.
THAT IS THE PRICE YOU PAY
FOR ALLYING WITH THE TOYOTOMI
AND ATTEMPTING
TO INVADE MY LANDS.
SHOULD YOU STRIKE ME DOWN HERE
AND NOW,
MY BELOVED ECHIGO WILL BE YOURS,
BUT YOUR VICTORY WILL MOST
CERTAINLY COME AT THE COST
OF YOUR OWN KAGA.
- ARE YOU CLAIMING YOU SENT
YOUR TROOPS TO KAGA
WHILE WE MADE OUR WAY HERE?
I FIND THAT HARD TO BELIEVE.
- AS WOULD I.
ALTHOUGH I IMAGINE YOUR SCOUTS
WILL SOON COME RUNNING
BEARING URGENT NEWS,
HOWEVER, BY THEN IT WILL BE
TOO LATE TO ACT.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO.
- WE CANNOT WITHDRAW.
LORD HIDEYOSHI AND LORD HANBEI
HAVE PLACED THEIR FAITH IN US.
THEY HAVE ENTRUSTED US
WITH THE SUBJUGATION OF UESUGI.
FOR THE SAKE OF BUILDING
A STRONGER COUNTRY.
- Matsu: BUT THE PEOPLE OF KAGA
WILL BE HELD HOSTAGE.
- WE WILL NOT ABANDON
OUR PEOPLE.
WE WILL DEFEAT UESUGI, THEN
HASTEN BACK TO OUR HOMELAND.
- WE FACE THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO.
THIS IS THE ONLY MAN LORD TAKEDA
SHINGEN, THE TIGER OF KAI,
RECOGNIZES
AS A WORTHY OPPONENT.
EVEN WITH INUCHIYO'S
PEERLESS SKILLS WITH THE SPEAR,
THIS WILL BY NO MEANS BE EASY.
I, MATSU,
WILL UNDERTAKE THIS TASK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- MY LORD HUSBAND,
PLEASE HURRY BACK TO KAGA.
- DO NOT BE A FOOL.
- YOUR CONCERN FOR ME
IS UNNECESSARY.
HAVING DEFEATED DATE,
ARMIES FROM ASHINA, NANBU
AND TSUGARU WILL BE SURE
TO ARRIVE HERE SOON.
- YES, BUT--
- SO MY OPPONENT IS TO BE YOUR
WIFE THEN, LORD TOSHIIE?
- IT IS.
PLEASE, MY LORD HUSBAND,
YOU MUST MAKE HASTE.
EXPOSING THE INNOCENT PEOPLE
OF KAGA TO SUCH DANGER
MUST NOT COME TO PASS.
- PREPARE YOURSELF.
- READY WHEN YOU ARE.
- MATSU.
WE WILL RETURN HOME.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO FIGHT THEM.
- RIGHT.
- WE'VE BEEN SURROUNDED.
- MY LORD HUSBAND,
IS IT POSSIBLE LORD UESUGI
HOPES TO FORCE OUR SURRENDER
WITHOUT BLOODSHED?
- INDEED.
LORD UESUGI KENSHIN,
HE IS A COMPASSIONATE WARRIOR,
JUST AS WE'D HEARD FROM KEIJI.
BUT BE THAT AS IT MAY.
I CANNOT, WILL NOT
LAY DOWN MY SPEAR NOW.
DESTROY THE UESUGI ARMY!
- ( shouting )
- I AM THE INVINCIBLE
PROTAGONIST.
I SPENT A YEAR EARNING
MY REPUTATION.
UESUGI'S FIRST UNIT.
NAOE KANETSUGU!
I HAVE NO INTENTION OF LOSING
TO THE LIKES OF--
WHY DOES THIS KEEP HAPPENING
TO ME?
- ( shouting )
- KEIJI.
YOUR DEMEANOR TELLS ME THAT
YOU HAVE NOT COME TO OUR AID.
SORRY, YOU MADE
YOUR POSITION CLEAR.
I'LL HAVE TO SPEAK WITH LANGUAGE
YOU UNDERSTAND.
- KEIJI.
- A WIN FOR MAEDA IS
A WIN FOR TOYOTOMI.
AND THAT IS NOT SOMETHING
I CAN ABIDE.
I WILL NOT STAND IDLY BY
AND LET IT HAPPEN.
- SO BE IT.
- MY LORD HUSBAND, NO.
- BETTER DO THIS FOR REAL,
TOSHIIE.
- DON'T WORRY,
I NEVER HOLD BACK.
( screaming )
- EVEN IF YOU MANAGE
TO SUBDUE YOUR OPPONENT,
SOMEDAY, SOMEONE ELSE WILL
ALWAYS COME TO SUBDUE YOU.
WHY CAN'T YOU SEEM
TO UNDERSTAND THAT?
- BUT I DO UNDERSTAND.
I WANT TO END VIOLENCE COMMITTED
IN THE NAME OF UNJUST DEEDS.
THAT IS WHY I FIGHT.
SO THAT NO ONE ELSE EVER HAS TO.
- KEIJI.  MY LORD INUCHIYO.
PLEASE STOP THIS.
WHY MUST YOU TWO CROSS SWORDS?
- ( explosion )
( men screaming )
- TOYOTOMI IS TRYING
TO BUILD A STRONG COUNTRY.
ONCE HE COMES TO POWER,
WE WILL ALL KNOW PEACE AT LAST.
- DAMN IT, TOSHIIE.
WHAT HE'S TRYING TO CREATE ISN'T
THE KIND OF WORLD YOU WANT.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I CANNOT YIELD.
( grunting )
- KEIJI.
- MY LORD INUCHIYOU.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO!
- HIDEYOSHI!
- I CANNOT YIELD.
- TOSHIIE.
I'M SO SORRY.
- ( screaming )
- DEFEND YOURSELF, KEIJI.
- Uesugi:
WITHDRAW, LADY MATSU.
THE MAEDA GENERAL
HAS BEEN GRAVELY INJURED.
- BUT, LORD UESUGI, I--
- FOR THE SAKE OF LOVED ONES,
FOR THEIR FUTURES,
THERE ARE THOSE WHO
TAKE UP THE SWORD
AND THOSE WHO DO NOT
AND BOTH ARE RIGHT.
YOUR NEPHEW HAS CHOSEN
THE PATH OF LOVE,
WHILE HIS FORMER FRIEND
HAS CHOSEN THE SWORD,
AS HAS YOUR HUSBAND.
BUT IN TRUTH, LORD TOSHIIE
AND KEIJI ARE NOT SO DIFFERENT.
BOTH WANT THE SAME THING.
PEACEFUL UNITY FOR ALL.
IT IS A BITTER IRONY.
- OH.
- WAKE ON UP, BOYS.
I SAID, WAKE UP!
- BIG BOSS.
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
YOU DID A GOOD JOB,
SURVIVING THAT ONE,
BUT WE HAVE TAKEN BACK OSHU
FOR THE TIME BEING.
- All: RIGHT.
- SON OF A--
- DAMN IT.
ONLY MASTER KATAKURA CAN KEEP
BIG BOSS'S BACK PROTECTED.
- WE'LL GO HOME AND PREPARE FOR
WAR, THEN WE'LL HEAD FOR OSAKA.
WE'LL CRUSH TOYOTOMI,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO
GET KOJURO BACK.
- RIGHT.
- OH!
- NO WAY.
THAT LOOKS LIKE.
- TO-- TOYO--
- TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI.
YOU DEFINITELY GOT BALLS
OF STEEL,
COMING HERE TO GREET ME
IN PERSON.
I SHOULD THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME THE TROUBLE
OF GOING ALL THE WAY
TO OSAKA.
- SNAKES ARE MORE TENACIOUS
THAN ONE MIGHT EXPECT,
NO MATTER HOW HARMLESS
THEY APPEAR.
- HA!  SURE YOU SAY THAT, BUT
YOU DON'T SEEM TOO CONFIDENT,
ESPECIALLY FOR SOMEONE
OF YOUR SIZE.
YOU'RE UNEASY,
LEFT THE EXTERMINATION
OF A SNAKE TO THE B-TEAM,
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY
TO CHECK UP ON IT FOR YOURSELF.
YOU'RE SHOWING ME
YOUR TRUE COLORS.
THOSE EYES SEE ME
FOR THE DRAGON I REALLY AM.
- A MISERABLE RETORT.
SO YOU INTEND TO DEFY ME.
EVEN WHEN ALL YOUR SCALES HAVE
BEEN PEELED AWAY
AND YOU'VE ALREADY
LOST YOUR RIGHT EYE?
- GUESS I WAS WRONG.
I GAVE YOU TOO MUCH CREDIT
IN THE BRAIN DEPARTMENT.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A SNAKE AND A DRAGON
IS IN ITS BITE.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU CAN'T TAKE A DRAGON'S SCALES
UNTIL HE'S KICKED THE BUCKET.
NOT A SINGLE DAMN ONE.
I SHALL NOW TEACH YOU A LESSON
IN UTTER DEFEAT.
- ( screaming )
- YUKIMURA, WE SHOULD SEND
A FEW MEN TO FIND A PLACE
TO MAKE CAMP SOON.
- THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
- IS THERE SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- NO, JUST EVER SINCE
WE ENTERED OMI,
IT SEEMS THE PEOPLE HERE HAVE
BEEN LABORING CEASELESSLY,
WORKING TO THE BONE,
MORNING, DAY AND NIGHT.
AND LOOK AT THEM.  THEY'RE
ALL WOMEN OR THE ELDERLY,
OR THOSE STILL
OF TENDER YEARS.
- IT IS MOST LIKELY DUE
TO TOYOTOMI'S CONSCRIPTION.
THEY SAY THAT ALL THE SOLDIERS
UNDER HIS COMMAND
ARE ROUNDED UP IN ONE PLACE
AND PUT THROUGH UNIMAGINABLY
RIGOROUS MILITARY TRAINING.
- I HAD HEARD TALE OF THIS
FROM SASUKE AS WELL, BUT...
( gasps )
I MUSTN'T.  RIGHT NOW,
I MUST TAKE THE TROOPS
MY LORD ENTRUSTED TO ME
AND VENTURE STRAIGHT TO SATSUMA
TO FOIL TOYOTOMI'S
SINISTER DESIGNS.
IF I CONCERNED MYSELF WITH
EVERY PERSON I CAME ACROSS...
MASTER OYAMADA,
I SHALL BE BACK IN A MOMENT.
- ( Ichi whimpering )
I-- I AM SO SORRY.
- THAT VOICE.
IT CANNOT BE.
- THIS--
THIS IS ALL
MY FAULT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ichi: THIS CASTLE,
IT IS MY BROTHER'S
GRAVE MARKER.
I BEG OF YOU,
PLEASE LET HIM REST IN PEACE.
WHEN WE RETURN,
IT WILL BE ALL MY FAULT AGAIN.