- ( shouting )
- LONG TIME NO SEE,
SANADA YUKIMURA.
SO YOU DOING
ALL RIGHT THERE?
- ONE-EYED DRAGON,
DATE MASAMUNE.
I HAVE YEARNED FOR THIS
MOMENT THESE PAST YEARS.
NOW, WITH HONOR FIGHT ME!
- THAT'S WHY I'M HERE,
BUT DON'T HOLD ANYTHING BACK.
I WANNA HAVE SOME FUN
WITH THIS.
YEAH, LET'S GET IT ON!
BURN, MY SOUL.
BURN ABLAZE!
- OH, MAN.
ALL SIX SWORDS FROM THE START.
- CAN YOU BLAME HIM?  SANADA'S
MORE OF A BADASS THAN BEFORE.
- (  shouting )
- LISTEN UP, GUYS.
AS SOON AS BOSS MASAMUNE WINS,
WE CHARGE.
- All: YEAH!
- HERE AT KAWANAKAJIMA, MY LORD
TAKEDA AND LORD KENSHIN
WILL FINALLY HAVE
THEIR DECISIVE BATTLE.
I WILL NOT LET YOU INTERFERE!
- SORRY, BUT THE ONE-EYED
DRAGON OF OSHU'S
GONNA CONQUER THIS COUNTRY,
AND NO ONE'S GONNA STAND IN
MY WAY.  THIS PARTY'S CRASHED.
- ( grunting )
- ( screaming )
- ( laughs ) I'VE NOT FELT LIKE
THIS IN SOME TIME.
- NOR HAVE I.
- MAY THIS BATTLE FINALLY
ENRICH BOTH OUR HEARTS,
LORD KENSHIN.
- TIGER OF KAI,
I SHALL REGALE YOU
BY BRINGING ALL I HAVE TO BEAR
UNDER BISHAMONTEN'S
DIVINE GUIDANCE,
I SHALL TAKE YOU DOWN.
- PLEASE LET ME MAKE IT
THERE IN TIME.
I RESPECT YOUR AMBITION,
ONE-EYED DRAGON,
BUT YOU SHOULD WITHDRAW.
- HUH?
- I WISH NOTHING MORE THAN
TO SETTLE OUR RIVALRY,
BUT YOU SHOULD WAIT UNTIL
WE HAVE DEFEATED THE UESUGI,
SO WE MAY HONOR THE DATE
WITH THE CLEAN,
ONE-ON-ONE BATTLE
YOU HAVE EARNED.
- FUNNY YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
A BIT, RED.
THE BEST TIME FOR A FIGHT'S
WHEN IT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
SHOULD I HAVE SCHEDULED
AN APPOINTMENT?
IN THE TIME IT TAKES ME
TO STOMP YOU,
THE FIGHT BETWEEN OLD MAN TAKEDA
AND THE WAR GOD'LL BE DECIDED.
I WON'T EVEN HAVE TO INTRUDE.
WHICHEVER ONE OF THEM'S STILL
STANDING WILL FALL PREY
TO THE DRAGON.  SEE?
- YOUR WORDS TELL ME YOU
HAVE NOT CHANGED, EITHER.
YOU LEAVE ME LITTLE CHOICE.
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- PHANTOM DIVE!
- ( screaming )
- LORD TAKEDA.
- MY LORD KENSHIN.
- WHAT IS THE MATTER, SASUKE?
- YES, KASUGA, WHAT IS IT?
- AN URGENT REPORT, MY LORD.
- ARMY FROM THE NORTHWEST.
LOT OF TROOPS.
- MY FIST CLENCHES
WITH THE FURY OF A VOLCANO.
SANADA YUKIMURA
WILL NEVER YIELD.
NEVER.
- IT'S A SHAME TO SEE HIM FALL,
BUT HE'S DONE.
- ( shouting )
- ( groaning )
- WARRIORS AT KAWANAKAJIMA,
HEAR OUR DECREE.
WE, THE TOYOTOMI ARMY,
HAVE NOW
COMPLETELY SURROUNDED
THIS BATTLEFIELD.
WE WILL ACCEPT YOUR IMMEDIATE
AND UNCONDITIONAL SURRENDER.
UNDER OUR TERMS, THE TOYOTOMI
WILL TREAT YOU FAIRLY,
AND WE WILL LEAVE YOU
WITH YOUR LIVELIHOODS.
- I'VE BEEN CARELESS.
- RELEASE BOWS!
- ( roars )
( roars )
I AM TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI.
PLEDGE YOUR FEALTY TO ME NOW
AND BECOME ONE UNDER MY COMMAND.
TOGETHER WE SHALL BRING
PROSPERITY
TO THE LAND AS MEN OF VALOR.
- GOTTA SAY, NEW GUY, YOU SURE
KNOW HOW TO MAKE AN ENTRANCE,
BUT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
JUST AIN'T GONNA FLY.
- DATE MASAMUNE.
WHAT A SURPRISE.
- Sanada:
LORD MASAMUNE.
- HOO-BOY!
WORKED YOU OVER PRETTY GOOD.
NOW THEN, HOW TO FIGHT
OUR WAY OUT OF HERE.
MASTER KATAKURA.
- SARUTOBI.
I NEED YOU TO RUN A MESSAGE.
OBEY ME.
THOSE WHO DO NOT
SHALL BE GRANTED NO MERCY.
- WHAT A RELIEF.  I THOUGHT YOU
WERE SCARED OF A REAL FIGHT.
I TELL YOU WHAT, CHIEF.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT
IF YOU CAN PIERCE ONE
OF THIS DRAGON'S SCALES.
- YOU DO NOT KNOW
YOUR PLACE, WHELP.
SHALL I BE THE ONE
WHO SHOWS IT TO YOU?
- OH, PLEASE TRY.
BEEN TOO LONG SINCE I FACED
SOMEONE WHO TRULY MADE ME SICK.
- BOSS MASAMUNE.
- KOJURO, NO INTERFERENCE.
- Takenaka:
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON OF OSHU.
THE TIGER OF KAI,
THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO.
COMMANDERS OF UNCOMMON QUALITY.
IT SEEMS LIKE A BIT OF A WASTE
THAT WE WILL BE FORCED
TO CRUSH THEM.
- NO MATTER.  ALL WE DESIRE
OF THEM ARE THEIR TROOPS.
- DATE MASAMUNE,
THE BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
FULL SPEED AHEAD.
- WHAT DID I JUST TELL YOU?
- BOSS MASAMUNE,
THERE ARE TWO OF THEM.
PLEASE ALLOW YOUR RIGHT EYE
TO ENGAGE THE OTHER OPPONENT.
- ALL RIGHT, GUY IN THE COSPLAY
MASK IS ALL YOURS.
- ( screaming )
- WAR DANCE!
- SHATTER!
- BOSS MASAMUNE, LET US TAKE
THIS OPPORTUNITY TO WITHDRAW.
- DO WHAT?
( shouts )
- ( horse whinnies )
- LET THEM RETREAT.
- Narrator: TURBULENT TIMES
ONCE AGAIN FELL UPON THE LAND
OF THE RISING SUN.
SEEKING TO CONQUER
THE FRACTURED COUNTRY,
WARRIORS RETURNED
TO THE BATTLEFIELD
WITH EVEN GREATER FERVOR
AND BARING EVEN SHARPER FANGS.
- NO, I'M TOO LATE.
YOU BASTARDS, I SHOULD HAVE
BEEN HERE TO STOP THIS.
- HIDEYOSHI.
DAMN YOU.
- Narrator:
THE SENGOKU PERIOD,
A TIME OF CHAOS AND BLOODSHED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- TOSHI, WHY WOULD YOU JOIN UP
WITH A MAN LIKE TOYOTOMI?
I GOT WIND OF IT IN KYOTO.
I WAS SURE YOU TWO WOULD BE
AT KAWANAKAJIMA,
SO I RUSHED THERE AS FAST
AS I COULD.
IF I'D FOUND YOU,
EITHER OF YOU,
AMONG THE DEAD THERE, I ...
- I AM IN AGREEMENT
WITH LORD HIDEYOSHI.
THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN
HAS GROWN VULNERABLE.
THANKS TO ODA NOBUNAGA,
AND THE DEEDS COMMITTED
IN THE NAME
OF HIS "WORLD UNDER
WARRIOR RULE."
WE WERE THERE.
WE LET IT ALL HAPPEN.
TOYOTOMI IS TRYING TO MAKE
THIS COUNTRY STRONG
AND PROSPEROUS AGAIN
INSTEAD OF ONE DOMAIN
FIGHTING ANOTHER,
HE WOULD HAVE US WORK TOGETHER
AS ONE, AS A NATION.
I'VE BEEN AWAITING
YOUR RETURN.
PLEASE, KEIJI,
WILL YOU HELP US?
YOU AND LORD HIDEYOSHI
ARE OLD ACQUAINTANCES.
CLOSE FRIENDS,
ARE YOU NOT?
- THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
I GUESS A PART OF ME KNEW
A DAY LIKE THIS MIGHT COME,
BUT I NEVER IMAGINED I WOULD
HEAR THESE WORDS COMING
FROM YOU, TOSHI.
AND, MATSU, YOU'RE OKAY
WITH ALL OF THIS?
WE ALL WANT THE COUNTRY
TO BE STRONG.
BUT DO HIDEYOSHI'S MEANS
JUSTIFY THAT END?
- WE COULD HAVE FOUND A WAY
TO MAINTAIN NEUTRALITY.
HOWEVER, MY LORD INUCHIYO
DID NOT CONSIDER IT
THE HONORABLE THING TO DO.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU'LL SUPPORT
WHATEVER DECISION TOSHI MAKES.
- I WILL, AS THE WIFE
OF ANY WARRIOR SHOULD.
- LORD HIDEYOSHI HAS
ALREADY LOST THE ONE HE LOVES,
BUT HIS GRIEF DOES
NOT RULE HIM.
IT FUELS HIS NOBLE AMBITION.
IF I WERE EVER TO--
IF MATSU EVER--
LORD HIDEYOSHI
IS ME IF I LOST MATSU.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO--
- KEIJI, PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
- YOU'RE LEAVING ALREADY?
WAIT.
AT LEAST HAVE
SUPPER BEFORE YOU GO.
I PREPARED ALL OF YOUR
FAVORITE DISHES FOR YOU.
- YEAH, I WISH I COULD,
BUT I'LL TAKE A RAIN CHECK,
OKAY?
- KEIJI.
- SO, TOSHI,
WHERE'S TOYOTOMI'S NEXT TARGET?
- KEIJI, DON'T.
- OF COURSE YOU CAN'T SAY.
TOYOTOMI HAS INITIATED
A KIND OF SECRET INVASION.
I'M SORRY, SIR.
I SHOULD HAVE FIGURED
IT OUT SOONER.
THEY'VE BEEN SYSTEMATICALLY
EMBEDDING THEIR PEOPLE
IN EVERY ARMY FOR SOME TIME NOW.
- AND HE'S TAKEN UTSUNOMIYA
AND ODAWARA.
- YOUR LORDSHIP.
GIVEN THIS AFFRONT,
SURELY WE HAVE NO RECOURSE,
BUT TO ATTACK OSAKA.
THOUGH HE SURPRISED US
AT KAWANAKAJIMA,
WITH THE UNSTOPPABLE TAKEDA
CAVALRY AT OUR SIDE,
IF WE COULD ONLY FACE THEM
FULLY PREPARED,
THEN WE WOULD HAVE AN EXCELLENT
CHANCE OF WINNING--
- BUFFOON!
WE'VE LOST ALREADY.
THOSE LANDS WERE
UNDER OUR CARE.
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO KAI
IF LEFT UNATTENDED?
I'M CERTAIN YOU CAN IMAGINE.
- THAT IS THE REASON
WE MUST STRIKE NOW WHILE
HIS GUARD IS DOWN!
- PRECISELY WHAT TOYOTOMI WANTS.
FALL FOR THAT RUSE,
AND WE COURT OUR OWN DEMISE.
- THEN WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE US DO?
STAND IDLY BY AND WAIT
FOR TOYOTOMI TO INVADE US?
- YOU LACK PATIENCE.
YUKIMURA, I AM SYMPATHETIC
TO YOUR POSITION.
YOU WERE BESTED BY YOUR RIVAL
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
HAD IT NOT BEEN FOR TOYOTOMI'S
UNEXPECTED ARRIVAL,
YOU WOULD HAVE SUFFERED UTTER
DEFEAT AT MASAMUNE'S HANDS,
WHICH MAKES IT DOUBLY
HUMILIATING, I'M SURE.
- YOUR LORDSHIP,
AS YOUR HUMBLE SERVANT,
I BEG FOR YOUR FORGIVENESS.
MY DESIRE WAS MERELY
TO REDEEM MYSELF
AND DEMONSTRATE MY DEVOTION.
- YOU MAY BEGIN YOUR REDEMPTION
BY LEARNING TO SUPPRESS DESIRE.
ALL THE MORE SO, GIVEN YOUR
RECENT BRUSH WITH MORTALITY,
CAST YOUR SELF-DOUBT ASIDE AND
KEEP YOUR EYES ON THE FUTURE.
- I UNDERSTAND, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- SASUKE, WHAT NEWS
OF MOVEMENTS TO THE WEST?
- AN AGENT OF TOYOTOMI APPEARS
TO BE MAKING CONTACT
WITH MORI OF AKI.
- HMM, AN ALLIANCE?
- LOOKS LIKE.
DUE TO SHEER SIZE,
MORI'S ABILITY TO MAINTAIN
HIS HOLDINGS IS A BIT TENUOUS.
OF COURSE, THE ALLIANCE WOULD
BE A HUGE LAND-GRAB FOR TOYOTOMI
AS FOR MORI, HE'D GAIN
THE MILITARY BACKING
FOR A MORE-THAN-DECISIVE
BATTLE WITH HIS RIVAL,
CHOSOKABE OF SHIKOKU.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE--
- I STILL BELIEVE OUR ONLY
CHOICE IS TO STORM OSAKA.
- YOU BUFFOON!
YOUR VIEW IS TOO NARROW, BOY.
BY THAT MERE FACT, YOU HAVE
ALREADY LOST TO TOYOTOMI.
- IF HE ADDS MORI'S HOLDINGS
TO HIS OWN,
HIS DOMAIN WILL ENCOMPASS
AN ENTIRE HALF OF THE LAND
OF THE RISING SUN.
- LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
WE NEED NOT LOSE OUR HEADS,
BECAUSE IT IS STILL ONLY HALF!
- ( screams )
- HAVE YOU TAKEN NOTHING
AWAY FROM YOUR RECENT DEFEAT?
WHEN YOU ARE SURROUNDED AND YOU
CANNOT FIGHT YOUR WAY OUT OF IT,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
- FIND A WAY TO ESCAPE?
- WE WILL MAKE OUR WAY WEST.
- WEST AS IN SETO, OR--
NO, YOU'RE SAYING WE'LL
GO EVEN FARTHER WEST?
- KYUSHU HAS YET TO FALL
INTO TOYOTOMI'S HANDS.
I HEAR WORD OF A FORCE THERE.
IN THE SOUTHERNMOST REGION
OF SATSUMA,
THEY ARE RESISTING HIS INVASION.
- SO THEN?
- YOU WILL TRAVEL TO SATSUMA
AS MY REPRESENTATIVE.
DEFEND THE LAND AND PEOPLE
AS THOUGH THEY ARE YOUR OWN.
AFTER WHICH, YOU WILL STRIKE AT
MORI AND TOYOTOMI FROM THE WEST.
- YES, IT'S BRILLIANT.
ALTHOUGH TOYOTOMI BELIEVES THAT
HE ALREADY HAS US SURROUNDED,
INSTEAD WE WILL TURN THE TABLES
AROUND AND SURROUND HIM.
- I WILL NOT LEAVE KAI UNTIL
I HEAR OF YOUR SUCCESS.
ALL WILL DEPEND UPON YOUR
PERFORMANCE, YOUNG CUB.
- YES, YOUR LORDSHIP.
ON MY HONOR, I, SANADA GENJIRO
YUKIMURA, WILL NOT FAIL YOU.
- AND REMEMBER, BOY,
IN THIS MATTER,
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
- YES, YOUR LORDSHIP.
I UNDERSTAND.
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE HE LET
UTSUNOMIYA AND ODAWARA FALL.
WHAT THE HELL WAS OLD
MAN TAKEDA DOING?
- IT APPEARS SEVERAL HOLDINGS
NOT UNDER THE TIGER OF KAI'S
DIRECT SUPERVISION WERE ATTACKED
SIMULTANEOUSLY BY DOUBLE AGENTS.
AND WE'VE JUST RECEIVED WORD
THAT MORI MOTONARI OF AKI
IS NEARING AN ALLIANCE
WITH TOYOTOMI.
- ( murmuring )
- HOWEVER,
WE HAVE A MORE IMMEDIATE
PROBLEM IN FRONT OF US.
THE NEIGHBORING LANDS WE'VE
CONQUERED HAVE NOW BEGUN
TO SHOW SIGNS OF UNREST.
- Date:
MEANING THIS "SECRET INVASION"
IS PROBABLY UNDERWAY
IN OSHU NOW, TOO.
- INDEED, WHILE I APPRECIATE
YOUR DESIRE TO MARCH
ON OSAKA IMMEDIATELY,
WE WILL FAIL IF THEY STRIKE
OUR HOME WHILE WE ARE AWAY.
THE PRIORITY IS DISCOVERING
WHAT THESE LANDS ARE UP TO.
WE MUST BE PREPARED TO CONQUER
THEM ALL OVER AGAIN.
- BASICALLY, A WHOLE LOAD
OF TROUBLE WE DON'T NEED
IS COMING THIS WAY.
- MOST LIKELY IT
HAS ALREADY ARRIVED.
TOYOTOMI WAS AWARE NOT ONLY OF
TAKEDA'S AND UESUGI'S MOVEMENTS,
BUT ALSO OF OUR PLANS TO ONCE
AGAIN INTERRUPT THEIR BATTLE
AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
INFORMATION THAT
COULD NOT HAVE BEEN HAD
WITHOUT BEING PRESENT
AT OUR WAR COUNCIL.
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING
AT ME FOR?
- OH!
NO TRAITORS OVER HERE.
- TOYOTOMI'S PLAN WAS TO GET US
ALL UNDER HIS THUMB
AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
THINK THE BASTARD'S JOB WAS
JUST TO MAKE SURE WE GOT
WHERE WE WERE SUPPOSED TO?
- NO, TAKENAKA HANBEI IS
MORE SHREWD THAN THAT.
HE WOULD HAVE ANTICIPATED
THE CHANCE OF FAILURE.
I BELIEVE IT'S LIKELY THEY WOULD
HAVE KEPT THEIR MOLE IN PLACE.
- IN THAT CASE,
DO WE SMOKE HIM OUT?
- I AM A BIT RELUCTANT
TO INTERROGATE OUR OWN PEOPLE.
BUT WE CAN START
FIRST THING TOMORROW.
- GUESS WE'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
- NO ONE HAS FLED UNDER
THE COVER OF DARKNESS.
WERE OUR SUSPICIONS GROUNDLESS?
OR IS THE SNAKE PREPARED
FOR THE WORST?
- Takenaka: WHAT AN UNCOMMONLY
GENTLE EXPRESSION.
DATE'S TRUSTED STRATEGIST,
WHO BROKE THROUGH
OUR PERFECT ENCIRCLEMENT,
WHO, WHEN CORNERED LIKE RATS,
CREATED AN ESCAPE ROUTE
BRILLIANTLY ORCHESTRATING
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF TROOPS.
IS THIS THE TRUE FACE
OF THE RIGHT EYE OF THE DRAGON?
- ( gasps )
TAKENAKA HANBEI.
- WHENEVER YOU'RE LUCKY ENOUGH
TO BE HOME,
THIS IS WHERE YOU COME EVERY
EVENING BEFORE TAKING TO BED.
ISN'T THAT CORRECT?
I HAVE A GENERAL IDEA
OF YOUR ROUTINE.
MASAMUNE'S AS WELL,
THANKS TO HIM.
- MASTER KATAKURA.
- DAMN YOU!
TAKENAKA, YOU BASTARD!
- MY DEAR KATAKURA,
LET US MAKE A DEAL.
IT'S SIMPLE.
I WANT YOU TO JOIN
THE TOYOTOMI ARMY.
- WHAT?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Takenaka: IT SEEMS THE TIME
HAS COME TO SAY FAREWELL.
PLEASE, DO JOIN US AGAIN
FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER,
AND YOU, TOO, SHALL KNEEL BEFORE
THE MIGHT OF TOYOTOMI.