- WE ARE SO SORRY, BIG BOSS.
- WE SEARCHED ALL OVER
THE PLAINS OF SURIAGEHARA,
BUT WE COULDN'T FIND THE LAST
OF YOUR SIX SWORDS.
- NO WORRIES.
THE ONES I GOT LEFT
WILL DO ME JUST FINE.
- BOSS KATAKURA!
- WHAT THE HELL'S ALL THIS?
SPEAK, KOJURO.
- I HAVE FAILED YOU,
SO I MUST TAKE MY OWN LIFE.
- WHAT?
- ON THAT BATTLEFIELD
AT HITOTORIBASHI.
THOUGH WE SECURED VICTORY
FOR OURSELVES,
I SWORE AN OATH
TO PROTECT YOUR BACK,
YET I ALLOWED YOU TO SUFFER
A MOST GRIEVOUS INJURY.
- AH, IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
NO, LORD.
WITH THE SLIGHTEST DEVIATION,
THAT WOUND COULD HAVE TAKEN
NOT ONLY THE USE OF YOUR SWORDS,
BUT ALSO YOUR LIFE.
- ( gasping )
- I KNOW THIS IS
HIGHLY IRREGULAR,
PERHAPS DRASTIC,
BUT I MUST PAY FOR MY MISTAKE.
- NO, BOSS KATAKURA, WAIT.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
- JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE
HERE, BOSS.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
SOMEONE'S GOTTA ACT
AS YOUR SECOND.
- BIG BOSS, NO!
- ( groaning )
- BIG BOSS!
- OH, MAN, WITH HIS
INJURED RIGHT HAND EVEN.
- AND THAT CUT HAD GOUGED HIM
ALL THE WAY TO THE BONE.
- THIS IS MADNESS.
- YOU GOTTA STOP CODDLING ME
LIKE I'M A CHILD.
YOU'RE MY RIGHT EYE,
DAMN IT.
IF I LOSE MY RIGHT ARM,
DON'T WASTE MY TIME
SPILLING YOUR GUTS OUT.
YOU BECOME MY RIGHT ARM, TOO.
AS YOU CAN SEE, NOT A SINGLE
BLADE TOUCHED MY BACK.
AND BESIDES...
I STILL GOT ALL OF MY CLAWS,
TODAY, TOMORROW, WHENEVER.
SO YOU GOT NOTHING
TO ATONE FOR.  ARE WE CLEAR?
- LORD MASAMUNE.
- WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
WE'RE COOL.
- I AM SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- I, KOJURO,
WILL SERVE AS YOUR RIGHT EYE
WITH EVEN GREATER RESOLVE.
MAY I OFFER MY CONGRATULATIONS
FOR YOUR CONQUEST OF OSHU.
- All:
CONGRATULATIONS, BIG BOSS.
- KOJURO.
- ALL RIGHT, BOYS, YOU READY?
- YEAH!
- PICK UP THE PACE.
- LET'S FIRE IT UP!
- YEAH!
- NOW GO KICK SOME ASS!
- BIG BOSS, UESUGI'S ARMY IS
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE RIVER.
- WHAT?
- THERE'S TOO MANY OF 'EM
FOR US TO MAKE IT THROUGH
WITHOUT A BUNCH OF TROUBLE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- BIG BOSS, IT'S NO USE.
NO MATTER WHAT WE SAY, THOSE
UESUGI JERKS JUST IGNORE US.
AND THEY'RE BLOCKING ALL
THE PATHS GOING AROUND 'EM, TOO.
- SORRY, BOSS, WE DIDN'T SPOT
ANYONE EVEN RESEMBLING
THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO.
- MAYBE THE UESUGI HAVE ALREADY
BEEN TAKEN OVER BY THE TOYOTOMI.
- SO THEN, COULD THERE BE
OTHERS?
CRAP, THEY'RE TRYING
TO BOX US IN AGAIN.
- OH, SHUT IT.  GETTING ALL
WORKED UP ISN'T GONNA HELP US.
- HAD TO BE HITOTORIBASHI.
- PARDON THE INTRUSION,
MY DEAR KATAKURA.
YOUR LORD IS REALLY
QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
NANBU, TSUGARU, SOHMA
AND ASHINA BOXED HIM IN.
FOUR ENTIRE ARMIES AND IT WOULD
APPEAR HE NEVER SUCCUMBED.
I TRULY DID NOT THINK
THE DATE COULD ACCOMPLISH
SO MUCH WITHOUT YOU.
- OF COURSE THEY COULD.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE
LORD MASAMUNE.
- YES, WELL, THOUGH MY HOPE
HAD BEEN FOR HIDEYOSHI
TO CONSERVE HIS ENERGIES,
I WOUND UP NEEDING HIM
TO PAY A PERSONAL VISIT TO OSHU.
YOU CAN REST EASY.
AS TO THE DEAR MASAMUNE'S FATE,
I WON'T TORTURE YOU
BY WITHHOLDING
THE ULTIMATE OUTCOME.
A SOUVENIR,
COLLECTED BY A SOLDIER
IN LORD HIDEYOSHI'S CONTINGENT.
ONE OF DEAR MASAMUNE'S
VAUNTED DRAGON CLAWS, YES?
I WON'T ASK THAT YOU JOIN
OUR CAUSE IMMEDIATELY.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU TIME
TO ACCEPT
THAT THE MAN YOU ONCE SERVED
IS NO MORE.
ALTHOUGH I CANNOT WAIT
FOR TOO LONG,
I'M NOT A HEARTLESS MAN.
I CAN SYMPATHIZE WITH WHAT
YOU MUST BE GOING THROUGH.
- Toyotomi: HANBEI, RESORTING
TO SUCH MEASURES IS UNNECESSARY.
- HE WILL BE OF USE TO YOU,
WITHOUT FAIL.
I FEEL I MUST APOLOGIZE.
- FOR WHAT?
- FOR WASTING YOUR TIME
WITH A TRIP TO OSHU.
- YOU SEEMED FAIRLY CONCERNED
ABOUT THE DATE.
I WANTED TO SEE FOR MYSELF.
- I NEVER IMAGINED THEY WOULD
BREAK THROUGH
SUCH AN ENCIRCLEMENT.
WITH MY MISHANDLING
OF KAWANAKAJIMA,
TWICE NOW,
I HAVE UTTERLY FAILED YOU.
- PAY IT NO MIND.
FOR IN THE END,
EVEN I RETURNED WITHOUT SENDING
THE ALREADY INJURED
ONE-EYED DRAGON
TO MEET HIS MAKER.
- TRUE, THAT WAS UNEXPECTED.
THOUGH I AM CERTAIN YOU
HAD GOOD REASON
FOR NOT FINISHING HIM OFF.
AT THE VERY LEAST,
NOW WE ARE FREE TO BEGIN
OUR INVASION OF SHIKOKU.
NOW OUR IMPECCABLY TRAINED
ARMY AWAITS YOUR ORDERS
TO LEAD THEM IN GLORIOUS BATTLE.
- MY BRAVEST AND MIGHTIEST
SOLDIERS, HEAR ME.
COME WITH ME AND REIGN SUPREME
OVER ALL.
IN ORDER TO KEEP THIS LAND
FROM FALLING TO RUIN,
IN ORDER TO BUILD A NEW ERA,
THE TIME HAS COME TO GO TO WAR.
- ( cheering )
- JUST LIKE THEIR STANDOFFS
AGAINST THE TAKEDA.
THEY SURE TAKE
THEIR SWEET-ASS TIME.
THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO.
- LORD UESUGI.
- BIG BOSS,
THERE GONNA BE A FIGHT?
- NAH, YOU BOYS CAN ENJOY
YOUR PICNIC FOR A WHILE LONGER.
TOYOTOMI AIN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
- LORD KENSHIN.
- KASUGA, WHAT NEWS HAVE YOU
TO REPORT?
- IT SEEMS THE ALLIANCE
HAS NOW BEEN FORMED.
TOYOTOMI APPEARS
TO BE MAKING PREPARATIONS
TO SEND HIS MAIN ARMY WEST.
AS YOU GUESSED, IT IS BELIEVED
HE WILL ATTACK SHIKOKU
WITH MORI.
- I SEE, THANK YOU.
- ALSO REGARDING MAEDA KEIJI.
IT SEEMS HE IS MAKING
HIS WAY TO OSAKA.
WHO KNOWS WHAT
HE INTENDS TO DO.
- THEN YOU ARE CONCERNED
FOR HIM.
- NO, MY LORD.
I MERELY ASSUMED
THAT YOU MIGHT BE CURIOUS
ABOUT HIS SAFETY.
- MY MOST BEAUTIFUL BLADE.
HOW I ADMIRE
YOUR GENTLE NATURE.
TRULY IT WARMS ME TO MY HEART.
- ( shouts )
- THEY'RE GOING TO WAR.
THERE HE IS.
HIDEYOSHI, HOLD UP.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
DISSOLVE YOUR ALLIANCE
WITH THE MAEDA.
STOP TRYING TO FORCE EVERYONE
TO YOUR SIDE.
HIDEYOSHI!  HIDEYOSHI!
PLEASE LISTEN
TO WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
DAMN IT, STOP!
- HELLO, DEAR KEIJI,
YOU SEEM WELL.
- HANBEI.
- AH, YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
STILL HAVE THAT SAME LOOK
IN YOUR EYES.
- YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED, EITHER.
- I'VE HEARD THE NEWS
FROM TEDORIGAWA.
IF YOU HADN'T FLED
AFTER YOUR SHOW OF DEFIANCE,
THE MAEDA ARMY ITSELF WOULD HAVE
BEEN HELD RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE SHOW OF HOSTILITY
AGAINST TOYOTOMI. REMEMBER THAT.
- THE MAEDA WILL NOT HELP
THE TOYOTOMI
OPPRESS INNOCENT PEOPLE.  NOW
JUST LET ME TALK TO HIDEYOSHI.
- HIDEYOSHI'S GAZE
IS UPON THE WORLD.
A MAN WHO THRIVES ON DEBAUCHERY,
WHO ONLY GOES ONLY
WHERE THE WIND MAY
CARRY HIM.
SHOUT INTO HIS EAR.
HE WILL NOT HEAR
SUCH A MAN'S WORDS.
HE IS IN A DIFFERENT WORLD
FROM YOU NOW.
- WHO ARE YOU INVADING?
SHIKOKU?
- Sanada: HERE, AS ELSEWHERE,
THERE ARE NO MEN LEFT.
THEIR FATHERS,
THEIR HUSBANDS AND SONS,
THEY'VE ALL BEEN SENT OFF
TO WAR.
- YUKIMURA, IS SOMETHING AMISS?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- ONCE AGAIN, I OWE YOU
AN APOLOGY, MASTER OYAMADA.
I SIMPLY COULD
NOT IGNORE THIS.
- IT'S FINE, BUT WE
SHOULD HURRY ON OUR WAY.
- WE WIELD OUR MILITARY MIGHT,
PRIDE OURSELVES ON OUR STRENGTH
FOR THE FUTURE OF THIS LAND.
WE FIGHT EACH OTHER OVER IT.
I NEVER QUESTIONED ANY OF IT
IN THE SLIGHTEST,
BUT IN ALL THIS TIME,
HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE
WE ACTUALLY HELPED?
- PLEASE, YOUR LORDSHIP,
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME, AT
THE END OF ALL THIS WAR-MAKING,
WILL THIS LAND
OF THE RISING SUN
EVER FINALLY KNOW PEACE?
- WHAT ON EARTH'S GOING
ON DOWN THERE?
- THAT'S TOYOTOMI'S BANNER.
- PERHAPS THEIR ALLIANCE
WITH MORI HAS COME TO FRUITION.
THEY'RE INVADING
SHIKOKU TOGETHER.
- AND REMEMBER,
IN THIS MATTER,
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE,
BOY.
- HOW COULD I HAVE
LET THIS HAPPEN?
WITHOUT REALIZING IT,
I'VE BEEN NEGLECTING MY MISSION.
YOUR LORDSHIP,
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
- Katakura: THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOU TO FINALLY
REVEAL YOURSELF AS A CONTENDER.
FIRST, LET US STRIKE AT
THE DEADLOCK AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
TAKEDA AND UESUGI HAVE STOOD OFF
AGAINST EACH OTHER THERE
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
- KOJURO.
- SIR.
- AFTER HITOTORIBASHI,
WHY WERE YOU GONNA COMMIT
HARA-KIRI?
- IT WAS BECAUSE
I WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE TERRIBLE INJURY YOU
SUSTAINED DURING THAT BATTLE.
- I WANNA KNOW THE REAL STORY.
I SAW A CHANCE TO UNIFY OSHU
IN ONE QUICK STRIKE
AND TOOK THE OFFENSIVE,
BUT YOU WERE AGAINST US
GOING TO WAR THAT TIME.
- REGARDLESS,
WE WERE VICTORIOUS,
AND ALL OF OSHU IS NOW
UNDER DATE CONTROL.
- BUT YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE SUFFERED UNBELIEVABLE
CASUALTIES.
YOU WERE GONNA TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE WHOLE DAMN THING
AND LEAVE ME--
- I HAD INTENDED
TO TRY AND MAKE YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT WOULD MEAN
TO SUFFER A TRUE LOSS.
YOU MAY WIN THE WAR,
BUT IF YOU HAVE NO ONE LEFT
TO SHARE WHAT COMES AFTER.
YOU WERE STILL YOUNG,
AND I HAD INTENDED TO FORCE
THIS REALIZATION UPON YOU
BY REMOVING YOUR RIGHT EYE
ONCE AGAIN.
- SHUT THE HELL UP!
YOU DON'T GET TO BE COCKY.
I'M NO MATCH FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
- I MUST HUMBLY DISAGREE.
- NEVER AGAIN WILL I LET
THE DATE ARMY LOSE ANOTHER SOUL.
- LORD MASAMUNE.
MY RESOLVE IS FIRM.
- Man:
HEY, UESUGI'S PULLING OUT!
- THEY'RE LEAVING?
- ( murmuring )
- Kasuga:
MY LORD KENSHIN,
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE THIS
OF ALL PLACES TO STALL DATE?
- IN THE DAYS BEFORE DATE
HAD CONQUERED ALL OF OSHU,
I AM TOLD THIS IS WHERE HE
FOUGHT HIS MOST DESPERATE BATTLE
AND WHERE HE SUFFERED
HIS GREATEST LOSSES.
TO CALM THE DRAGON'S
IMPETUOUS SOUL,
TO HELP HEAL HIS WOUNDS
AND REBUILD HIS STRENGTH,
NO OTHER PLACE COULD HAVE
SERVED AS WELL.
- BIG BOSS?
- I'M GONNA GO SAY
A QUICK THANK YOU.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, MILORD,
WHY GO TO SUCH LENGTHS?
- SIMPLE REALLY.
DATE MASAMUNE,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON,
IS THE MOST WORTHY RIVAL
OF THE YOUNG CUB,
WHOM THE TIGER OF KAI HAS
MENTORED WITH GREAT CARE.
AND BECAUSE I BELIEVE
HE IS A MAN CAPABLE
OF QUELLING THE WARS
THAT WILL FOREVER
PLAGUE MANKIND.
- LORD KENSHIN!
- ( gasping )
- I HAD A NICE CHANCE
TO COOL DOWN THERE.
- AN INDOMITABLE SPIRIT.
THE REST WILL BE UP TO YOU
AND HEAVEN'S WILL.
- I'D SAY THAT WAS A CLEVER
STUNT YOU PULLED,
BUT DON'T COUNT ME
IN YOUR DEBT.
YOU'RE GONNA REGRET THIS.
- SHOULD YOU FAIL TO RETURN,
I SHALL CLAIM OSHU
AND UNIFY IT IN YOUR MEMORY.
IT WOULD NOT BE SO TERRIBLE
A PLACE TO SEEK
TO CONQUER
THE COUNTRY FROM.
YOU NEED NOT FEAR
FOR YOUR PEOPLE.
YOU'RE A CRAFTY SON OF A BITCH.
YOU REMIND ME A LOT
OF THE TIGER OF KAI.
- I CAN THINK OF
NO GREATER COMPLIMENT.
- OKAY, BOYS,
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
- ( cheering )
- LOCK AND LOAD.
- YEAH!
- GET READY.
IT'S GONNA BE
ONE HELL OF A PARTY!
- Narrator:
AT AROUND THE SAME TIME,
ON THE INLAND SEA OF SETO,
CHOSOKABE OF SHIKOKU AND MORI
OF AKI HAD BEGUN THEIR BATTLE
FOR SUPREMACY
IN SPECTACULAR FASHION.
- DOESN'T MATTER IF THAT BASTARD
JOINS FORCES WITH TOYOTOMI.
I'LL PUT AN END
TO THIS RIGHT QUICK.
WELL, AVAST.
THEY'RE ALL A-PANIC
'CAUSE WE FIRED THE FIRST SHOTS.
THE FUGAKU'S FINALLY COMPLETE
WITH HER 11-FOOT CANNON.
WE'LL TAKE A MINUTE HERE
TO CRUSH MORI
AND THEN WE'LL TAKE THE REST
OF THE COUNTRY.
GOT IT, YOU SONS OF BITCHES?
- AYE, CAPTAIN!
- CHOSOKABE'S FORTRESS,
THE FUGAKU.
THAT IS ONE FINE PIECE OF WORK.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chosokabe:
ALL RIGHT, YOU SONS OF BITCHES.
NEXT TIME, THE OGRE OF THE
WESTERN SEA WILL BE KNOCKING OUT
BOTH TOYOTOMI AND MORI.
YOU FOLKS SITTING COZY
BETTER GET READY FOR IT, TOO.
DON'T MISS THE BOAT AS WE SET
SAIL TO CONQUER THE COUNTRY!