- ( bird squawking )
- DO I BIDE MY TIME?
OR GO ON THE OFFENSIVE?
IT'S HIGH TIME
I FOUND MY RESOLVE ANYWAY.
- Bekunosuke: CAPTAIN!
- Shige: THERE'S TROUBLE!
- SHIGE, BEKUNOSUKE. WHAT'S UP?
- A REPORT FROM ZENNOJI.
- A BOAT CARRYING
TWO STRANGERS WAS SPOTTED.
AND THEY'VE JUST COME ASHORE.
- A PLEASURE TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
I AM THE PROTECTOR OF KAGA,
MAEDA MATAZAEMON TOSHIIE.
I OFFER YOU MY GRATITUDE IN
GRANTING US THIS AUDIENCE TODAY.
- AND I AM LORD TOSHIIE'S WIFE,
I AM KNOWN AS MATSU.
- I'M CHOSOKABE MOTOCHIKA.
CAN'T SAY I'M HAPPY
TO SEE YOU HERE.
SORRY, THAT'S RUDE OF ME.
YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE HERE TO MAKE WAR.
SO, WHAT CAN THE OGRE OF
THE WESTERN SEA DO FOR YOU?
WHAT BRINGS YOU TWO
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
- A MESSAGE,
WE ASK THAT YOU CEDE
SANUKI AND IYO.
- ( men gasp )
- OUR LORD ODA NOBUNAGA,
WHOM WE SERVE,
STATES THAT IF YOU WILL FORGO
ALL LANDS SAVE FOR TOSA AND AWA,
HE WILL GUARANTEE THE SECURITY
OF YOUR REMAINING HOLDINGS.
- ( men grunting )
- PIPE DOWN, YOU DOGS!
- ( scoffs ) HE EXPECTS
ME TO JUST HAND OVER
MY INLAND COASTLINE?
HE TALKS LIKE HE'S
ALREADY BECOME
SUPREME RULER OF THIS WORLD.
HEY, I GOT A MESSAGE
YOU CAN TAKE BACK TO HIM.
"WATCH YOUR BACK, DEVIL KING,
OR YOU MAY FIND A BLADE IN IT".
- LORD CHOSOKABE,
OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA,
THIS IS TO PREVENT
THE WHOLE OF SHIKOKU
FROM BEING RAZED TO THE GROUND.
I BEG OF YOU, PLEASE ACQUIESCE.
- WHAT IF I SAY NO?
- MATSU!
WE WERE PREPARED
FOR THAT ANSWER.
LORD CHOSOKABE, I ASK THAT
YOU HONOR ME WITH A DUEL,
UPON WHICH...
- ( scoffs )
I'VE HEARD MANY TALES OF YOU,
MATAZA OF THE SPEAR.
AND I'VE LONG WISHED
FOR A CHANCE TO FACE YOU.
BUT LET'S HOLD UP A SEC.
LIFE CAN BE A REAL BITCH WHEN
YOU CHOOSE THE WRONG MASTER.
IT'S TRUE IN ANY ERA,
AND WHETHER YOU'RE
ON LAND OR AT SEA.
EVERY ORDER IS TO BURN
THIS OR MASSACRE THAT.
ACTS OF INJUSTICE
THAT BETRAY YOUR MORAL COMPASS.
UNTIL YOU CAN NO LONGER BEAR IT.
YOU PETITION THE DEVIL KING,
AND HE RESPONDS
WITH AN ULTIMATUM.
WIN ME OVER,
THE MAN WHO CONQUERED SHIKOKU,
OR HE WILL DESTROY KAGA
IF YOU FAIL.
THAT PRETTY CLOSE?
MY SCOUTS TOLD ME OF
HOW HE TREATED POOR AZAI OF OMI.
- Toshiie: OUR PLIGHT WAS
THAT TRANSPARENT?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE YOU'RE WELL LOVED
BY YOUR GOOD PEOPLE.
YOUR WIFE'S GOT
A LOT OF NERVE, THOUGH.
JUST LIKE THAT BASTARD
SAID SHE WOULD.
- WHAT BASTARD?
- ( sneezing )
( coughs )
- ( gasps )
- Man 1: LORD MORI.
- Man 2: WE WOULD NEVER EXPECT
YOU MIGHT COME IN PERSON
TO SUCH A PLACE.
- Mori: STAND DOWN
FOR THE MOMENT.
- Men: MY LORD.
- ( monkey screeching )
- OH, GOOD WORK, BOY.
- THE NEXT TIME YOU ALLOW THAT
FILTHY THING NEAR MY PERSON,
I WILL CUT IT DOWN
WITHOUT HESITATION.
- YOU'RE STARTING TO THINK
MY PLAN'S NOT SUCH A CRAZY IDEA,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU CAME
DOWN HERE WITH YUMEKICHI.
IS THAT WHAT YOU CAME TO SAY,
MORI, MY MAN?
- BEFORE YOU QUESTION ME,
TELL ME WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
- WE'VE ALREADY BEEN
THROUGH ALL THIS. MY NAME IS...
- IF YOU ARE THE VAGABOND
OF THE MAEDA,
YOU WOULD NEVER ASK
THE CHOSOKABE AND THE MORI
TO COLLUDE IN AN
ALLIANCE AGAINST ODA.
AS A MEMBER OF
THE MAEDA FAMILY OF KAGA,
WHICH SERVES ODA,
IT SIMPLY MAKES NO SENSE.
- THAT'S WHERE, YOU KNOW,
I'M DOING WHAT
I THINK IS FOR THE BEST.
- RIGHT, LITTLE BUDDY?
- ( monkey screeching )
- SO YOU ONLY HAVE THE MONKEY
TO VOUCH FOR YOU.
IF YOU WISH TO KEEP YOUR HEAD...
- NEVER MIND THAT,
THOSE SPIES YOU SENT TO SHIKOKU,
THEY HAVEN'T RETURNED YET,
HAVE THEY?
CHOSOKABE HAS THEM.
I CAUGHT THEM MYSELF
AND GAVE THEM TO HIM AS A GIFT.
YEAH, OKAY, I'M NOT SURE
I'D BELIEVE ME EITHER.
- ( Chosokabe grunts )
- ( Keiji grunts )
NOW DON'T GET ME WRONG,
LIKE YOU, HE WAS NO PUSHOVER,
BUT ONCE I MANAGED
TO DUEL HIM TO A DRAW,
HE FINALLY GAVE ME THE CHANCE
TO SIT DOWN AND TALK.
- ( Chosokabe scoffs )
- THE OGRE OF THE
WESTERN SEA IS ON BOARD.
THE NEXT MOVE IS UP TO YOU.
WHETHER I AM WHO I SAY
ISN'T THE ISSUE.
THE POINT IS
TO GET YOU TWO TO AGREE
TO JUST ONE MEETING
WITHOUT TRADING BLOWS.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
FORTUNATELY, AFTER
BEING HELD HERE,
I'VE DISCOVERED CHOSOKABE'S
SPIES ARE, WELL, SAFE.
WHICH IS GREAT.
YOU CAN EXCHANGE YOUR HOSTAGES
ON THE INLAND SEA OF SETO.
AND WHILE YOU'RE BOTH THERE,
YOU CAN DISCUSS JOINING
FORCES AGAINST ODA.
- Mori: AND YOU THINK
I WOULD AGREE TO THAT?
- ( sighs )
I'M KINDA GONNA MAKE YOU.
- REALLY?
- IT MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
WHAT YOU SET OUT TO DO,
BUT HAVING
TURNED THE TABLES
ON EVERY FOE WHO'S
TRIED TO INVADE AKI,
YOU NOW FIND
YOURSELF THE RULER
OF THE ENTIRE
SURROUNDING REGION.
UNTIL RECENTLY,
YOU PRETTY MUCH JUST HAD TO
KEEP YOUR EYE ON CHOSOKABE,
WHO CONQUERED ALL OF SHIKOKU.
BUT NOW THAT YOU'RE
AT THE POINT WHERE
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE INVASION
BY THE DEVIL KING,
YOU'RE PLOTTING
TO GET YOUR HANDS
ON THE NEW WEAPON
CHOSOKABE'S SUPPOSEDLY MAKING.
MOTOCHIKA HAS EMBRACED
THE CRAFTSMANSHIP
OF MECHANICAL WEAPONRY.
AND THE FLOATING FORTRESS FUGAKU
IS REALLY THE PINNACLE OF THAT.
IN THE FIGHT FOR SUPREMACY
OVER THE INLAND SEA OF SETO,
IT'S AN ABOMINATION THAT
THREATENS THE BALANCE OF POWER.
SO, OBVIOUSLY, I CAN
ONLY ASSUME YOU WERE
PLANNING ON DESTROYING
IT OR STEALING IT.
TOO BAD FOR YOU,
IT'S ALREADY BEEN COMPLETED,
AND IS SET TO SAIL
FOR AKI AT ANY TIME.
- I BEG YOUR PARDON?
- I'M DYING IF I'M LYING, RIGHT?
I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
THE MAIN CANNON
ON THIS THING IS JUST HUGE!
FOR REAL! IT'S A MONSTROSITY,
LIKE SOME GIGANTIC
ARMORED SEA TURTLE.
- YOU ARE CERTAIN
CHOSOKABE AND HIS PIRATES
WILL BE APPEARING
ABOARD THIS FUGAKU?
- YEAH. MOTOCHIKA IS A PIRATE
WHO KEEPS TO HIS WORD,
AND HE'S GUARANTEEING
THE SAFETY OF YOUR MEN.
BUT IF YOU DON'T MEET HIM
OUT THERE ON THE OPEN SEA,
HE'LL THINK I'M TRYING
TO DOUBLE CROSS HIM
AND I'LL END UP FODDER
FOR HIS GIGANTIC CANNON.
- OF ALL THINGS, YOU ARE USING
STRATEGY TO FORCE MY COMPLIANCE.
- ( scoffs )
- VERY WELL,
I SHALL AGREE, AT LEAST,
TO EXCHANGE OUR PRECIOUS MEN.
- ( scoffs )
- ENCIRCLE ODA?
- Matsu: OUR KEIJI?
ARE YOU SURE?
- OH, YES. BY THIS POINT,
HE SHOULD HAVE MADE HIS WAY
TO THE HEART OF MORI'S CAMP.
THE MEN I SENT TO OBSERVE ENEMY
MOVEMENTS HAVEN'T RETURNED,
AND I HAVE MORI'S SPIES THAT
KEIJI BROUGHT ME AS A GIFT.
PLAN IS TO EXCHANGE
HOSTAGES AT SEA,
THEN CALL A BRIEF TRUCE
AND JOIN FORCES
TO KNOCK OUT THE DEVIL KING.
- HE'S OUT OF HIS MIND!
- I HAVE HEARD LORD MORI
MOTONARI IS NOT A GENERAL
WHO INVADES OTHER LANDS
ON HIS OWN INITIATIVE.
- TO WALK INTO HIS
CAMP AND URGE HIM
TO TAKE UP ARMS
AGAINST ODA IS...
- NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
KEIJI'S GOT HIS WORK CUT OUT
IF HE WANTS TO WIN HIM OVER.
BUT IF THE REST OF KYUSHU
FALLS THE SAME WAY
THAT OLD GOAT SHIMAZU WENT DOWN,
EVEN MORI WILL HAVE TO
GIVE IT SOME THOUGHT,
BUT DON'T GET ME WRONG,
I'D RATHER NOT JOIN
FORCES EITHER,
BUT, GIVEN THE SITUATION,
I WILL DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
SO, THIS IS WHERE I NEED YOU
TO FIND YOUR RESOLVE, AS WELL.
KEIJI HATCHED THIS
OUTRAGEOUS PLAN,
AND THE ONLY REASON HE'S
EVEN TRYING TO PULL IT OFF
IS FOR YOUR SAKE, FOR THE
HONOR OF THE MAEDA.
- Matsu: AND HERE I THOUGHT
HE SPENT ALL THIS TIME
PLAYING AROUND.
- Toshiie: WE DO SERVE
LORD NOBUNAGA.
IT'S NO SURPRISE
HE COULDN'T TELL US.
- Matsu: WHY DO
I GET THE FEELING
YOU KNEW WHAT HE WAS PLANNING?
- THAT'S JUST
THE KIND OF MAN KEIJI IS.
BESIDES, EVEN IF CHOSOKABE
HAD AGREED TO CEDE HIS LANDS,
ODA WOULD HAVE SIMPLY USED
IYO AND SANUKI AS A FOOTHOLD
TO CONQUER THE REST OF THE LANDS
ON THE INLAND SEA.
- PERHAPS.
NO, I'M FOOLING MYSELF.
I'M SURE YOU'RE RIGHT.
I, MATSU, HAVE FOUND MY RESOLVE.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- I WROTE THIS
BEFORE WE LEFT KAGA,
FOR LORD NOBUNAGA,
TO RELATE OUR INTENT
TO SECEDE FROM ODA.
- MATSU.
- MY LORD INUCHIYO, HEAR ME OUT.
WHILE HE HAS SHOWN
US GREAT FAVOR,
LORD NOBUNAGA'S ACTIONS
NO LONGER CONTAIN
ONE SHRED OF HONOR.
- BUT I HAVE GIVEN MY WORD.
- THIS HAS TROUBLED
YOU FOR SOME TIME.
YOU WISH TO HONOR THE SANCTITY
OF ALL LIFE, EVEN OUR FOES.
FOR ALL MEN HAVE GIFTS
AND TALENTS THAT
SHOULD NOT BE SQUANDERED.
SO YOU SEARCH FOR ANOTHER WAY,
WHERE WE CAN SUPPORT THOSE
WHO MIGHT UNITE US AND LEAD US.
YOU SPOKE OF THIS
WITH EVERY BATTLE.
NOW KEIJI'S PRANK WITH THE COLD
BATHWATER MAKES SENSE.
HE COULDN'T STAND
SEEING YOU LIKE THAT,
SO HE TRIED TO LIVEN THINGS UP
IN THE HOUSE A LITTLE.
WHICH MEANS, THE REASON YOU TOLD
ME TO LET KEIJI GO AT THE TIME,
MUST HAVE BEEN
BECAUSE IN YOUR HEART,
EVEN THOUGH YOU
COULDN'T TELL HIM,
YOU AGREED WITH WHAT
HE WAS ABOUT TO DO.
- INDEED.
- ( bird squawking )
- ALL RIGHT, YOU DOGS,
IT'S THE FUGAKU'S MAIDEN VOYAGE.
LET'S GIVE HER ALL WE'VE GOT!
- Men: AYE!
- ( rumbling )
- ( cawing )
- ( monkey chattering
nervously )
- WHAT'S WRONG, BUDDY?
JUST HANG IN THERE
A LITTLE LONGER, YUMEKICHI,
AND WE'LL GET YOU GUYS
BACK TO MOTOCHIKA SOON, TOO.
- WE APPRECIATE IT,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
- Keiji: WELL, IT WAS MY BAD.
SORRY I BLABBED
ABOUT THE FUGAKU.
- Man 1: NAH, AS LONG AS
EVERYTHING WORKS OUT.
- Man 2: BUT THE
FUGAKU'S MAIN CANNON,
- IT'S STILL NOT...
- SHH!
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE COMPLETED,
AS LONG AS MORI DOESN'T
CALL YOUR CAPTAIN'S BLUFF.
HEY! MORI, MY MAN.
DON'T YOU HAVE ANY AMBITIONS
OF CONQUERING THE WORLD?
- I'VE NO USE FOR THE WORLD.
THE SUN HOLDS MY AMBITIONS.
- OH? IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, IN THAT CASE, WE NEED
YOU AS PART OF OUR ALLIANCE,
SINCE THE DEVIL KING HOPES
TO BLANKET THE SUN
WITH HIS OMINOUS CLOUD.
- I SAID, I WOULD THINK ON IT.
- ( sighs )
( chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THESE FOLKS
SURE ACT LIKE
THEY'RE AT A NEVER
ENDING FUNERAL.
- Chosokabe: YOU DOGS GET
YOUR FILL? YOU READY TO FIGHT?
- Men: AYE!
- FATE WILL SOME DAY GRANT US
GLORIOUS BATTLE WITH MORI,
BUT TODAY, WE RETURN
THEIR SPIES UNHARMED,
WITH HONOR AND RESPECT.
THOUGH TREASURES
IN THIS WORLD ABOUND,
NONE ARE AS PRECIOUS AS THIS SEA
WE SAIL AND THE LANDS WE SOW.
IF THE DEVIL KING
WANTS TO BURN IT ALL,
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO SAVE IT
BEFORE WE FIGHT OVER IT.
- All: AYE!
- BUT IT IS STILL
MORI MOTONARI WE FACE!
- DO NOT LET YOUR GUARDS DOWN!
- All: AYE!
- PUSH COMES TO SHOVE,
WE TAKE THE FUGAKU STRAIGHT
TO AKI AND UNLOAD.
AND AS THE SOLE COMMANDER
OF THE INLAND SEA OF SETO,
THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN
SEA WILL DEFEAT ODA!
- All: AYE!
- Mori's spy: SO, THIS IS IT!
LADY MATSU OF MAEDA'S
VAUNTED HOME COOKING.
- DID KEIJI SAY SOMETHING?
- YES, HE SAID, "MATSU'S COOKING
IS THE BEST IN THE WORLD."
- AW, BLESS THAT BOY.
- Mori's spy: MASTER KEIJI SAID
HE WANTS EVERYONE TO EAT
GOOD FOOD WITH GOOD PEOPLE,
TO LAUGH AND CRY AND LIVE,
THAT'S THE WORLD HE
WANTS TO HELP BRING ABOUT.
- MOTOCHIKA AND HIS MEN,
THEY'RE GOOD NATURED GUYS, YEAH?
DON'T YOU THINK IT MIGHT BE FUN
TO BE THEIR FRIENDS?
IF PEOPLE WOULD JUST
STOP FOR A MINUTE
AND GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER,
THEY WOULDN'T ALWAYS
BE HURTING EACH OTHER.
- Mori's spy: MASTER KEIJI SAID
HE PREPARED EVERYTHING
THE WAY YOU ALWAYS DO IT,
BUT, UH, HE MUST NOT HAVE BEEN
PAYING VERY CLOSE ATTENTION.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE HIM.
- ( all laughing )
- ( gasps )
- Man: WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- NOW THEN, YOUR MOVE.
- TOSHI. MATSU.
- KEIJI.
- AHOY, MAEDA KEIJI.
YOU PLAYED THIS OFF PERFECTLY.
HOW GOES, MORI MOTONARI?
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
LOOK HERE, I GOT YOUR SPIES,
SAFE AND SOUND.
- Mori's spy: LORD MORI!
- AND I HAVE SPARED
YOUR MEN'S LIVES.
- ( moaning ) CAPTAIN.
- THAT SON OF A BITCH!
- NOW, CHOSOKABE,
LET US BEGIN THE NEGOTIATIONS.
- Man: CAPTAIN.
THEY'VE GOT US SURROUNDED.
- MORI! YOU...
- ALL GOES ACCORDING
TO MY CALCULATIONS,
FORGIVE THE PUN, MAEDA KEIJI,
BUT YOUR MONKEY BUSINESS
WAS ALL PART OF MY PLAN.
- WHAT?
- I WAS AWARE IN ADVANCE
THAT YOU WOULD BE COMING
TO THE INLAND SEA OF SETO,
AND I MADE USE OF THAT.
- SO WE'VE BEEN DANCING
TO YOUR TUNE THIS ENTIRE TIME.
- THERE ARE NONE IN THIS WORLD
WHO CAN THWART MY CUNNING.
CHOSOKABE, LEAVE YOUR
FORTRESS FUGAKU TO ME,
AND FLEE HERE
WITH ALL SWIFTNESS.
I AM A CHILD OF THE SUN.
IT IS UNTHINKABLE FOR ME TO
CALL A LOWLY PIRATE MY EQUAL.
- Keiji: LISTEN TO ME. YOU TWO
ARE FINALLY FACE TO FACE.
PLEASE, JUST TALK TO HIM.
- LORD MORI, HE IS RIGHT.
WE BEG OF YOU.
PLEASE JOIN IN TAKING DOWN ODA.
- AFTER WHICH,
WE MIGHT FIND A WAY
TO LIVE IN PEACE WITH CHOSOKABE.
- YOU ARE NO LONGER REQUIRED.
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- ( all gasping )
- ( yells )
- FOOLISHNESS.
MERE SPIES WOULD PRESUME
TO QUESTION MY JUDGMENT?
- HEY, MORI!
- Matsu: MASTER HASHINOSUKE!
OH, GOD. NO.
- Toshiie: WHY SUCH CRUELTY?
- SCALAWAG! ARE YOU INSANE?
THESE ARE MEN WHO HAVE RISKED
LIFE AND LIMB IN SERVICE OF YOU.
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- HARUKICHI!
- SUKEROKU!
- Keiji: NO. HARUKICHI. SAHEITA.
THOSE MEN,
THEY HAD FAMILIES BACK HOME.
- THE FIELD OF BATTLE
IS A CHESSBOARD.
AND MY PAWNS ALREADY
HAVE YOU AT CHECKMATE.
AT THIS RANGE, YOU ARE TOO
CLOSE FOR YOUR CANNONS
TO TAKE AIM AT ME.
- DON'T DO THIS!
- DAMN IT, MORI, YOUR OWN MEN?
- PAWNS ARE MADE
TO BE SACRIFICED.
- LORD CHOSOKABE!
- HOLD!
- MOVE IT!
- MORI!
- KEIJI, DON'T!
- ( grunts )
- KEIJI!
KEIJI.
- ( grunts )
ALL RIGHT, YOU DOGS,
THIS IS FOR VENGEANCE.
NOW LET'S GO SHOW THEM WHAT THE
WARRIORS OF TOSA ARE MADE OF!
- All: AYE!
- ( all yelling )
- SEIZE THEIR FORTRESS FUGAKU.
- LET GO OF ME!
- MATSU!
- KEIJI'S... OH, GOD, HE'S...
- KNOWING HIM, HE'LL BE FINE.
- ( grunts )
- YOU CANNOT OUTWIT ME.
ACCEPT YOUR DEFEAT.
SO, THE MAN WITH NO BRAIN
RELIES ON HIS BRAWN.
THERE IS NO SHAME IN THAT.
THINK OF YOUR DEATH
AT MY HAND AS AN HONOR.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
I DARE YOU. TRY IT!
- NONE SHALL BE ALLOWED
TO BLOT OUT THE SUN.
- ( grunting )
- ( yells )
- IT'S TIME TO PAY
FOR YOUR SINS, MORI.
YOUR SHRINE ON ITSUKUSHIMA
ISLAND WILL READ "EVIL GOD".
- THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
IS MINE.
I SHALL BE THE ONE
TO PROTECT IT.
- ( grunts )
- ( yelling )
- MAEDA. KEIJI!
- SO YOU SURVIVED,
DAMN MONKEY TRAINER.
- MOTOCHIKA, PLEASE CALM DOWN.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL. BUT IF
YOU LET THAT RAGE RULE YOU,
WE'RE RIGHT WHERE WE STARTED.
MORI, MY MAN, I MISJUDGED YOU.
YOU'RE A CRUEL BASTARD.
- OUT OF MY WAY, VAGABOND.
THIS FIGHT STARTED
LONG BEFORE YOU GOT HERE.
- ANY MAN WHO DARES
MOCK ME SHALL BE SLAIN
BY THE POWER OF THE SUN.
- YOU PIGHEADED MORONS!
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
RIGHT NOW IS TO MAKE WAR,
TO KEEP MORE WARS FROM
HAPPENING, ALL RIGHT?
IF YOU NEIGHBORS
CAN'T JOIN FORCES,
JUST FOR THE MOMENT,
THERE WILL BE NO
FUTURE TO FIGHT OVER.
- ( screaming )
( gasps )
- Keiji: KASUGA!
DON'T TELL ME. IT'S TIME.
- THEY'VE BEGUN
THE FINAL ASSAULT?
( grunts )
MORI, WE WILL FINISH THIS LATER.
- Keiji: THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE,
VERY NINJA LIKE TODAY.
- IS THAT DIFFERENT
FROM MY NORMAL FACE?
- I HEARD ABOUT POOR KENSHIN.
I'M SURE HE'LL...
- OF COURSE HE WILL.
THAT IS THE MAN HE IS.
- YEAH, THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
THE POWER OF BELIEVING IS
AN INCREDIBLE THING, ISN'T IT?
LONG AS HE HAS YOU,
KENSHIN WILL...
- OH, SHUT UP.
SAVE YOUR SPEECHES
FOR SOMEONE WHO ACTUALLY CARES.
- THE SEA OF SETSU, HUH?
THAT OUGHT TO BE
AN EASY ROW FOR MY GUYS!
- Mori: WE WILL HEAD
FOR AZUCHI BY LAND.
WHETHER OR NOT WE BECOME
INVOLVED WITH THE HOSTILITIES
WILL DEPEND.
AND JUST MAYBE A SURPRISE ATTACK
ON CHOSOKABE MIGHT BE IN ORDER.
- ( theme song playing )
- Man: CAPTAIN, FUGAKU'S MAIN
CANNON STILL ISN'T COMPLETE.
- Chosokabe: DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT.
THE EASTERN GENERALS HAVE
GOTTA BE RUNNING OUT OF OPTIONS,
'CAUSE NOTHING THEY'VE GOT
CAN GET THROUGH AZUCHI
CASTLE'S WALLS.
JUST KEEP FIRING
AS MUCH AS SHE CAN TAKE.
IF THEY'RE TOO STUPID
TO DODGE A FEW CANNONBALLS,
THEY NEVER HAD A CHANCE AGAINST
THE DEVIL KING TO BEGIN WITH.
- THAT KINDA MAKES SENSE.
- Man: CAPTAIN,
SHE'S AT HER LIMIT.
- Chosokabe: ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
SHE HUNG IN LONG ENOUGH.
I'M SURE AT LEAST
ONE FOUND ITS MARK.
- Narrator: NOW, WITH THE
ADDITIONOF THE TWO GENERALS
OF THE INLAND SEA OF SETO,
THE LONG SOUGHT ENCIRCLEMENT
OF ODA WAS ABOUT TO BE REALIZED.
THOUGH WHEN THIS BATTLE ENDS,
THE GENERALS MAY ONCE
AGAIN CROSS SWORDS,
EACH OF THEM HAS A CLEAR
VISION OF THE FUTURE
WHICH THRIVES IN THEIR HEARTS.
- Keiji: THE LAST BIG FIGHT
AGAINST THE DEVIL KING.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M NOT
JOINING IN ON THE FUN.
MAEDA KEIJI,
WILL HAVE HIS WAY!