- LORD NAGAMASA, RUN!
- ( gunshots )
- ( groans )
ICHI.
- ( gunshots )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( chuckles )
- ( grunting )
- MY LORD NAGAMASA.
LORD NAGAMASA.
MY HUSBAND, NO.
- ICHI, THIS IS A
FIELD OF BATTLE.
IT ISN'T SAFE FOR YOU HERE.
- ( crying )
- Akechi: ( chuckles ) THANK YOU
FOR YOUR SERVICES RENDERED,
LADY O-ICHI. I DO FEEL
IT'S WORTH MENTIONING
THAT YOU DID NOT ACCOMPLISH
ONE OF YOUR OBJECTIVES.
WORKED OUT IN THE END, THOUGH.
LADY O-ICHI'S MARRIAGE INTO
THE AZAI WAS THE GROUNDWORK
FOR AN ATTACK ON ASAKURA.
- ( gasps )
- HER ROLE WAS SEDUCTION,
OF COURSE.
NOT JUST OF YOU, BUT OF
YOUR TOP GENERALS,
TO UNDERMINE YOUR AUTHORITY.
OR SO IT WAS SUPPOSED TO GO.
BUT LADY O-ICHI WAS
INCAPABLE OF THIS.
BECAUSE, LIKE A FOOL,
SHE FELL IN LOVE.
LIKE A PUPPET ON A STRING,
TOO PROUD TO REVEAL
HER TRUE SELF,
YET TOO WEAK TO CARRY
OUT HER SECRET MISSION.
BECAUSE SHE CHOSE TO
NURTURE HER MARITAL BONDS,
SHE BROUGHT ABOUT AN
EVEN MORE TRAGIC END.
FOR THOSE CLOSEST TO HER
NOW SHARE IN HER MISFORTUNE.
BEAUTIFUL TO BEHOLD,
ROTTEN TO THE CORE,
SISTER OF THE DEVIL KING.
- ICHI, HAVE YOU TRULY
DECEIVED ME ALL THIS TIME?
- MY LORD HUSBAND, I AM SORRY.
YOU AND THE PEOPLE OF AZAI,
YOU DESERVED BETTER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I AM SORRY, SO SORRY.
- ( gasps )
- HOW YOU MUST HAVE SUFFERED.
- YOU NEEDN'T BE
MAUDLIN ANY LONGER.
- LORD NAGAMASA.
- ( choking )
MY SOLDIERS OF JUSTICE,
I'M SORRY.
WHILE PERISHING HERE
IS MY DEEPEST REGRET.
I, NAGAMASA, HAVE UPHELD
JUSTICE TO MY VERY LAST BREATH.
ICHI, TELL ME I
WAS NOT WRONG,
THAT ALL OF THIS
WAS NOT IN VAIN.
- NO, MY BELOVED,
YOU WERE NOT WRONG.
YOU WERE NEVER WRONG.
- THANK YOU.
ICHI, I LOVE YOU.
- NAGAMASA? NAGAMASA? NAGAMASA.
( crying )
- ( chuckles ) YOUR WEEPING, MY
LADY O-ICHI IS MUSIC TO MY EARS.
- KOJURO.
- SIR.
BOSS, WHAT'RE YOU...
- WE MEET AGAIN.
- ( chuckles ) CRASHING
OTHER PEOPLE'S BATTLES
IS GETTING TO BE YOUR SPECIALTY.
AND TO THINK NOT
A SINGLE ROUND HIT YOU.
- IT SEEMS YOU'RE
EXTRAORDINARILY LUCKY.
- YOU SERVE THE DEVIL KING?
- MASAMUNE, DON'T DO THIS, SIR!
- THIS MAN WAS YOUR SHIELD.
HE FOUGHT FOR YOU
AND YOU GUNNED HIM DOWN
FROM BEHIND LIKE A RABID DOG.
THIS AGGRESSION WILL NOT STAND.
- ( laughs ) I SEE
YOU'RE ANGRY, ONE-EYED DRAGON.
- SHALL WE HAVE A LITTLE FUN?
- YOU ARE ON. LOTS OF LUCK!
- YOU FREAK, WHAT THE
HELL IS WITH THE DRUNK
LOOK ON YOUR FACE?
- MY DEAR BOY, I AM
SAVORING THE AFTERGLOW.
- WHAT?
- NOTHING IN THE WORLD
GIVES ME GREATER DELIGHT
THAN TRAMPLING THE STEADFAST
BOND BETWEEN TWO LOVERS.
THE ONLY PLEASURE
THAT COULD EVEN COMPARE...
WOULD BE A WORTHY FOE,
DRENCHED IN BLOOD AND TEARS,
GROVELING AT MY FEET
FOR HIS LIFE.
NOW, LET THE FESTIVITIES BEGIN!
- ( grunts )
- THERE'S IEYASU!
- GET HIM!
- ( screams )
- TADAKATSU?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
TADAKATSU? WHY?
- MY LORD IEYASU,
ODA HAS FORSAKEN US.
NO, WORSE. HE HAS DECEIVED US.
- WE WERE COUNTING ON
HIS ARQUEBUS CORE.
WE'RE SO BADLY OUTNUMBERED,
NOW, OUR DESTRUCTION
IS INEVITABLE.
- IF WE RETREAT...
- RETREAT?
BUT IF WE WITHDRAW NOW,
IT WOULD DISHONOR THE MEN
WHO GAVE THEIR LIVES HERE.
- IF WE DO NOT,
WE WILL CERTAINLY SHARE
THE SAME FATE AS AZAI.
- PLEASE, LORD,
MAKE YOUR DECISION.
- ALL RIGHT, WITHDRAW.
WHAT'RE YOU...
TADAKATSU!
- ( Japanese song playing )
- IT WOULD SEEM MASTER TADAKATSU
PLANS TO ACT AS OUR REAR GUARD
AND HOLD OFF THE ENEMY.
- ( all screaming )
- SO, YOU WISH TO DO BATTLE
WITH SANADA YUKIMURA.
JUST COME BACK ALIVE.
PULL OUT! ALL UNITS, RETREAT!
- YUKIMURA, THE SO-CALLED
GREATEST WARRIOR IN THE LAND,
RECOGNIZES YOU
AS AN EXCEPTIONAL GENERAL.
HOLD YOUR GROUND,
BY ANY MEANS POSSIBLE.
- SIR. I PROMISE YOU,
I WILL NOT FAIL.
- ALL UNITS! ON ME!
- ( cheering )
- KEIJI, TURN BACK.
- PLEASE, KENSHIN, LET ME GO.
IF I TURN BACK NOW,
WHO WILL DEFEAT
THE DEVIL KING. AND WHEN?
- WE WILL SIMPLY
HAVE TO REGROUP.
- HOW CAN WE?
- WE STILL DRAW
BREATH, DO WE NOT?
- I'M SORRY, THIS IS ONE TIME
WHERE EVEN YOUR REQUEST
ISN'T GOING TO STOP ME. YAH!
- KEIJI!
- ( all yelling )
- Tokugawa's soldier:
TAKEDA SHINGEN IS CLOSING IN!
- PLEASE, LORD IEYASU,
LET US MAKE HASTE.
- TADAKATSU.
- REFINED TECHNIQUE,
A KIND HEART, LOVE OF YOUR LORD
AND LOVE OF YOUR COMRADES,
MASTER HONDA TADAKATSU,
YOU TRULY ARE THE GREATEST
WARRIOR IN THE LAND.
LORD IEYASU IS A GENERAL
WORTHY OF LAYING DOWN YOUR
LIFE TO FOLLOW. HOWEVER,
HE SOUGHT TO SAFEGUARD HIS
HOUSE BY ALIGNING WITH ODA.
WAITING FOR THE WINDS TO CHANGE.
EVEN IF IT WAS UNAVOIDABLE,
HIS ONLY MEANS OF SURVIVAL,
TO ME, IT'S JUST...
( screams )
TIGER FLAME!
- ( all scream )
- IF WE DO ESCAPE,
THEN TO WHAT PURPOSE?
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO LOSE YOU GUYS.
I MUST PROTECT
THE HOUSE OF TOKUGAWA.
- Nohime: SO, YOU PLAN TO
JOIN THE EASTERN ALLIANCE,
LITTLE TAKETCHIYO?
- LADY NOHIME.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'D COME TO HELP.
- ( gunshots )
- LORD SHINGEN.
- BRIDE OF ODA, YOU
WOULD SELL HIS SOUL
AND STAIN YOUR HANDS
IN HIS BLOOD?
- ( gunshots )
- THE WORLD BELONGS
TO MY HUSBAND.
TRY AND DIE LIKE MEN.
- MASTER HONDA, LOOK OVER THERE!
ODA SEEKS TO DESTROY
NOT ONLY MY ARMY,
BUT TO CUT OFF TOKUGAWA'S PATH
OF RETREAT AT THE SAME TIME.
IT IS STILL NOT TOO
LATE TO FIX THIS.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER, WE CAN
DEFEAT THE DEVIL KING.
- JOIN WITH US.
- Tokugawa: TADAKATSU!
TADAKATSU, I'M ON MY WAY!
- MY LORD KAZUSANOSUKE
DID NOT WISH TO MAKE
AN ENEMY OF YOU.
- ( gasps ) THE LADY ODA? WHAT?
- HONDA TADAKATSU,
ENJOY A HERO'S DEATH.
- ( loud explosion )
- ( screams ) MASTER HONDA.
- Tadakatsu!
- ( loud explosion )
- TADAKATSU!
- MASTER HONDA!
- ( chuckles ) WITH THAT,
THE EASTERN LANDS ARE CRIPPLED.
RIPE FOR EXTINCTION
ANY GIVEN TIME.
- ( grunts )
- WHAT'S WRONG, ONE-EYED
DRAGON? I EXPECTED MORE.
SO, ARE YOU GOING TO DANCE
FOR ME, OR NOT?
- NICE SPEECH. YOU COULD BE
HELL'S GATEKEEPER.
- MASAMUNE, GIVE THE ORDER
TO WITHDRAW.
WITH THAT MANY
FIREARMS TRAINED ON US,
IF WE FACE THEM HEAD-ON,
WE'LL BE WIPED OUT.
AS YOUR RIGHT EYE, I WILL
SHARE THIS SHAME WITH YOU.
- ( laughs )
- DAMN IT. SOUND THE RETREAT.
- RETREAT! RETREAT!
- ( blowing )
- ( chuckles ) I SUPPOSE
WE'LL HOLD FIRE.
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM SPORTING.
- ( Japanese song playing )
- ( Tokugawa crying )
- Sanada: YOUR LORDSHIP.
- YOU ARE SAFE, I SEE.
- SIR, MASTER HONDA THREW ME
CLEAR OF NOHIME'S ATTACK.
HONESTLY, HE SAVED MY LIFE.
BUT YOUR LORDSHIP, I DO NOT
UNDERSTAND WHY ODA ATTACKED
TOKUGAWA IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE ALLIES.
- THEIR ALLIANCE WAS LIKELY
BASED ON ODA WANTING TO KEEP
TADAKATSU'S STRENGTH AT BAY.
JUST AS HE ATTEMPTED
TO DIVIDE AZAI AND ASAKURA,
WHO MIGHT HAVE FORMED
A STRONG ARMY AGAINST HIM.
- TOKUGAWA MUST HAVE
BEEN DECEIVED AS WELL.
- THAT IS SO DASTARDLY.
- ALL BLAME RESTS ON MY
SHOULDERS. I BELIEVED IN HIM.
I MADE A DEAL WITH
THE DEVIL KING
IN HOPES OF WINNING BATTLES,
AND THIS IS WHAT IT'S WROUGHT.
( grunts )
TADAKATSU, I WANTED
TO CONQUER THIS WORLD
WITH YOU AT MY SIDE.
( crying ) TADAKATSU.
- TADAKATSU WAS NOT
YOUR ONLY STRENGTH,
NOT WHEN YOU STILL HAVE LOYAL
TROOPS WHO WILL STAND BY YOU.
YOU UPHELD TWO THINGS TODAY.
YOUR WORD AND THE SPIRIT
OF THE MIKAWA WARRIOR.
- I, SHINGEN, SAW IT ALL.
- I'M SO SORRY.
LORD SHINGEN, THOUGH
I HAVE LOST TADAKATSU
AND MANY OF MY SOLDIERS,
I NOW HUMBLY ASK TO JOIN
IN YOUR FIGHT TO DEFEAT
THE CURSED DEVIL KING.
- YUKIMURA, TRANSPORT AS MANY OF
THE INJURED AS POSSIBLE TO KAI.
- EXTEND OUR HELP,
REGARDLESS OF CLAN.
- SIR.
- Keiji: I HAVE TO WONDER,
HOW MANY OF THEM FOUGHT
BECAUSE THEY WANTED TO?
SUCH IS WAR.
IT AFFECTS EVERYONE,
WHETHER THEY CHOOSE
IT TO OR NOT.
THE MEN DOWN THERE COULD
HAVE BEEN SINGERS OR ARTISTS,
OR SOME OF THEM EVEN POETS
AND SCHOLARS. WIVES AND LOVERS,
SONS AND DAUGHTERS,
MOTHERS AND FATHERS
WHOSE LOVE CAN
NEVER BE REPAID.
ALL LEFT BEHIND WITH ONLY TEARS.
THAT IS WHAT I WANTED
TO PUT AN END TO.
- A DEMON RUNNING AMOK
CAN ONLY BE PUT DOWN
WITH THE USE OF FORCE.
KEIJI, WILL YOU GO
TO THE WEST FOR ME?
WITH THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
BETWEEN THEM, MORI AND CHOSOKABE
ARE ON THE VERGE OF HOSTILITIES.
GO WIN THEM OVER.
- IF ODA GETS PAST THEM,
OUR PLANS WILL BE FOR NOTHING.
- I AM NOT SAYING
IT WILL BE EASY.
BUT WE MUST ACT BEFORE
THE DEVIL KING'S MENACE
BLANKETS THIS LAND
OF THE RISING SUN.
- ( squeals )
- GIVE MY REGARDS TO YOUR GOD,
I'M SURE I COULD USE
BISHAMONTEN'S HELP.
- MASAMUNE?
- Sanada: ONE-EYED DRAGON, WAIT!
LORD MASAMUNE!
IT IS FAR TO OSHU. COME TO KAI,
YOU CAN REST THERE.
- MASAMUNE, LET US TAKE
THE TAKEDA CLAN'S OFFER.
WE HAVE MANY INJURED.
MASAMUNE, SIR?
- MASAMUNE!
- BIG BOSS!
- MY LORD, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HOW DID I NOT NOTICE YOU HAD
BEEN STRUCK BY AN ARQUEBUS?
I BLAME MYSELF. I COULD HAVE
STOPPED YOUR FIGHT WITH AKECHI.
AS YOUR RIGHT EYE,
I SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- BOSS MASAMUNE WILL BE FINE.
- ( all sighs )
- ENOUGH! QUIT MOPING
AND MAKE YOURSELVES USEFUL.
GATHER ALL OUR ABLE-BODIED MEN
AND GET OUT THERE!
FOLLOW TAKEDA'S EXAMPLE
AND TEND TO THE INJURED.
- NO MATTER WHAT
FAMILY THEY CLAIM.
- All: SIR.
- FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY,
I MUST THANK YOU.
- IT SEEMS HE IS NO
LONGER AT DEATH'S DOOR
BUT HE HAS LOST QUITE
A LOT OF BLOOD.
MY PEOPLE ARE PREPARING
SOMETHING TO POUR DOWN
HIS THROAT. IT SHOULD HELP HIM.
- AGAIN, MY THANKS.
- RIGHT EYE OF THE DRAGON,
DO YOU RESENT OUR USE
OF DATE'S ARMY AS THE
SPEARHEAD IN OUR ATTACK?
- WE HAVE ALWAYS ACTED
OF OUR OWN ACCORD.
FROM THE START, OUR ACTIONS
WERE UNRELATED
TO YOURS AND UESUGI'S.
- THERE ARE GENERALS WHO
STILL WISH TO FIGHT OVER LAND.
IT IS THEIR HOPE THAT
WE OURSELVES FALL,
AS WE DEFEAT ODA.
HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE MAN,
ONE WHO IS NOT A GENERAL,
WHO WE HAVE SENT TO SPEAK
TO MORI AND CHOSOKABE.
- MAEDA KEIJI.
- WITH US ALLIED AT HIS BACK,
HE HAD PLANNED TO
FACE ODA ON HIS OWN.
HE HAD HOPED TO RESOLVE
THE MATTER WITHOUT BLOODSHED.
A FASCINATING MAN. IT'S A
SHAME HE SQUANDERED
HIS TALENTS FOR SO
LONG AS A VAGABOND.
- I ASSUMED HE'D
PLANNED THE OPPOSITE.
- VICTORY IS POINTLESS IF IT
LEAVES US ALL COMPLETELY SPENT.
TIME IS SHORT, BUT I WOULD LIKE
TO HAVE ODA FULLY ENCIRCLED
BEFORE WE ATTEMPT THIS AGAIN.
- IT WILL BE MOST DIFFICULT
TO GET MORI AND CHOSOKABE
TO YOUR SIDE.
ALSO, THE IDEA OF TEAMING UP
TO DEFEAT A COMMON ENEMY,
IS NOT THE WAY OF THE DATE.
BUT...
NECESSITY KNOWS NO LAW.
- ONE-EYED DRAGON,
LORD DATE MASAMUNE,
AFTER WE HAVE
DEFEATED THE DEVIL KING,
LET US MEET ON THE
FIELD OF DECISIVE BATTLE.
LET US SETTLE OUR RIVALRY
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- LORD NAGAMASA.
- MITSUHIDE, YOU WERE AWARE
OF THE EASTERN CLANS' MOVEMENTS,
YET YOU REMAINED SILENT.
- THEY WERE A PATHETIC
BAND OF WEAKLINGS.
I JUDGED THEM TO BE OF
NO REAL THREAT TO US.
- IT IS FOR LORD ODA
TO PASS JUDGMENT.
YOU PUT A CHINK IN THEIR ARMOR,
BUT HAD YOU NOT SET THE
ARQUEBUSES AGAINST DATE,
TAKEDA'S CAVALRY
COULD HAVE BEEN WIPED OUT.
WHAT'S MORE, YOU CAUSED
AZAI'S POINTLESS DEATH.
AND FORCED OUR HAND IN
DISSOLVING OUR ALLIANCE
WITH TOKUGAWA.
AN ARRANGEMENT STILL
OF GREAT USE TO US.
- WHICH GAVE YOU THE CHANCE
TO KILL HONDA TADAKATSU.
AS FOR AZAI, WE HAD PLANNED
TO CRUSH HIM ALONG WITH ASAKURA.
WITH THE EASTERN
GENERALS INCAPACITATED
FOR THE TIME BEING.
I NEED ONLY PROCEED TO ECHIZEN,
WHICH WILL CLEARLY BRING THE
BALANCE BACK TO YOUR FAVOR.
- TO WHAT PURPOSE DID YOU LET
THE DATE MAGGOT ESCAPE?
- AS SHE WAS THERE ON THE FIELD,
I
WAS CONCERNED ONLY WITH
LADY O-ICHI'S SAFETY.
- ( grunts ) MITSUHIDE,
COME CLOSER.
- SIR.
- ( gasps )
- YOU HAVE CROSSED A LINE.
NEXT TIME, IT WILL NOT BE SAKE
IN WHICH YOU ARE DRENCHED.
BUT YOUR OWN BLOOD,
SPURTING FROM YOUR HEAD.
- I BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS.
YOU HAVE MY MOST HEARTFELT
APOLOGIES, LORD NOBUNAGA.
- ONE SHOULD OBTAIN
THE THINGS THAT ONE DESIRES.
ALL THINGS WITH FORM
EVENTUALLY CRUMBLE.
THAT BEING THE CASE,
ONE SHOULD FOLLOW
WHAT DESIRE DEMANDS.
- ( theme song playing )
- Sarutobi: RIN, PYO, TOH, SHA,
KAI, JIN, RETSU, ZAI, ZEN.
SEE THAT? MY NINJA MIND TRICK
MADE YOU WANT TO COME BACK
NEXT TIME, RIGHT?
WHAT NO TRICKS NEEDED?
GOOD, GOOD. I KNEW I LIKED YOU.