- ( explosions )
- ( laughs ) FINALLY,
THE OLD GIRL'S ALL DONE UP.
PACKS ONE HELL OF A PUNCH,
AND IF WE CAN SPOT 'EM,
SHE CAN BLAST 'EM.
NO ONE'S BOARDING US,
THANKS TO THIS LITTLE BEAUT,
THE CROWN JEWEL OF THE FUGAKU.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU SONS OF BITCHES
REARING FOR A FIGHT?
- ( cheering )
- CAPTAIN!
- WHAT'S UP, BEKUNOSUKE?
- MORE BOATS COMING ASHORE
FROM THE WEST, CAPTAIN.
HAILING FROM MORI'S DOMAIN
BASED ON THE LOOKS OF 'EM.
- WELL, THEN BRING 'EM ABOARD.
THEY'RE REFUGEES NEEDIN' HELP,
SO THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE GONNA GIVE 'EM.
YATARO, HIKOJI, TAKE THIS
BATCH TO YOUR VILLAGE.
MAKE 'EM FEEL AT HOME.
- Both: AYE, CAPTAIN.
- WHERE DO THEY GET OFF,
DRIVING AWAY THEIR OWN PEOPLE
LIKE THEY'RE NOTHING?
- Man: BEGGING YOUR PARDON,
CAPTAIN CHOSOKABE.
I MAY BE OLD, BUT I'VE GOT
SOME FIGHT LEFT IN ME.
- PLEASE, CAPTAIN, SIR,
LET US FIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
- AT LEAST WE CAN MAKE SURE YOU
AND YOUR MEN ARE WELL FED.
- PERMISSION TO COME ABOARD,
CAPTAIN.
- THESE WOMEN AND CHILDREN CAME
HERE FROM HARIMA AND MIMASA.
AND THE OLD FELLAS ARE
FROM KAWACHI.
- YEAH, THEY ALL FEEL
LIKE THEY OWE YOU ONE.
- CAPTAIN!
- THANKS FOR OFFERING,
BUT THE ANSWER IS NO.
THE FUGAKU'S A PIRATE SHIP.
NO PLACE FOR HONEST FOLK
LIKE YOU.
IT'S A PLACE FOR RUFFIANS,
HARD MEN WHO DON'T FEAR
THE WATERY GRAVE
THAT AWAITS 'EM.
YOUR HUSBANDS AND FATHERS
AND SONS WHO FELL IN BATTLE,
THEY WOULDN'T WANT YOU DOING
THIS.  AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA
FIGHTS ON YOUR BEHALF,
SO RETURN TO YOUR LANDS.
FOR YOU,
THE BATTLEFIELD IS BACK HOME.
IT'S TIME TO PIECE YOUR LIVES
TOGETHER AGAIN.
I KNOW, IT AIN'T AS EXCITING
AS SWINGING A SWORD AROUND,
BUT IT'LL WORK.  TRUST ME.
DON'T WORRY, LAD.
I'LL GET THE BAD GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DOGS.
GET SET FOR A HELL OF A FIGHT.
BLAST MORI AND TOYOTOMI
AND THEN THE WHOLE DAMN COUNTRY
IS OURS.
- AYE, CAPTAIN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Man: LORD TOSHIIE.
PLEASE WAIT, MILORD.
- Matsu: I BEG OF YOU, MY LORD
INUCHIYO, DO NOT DO THIS.
- Toshiie: LET GO OF ME!
CAN'T YOU ALL UNDERSTAND?
I MUST LEAVE,
FOR THE SAKE OF KAGA.
- Matsu: WIELDING A SPEAR
IN YOUR CONDITION ISN'T BRAVERY.
IT'S SUICIDE.
- NO, UNHAND ME, MATSU.  OW!
I AM THE MASTER OF MY FATE,
AND I'M LEAVING-- OW!
- YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
- Man: LADY MATSU.
- Toshiie: WAIT.
LET'S TALK THIS OUT.
- Matsu: GOROMARU!
- ( screaming )
( groaning )
KEIJI.
- YEAH, SO LONG TIME NO SEE.
- MATSU, MATSU, IT'S KEIJI.
KEIJI'S FINALLY COME HOME.
- WELCOME BACK.
- Keiji: WHAT WAS ALL
THAT YELLING ABOUT?
- TOYOTOMI HAS CALLED
UPON THE MAEDA.
HE WANTS US TO JOIN
THE RANKS ENCIRCLING KAI.
- ENCIRCLING KAI?  THEY TRYING
TO STARVE THEM OUT OR SOMETHING?
- MATSU.
WITH ODAWARA
AND UTSUNOMIYA TAKEN,
TAKEDA IS PINNED DOWN
ESSENTIALLY.
BUT WITH MOST OF TOYOTOMI'S
FORCES EN ROUTE TO AKI,
IT WOULD NOT BE DIFFICULT
FOR TAKEDA TO CLAIM OSAKA.
- THAT MAKES SENSE.
IF I KNOW MOTOCHIKA,
HE'S GOING TO GIVE THEM ONE HECK
OF A FIGHT.
BUT TOYOTOMI TOOK UTSUNOMIYA
AND ODAWARA
TO KEEP TAKEDA
WHERE HE IS, RIGHT?
BECAUSE KENSHIN TEAMED WITH
TAKEDA AGAINST THE DEVIL KING
DOESN'T MEAN HE'LL SIDE
WITH HIM THIS TIME AROUND.
- YES, MY SENTIMENTS EXACTLY.
OUR LOYALTY TO THE CAUSE
IS BEING TESTED
AND IF WE IGNORE TOYOTOMI'S
ORDERS, HE'LL DESTROY KAGA.
- JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE NO BETTER OFF NOW
THAN YOU WERE WHEN YOU THREW
IN YOUR LOT WITH THE DEVIL KING.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
TOYOTOMI IS NOT ODA.
LISTEN TO ME, KEIJI.
HE SEEKS ONLY THE HELP
OF THOSE STRONG ENOUGH
TO GIVE IT.
TO ATONE FOR THE DARK DEEDS
I COMMITTED AS A MEMBER
OF THE ODA FACTION AND TO
PROTECT THE PEOPLE OF KAGA,
I WILL JOIN THE FIGHT
AGAINST TAKEDA.  I HAVE TO.
THAT IS MY DUTY
AS LEADER OF THE MAEDA FAMILY.
AND AS A WARRIOR,
I'LL FULFILL IT.
- TOSHIIE.
- WHENEVER YOU GO INTO BATTLE,
KNOW THAT MATSU IS
BY YOUR SIDE,
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU
OVERDOING IT, UNDERSTAND?
IF THE DAY EVER DAWNS
WHEN I COOK FOR ONLY ONE,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D DO.
- MATSU.
WE'LL BE DINING TOGETHER
FOR A LONG TIME.
- I NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
I REALLY BACKED YOU TWO
INTO A CORNER, HUH?
- THIS WASN'T YOUR DOING,
KEIJI.
EVEN IF OUR ATTACK
ON ECHIGO WAS A VICTORY
IN EVERY SENSE
OF THE WORD, I KNEW
IT WOULD COME TO THIS
SOONER OR LATER.
MATSU TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED
TO LADY NENE.
I TOLD YOU ONCE THAT TOYOTOMI
WAS THE MAN I'D BE
IF I LOST MATSU,
BUT NOW I KNOW THAT ISN'T TRUE.
THE THINGS THAT MAN HAS DONE
IN THE NAME OF POWER,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THEM
AND I PRAY I NEVER DO.
- KEIJI, ALL I ASK IS THAT YOU
REMAIN TRUE TO YOURSELF.
I'VE BEEN SO QUICK TO VOICE MY
DISAPPROVAL WITH YOU
IN THE PAST, WHEN WHAT I SHOULD
HAVE DONE WAS TAKE A MOMENT
TO ASK MYSELF WHY YOU DIDN'T
WANT TO LIVE A WARRIOR'S LIFE.
- THE BREACH BETWEEN TOYOTOMI
AND YOU CAN NEVER BEEN MENDED.
I UNDERSTAND THIS,
MUCH TOO LATE.
MY COURSE IS SET,
FOR GOOD OR FOR ILL,
BUT BELIEVE ME
WHEN I SAY THIS.
WHATEVER MAY HAPPEN, KEIJI,
NO MATTER WHAT THIS WORLD
THROWS AT US, WE ARE FAMILY.
- TOSHIIE, MATSU, I--
FOR A TRANQUIL LAND
OF THE RISING SUN,
SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE DIED
FOR IT.
HAVE WE GOTTEN ANY CLOSER?
- HEY, CAPTAIN.
MORI'S SHIPS ARE JUST LAZING
ABOUT WITH THEIR SAILS TIED UP.
- YOU'RE WAITING FOR TOYOTOMI,
ARE YOU?  WISE MOVE, MOTONARI.
NEVER HEARD TALK OF TOYOTOMI
HAVING A NAVY, THOUGH.
I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE UP TO.
MAYBE THEY'RE ONTO OUR COURSE
AND THERE'S 10,000 OF THOSE
BASTARDS WAITING FOR US TO LAND.
- WAIT, CAPTAIN, YOU'RE SAYING
THOSE SHIPS OF MORI'S--
- ARE JUST BAIT
TO LURE US CLOSER.
- BAIT US, BRIBE US OR BEG US,
WE'RE TAKING OUT THE LOT OF 'EM.
HIT 'EM LIKE A TYPHOON.  HOLD
'EM BACK AND KNOCK 'EM DOWN.
EASY FOR THE FUGAKU.
ENOUGH LOLLYGAGGING,
YOU SALTY SONS OF BITCHES.
PRIME THE CANNON FOR BATTLE.
WE'RE TAKING DOWN MORI'S NAVY
TODAY.
- ( cheering )
- SEND THEM ALL TO HELL
IF IT BRINGS YOU CLOSER,
YOU COCKSURE FOOL.
- BUT, LORD MORI, AS IMPORTANT
OF A TARGET AS THE FUGAKU IS,
AT THIS RATE,
OUR LOSSES WILL BE--
- OUR LOSSES ARE PART
OF THE PLAN.
WHAT GOOD ARE PAWNS IF NOT TO
FALL AT THEIR MASTER'S COMMAND?
- QUITE RIGHT, MILORD.
BUT WHAT IS YOUR NEXT MOVE?
- IF I HAD SPURNED THIS ALLIANCE
WITH TOYOTOMI,
HE WOULD HAVE APPROACHED
CHOSOKABE WITH THE SAME OFFER.
HAVE ONE PUT THEIR BOOT
TO THE OTHER'S THROAT.
IN DOING SO, LAY THE FOUNDATION
FOR THE CONQUEST OF KYUSHU.
THAT'S TOYOTOMI'S SCHEME
OR TAKENAKA HANBEI'S, RATHER
I'M MERELY LOOKING FOR A WAY
TO TWIST IT TO MY ADVANTAGE.
- RIGHT.
- THINGS SEEM TO BE GOING
TO PLAN, MY DEAR MOTONARI.
- WE'RE RUNNING
HALF AN HOUR LATE,
AND I'VE LOST MORE SHIPS TO THIS
FEINT THAN WE'D ANTICIPATED.
- YOU'RE TO BE COMMENDED FOR
DRAWING THE FUGAKU OUT THIS FAR.
FEAR NOT.  MY MASTER WILL
SHATTER THE PIRATE'S BONES.
THIS POUND OF FLESH YOUR FOE
HAS CARVED FROM YOU
WILL SURELY BUY THE LAND OF AKI
PEACE AND PROSPERITY.
AKAGAWA, ORDER ALL THE SHIPS
TO RETREAT AT ONCE.
- RIGHT.
- CAPTAIN, MORI'S SHIPS
ARE TURNING TAIL.
TOYOTOMI FOOT-SOLDIERS.
A WHOLE MESS OF 'EM.
- WHAT DID I SAY?
LURED US TO THE COAST
'CAUSE THEY WANT
TO DUKE IT OUT ON DRY LAND.
HAVE IT YOUR WAY, MOTONARI.
YOUR NEW PAL CAN PLAY, TOO.
THAT'S IF YOU CAN DODGE MY
CANNON FIRE LONG ENOUGH FOR ME
TO SAIL OVER
AND KICK YOUR ASSES.
- ( gasps )
- OH!
- Man:
THAT-- THAT'S THE GUY.
- CAPTAIN,
THAT HUGE ENEMY GENERAL'S
WALKING RIGHT OUT
INTO THE SEA.
- WHAT'S THAT LAND SHARK
UP TO?
- CHOSOKABE MOTOCHIKA,
SWEAR FEALTY AND I'LL LET YOU
KEEP YOUR LITTLE FLOATING TOY.
FOR IF YOU REFUSE ME...
( roars )
I PROMISE THAT YOU WILL
MEET YOUR DOOM THIS DAY.
- HE PARTED THE VERY WATERS.
- THE SEA IS GONE.
- CAPTAIN, WHAT IN THE--
WHAT THE NINE HELLS IS HE?
- TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI
IN THE BIG UGLY FLESH.
- CAPTAIN, TROUBLE.
BOTH ARMIES ARE COMING AT US.
- AIM AT THE SCRUFFY BASTARD
IN FRONT.
THAT OCEAN-PUNCHING APE
IS THE TOYOTOMI GENERAL.
- GOT 'EM IN OUR SIGHTS.
- FIRE!
- WHAT?
- ( gasping )
- HE STOPPED AN 11-FOOT
CANNONBALL WITH ONE HAND?
- ONE PUNY GUN WAS THE SOURCE
OF YOUR HUBRIS.
YOU ARE NO WARRIOR.
NO OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA.
YOU'RE JUST A WHARF RAT!
- ( shouting )
- CAPTAIN.
- ( horse whinnies )
- UNBELIEVABLE.
THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
IS GONE.
- BELIEVE IT.  TOYOTOMI SENT
THE WATER FLYING WITH ONE PUNCH.
- SASUKE.
- NO OFFENSE,
BUT SHOULD WE EVEN BE HAVING
THIS TALK RIGHT NOW?
I FIGURED YOU WOULD HAVE ARRIVED
IN SATSUMA EARLIER THAN THIS.
- YES, FORGIVE ME.
- YUKIMURA, THIS IS NO PLACE
FOR US TO TARRY.
- YOU WOULD HAVE US LEAVE?
- YOU WITNESSED TOYOTOMI'S POWER
FIRSTHAND AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
CHOSOKABE'S FORTRESS WILL FALL
TO ITS ATTACKERS.
IT'S ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME.
- RUN!
- ( laughs )
YOU BASTARDS THOUGHT MY FUGAKU
WAS JUST SOME OVERGROWN BOAT?
SHE CAN HOLD HER OWN
ON DRY LAND, TOO.
PUT YOUR BACKS INTO IT, DOGS.
- ( cheering )
- AS I EXPECTED,
IT CAN FUNCTION OUT OF WATER.
A MORE THAN WELCOME ADDITION
TO OUR ARSENAL,
IF DEAR MOTOCHIKA HAS WISDOM
ENOUGH TO SURRENDER.
- CHOSOKABE WILL NEVER SUBMIT
TO ANYONE.
- YES, I'M WELL AWARE
OF HIS DISPOSITION.
- ENJOY MY TREADS,
YOU HULKING BASTARD.
- YOUR SCATTERED BONES WILL BE
A WARNING TO ALL WHO OPPOSE ME.
- ( screaming )
- SON OF A BITCH.
- ( bird squawking )
- I DON'T RECALL INVITING
YOU ABOARD.
YOU'VE STUMBLED INTO OGRE
TERRITORY, DUMB BASTARD.
IT'S ONE OF THEM FATAL MISTAKES
YOU MAKE ONLY ONCE.
- I SEE YOU
FOR WHAT YOU ARE, CHOSOKABE.
A TOOTHLESS OGRE, LORDING
OVER YOUR TINY ISLAND KINGDOM.
THERE IS NO PLACE FOR PIRATES
IN THE COUNTRY
I'M PUTTING TOGETHER.
ABANDON THIS FORTRESS,
KNEEL ON THE DECK BEFORE ME,
YOU'LL HAVE A PLACE
IN MY ARMY,
A FORCE THAT WILL DOMINATE
THE WORLD.
- MIGHT AS WELL STOP WASTING
YOUR BREATH.
THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA
DON'T TAKE ORDERS
FROM SOME ARMOR-CLAD CHIMP.
- AS I BEAT THE LIFE OUT OF YOU,
KNOW ONE THING.
YOU WILL DIE FOR THE GOOD
OF YOUR COUNTRY.
- YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN TAKE ME?
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO.
- CAPTAIN,
THEY'RE COMING RIGHT FOR US.
- Sanada:
THIS IS DIFFICULT TO WATCH.
CHOSOKABE IS SAID
TO BE A GOOD MAN.
FROM WHAT WE'VE HEARD,
HE'S TAKEN IN FAMILIES LEFT
FATHERLESS BY TOYOTOMI'S
MILITARY CONSCRIPTION,
AS WELL AS REFUGEES
FROM LANDS DEFEATED BY MORI.
- ONCE THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
IS UNDER THEIR CONTROL,
THEY'LL BEGIN INVADING KYUSHU.
OUR MISSION IS TO RACE AHEAD
OF THEM AND PREVENT THAT
FROM HAPPENING.  YOU SEEM TO
HAVE FORGOTTEN THIS AS OF LATE.
UP UNTIL RIGHT NOW, I WAS
CONTENT IN HOLDING MY TONGUE
OUT OF RESPECT FOR OUR LORD'S
COMMAND THAT WE HELP YOU,
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
I, OYAMADA, REFUSE TO COMPLY.
- MASTER SANADA,
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE THE COMMANDER
OF THIS CAVALRY.
GOOD OR BAD,
IT'S ALL ON YOU.
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
IS MY STOMPING GROUNDS.
I TAKE NONE TOO KINDLY
TO BASTARDS WHO RUIN IT.
- THE WORLD IS BIGGER THAN
THAT ONE EYE OF YOURS CAN SEE.
THE SHAME MUST BURN
YOU ALIVE, PIRATE.
EXPOSED AS A WEAKLING
BEFORE ALL YOUR MEN.
STRENGTH WILL BRING
OUR FRACTURED LAND TOGETHER.
WITH MY POWER, I WILL STAND
ASTRIDE THE GLOBE.
- CAN'T WE JUST GIVE YOU
A BANANA AND CALL IT A DAY?
I SWEAR ON MY LIFE, YOU'RE
NOT GETTING YOUR GRUBBY PAWS
ON THE INLAND SEA OF SETO
OR THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN.
ALL YOUR TALK
OF CONQUERING THE WORLD
AND YOU AIN'T EVEN FINISHED
THIS LITTLE FRACAS YET.
NOW, PUT UP YOUR DUKES,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
- YOU ARE NOTHING.
GO TO YOUR DOOM KNOWING YOU
COULD NEVER HAVE DEFEATED ME.
- All: CAPTAIN!
- CHOSOKABE NEEDS OUR HELP.
PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
- Sasuke: IT'S TOO LATE.
THEY'VE LOST.
BUT IF WE MAKE A BREAK
FOR SATSUMA NOW--
- NO, SASUKE.
I AM NOT LEAVING A BRAVE WARRIOR
AND HIS SOLDIERS HERE TO DIE.
- BUT WE--
WAIT, MASTER OYAMADA.
- I UNDERSTAND NOW,
MASTER YUKIMURA.
- ( coughs )
- HAVE YOU TAKEN ILL?
- I'M FINE.
JUST A BIT SURPRISED.
A PLAYER WHOSE PRESENCE WE
COULDN'T HAVE ACCOUNTED FOR
IS ABOUT TO TAKE THE STAGE.
THE TAKEDA OF KAI.
WHAT DO THEY MEAN TO ACCOMPLISH
WITH SO FEW MEN?
- KNOW THAT I,
SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA,
NOW ENTER THIS FIGHT
TO HELP MASTER CHOSOKABE!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( shouting )
- ( grunting )
- CLEAR A PATH FOR YUKIMURA.
- ( slashing )
- All: MASTER OYAMADA!
- OYAMADA, NO!
MASTER OYAMADA.
- STOP TICKLING ME.
OR WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO HURT?
LISTEN UP, DOGS.
EVERYONE BACK TO THE FUGAKU.
- OGRE OF A CONQUERED ISLAND,
GO SAIL THE SEA OF CORPSES I'VE
SENT TO HELL AHEAD OF YOU.
- PAY CLOSE ATTENTION,
YOU BASTARD,
'CAUSE THIS IS HOW A PIRATE
MEETS HIS END!
- CAPTAIN!
- VICTORY IS OURS.
ALL UNITS, BACK TO THE SHORE.
- TOYOTOMI JUST TOOK
SOMEONE OUT.
I CAN FEEL IT IN MY GUT.
WHICH DOMAIN WENT BELLY-UP,
SHIKOKU MAYBE?
MORE POWER TO 'EM.
THE MORE LAND THEY GRAB
BEFORE I GO TOE-TO-TOE WITH 'EM,
THE EASIER IT'LL BE
FOR THIS DRAGON TO SWOOP IN
AND TAKE THE WHOLE BALL OF WAX.
SMACK DOWN TOYOTOMI
AND THIS WAR IS DONE.
I GET BACK WHAT'S MINE
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
HYAH!
- Miyamoto: MIYAMOTO MUSASHI,
THE MAN, THE MYTH, THE LEGEND.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU CHUMPS
WAITING-- NOT.
NEXT UP, A TASTE
OF MY BADASS-NESS.
KILLER TECHNIQUE
AND A WHOLE LOT OF HURT.
BETTER SHOW,
UNLESS YOU WANNA BE NEXT.
I'LL BE ROCKING MY MOVES
RIGHT FROM THE START.