- Yoshinao: BIG BOSS,
THAT'S TAKEDA'S BANNER!
- Samanosuke:
DON'T TELL ME HE'S SIDING
WITH TOYOTOMI NOW!
- MAYBE, BUT I'M GUESSING NOT.
I DON'T THINK
THE TIGER OF KAI'S
PICKING ANY MORE FIGHTS
THAN HE'S GOT TO RIGHT NOW.
BUT HELL, WE'VE GOT TO TAKE
HIM ON SOME DAY.
GET YOUR GAME FACES ON!
TIME TO KICK SOME ASS!
- ( cheering )
- MAN, IF HE TOOK DOWN TAKEDA,
THINGS ARE GOING
TO GET UGLY IN A HURRY.
- Takeda:
SUCH A LOSS.
OF ALL MY VASSALS,
OYAMADA NOBUSHIGE'S FAITH
IN YUKIMURA WAS UNSWERVING.
IT WAS THAT FAITH THAT LED
HIM ONTO THE BATTLEFIELD.
THAT LED HIM TO HIS END.
- YES, LORD.
BUT HE DIED BRAVELY.
HE SHOWED MASTER SANADA
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE A GENERAL.
- NOBUSHIGE.
- IN HIS DEATH, OYAMADA
LEFT BEHIND A LESSON
FOR MASTER SANADA.
I JUST HOPE THAT HE CAN SEE
THE WISDOM IN IT.
THOUGH, FROM WHAT I SAW, HE'S--
- HE'S MIRED IN SELF-DOUBT.
- THEN I'LL GO
TO SATSUMA, MILORD.
I'LL TAKE OYAMADA'S PLACE
BY HIS--
- NO, YOU WILL NOT.
IF YOU HURRY OVER TO SAVE
YUKIMURA FROM HIMSELF,
THEN OYAMADA WILL HAVE DIED
FOR NOTHING.
- BUT LORD, THE FUTURE
OF THE TAKEDA CLAN
MIGHT HINGE ON WHAT HE DOES.
OUR FATE IS A SHARED ONE.
THIS IS TRULY WHAT IT MEANS--
RAISING SOMEONE AND HANDING
YOUR TOMORROWS TO THEM.
I SHOULDER
THE SAME BURDEN AS HE.
- MILORD...
- THERE IS STRENGTH
IN YOU, YUKIMURA.  CLAIM IT!
NEVER LOSE SIGHT OF THE PATH
ON WHICH YOU JOURNEY.
WHAT OF THE TROOPS
THAT SURROUND THE VILLAGE,
ANY DEVELOPMENTS?
- WELL, SO FAR THEY'RE
JUST STANDING THERE.
THEY HAVEN'T MADE
ANY HOSTILE MOVES.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN HARASSING
THE OUTLYING HOMES.
I THINK THEY'RE HERE TO ENSURE
WE DON'T MOBILIZE OUR FORCES.
BUT IF THAT SHOULD CHANGE,
WE'LL BE NOTIFIED AT ONCE.
- HAVING SAFELY WARDED OFF
TOYOTOMI'S SECRET INVASION,
MASAMUNE HAS BROUGHT
HIS NEIGHBORING LANDS
BACK IN LINE.
BRASH AS HE IS,
HE'S PROBABLY EN ROUTE
TO OSAKA NOW.
- MY SCOUTS SAY
HE'LL BE PASSING US SOON.
I'M SURPRISED HE'S GOING FOR IT.
WITHOUT THE BENEFIT
OF HIS RIGHT EYE,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
SEEMS TO BE FLYING BLIND.
- NOW I SEE WHAT HE'S UP TO.
- WHAT?
- DAMN THAT TOYOTOMI.
- WE'RE GOING TO KNOCK
THEIR ASSES BACK TO KAI!
- ( cheering )
- LORD TAKEDA, IT'S THE SOLDIERS
ENCIRCLING KAI.
THEY'RE ENGAGING DATE
DISGUISED AS YOUR TROOPS.
- LET'S SHOW THEM HOW HIGH
A DRAGON CAN SOAR!
- ( shouts )
- ( theme music plays )
- Katakura:
LORD MASAMUNE...
I, KATAKURA KOJURO,
AM CERTAIN YOU STILL LIVE.
I'VE NEVER DOUBTED
YOUR SURVIVAL FOR A MOMENT.
SO PLEASE, DO NOT ACT RASHLY
WHILE I AM AWAY.
I BEG OF YOU.
- KOJURO...
- ONE-EYED DRAGON,
THESE WARRIORS ARE NOT TAKEDA'S.
THEY'RE TOYOTOMI'S
IN DISGUISE.
- SON OF A BITCH.
- Narrator:
MEANWHILE, HAVING FAILED TO SAVE
CHOSOKABE AND HIS PIRATES
FROM TOYOTOMI'S ATTACK,
SANADA YUKIMURA NOW TRUDGED
HIS WAY INTO KYUSHU.
HIS COASTAL DESTINATION,
SATSUMA,
WAS ALMOST WITHIN REACH.
- Matsunaga: WHATSOEVER A
MAN SOWETH, THAT SHALL HE REAP.
LOOK AT YOU, TREKKING
TO KYOTO IN THESE DARK TIMES.
WHAT IS A GENERAL,
BUT AN AGENT OF CARNAGE,
WHO CLINGS TO HONOR
AS A JUSTIFICATION FOR VIOLENCE?
- Sarutobi:
WHY DO YOU THINK OYAMADA
LED THOSE MEN INTO BATTLE
AT YOUR COMMAND?
IN TIMES OF PEACE,
IT'S DIFFERENT.
YOU HAVE THE LUXURY
OF GROWING INTO YOUR JOB.
BUT THESE ARE UNCERTAIN DAYS.
NONE OF US MAY LIVE
TO SEE TOMORROW.
IF YOU WAIT
UNTIL YOU'RE THE LEADER
TO START ACTING LIKE ONE,
IT'S TOO LATE.
IT'S AN EXPENSIVE LESSON.
ONE THAT OYAMADA PAID FOR
ON YOUR BEHALF.
YOU MADE A CHOICE TO HELP
CHOSOKABE, WHATEVER THE COST.
YET THERE YOU WERE, MASTER,
RUNNING TO OYAMADA'S SIDE
AFTER THEY STRUCK HIM DOWN.
WE RODE IN UNDER PROTEST.
AND YOU COULDN'T EVEN
STAY THE COURSE.
IF THIS IS THE KIND
OF MAN YOU ARE,
EVEN I MIGHT HAVE TO START
LOOKING FOR OTHER EMPLOYMENT.
- ( crying )
I'M SO SORRY!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
MASTER OYAMADA!
YOUR DEATH WAS MY FAULT!
- ( crying continues )
- STOP THAT YELLING.
DO YOU THINK THAT'S
WHAT OYAMADA WOULD HAVE WANTED?
THE QUESTION IS, WHAT WILL YOU
DO FROM HERE ON OUT?
- Sanada: I'VE WIELDED THESE
SPEARS IN FIGHT AFTER FIGHT,
HOPING THAT I MIGHT PLAY
SOME TINY PART IN BRINGING PEACE
TO THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN.
BUT TRY AS I MIGHT, THE WORLD
IS THE SAME AS IT EVER WAS.
WHAT HAVE I WROUGHT
WITH THESE SPEARS?
NOTHING BUT PAIN AND SUFFERING.
UPON FOE AND FRIEND ALIKE.
AND THE ENTIRE TIME WE'VE BEEN
OUT ON THIS MISSION,
I'VE BEEN FIGHTING
LIKE A NOVICE.
I CAN'T STOP THINKING OF--
I FAILED YOU.
FORGIVE ME, YOUR LORDSHIP.
- Soldier:
MASTER YUKIMURA!
- ALRIGHT.
GENTLEMEN, I ASSUME YOU ARE
WITH THE DEFENDERS OF SATSUMA.
WE ARE AN ENVOY OF LORD TAKEDA,
SENT HERE FROM THE LAND OF KAI.
MY GREETINGS. I AM KNOWN
AS SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
I BEAR A MESSAGE
FOR YOUR LEADER, IF YOU--
- ( screaming )
- NO, COME BACK!
HOLD ON A MOMENT, PLEASE!
LOOK, I THINK THERE'S BEEN
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
YOU'RE RIGHT TO BE VIGILANT
IN DEFENSE OF SATSUMA,
BUT WE MEAN YOU NO--
- ( rustling )
- I JUST WALKED INTO A TRAP.
- ( laughing )
- CHECK IT, I SET UP
MY SIGNATURE AMBUSH
AND YOU CHUMPS
WALKED RIGHT INTO IT.
- SO, YOU PLANNED THIS.
AM I TO ASSUME YOU ARE
THE LEADER OF THIS OUTFIT?
- NOW, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
KICK THEIR ASSES!
- Sanada:
DEFEND YOURSELVES,
BUT DO NOT HURT THEM
IF YOU CAN AVOID IT.
- Soldiers:
YES, SIR!
- WANT SOME OF THIS?  ALRIGHT!
YOUR MOMMA'S SO FAT,
TADAKATSU COULDN'T PICK HER UP!
- HE'S HAD NO FORMAL TRAINING,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BUT THAT MAKES HIS NEXT MOVE
ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO READ.
- COME ON, YOU TRYING TO COPY
MY TWO-SWORD STYLE?
LOOK, I'VE GOT PLACES TO BE.
SO JUST LOSE ALREADY!
- LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
IF YOU ARE THE COMMANDER
OF SATSUMA'S MILITARY FORCE--
- BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS, JERK!
- FINE, IT NEED NOT BE YOU.
IF THERE'S ANY OTHER COMMANDER
I CAN SPEAK WITH,
WOULD YOU PLEASE GRANT ME
AN AUDIENCE WITH THEM?
- CRAP.
YOU KNOW, YOUR SPEAR-WORK
IS PRETTY BADASS.
- WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR THE COMPLIMENT.
LET US TRY THIS AGAIN.
- OLDEST TRICK IN THE BOOK!
WHO'S GOT TWO THUMBS,
AND JUST KICKED YOUR ASS?
THIS GUY!
- I'M LIKING YOU
LESS BY THE MOMENT.
- BOO-HOO, MAN.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO THROW
IN THE TOWEL, ARE YOU?
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ALL STUBBORN AND CRAP,
I GUESS I'LL TAKE YOU
TO SEE OL' POPS.
COME ON, POKEY.
- THAT IS HIM, RIGHT?
- YO, POPS!
TURNS OUT THOSE WEREN'T
TOYOTOMI'S GUYS!
THEY CAME OUT HERE TO SEE YOU.
THEY SAY THEY CAME
FROM THE LAND OF IKA.
- Sanada: WHAT? I NEVER
SAID WE WERE FROM IKA.
WE'RE FROM KAI.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- I'M SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA,
SIR.
VASSAL OF LORD TAKEDA SHINGEN
OF KAI.
I'VE COME AT MILORD'S REQUEST
TO BOLSTER YOUR FORCES
WITH YOUR PERMISSION.
THAT WE MAY THWART TOYOTOMI
HIDEYOSHI'S INVASION OF SATSUMA.
- DUDE, POPS!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
THAT'S TOTALLY SHOCHU WINE, HUH?
- JUST WATER.
- YOU'RE SUCH A LIAR!
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO DRINK THAT STUFF
UNTIL YOU'RE
ALL HEALED UP, REMEMBER?
- I TOLD YOU, BOY.
IT'S WATER.
- OH, NO IT AIN'T!
- THAT THERE'S
THE BEST MEDICINE.
SANADA YUKIMURA, WAS IT?
THE OLD TIGER OF KAI
PUT YOU THROUGH A BIT OF FUSS
COMING ALL THIS WAY TO SEE ME.
SHIMAZU YOSHIHIRO OF SATSUMA,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
- BUT HOW?!
LORD SHIMAZU, I THOUGHT
YOU HAD PERISHED.
HOW GOOD IT IS
TO FIND YOU ALIVE!
- ( door opens )
- Takenaka:
HAVE YOU AN ANSWER YET?
WE'VE BEEN MORE THAN PATIENT.
- Katakura:
I GIVE NO ANSWER
UNTIL I HAVE SEEN
LORD MASAMUNE'S HEAD.
BRING TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI TO ME.
OR ME TO HIM.
FOR IF HE HAS DEFEATED MILORD,
I DEMAND THE RIGHT TO FACE HIM
IN SINGLE COMBAT.
- THE REALITY OF YOUR SITUATION
CONTINUES TO ELUDE YOU.
YOU OWE THIS CLAN A GREAT DEAL,
MY DEAR KATAKURA.
YOU THWARTED US AT KAWANAKAJIMA,
SETTING BACK OUR UNIFICATION
OF THE COUNTRY.
AND BY EXTENSION,
OUR GRAND CONQUEST OF THE GLOBE.
AS OUR CAPTIVE, YOU'RE
NOW OBLIGED TO HELP US.
YOU WILL HOLD A POSITION
OF HONOR IN A FIGHTING FORCE
THAT WILL SOMEDAY
RULE THE WORLD.
ANY TRUE WARRIOR WOULD KILL
FOR SUCH AN OPPORTUNITY.
- ANY WORLD LORDED OVER
BY YOU PEOPLE
DOESN'T INTEREST ME.
- WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL SING
A DIFFERENT TUNE WHEN WE HAVE
THIS COUNTRY UNDER OUR THUMB.
THERE WILL BE NO MASTERS
LEFT TO SERVE,
SAVE LORD HIDEYOSHI.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU
AT ALL, TAKENAKA.
- I IMAGINE NOT.
- WHY DO YOU WASTE
YOUR TIME WITH THIS?
YOU'RE NOT SOME FLUNKY
WITH NO BRAIN IN HIS HEAD.
BUT HERE YOU ARE.
WITH YOUR HONEYED WORDS
AND YOUR STALE PROMISES.
TRYING TO RECRUIT
THE LAST MAN ON EARTH
WHO WOULD EVER
STOOP SO LOW--
- ( grunts )
- YOU FORGET YOURSELF,
MY DEAR KATAKURA.
UNDERSTAND THAT I AM
NOT ASKING YOU TO JOIN US.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
- HAVEN'T I?
WHY SUCH A DAMNABLE HURRY?
- YOU WILL COME TO ADMIRE
LORD HIDEYOSHI, AS DID I.
YOU'LL KNEEL
IN THE PRESENCE
OF SUCH OVERWHELMING STRENGTH.
- Date: HE DISGUISED
HIS SOLDIERS AS YOURS
IN THE HOPES OF PISSING ME OFF.
REAL MATURE, TOYOTOMI.
WHAT IS HE, FIVE?
- Takeda: THAT SAID, HE
SEEMED TO HAVE YOU FOOLED.
AT LEAST MOMENTARILY.
WAS IT THE VOICE
OF YOUR RIGHT EYE, PERHAPS?
SUGGESTING CAUTION AS YOU WENT
TO FREE HIS BLADE?
THIS IS LIKELY
HIS OPENING GAMBIT.
TOYOTOMI'S NEXT MOVE WILL BE
DECIDED IN LARGE PART
BY HOW YOU AND I
GO FORWARD FROM HERE.
- HE WENT TO A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO TRY AND LOCK US
AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
- I DOUBT THEY THOUGHT
THEIR RUSE WOULD RESULT
IN BOTH OF OUR DEATHS.
THAT LEAVES FAR TOO MUCH
TO CHANCE.
IT COULD BE THEY WANT US
TO ONCE AGAIN JOIN FORCES
IN PURSUIT OF A SHARED FOE.
- AND THAT HELPS THEM, HOW?
- TOYOTOMI WOULD RATHER
FACE BOTH OF US AT ONCE.
HE BOASTS AN OVERWHELMINGLY
POWERFUL FORCE.
INSTEAD OF CHASING
INDIVIDUAL ARMIES,
I'M SURE HE'D PREFER
TO DESTROY US EN MASSE.
HE MAY BE ANGLING
FOR A SCENARIO
REMINISCENT OF WHEN WE
ENCIRCLED ODA.
JUST TO GET US ALL
IN ONE PLACE.
- HE SITS ON HIS ASS
AND WE COME RUNNING, HUH?
KILL EVERYONE, MOP UP,
TAKE THE COUNTRY FOR HIMSELF.
HELL, HE MAKES IT SOUND SO EASY.
- I'M TEMPTED TO GIVE HIM
WHAT HE WANTS
AND FORM AN ALLIANCE WITH YOU.
BUT ON OUR TERMS.
JUST BECAUSE WE TEAM UP
AGAINST HIM,
DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE OBLIGATED
TO MARCH ON HIM
AT THE SAME TIME.
WELL, ONE-EYED DRAGON?
DOES CONQUERING ODAWARA
INTEREST YOU?
THE DATE CLAIM ODAWARA,
AND WE TAKE UTSUNOMIYA.
UESUGI PLAYS HIS PART
AS I'M SURE HE SHALL.
WITH ECHIGO AND OSHU
AT OUR BACKS,
WE CAN DO THIS WITH LITTLE RISK
AND FORM A DEFENSIBLE BLOC
ACROSS THE EAST.
- SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD, OLD MAN.
I BET YOU IT WOULD EVEN WORK.
BUT YOU ALREADY KNOW
WHAT MY ANSWER IS.
WE'RE MOUNTED UP AND READY
TO BUST OUR WAY INTO OSAKA.
TOYOTOMI'S GOT SOMETHING.
SOMETHING HE'S GOING TO REGRET
TAKING FROM ME.
WE HAVE A LITTLE SCORE
TO SETTLE, HE AND I.
- WERE HE HERE TO GIVE
HIS OPINION,
YOUR LIEUTENANT KATAKURA
MIGHT ADVISE YOU
TO ERR ON THE SIDE OF CAUTION.
- YEAH, TOO BAD FOR YOU
HE'S NOT AROUND TO TELL ME.
THAT'S WHY I NEED HIM BACK.
HEY, WHAT'S YOUR BOY
YUKIMURA UP TO?
- I SENT HIM TO KYUSHU.
IN HOPES THAT HE CAN
FORM AN ALLIANCE
WITH THE MEN DEFENDING SATSUMA.
- YOU AND YOUR ALLIANCES.
SO YOU PLAN TO HIT
TOYOTOMI FROM THE WEST, TOO?
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT I'LL HAVE TAKEN HIM OUT
BEFORE THE KID
EVEN GETS A CRACK AT IT.
- JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU THINK THAT DEFEATING HIM
IS GOING TO BE EASY?
YOUR WILLPOWER AND PRIDE
ONLY COUNT FOR SO MUCH.
THIS IS NOT A FOE YOU CAN TAME
BY CHARGING HEADLONG
INTO ITS DEN
WITH BUT A SINGLE BATTALION
OF MEN AT YOUR BACK.
- I'M NOT GOING THERE TO DIE.
OF COURSE, I GUESS
THAT AIN'T UP TO JUST ME.
- ANY DRAGON THAT DOESN'T
TAKE TO THE SKY
MAY AS WELL BE DEAD
TO BEGIN WITH, RIGHT?
- SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I CAN'T LET HIM HAVE IT.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
WHEN I FIRST LAID EYE
ON THAT OVERGROWN BASTARD.
HE'S NOT TAKING MY COUNTRY,
NOT ON MY WATCH.
TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI...
YEAH, HE'S GOT A WICKED RIGHT.
BUT SOMETHING'S OFF
ABOUT THAT GUY.
WHAT HE HAS AT HIS DISPOSAL
ISN'T STRENGTH.
I'LL NEVER RECOGNIZE IT
AS STRENGTH.
I'LL DIE FIRST.
TAKEDA.
IF I DON'T COME BACK, TELL HIM--
LISTEN TO ME, JEEZ.
TELL THE CUB I WISH
I COULD HAVE SCHOOLED HIM,
ONE MORE TIME.
- Takenaka:
DATE SEEMS AS DETERMINED AS EVER
TO MARCH ON OSAKA
WITH THAT RAGTAG BUNCH OF HIS.
AND THIS IS AFTER HIS LOSSES
AT SURIAGEHARA.
I'VE NEVER KNOWN A COMMANDER
WHO WAS SO DIFFICULT TO READ.
- DO YOU THINK THE TIGER OF KAI
PROPOSED JOINING THEIR FORCES
AGAINST US?
- OH, UNDOUBTEDLY.
LORD SHINGEN SHOULD BE
WELL-ACQUAINTED
WITH DATE'S IMPETUOUS NATURE.
HE PROBABLY SPOKE
OF ALLIANCES, ANYWAY.
IT WOULD PROVE MUCH
TO TAKEDA'S FAVOR
IF DATE DID ACQUIESCE.
AS THINGS CURRENTLY STAND,
TAKEDA IS BOUND TO KAI.
THUS HE'D TRY TO SELL
DEAR MASAMUNE ON TAKING ODAWARA.
WE'VE SHORED UP THE CASTLE'S
DEFENSES CONSIDERABLY.
BUT MAYBE HE THINKS
DATE COULD PULL IT OFF
IF HE GAVE IT HIS ALL.
THEY ALL ATTACKED ODA AT ONCE.
I DOUBT THEY'LL REPEAT
THAT SAME STRATEGY AGAINST US.
TAKEDA WAS HOPING TO ESTABLISH
A LINE OF DEFENSE
FROM ECHIGO TO ODAWARA.
THEY COULD THEN WAIT
IN RELATIVE SAFETY
FOR MORE TROOPS
TO COME UP FROM KYUSHU.
PITY IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE
WANTED THEM TO DO.
GENERALLY, MILORD,
OUR FORTE IS NOT IN DEFEATING
INDIVIDUAL ARMIES.
BUT IN CRUSHING
MANY FOES AT ONCE.
THEY LIKELY GATHERED
AS MUCH AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
I THOUGHT IF WE WERE
TRANSPARENT WITH OUR INTENTIONS
WE COULD TWIST THIS KNOWLEDGE
OF OUR STRENGTHS
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
GOAD THEM INTO TAKING
THE BAIT, AS IT WERE.
AFTER ALL, OUR NEW WEAPON
IS SLATED TO ARRIVE
JUST AS THEY WOULD HAVE
FINISHED GETTING INTO POSITION.
BETWEEN YOUR STRENGTH,
AND THE NEW ADDITION
TO OUR ARSENAL,
IT WOULDN'T MATTER
WHETHER THEY DREW
A DEFENSIVE LINE DOWN
THE MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY
OR ATTACKED US FROM THE WEST.
IN EITHER EVENT, OUR STRATEGY
AND BATTLE FORMATION
WOULD HAVE BEEN
FAIRLY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
BUT NOW, THE DATE CLAN
HAS SPOILED ALL MY FUN.
IT MAKES ME WANT
TO DESTROY THEM.
IT MATTERS NOT.
OUR COURSE OF ACTION IS SET.
- BRILLIANT WORK, HANBEI.
- SOON YOU'LL HAVE
THE COUNTRY SITTING
IN THE PALM OF YOUR HAND.
- Servant:
BEG PARDON.
PLEASE FORGIVE
THE INTERRUPTION, BUT--
- OUT WITH IT ALREADY.
- THERE'S A MAN
CLAIMING TO BE THE HEAD
OF THE MAEDA CLAN AT THE GATES.
HE REQUESTS AN AUDIENCE
WITH LORD HIDEYOSHI.
- ( theme music plays )
- Matsunaga:
THIS IS A TURBULENT TIME
FOR THE COUNTRY.
HANG NOT YOUR HOPES
ON TOMORROW.
TRULY THERE IS NO GUARANTEE
ALL YOU BRAVE HEROES
WILL YET LIVE TO SEE IT.
YOU'RE QUITE
THE CURIOUS SPECIMEN.