- Date: YOU KNOW, SOMEONE'S
BOUND TO WANT TO THROW
A NEW PARTY SOON ENOUGH.
- YES, MY LORD.
IT CAN'T BE LONG
UNTIL WE LIVE
IN A TIME OF WAR AGAIN.
WE MUST COMPLETE THE REBUILDING
OF OSHU BEFORE THEN.
- YEAH, LOOKS LIKE WE
WON'T HAVE ANY TIME TO BE BORED.
AIN'T NO QUESTION YOU-KNOW-WHO'S
ALL FIRED UP RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- SANADA YUKIMURA,
YOU DEFEATED HIM HANDEDLY
THE LAST TIME YOU FOUGHT.
BUT I THINK IT
ONLY STRENGTHENED HIS RESOLVE.
- PROMISED HIM A REMATCH,
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S GOING
TO HOLD ME TO IT.
- THE BOY'S DEFINITELY A PRODUCT
OF TAKEDA'S TRAINING.
AFTER THE BATTLE OF NAGASHINO,
WHEN WE STAYED WITH
THE TIGER OF KAI FOR AWHILE,
I HAD THE DISTINCT PLEASURE
OF SPARRING
WITH HIS YOUNG PROTEGE
ONCE OR TWICE MYSELF.
- "TAKEDA'S TRAINING," HUH?
TAKEDA'S FUN HOUSE
IS A LOT MORE LIKE IT.
I GOT TO ADMIT THOUGH,
MY FAVORITE PART
OF THAT WHOLE DAY--
YOU IN THAT MASK.
THAT WAS CLASSIC.
YEAH, I WOULD HAVE NEVER GUESSED
YOU LIKED TO PLAY DRESS-UP.
- NO, IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT!
I-- THEY MADE ME WEAR IT.
- CALM DOWN,
EVEN THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
GOT SWEPT UP
IN OLD MAN TAKEDA'S ENTHUSIASM.
- Takeda:
YOU BUFFOON!
STARTING NOW,
YOUR TRAINING IS BEGUN.
CRYING CHILDREN
WILL DRY THEIR EYES,
SLEEPING BABIES SHALL AWAKEN
AND TAKE TO THE SKIES!
FOR IT IS TIME
FOR THAT MOST EPIC OF EVENTS--
THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA!
- TRULY?!
HOW LONG HAVE I
DREAMED OF THIS DAY?
THANK YOU
FOR THIS WONDEROUS BOON
YOU HAVE GRANTED ME!
- JEEZ, DON'T BURST
A BLOOD VESSEL, KID.
- A LORD IS BESET
WITH MANY A FOE,
HOW THEY DOG HIS EVERY STEP.
BUT THE TRUE WARRIOR
SHALL OVERCOME.
YUKIMURA, SHOW YOUR LORD
THE FULL MEASURE
OF YOUR MANLY SOUL.
- I WILL!  FOR I, YUKIMURA,
SHALL FULFILL
MY MASTER'S EXPECTATIONS!
AND SUNDER EVERY OBSTACLE!
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- BUT LET US NOT FORGET
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
YOU, TOO, SHALL TAKE PART
IN THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA!
- ONLY IF YOU CHANGE
THE NAME FIRST.
- Takeda: EXCELLENT, I'LL AWAIT
YOU BOTH AT THE TRAINING HALL.
MAY THE BETTER MAN WIN.
UP, UP, AND AWAY!
- YES, YOUR LORDSHIP.
I HEAR AND OBEY.
AT LONG LAST, I AM TAKING PART
IN THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA!
MERE WORDS CANNOT CONVEY MY JOY!
- MIND TELLING ME WHAT THE HELL
THIS MAN PARTY'S ALL ABOUT?
- OH, YEAH.
LORD TAKEDA'S GIVEN YOU LEAVE
TO PARTICIPATE AS WELL.
WHAT A STROKE OF GOOD LUCK.
- WHAT'S SO LUCKY ABOUT IT?
- THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA,
ALSO KNOWN AS
THE TAKEDA CONTEST OF MEN.
SINCE ANCIENT TIMES,
THOSE CHOSEN TO RULE
THE LAND OF KAI HAVE USED IT
AS A CHANCE TO TEST THEIR METTLE
AND BECOME TRUE WARRIORS.
ALMOST NOBODY OVERCOMES
ALL OF THE
GRUELING CHALLENGES WITHIN.
LEGEND HAS IT, THAT THE CONTEST
DEMANDS THE IMPOSSIBLE
OF THOSE WHO DARE TO ENTER IT.
- Date: THAT SO?
- Sanada:
THOSE WHO'VE EMERGED
FROM THE TRAINING GROUNDS
VICTORIOUS,
HAVE ALL GONE ON TO CARVE OUT
A LASTING NAME FOR THEMSELVES
IN KAI'S HISTORY.
MY LORD IS ONE
OF THESE LEGENDARY FEW.
THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA
IS A RARE OPPORTUNITY
FOR A WARRIOR OF KAI
TO PROVE HIMSELF TO THE WORLD!
AND NOW IT'S MY TURN
TO CLIMB THESE STAIRS!
I, SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA,
NEVER DARED HOPE
FOR SUCH A CHANCE.
- HUH, SO IN OTHER WORDS--
TO ALL YOU TAKEDA GUYS,
THIS HERE IS THE PARTY
OF A LIFETIME.
- Sarutobi:
WELL MET, WARRIORS.
ENTER MY DOMAIN.
EVEN WITH THE MASK,
IT'S OBVIOUSLY ME.
HOW DID I GET ROPED INTO THIS?
- Sanada:
FAMILIAR MOUTH AND CHIN,
GIANT THROWING STAR,
ARTFULLY CAMOUFLAGED
NINJA ATTIRE
THAT ALLOWS ONE TO BLEND
INTO THE WOODS AROUND HIM.
WHO ARE YOU?
- VERY FUNNY.  THAT WAS A JOKE,
RIGHT, MASTER SANADA?
NO, NOT KIDDING.
I AM KNOWN AS TENKO MASK,
THE HEAVENLY THOUSAND-YEAR FOX
OF LEGEND!
- YEAH, CAN IT, STARFOX.
YOU'RE THAT NINJA--
- I'VE NEVER MET EITHER OF YOU!
BUT YOU'LL KNOW ME SOON ENOUGH,
AS I PUT YOUR FIGHTING SOULS
TO THE ULTIMATE TEST!
- IT'S JUST AS I'D HOPED.
BEHOLD, MASTER TENKO,
THE MIGHT OF OUR ONSLAUGHT.
- THINK I'M GOING
TO CALL IT A DAY.
I'M ALL MAN-STRAVAGANZA'D OUT.
- HOLD ON, IS THERE BAD BLOOD
BETWEEN YOU AND TENKO MASK?
- SON OF A-- YOU'RE NOT
EVEN KIDDING, ARE YOU?
- PLEASE, ONE-EYED DRAGON,
LEAVE HIM BE.
MASTER SANADA IS VERY TRUSTING.
DON'T GO SPOILING THE FUN.
- NO WAY, TENKO MASK
HAS HEARD OF ME?!
- WHAT? UH, YES, I HAVE!
BECAUSE I AM VERY GOOD FRIENDS
WITH SARUTOBI SASUKE.
- WHOA, I HAD NO IDEA.
WELL ANY FRIEND OF SASUKE'S
IS A FRIEND OF MINE.
- Date:
HEY, SARUTO--
TENKO MASK, MY BAD.
THIS GUY OUT HERE
WITH THE SCHNOZZ A BUDDY
OF YOURS OR SOMETHING?
- HUH?  ARE YOU BLIND?
THAT'S YOUR SECOND-IN-COMMA--
I MEAN, YES!
HE'S WITH ME!
- ANOTHER OPPONENT TO TEST US.
A BLAZING RED TENGU MASK,
AND ODDLY FAMILIAR BLADES
ON YOUR RIGHT HIP,
SUGGESTING A LEFT-HANDED
SWORDSMEN.
- HEY, KOJURO.
THE HELL ARE YOU UP TO?
- LORD MASAMUNE, I DIDN'T WANT
YOU TO SEE ME LIKE THIS.
- YOU AND ME BOTH.
CARE TO EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE
LOOKING LIKE A DAMN FOOL?
- WE OWE TAKEDA A GREAT DEBT
FOR HIS RECENT KINDNESS.
ON A PERHAPS NOT UNRELATED NOTE,
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN
PRACTICING MY SWORDPLAY
WITH AN EXCESS OF FERVOR
AND DESTROYED ONE
OF THE LANTERNS IN HIS GARDEN.
WHEN HE BROUGHT ME THIS MASK,
I COULDN'T SAY NO.
WELL, COULD I?  PLEASE, MY LORD,
ADD NOT TO MY SHAME!
- FINE, WHATEVER.
- IF I HAD TO WAGER A GUESS,
I'D SAY YOU AND LORD MASAMUNE
HAVE MET BEFORE.
- FEAR THE VISAGE OF TEN--
TEN... GU... MASK, YEAH.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY
YOUR NAME WAS, AGAIN?
YOU KNOW, IT WOULDN'T KILL YOU
TO ANNOUNCE YOURSELF
WITH A LITTLE MORE VERVE.
BELIEVE ME, WHOEVER YOU ARE,
IF YOU CAN'T EVEN BE BOTHERED
TO ANNOUNCE YOURSELF
PROPERLY ON THE BATTLEFIELD,
WHO'S GOING TO WANT TO CROSS
SWORDS WITH YOU?
- AWKWARD, AND KATAKURA
GETS TALKED DOWN TO
BY AN OBLIVIOUS SANADA.
- MANY THANKS
FOR THE SAGE ADVICE.
IF IT'S VIGOR YOU WANT,
YOU'LL HAVE IT.
MY NAME IS TENGU MASK,
THE ONE AND ONLY!
SANADA YUKIMURA,
I SHALL BE YOUR UNDOING.
- I HEAR YOU LOUD AND CLEAR.
I DID NOT MEAN TO OFFEND,
I WOULD BE HONORED TO FIGHT!
- ( sighs )
- Takeda: BEGIN!
- LOOK AT YOU!
IT SEEMS YOUR INJURY
FROM NAGASHINO
HEALED UP QUITE NICELY.
- LISTEN, THE KID
MADE IT SOUND LIKE
THIS WAS GOING TO BE
SOME EPIC THROWDOWN,
SO WHAT'S UP
WITH ALL THIS BULLSH--
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT IT'LL TAKE
TOO LONG TO EXPLAIN.
HE'S SO EXCITED,
SO JUST PLAY ALONG, 'KAY?
- RAGING FLAMES!
YOUR FIGHTING STYLE
IS SIMILAR TO LORD MASAMUNE'S.
YOU ARE NO ORDINARY WARRIOR.
- I'VE BEEN WANTING TO TEST
YOUR METTLE WITH MY OWN BLADE
FOR A LONG TIME NOW
TO SEE IF YOU'RE A WORTHY RIVAL
FOR THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
SO COME, SANADA.
PROVE YOUR MIGHT TO TENGU MASK.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
- IT'D BE MY PLEASURE.
- LOOK AT KOJURO,
HE'S HAVING A BALL.
- Sarutobi:
TIME TO CHANGE THINGS UP A BIT.
EVEN ONE AS JADED AS YOU
WILL GET A KICK OUT OF THIS.
- Date:
WHAT THE-- ?
- MY PERFECT SPEAR OF CONQUEST!
SANADA YUKIMURA IS HERE... YEAH?
- LOOKS JUST LIKE HIM.
- AH, YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
- SERIOUSLY, NINJA.
THAT'S TOP-NOTCH WORK.
YOU'RE HIS SPITTING IMAGE.
- REALLY?!
WHOA!  TIME OUT!
- YOU DID SO WELL,
I JUST WANT TO KICK YOUR ASS.
- DATE, YOU KNOW THAT I'M
NOT REALLY MASTER SANADA, RIGHT?
- CRAZY STORM!
MAGNUM STEP!
PHANTOM DIVE!
- SARUTOBI COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
A WORSE MAN TO IMPERSONATE
IN FRONT OF MY LORD.
- Sanada:
TENGU MASK!
YOU BETTER NOT LET DOWN
YOUR GUARD!
- ( whistles )
LOOKING GOOD THERE, HANDSOME.
- CAN THE SWEET TALK,
ONE-EYED DRAGON.
DON'T HOLD BACK NOW-- I WON'T.
BIG BOSS OF OSHU, DATE MASAMUNE.
OH, YEAH.
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
- NOW WE'RE TALKING.
- Katakura: YOU'RE NOT READY
TO FACE LORD MASAMUNE
IN BATTLE, BOY.
- COME ON, WHAT MAKES
YOU THINK THIS IS OVER?
- HE'S THROWING A PUNCH?!
- YOU'RE AS SKILLED
AT HAND-TO-HAND COMBAT
AS YOU ARE WITH A BLADE.
THERE'S NO DENYING IT,
YOU BESTED ME.
STRIKING OUT AT ME WITH
YOUR INJURED HAND
WAS BRAVE... AND FOOLISH.
- I ONLY DID IT BECAUSE
I WANTED TO PASS THIS TEST.
- I CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I FOUGHT SOMEONE UNARMED.
NOT SINCE LORD MASAMUNE HIMSELF
WAS A CHILD, MOST LIKELY.
YOU ARE NOT THE WISEST WARRIOR
I'VE EVER MET,
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBTING
YOUR DETERMINATION.
TAKE IT, YOU DO THEM JUSTICE.
- I'M IN YOUR DEBT, STRANGER.
- ( glass breaking )
- Sanada:
DO MY EYES DECEIVE ME?
IT'S A MOB OF MASAMUNES!
BUT WHICH ONE IS THE REAL ONE?
- THE ONE IN THE MIDDLE
THAT THEY'RE ALL GANGING UP ON.
DAMN IT, SARUTOBI.
YOU'RE TAKING THINGS TOO FAR.
- Masamune:
16-TO-1 AIN'T NO KIND OF ODDS.
OKAY, YOU FAKE BASTARDS,
I'M THROUGH PLAYING AROUND.
GUESS I'LL TAKE THE WHOLE LOT
OF YOU OUT AT ONCE.
- Sanada:
HE'S DRAWN HIS SIX SWORDS!
THAT TENKO MASK,
HE MIGHT BE TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
- Katakura:
LORD MASAMUNE!
I, TENGU MASK, WILL GUARD
YOUR BACK UNTIL MY DYING BREATH!
- HOLD UP, ARE YOU KOJURO NOW?
- MASAMUNE'S RIGHT, WHY WOULD
TENGU MASK TAKE HIS SIDE?
- SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO DROP OUT OF CHARACTER.
- THEN WHY'D YOU STILL CALL
YOURSELF TENGU MASK?
- HUH, DID I REALLY?
WAIT, WHY AM I EVEN WORRYING
ABOUT THIS?!
ALL THAT MATTERS IS DEFENDING
MY LORD FROM HIMSELF.
- WELL THEN, GUESS
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
THAT SAID, THE REAL CHALLENGE
IS STILL TO COME.
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- Sarutobi:
ALL DOUBLES, RETURN TO SHADOW.
- Date: I GET IT, THIS IS
ALL STARTING TO MAKE SENSE.
- LORD MASAMUNE?
- LOOKS LIKE OLD MAN TAKEDA
PUNKED US PRETTY GOOD.
BUT I'M HAVING A GOOD TIME,
YOU KNOW, SO WHAT THE HELL.
WHY THE LONG FACE, SANADA?
ON YOUR FEET.
IT'S TIME TO FACE
OUR NEXT CHALLENGE.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO GO ON
BY YOURSELF.
THE ONLY REASON I'M IN ONE PIECE
IS BECAUSE TENGU MASK
TOOK PITY ON ME.
MY LORD EXPECTED
GREAT THINGS OF ME HERE,
AND I'VE ALREADY LET HIM DOWN.
- Takeda:
YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- Takeda: CRUSHING YOUR FOE
IS NOT THE ONLY MARK OF VICTORY
IN THE MAN-STRAVAGANZA.
TENGU MASK LAUDED YOU
FOR YOUR DETERMINATION
MERE MOMENTS AGO, DID HE NOT?
- I SUPPOSE SO.
- INDEED, AND WITH THAT HONOR
YOU WIN THE RIGHT
TO ATTEMPT THE FINAL TRIAL
OF THE TAKEDA MAN-STRAVAGANZA!
BEYOND THIS DOOR LIES
THE CHAMBER OF MEN,
A DOMAIN THAT ONLY
THE FIERCEST WARRIORS
ARE PERMITTED TO ENTER.
WITHIN YOU SHALL ENCOUNTER
YOUR FINAL FOE.
NOW, GO! TAKE YOUR PLACE
AMONG THE LEGENDS OF KAI!
- YES, LORD.
I WILL DO AS YOU COMMAND.
AND SO I GO
TO THE CHAMBER OF MEN.
- CRIMINY, TAKEDA'S GOT
AN OVER THE TOP NAME
FOR EVERYTHING, DOESN'T HE?
- MY LORD, YOU DON'T SUPPOSE
THE TIGER OF KAI HIMSELF IS--
- YEAH, BUT HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIND OUT FOR SURE
UNLESS I PLAY ALONG
TO THE BITTER DAMN END.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS, MY LORD?
- I DON'T MIND
DOING HIM A SOLID.
HE'S BEEN GOOD TO US.
THOUGH THE DUDE BEHIND
DOOR NUMBER TWO
IS A TOUGHER HOMBRE THAN YOU
WANT TO GO MESSING WITH.
- AT LEAST TRY TO BE CAREFUL.
- SURE.
KOJURO--
- SIR?
- I KNOW I GAVE YOU CRAP FOR IT,
BUT YOU ROCKED THAT MASK.
- I AM HONORED BY YOUR PRAISE.
- Date:
COME ON, SANADA.  CHOP, CHOP.
- YES, RIGHT AWAY!
MAY I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- YOU JUST DID.
- WELL, IT'S ABOUT TENGU MASK.
HE LOOKS A LOT LIKE KATAKURA,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- Takeda:
I HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
I AM NONE OTHER THAN THE MASTER
OF THIS TRAINING HALL,
THE STOKER OF FLAMES WHO
BREATHES LIFE INTO THE INFERNO,
HYOTTOKO MASK!
- WHAT A FINE FIGURE HE STRIKES!
VIGOR RADIATES FROM EVERY FIBER
OF HIS BEING.
HE STANDS AS THOUGH
HEWN FROM ROCK,
BUT I CAN TELL HE MOVES
WITH THE GRACE OF A TIGER.
A TIGER, YES!
IT'S AS THOUGH I'M LOOKING AT--
- IN BATTLE I AM AS RELENTLESS
AS THE DEVOURING FLAMES
TO WHICH I TEND,
CAN YOU TAKE THE HEAT?
- Date: THERE BETTER BE
MORE TO YOU THAN HOT AIR
'CAUSE THIS DRAGON'S
BEEN SHARPENING HIS CLAWS.
- DEFEAT ME OR MEET A FIERY END
WITHIN THIS CAVERN.
SUCCEED OR PERISH,
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
- PERISHING ABLAZE
WOULD SUIT ME WELL.
BUT NOT WHILE I STILL HAVE
SO MUCH TO PROVE
AND A NAME TO MAKE FOR MYSELF.
I WILL DEFEAT YOU,
HYOTTOKO MASK,
AND COMPLETE
THE MAN-STRAVAGANZA!
- AGE BEFORE BEAUTY, KID.
- LORD MASAMUNE,
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
THE AURA HE EXUDES
IS THAT OF NO ORDINARY MAN.
I GET THE FEELING HE'S
AS GREAT A WARRIOR AS MY LORD.
- WOW, WHAT A COINCIDENCE, HUH?
- SO YOU ARE TO BE THE KINDLING,
ONE-EYED DRAGON OF OSHU.
- TOUGH TALK, SPARKY.
LET'S DANCE.
YOU BETTER GIVE ME
ONE HELL OF A FIGHT.
- YOUR BRAVADO PLEASES ME.
STRIKE WHEN YOU ARE READY.
- BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE,
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
- LORD MASAMUNE,
THAT HYOTTOKO MASK--
HE HAS THE STRENGTH OF 20 MEN.
AND THE SPEED WITH WHICH HE
WIELDS THAT MIGHTY AXE OF HIS,
IT REMINDS ME OF SOMEONE,
BUT WHO?
THINK, YUKIMURA, THINK!
- WELL MET, ONE-EYED DRAGON.
THE TALES REGARDING
YOUR SWORDPLAY ALL RING TRUE.
THOUGH YOU'VE LANDED NARY A HIT,
YOUR SPEED AND TECHNIQUE
HAVE CUT ME TO THE QUICK.
THERE IS MORE TO YOU
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
- FEELING'S MUTUAL,
YOU'RE AS HEAVY AS A MOUNTAIN
BUT YOU'VE GOT THE SPEED
OF A TYPHOON.
AND YOU DEFINITELY
BRING THE HURT
WITH THAT BLAZING AXEWORK.
YOU MAY BE DRESSED ALL IN RED,
BUT YOU AIN'T FLASHY.
YOU'RE AS COOL AS A CUCUMBER.
FOR AN OLD GUY,
YOU'RE A REAL BADASS.
- Sanada: LORD MASAMUNE HAS
DRAWN ALL OF HIS SWORDS AGAIN.
- YOU HAVE SPLIT MY MASK
ASUNDER, ONE-EYED DRAGON.
I ADMIT MY DEFEAT.
- NO, CAN IT BE?!
HYOTTOKO MASK'S TRUE FACE IS--
IS THAT OF MY LORD.
MY LORD TAKEDA'S...
LONG-LOST TWIN!
- Takeda:
NO, YOU BUFFOON!
- THAT LEGENDARY PUNCH,
IT WAS JUST LIKE HIS.
- Takeda:
YOU ARE A DOLT, YUKIMURA!
- Sanada:
HE KNOWS MY NAME!
THIS FEELING-- AS THOUGH EVERY
BONE IN MY BODY WERE BROKEN,
THAT BOULDER-LIKE FIST
BORING DEEP INTO MY FACE
AND THEN LAUNCHING ME
HEAVENWARD WITH SUCH EASE.
THE IDENTITY OF HYOTTOKO MASK
IS CLEAR NOW-- OF COURSE!
THERE IS NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
HE IS MY--
- YOU FINALLY FIGURED IT OUT,
MY YOUNG CUB.
- Sanada:
MY LORDSHIP!
- WELL THAT TOOK HIM
LONG ENOUGH.
BETTER LATE THAN NEVER.
OKAY THEN, I'M OUT.
- LORD MASAMUNE?
- I BELIEVE YOU OWE ME A FIGHT.
- BUT I COULDN'T
POSSIBLY DO THAT.
FOR SOMEONE
AS INEXPERIENCED AS I
TO CROSS BLADES WITH YOU,
THE THOUGHT OF IT--
I WASN'T READY
FOR THE MAN-STRAVAGANZA.
- YUKIMURA.
- YES?
- YOU ARE...
AN UTTER BUFFOON!
YOU ARE A TAKEDA WARRIOR OF KAI.
YOUR OPPONENT
CRAVES SATISFACTION
AND YOU REFUSE TO FACE HIM,
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?!
- FORGIVE ME, MY LORD.
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT
IN ME FIGHTING
WHEN I KNOW THERE'S
NO POSSIBLE WAY I CAN WIN?
- Takeda: BECAUSE THE
ONE-EYED DRAGON BESTED ME.
IF YOU'RE WORTHY OF HIS RIVALRY,
HIS DEEDS ARE NOT BEYOND YOU.
- I WATCHED LORD DATE BATTLE YOU
WITH A FEROCITY I NEVER KNEW
HE POSSESSED.
BUT WHEN I LOOK WITHIN MYSELF,
I DO NOT SEE IT.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME
YOU GIVE UP, THEN?
YUKIMURA, IF YOU LACK THE HEART
TO ARISE AND TAKE UP ARMS
AGAINST ME,
HOW CAN I CALL YOU A MAN?
I CAN'T HELP BUT PITY
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON.
HE TOOK ON A SIMPERING COWARD
AS A RIVAL,
WHO WOULD ACCEPT SUCH A MATCH
BUT A COWARD HIMSELF?
THEY WILL MOCK HIM
FROM SEA TO SEA!
- THEY MAY CALL ME
WHAT THEY WILL,
A COWARD EVEN,
BUT NOT LORD MASAMUNE.
- YOUR FIERCEST RIVAL
IS NOTHING LESS
THAN YOUR GREATEST FRIEND.
ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO SLINK
AWAY HAVING STAINED HIS HONOR?
ARE YOU?!
- I'M NOT SLINKING AWAY.
LORD DATE AND I
ARE MEN!
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- NEVER FORGET
WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
THAT WAS A PUNCH
WORTHY OF THE MAN-STRAVAGANZA.
- WHY DON'T YOU DODGE MY BLOWS?
- THE WORTH OF A PUNCH
IS FOUND IN TAKING IT.
PERSEVERE, MY YOUNG CUB.
YOUR BLOOD AND SWEAT AND TEARS
ARE NEVER SHED IN VAIN,
YOU ARE
A FEARLESS WARRIOR OF KAI,
FOR THIS DAY,
YOU HAVE BECOME A MAN!
- YES, LORD TAKEDA, AND I HIM.
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- Date:
REMEMBER KID,
YOU AND ME STILL GOT
SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
DON'T GO LOSING
TO ANYONE UNTIL THEN.
- ALRIGHT, BUT YOU
HAD BETTER NOT LOSE EITHER.
LORD MASAMUNE,
TO HAVE FOUND A RIVAL
THE LIKES OF YOU
DURING MY LIFETIME,
I FEEL VERY LUCKY INDEED.
- HEY, HEY.
IF YOU GO POURING
YOUR HEART OUT TO ME NOW,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE
ANYTHING LEFT TO SAY
WHEN I BEAT YOU.
- TOO BAD.
GUESS YOU'LL NEVER HEAR IT
'CAUSE I'M GOING TO WIN.
- ATTA BOY.
- YEAH, I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN YOU
WEREN'T THE HAND-SHAKING TYPE.
- PLUS WE'VE ADDED QUITE A
SPIRITED BUNCH TO OUR ROSTER.
THEY SEEM PRETTY IMPATIENT
TO RAISE A WAR CRY.
- EXCELLENT, WE'LL HAVE
TO LET THEM SEE THE COUNTRY
UNDER THE DRAGON'S RULE.
- SIR.
- AND ALONG THE WAY, I'LL BE
ENTRUSTING MY BACK TO YOU.
AS ALWAYS, KOJURO.
YOU READY FOR IT?
- YOU NEED NOT EVEN ASK.
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR.
ARE YOU BOYS READY?
- YOUR THOUGHTS WERE
UPON HIM AGAIN,
WEREN'T THEY, YUKIMURA?
- THEY WERE, I FELT AS THOUGH
I JUST HEARD HIS VOICE.
- THAT FIRE IN YOUR VEINS
BURNS WITHIN HIS AS WELL.
AN OATH BETWEEN RIVALS,
BETWEEN FRIENDS,
CAN UNITE TWO PEOPLE
WHETHER NEAR OR FAR.
- YES, I FEEL IT, YOUR LORDSHIP.
PLAIN AS DAY.
OUR FATES ARE ONE,
NOW AND FOREVER.
- YES, YOUR MEETING HIM
WAS DESTINY.
- IT'S ALL COMNIG DOWN TO ONE
LAST RUMBLE, SANADA YUKIMURA.
AND YOU AND ME ARE THE ONLY ONES
GETTING INVITES!
- LORD MASAMUNE, WE SWORE AN
OATH TO ONE ANOTHER AS EQUALS.
AND I SWEAR I WILL UPHOLD IT!
- WE'LL MEET AGAIN.
- SOMEWHERE, SOME DAY.
- ( both ) IN THE BATTLE THAT
DECIDES THE FATE OF THE WORLD!
- ( theme music plays )