- ( thunder rumbling )
- Ichi: I HEAR IT.
I FEEL IT.
THE SORROW,
THE PAIN,
THE HATRED, THE CURSES.
THESE ARE THE GIFTS
MY BROTHER HAS GIVEN,
AND THEY ARE ALL MY FAULT.
- Azai: ICHI.
- MY LORD NAGAMASA, HOW...
- ICHI, HOW LONG WILL
YOU SIT THERE, UNMOVING?
- MY LOVING HUSBAND,
YOU WOULD MOCK ME
AS MY BROTHER DOES?
- I AM ASKING WHY
YOU DO NOT FOLLOW
WHAT IS IN YOUR HEART, ICHI.
- MY LORD, ALL I WANT IS TO
BE AT YOUR SIDE ONCE AGAIN.
- IF THAT IS WHAT WILL
ASSUAGE YOUR TROUBLED SOUL,
TAKE THE BLADES THE DEVIL
KING LEFT YOU, END YOUR LIFE.
TO CEASE TO THINK
IS THE TRUE EVIL.
WHY DO YOU STAY HERE,
WHEN YOU KNOW THE DEVIL
KING WILL BE SO CRUEL TO YOU?
IT IS BECAUSE THERE IS A FEAT
NO WARRIOR CAN ACCOMPLISH.
A FEAT WHICH YOU AND
ONLY YOU ARE CAPABLE OF.
OR AM I MISTAKEN?
LOOK STRAIGHT UPON THIS TASK.
DO NOT FLEE FROM IT.
HAVE FAITH THAT
HIS HUMANITY REMAINS,
FOR YOU ARE THE SOLE PERSON
LEFT WHO MIGHT HELP HIM FIND IT.
- MY LORD NAGAMASA!
STOP MY BROTHER.
I CAN DO THIS, I CAN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( urging horses )
- THIS PARTY IS INVITATION
ONLY, YUKIMURA,
SO YOU BETTER BE READY
TO KICK SOME SERIOUS ASS.
- MY HEART BURNS BRIGHT
WITH THE PASSION OF BATTLE.
I SHALL FACE WHATEVER AWAITS
AT HONNOJI WITH ALL MY MIGHT.
- OLD MAN TAKEDA,
DON'T KICK OFF JUST YET.
I'M PROTECTIN' THE LAND
WE'RE GONNA FIGHT OVER,
BUT THAT FUN COMES LATER.
- YOUR LORDSHIP,
I INTEND TO REALIZE THE PEACEFUL
WORLD TO WHICH YOU ASPIRE,
AND TO DO SO, I HAVE THROWN
IN MY LOT WITH LORD MASAMUNE.
EVEN WITHOUT YOU AT MY BACK,
I ASK THAT YOU WATCH OVER ME
AS I PUT THE DEVIL
KING TO THE BLADE.
- THE ENEMY IS AT HONNOJI.
LONG HAVE I AWAITED THIS MOMENT.
WITH EVERY BATTLE, MY LORD,
YOU HAVE COMPLETELY
DESTROYED YOUR FOE.
SO, I IMAGINE THERE IS MUCH
YOU HAVE YET TO KNOW OF THEM.
LIKE THE HATRED THOSE LEFT
BEHIND BEAR IN THEIR HEARTS.
PRECISELY BECAUSE YOU
ARE THE INVINCIBLE
AND MERCILESS DEVIL KING,
YOU WOULD BE OBLIVIOUS TO
THE REPRISAL FROM A FOE
DRIVEN BY RAGE AND
HIDDEN STRENGTH.
( laughs ) AM I CORRECT,
LORD NOBUNAGA?
HAVE YOU RETIRED FOR
THE DAY? OR ARE YOU MERELY
ENJOYING AN INTIMATE
MOMENT WITH YOUR KICHO?
PLEASE, MY LORD. DO INDULGE
TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT
YOUR TIME TOGETHER,
FOR THAT WILL BE YOUR CASKET.
- ( snoring )
- BIG BOSS.
- SO, UM...
- All: HMM.
- OKAY! NOW LISTEN UP, YOU...
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ON YOUR FEET, MEN,
PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
- ( all gasping )
- BOSS KATAKURA.
- WHAT ARE YOU ALL
STILL SITTING THERE FOR?
I GAVE YOU AN ORDER!
- YEAH. BUT, BOSS...
- THE BIG BOSS SAID THE
DATE ARMY WAS DISBANDED.
- Katakura: JUST COME WITH ME.
OH, COME ON, LIKE YOU WERE
NOT GONNA DO IT ANYWAYS?
- ( gasps ) OH.
- HOLY...
- ALL THESE MEN.
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
- Katakura: RIGHT ABOUT
WHEN I'D HOPED,
EVERYONE WHO SHOULD HAVE A
STAKE IN THIS CAME TOGETHER.
EVEN THOSE WHO'VE BEEN
LAYING LOW UNTIL NOW.
AND BOSS MASAMUNE NEVER
SAID WORD ONE ABOUT US
NOT BEING ALLOWED TO BAND
TOGETHER AGAIN. AM I WRONG?
- ( all exclaiming )
- YOU'RE THE BEST, BOSS!
- LET'S GO KICK SOME ASS!
- ( soldiers roaring )
- WE RIDE FOR HONNOJI IN
THE LAND OF YAMASHIRO.
WE SHALL GUARD MASAMUNE
AND SANADA'S REAR.
AND WE WILL ROUT ODA'S FORCES,
TO THE VERY LAST MAN!
- All: YEAH!
( all cheering )
- ( blows conch shell )
- THERE'S OUR TARGET,
COMING INTO VIEW NOW.
YOU READY FOR THIS?
- THOUGH A HUNDRED ARROWS COME
FLYING AT ME, I SHALL NOT STOP.
- GOOD, GOOD.
WE GOT NO BUSINESS WITH THEM.
WE'RE GOING STRAIGHT IN.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN!
- ( gasping )
- Date: HERE WE GO!
- ( horse neighs )
- BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE!
I'M HERE FOR THE
DEVIL KING'S HEAD!
- I AM TAKEDA GENERAL,
SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA!
COME FORTH, ODA NOBUNAGA,
AND YOUR DASTARDLY
GENERALS AS WELL.
LET US HAVE A FAIR FIGHT.
- ( grunting )
- RAGING FLAME!
- ( men screaming )
- IF YOU AIN'T COMIN' OUT...
- Both: WE'RE COMING IN FOR YOU!
- Akechi: NO SIGN
OF ENEMY FORCES.
IT SEEMS UNLIKELY
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON WOULD STORM
IN WITH JUST KAI'S YOUNG CUB.
- ( horse neighs )
- ODA FACTION, IF YOU
CALL YOURSELVES WARRIORS,
COME OUT HERE AND
ACCEPT THIS CHALLENGE!
- ALRIGHT, WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU, DEVIL KING?
HOW 'BOUT YOU, AKECHI?
- THEY ARE NOWHERE TO BE FOUND!
- CRAP. WHAT IS THIS?
- ( bird chirping )
- IT IS TOO QUIET DOWN THERE.
( chuckles ) NOW I GET IT.
- AKECHI MITSUHIDE!
- Date: YOU'VE KEPT US
WAITING LONG ENOUGH.
WHERE THE HELL IS
THE DEVIL KING HIDING?
- IT WOULD SEEM
THAT I AM THE ONE WHO HAS
FALLEN INTO ODA'S LITTLE TRAP.
- HOW FITTING.
YOU'VE BEEN FORSAKEN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THE NOBUNAGA WHO
ARRIVED WAS A DECOY.
THE DEVIL KING
ISN'T EVEN HERE.
ODA NOBUNAGA
WANTS ALL OF US,
TO KILL EACH OTHER
HERE AT HONNOJI.
- ( gasps )
- BY NOW, I IMAGINE THINGS ARE
GOING AS MITSUHIDE EXPECTED,
AND THE REMNANTS OF
THE EASTERN ALLIANCE
HAVE BEEN LURED TO HONNOJI.
BECAUSE I BROUGHT DOWN
THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO,
MITSUHIDE BELIEVED WE WERE
DECEIVED AND COULD BE USED.
EVEN IN HIS WILDEST DREAMS,
HE DID NOT SUSPECT THAT
HE WOULD BE SURROUNDED
AND STRUCK DOWN,
ALONG WITH THE ENEMY
HE DIRECTED AGAINST YOU.
MY LORD KAZUSANOSUKE,
I MUST THANK YOU
FOR ALLOWING
YOUR HUMBLE WIFE
TO ARRANGE THESE
MATTERS AS I SAW FIT.
THAT HE WOULD SEEK TO
LURE YOU INTO A TRAP.
I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SATISFIED
TO SIMPLY HAVE HIM PURGED.
- HE IS A FILTHY MONGREL
WHO KNOWS NO GRATITUDE.
DISPOSE OF HIM
HOW YOU SEE FIT.
- KICHO, IT SEEMS I HAVE
UNDERESTIMATED YOU.
THE FEELING THAT ONE HAS MISSED
OUT ON THE FINEST FEAST,
IS TRULY ABYSMAL.
- SO YOUR PLAN WAS TO TAKE OUT
THE DEVIL KING ALONGSIDE US.
AND SEIZE THE
LAND FOR YOURSELF.
- I HAVE NO INTEREST
IN THE LAND.
A MAN WHO CALLS HIMSELF
DEVIL KING OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN,
ATTACKED BY A SWARMING
FORCE BENT ON REVENGE.
I WANT HIM TO SCREAM.
I WANT TO HEAR HIM
BEG FOR HIS LIFE.
AND FINALLY,
TO TAKE THAT LIFE,
WITH THESE HANDS!
- BUT HOW CAN THIS BE?
WHAT KIND OF GENERAL WOULD WISH
TO BETRAY AND KILL HIS OWN LORD?
- AND THAT LORD IS
TRYING TO KILL HIM AS WELL.
IT'S CRAZY, I KNOW.
THEY KINDA DESERVE EACH OTHER.
HERE HE COMES.
- THIS PENT-UP FRENZY WITHIN ME,
I SHALL TAKE THE LIBERTY
OF VENTING IT UPON YOU!
( yells )
YEAH!
- ( grunting )
- YEAH!
- ( yelling )
- NOT BAD, GENTLEMEN.
I'M RATHER ENJOYING MYSELF.
- IT... IT'S NOTHING. NO.
- ( bell ringing )
- THIS IS UESUGI'S
FOOLISH NINJA,
WHOM I CAPTURED BEFORE
WE LEFT OWARI.
OH ICHI, I KEPT HER
ALIVE JUST FOR YOU.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IF YOU INTEND TO
SERVE THE ODA FAMILY,
TO SERVE MY LORD KAZUSANOSUKE,
YOU WILL EXECUTE THIS WOMAN.
- ( gasps )
- AKECHI MITSUHIDE.
THE SNEAK ATTACK YOU
LAUNCHED ON MY LORD,
AS WELL AS THE PAIN YOU'VE
CAUSED THE PEOPLE OF KAI,
WILL BE AVENGED!
( yells )
( grunting )
- YOUNG CUB HONEST TO A FAULT.
UNLIKE THE TIGER OF KAI,
I NEED NO TRICKERY
TO PUT YOU DOWN.
- DON'T GET TOO FIRED UP,
YUKIMURA. LET'S PLAY THIS COOL.
- I AM MUCH OBLIGED, MY LORD.
- ( Akechi chuckles )
THOUGH, GIVEN THIS FIRE,
THAT MAY BE A
TRICKY PROPOSITION.
- WHOA! AMAZING.
GUYS, YOU CAN GO HOME NOW.
I'LL REPORT BACK IN
WITH LORD ODA LATER.
MITSUHIDE, YOU'RE
GONNA DIE HERE.
- LORD NAGAMASA.
- DO YOU NOT WISH
TO BE OF USE
TO LORD KAZUSANOSUKE,
YOUR BROTHER?
SIMPLY DEPENDING ON HER HUSBAND
AND WAITING FOR THE WAR'S END.
IS NOT A WOMAN'S DUTY
IN THESE TIMES.
- I CAN... I CAN DO THIS.
- GOOD, SHOW US YOUR RESOLVE.
IF YOU SAY YOU CANNOT,
- NO, I... I CANNOT.
- I SEE. THEN I
HAVE YOUR ANSWER.
- ( both grunting )
- ( exclaiming )
- Oda: WOMAN!
USE SOME DISCRETION.
DO NOT STAIN MY CASTLE WALLS
WITH THE BLOOD OF FOOLS.
- I APOLOGIZE, LORD.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- SISTER OF THE DEVIL KING,
WILL YOU COME WITH ME?
- ALAS, I CANNOT.
I MADE A PROMISE TO MY LORD.
- I SEE.
GO WITH CAUTION THEN.
- DO NOT WORRY.
- ( blowing air )
( exclaims )
- ( screaming )
- ( gasping )
- OH, HOW IT HURTS.
I WOULD EXPECT
NO LESS OF YOU.
YOU MAKE THE VERY MARROW
IN MY BONES QUIVER.
RANMARU?
- YOU KNOW, I REALLY
DON'T LIKE YOU VERY MUCH.
BUT I PITY YOU, SO I'LL HELP.
BUT, YOU GOTTA
APOLOGIZE TO ODA.
- WELL, ISN'T HE A
THOUGHTFUL LITTLE RUNT.
- I MUST ADMIT I FEEL RATHER
CONFLICTED ABOUT THIS.
- BECAUSE YA MAKE THINGS
HARDER THAN THEY NEED TO BE.
WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO IT,
NO ONE'S COMPLETELY
IN THE RIGHT HERE.
IT'S ONLY WHEN YOU KEEP
YOUR EYE TO THE FUTURE
THAT THESE INJUSTICES
BECOME JUST.
IT'S THE WAY OF THE TIMES.
- HOW FAR I HAVE FALLEN TO
GARNER THE PITY OF A CHILD.
I UNDERSTAND.
I SHALL OFFER A HEARTFELT
APOLOGY TO LORD NOBUNAGA.
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps )
- HEY.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT FLEW WELL.
CAME IN HANDY, DIDN'T IT.
JUST LIKE I SAID, RIGHT?
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
WAS THAT WHISTLE?
- WHISTLE? IT'S THE LATEST
IN FLYING NINJA TOOLS.
- I JUST ASSUMED WHEN I BLEW
INTO IT, YOU'D COME RUNNING.
- WHAT? THAT'S THE
STUPIDEST THING I EVER HEARD.
WHATEVER. IT STILL
WORKED, DIDN'T IT?
- ( sighs )
( exclaims )
SO, WHAT'S THE WORD?
- ODA NOBUNAGA
IS AT MOUNT AZUCHI.
- ( Ranmaru yells )
- STAY OUT OF THIS, KID!
- SHUT UP, JERK.
I'M NOT A KID!
- ( groaning )
( gasps )
- TIME TO PUT A
QUICK END TO THIS.
- ( yelling )
- SUCH LOVELY PAIN.
- READY TO FINISH THIS CRAP?
- LORD MASAMUNE, I ASK THAT
YOU YIELD THIS BATTLE TO ME.
- Kojuro: MASAMUNE!
- HEY THERE, KOJURO.
GLAD YOU MADE IT.
- THE DEVIL KING IS
AT MOUNT AZUCHI.
I HAVE RELIABLE WORD
FROM AN ECHIGO NINJA.
FROM A GREAT FORTRESS
ATOP A MOUNTAIN
BLANKETED BY OMINOUS
CLOUDS, HE IS PREPARING THE
FINISHING TOUCHES ON HIS
WORLD UNDER WARRIOR RULE.
THERE WILL NEVER BE ANOTHER
OPPORTUNITY LIKE THIS.
PLEASE, LEAD THE ARMY
OUTSIDE TO THE DEVIL KING.
YOU, TOO, SANADA YUKIMURA.
- BUT, I MUST SETTLE
MATTERS WITH HIM.
- LEAVE THIS MONSTER TO ME.
DON'T LET YOUR PERSONAL FEELINGS
OUTWEIGH THE GREATER CAUSE.
WHAT YOU SWORE TO DO
FOR THE TIGER OF KAI,
WASN'T SUPPOSED TO BE SOME
PETTY ACT OF REVENGE.
- NO, YOU ARE RIGHT.
- THEN WE'RE GONE.
BUT WE GOT HIM NICE
AND WARMED UP FOR YOU.
IT IS IN YOUR HANDS,
MASTER KATAKURA.
- Akechi: AZUCHI CASTLE.
SO, IT HAS BEEN COMPLETED.
FOR THE FINAL BANQUET,
THAT MAY BE THE MORE
SUITABLE LOCATION.
- IT'S UNFORTUNATE THEN,
THAT YOU WERE NOT INVITED.
- PLEASE, NOHIME,
LET ME SEE MY BROTHER.
- THERE IS NO NEED FOR THAT.
- ( gun cocking )
- FOOLISH SISTER-IN-LAW.
AT LEAST PERISH
WITHOUT SUFFERING.
- ( gunshot )
- ( theme song playing )
- Date: SORRY TO
KEEP YOU WAITING.
I'LL FINALLY BE SLAMMING
THESE SIX SWORDS
DOWN ON THE DEVIL KING'S FACE.
I PROMISE.
YOU'RE INVITED TO
THE TIME OF YOUR LIFE.
YEAH. LET'S PARTY.