- YOU KNOW WHY I'M HERE.
TIME IS GROWING SHORT.
VERY SOON I SHALL HAVE
YOUR ANSWER OR YOUR LIFE.
I MUST INSIST UPON A DECISION
BY THE TIME I'VE RETURNED.
- RUSHING OFF TO DESTROY
MORI OF AKI, RIGHT?
YOU ALWAYS INTENDED
TO KILL YOUR ALLY.
AS DID HE, NO DOUBT.
YOU TWO DESERVE EACH OTHER.
BASED ON WHAT I COULD HEAR,
YOUR MAIN FORCE IS HEADED EAST,
FOR ODAWARA, LIKELY.
THREE OR FOUR ARMIES
LIE IN WAIT,
YOUR BATTALION AND A FEW OTHERS
NEARLY AS BIG.
YOU MEAN TO FINISH THIS WAR.
- THERE ARE TWO PATHS
LAID OUT BEFORE YOU--
SERVE THE TOYOTOMI FOR THE SAKE
OF YOUR HOMELAND'S FUTURE,
OR SLIT YOUR BELLY FORTHWITH
THAT YOU MAY SERVE
MASAMUNE'S GHOST.
NOT EVEN YOU ARE FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO TRY AND AVENGE
HIS DEATH ALONE.
- THE ONLY PATH I ACKNOWLEDGE
IS THIS ONE--
MY LORD SEES THROUGH
THAT CHEAP TRAP
MATSUNAGA'S BAITED FOR HIM
AND GRINDS THE TOYOTOMI TO DUST.
- THEN YOU CLING
TO A FAIRY-TALE.
TRUTH BE TOLD, I DON'T THINK
YOUR MASTER WILL FALL
TO THE OLD MAN'S DUPLICITY,
EITHER.
THE SERPENT HAS HIS EYE
ON OTHER PREY.
MATSUNAGA IS THERE
MERELY TO FORCE AN IMPASSE.
A STALEMATE THAT I WILL BREAK.
- ( theme music plays )
- Sarutobi:
NO IDEA WHO HE'S WORKING FOR,
BUT HE'S DEFINITELY
MADE THINGS EASIER FOR US.
- Kasuga:
BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHY HE'S HERE.
WE MAY HAVE TO FACE HIM.
- TOYOTOMI'S WAR STRATEGY
IS FAR MORE INTRICATE
THAN WE'D THOUGHT.
THE ONLY WAY WE'LL GET
WISE TO HIS PLAN
IS TO SNEAK IN AND TAKE A LOOK.
MASTER KATAKURA!
- Katakura: SARUTOBI!
- GUESS YOU OWE ME ONE, HUH?
- IT LOOKS LIKE THERE ARE
STILL PLENTY OF SOLDIERS
GUARDING THE PLACE.
- Sarutobi: WE'LL BE FINE,
SO LONG AS WE KEEP QUIET.
- I SEE WHAT THEY'RE UP TO.
THE UNIT HEADED
THIS WAY FROM AKI
IS THE MOBILE FORTRESS
MY SCOUTS REPORTED.
MORI MUST HAVE REBUILT
CHOSOKABE'S FUGAKU.
- Katakura: THEY EVEN
ANTICIPATED STEALING IT
FROM MORI IN THE END.
THAT'S WHY THEY FORMED
THE ALLIANCE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- Sarutobi:
WHAT?  YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
- Kasuga: JUST LIKE MORI HAS
ALWAYS PLANNED ON BETRAYING THEM
WITH A CASTLE ATTACK.
THEY ARE BOTH DANGEROUS FOES.
- Sarutobi:
THIS ARROW HERE,
DOES THIS MEAN THEY'VE SENT
TROOPS TO THE FAR NORTH BY SEA?
- THEY INTEND TO ATTACK
UESUGI FROM BEHIND.
KYUSHU'S IN SIMILAR PERIL.
- AND THESE ARE THE MEN
SENT TO TAKE OUT SATSUMA.
WHERE ARE THEY GETTING
ALL THESE SOLDIERS?
- Katakura: NO ONE BUT TOYOTOMI
COULD EVEN DARE TRY THIS.
IT'S A WAR TO END ALL WARS.
- LORD KENSHIN...
- FLY TO YOUR LORD, WARN HIM.
- THANK YOU.
- Katakura:
THAT "X" IS MATSUNAGA.
- Sarutobi: HE IS STILL
ALIVE. I'D HEARD AS MUCH.
- ANOTHER PART OF THE PLAN.
TAKENAKA'S USING THE VILLAIN
TO STALL MY LORD,
SO HE CAN DESTROY THEM BOTH
WITH THE FORTRESS
HE STEALS FROM MORI.
- HERE, YOU'LL NEED A SWORD.
THIS IS NO TIME TO BE
WALKING AROUND UNARMED.
- SARUTOBI!
- SASUKE!
- SON OF A--
LOOK WHO IT IS,
THE SILENT NINJA HIMSELF.
- FUUMA KOTARO!
- GO ON, KASUGA.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- ECHIGO'S IN FOR
A SURPRISE ATTACK
IF YOU DON'T WARN THE WAR GOD.
- Katakura:
SARUTOBI, IT'S THE SWORD!
- YOU TOO, MASTER KATAKURA.
NOW, GO!
- SASUKE...
- LISTEN TO ME,
GET RID OF THE SWORD.
THAT NINJA'S
MATSUNAGA'S SERVANT.
HE'S HERE TO TAKE THAT SWORD.
- WHAT?
HE SHOULD HAVE JUST SAID SO.
HEY, YOU WANT THIS, HUH?
GO FETCH!
- Zenkichi:
LET US OUT OF HERE, DAMN IT!
- Pirate: YOU'RE MESSING WITH
THE WRONG BUNCH OF PIRATES!
- Genbei: I'M GOING TO BUILD
THE CAPTAIN A MEMORIAL
OUT OF YOUR FACE!
- ( shouting )
- Matsunaga:
MY GOODNESS,
NOT A SCRATCH ON YOU.
EN ROUTE TO ODAWARA?
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
BUT PLEASE DON'T TARRY
ON MY ACCOUNT.
- IT'S MATSUNAGA!
- HOW IN THE HELL
IS HE STILL ALIVE?!
- REAL NICE, DROPPING
A DAMN MOUNTAIN ON US.
- I NEVER HAD YOU PEGGED
FOR A TOYOTOMI LICKSPITTLE,
OLD MAN
- FAR FROM IT,
I TEND TO DISREGARD ANY PACT
MADE WITH SOMEONE WHO SHOULD
KNOW BETTER THAN TO TRUST ME
THE MOMENT I'VE ENTERED INTO IT.
BEST TO KEEP THINGS SIMPLE
AT MY AGE.
- YOU'RE A RIGHT EELY BASTARD,
AIN'T YOU?
- I GOT A LOT TO PAY YOU
BACK FOR, WITH INTEREST!
- Matsunaga: AH, GOOD.
MY SERVANT COMES WITH A GIFT.
TOYOTOMI OFFERED ME MANY A BLADE
AND BAUBLE TO KILL YOU.
BUT I COVETED THAT WHICH HE
SOUGHT TO KEEP HIDDEN--
MIKAZUKI MUNECHIKA.
I SHALL MARVEL AT ITS PERFECTION
AS I DRINK FROM THE SKULL
OF THE DEMON KING ODA NOBUNAGA.
- WHAT?
- NOW, CHILDREN,
I BID THEE GOODNIGHT.
- Katakura:
LORD MASAMUNE!
- Soldiers:
BOSS KATAKURA!
- KOJURO...
- YOU ARE CHOSOKABE MOTOCHIKA,
YES?
- WHAT OF IT?
- A BATTLE TO AVENGE YOUR DEATH
IS RAGING IN OSAKA CASTLE.
THEY ARE FIERCE,
BUT THEY ARE FEW.
THEY'RE MEN IN NEED
OF A CAPTAIN.
- WELL, CAPTAIN?
- SO...?
- YOU DON'T SAY?
GUESS I GOT MYSELF
A PRESSING ENGAGEMENT.
I GOT TO GO RESCUE
MY BRAVE SONS-OF-BITCHES.
I'LL BE IN ODAWARA,
STRAIGHT AWAY.
AH, WHO AM I FOOLING?
- YOU AND I BOTH KNOW,
TIME YOU GET THERE
I'LL BE EITHER
VICTORIOUS OR DEAD.
- Chosokabe:
ONE-EYED DRAGON,
- YEAH?
- YOU BEST PULL THROUGH.
- AYE-AYE.
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU,
LET'S DUEL OUT ON THE WATER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME,
COURSE I'LL BE WINNING THAT ONE.
- AHOY, YOU SEA DOGS!
WE'RE GOING TO OSAKA!
- FORGIVE ME, LORD.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE LEFT THE--
- SAVE THE APOLOGY.
JUST GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
- OH, BOSS KATAKURA!
- MORI MOTONARI'S FORTRESS
IS CLOSING IN
AND TOYOTOMI WILL STEAL IT,
THEIR ARMY HEADED FOR ODAWARA.
THE FORTRESS AND A THIRD FORCE
HIDDEN IN THE NORTH
WILL UTTERLY DOMINATE
THE KANTO PLAIN.
- THEN WE'LL HAVE TO BEAT
THEM TO THE PUNCH.
SEEING HOW WE'RE
SO BADLY OUTNUMBERED AND ALL.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO SAY?
- PRECISELY.
PLEASE, LEAVE IT TO ME.
I, KATAKURA KOJURO,
WILL PROTECT YOUR BACK,
NOW AND EVER!
- ( all ):
BOSS KATAKURA!
- GOOD LUCK.
YOU'RE THE BEST MAN FOR THE JOB.
- Katakura:
THAT SCAR ON HIS BACK,
IT COULD NOT HAVE COME
FROM HIDEYOSHI'S FISTS.
YOU WILL PAY, TAKENAKA HANBEI!
- MY DEAR, MOTONARI,
ONE NEEDS NO OVERWHELMING FORCE
TO TOPPLE THE MORI.
YOUR MEN DESPISE YOU
AND WILL SCATTER TO THE WIND
THE MOMENT YOU DIE.
WHAT PAWN MOURNS
THE PASSING OF THE PLAYER
WHO SHOVED IT
OUT INTO HARM'S WAY?
THOSE WHO REMAIN WILL SURRENDER
TO US, MEEK AS LAMBS.
- Mori:
TOYOTOMI,
HOW PATIENTLY YOU WAITED
FOR THE DEVIL KING TO FALL,
FOR YOU SHARE HIS AMBITION.
YOU SCAVENGE THE CARRION
OF ANOTHER HUNTER'S KILL.
- MAY I OFFER
MY CONGRATULATIONS, LORD MORI?
SOON NOW,
THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN
WILL GROVEL AT YOUR FEET.
ALL WE NEED DO
IS SIMPLY ADVANCE UPON OSAKA
IN YOUR INVINCIBLE FORTRESS,
MY LORD.
PLEASE, A TOAST.
- MASTER AKAGAWA!
WHAT REASON CAN YOU HAVE
FOR SUCH BRUTALITY, LORD?
- OUR LORD HAS LOST HIS MIND!
- DRINK THE SAKE FOR YOURSELF,
AND PROVE THAT I AM INSANE.
- ALRIGHT...
- ( glass breaking )
- ( choking )
- SORRY, AKAGAWA.
I KNEW FROM THE START
THAT YOU WERE A TOYOTOMI SPY.
I'D FACTORED IT
INTO MY CALCULATIONS.
ALL THIS TIME,
YOU WERE A MODEL SERVANT,
KNOWING IT WOULD EARN YOU
THE ACCESS TO MY PERSON
YOU WOULD NEED TO POISON ME.
MY SINCEREST THANKS, TAKENAKA.
THIS PAWN OF YOURS PROVED
VERY USEFUL TO THE MORI CAUSE.
- I HAVE FINALLY HAD
AN EPIPHANY.
I, YUKIMURA, HAVE DONE NOTHING
BUT TROT BEHIND YOU.
YOU SPEAK OF THE FUTURE
YOU ENVISION, YOUR LORDSHIP,
AND I NOD.  BUT I HAVEN'T BEEN
SEEING IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
WHEN I TAKE UP MY SPEARS,
IT SHOULD NOT BE TO FIGHT
FOR A FUTURE YOU DESIRE.
IT SHOULD BE BECAUSE I WANT
THAT SAME FUTURE JUST AS BADLY,
BECAUSE I SEE IT FOR MYSELF.
THIS IS THE FIRE
BURNING WITHIN ME
WHEN I FIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
FROM THIS DAY FORTH,
AND FOR ALWAYS,
I PLEDGE MY LIFE
TO A WORLD BEYOND WAR!
HEAR ME, YOUR LORDSHIP,
I'VE BEEN BLIND,
BUT NOW I SEE THE WISDOM
OF YOUR WAYS.
YOUR TEACHINGS HAVE BECOME
PART OF MY FLESH AND BLOOD,
PART OF MY VERY BONES.
I CANNOT REMAIN A TIGER CUB
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
FOR SOME DAY, I MUST BECOME...
THE TIGER OF KAI HIMSELF!
- Soldier 1: THE SIGNAL
FLARE HASN'T BEEN FIRED OFF.
- Soldier 2: AND IT HASN'T
SLOWED DOWN, EITHER.
DO YOU THINK THE SPY
WAS DISCOVERED?
- WHY HAS MASTER TAKENAKA
STILL NOT ARRIVED?
- I THINK WE SHOULD MAKE
A FULL RETREAT, RIGHT NOW.
- CANNONEERS, MAKE READY
TO FIRE THE MORNING STAR.
TOYOTOMI, YOU'LL SEE
THE LIGHT SOON ENOUGH.
- CHOSOKABE'S FORTRESS?
BUT I THOUGHT--
- NO, IT'S DIFFERENT.
- FIRE AWAY!
THIS IS MY PLAN, FINALLY
COME TO FRUITION.
TOYOTOMI HIDEYOSHI
MAY HAVE SINGLEHANDEDLY
DESTROYED THE FUGAKU,
BUT HIS PRODIGIOUS STRENGTH
WILL NOT SAVE HIM,
NOT WHEN THE MORNING STAR
SETS HIS WORLD AFLAME.
STRENGTH HAS NO MEANING
WHEN I CAN BURN
THE MIGHTIEST FOE
TO CINDERS FROM AFAR.
THE SUN GRANTS ME PROTECTION
AND LENDS ME ITS FIRE.
THERE CAN BE NO DOUBT,
HEAVEN ITSELF SMILES
UPON MY CONQUEST.
- WHAT DEVILRY IS THIS?
ATTACKING IT IS
TANTAMOUNT TO SUICIDE.
BUT ATTACK IT,
WE CERTAINLY MUST.
ALL IN FAVOR OF SINKING
THAT FORTRESS?
- ( all ): SIR!
- THE QUESTION IS HOW?
WITH A WEAPON LIKE THAT
AT MORI'S DISPOSAL,
HE'LL PUT THE ENTIRE LAND
TO THE TORCH.
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
TOYOTOMI LED HIS MAIN ARMY
TOWARD ODARAWARA,
A STRONGHOLD
FROM WHICH HE'D BRING
ALL OF THE KANTO PLAIN
UNDER HIS BOOT.
- HIDEYOSHI,
I SWEAR I WILL STOP YOU.
IF STRENGTH IS ALL
THAT YOU VALUE IN THIS LIFE--
HIDEYOSHI, WAKE UP!
IF YOU DON'T ACKNOWLEDGE
YOUR WEAKNESS,
INSTEAD OF JUST HIDING IT AWAY,
YOU'LL NEVER TRULY KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE STRONG!
THE PEOPLE YOU CHERISH
MIGHT BE THE HOLE IN YOUR ARMOR,
BUT IT'S THOSE VERY PEOPLE,
DAMN IT, WHO WILL INSPIRE YOU
TO FIND YOUR REAL STRENGTH!
YOU CHERISHED HER, HIDEYOSHI.
I KNOW YOU CHERISHED HER,
SO DID I!
HOW DO YOU MURDER
THE WOMAN YOU LOVE?!
JUST OPEN YOUR EYES, HIDEYOSHI!
THIS ISN'T THE REAL YOU!
PLEASE, WAKE UP
FROM THIS NIGHTMARE!
- BEEN A WHILE HASN'T IT,
ONE-EYED DRAGON?
- KEIJI, YOU EVER GOING TO TAKE
ALL THIS SERIOUS ENOUGH
TO USE THAT SWORD?
- THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG.
I TAKE EVERYTHING
SERIOUSLY, ALWAYS.
IF THE ONLY TIME YOU MEET
PEOPLE HALFWAY
IS WHEN YOU'RE STABBING THEM,
THIS WAR'S NEVER GOING TO END.
IT'S STRANGE, I KNOW,
BUT JUST THE TINIEST THINGS
IN COMMON ARE ENOUGH
TO MAKE YOU NOT WANT
TO HURT A MAN.
PEOPLE ARE GOOD, BASICALLY.
I NEED TO BELIEVE THAT.
I KNOW YOU DON'T.
BUT WE KEEP TAKING LIVES
LIKE IT'S NOTHING.
WHY?
STRANGERS, AND FRIENDS,
AND LOVERS ALIKE.
WHY HER? OF ALL THE PEOPLE
IN THE WORLD.
- YOU STOOD YOUR GROUND,
FLOWER BOY,
I RESPECT YOU FOR THAT.
ALSO, IF YOU'RE SAYING
WHAT I THINK YOU'RE SAYING,
THEN TOYOTOMI'S AS VILE
A BASTARD AS I ALWAYS THOUGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF PAST
YOU HAVE WITH HIM,
BUT IF YOU'RE GOING TO TRY
AND TELL ME WHAT A GOOD MAN
HE WAS BACK IN THE DAY,
SAVE YOUR BREATH.
- I WON'T.
- LEAVE HIM BE, BOYS.
THAT VAGABOND FACED HIM
WITH NOTHING BUT WORDS,
WHEN NO ONE ELSE
HAD THE GUTS TO TRY.
HE'LL STAND WHEN HE'S READY.
- ( horse galloping )
- WHAT WILL YOU DO,
SANADA YUKIMURA?
THE TAKEDA CAVALRY,
AND THE TROOPS LORD SHIMAZU
ENTRUSTED TO YOU,
THEIR FATE HINGES ON YOU
MAKING THE RIGHT DECISION.
- MASTER, CONGRATULATIONS
ON A JOB WELL DONE IN SATSUMA.
- WHAT NEWS TO REPORT, SASUKE?
- HIDEYOSHI IS HEADED
FOR ODAWARA WITH HIS MAIN ARMY.
LORD KENSHIN HAS
UTSUNOMIYA CONTAINED.
BUT TOYOTOMI'S SECRET ARMY
TO THE NORTH
IS CLOSING IN FROM BEHIND.
AND IT SEEMS A THIRD
TOYOTOMI BATTALION
HAS BEEN DEPLOYED TO KYUSHU.
THEY MEAN TO CONQUER THE COUNTRY
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
BUT THOSE CREWMEN OF CHOSOKABE
BEING HELD CAPTIVE
AT OSAKA CASTLE HAVE BEEN FREED.
THEY'VE SWORN VENGEANCE AND
ARE READY TO GO DOWN FIGHTING.
AND REUNITED WITH HIS RIGHT EYE,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
RACES TO ODAWARA
FOR A FINAL SHOWDOWN
WITH HIDEYOSHI.
MASTER, OUR CLAN'S MAIN ARMY
STILL HAS YET TO TAKE THE FIELD.
SHALL I CALL FOR REINFORCEMENTS?
- NO NEED, I WOULD RATHER
OUR LORD STAY HIS HAND
FOR THE MOMENT AND WATCH HOW
THESE BATTLES UNFOLD.
THERE'S NO WAY TO BE SURE
WHAT IS IN STORE FOR ANY OF US.
HAVE HIS LORDSHIP REMAIN IN KAI,
THAT HE MAY STRIKE
WHEREVER HE CAN DO MOST GOOD.
- GOOD THINKING, MASTER.
I'LL PASS THAT ALONG.
LOOKS LIKE THE TIGER CUB
HAS GROWN UP.
- LORD MASAMUNE,
YOU'RE ALIVE AFTER ALL.
- Sarutobi:
ALL SIGNS POINT TO TAKENAKA
HAVING DESIGNS
ON MORI'S FORTRESS.
BUT THUS FAR, HIS SOLDIERS
ARE NOWHERE TO BE SEEN.
- Sanada: HE WANTS TO
CAPTURE THAT BEHEMOTH?!
- YEAH.
- SASUKE, WHAT KIND OF TERRAIN
LIES ON THE PATH AHEAD OF US?
WE'RE STOPPING THAT FORTRESS,
WHATEVER THE COST!
- Soldier:
MASTER HANBEI!  MASTER HANBEI!
THE ADVANCE PARTY'S BEEN
ANNIHILATED BY MORI'S WEAPONRY.
- HOW CAN THIS BE?
- SO, AKAGAWA,
YOU HAVE FAILED ME.
TYPICAL.
- WELL, WHO DO WE HAVE HERE?
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, MUTTON CHOPS.
HOW'S ABOUT A REMATCH?
WINNER TAKES ALL, YOU IN?
OH, AND THANKS FOR SENDING
YOUR ARMIES OUT
TO CONQUER THE COUNTRY.
'CAUSE IF I BEAT YOU RIGHT HERE,
I GET THE WHOLE BALL OF WAX.
AND THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
WILL RULE THE LAND.
- YOU COULD FIGHT ME
FOR THE REST OF TIME
AND STILL YOU WOULD NOT WIN.
YOU'VE NEARLY DIED TWICE NOW
OR HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
- GUESS YOU DIDN'T HAVE
THE STONES TO FINISH ME OFF.
- HANBEI MERELY SLICED
THROUGH YOUR COAT.
I SHALL MAKE IT A BURIAL SHROUD
FOR WHATEVER REMAINS
OF YOUR CORPSE!
- ONE PROBLEM,
YOU'LL BE NOTHING BUT DUST
BY THE TIME I DIE.
COME ON!
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Date: YOU CAN'T
CONQUER THIS COUNTRY
WITH NOTHING BUT STRENGTH.
I DON'T CARE
HOW BADASS YOU ARE.
WHEN THE HEAVENS PART,
IT'S A NO-HOLDS-BARRED
RACE TO THE TOP.
SO CUE UP MY THEME SONG
ONE LAST TIME.
I'M GOING TO DO THIS IN STYLE.