- ( cheering )
- ( men urging horse )
- HIYAH!
- ARE YOU READY, GUYS?
- Men: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GUN IT!
- ( men whooping )
- 'KAY BOYS, HERE COMES
THE FUN PART.
- LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
- ( horse neighing )
- Men: YEAH!
- ( laughing )
- HERE WE GO!
- ( horse neighing )
- ( men screaming )
- Date: BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE.
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
( laughing )
- ( men gasping )
- ( loud banging )
- ( guards gasping )
- YOUR CASTLE GATE IS
LIKE A PAPER SCREEN
UNDER MY PERFECT SPEAR
OF CONQUEST.
SANADA YUKIMURA IS HERE.
THOSE VALIANT OF HEART,
MAKE YOUR STAND NOW.
- ( men shouting )
- ( grunting )
- ( explosion )
- ( men groaning )
- I PRAY THEE, WATCH, YOUR
LORDSHIP, WITHOUT FAIL.
I SHALL HOIST YOUR BANNER
OVER THE CAPITAL.
BEHOLD THE MIGHT
OF CLAN TAKEDA!
( grunting )
- ( screaming )
- ( theme song playing )
- Narrator: THE SENGOKU PERIOD,
A TIME OF CHAOS AND UPRISINGS.
SAMURAI LORDS SPILLED
HOSTILITIES ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THE MAP OF POWER REDRAWN
AT AN EVER-INCREASING PACE.
- IN THE NAME OF JUSTICE, IT IS
MY DUTY TO DESTROY ALL EVIL.
OICHI, GAZE WELL
ON MY VALIANT FORM.
- YES. LORD NAGAMASA.
- ANY WHO DARE INVADE MY LANDS,
SHALL BE SLAIN WITHOUT MERCY
BY THE POWER OF THE SUN.
- THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA
ISN'T A MYTH, IT'S ME.
COME GET ME ANYTIME,
IF YOU WANT TO GET EATEN.
- ( cheering )
- YEAH, RIGHT ON!
- I WILL DEFINE THIS ERA.
HONDA, ON YOUR HONOR AS A
MIKAWA WARRIOR, GO DESTROY.
- ( sword striking )
- ( laughing )
RECITE THE SUTRAS.
TIME TO PUT YOUR DEAD TO REST.
- ( fire crackling )
I COLLECT YOUR LIVES,
BUT NOT YOUR BONES.
- Oda: I AM TO BE WORSHIPED.
FOR DEFYING THE KING OF THE
HOUSE OF A HUNDRED DEMONS,
YOU WILL ATONE IN THIS LIFE
AND THE NEXT.
- ( rumbling )
- THERE ARE NONE BEFORE ME.
THERE SHALL BE NONE AFTER ME.
I AM THE DEVIL KING OF THE
SIXTH HEAVEN, ODA NOBUNAGA!
- REPORT, SASUKE.
- IT IS AS YOU SURMISED.
- HMM.
- YUKIMURA.
- SIR!
- TAKE A DETACHMENT AND ATTACK
THE ENEMY FROM THE FLANKS.
- DO WHAT?
YOUR LORDSHIP,
THOUGH I KNOW THEY HAVE THE HIGH
GROUND, WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
IT IS THE TAKEDA WAY TO FACE OUR
ENEMIES HEAD ON IN FULL FORCE.
- BUFFOON! WAR IS MORE
THAN OUR TIME-HONORED TACTICS.
YOU MUST ADAPT,
OR YOU PAVE THE WAY TO
YOUR OWN DEMISE, YUKIMURA.
- BUT, YOUR LORDSHIP,
YOU AND LORDKENSHIN
SHARE A WORTHY RIVALRY
OF THE RAREST KIND.
IF WE LAUNCH A SURPRISE ATTACK
UNDER THE COVER OF NIGHT,
IF NOTHING ELSE, I WORRY IT
IS YOUR REPUTATION THAT WILL...
( groaning )
- IT IS BECAUSE OF THAT RIVALRY.
THIS IS A MERE DIVERSION.
YOU WILL STRIKE DOWN UESUGI'S
COMMON SOLDIERS AND GENERALS.
TO DRIVE OUT KENSHIN HIMSELF.
- YOUR LORDSHIP.
- CALL IT THE
WOODPECKER MANEUVER.
IF IT FAILS, MAY OUR DESCENDANTS
LEARN FROM OUR FOOLISHNESS.
BUT YOU AND I, TOGETHER,
CANNOT FAIL!
- YOUR LORDSHIP, I WAS IGNORANT
OF THE AMOUNT OF THOUGHT
YOU HAD GIVEN THIS.
I, YUKIMURA,
MUST ADMIT MY MISTAKE.
UPON MY VERY LIFE, I SHALL
CARRY OUT THIS COMMISSION.
- WELL SAID, YUKIMURA.
- YOUR LORDSHIP.
- YUKIMURA.
- YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- ILLUMINATING.
- ( horse neighing )
- ( screaming )
- DID WE DO
THE RIGHT THING HERE, MY LORD?
OR SHOULD WE HAVE TOLD
MASTER SANADA,
THE TRUE OBJECTIVE
OF THIS STRATEGY?
- REGARDLESS OF WHAT
WE TELL HIM,
HE WILL BE EQUAL TO THE TASK.
IF HE IS NOT, THEN SO BE IT.
- ( grunting )
SO YOU'VE RETURNED, KASUGA.
- SIR.
AS MY LORD EXPECTED,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON OF OSHU
IS CURRENTLY APPROACHING
THE UESUGI CAMP,
ATTEMPTING TO OUTFLANK US.
- INTERESTING.
I HAD THOUGHT IT A POSSIBILITY
UPON HEARING OF HIS
ONSLAUGHT IN THE FAR NORTH.
NOW I SEE MY FEARS
WERE NOT UNFOUNDED.
- MY LORD.
- OUT WITH IT.
- MY LORD, A DETACHMENT
HAS JUST LEFT THE TAKEDA CAMP.
THEY ARE MAKING THEIR WAY HERE
TO SAIJO MOUNTAIN.
SINCE THEY LEFT
UNDER COVER OF NIGHT,
A SURPRISE ATTACK IS LIKELY.
- TIGER OF KAI,
QUITE A BRILLIANT MOVE.
- LORD KENSHIN?
- I AM FREE NOW
TO FIGHT HIM MY WAY.
WELL DONE,
MY MOST BEAUTIFUL BLADE.
GENTLEMEN! PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
WITH DIVINE STEEL
IN YOUR HEARTS, FOLLOW ME!
OUR TARGET IS THE TIGER OF KAI!
MAY BISHAMONTEN GUIDE US!
- LET HEAVEN'S WILL BE DONE.
- ( men cheering )
- BOSS MASAMUNE.
- YEAH.
WHAT'S UP, KOJURO?
- WE SHOULD HALT THE ARMY
AND SEND ANOTHER SCOUT
UP SAIJO MOUNTAIN.
- WHAT?
- I SENSE TROUBLE, SIR, LIKE
THEY'RE WAITING FOR US.
- HA! ALL THE MORE FUN THEN.
IT JUST MEANS
THEY'RE READY TO PARTY.
- WE NO LONGER HAVE
THE ELEMENT OF SURPRISE.
- NO PROB. RACE YOU, KOJURO.
- ( horse neighing )
- BUMMER. LOOKS LIKE
THEY ALREADY TOOK OFF
TO FIGHT OLD MAN TAKEDA.
- Katakura: OR IT COULD
BE A TRAP.
- ( men shouting )
- THOSE AREN'T UESUGI'S TROOPS.
ALL UNITS, HALT! FULL STOP!
A CRESCENT SYMBOL
AND ONLY ONE EYE?
ARE YOU OSHU'S ONE-EYED DRAGON?
- ( men murmuring )
- I AM SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
LORD DATE MASAMUNE,
BOSS OF OSHU, I PRESUME?
WHAT BUSINESS HAVE YOU HERE?
- YEAH.
LISTEN, RED.
- WHAT DID... BLACKGUARD!
- CLEARLY, YOU'RE TAKEDA'S
SACRIFICIAL PAWN, BUT...
I'M TAKING UESUGI,
AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
SO, ARE YOU GONNA TURN TAIL
AND RUN, OR FACE ME HERE?
EITHER WAY, DATE ENDS UP
THE SOLE VICTOR.
- I KNOW NOT WHAT GROUNDS MY
LORD HAS TO MAKE SUCH A CLAIM.
- I'M JUST SAYING THE
ONE-EYED DRAGON'S
A MAN OF ACTION. YOU SEE?
- YOU WILL NOT DISRUPT OUR FIGHT
WITH LORD KENSHIN.
I SHALL NOT ALLOW IT.
- PERFECT.
KOJURO, DON'T LET ANYONE
INTERFERE WITH US.
- YES SIR.
BOSS OF OSHU, DATE MASAMUNE!
- VASSAL OF KAI,
SANADA YUKIMURA!
I HONOR THIS FIGHT WITH
ALL MY STRENGTH!
- FULL SPEED AHEAD!
- ( both screaming )
( both grunting )
( both straining)
- HE BLOCKED
BIG BOSS-MAN'S ATTACK.
- ( swords clanking )
- HA! WHAT KIND OF SPEAR
FIGHTER LETS ME GET WITHIN
STRIKING RANGE SO EASY?
- ( growling )
( gasping )
- SORRY, JUST A SCRATCH.
- I AM GLAD YOU'VE FINALLY
ARRIVED ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
- YOU WAITED. MOST THOUGHTFUL.
- A THANK YOU,
FOR THE SALT THAT TIME.
- ( loud explosion )
- ( groaning )
- ( exclaiming )
- WELL MET, YOUNG CUB.
- YUKIMURA, YOU HAVE
A NEW RIVAL.
- ( explosion )
- PERHAPS THIS VERY MOMENT,
IS WHAT THIS LONG STANDOFF
HAS BEEN FOR.
- THE DEER HAS FALLEN.
SURELY OUR TIME TO CLAIM
THE KILL IS SOON AT HAND.
- ( explosion )
- ( screaming )
- ( swords clanking )
- BOSS DREW ALL SIX SWORDS.
- GOOD, THE BASTARD'S BEEN
ASKING FOR IT.
- ( both grunting )
( both panting )
- Sarutobi: HOLD!
- Date: WHO THE HELL'RE YOU?
- MASTER ONE-EYED DRAGON,
WON'T YOU CALL IT A DRAW?
SARUTOBI SASUKE,
SANADA NINJA CORPS, TAKEDA ARMY.
I HATE TO SPOIL YOUR FUN,
BUT OUR MAIN ARMY AND UESUGI
WILL SOON HAVE THIS
PLACE SURROUNDED.
A CLEAR THREE-SIDED FIGHT
MIGHT BE DIFFERENT.
BUT WITH BOTH ARMIES
MARCHING ON YOU AT ONCE,
EVEN YOU WOULD BE
AT A DISADVANTAGE.
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT CRAP.
AS IF I'M SUPPOSED TO JUST TAKE
THE WORD OF AN ENEMY NINJA.
- MASAMUNE, I BELIEVE
OUR WITHDRAWAL MAY BE WISE.
- KOJURO.
- EVEN IF WE ARE EQUAL
TO THE TASK,
NO SMALL NUMBER OF LIVES
WILL BE LOST.
- ( grunting )
- ( horse neighing )
- WHOO! THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
IF THAT FIGHT KEPT GOING,
EVEN YOU WOULD'VE BEEN...
UH... MASTER?
- IT BURNS.
- HUH?
- THERE IS A BURNING
IN MY HEART.
SUCH AMBITION.
SUCH FIGHTING SPIRIT.
SUCH STRENGTH. IT BURNS.
- SO, HE UH...
LIGHTS YOUR FIRE, DOES HE?
- THE ONE-EYED DRAGON,
DATE MASAMUNE.
- SANADA YUKIMURA,
THE YOUNG CUB.
- Sanada: WHAT?
YOU ANTICIPATED DATE'S AMBUSH?
- Takeda: YES.
LIKELY, KENSHIN DID AS WELL.
WHICH MUST BE WHY
HE MAINTAINED POSITION
ATOP THE MOUNTAIN FOR SO LONG.
- SO, WHAT WAS MY ROLE
IN ALL THIS?
- IF DATE'S INTERFERENCE
HAD NOT COME TO PASS.
YOU WOULD HAVE COMPLETED YOUR
MISSION AS ORIGINALLY PLANNED.
BY ALL RIGHTS,
I HAD NO REASON TO KEEP THESE
DETAILS FROM YOU, YUKIMURA.
- THEN... TO WHAT PURPOSE?
- A GENERAL MUST BE CAPABLE
OF RESPONDING TO THE UNEXPECTED.
HAD YOU NOT RETURNED,
THEN SO MUCH FOR
MY MILITARY PROWESS.
- I SEE NOW, YOUR LORDSHIP.
EVERYTHING IS A TEST.
AND I HAVE FAILED THIS ONE.
I HAVE NO HONOR TO SPEAK OF.
IF IT WAS NOT FOR SASUKE,
I WOULD NOT HAVE
COME BACK UNSCATHED.
- THIS ONE-EYED DRAGON.
HE IS THAT STRONG, IS HE?
- OH, YES.
QUITE STRONG, LORDSHIP.
SO MUCH SO,
IT STIRRED MY VERY SOUL.
- SARUTOBI SASUKE, REPORTING IN.
- GOOD WORK.
- WHAT NEWS FROM SUNPU?
- IMAGAWA SHOWS SIGNS
OF RAISING AN ARMY.
IT SEEMS THEY PLAN TO ATTACK ODA
WHILE HE IS INVADING ISE.
- YES, AS I EXPECTED.
PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
WE SHALL TAKE IMAGAWA BY STORM!
- SIR! ONE QUESTION.
THE TRUCE WITH UESUGI,
YOU KNEW IT WOULD BENEFIT
THIS SITUATION AS WELL?
- ( scoffing )
THANK YOUR MAN, SASUKE.
I HAD TO ASK MUCH OF HIM.
- ( laughing )
HOW IMPRESSIVE.
SHREWD AS ALWAYS, MY LORD. I...
( gasping )
- MY LORD, THAT WOULD
KILL A NORMAL MAN.
- ( groaning )
- I WATCH OTHER LANDS
AS A MATTER OF COURSE.
YUKIMURA, TO BE
A GOOD COMMANDER.
ALWAYS CONSIDER
EVERY EVENTUALITY.
- ( screaming )
THANK YOU FOR THE VALUABLE
LESSON, YOUR LORDSHIP.
HOWEVER, I INTEND TO
SERVE YOU, MY LORD.
- AND, GOD WILLING, SOMEDAY
THE WORLD UNDER YOUR RULE.
- BUFFOON!
AS A WARRIOR IN THESE TURBULENT
TIMES, SHOW SOME AMBITION.
GRAB THE REINS OF POWER
IF GIVEN THE CHANCE.
- ( groaning )
- YUKIMURA, EVEN I AM DESTINED
TO GROW OLD SOMEDAY.
- NO, YOUR LORDSHIP.
OF ALL MEN, IF ONE WILL NOT
GROW OLD, IT IS YOU, SIR!
- UH... COMMANDER?
- Takeda: I AM ONLY HUMAN.
NEVER FOOL YOURSELF
TO BELIEVE OTHERWISE.
( grunting )
YUKIMURA!
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- YUKIMURA!
- BRILLIANT.
- YOUR LORDSHIP!
- ( men cheering and laughing )
- ALL RIGHT, YEAH, NICE SHOW.
- DANCE FOR US, MAN.
- WE MISSED THE WAR GOD
OF ECHIGO AND THE TIGER OF KAI.
ALL THAT AND NOTHING TO SHOW
FOR IT.
- ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
YOU DON'T APPEAR
TO BE TERRIBLY DISAPPOINTED.
- SO WHY DID YOU STOP ME?
WERE YOU AFRAID
I WAS GONNA LOSE?
- NO.
I MERELY GAVE WEIGHT
TO THE POSSIBILITY
THAT THE NINJA CLAIMING
TO SERVE TAKEDA
WAS SPEAKING THE TRUTH.
EITHER WAY, THOUGH,
IF YOU HAD CONTINUED
THAT FIGHT,
ONE OF YOU, MAYBE BOTH,
WOULD NOT HAVE LIVED.
- HMM.
GUESS I GOT
A LITTLE OVERHEATED.
GOT TO PLAY IT COOL.
- SO, ARE WE RETURNING
TO OSHU TOMORROW?
- NOT YET.
WE DIDN'T WORK OUR WAY
DOWN TO THE LAND OF MUSASHI
JUST TO TURN BACK NOW.
- THEN, LET'S HOLD A WAR COUNCIL
ONCE THE SCOUT I
SENT OUT RETURNS.
CERTAINLY IMAGAWA WILL
GIVE IN TO THE PRESSURE
OF HIS NEIGHBORS.
I IMAGINE HE'S RAISING
AN ARMY NOW.
- ( scoffing )
GREAT MINDS, AS THEY SAY.
- HOWEVER, TAKEDA IS NO FOOL.
WE'LL HAVE TO
ASSUME HE'LL STRIKE
AT THIS NEW THREAT BEFORE
THEY GAIN ANY GROUND.
- BUT TAKEDA JUST HAD IT OUT
WITH UESUGI.
- I SUSPECT THEIR
ARMIES DID NOT ACTUALLY
CROSS SWORDS AT KAWANAKAJIMA.
WHEN THEY LEARNED
OF OUR AMBUSH,
I'D VENTURE BOTH COMMANDERS
DECIDED TO WAIT FOR ANOTHER DAY.
- TRICKY SON OF A...
- STEAL THE TIGER OF KAI'S
THUNDER AND BRING DOWN IMAGAWA?
IT COULD BE FUN.
- AND YOU HAVE A PLAN?
- BUT OF COURSE,
WE IMITATE TAKEDA HIMSELF.
IF I HAD TO GIVE IT A NAME?
THE WOODPECKER MANEUVER.
- THAT DOES SOUND LIKE
A FUN GAME.
COUNT ME IN, KOJURO.
- Hojo: WHAT?
OSHU'S ONE-EYED DRAGON
DARES ATTEMPT
TO INVADE US
HERE IN ODAWARA?
- MY LORD, YOUR DECISION?
- ( grunting )
HE WILL LEARN RESPECT FOR THE
ANCESTRAL POWER OF THE HOJO.
- TEAR IT UP, BOYS. LET'S PARTY.
- YEAH!
- I AM CALLED...
- ( men cheering )
- IMPUDENCE! TURNING THEIR BACKS
ON THE ENEMY WITHOUT A FIGHT?
ALL OF YOU, AFTER THEM!
- ( men shouting )
- SOMETHING AMISS, YUKIMURA?
- ( men cheering )
- THAT'S DATE'S ARMY!
- ( scoffing )
- MASAMUNE!
- CURSED DRAGON!
LOOK, HE IS IN LEAGUE
WITH TAKEDA.
THERE CAN BE NO TURNING BACK.
CRUSH THEM.
- ( men shouting )
- HOJO UJIMASA'S FORCES.
- ONE-EYED BASTARD.
THIS WAS A TRAP.
YUKIMURA, I'LL DEAL WITH THIS.
TAKE OUR BEST MEN
AND GO AFTER DATE.
DO NOT LET HIM
TAKE YOSHIMOTO'S HEAD.
- Sanada: RIGHT AWAY, YOUR
LORDSHIP. YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
DATE IS EMPLOYING
THE WOODPECKER MANEUVER.
THAT HE WOULD NOT ONLY STEAL
LORD SHINGEN'S TACTICS,
BUT USE THEM AGAINST US.
YOU ARE A BOLD MAN,
LORD MASAMUNE.
YOU'LL FIND SO AM I.
- A ONE-EYED DRAGON WILL BITE
OFF THE HEAD OF IMAGAWA.
COUNT ON IT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Sanada: PERFECT SPEAR
OF CONQUEST.
SANADA YUKIMURA IS HERE.
I HUMBLY ASK THAT YOU OBSERVE
OUR EXPLOITS NEXT TIME.
AS OUR BATTLE GROWS
EVEN MORE HEATED!