- MITSUHIDE.
- WHY IS YOUR ARMY
NOT AT YOUR BACK?
OSHU'S ONE-EYED DRAGON AND
HIS ARMY ARE CLOSING IN FAST,
HOPING TO TAKE
THE DEVIL KING'S HEAD.
- ONE-EYED DRAGON?
- TOKUGAWA IS MOVING
TO HOLD BACK TAKEDA
AND UESUGI AT NAGASHINO.
IF DATE GETS PAST THEM,
IT WILL BE PROBLEMATIC.
AT THE MOMENT, I BELIEVE THAT
IS MORE PRESSING THAN ASAKURA.
YOU MUST KNOW WHY I HAVE
REVEALED THIS ONLY TO YOU.
YOU MUST SHOW HONOR IN
BATTLE FOR LORD NOBUNAGA
TO ACCEPT A PEACEFUL
END WITH ASAKURA.
AND SHOULD HE NOT,
LADY O-ICHI'S LIFE WOULD
HANG IN THE BALANCE.
- HE WOULDN'T.
- ( theme song playing )
- Azai: WE HEAD FOR NAGASHINO
AND HITARAGAHARA.
WE SHALL SEE JUSTICE
SERVED THE AZAI WAY,
FOR THIS IS A RIGHTEOUS BATTLE.
SOLDIERS OF JUSTICE,
FOLLOW ME TO GLORY!
- BOSS MASAMUNE.
- HMM?
- ABOUT THIS MAEDA VAGABOND,
I'M STILL NOT SURE I TRUST HIM.
- WHAT, YOU THINK HE'S LURING US
INTO THE DEVIL KING'S CLUTCHES?
- IT IS NOT INCONCEIVABLE.
HE MAY NOT BE TIED
DOWN TO HIS HOUSE,
BUT HE STILL CLAIMS
THE FAMILY NAME.
MAEDA TOSHIIE SUPPORTS ODA.
AND IN RETURN, I HEAR HE WAS
JUST GIVEN THE LAND OF KAGA.
- WHATEVER. AS LONG AS HE
DOESN'T GET IN MY WAY.
- YUKIMURA.
- YES, SIR?
- YOU'RE WITH ME.
- SIR.
- LORD IEYASU!
IT'S TAKEDA SHINGEN, SIR.
HE'S HEADED THIS WAY.
- WHAT?
LORD SHINGEN.
- IT'S TAKEDA SHINGEN.
- THAT'S SANADA YUKIMURA.
- Tokugawa: HOLD!
- YOUR SPEARS, YUKIMURA.
YOU WILL NOT NEED THEM.
IT HAS BEEN
TOO LONG, TAKECHIYO.
- AH! LORD SHINGEN. YOU ARE
LOOKING AS WELL AS EVER.
I AM GLAD.
- HMM.
- LORD TOKUGAWA,
I AM SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
IT IS A PLEASURE TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
- I HAVE HEARD TALES
OF YOUR MANY VALOROUS DEEDS.
YOU HAVE NO NEED TO WORRY.
I WOULD NOT BE SO UNCOUTH AS
TO ATTACK YOU OR LORD SHINGEN
WHILE YOU'RE BOTH UNARMED.
FORGIVE MY SILENCE
IN OUR CORRESPONDENCE.
BUT FOR US TO MEET
IN SUCH A MANNER,
ESPECIALLY HERE UPON
THE FIELD OF BATTLE...
- I BELIEVE, RATHER,
I KNOW IN MY HEART,
YOU ARE MERELY WAITING
FOR THE RIGHT MOMENT.
FOR I ALSO KNOW YOU MUST
SUFFER THE HUMILIATION
OF YOUR GOSSAMER ALLIANCE
WITH ODA IN SILENCE.
- INDEED. FOR NOW,
I MUST ENDURE
BUT SOMEDAY, I SHALL SURPASS
EVEN YOU, LORD SHINGEN.
THIS WORLD, THIS ERA, WILL BE
FORGED BY THESE HANDS!
BUT THE TIME IS NOT YET RIGHT
TO EMBARK ON MY GREAT ENDEAVORS.
WHICH IS WHY I HAVE ALLIED
MYSELF WITH THE OPPONENT
I LEAST WISH TO FACE
UPON A BATTLEFIELD.
- YOUR TIME WILL
NEVER COME, TAKECHIYO.
BEFORE YOU CAN EVEN THINK
TO SEIZE THE COUNTRY,
YOU WILL SURELY BE USED
AND THEN CRUSHED BY ODA.
- ( chuckles )
TAKING UP ARMS LIKE THIS
IS UNLIKE YOU, LORD SHINGEN.
AND SUCH RASH
BEHAVIOR IS ILL-BEFITTING
OF THE WAR GOD OF ECHIGO.
BRUTE FORCE WILL ONLY
BRING YOU FAILURE.
- Takeda: THIS IS NOT
A TIME WHEN PATIENCE
WILL REVEAL A PATH TO SURVIVAL.
WE MUST POOL ALL
OF OUR RESOURCES,
BEFORE IT IS TOO LATE.
IF WE LEAVE ODA UNCHECKED,
FIGHTING OVER LAND WILL BE
THE LEAST OF OUR CONCERNS.
FOR WHAT GOOD IS
LAND IN A WORLD
WHERE NOT EVEN A BLADE
OF GRASS WILL GROW?
TAKECHIYO, LIVE YOUR
LIFE UNFETTERED
BY THE FEAR OF DEATH,
JOIN WITH US AGAINST ODA.
- ( wind howling )
- ALAS, I CANNOT.
WHETHER I DIE OR REMAIN,
IT IS ALL THE SAME TO ME.
ODA HAS CHARGED ME WITH
PROTECTING THE EAST,
AND I WILL NOT
BETRAY THAT ALLIANCE.
- IF THAT IS SO...
- ONCE I HAVE GIVEN MY WORD,
EVEN IF IT IS TO
THE DEVIL KING ODA,
WHO COMMITS ALL
MANNERS OF ATROCITIES,
EVEN KNOWING I MAY
FACE HIS BETRAYAL,
I WILL NEVER BETRAY
A SOLEMN OATH!
ON MY HONOR,
AS A MIKAWA WARRIOR!
ALL UNITS, ENGAGE!
- ( soldiers yelling )
- IN TRUTH, I HAVE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT.
I CANNOT BE THE
ONE TO INITIATE,
BUT I MAY ENGAGE ANY AGGRESSORS.
IF I WIN THIS BATTLE,
IT WILL SURELY LAY THE
FOUNDATION OF MY POWER
TO EVENTUALLY CHALLENGE ODA.
- AS YOU ARE NOW, DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE CAPABLE OF THAT?
- WATCH ME AND FIND OUT.
- YUKIMURA, WE ARE
FINISHED HERE.
- YOUR LORDSHIP, SHOWING ONE'S
BACK TO ONE'S ENEMY.
LORD IEYASU.
- Uesugi: IN THESE
TURBULENT TIMES,
RIGHT AND WRONG HAVE
ALL BUT LOST THEIR MEANING.
BUT SO LONG AS THE PEOPLE NEED
LEADERSHIP AND PROTECTION,
THE PATH OF RIGHT
MUST STILL BE TAKEN.
BOTH ARMIES, ADVANCE!
MOVE SWIFTLY,
AND ANNIHILATE THE ENEMY!
- ( soldiers yelling )
- ( urging horse )
- YUKIMURA, YOU AND I WILL
STRIKE AT TOKUGAWA FROM BEHIND.
- YOUR LORDSHIP, WAS A
PINCER ATTACK ALWAYS YOUR PLAN
IF LORD IEYASU COULD
NOT BE WON OVER?
- I DID NOT WANT IT THIS WAY,
BUT TAKECHIYO MOST
CERTAINLY HAD TO REALIZE
I WOULD NOT WITHDRAW UNLESS
HE ORDERED A CHARGE.
WHICH HE COULD ONLY ATTEMPT
WITH THE SO-CALLED INVINCIBLE
HONDA TADAKATSU AT HIS COMMAND.
- HONDA TADAKATSU?
- OR PERHAPS, HE HAS SOME
OTHER GAMBIT YET TO REVEAL.
- RIGHT, JUST BY SHEER
NUMBERS OF TROOPS.
FIGHTING US HEAD-ON
WOULD SEEM TO BE RECKLESS.
- THEN WE PROCEED
WITH CARE. ONWARD!
- SIR!
- Tokugawa: ISN'T ODA'S
ARQUEBUS CORPS HERE YET?
- ACCORDING TO MASTER
AKECHI'S SIGNAL,
THEY SHOULD ARRIVE SHORTLY.
- I SEE.
- EVEN THE VAUNTED TAKEDA
CAVALRY WON'T STAND A CHANCE
IN THE FACE OF A LEGION
OF ARQUEBUSES, MY LORD.
- WATCH FOR OUR MOMENT,
THEN WITHDRAW THE TROOPS.
WE'LL TAKE BOTH ARMIES
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
- SIR!
- LORD SHINGEN,
PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
BUT THE FUTURE WILL BE
FORGED WITH THESE HANDS.
- ( soldiers yelling )
- AH, MY MOST BEAUTIFUL BLADE,
HOW YOUR BLOOM
DAZZLES THE BATTLEFIELD.
- ( exclaims )
I AM NOT WORTHY
OF SUCH WORDS.
- ( soldier grunting )
- I SHALL PROTECT YOU,
LORD KENSHIN.
- PERFECT! SPEAR! OF CONQUEST!
SANADA YUKIMURA IS HERE!
( grunting )
- ( grunting )
- Tokugawa: I EXPECTED NO LESS
OF LORD SHINGEN.
- ALL UNITS, MOVE FROM FISH
SCALE TO CRANE WINGS FORMATION.
TAKE THE MAIN ENCAMPMENT!
- ( soldiers yelling )
- ( Itchan groaning )
- ITCHAN!
- TETCHAN.
- DAMN IT.
HE WAS A GOOD MAN!
ITCHAN.
FOR LORD IEYASU!
( yelling )
- WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU, MASTER?
THIS ISN'T YOUR FIRST BATTLE.
DID MEETING IEYASU DULL
YOUR FIGHTING SPIRIT?
- NO, NOTHING OF THE SORT.
- Takeda: THAT IS THE PAIN
OF TAKING A LIFE.
- Sanada: YOUR LORDSHIP.
- OUR FOES ARE LIKE US.
THEY, TOO, HAVE PEOPLE
THEY HOLD IN THEIR HEARTS,
FUTURES THEY HOPE FOR.
BUT THE ODA FACTION DOES NOT!
- ( men screaming )
- OUR OPPONENTS
ARE STILL MEN, YUKIMURA.
AS YOU WIELD YOUR SPEARS,
DO NOT EVER FORGET THAT.
- SIR!
- LORD TAKEDA, INSTEAD OF
ATTACKING ASAKURA,
ODA IS SENDING HIS ARMY HERE.
- THEN THIS BATTLE
MAY YET BE DECISIVE.
- AS EXPECTED, WE CAN DO
NOTHING ABOUT BEING OUTNUMBERED.
HONDA TADAKATSU,
GREATEST WARRIOR IN
THE LAND, MOVE OUT!
TADAKATSU!
- TAKE HIM DOWN AND MAKE
A NAME FOR YOURSELF.
I AM CALLED NAOE KANETSUGU.
UESUGI'S FIRST UNIT.
THE FIRST UNIT IS ONLY ME,
FOR I AM UNSTOPPABLE!
INVINCIBLE BEATS UNSTOPPABLE!
- ( soldiers screaming )
- TADAKATSU,
DON'T TELL ANYONE THIS,
BUT YOU'RE ALMOST
TOO GOOD FOR ME.
THAT'S THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
OF OSHU.
- TOKUGAWA IS MOVING TO BLOCK
TAKEDA AND UESUGI'S PATH.
- IT'S JUST A SKIRMISH. ONCE WE
KNOCK OFF THE DEVIL KING,
WE'LL DOUBLE BACK AND CLEAN UP,
THEN WE GET SHINANO, TOO.
- EVEN THE TIGER OF KAI
COULDN'T CONVINCE HIM.
- ( horses neighing )
- ( whistling )
YOU'VE GOT SOME KINDA NERVE
TRY'N TO BLOCK MY WAY.
WHO ARE YOU AND
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
- HEAR ME WELL. I AM AZAI
BIZEN-NO-KAMI NAGAMASA.
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO GO ONE STEP FURTHER.
- AZAI NAGAMASA?
- IN THE NAME OF JUSTICE,
I SHALL CLEANSE THE
WORLD OF YOUR SINS.
- AZAI NAGAMASA. THE DEVIL
KING'S BROTHER-IN-LAW.
PERHAPS ODA SENT HIM HERE.
- HMPH.
- WHERE ARE YOU
WATCHING FROM, DEVIL KING?
- ( Keiji urging horse )
- LORD KEIJI?
- DUDE.
- Bunshichi: WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- Magobei: HE'S NOT
RUNNING AWAY?
- ( gasps )
- LORD KENSHIN, LOOK.
- Uesugi: KEIJI.
- THAT BASTARD!
MAEDA KEIJI FINISHED
SETTING THE STAGE,
AND NOW HE'S RETURNING
TO HIS OWN SIDE.
I BELIEVE ODA
INTENDS TO CRUSH US,
TAKEDA AND UESUGI
HERE IN NAGASHINO.
- SOUNDS LIKE FUN. WILDER THE
PARTY THE BETTER, RIGHT?
- ICHI, GUIDE MY SWORD.
WAIT FOR ME.
SOLDIERS OF JUSTICE, FOLLOW ME.
ANNIHILATE THE FORCES OF EVIL!
- ( soldiers yelling )
- I MAY LOSE MUCH,
BUT NEVER MY HONOR.
- MASAMUNE, LEAVE THEIR
SOLDIERS TO US.
- THANKS, KOJURO.
I'M SURE YOU GOT THIS.
( urging horse )
- BIG BOSS!
- IT'S BEEN TOO LONG.
- LET'S MAKE THIS COOL.
HEY, NOT BAD FOR A WARM-UP.
BOSS OF OSHU, DATE MASAMUNE.
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
- AZAI NAGAMASA.
SO, HE SERVES AS ODA'S VANGUARD.
- Akechi: BEHOLD, LORD NOBUNAGA.
AS HE IS PASSIONATELY LOYAL,
LORD AZAI ATTEMPTS TO REPEL
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON FOR YOU,
HIS BELOVED BROTHER-IN-LAW.
- NAGAMASA.
- MITSUHIDE, THE ARQUEBUS CORPS
THAT WAS GOING TO IEYASU.
WHERE ARE WE ON THAT?
- I ASSIGNED THEM AS REAR
SUPPORT FOR AZAI.
I FELT IT WAS A
NECESSARY PRECAUTION
AGAINST DATE'S MOBILITY.
- ( soldiers yelling )
- GOOD, TADAKATSU.
ODA'S ARQUEBUS CORPS
WILL BE HERE SOON.
WE, THE TOKUGAWA, WILL...
- ( Sanada yelling )
MASTER HONDA TADAKATSU,
GREATEST WARRIOR IN ALL
THE LAND, I PRESUME?
STAND FIRM! YOU FACE
SANADA YUKIMURA!
LET US HAVE A CLEAN FIGHT.
( grunting )
I WILL NOT YIELD!
- HE STOPPED
TADAKATSU'S ATTACK?
- MASTER!
- SASUKE.
- ( grunting )
- YOUR LORDSHIP,
I SHALL TAKE HIM ONE-ON-ONE.
- HE IS NOT ONE WHO
CAN BE DEFEATED ALONE.
- ( yelling )
- HOLD YOUR GROUND, TADAKATSU.
- ( grunting )
- ( soldiers grunting )
- WHERE IS ODA'S
ARQUEBUS CORPS?
- HONDA TADAKATSU'S MOVEMENTS
ARE BEING RESTRAINED.
AT THIS RATE, TOKUGAWA'S ARMY
WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER,
MY LORD HUSBAND.
- ( grunting )
GLEAMING. CROSS SLASH!
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU EARN THE FULL FURY
OF MY DRAGON CLAWS!
- I WOULD DIE
BEFORE I SURRENDER.
- ( gasps )
MASTER AKECHI, YOU WOULDN'T
ORDER THE ARQUEBUS CORP
TO ATTACK FROM WHERE THEY ARE?
- WELL, WE DO NEED TO
KEEP THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
PINNED DOWN.
- BUT MY LORD NAGAMASA
WOULD BE...
- ( horse galloping )
- KEIJI, WAIT!
- KENSHIN!
- I SEE IT NOW. THIS WAS
YOUR PLAN FROM THE START.
UNITE THE EASTERN GENERALS
TO HOLD THE DEVIL KING IN CHECK,
AND WITH ALL OF US BUSY, YOU
WOULD USE THE MAEDA NAME
TO TRY AND TALK
SOME SENSE INTO HIM.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOUR
PREPARATIONS ARE LACKING.
- I'LL NEVER
KNOW UNLESS I TRY!
BEFORE THIS GETS ANY
MORE OUT OF HAND, I...
- AND THE DEVIL KING'S RESPONSE
IS QUITE OBVIOUS.
YOU PUT FAR TOO MUCH FAITH
IN THE GOOD IN PEOPLE.
- Keiji: COME ON. THE DEVIL KING
WASN'T ALWAYS A DEVIL, WAS HE?
- Uesugi: SADLY, IN THIS WORLD,
THERE ARE SOME WHO
ARE TRULY BORN EVIL.
AS YOUR FRIEND, I CANNOT
ALLOW YOU TO GO TO YOUR DEATH.
- BROTHER, PLEASE STOP THEM.
PLEASE SPARE MY LORD NAGAMASA.
- MITSUHIDE, THIS TIME,
YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR.
- MY LORD.
YOU HAVE MY APOLOGIES.
- BROTHER, PLEASE.
- Akechi: LADY O-ICHI.
GO NOW,
WHILE THERE IS STILL TIME.
- ( horse neighing )
- HEAVEN-RENDING
BLADE OF SOARING!
- ( gasps )
- WOW, YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
X!
- MY RIGHTEOUS WILL
IS UNYIELDING!
I GO WHERE THE BEACON
OF HONOR GUIDES ME.
EVEN IF I SHOULD LOSE
ALL MY LIMBS,
I WILL NOT FALTER.
SILENT DEATH SHOCK.
- MY LORD NAGAMASA!
- ICHI!
- ( grunts )
- LORD NAGAMASA, RUN!
- ( chuckles )
NOW THEN, LET'S SEE ALL
OF YOU DANCE FOR ME.
- ( guns firing )
- MASAMUNE!
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasping )
- ( groaning )
- ICHI.
- ( crashing )
- ( theme song playing )
- Ichi: THE LIFE OF A
TRAMPLED SOUL IS ENDED.
I AM SO SORRY.
IT IS ALL MY FAULT.
BUT I PROMISE
I WILL WORK TO ATONE.
PLEASE RETURN NEXT TIME.