- SORRY, FELLAS.
I THINK WE'RE, UH--
OH, YOU AIN'T
GOING TO LIKE THIS.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED TO BORROW
YOUR HORSES FOR A BIT.
- Samanosuke:
WHAT DID HE JUST SAY?
THIS GUY IS NUTS.
- SO A BUNCH OF BANDITS
WANT TO HORSEJACK MY ARMY?
WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DEALING WITH?
- SEE THAT?  YOU'RE JUMPING
TO ALL SORTS OF CONCLUSIONS.
NO BANDITS HERE, WE'RE PIRATES.
WELL, MINUS A SHIP.
THE WRECKAGE OF MY LATE FORTRESS
DRIFTED ASHORE.
ANYWAY, YOUR HORSES WILL BE
SERVING THE GREATER GOOD.
- YEAH, I THINK I'M
GOING TO PASS.
AND FYI,
YOU KIND OF SUCK
AT ASKING FOR FAVORS.
YOU CRACK ME UP, YOU KNOW THAT?
HERE YOU ARE,
ON TOP OF A DAMN MOUNTAIN,
OCEAN NOWHERE IN SIGHT,
CALLING YOURSELF A PIRATE.
AND THAT ANCHOR-LOOKING THING
JUST SCREAMS SUBTLETY.
YOU'RE MY KIND OF CRAZY.
- ( theme music plays )
- HEY, FOUR-EYES,
WANT SOME ADVICE?
HAND OVER THOSE HORSES
WITHOUT A FIGHT!
- CAPTAIN CHOSOKABE
AIN'T MESSING AROUND.
SO HAND THEM OVER
BEFORE SOMEONE GETS HURT.
- WHAT DID YOU CALL ME?!
- PRETTY COCKY FOR NOT
HAVING A SHIP, AIN'T YOU?
- YOUR CAPTAIN COULD
NEVER BEAT THE BIG BOSS.
NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN, DIG?
NO WAY.
- I DON'T KNOW
HOW THEY ARE AS PIRATES,
BUT THEY TALK SOME GOOD TRASH.
- DAMN STRAIGHT.
YOUR SONS-OF-BITCHES
GOT SOME BALLAST
BELOW DECK, TOO.
- WANT TO PLAY,
CAPTAIN LAVENDER?  LET'S PLAY.
BUT DON'T GO PULLING
ANY CHUMP MOVES, ALRIGHT?
- WORKS FOR ME.
WHEN YOU'RE AS GOOD AS I AM,
WHO NEEDS TO CHEAT?
- ( squawks )
- BRING IT ON!
- Bunshichi:
ATTA BOY, BIG BOSS!
- Magobei:
HIT HIM ON THE UPSWING!
Samanosuke:
YOU CAN BEAT THIS POSER
WITH A SINGLE BLOW!
- BIG BOSS KICKS ASS!
NO WAY HE'S LOSING TO THIS GUY.
- Chosokabe's Army:
GO, CAPTAIN!
- ( chanting continues )
- BIG BOSS!  BIG BOSS!
BIG BOSS!
- ( together )
BIG BOSS! BIG BOSS!
- GO, CAPTAIN!
- BIG BOSS!
- COCKY BASTARD.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
DEATH FANG!
CRAZY STORM!
- YOU WANT CRAZY, HUH?
- ( footsteps )
- Matsunaga:
AS I LIVE AND BREATHE,
THE RIGHT EYE OF THE DRAGON.
- MATSUNAGA!
- TURNS OUT THE NETHERWORLD
HAS LITTLE IN THE WAY
OF TREASURE FOR ME TO COVET.
SO I TOOK MY LEAVE.
HUNTING BAUBLES AMONG THE LIVING
HAS PROVEN FAR MORE REWARDING.
- YOU'VE MADE YOUR RETURN
FROM THE LAND OF THE DEAD.
IF ANY COULD, IT'D BE YOU.
- YOU FLATTER AN OLD MAN.
WHAT SEPARATES LIFE AND DEATH,
BUT A MOMENT OR A BIT OF STEEL?
- SO, YOU'VE SET YOUR SIGHTS
ON SOMETHING OF TOYOTOMI'S?
- AND I'LL TAKE IT
WITHOUT THIEVERY.
TOYOTOMI'S STRATEGIST
HAS GIVEN ME A TASK.
TO WIT, THE DESTRUCTION
OF THE DATE ARMY.
WHAT TREASURE I TAKE
IS FOR A JOB WELL DONE.
THAT INSOUCIANT MASTER
OF YOURS LIVES.
THOUGH I TRUST
THIS IS NO SURPRISE.
WHAT BETTER BAIT, THEN,
TO LURE IN THE DRAGON
THAN ITS OWN RIGHT EYE?
- WHY BOTHER ASSIGNING
THIS TO YOU?
- TOYOTOMI AND HIS THIRST
FOR CONQUEST MEAN NOTHING TO ME.
NOTHING ENDURES, NOT EVEN STEEL.
I ACCEPTED HIS OFFER, THINKING
IT WOULD BE A FINE CHANCE
FOR ME TO TAKE
DATE'S SIX DRAGON SWORDS.
BUT ALAS, ONLY FIVE REMAIN.
BUT ITEMS CAN ACHIEVE WORTH
IN A NUMBER OF WAYS.
THAT WHICH MAKES ONE UGLY,
MAKES ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL.
TAKE THIS BLADE--
SCARRED, BROKEN,
A SHADOW OF ITS FORMER SELF.
HAVING SURVIVED JUST BARELY,
NOW IT IS PRICELESS.
I WONDER IF THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
FEELS THE SAME
ABOUT THAT WHICH HE HOLDS DEAR.
HOW THE TEARS MIGHT
BEDEW HIS CHEEK
IF DATE WERE TO FIND
HIS RIGHT EYE ALL BUT DEAD.
A MAN LACKING IN SCRUPLES
COULD DISPATCH HIM RATHER EASILY
IN SUCH A MOMENT, NO?
- YOU FIEND.
- TOYOTOMI'S LIEUTENANT
HAS PLACED
BUT ONE RESTRICTION ON ME--
HE FORBADE ME TO KILL YOU.
IN OTHER WORDS--
- MATSUNAGA!
- SO LONG AS I DON'T KILL YOU,
I HAVE CARTE BLANCHE TO BEAT
YOU WITHIN AN INCH OF YOUR LIFE.
THIS WILL BE FUN.
- WHOA, CHECK IT OUT.
THAT GUY IN THE BLUE--
HE'S ONE STRONG BASTARD.
- HE'S AS GOOD AS BIG BOSS.
- THIS IS NO ORDINARY PIRATE
WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE.
- Date: I WASN'T EXPECTING
TO GET A WORKOUT TONIGHT.
THIS IS A NICE WARM-UP
FOR THE BEATDOWBEAT DOWN
I PLAN TO PUT
ON TOYOTOMI LATER.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST THE LEADER
OF A SECOND-RATE BAND
OF HOOLIGANS.
BUT YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
- CRAZY, AIN'T IT?
BUT DON'T GET SWEET ON ME.
WHEN THESE BEAUTS COME OUT,
IT MEANS THERE'S NO SECOND DATE.
YOU SEE?
- RIGHT BACK AT YOU,
LITTLE BOY BLUE.
'CAUSE WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOU,
THERE WON'T BE ANYTHING LEFT.
- ALRIGHT THEN, LET'S DANCE!
- WELL, ANCHORS AWAY!
RAMMING SPEED!
PHANTOM DIVE!
- THOSE SIX SWORDS
AND THAT CRESCENT MOON HELMET...
- WAIT, IS THAT GUY--
COULDN'T BE!
- HE'S STRONG AS AN OX
AND THE WAY HE HANDLES
THAT ANCHOR!
- NO WAY, YOU THINK
THAT DUDE IS-- ?
- YOU KIND OF ROCK.
WELL, FOR A GUY WHO CAN'T
FIGURE OUT A JACKET.
- THIS FROM THE MAN
WHO PUT HANDLEBARS
AND CHROME PIPING
ON THE SIDE OF HIS HORSE!
- THE ONE-EYED DRAGON!
- THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA!
- SO WHAT BRINGS YOU OUT HERE?
YOU GUYS HITCH-HIKING
ACROSS THE COUNTRY OR SOMETHING?
- YEAH, OR SOMETHING.
TO TELL YOU TRUE, THE CREW
AND I ARE IN A BAD SPOT.
I'M OUT TO AVENGE
MY BEAUTIFUL FUGAKU
FOR THE OUTRAGE
THEY'VE DONE TO HER.
AND RESCUE THOSE SONS-OF-BITCHES
WHAT GOT CAPTURED.
OUR DESTINATIONS
ARE ONE AND THE SAME-- OSAKA!
- Akagawa: THE TECHNOLOGY
CHOSOKABE HAD AT HIS DISPOSAL
IS REMARKABLE, MILORD.
UNRIVALED, IF I MAY BE SO BOLD.
THIS FUGAKU,
IS THE CULMINATION OF ALL OF IT.
- WHY DO YOU SQUAWK "FUGAKU"
LIKE A MINDLESS BIRD?
IT BELONGS TO THE MORI NOW,
THE OLD NAME IS DEAD.
- RIGHT, SO THEN WHAT IS--
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I SAID IT BELONGS
TO ME NOW, FOOL.
- ITS NEW NAME IS THE SUN?
- WHAT OTHER NAME
COULD THERE POSSIBLY BE?
- FORGIVE MY IGNORANCE, MILORD.
- MAKE THESE WRETCHES
WORK FASTER.
IT MUST BE COMPLETED
ON SCHEDULE.
DENY THEM SLEEP
UNTIL THE TASK IS DONE.
- MILORD--
- I WILL BE DEPARTING AKI
FOR A TIME.
- RIGHT, AND I SHALL ATTEND
TO MATTERS WHILE YOU ARE AWAY.
- THIS TOO IS PART OF MY PLAN
TO DECEIVE THE TOYOTOMI.
MY CALCULATIONS
ARE ALL-ENCOMPASSING.
- Miyamoto:
PAY ATTENTION!
- ( thump )
- Sanada:
NOT AGAIN!
I WAS CARELESS, WHY DO I KEEP
GETTING LOST IN MY THOUGHTS?
WHEN I NEED TO BE ON MY TOES?
- HEY, OSTRICH HEAD,
YOU WANT TO DO THIS OR NOT?
I MEAN, I'M TAKING TIME
OUT OF MY BUSY SCHEDULE HERE
TO SPAR WITH YOU, MAN.
- MASTER MUSASHI,
PLEASE ACCEPT MY APOLOGIES.
IF YOU'RE GAME, I WOULD
LIKE TO CONTINUE.
I'M AWFUL, IF I DON'T
SNAP OUT OF IT
I CAN FORGET ABOUT MY REMATCH.
IT WOULD SHAME ME
TO FACE MASAMUNE LIKE THIS.
- Sanada:
TELL ME, YOUR LORDSHIP,
WHY DO MY ARMS HANG
AT MY SIDES LIKE LEAD?
WHY DO I WIELD
MY PRECIOUS SPEARS
AS THOUGH THEY INTRUDE
UPON MY HANDS?
YOUR LORDSHIP, WHY HAVE YOU
TURNED AWAY FROM ME?
FAVOR ME WITH YOUR WISDOM,
I BEG OF YOU!
GIVE ME GUIDANCE!
YOUR LORDSHIP!
- WHO IS THIS MASAMUNE GUY?
- HUH?
- LIKE, WHAT KIND OF GUY IS HE?
HE'S STRONG, YEAH?
- WELL, YES,
OF COURSE HE'S STRONG.
HE'S ONE OF THE STRONGEST.
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON,
LORD DATE MASAMUNE OF OSHU.
HE'S MASTERED
THE SIX SWORD TECHNIQUE,
AND HE'S A MOST EARNEST
OF GENERALS.
EVEN THOUGH HE IS STILL YOUNG.
- SIX SWORDS?  HOLY CRAP!
THIS MASAMUNE SOUNDS
LIKE A BADASS.
IF THAT'S HOW IT IS,
I'D BETTER START PRACTICING
WITH SEVEN OF THEM.
SCREW THAT, I'M GOING EIGHT!
- MY CLAN RECEIVED WORD
THAT HE FOUGHT TOYOTOMI.
THERE WAS NO NEWS OF HIS FATE.
PERHAPS SASUKE HAS
ALREADY BEEN TOLD BY HIS NINJA
THAT LORD MASAMUNE
IS SAFE AND SOUND.
I'M SURE HE IS FINE,
HE HAS TO BE.
HE'S PROBABLY MARCHING
ON OSAKA THIS VERY MOMENT.
COME, GOOD MUSASHI.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN!
- OH, SNAP. YOU'RE AWESOME
WHEN YOU'RE ACTUALLY TRYING.
- THINKING OF LORD MASAMUNE
JUST NOW HAS BOLSTERED MY SOUL
WITH A NEWFOUND RESOLVE!
- DREAMING ABOUT YOUR BOYFRIEND
WON'T DEFLECT A ROCK
TO THE HEAD!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
THROWING ROCKS IS DANGEROUS,
NOT TO MENTION UNSPORTSMANLIKE!
FINE, YOU BIG BABY.
NO MORE ROCKS.
HOW ABOUT SAND?!
- WAIT!
KICKING SAND IN MY FACE
IS UNGENTLEMANLY!
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING!
- ( screams )
- AND YOU DUG A PIT, HOW CLEVER.
CAN WE GO BACK
TO YOU THROWING THE ROCKS?!
- NEVER SEEN A TIGER CUB
FLY BEFORE.
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL, POPS?!
YOU'RE BOOZING IT UP AGAIN?
- ( laughing )
I TOLD YOU, IT'S WATER.
- LORD SHIMAZU!
- WHAT'S ALL THE SQUAWKING FOR?
- ENEMY SOLDIERS, SIR!
WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
- Miyamoto:
IS IT THAT PUNK-ASS TOYOTOMI?
- RECKON WE KNEW
IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
- GET YOUR GAME FACES ON.
WE'LL BE IN OSAKA
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
AND THEN WE'RE
GOING TO KICK SOME ASS!
- ( cheering )
- LET'S RESCUE OUR MAIDS
AND PAY THAT GORILLA BACK
FOR WHAT HE DID TO THE FUGAKU!
WELL, DOGS, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- AYE-AYE!
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
YOU KNOW, I HEARD THAT SHIP
OF YOURS WAS OUT OF THIS WORLD.
BUT BUSTING HEADS
LANDLUBBER STYLE
MIGHT BE A NICE CHANGE OF PACE.
- TRUE ENOUGH,
THE OLD GIRL NEVER WAS
MUCH GOOD FOR A SNEAK ATTACK.
THIS IS A FINE BREEZE,
EVEN IF IT DON'T SMELL
OF THE SEA.
THAT SLIPPERY WHORE'S SON, MORI.
STRIKING TOYOTOMI'S COLORS
LIKE HE DID.
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
HE SHOULD HAVE HAD STONES ENOUGH
TO SETTLE OUR FEUD
BY HIS LONESOME.
WAS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
- HUH?
- OH, BEG YOUR PARDON.
THERE WAS A DUEL I WAS
PARTICULAR KEEN ON HAVING
BEFORE I CONQUERED
THE COUNTRY, SEE.
BUT NOW IT'S LOOKING LIKE
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED FOR GOOD.
IT'S A DARK DAY FOR PIRACY
WHEN A SCOUNDREL SUCH AS ME
CAN'T LAND A WORTHY RIVAL.
DID I HAPPEN TO STRIKE
A NERVE, DRAGON MAN?
YOU'VE GOT THAT LOOK
LIKE YOU WERE REMINDED
OF SOMEONE JUST NOW.
- HUH?
THERE'S THIS ONE GUY I FOUGHT
A COUPLE OF TIMES.
MAN, WHAT A BOY SCOUT.
DON'T KNOW IF I'LL
EVER SEE HIM AGAIN, THOUGH.
HE'S NAIVE, LIKE, REALLY NAIVE.
GOING TO GET SOMEBODY KILLED.
PROBABLY HIMSELF, TOO.
- OH, YEAH?  SOUNDS TO ME
AS THOUGH YOU ADMIRE HIM
ALL THE MORE FOR IT.
- YEAH?
THE DUDE'S GOT MOXIE.
I KID YOU NOT,
HE'S SOMETHING ELSE, THIS GUY.
I MEAN, HE WIELDS HIS SPEARS
WITH SUCH FURY AND PASSION
I LOSE MY COOL EVERY TIME.
IT'S LIKE FIGHTING IN A BONFIRE.
- YOU DON'T SAY?
HOPE I GET TO SEE
THAT SPEARWORK OF HIS
FOR MYSELF ONE OF THESE DAYS.
- SANADA YUKIMURA,
HOW'S YOUR PLAN GOING?
- Shimazu:
WE'RE OUTNUMBERED, NO DOUBT.
BUT WE KNOW THE LAY OF THE LAND
AROUND HERE.
THEY WON'T BE TRYING
ANYTHING AT NIGHT.
YOU, MY BOY, ARE GOING
TO LURE THOSE BASTARDS IN.
- LEAVE IT ME, POPS!
- AND TIGER CUB,
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU AS WELL.
DRAW THEM IN NICE AND CLOSE
WHEN YOU TURN TAIL AND RUN.
- SIR!
- I'LL DO MY BEST, MILORD.
- Narrator:
WHAT SHIMAZU YOSHIHIRO
AND SANADA YUKIMURA
DID NOT YET KNOW
WAS THAT FAR TO THE REAR
OF TOYOTOMI'S ARMY,
MORI MOTONARI'S FORCES
WERE POISED
AND READY TO SWOOP IN
AS REINFORCEMENTS.
- WHAT NEWS
OF OUR NAVAL DEPLOYMENT?
- Soldier:
MILORD, WE'VE REASON TO BELIEVE
THEY'LL ARRIVE
AT THE SOUTHERN SHORE OF SATSUMA
AROUND THE SAME TIME AS US.
- SATSUMA'S DEFENDERS
ARE NOTHING.
A PATCHWORK ARMY AT BEST.
IT MATTERS NOT WHO LEADS THEM,
MY PLAN WILL LEAVE THEM
BEGGING FOR MERCY.
A BOON I SHALL DENY THEM.
- Takenaka:
WE HAVE ARRANGED FOR MOTONARI
TO ATTACK THE SOUTHERN TIP
OF THE COUNTRY, MILORD.
- MORI VENTURING OUTSIDE OF AKI
IS A RARE EVENT INDEED.
EASIER FOR HIM TO BETRAY US
WHILE PLAYING THE PART
OF THE FAITHFUL ALLY.
- Takenaka:
AS SOON AS WE CRUSHED CHOSOKABE,
DEAR MOTONARI LOST NO TIME
IN ABDUCTING THE ENGINEERS
WHO'D BUILT THE FUGAKU
AND BROUGHT THEM TO AKI.
MAKING SURE BOTH LAND
AND SEA ROUTES
WERE HEAVILY GUARDED,
HE MOBILIZED HIS ENTIRE NAVY.
TURNING EVERY REMNANT
OF HIS FOE'S TECHNOLOGY
TO THE TASK OF SALVAGING
THE FUKAGU'S REMAINS.
WIN OR LOSE
ON THE BEACHES OF SATSUMA,
MOTONARI LIKELY INTENDS
TO ATTACK US IN OSAKA.
AS SOON AS THE FORTRESS
HAS BEEN RESURRECTED.
- THAT, MILORD, IS WHEN WE
SHALL SEIZE IT FROM HIM.
- Toyotomi:
SO THE SAFETY OF HIS OWN DOMAIN
WAS NEVER MORI'S ONLY OBJECTIVE.
- Takenaka: HE'S STILL
AN ISOLATIONIST AT HEART.
BUT HE'S CLEVER ENOUGH TO SEE
WHICH WAY THE WIND IS BLOWING.
PREDICTING THAT OUR CONQUEST
WOULD BE THE DEATH OF HIM,
NOW HE'S RESOLVED TO CONQUER
THE COUNTRY HIMSELF.
- HE SEEKS TO UNITE
THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN?
HE'S A FOOL, SUCH GOALS
ARE BEYOND HIM.
- HOW TRUE.
NOW, AS TO
THE FINISHING TOUCHES--
- YES, WE WILL MOVE
OUR BASE OF OPERATIONS
TO ODIWARA AND UNIFY THE EAST.
- WE HAVEN'T YET ASCERTAINED
WHO'S LEADING THAT ARMY
AT THE SOUTHERN TIP.
OUR INTELLIGENCE
HAS BEEN LACKING.
BUT GIVEN THAT TAKEDA MEN
WERE SEEN GALLOPING SOUTHWEST,
LORD SHINGEN SEEMS
READY TO STAND WITH SATSUMA
AND HELP THEM REPEL ANY ATTACK
WE MIGHT MOUNT AGAINST THEM.
THE TIGER OF KAI
DOESN'T DEAL IN HALF MEASURES.
WE IGNORE THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF THIS AT OUR OWN PERIL.
WE MUSTN'T BE PUT
ON THE DEFENSIVE.
- IN TIME, WE WILL TAKE
MORI'S FORTRESS
AND USE IT TO BEND
THE ENTIRE WORLD TO OUR WILL.
BUT FOR NOW, THE THREAT OF IT
WILL DEFEND OSAKA IN MY ABSENCE.
THE EAST WILL NOT
DARE RISE AGAINST ME.
OUR PREPARATIONS IN THE NORTH
AND TO THE NORTHERN SIDE
OF KYUSHU ARE COMPLETE.
- I'LL TAKE COMMAND
OF THE FORTRESS, LORD.
LEAD OUR MEN INTO BATTLE KNOWING
THAT ALL IS AS IT SHOULD BE.
- I CAN ALWAYS DEPEND
ON YOU, HANBEI.
MANY THANKS.
- Takenaka:
I'M SORRY, HIDEYOSHI.
THIS HAS TAKEN LONGER
THAN I HAD THOUGHT.
SOON WE WILL TRIUMPH,
AND THE LAND OF THE RISING SUN
WILL SIT CONQUERED
IN THE PALM OF YOUR HAND.
- ( grunting )
DAMN YOU, TIME.
YOU'RE THE ONE FOE
I CAN'T SEEM TO OUTWIT.
- HIDEYOSHI...
- HEY, MAEDA KEIJI, WAKE UP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I'VE COME WITH A MESSAGE
FROM MY LORD KENSHIN.
TRY AS YOU MIGHT
TO STAY NEUTRAL,
TOYOTOMI WILL BE
YOUR FOE ONE DAY.
MAKE OF THIS MESSAGE
WHAT YOU WILL
AND DEAL WITH THIS DILEMMA
HOWEVER YOU BEST SEE FIT.
BISHAMONTEN IS A GOD OF BATTLE,
BUT HIS DIVINE PROTECTION
REACHES FAR BEYOND
THOSE WHO RUSH EAGERLY
INTO CONFLICT.
- TELL HIM, "THANKS."
- YOUR UNCLE TOSHIIE
HAS LEFT FOR BATTLE.
- HUH?!
- IT SEEMS HE WANTS TO AID
IN THE DEFENSE OF ECHIGO.
- BUT WHY?
IF HE DOES THAT--
- I GUESS HE COULDN'T BEAR
TO SIT BACK
AND DO NOTHING AT ALL.
- I CAN'T LET HIM.
TOSHIIE'S STILL HURT
FROM BEFORE,
HE'LL GET HIMSELF KILLED!
- MY LORD KENSHIN HAS
NO INTENTION OF WAGING WAR.
HE'S MOVING TROOPS
AS A DIVERSION.
WITH ANY LUCK, IT'LL GIVE TAKEDA
A CHANCE TO TAKE BACK ODIWARA.
- BUT STILL--
- HURRY, MAEDA KEIJI,
TIME IS SHORT!
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN TOYOTOMI
VENTURES FORTH.
THIS HAS TO BE PAINFUL
FOR YOU, I KNOW.
BUT YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO IT.
- KASUGA...
- YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO SIMPLY WANTS
TO LIVE IN PEACE.
- YUMEKICHI?
- Chosokabe: SO THEN,
HOW BEST TO SKEWER THEM?
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
- WE COULD SPLIT UP.
WE COULD SEND ONE GROUP
OUT TO WAKASA
AND THE OTHER ONE TO YAMASHIRO.
- NICE.
- GOOD THINKING.
- IT'S SETTLED THEN.
YOU PIRATES LAUNCH
A SURPRISE ATTACK IN WAKASA
TO DISTRACT THEM,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON
WILL FINISH THEM OFF
IN YAMASHIRO.
- ALRIGHT, YOUR SONS-OF-BITCHES
WILL HIT THEM
WITH A SURPRISE BROADSIDE
IN WAKASA,
THE OGRE OF THE WESTERN SEA
LANDS THE COUP DE GRACE!
- ( both )
HANG ON, WHAT?!
- WHERE YOU GET OFF TELLING US
TO BE THE DAMN BAIT?
- OH, SO WE'RE THE CHUM?
- HOLD ON NOW,
EVERYONE CHILL.
- DOES IT REALLY MATTER
WHO THE BAIT IS?
- ( both )
YOU BET YOUR ASS!
- WHAT'S IT SAY?
- IT'S FROM MATSUNAGA HISAHIDE.
- WHAT?
- ( theme music plays )
- Mori: ALL IS IN ACCORDANCE
WITH MY CALCULATIONS.
MY PAWNS NOW COVER THE BOARD.
READY TO FIGHT AND DIE
BY MY COMMAND.
WHEN THE NEXT SUN RISES,
BE SURE TO WITNESS FOR YOURSELF
THE CUNNING THAT I,
ITS CHILD, DISPLAY.