- Narrator: THE SENGOKU PERIOD,
A TIME OF CHAOS AND BLOODSHED.
WHEN THE BATTLE CRIES OF
THOUSANDS OF BRAVE WARRIORS,
RANG OUT ACROSS THE LAND.
SOME WERE DRIVEN BY AMBITION,
OTHERS BURNED WITH LOFTY IDEALS.
SOME SOUGHT TO DEFEND
JUSTICE AND PRIDE,
WHILE OTHERS,
HAD MORE TANGIBLE GOALS.
THEIR EYES FIXED SOLELY
ON A DISTANT PRIZE,
WAITING FOR THEM TO CONQUER.
- ( theme song playing )
- Narrator: DATE MASAMUNE,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON OF OSHU,
USING A CLEVER PLAN DEVISED
BY HIS RIGHT-HAND MAN,
LURED THE HOJO ARMY
INTO THE ADVANCING TAKEDA ARMY.
DATE THEN HEADED FOR SURUGA
TO BRING DOWN IMAGAWA YOSHIMOTO.
ON SHINGEN'S ORDERS,
SANADA YUKIMURA PURSUES
DATE AND HIS ARMY
IN ORDER TO STOP THEM.
- YOU ARE A BOLD MAN,
LORD MASAMUNE.
YOU'LL FIND SO AM I.
- A ONE-EYED DRAGON WILL BITE
OFF THE HEAD OF IMAGAWA.
- ( sighs )
- Uesugi: DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
OR WAS THERE SOMETHING ELSE
YOU WANTED TO ASK?
- I... FORGIVE ME,
LORD KENSHIN.
I DID NOT INTEND TO...
- THE REASON TAKEDA AND
I DID NOT CROSS SWORDS
AT KAWANAKAJIMA, WAS TO
AVOID THE NEEDLESS CASUALTIES
A THREE-WAY BATTLE WITH DATE
WOULD HAVE BROUGHT US BOTH.
FURTHERMORE, THERE WAS
THE TIGER OF KAI'S
YOUNG CUB TO CONSIDER,
AND THE WORTHY RIVAL HE FOUND,
THE ONE-EYED DRAGON,
DATE MASAMUNE.
THE FURY OF THEIR
BLAZING AMBITION
AND THE PURITY OF
THEIR FIGHTING SPIRIT
MADE OUR HEARTS SWELL
WITH HONOR AND PRIDE.
- SUCH THOUGHTS
HAD NOT OCCURRED TO ME.
AND TAKEDA SHINGEN,
FELT THE SAME WAY?
- I EXPECT SO.
- WITHOUT EXCHANGING A WORD?
- A GRAND QUIRK OF FATE.
FORTUNATE IS THE MAN
WHO FINDS SUCH A RIVAL
WITHIN THE SPAN
OF HIS FLEETING LIFE.
- TAKEDA HAS MOBILIZED TO LAUNCH
AN ATTACK ON IMAGAWA, MY LORD.
- WE MUST...
- WE MUST ENSURE OTHERS
NEITHER STRIKE AT HIS LANDS
DURING HIS ABSENCE.
NOR ATTACK HIM FROM THE REAR.
WE SHALL HAVE TO REMAIN
EVER VIGILANT, KASUGA.
- WHY DO YOU NOT CONSIDER THIS
TO BE A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY?
- I HAVE TWO WISHES. FOR A
FAIR BATTLE WITH TAKEDA,
INTO WHICH I MAY POUR
MY HEART AND SOUL.
AND FOR THE ETERNAL PEACE
AND PROSPERITY OF ECHIGO.
THAT IS WHY NOT.
- LORD KENSHIN.
( gasping )
- KASUGA.
BE MY EYES AS TAKEDA
TAKES SUNPU.
USE IT AS A CHANCE TO SCOUT
NEIGHBORING LANDS' ACTIVITIES.
- SIR!
- IN PARTICULAR, WATCH
THE MOVEMENTS OF ODA IN OWARI.
- I UNDERSTAND, LORD KENSHIN.
- MAY BISHAMONTEN'S
DIVINE PROVIDENCE BE WITH YOU.
MY MOST BEAUTIFUL BLADE.
- ( moaning )
- ( yawning )
WE DO SO HATE TO TRAVEL.
( snoring )
- Man: LORD YOSHIMOTO.
LORD YOSHIMOTO.
THIS MOST CERTAINLY BE NOT
THE TIME FOR NAPPING.
- THE LORD DOTH NOT "NAP".
- MY LIEGE, PLEASE FORGIVE
MY IMPERTINENCE.
AS YOU ARE AWAKE,
I SHALL DELIVER MY REPORT
WITH ALL DUE HASTE.
- IT MATTERS NOT.
DO AS YOU SEE FIT.
- BUT THIS IS A MATTER
OF GREAT IMPORTANCE.
I CANNOT MAKE
THIS DECISION ALONE.
- HMM?
WE SUPPOSE THE FOOL OF OWARI
HAS COME TO SURRENDER?
- THAT'D BE UH...WOULDST BE
MOST IMPLAUSIBLE, SIR.
- SO, HATH RIGHTEOUS VICTORY
BEEN CLAIMED?
MARVELOUS!
ONWARD TO THE CAPITAL!
- ( bird chirping )
- UH, YOUR EMINENCE.
WE ARE STILL MAKING OUR WAY
TO THE BATTLEFIELD.
- WHAT IS IT THEN?
SKIES ARE CLEAR.
AND WE HAVE ENJOYED
OUR NOONDAY MEAL, HAVE WE NOT?
- 'TIS TRUE, WISE LORD, AND YOUR
ARMY MAKES FINE PROGRESS,
BUT AN UNKNOWN FORCE
APPROACHES WITH DUE HASTE,
SET TO ATTACK US FROM THE REAR.
- ( gasping )
- ( horses approaching )
- Imagawa: OH, DEAR.
- ( gasping )
- ( laughing )
- ( screaming ) WHY DID YOU
NOT TELL ME THIS SOONER?
- ( men screaming )
- 'KAY, BOYS! YOU READY?
- All: YEAH!
- Date: HERE WE GO!
- NOW! BREAK!
- ( shouting )
- ( screaming )
- ( stammering )
MEN, HURRY,
FORM UP ON ME.
PROTECT YOUR LORD.
JUST SLAY THOSE MEN RIGHT NOW!
- ( men shouting )
- ( grunting )
- OH, DEAR! OH, DEAR! OH, DEAR!
- NO MERCY.
- OH, DEAR.
( gasping )
( stammering )
STAY AWAY FROM ME.
DO YOU NOT KNOW WHO I AM?
- OLD MAN IMAGAWA, RIGHT?
- UH...
- I'M THE BIG BOSS OF OSHU,
DATE MASAMUNE.
SORRY. YOU GOT SOMETHING I NEED.
- ( stammering ) MEN!
PROTECT YOUR LORD. TO ARMS,
I SAY. SLAY THIS MAN.
DO SOMETHING!
- IF YOU'RE THEIR COMMANDER,
FACE ME MAN-TO-MAN.
- ( whimpering )
- Sanada: HOLD!
- ( horses approaching )
- LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- ( gasping )
- MY LORD HAS SET HIS SIGHTS
UPON THE CAPITAL.
SURUGA IS A KEY STEP
ON THAT PATH.
I CANNOT ALLOW YOU TO BRING DOWN
IMAGAWA YOSHIMOTO.
- ( scoffing ) YOUR FRIENDS ARE
IN DANGER OF HAVING A HOLE
PUNCHED IN THEIR
FLANK BY HOJO.
SO I COMMEND YOU
FOR COMING AFTER ME.
- TAKEDA WILL NOT WAVER.
HOJO IS A TRIFLE.
- ( laughing ) YOU'RE NOT
PAYING ATTENTION.
EVEN THE TIGER OF KAI'S HEAD
WILL BE MINE EVENTUALLY.
YOU GET IT NOW?
NO MATTER HOW GREAT
THE FOE HE FACES,
MY LORD ACCEPTING DEFEAT
IS AN IMPOSSIBILITY.
EVEN I, THE TIGER'S YOUNG CUB,
HAVE NO INTENTION OF
FALLING ON THIS BATTLEFIELD.
NOT WHILE UNFINISHED BUSINESS
STILL REMAINS.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
FOR IMAGAWA'S HEAD,
SANADA YUKIMURA.
- I WISH NOTHING MORE.
- KOJURO, YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
- SIR! NO INTERFERENCE,
WHATSOEVER.
- ONE-EYED DRAGON,
DATE MASAMUNE,
I FIGHT YOU WITH HONOR!
- WOW, DEJA VU.
- ( both screaming )
- COLOR ME IMPRESSED.
- ( both grunting )
- ( groaning )
- ( grunts )
THE TIME, MEN, IS NOW!
LET US TAKEODAWARA CASTLE!
- ( men cheering )
- EVERYONE, FOLLOW ME!
- ( men shouting )
- FOR GLORY!
- ( screaming )
- ( men groaning )
- Hojo: YOU? THE TIGER OF KAI?
I WAS TOLD IT WAS
OSHU'S DATE MASAMUNE
WHO WAS RANGED AGAINST
THE HOJO FAMILY.
- IF YOUR GUARD IS DOWN,
NO ATTACK SHOULD
COME AS A SURPRISE.
REGARDLESS OF BY WHOM.
IN THIS TIME OF CHAOS
AND BLOODSHED,
I HAD HOPED THE TAKEDA
AND THE HOJO
WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO FORGE AN ALLIANCE
WHICH COULD BENEFIT
BOTH OF OUR DOMAINS.
- SO INSTEAD, YOU WOULD
ATTACK ME?
THOSE WHO OPPRESS THE ELDERLY
DIE MISERABLE DEATHS.
YOU WILL SHOW ME RESPECT!
- ALAS, I CANNOT.
FOR I DID NOT SEE YOU,
THEIR COMMANDER,
UPON THE FIELD OF BATTLE.
- MANY GOOD MEN
HAVE FALLEN, UJIMASA.
- ( gasping ) FOR THAT,
GENERATIONS OF
HOJO GLORY WILL NOT
BE TARNISHED
BY THE LIKES OF YOU!
I WILL GIVE UP THE CASTLE
OF MY HONORED ANCESTORS,
TO NO ONE!
- YOUR MEN ARE YOUR CASTLE.
THOSE BRAVE WARRIORS
WERE TOO GOOD,
FOR A SELF-SERVING LORD
SUCH AS YOU.
- YOU SPEAK RUBBISH!
- ( grunts )
- ( laughing )
NOW, SHINGEN, FACE THE
LEGENDARY NINJA, FUMA KOTARO.
STAND PARALYZED
AS FEAR TAKES ITS GRIP.
BEFORE YOU PERISH
AT THE POWER OF THE HOJO.
- Takeda: IS THIS THE BEST
YOU HAVE LEFT?
A SILENT MERCENARY.
- ( both grunting )
- OH DEAR. GAMBLING
WITH OUR LIFE
AS THOUGH IT WERE A
MEANS OF ENTERTAINMENT.
THIS IS MORE THAN
OUR HONOR CAN BEAR.
SINCE IT HAS COME TO THIS...
- Date: DEATH FANG,
BLAZING WHEEL!
- ( rumbling )
- ( man gasping )
- I... WE MUST RETREAT.
READY THE DECOYS.
- Takeda: TORIYA!
( grunting )
( scoffing ) I HAVE ALREADY
DECIPHERED YOUR EVERY MOVE!
( grunting )
- ( exclaims ) CONFOUND YOU.
I SWEAR, YOU WILL NOT
TAKE ME, SHINGEN.
ON MY HONOR AS A HOJO,
I WILL DEFEAT YOU!
- GOOD, UJIMASA,
A FINE SHOW OF SPIRIT.
- HONORED ANCESTORS,
LEND YOUR STRENGTH TO ME!
- ( howling )
- HE CALLS FORTH THE GHOSTS
OF HIS ANCESTORS?
- ( screaming )
- ( grunting )
- HONORED ANCESTORS!
- THE LIGHT OF BYGONE GLORY.
IS EVER DIMMED BY THE TINGE
OF MELANCHOLY.
THE FAINT DREAMS OF YESTERDAY.
SURELY, WILL LIVE TOMORROW.
SO, YUKIMURA,
HOW FARES YOUR BATTLE?
- THE TIGER OF KAI.
UPON MY LORD'S MIND,
HIS PRESENCE WEIGHS TOO HEAVILY.
- ( explosion )
- ( gasping )
SARUTOBI SASUKE,
EXPLAIN YOURSELF!
- MY, MY, AREN'T YOU
ALL WORKED UP?
I COULD SENSE YOUR BLOOD LUST
FROM EIGHT LEAGUES OUT.
IT'S MY LORD COMMANDER'S HEAD
YOU WANT, YES?
AND I WAGER THE ORDERS
WERE "SCOUTING ONLY".
BUT TO MAKE
AN UNSANCTIONED KILL?
WHAT WOULD YOUR SHINOBI
MASTERS SAY ABOUT THAT?
- WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW, RAT?
- LOOK, ALL I'M SAYING IS,
IN THIS DAY AND AGE,
NO GOOD EVER COMES OF DOING
MORE THAN YOU'RE PAID TO DO.
- YOU KNOW I CAN NEVER
RETURN TO MY VILLAGE.
- YOU CAN ONLY BLAME YOURSELF
FOR THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, DARLING,
DATE CAUSED MY LORD SOME DELAY.
- HE'S CURRENTLY IN ODAWARA.
- WHAT?
- AS I RECALL,
A LEGENDARY NINJA RESIDES THERE
IN HOJO'S EMPLOY.
( chuckles ) IT'S A SHAME,
I THINK HE'S ABOUT TO
LOSE HIS LIVELIHOOD.
OH, HEY!
WHY DON'T WE SEND HIM
OVER TO UESUGI?
THEN YOU CAN COME WITH ME
AND WORK FOR TAKEDA.
IT'S A LOT OF FUN.
- ENOUGH! YOU MOCK MY PAIN!
- ( rain pattering )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( Date sighing )
GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU,
BEST PARTY I'VE
BEEN TO IN FOREVER.
MY LORD,
MY HEART CONCURS,
FOR THE TIGER OF KAI'S YOUNG CUB
HAS NEVER BURNED SO BRIGHTLY
UPON THE FIELD OF BATTLE.
- Katakura: BOSS MASAMUNE!
- ( chuckling )
- Date: SHIT.
- THERE ARE THREE LORD IMAGAWAS?
- ( horses neighing )
- Date: KOJURO!
- ON IT.
- ( urging horse )
- WE'LL LEAVE THE REST
TO YOU, BOYS.
- ( men cheering )
- ( urging horse )
- ( whooshing )
- HUH?
( screaming )
- ( grunting )
- ( arrow whooshing )
- ( Man groaning )
- Katakura: A CHILD?
- DARN IT. I GOT A FAKE ONE.
- "LUCK LIES IN THE LEFTOVERS".
OR SO THEY SAY, MASTER.
- SASUKE!
- I WOULD HAVE TO RECOMMEND
YOU ABANDON THIS PURSUIT, SIR.
THE ODDS ARE TWO-TO-ONE
YOU'LL COME UP WITH A LOSER.
- BUT HE COULD BE THE ONE.
- WE'VE BEEN TOO RECKLESS.
ODA TOOK KITABATAKE WITH EASE.
BUT INSTEAD OF RETURNING
TO OWARI,
HE'S NOW LYING IN WAIT
FOR IMAGAWA.
IF WE KEEP GOING...
- ( gasping )
- SORRY, FAKER,
YOU'RE OF NO USE TO ME.
- ( gunshot )
- NOR IS THE REAL ONE,
TO BE HONEST.
- Sanada: YOU! WOMAN!
WHO... UNDER WHOSE BANNER DO YOU
WIELD SUCH WESTERN WEAPONRY?
- CAREFUL YOU DON'T GET BURNED,
LITTLE BOY.
- ( urging horse )
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- ( laughing )
IT WOULD APPEAR THE RUSE
HAS FOUND ITS END.
THE HEAD OF IMAGAWA IS MINE.
- Imagawa: ( gulping ) OH, DEAR.
- YOU DARE PLAY ME FOR A FOOL?
- ( laughing )
- ( horse neighing )
- ( straining )
- ( explosion )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- BOSS MASAMUNE!
THAT'S...
- LOOK. THOSE MUST BE
ODA NOBUNAGA'S FORCES.
- UH, MASTER? SIR?
- LORD ODA NOBUNAGA,
SO-CALLED DEVIL KING OF OWARI.
MY NAME IS
SANADA GENJIRO YUKIMURA.
I AM THE VASSAL OF TAKEDA,
TIGER OF KAI!
- DO ME A FAVOR.
KEEP IT DOWN, WOULD YOU?
HE'S GOT ME PINNED.
WITH HIS DAMN GAZE.
- ( gasping )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( gun shot )
- ( gasping )
- DEVIL KING
OF THE SIXTH HEAVEN.
- Date: ODA NOBUNAGA.
- ( theme song playing )
- Keiji: LIFE IS SHORT, MY GOOD
PEOPLE. FIND LOVE WHERE YOU CAN.
RATHER THAN THE FIRES
OF BLOODY CONQUEST,
LET US SET ABLOOM
THE FLOWERS OF LOVE.
NEXT TIME, I, MAEDA KEIJI,
WILL SHOW YOU THE LIGHT!