Even if rain falls,
I won't worry...
if spears come flying down,
Whatever happens, I won't worry.
You know, Eila...
That's dangerous;
you should use your shield.
What...? Haven't you been
paying any attention...?
This is how I do it.
Whoa...! Big, whoa!
Is that all?
Yep, it looks
like we got them...
Seems a bit too easy,
though, doesn't it?
We've taken care
of all the little ones,
but I haven't been able to
find their main controller yet.
Do you think it's still active?
Are you sure we didn't
blow that sucker up already?
Don't the small ones disappear
once the main ship is destroyed?
What is that?
Look, it goes straight
up through the clouds!
Creepy.
No way... Don't tell
me that's the main one.
Wait here... I'll be right back!
Major!
It just keeps going.
There's the core.
I can't go higher.
This is not good.
Temporary retreat...
We're returning to base.
But we haven't eliminated
the enemy yet...
We'll rethink our plan
once we've returned...
Everyone has been out
for too long today...
We need to head back before
we run out of magic energy.
Hey, what's that?
What's what?
Is it a twig or something?
Why are you annoying me?
It's nothing.
Where did you find it...?
And why do you even
have it to begin with?
Why do you care? Leave me alone.
Well, can I at least see it?
I'm just curious, that's all.
Good grief... You fly so fast...
How do you move
around so quickly like that?
Easy; I just use my magic
to see the future...
I have the ability to predict
everyone's movements...
It can be an enemy...
or even you...!
If you wanna be like me,
you need to find some speed!
You really haven't been
paying attention, have you?
I don't mean to
brag or anything,
but I've never even used
a shield during combat.
If you ask me, people
who rely on those things
will always be second-rate.
Don't say that!
People keep telling me my shield
is my only redeeming quality!
You know you shouldn't
say things like that, Eila.
Welcome back, everyone.
Thank you!
Hey, Sanya!
I guess you have
night patrol now, huh?
That's right.
Hold on, Sanya.
There's no need tonight.
Return to base with us.
Yes, ma'am.
Central Command
contacted us earlier.
About this latest
Neuroi incident?
That's right...
Romagna's navy and
air force want in...
They're going to
take over from here.
Apparently, they
want results, too.
I guess we'll sit back
and see how it goes.
It must be hard for
you to carry something
this big around all
the time, huh, Sanya?
No. I'm used to it.
She needs to carry it
because she gets solo night
patrol duty every day.
If anything were to happen,
she could easily hold her own
in a fight with
this Flieger-Hammer.
Really...?
That's so incredible, Sanya.
You know... I bet it's better
when someone's with you.
That way it doesn't
get so lonely.
That's true.
Oh... I almost forgot. Ta-da!
Hey...! The twig.
From a needle-leaf tree...?
Maybe?
Here you go... for you.
You're giving her a twig?
Wow!
Thank you so much, Eila!
We flew near a
cypress forest today,
so I couldn't resist getting it.
The forest looked a little
like Orussia in the winter;
you would've loved it.
There were a lot
of cypress trees
by the house I used to live in.
How sweet!
That's so nice of her!
These photos were
taken by air force recon.
It kinda looks like a scratch
in the film, doesn't it?
You're looking at the Neuroi
that appeared earlier today...
This is a complete shot of it.
Its estimated length is
over thirty thousand meters.
Thirty thousand?!
You mean it's thirty
kilometers tall?!
That's a lot... Compared
to Mt. Fuji, it's like...
It seems to be
headed towards Rome
at approximately ten
kilometers per hour...
It's not traveling fast.
The biggest problem we'll have
is the location of its core.
Right here.
The very top?
Yes. I actually saw it up
there with my own eye.
But the highest our
Striker Units can go
is only ten thousand meters...
And even that's pushing it.
Yes. That's why our
plan will utilize these.
Rocket boosters.
Will those let us fly all the
way up to where the core is?
No, I seriously doubt
it's as simple as that.
You're right.
The boosters are very powerful,
but they can only fly
for a short period of time
because of the enormous
amounts of energy they consume.
Then why don't we carry
someone part of the way...?
They can just boost
up from there, right?
Yes. Exactly.
Still, thirty thousand
meters high is gonna be rough.
There's not even
any air up there.
What?! Why isn't there air?
You won't be able to
hear anyone then, either.
Oh yeah! That's true, too.
What?! You can't hear anything?
We're talking about
an ultra-high altitude.
One that far surpasses
normal human limits.
It's completely unknown.
Yes, but there's nothing
Witches can't do...
We should all be okay.
Now, we're going to need someone
with instantaneous wide
range attack capabilities...
Sanya...
I would like you
to attack the core.
An attack with your
Flieger-Hammer launcher
will be indispensable
to this particular mission.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I think I should go with her!
Oh, do you, Eila...?
I have a question...
How many times have you
raised a shield in battle?
A shield...?
Yeah, I don't mean
to brag or anything,
but I have never used a
shield in actual combat before.
You can't do it then.
Right...! I can't then!
In this case...
you're just not up to it.
What...? Well, why not?
Besides the use of
boosters in this plan...
surviving the harsh
environment will also consume
an enormous amount
of magic energy...
And that's all before the
attack even takes place.
Which will unfortunately leave
Sanya unable to protect herself.
She'll need someone
to serve as her shield
and keep her out of harm's way.
Okay... I can do that.
I mean it's not like
I can't create a shield.
But you've never used
one in actual combat.
Right, I knew you'd understand!
That means you can't do it.
Miyafuji! You'll protect her!
Oh... Yes, ma'am.
You have the most
powerful shield here
and are the best
suited for this task.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me...
But I'd appreciate it if
you'd give me some more room.
I would if I could.
It's just cramped in here.
Why on Earth did you wanna meet
me in this stupid sauna, anyway?
Because you're always fighting
with Yoshika for some
weird reason, and...
you know, an enemy of
an enemy is a friend, right?
Yeah, I have no idea
what you're talking about...
Seriously though;
I need to get out of here...
I hate everything about saunas.
Get over it! I just need
you to help me out!
So, Sanya...
What are you doing?
Come on, you four-eyed freak!
You know what, I don't like
it when you call me that!
Umm...
Are you guys really
sure about this?
Yes, we're sure. Just do it.
Okay... but...
Now... Eila...
It's up to you to
pretend that I'm Sanya,
and protect me with your shield.
I can't pretend you're Sanya.
Are you really,
really sure about this?
Just shut up and do it!
Right...! Here goes!
Sorry...
Are you all right, Perrine?
Why did you dodge
the bullet like that...?!
You are defeating the whole
purpose of this training!
Totally my fault...
I just can't imagine
why I'd protect you.
Well, maybe because
I'm the only person
who's helping you right now?!
Gah...! Lynne, we're waiting.
So, whenever you're
ready, shoot me again!
I don't wanna.
Just do it!
Right...! Here goes!
You know...
I so understand
where Eila's coming from.
Yeah, I don't think
I could imagine
protecting Perinne, either.
How many times do
I have to tell you?!
Stop dodging and
use your shield!
Please can we stop!
I don't like this at all!
Weird... What's this?
That's your coat, silly.
It's cold in the
stratosphere, remember.
Oh, yeah... I haven't
worn this thing in forever.
So... how did it go?
Huh?
Your training... with Perrine?
Oh... I uh...
you knew about that?
Yeah, how did it go?
Not good... I'm awful.
Sorry.
Sanya? Are you taking all
of those scarves with you?
Oh no... Just one.
The other two are
for you... and Yoshika.
Miyafuji?
Yoshika didn't bring
anything with her from Fuso,
so I thought I'd lend her
one of mine... However...
I'm still hoping you'll learn
to use a shield, Eila...
Aren't you?
It's no use.
I guess there're some
things I'm not good at.
You mean...
You're gonna give up?
If I can't do it, I can't do it.
It doesn't matter
how hard I try.
But giving up is the whole
reason you can't do it!
Please don't quit now...
You're better than that.
Why don't you just
have Miyafuji protect you?
No need to worry
about her giving up!
Stop being so stupid!
You stop being so bossy!
Hey, Sanya!
Ow... That hurt...
You guys fought? That's funny.
I don't think it's
very funny at all.
Well... are you gonna do
anything about it, Sanya?
Whaddaya mean?
Yeah, guess an assignment's
an assignment.
I'm told a Romagna fleet
and air unit made contact
with the Neuroi this morning.
Sometime before dawn.
And the result?
Their own attack
ended up leaving the Zara
and Pola cruisers
completely crippled.
So I guess that
means we're up next.
That looks incredible
on you, Francesca!
But I'm hot.
Oh, come on--quit complaining...
The stratosphere is,
like, stupid cold, you know!
I hate it when it's stupid cold.
Here. These are a must-have
for any high altitude season!
I'm hot.
Um, Captain Barkhorn's
coat's a little big on me,
don't ya think?
So what? You'd rather
freeze to death instead?
Did you make those, Lynne?
Yes, I tried fixing
some ginger tea for us.
It's supposed to
warm up the body.
Really...? Thank you.
I added lots of sugar, so it
would be easier to drink...
I, uh, hope you all like it.
Grody.
Come on... It's actually
better than I figured...
Oh, I love it!
Um... it gets better if
you give it just a little bit.
If you think about it like
you're taking medicine,
it's not that bad at all.
Hi, my name is Yoshika, and
I like to wear Sanya's scarf.
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
First...
we'll utilize Launch Team One,
consisting of five members.
They will climb to ten thousand
meters using normal propulsion.
Once we've reached
our maximum altitude,
Launch Team One will break away
from the rest of the group.
Launch Team Two will then
immediately ignite
their rocket boosters...
They will carry the strike
team, Miyafuji and Sanya,
to twenty thousand meters.
When that height is reached,
Yoshika and Sanya will then
ignite their booster rockets.
They will proceed
to climb even higher,
to thirty-three thousand, three
hundred thirty-three meters,
where the Neuroi
core is located.
At that point, they'll
switch to a ballistic flight
and head for the core.
Do you know how
cold it is up there...?
Negative seventy
degrees Celsius...
With no air, too...
Without magic,
they'd both die instantaneously.
Although, there's
still no guarantee
they'll come back alive.
Okay, it's time!
Let me go! I can do it!
I swear I can!
I'll be the one
to protect Sanya!
What are you doing, Eila?
Please! You said it yourself...!
Giving up is the
reason I can't do it!
Remember? I'm not going
to give up! Not on you!
I'm going to protect you, Sanya!
Yoshika!
I got you...! Are you ready?
You can't, Eila!
Your magic won't last!
You won't be able to come back!
Don't worry. I can
bring her back down.
I'll bring you back. I promise.
Those two have to
be completely crazy!
Go girls! Get it! Together!
Can you hear me at all?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
No. I should apologize, too.
Hey, look over there!
It's Orussia...
Oh yeah...
It's almost like I can
reach the Ural Mountains.
Do you want to
keep flying past them
and see what's
on the other side?
Okay. As long as I'm
with you, I can go anywhere.
I was kidding. I'm sorry.
We have a home... And we get
to go back there... together.
I think I finally understand
where she's coming from...
I know what it's like
to wanna protect someone
more than anything.
Emergency alert!
It appears someone has
infiltrated the base!
All hands, conduct
a search immediately!
On the next Strike Witches Two:
Oh... "It's All Creepy Crawly".