Not much longer until
this elementary school
is finally finished...
All right!
Just look at it... The village
has come a long way.
It's unbelievable...
and wonderful.
Perrine, I have a question.
Sure, what is it, honey?
It's just my friends can't
come to school with me anymore.
Really? And why not?
Come and see!
That's why.
The bridge...
Yeah... my friends can't come
over here because it got broken.
Heads up, girls!
Everyone! Prepare for battle!
Yes, ma'am!
She's climbing so quickly!
Don't get too far ahead of us!
My turn!
The bridge!
Don't worry about it.
The damage is minimal...!
Stay in formation!
Get back here!
For that little trick,
you'll pay...!
Wow... She's mad!
Now's our chance!
All units, attack!
Yes, ma'am!
I can see the core.
What kinda stupid jerk
hurts an innocent bridge?!
You did it!
Way to go!
Congrats... Wonderful work.
You all performed well.
I think you're
getting accustomed
to the Shinden, Miyafuji.
Thanks...! But I still need
to train a whole lot more
if I plan on mastering it.
That's a great attitude!
Perrine!
What...?! Oh... yes, ma'am?
You fought
especially well today.
Oh... Yes, thank you very much.
Well that was weird.
Way weird.
Whaddaya mean?
Well come on, anytime
the Major praises her,
Perrine gets all like...
"Oh, Major...! I am
great... That's so true!"
"And please... keep
telling me how awesome I am!"
It's true.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
We had so many heirlooms...
I can't believe this is all
that's left of the Clostermanns.
The rapier... it's all I have...
But if I sold it...
I might be able to
get enough money
to rebuild the
bridge for those kids.
Mother... Father...
I don't know what I should do.
It's me, hello!
You scared me!
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Why are you in here...?!
You know you're supposed
to knock first, don't you?
Yes, but... the beach.
We're going to the beach
tomorrow, isn't that great!
Oh... yeah.
Yahoo!
Yay...! Hurry up, you guys!
Let's go, already!
Hold on...! Wait!
We have to do our
warm up exercises!
Splish splash!
Great! Now you made me get wet.
Listen up!
You must not hold back just
because it's a
training exercise!
But be careful...
It has been a while.
I hate this kind of training!
I don't even know what it's for.
Yes... Complete waste of time.
Hurry up and dive in!
This is such lovely weather.
Yeah, it is nice.
Oh! Impressive,
Perrine...! Good.
Thank you! I owe
it to your guidance.
Yes. You. Ma... jor...
Air!
Stop! You're going to drown me!
I almost died!
Exercise... complete!
I'm hungry...
I'm sleepy...
That was exhausting.
Yeah, but we haven't
trained in a while.
And thank goodness
you were there, Perrine!
What, so I could nearly drown?
I'm not thankful for that!
Honestly!
It's so pretty.
Are you okay, Perrine?
Hey, Francesca!
What are you doing?
Guess what! Guess what!
I found a box under the water!
What?! You did?
Yeah, it's like this big
and has a giant lock on it.
If you ask me,
it's a treasure chest!
Cool!
That's awesome!
Did she just say,
"treasure chest"?!
Well... if you think about it,
the Adriatic Sea has always
been an active area for trade...
Actually, it wouldn't
surprise me in the least
if there were more than one
of those treasure
chests down there.
That's so cool...!
I think we should
investigate...!
Don't you, Lynne?
Sure!
Wait a minute...!
You can't possibly
believe there's
an actual treasure
chest down there...
That's ridiculous!
But you just said
you thought there was!
I did not! I just said
it wouldn't surprise me.
That's totally different!
Oh no!
Lynne! Francesca...!
I gotta go too!
Hey! Why are they leaving?
I can't stay down
here much longer...
But... I need this treasure...
For the kids!
Tonnerre!
She's been down a long time...
Yeah, I'm getting worried.
Hopefully she didn't get eaten.
What?
Didn't you know...?
There're all kinds
of super dangerous,
eat-you-up creatures in the sea.
Like the giant squid...!
And giant sea cucumbers!
There are even giant starfish!
We have to find her
before they get her!
What if we're too late!
Neuroi!
Excuse me! Who are you
calling... a Neuroi?!
Oh... it's just Perrine.
Out of the way!
Wow, you really wanted
that treasure, huh?
Yes. I really did
want that treasure, huh.
She fainted; oh no!
Perrine...! Perrine!
Did you just hear something?
Nope.
I'm sorry you had
to wait so long!
Tada! May I present
your new bridge!
Thank you very much...!
You're the best, Perrine!
No, you are!
Perrine!
Can you hear me?!
Yes... I'm the greatest.
Good. You're okay!
We were so worried!
I bet there's something
really rich in here!
Come on, treasure box...
open up for me!
What do you think you're doing,
Ensign Francesca Lucchini?
I have already decided how that
treasure is going to be used!
Look...! It's open!
What the...?
That's another chest, isn't it?
Yeah...
This is good...
That just means the treasure
must be super mega
valuable, then...
I bet it's filled with silver,
gold, and even jewels!
Jeez, how many are there?
Every time we open one chest,
there's another one inside...
I want the stupid
treasure already!
Will you please
be quiet so I can think?
This one has to be
the last of them...
I'm going to open it.
It's empty.
Oh, the horror!
I can't believe it...
I guess there never
was a treasure...
Perfect... I can't help now...
Please... don't cry!
Yeah... it's just a treasure!
Ha...! Look...! A fort!
I see... You were hoping
you could fix the bridge
with the treasure, huh?
Oh, so that explains why
you were acting kind of
different after you
got back from Gallia.
Uh-huh... I thought maybe
this treasure would be
able to help them...
That's okay, though...
I can still sell my
family's last heirloom.
Last...? Oh.
Hey! This is making
a sound, guys!
Like what?
Like a sound...
If it's empty, why's it
making any noise at all?
Listen!
Oh! Something's there...!
Hey, give it to me!
There's a little shop
in my neighborhood
that makes secret
boxes like these.
I got it!
What's this paper?
It looks like a map...
You think so?
Yeah, it's a treasure map!
Here's the cave!
Amazing... The map
said it would be there!
Wow, you mean you can
read it...?! That's cool!
You know how to read Latin?
Yes. Every girl
from a decent family
should be well versed in Latin!
Wow!
You know what...? I'm really
glad you're happy again.
What nonsense...!
We need to get a move on...
Well...? Are you coming or not?
Right behind you!
Ready...? Let's go!
Right!
It's beautiful.
It's like a sparkling,
starry sky!
The sunlight coming through
the entrance is
reflecting off the water!
Who would've thought
it'd be so pretty?
This is amazing!
Hey, look! There're paths.
Which way?
It seems both of
them will lead us
further inside, but...
let's go to the left!
And which way is that?
If you don't wanna
get separated,
be quiet and follow me!
Oh, that left.
Francesca...? She's disappeared?
Yeah. She wanted to
look at fish, which I totally
have a problem with,
and she hasn't come back yet.
I bet she's with
Miyafuji's group;
they ran off after training...
We should probably check it out.
Yes. Let's go.
So pretty!
I love how the moss on the wall
just kind of glows like that...
Hey, can you see the map
in this light, Perrine?
Yeah? I hope you can...
You're the only one of us who
knows how to read that thing.
No pressure!
No pressure... Gee, thanks.
According to this, we'll be safe
if we just keep
going straight ahead.
Seriously?
Yeah...! So... shall we?
No! Perrine!
It looks like a pitfall!
It's a pit that I'm
falling in. That's for sure!
Don't worry!
We're not gonna let go!
Straight's not safe... at all.
Well?
It's still warm.
Someone was just here...
But apparently
they headed farther in.
Great. Which way did they go?
Maybe we should split up.
No. That would be
much too dangerous.
How about we go right?
Ugh... This is such
a pain in the caboose!
Nah--this is fun!
It's like we're explorers!
This is not a game!
The cave appears to be
man-made, doesn't it?
Ancient Witches used
to inhabit this area...
In fact our base actually lies
over some of their ruins...
I suppose this cave could
be an extension of them.
Huh.
Look at that...! What an
impressive looking jar.
This must be the work of
our early predecessors...
It's incredible.
And beautiful.
We're talking
about a jar, right?
Look out!
Major!
Major!!
What... what is this?!
Mio...! Mio!
Major!
Good job!
Mio! Say something
to me... Anything...! Mio!
Hold on...! You know what...
Smell it... What is that?
Well... it's sure not blood.
It's familiar.
Yeah.
It's wine.
Mio?
Banzai!
You there, Mio...?
It's me, Minna...
Um, can you hear me?
Of course... Hear this!
Um... Major?
I... Uh... Oh...
She's running away.
Major...! Wait!
I'm confused.
What do we do...? Oh no! Minna?
Uh, Minna's out cold.
Okay...?
Yeah... this is not good.
Caves are not supposed
to sound like that!
What if it's a monster?!
You guys! We have to hide!
Did you see that?
Yeah... A person?
It sounds like an
ancient evil spirit!
Like a ghost?
Let's go... home!
Maybe we should
just go, Perrine.
No way! I haven't come
all this way for nothing!
Hold on, treasure!
I'll be right there!
Perrine!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Don't leave me behind!
Aw, come on... Are we there yet?
Hang in there, Francesca!
Just a little farther!
I'd bet money it's
just beyond this light.
Ya think?
This place is huge!
It has to be the
treasure room on the map!
No question about it!
We've finally made it, everyone!
What a big statue...
It's as big as the giant
Buddha statue in Kamakura!
It's kinda scary, if you ask me.
On the other side.
Yes... That's where
the treasure should be.
We're so close
I can almost taste it!
Come on. Let's go!
Oh, cool...! A swordie!
Okay... Where are you...
You should be here!
Treasure...
The children need you!
Duh, duh-duh...! Ta-da...!
What do you think...? Thanks!
You look so cool!
Yeah, you look strong
and really fierce!
I think I might just
have to keep you... yep!
It's moving!
Look out, Perrine! Be careful!
I plan on it!
I won't give up!
Not until the bridge
gets built...! I can't!
Although I'm kind
of at a disadvantage,
unarmed like this...
What am I going to do now?
Perrine!
Father! Mother!
People of Gallia!
I shall not be beaten!
Tonnerre!
Wow, you got him!
Three cheers
for Perrine! Hooray!
Hooray! And cheers! Hooray!
You did it, Perrine!
Look... There's a door!
It's the treasure!
This is the treasure room?
It's just herbs...?
Cloves and bay leaves...
Oregano, saffron...
and that's pepper!
Please don't tell me
this is the treasure...
Perrine!
Major Sakamoto, what're
you doing inside of here?
Hey, so what are
you crying about?
Because...
Well... I spent
a really long time
looking for this treasure...
but it's just a
bunch of dumb spices...
I'm sure at one point
they must've been
worth a ton of money,
but now they're so easy to find,
they won't help at all...
And now I can't give anything
to the Gallia Restoration Fund.
But that's no reason to cry...
Your feelings are
what truly matter...
It's your love for Gallia
that is the real treasure.
I hope you can see
the truth in that.
Thank you, Major...
Hey...! The Major
found Francesca!
And Yoshika, and Lynne...!
Well...? Are you coming
or not, Hartmann?
She's so heavy...
What have you guys been doing?
Oh! Shirley!
You had us worried.
Wanna head back?
Sure.
I bet they were ancient ruins,
and the spells the Witches
put on the treasure
were still in place.
That's probably why the
plants were still alive...
And... it's probably why the
statue woke up and attacked you.
How obnoxious was
that statue, am I right?
Oh, yeah...! Here, Perrine.
This letter came for you.
Hey! It's from Gallia...
It's the kids...
The bridge!
Everyone must've helped fix it!
They worked together
to rebuild the bridge...
I guess we always had
the real treasure after all...
I'm so happy.
That's a relief, huh?
Yes. I need to help defeat
the Neuroi as
quickly as possible...!
That way I can return to Gallia!
We should go too, Lynne!
Sure...! Why not?!
Oh really...?
Well, then I'll be kind enough
to at least show
the two of you around.
Wow, thank you, Perrine!
I gotta a really bad sunburn.
I can't even put on my tights.
Interesting...
What a mysterious base...
On a side note...
Have you all seen Minna?
Hey, Hartmann!
How many aircraft
have you shot down?
One, two, three... I dunno...
On the next Strike Witches 2:
"Five Hundred Overs."
So, how many is that?