In the spring of 1945, a
new type of Neuroi suddenly
appeared in the
skies above Venezia...
Instantly, Fuso Witches Yoshika
Miyafuji and Mio Sakamoto left
for Europe to stand up to
this new, mysterious menace...
However, just
before their arrival,
a different Neuroi
appeared before the girls
and attacked, perhaps in
an attempt to delay them.
But will it work?
Neuroi confirmed...!
There...! At about
twelve thousand!
Damn it...!
I can't believe they've
extended their reach this far!
Hijikata!
Her magic energy
is stable now...
You've certainly
improved, Miyafuji
We need to move out...!
Let's drop altitude
and try to lose them!
Roger!
Where are you going?
How does it look?!
You think we can lose them?!
We're doin' everything
we can here!
Well keep trying!
What's happening?
You didn't think I was going to
lead us out there, did you...?
Not to worry...!
We're planning to evade for
now and wait for reinforcements.
Right!
Neuroi spotted...!
Straight ahead!
All ships to third
Battle Speed...!
Bear down... Neuroi spotted!
All ships to third
Battle Speed...! Mark!
Prepare for battle!
Commence fire!
Amazing... The Neuroi incendiary
shells are so powerful...!
Prepare to attack!
What's that?!
Ready, fire!
Did we get it?
Wow...
It's not going to be enough to
take down a Neuroi of that size.
From here it looks
like it's taking a hit,
but they won't be
able to reach its core!
It just took out a destroyer!
Sergeant...! Where are
the Romagna Witches?!
Not coming...!
I requested help from Romagna's
First Fighter Wing earlier,
but unfortunately we're now
outside of their flight range.
We're going to have to
figure something else out.
They got another one!
They're taking
too long to escape...!
They're like sitting ducks!
The Five Hundred and Fourth
Fighter Wing is close...
but they're unable to fight...
Yesterday's battle
wiped them out...!
And all other Witch units
will be at least thirty minutes.
We don't have thirty minutes...
At the rate we're going,
we'll be wiped out in five!
Are you serious?!
I'm ready, Hijikata!
Right!
Major...!
Major, are you hurt?!
It didn't hit me if that's
what you're asking...
But, my shield doesn't have
the strength that it used to.
I'm sorry.
How am I supposed to block
a Neuroi beam with that?
That's it...! Hijikata, I'll be
taking some time off soon.
I'm heading out!
Roger that...!
Prepare to launch striker!
Shiden Model
Fifty-Three is ready to go!
No. Wait! You can't!
Out of the way, Miyafuji!
No, ma'am...!
I know that you can't
create shields anymore!
You can't fly...!
I won't let you!
This certainly brings
back memories.
You tried to stop me
like this once before.
I'll be fine.
You don't have to worry...
I promise I have no intention
of losing my life out there.
Yeah, but...
It's true... I lost the
ability to use shields
when I turned twenty.
But I now have a newly repaired
Shiden Fifty-Three unit...
and this here.
I haven't forgotten
how you saved my life...
and I'm not going to throw
it away that easily...
You're just gonna have to
trust me... I am able to fight.
If that's the case,
then I have a request...
Will you let me fight
this battle with you?
Right...! Get ready
to go, Sergeant!
Right!
Miyafuji...! You take the lead
and draw the Neuroi away
from the Venezian fleet...!
I'll go after the core
and attack from the rear!
Got it!
Let's go...! Prepare flight!
Right...! Roger that!
Sakamoto!
I'm fine! It only
hit the liftoff unit...!
Look out...!
The next one's coming!
What was that?!
Wow...! Did you see
the size of her shield?!
Of course! That's
how powerful she is!
Major! I'm afraid the magic
charger's been damaged
and The Shiden-Kai
won't be able to fly!
Whaddaya mean?!
We want food! We want food!
We need supplies!
Yummy, yummy Fuso food!
You got me at Fuso food!
Can't wait to eat rice
with octopus carpaccio!
Then you lost me at 'octopus.'
Huh...?! Who doesn't like
octopus...? It's good!
What is wrong with you?
It's slimy and sticky and gross!
Slimy and sticky, you bet!
But not gross...
They make it wonderful!
It's times like this that
make me wonder who hurt you.
Calling all units!
Do you read me...!
This is Venenzian
First Squadron...!
We are currently locked
in combat with a Neuroi...!
Requesting immediate
assistance...!
Location, A-nine.
Sounds like we're
gonna have to hurry!
Roger that!
It's too dangerous, Major!
You're gonna have to be patient
and wait until the
Shiden-kai is repaired!
Do you realize how many
people will be hurt...?
The Neuroi aren't
going to wait for us.
I suppose you could
say I've caught something
from Sergeant Miyafuji.
The Venier has been
severely damaged...!
Engine output falling rapidly!
At this rate, it'll
be dead in the water!
Is there nothing we can do?
Commander...! There's a Witch!
You sure?
Who is that?!
A sun and moon emblem
with a white background...!
She's from Fuso!
A Fuso Witch?!
Hey you guys!
Did you hear the news?!
They've sent reinforcements!
What unit is she from?!
Wow!
I need you to move as far away
as you can while I distract it!
Negative...! We aren't going
to leave you here alone!
With all due respect,
sir, we don't have
any means of fighting
back at this point!
Yes, you're right...
Unfortunately we would
only get in the way...
I'm ordering all ships to bring
about a full speed retreat!
Thank goodness.
Please...!
Hurry and get out of here!
Major Sakamoto!
Ready...?! Attack straight on!
Roger!
Look out!
Major!
I've got this!
Reppuzan!
Sakamoto!
Sorry for the wait...
I would've arrived sooner,
but the Shiden-kai was damaged.
You could've
really hurt yourself.
Maybe. But I didn't, did I...?
I wasn't lying when I said
I didn't need a shield to fight.
As long as I have my
Reppumaru, I'm fine!
Wow... She's amazing.
I forget sometimes
how wonderful she is!
I'd like to know your opinion...
What do you think of "Reppumaru"
as a name for the sword...?
I spent all night trying to
come up with something fitting.
Oh... um... I don't know,
I guess it's pretty cool.
You guess...?
Pretty cool...? Thanks!
Shirley...! Look!
Yep... Those are Neuroi
fragments, all right.
Guess the Venezian fleet must've
beaten it, already...! Sweet!
Be careful, I'm still picking
up a Neuroi presence here.
Oh... You mean there
could still be more of them?
Very impressive, Major...!
Looks like you didn't need
the Shiden-kai after all!
Thanks, it was easy... Too easy.
It probably only feels that way
because you've gotten
so much stronger, lately.
I hope you're right, Sergeant.
Sakamoto, look over there!
Is the Neuroi regenerating now?!
It can't be.
The core's still alive!
I'm on it!
The core is in the tip of the
part that is regenerating...!
Just blast it open
and finish it off!
Right!
What...?! I see; so that's
its design...! Miyafuji...!
Listen up! The core is moving!
It's on the right tip now...!
Don't lose it!
I won't!
Damn! It's dodging her shots...!
And it's regenerating
quickly... This is bad!
Miyafuji...!
The core keeps moving
just before your shots hit...!
We're going to have to launch
multiple simultaneous attacks!
What do you mean by that?
You can't do it by yourself...!
Just hold on!
I'm coming to help you!
What's the status?!
About five more
minutes should do it!
I just need it to fly...!
You have three minutes left!
Major, be careful!
Hang on...! Her magic energy
is being pushed to its limit.
I don't know how much
longer I can keep going...
but I have to protect them!
What is she doing?!
You won't last...! Come back!
I found it!
No!
Sergeant, look...! Behind you!
Miyafuji!
Shield... have to put it up...
but can't move. Huh?
No way!
Nice timing!
Yahoo!
Is that you, Shirley?!
Yoshika, ciao!
Hi, Francesca!
Did you see that...?!
Every single one of
my shots hit the Neuroi!
What is with this thing?
This sucker's as hard as a rock.
But wait... I don't understand,
what are you guys doing here?
I think we could ask
you the same thing!
We could if we
wanted to waste time!
Huh...? That's so weird. I know
I hit it!
You did, but it
regenerates fast!
We don't have
the firepower for this!
An anti-armor rifle...
Then that means--!
It's Lyn!
Lyn!
Hi, Yoshika!
I'm so glad you're okay...!
And that you're here.
Me too, I just
arrived from Gallia!
That's great...! But we
really don't have time for this!
Perrine!
Are those rockets?!
Look!
Eila!
And Sanya!
Awesome!
I'm gonna move ahead.
You follow.
Right.
They're here...!
Are you done yet?!
Just one more minute!
The Neuroi enemy
has a mobile core!
Regeneration speed is more
than twice of a standard model!
So we just have to destroy it
quicker than it can regenerate!
Great... Just when
I finally managed
to get some time off with Chris.
But, weren't you the one
who wanted to fight the most?
I'm moving out!
Wait! Hold on!
It's them!
Look who's here!
Commander Minna!
Barkhorn!
And Hartmann!
Take the sides!
Roger that!
Commander Minna!
All-out assault!
We're right on it...!
Formation...! Let's go!
Roger that, Ma'am!
Major...!
The Shiden-kai is ready!
Perfect.
Output seems to be normal!
I'm ready to go...! Now!
Commence attack!
The core is out!
I've got this!
But Sakamoto!
Mio!
I'm all right!
What flight path is that?!
She's dodging all the attacks!
Just like you.
Oh no! It's going to hit her!
No, major!
Slice it up... Reppumaru!
Here it comes!
Reppuzan!
Whoa...! Did you just see that?
Yeah!
Perfect...! Just like always!
Well this is new.
I've never seen anyone
slice a Neuroi beam.
Maybe it's because no
one's ever tried it before?
There's really
nothing we can't do!
So those are the Strike
Witches I've heard about.
Wait a minute, Commander.
Is that the same squad
of witches that freed Gallia?
Yes... The Five Hundred and
First Joint Fighter Wing...
And now these legendary
ladies have descended
upon the Adriatic Sea!
Yoshika!
Oh, Lyn...! You're really here!
Yeah! I'm so glad
you came for me!
Y'know, I never thought
I'd see Yoshika here again.
Um, weren't you two
supposed to be in Africa?
Uh, yeah, but that was before
we heard Romagna needed us!
Oh... well, Sanya
and I were supposed
to leave for Suomus today...
But somehow we
took the wrong train
and ended up at
the Adriatic Sea!
Not really. Eila's
psychic skills told us
there was trouble here.
That truly is an
incredible sword.
The Reppumaru...
I infused it with magic
each time I hammered it...
It's instilled with
enchanted powers...
The blade essentially becomes
stronger than any shield.
Still, I worry about you
without an actual shield.
I appreciate your concern...
but I just want to fly.
I understand... You're not
going to step down, are you?
No.
I didn't think so.
Listen up...
These are our orders
from the General Headquarters
of Allied Forces.
Once you are back on active
duty... you are to return
to the Adriatic Sea
in order to intercept
and destroy the new Neuroi
that has invaded Romagna...
We will be sure to send you
all the necessary equipment
and materials to
complete this task...
Until then, do not
hesitate to contact the
local commanding officers
for anything you may require.
Well they sure are
playing their cards right.
Major General Galland
signed this herself.
Or at least was
forced to, anyway.
You're being very
disrespectful, Hartmann...
Orders are orders--regardless
of how they are given.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, Lyn... What do you think it
means that we all met up again?
Um, well...
I, Lieutenant Colonel
Minna Wilcke, with...
Major Mio Sakamoto
Captain Gertrud Barkhorn...
Captain Charlotte Yeager...
Lieutenant Erica Hartmann...
Lieutenant Sanya Litvyak...
Lieutenant Perrine
Clostermann...
Ensign Eila Ilmatar
Juutilainen...
Ensign Francesca Lucchini
Master Sergeant
Lynette Bishop...
And Sergeant Yoshika Miyafuji...
Together... we are
the Strike Witches...
and the Five Hundred
and First Joint Fighter Wing
is hereby reformed!
Roger!
Can you believe it, Yoshika?!
We get to be
together again...! Huh?
Training? Now...? Yoshika, wait!
Don't leave me...!
On the next Strike Witches 2:
"That Which We Can Do."