Reppuzan!
Then it's true...
I can't stop it.
It appears the Battleship Yamato
managed to arrive safely.
That fact alone should be enough
to vindicate the choice
to reestablish the
Five Hundred and
First Joint Fighter Wing.
I'd been told its
purpose was to increase
our military readiness
in this region...
is there something
more to it than that?
Now listen, Lieutenant
Colonel Minna...
Operation Trajan was our
last attempt to make contact
with the Neuroi,
and it ended in failure...
Any possibility of
coexistence has disappeared.
There are two
options before us...
we can either
kill or be killed...
and we'll need more
than just the Strike Witches
to exterminate them.
So that's why you
need the Yamato?
That's all we're cleared
to tell you at this time.
But on another subject...
I understand you'd like approval
for a new tactical operation.
Yes... I'd like to
send specific teams
of Witches to strike the Neuroi.
You have our approval
pending one simple addition,
which we think will
be very beneficial.
You may come in now.
It can't be.
Hartmann! Get up right now!
Sleepy.
You have to train...
The mission could
be green lit any minute.
We have a mission?
Minna's discussing the details
with the top brass right now...
When they approve it,
the two of us will
probably be chosen to fight.
Why just us?
A transport.
That's a Ju 52, to be exact.
Commander Minna
must be back already.
She jumped.
That's crazy.
Wow.
You are so cool.
Thanks... It's a pleasure to
meet you, my little kittens.
We're kittens?
Wow.
Sorry, kids... but I don't
like to give out autographs.
Okay... thanks?
Wow.
Maybe you two can help me.
The great Marseille.
Why are you here?
I thought that you were
supposed to be in Africa.
Is that Hartmann,
I see...? All right!
When's the last time I saw you?
Was it flight school?
No, it was with
JG 52's Group IV...
Do you remember
that total bitch,
the commanding officer
we had we couldn't stand?
You know, the one with the
anger issues and bad breath?
What was her name again?
It was Barkhorn
Exactly... Oh...! It's so
good to see you, Barkhorn.
How are you?
Angry. Can't you smell?
That girl is so cool...
She and Lieutenant Barkhorn
look like best friends.
I don't think you know
what you're talking about.
Man, she's gonna make
things suck around here.
Look. That girl is famous.
She's in a book.
Let me see. 'Karlsland
has many heroes,
but none brighter than
Captain Hannah Marseille.
'She is a member of
the 31st Air Squadron,
also known as the Storm
Witches, and an elite ace
made famous for shooting
down over 200 enemy aircraft.'
Two hundred...?! No way.
'She is known in Karlsland
for her beauty as
much as for her skills...
And both help to spread her
fame throughout the world...
She's called the
'Star of Africa'... Oh wow.
The Star of Africa...?
That's so cool...
I so want her autograph.
She doesn't do autographs.
Did you know her?
Tell us everything
you can about Marseille.
Well, Francesca and
I were stationed in Africa
for a little while
before we ended up here.
It's true.
Is she amazing or awesome?
We mostly just heard rumors
Rumors... That's right.
The other girls from Karlsland
probably know more about her.
That's right... She told us
you were in the same squad.
Yes, we were in
the same squadron
with the 'Star of Africa'...
of course, that was
back in Karlsland.
Then you guys have
to be good friends.
Friends with that snob...?
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
Okay. Listen up.
I will select two
Witches to infiltrate
and then break through here...
They'll take out the
Neuroi defenses...
and then destroy
the core. Questions?
Yes, ma'am... Why only two?
Our transport's a sub...
Storage space is very limited...
So there is only enough room
for two Witches with Strikers.
The only thing you all care
about is who got picked, right?
Here goes...
Assigned to us on a temporary
basis, the first Witch picked,
is Captain Hannah Marseille,
from the 31st Air Squadron.
This is an outrage
and an insult--
that assault team was supposed
to be me and Hartmann.
These orders come
straight from the top...
Only one member of
the 501st will participate
in the operation...
That person isyou,
Captain Barkhorn.
No thank you.
Barkhorn. You're not good
enough to be my partner.
What?
And why not?
What are you trying
to say... exactly?
I'll spell it out...
You lack the flying ability
and combat skills necessary
to keep up with me in battle.
That's enough.
There's only one person
here who can match me.
I'm not done with
you yet, Marseille...
As long as I've known you,
you've never had
the proper respect
for your superior officers,
but I'm about to change that.
Oh?
Lieutenant.
That's bad.
What should we do?
Stand down, Captain.
Oh, but we're same rank now.
Take it outside.
Stop, both of you.
Stop.
All this is just to get me
to be your partner...
So I'll do it.
Are you sure, Lieutenant?
Hartmann.
Well that's better...
Now I'm excited... aren't you?
They're amazing up there.
Well, with the giant egos they
both have, they'd better be.
That's right...
They're both squadron aces.
Correct. This is the
first joint operation
between two top aces
from separate squadrons.
That's exactly why the Allied
Brass like the idea so much...
They're scoring points
with the public
by throwing Captain
Marseille in the mix.
True... if it helps with the
mission, then I don't care...
but I'm not very convinced
of that so far...
They've still got a
lot of synching up to do.
Agreed... They don't seem
to be clicking just yet.
And that's nine wins for me.
Ow! I've been hit!
You just terminated
the exercise.
Return to base at once.
Yeah, sure.
What do you
think that was about?
Dunno... I couldn't
see what was happening.
The two of you are
confined to this room
until the day of the operation.
Captain Marseille...
Normally, you'd be
thrown in the stockade
for pointing a gun at someone
during a training exercise.
Unfortunately, we don't
have one on this base.
Instead... I get to confine
the both of you to your room.
Man... What did I
do to deserve this?
Acted stupid...
so this will give you two
some time to figure out how
to become a team for
the upcoming mission...
Is that clear?
Understood.
I got it.
Pull that again and
you're in real trouble.
You know this whole
thing is your fault, right?
Minna can be pretty scary, huh?
You should see how she
gets when she's actually mad.
So, why didn't you fight back?
I had my gun
aimed right at you...
with the way you fly,
you could've countered
and been on
my six in a heartbeat.
Hannah, you haven't
changed at all.
And why should I have to change?
Not everything in life
has to be a competition.
Winning is the only
thing that matters
when you're on
the battlefield...
That's why I always
have to make sure
I'm the best in everything
that I do... Understand?
That's crazy.
When you left the squadron,
we were still tied eight
kills to eight kills...
You're the only one
who's ever been my equal.
After this... that ends.
This mission is
gonna settle that...
And you will be the loser.
Fine. I forfeit. You win.
Again? That's exactly
what you said last time
before you ran off...
You coward.
Think what you want...
Winner... Captain Marseille.
I win again.
I want some more.
Right away.
So, do you like Fuso cooking?
Yeah... We've gotta
Witch from Fuso
who cooks for my squadron,
too, so ya know.
But I can't stand that stuff.
Really? But natto
is so good for you.
More rice.
There isn't any rice left.
What's that?
I ate more than you! Ha!
Two more wins for me.
And two more
I don't care's for me.
Winning is the first
priority of any soldier.
I told you, I'm not
competing with you.
Too bad...
With an attitude like that,
you're gonna be stuck as a
lieutenant forever, ya know.
Which would be really
sad if I cared.
I could so get used to this...
a hot bath completely
relaxes me...
They're what
I dreamed they'd be like
ever since I first
heard about them.
You don't have baths in Africa?
Not even one...
A drop of water is
precious in Africa...
So, we could never
waste it like this.
That must be rough.
Yeah... but Africa's great.
There are no commanding
officers to ride you,
and the Allied Command
is so far away
they almost never bother us.
So why did they decide to send
you off on this mission then?
Well... they wanted
to get people excited
about the war again,
which is fine...
It seems like a pretty small
price for me to pay...
to protect them.
Besides...
there's a certain girl
named Erica Hartmann
I wanted to see again.
You're so nuts.
Oh, hi Captain
Marseille and Hartmann.
So, how do you feel
after your first bath?
Everything I thought it'd be.
It's inspection time!
Stop that...
Those are not yours.
Ooh...! So big.
But, I'm afraid
Shirley still has you beat.
No way...
You can't out-boob me.
Look...Mine have an upward lift.
What good are
those unjiggly jugs?
It's better than
having old lady bags.
Can an old lady do this?
This is awesome.
Ya mean weird.
Unbelievable.
Morning...
Hey, what's that ya got there?
Uh... it's nothing...
I just... It's not even for me.
Wait... Don't tell me you're
getting Hannah's autograph?
It's for my sister...
She's a really big
fan of Marseille's.
That makes sense.
Yeah... I thought
maybe it'd cheer her up
next time I saw her.
That's sweet... Lemme ask her.
I thought you knew.
I never give out
autographs to anyone.
Do you think it's
really gonna kill you
to sign an autograph or two?
No, but you'd have to shoot me
to get me to sign an
autograph for her sister.
You're terrible...
What did Trudy ever do to you?
Start competing
with me for real...
Win and I'll give you all
the autographs you want.
If I beat you, you'll do it?
Absolutely.
It's time to go.
Come in...
Captain Marseille,
Hartmann... do you copy?
Yeah, loud and clear.
Your target is on
the island of Malta,
which has been taken
over by the Neuroi...
Our Intel has it that
these are the same Neuroi
that recently attacked
the Fuso fleet.
The recon photos showed that the
Neuroi's fortifications topside
are nearly impenetrable.
The submarine will sneak
you under the main defense,
and you'll destroy
it from the inside.
Are you both ready?
Oh I'm always ready.
We're a go, commander.
You're cleared for takeoff.
Let's go.
There are too many.
I count forty bogeys engaged.
Did she say forty?
Yes, she did.
No, thirty-eight!
Make that thirty-five.
Can't they count?
They're just keeping us
updated... as the numbers fall.
They're shooting them
down all by themselves.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-five.
Twenty-one now.
Ten.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Zero.
That just leaves the core.
Me first...
No way!
They got it. Look.
Wow. With only the two of them.
I took down 20.
That's exactly what I got.
I don't like ties.
You never have.
Let's settle this right here.
You better give me your
autograph when I win.
You mean 'if'.
What now?
I thought they were finished.
She's shooting.
But she hasn't hit her yet.
That girl.
Shooting each other's
against regulations!
Looks like they're
never going to change.
Aren't you supposed
to be freaking out?
They're live rounds!
Yeah, and they're witches...
they have their shields to
protect themselves if they want.
Yeah. Great... I feel better.
They're trying to find
out who's the best...
if you use your shield
or run out of ammo...
that's it... you have to
concede to the better fighter.
Marseille used a chandelle
to keep her in check,
and now Hartmann's using
a high G barrel roll
to flip behind her.
Amazing.
Now you're mine.
Sturm Attack.
No ammo.
Same with me.
I guess it's a draw.
This'll never end
with them... Great.
Oh, I've been
looking for that one.
There has got to be
something seriously wrong
with your head.
I've never seen you
clean up this room before.
I'm really sorry...
I just couldn't get an
autograph from Hannah.
That's okay... It's fine.
Why are you in such a rush?
It's because I have
a magazine interview
back home this afternoon.
Nothing the "Star of Africa"
can't handle.
One more thing...
I almost forgot.
Could you send this to
Barkhorn's sister for me?
Why can't you just
give it to her yourself?
I told you.
I have a busy schedule.
This is too much work.
Nooo!
The final showdown with
the Neuroi is nearly here.
But we're the Strike Witches...
We'll never stop fighting.
On the next Strike Witches 2:
"To Be Myself."