Lynne... We're out of rice!
But, what are we supposed to do?
No one's sent us any more yet!
Hey, Sakamoto...!
Can we get some
more rice? We ran out!
It seems everyone's been needing
to use the same supplies
at the same time...
This could be a problem.
What should we do now?
We're actually out of a
lot more than just rice...
You two feel like
taking a shopping trip?
Shopping trip? Okay!
From here on out...
we will be responsible for
providing our own supplies.
Shirley and Francesca,
I'm leaving you two in
charge of this mission...
I figured that would be best
since Francesca is a native ...
and Shirley is most
comfortable with the big truck.
Understood!
Awesome...!
I haven't driven in forever!
I apologize that we can't
send more of you today.
But there's no telling
when the enemy might attack.
Yay! We're going for a drive!
We're going for a drive!
I've been dying to get
off of the base for ages...
This is the best
assignment ever, thanks!
Sergeant Miyafuji
and Sergeant Bishop,
I'm sending you along as well.
Um, 'scuse me...? I'd rather
stay on standby, if that's okay.
What...? But why?
Yes, of course.
Then Miyafuji,
you'll accompany them.
'Kay!
Lucchini, we'll rely on
you to be their guide.
Yep...! You can count on me!
Miyafuji, make sure
you stay close to Shirley
and follow her instructions.
Right!
If anyone wants something
specific, let us know now.
Something we want...?
We could always use
new training equipment.
Perhaps, but that's
not what I meant,
I'm thinking more along
the lines of relaxation.
No argument here...
'Cause they say if
you're gonna work hard...
you should play hard...
and I agree.
If that's the case, then
baths will be important
for keeping up morale
after working all day.
Is training really
the only thing
you girls can think about...?
Does anyone have a
more realistic request?
Major?
Maybe... Maybe some
tea would be nice?
Yes, Lynne...! Teatime
is very important...!
I think I'd like a radio.
Wouldn't that be fun?
But, our transmitter
works just fine
and it's one of the
best you can get.
I mean one we can put in here...
Wouldn't it be nice
if we could listen to
some music or the news?
Yes, I suppose...
Then that's your assignment...
Does it all make sense?
Yep...! Tea and a radio...!
I'm writing everything down.
And a piano...!
Did you get that, too?
I think that might be a
little too heavy to carry.
Fine... I guess I won't be able
to hear Sanya play again...
And what about you...?
Is there anything you want?
Don't know...
Why don't you ask for
something that you want?
How about you, Barkhorn?
I'm all right...
Thanks for asking.
'Kay, well what about
a souvenir for Chris?
Oh... Maybe...
That would be nice...
Um... Yeah...
Some clothes, I guess...
You know, cute ones.
Huh?
I said clothes!
Um... We can do that...
What style does
she like...? Uh...
I don't know...
Does it really matter?
Why don't you guys
just pick something...?
She's Lucchini's size.
So we'll choose...? You sure?
Yeah... Fine...
Whatever you guys get
will be good. I trust you.
'Kay, you got it!
What about you, Perrine?
No, thank you...
I'm perfectly fine.
But... We never get to do this.
You deaf...? I said no!
Uh... I'm sorry.
It's not you, Yoshika...
She's been donating all her pay
to the Gallia Restoration
Foundation, lately,
and would rather her
share go towards that.
Really, huh?
I thought of something else...!
Do you think you could you get
some flower seeds,
too--as well as my tea?
Sure!
Let's see... We need to
ask Hartmann what she wants.
I haven't seen her today...
She's probably sleeping!
Hartmann...! Are you awake?!
Ninety more minutes, Mom.
What soldier do you know
that fights from a mattress?!
None! Get up!
Hey... We're about to
go do some shopping...
Is there anything you
want us to bring you?
Candy!
That's ridiculous. What you
need is an alarm clock!
I want candy! I want
candy! I want candy!
Quiet!
So if you could pick up an alarm
clock, too, that would be great.
Yes, ma'am.
And one alarm clock.
Don't leave!
A pillow!
I said... bring me... a pillow.
Okay.
It should be black with a small,
red embroidered
design on the top...
It has to be made of velvet...
Or maybe silk,
but I prefer velvet...
Make sure it's stuffed with down
or at least feathers from
a bird that lives near water.
Hold on...! Um...
You get all that?
I got that you want a pillow
and something about water birds,
but there was too
much to remember!
Fine, just give me that...
I'll write it down...
But don't mess up.
I'm not writing all
this for nothing...
You have to find one.
'Kay.
Be careful!
We'll see you later!
Please be safe out there.
Wow!
It's so pretty...! I wish
Lynne could've come with us!
Looks like a clear road
to me... Now to really drive!
Whoa!
Hold on!
Here we go!
We're gonna die!
You mean fly!
Go!
Make it stop!
Hold on, guys!
Hooray!
Nailed it!
My tummy hurts.
Hey...! Stop...!
Don't be sick, Yoshika!
Oh, wow! We're really here!
Is this your first time
in Rome or something?
Yeah... What's over there?!
One of the old
fighting coliseums.
Wow...! What about that?!
That's called a town hall!
It's the most
beautiful town hall ever!
So cute...!
It's like you're nine!
Rome is such a
beautiful, historic city.
Yes it is... and the
natives are gorgeous!
I'm pretty sure I can
guess what that means...
Were you born here?
It really is wonderful.
You're right.
You couldn't stop
bragging about Rome even
when we stayed in
an African paradise!
Yes I could...!
I just didn't want to
'cause it's that great!
Put your guns down...
We're all Team Rome, okay?
Are you sure about this place?
Yep...! This shop has everything
you could possibly want!
It does! Amazing!
Let's see...
Scratch radio off the list.
I'm getting this for me!
Hey, did you find an
alarm clock for Hartmann...?
Take this. My arm's falling off.
Okay!
Tea, flowers,
and now some clothes.
Ooh. That would look
great on you! Get it!
Oh no, it's not for me.
This is what Barkhorn
asked us to get.
What...?! Really...? Barkhorn?
Is it really that funny...?
No, wait! It's not for her,
it's for her sister!
Her sister, right.
I promise! She asked us
to pick something for her!
Stop it, Yoshika.
I can't take this...!
Barkhorn wants a dress!
Let go of me, jerk!
Super... Lucchini... Kick !
Safe!
How did you... But they...
Hi...! Come on, let's go!
Come back!
Thank you so much...
but, who are you?
You mean me?
I'm an upholder of justice...
Francesca Lucchini!
Nice to meet you. I'm Maria.
Maria! I like that name!
Well... I appreciate
you helping me.
Sure... What was happening?
Oh, um...
Oh...! I know...!
They're with the Mafia...!
I'm right, aren't I?!
Um, yes...
It's something like that.
I knew it!
You don't need to be hanging
around in back alleys...!
It's really quite dangerous!
'Kay... Thanks for the advice.
Guess what...?
I'm shopping, too.
Do you wanna go together?
Thanks, but I'm actually
not shopping today.
Then what are
you doing out here?
Well... um...
sightseeing, I guess...
Or, more like taking a walk.
A walk?
Yes... I rarely get
to leave my house...
so I don't know Rome very well.
I was born here,
but I know nothing about it...
Isn't that strange?
Lucky for you, you met
the Great Lucchini today!
Come on...! Let's go!
Really...? She's not
in the truck, either.
She was just sitting in a chair
at the store a few minutes ago.
Well, it looks like
she left, and what's more,
she took the money
we need with her.
What? Why?! We still
haven't bought any food!
Yeah, that's annoying, but
don't stress. She'll be back.
We have to go find her!
Huge, isn't it?!
It's stupendous!
Hey, Francesca...
I don't get where
she could've gone!
Watch and learn...
If you throw a coin
backwards like this...
It means you'll
return to Rome someday!
Like this?
Shirley, look!
Ya found her?!
A kitty!
Here! This one's for you!
Wow! Thank you!
Grazi!
Whoa!
Hot--ouch!
Bye-bye!!
Bye-bye!
Be careful!
My pouch is empty.
Okay, she's been eaten.
I give up.
I just can't believe
we didn't find her...
We must've asked
everyone we saw!
It's delicious...!
Shirley, you have to try this!
It's the best cake
in the whole world!
I'm busy being dead.
Here!
Woah...! That's the
best cake in the world!
I know!
Hey...! Can we have
another cake, please...?
I mean... two cakes!
And please hurry!
Tell the truth, Maria!
Don't you love the view?
It's my number
one favoritest ever!
It's so beautiful.
Perfect... I wish
I could just stay here,
instead of going back home.
All ya have to do is stay put!
Exactly.
Tell me something...
Do you believe I would be able
to protect this beautiful city?
Huh?
Look! There's smoke
coming from that house!
It's just someone
cooking a meal, silly.
So here's where
they all live...?
Every single one of those
houses holds a denizen.
A denizen?
I had no idea until today.
Seriously?
Hey! I just remembered
one more view
I have to show you before
you go back! It's amazing!
Sounds great!
I'd love to see it!
But maybe not right now.
I understand...
Then maybe you can show
it to me next time... right?
Yeah!
No way... I can't
believe they've come
this far south already!
It's the Neuroi!
Oh, no!
Let's go, Yoshika!
Right!
We need to escape
quickly, Miss Lucchini!
Sorry, gotta go!
Look...! There she is...!
I see her!
On top of the tower!
Tower?!
Shirley!
That's dangerous!
I gotta go...! I'm one
of the Strike Witches!
Will you hold this?
A Witch?
Yep!
See you later...!
I gotta protect Romagna!
Miss Lucchini.
I'll be protecting Romagna!
Don't get too far ahead of us!
I'm fine!
I know you are...
but you can't do it alone.
We wanna help protect
your home, too, Francesca...
Let us fly beside you!
You're the best...
Really... Thank you!
Ready...? Let's tandem attack!
There it is! Shirley!
Found the core!
All right! X Attack!
Right behind you!
That's it... Keep coming...
Right here!
It saw through it!
Goodness.
Yoshika...! Can ya hold this?!
Now I can show you!
Um... Where are we going?!
Now, just look out there!
This is the view I wanted to
show you from the beginning.
It's amazing...
but... aren't you ever
afraid, Miss Lucchini?
Why? Whaddaya mean?
Like what you just did...
You aren't afraid of fighting
such terrifying enemies?
The Neuroi?
If we don't fight them,
Romagna will disappear...
and we can't have that.
Protecting people's homes
and friends is what we do...
It's part of being a Witch!
So, like a noblesse
oblige, I suppose?
I don't know what that means.
You use big words sometimes.
You really think so?
Oh no!
Can you find your way?
Yes... I had the most
wonderful day today.
Thank you so much.
Really?
Yes...! Being with you
today has helped me realize
what I'm supposed to do here.
Okay... I'm glad then!
Ciao!
Bye-bye, Maria...!
I'll see ya later!
I'm sorry!
Really...
I can't believe you wasted
all of our food money
within a matter of hours.
And you didn't stop her...! I
guess it's partially my fault...
I'm the one who trusted you!
Have fun scrubbing. Bye!
Here... Will this work?
I'm so glad you found it!
It's exactly what you
wanted... That's great.
And this is for you, Sanya.
Oh thank you... I love it.
I'm surprised I found yours,
I mean talk about a tall order!
Come on, it wasn't that hard.
Just a suggestion:
Maybe you should make it
easier next time you
ask someone a favor.
These are for you, Perrine.
Thanks, but what are they?
They're flower seeds...
Lynne thought
it might be nice for us
to plant some of
them around the base...
Wouldn't that be pretty?
You thought of that?
Yes... I was hoping that
maybe you would teach me how
to grow and take care
of them sometime,
since you're so good at it.
What makes you think
I'd be interested in that?!
Let's go plant them together!
Will you please teach us?
Very well, if you insist.
The first thing we have to do is
find a sunny place
to plant the marigolds...
then a cooler place for
the chamomile and bergamots...
They'll need to stay
out of direct sunlight
in the summer time.
Want candy... Need candy!
Whadda you think of this one...
Is it the right size?
Wow... I mean...
Thank you... It is!
The bust is a little small.
No, it's not...! It's perfect!
Alright, alright...
It's perfect.
Are you ready?!
We interrupt this program
to bring you a live broadcast.
Maria, the Duchess of
the Duchy of Romagna
made her first official
appearance today.
She has asked to
address the nation
on a very important subject.
Yesterday, a terrible
Neuroi attack was launched
on Rome and threatened
the lives of our citizens...
However... the Neuroi was
repelled thanks to the actions
and bravery of a small,
but mighty, Witch.
I've learned so much from her...
She risked everything to protect
the lives of her loved ones...
and to guard the
security of Romagna...
We have the strength within
us if we just have the heart.
That's why...
I vow to do my part...
My love for all of you gives me
the strength to keep us safe...
Thank you, for your heart
and inspiration, my dear friend.
Miss Francesca Lucchini.
What?!
And so it is with
sincere gratitude
that I send a humble
token of my appreciation...
to the Five Hundred and
First Joint Fighter Wing Squad.
Ow... I'm stuck!
Sanya is hugging the
pillow I just bought...
That pillow is
lounging in her arms.
It's nestled in her chest,
and it's feeling the warmth
of her skin and even
listening to her heartbeat!
On the next Strike Witches 2:
"Higher than the Sky."