We haven't seen each
other since that day.
[CHUTARO]
Kagami!
[KAGAMI]
Easy, tiger.
No one's gonna
hurt you. I promise.
Let go of me!
You're a criminal!
You're supposed to be
in Gokumonjo prison!
[KAGAMI]
Hey.
Is it true your
big brother's dead?
No! It's a big lie!
Tenny's alive, he's just hiding!
That's why I'm looking for him!
Now let go!
[KAGAMI]
Huh.
You'd think he'd make
himself easier to find,
wouldn't ya?
You're clearly frantic.
Why doesn't he come out
and put your mind at ease?
Seems kinda heartless.
Shut up!
Come on. Level with me.
You know what happened.
Your brother was killed.
What? This is news?
He was the Orochi's vessel,
so the government
had to have him executed.
[CHUTARO]
I don't understand.
Sora said the exact same thing.
But it doesn't make any sense!
What is the stupid Orochi?
What's it got
to do with Tenny?
[KAGAMI]
Pay attention, kid.
Your brother was possessed
by an evil spirit.
The only way to stop that spirit
from taking over everything
was for the powers that be to
step in and do what they do.
[CHUTARO]
Huh?
You understand?
Your beloved Tenny
was a sacrifice.
[CHUTARO]
Tenny--
Tenny was--
Ah!
No!
[crying]
This hardly bodes
well, Commander.
It's been over two weeks, sir.
Yet the skies
over Lake Biwa--
weren't the clouds meant to
depart once the Orochi perished?
[SOSEI] There is, in my
opinion, but one explanation.
We were wrong.
Tenka Kumoh was not
the Orochi's vessel.
If this is true, then Tenka's
death was without cause!
[SOSEI] I am well aware
of that, thank you.
It suggests the Shiga police
are hiding something.
The question is what, exactly.
[CHUTARO]
No!
He didn't deserve
to be made a sacrifice!
Not him! Not him!
[KAGAMI]
That's the worst part, huh?
[CHUTARO cries]
[KAGAMI] He did absolutely
nothing wrong, and they knew it.
[CHUTARO]
Stop.
[KAGAMI] Don't you want
Tenny's murderers to pay?
Yes! Yes!
[KAGAMI]
Don't you want 'em to die?
[CHUTARO]
I do.
Then why not make it happen?
Kill them.
I could, couldn't I?
[KAGAMI]
Make 'em reap what they've sown.
Put your brother's
soul at peace.
Take back the Kumoh pride.
Revenge is sweet.
And it only costs your life.
[birds chirping]
[SHIRASU]
Try not to worry.
He hasn't been gone
as long as all that.
[sighs]
It's how he copes.
He'll come back
when he's hungry.
[door opens]
Okay. Let's hear it then.
Those looks on your faces
are making me uncomfortable.
[KITAMURA]
Uh.
We just saw a man
in the forest.
Naoto Kagami.
Wait! The crazy guy?
But wasn't he--?
How in heaven's name does
a man like that escape prison?
[TSUCHIYA] Every effort was made
to apprehend him, I'm told.
But his speed is ungodly.
That's not why we're here.
When we saw him,
he wasn't alone.
[SORAMARU]
What?
Well, he was with your brother.
He has Chutaro?
Wait, please. Calm yourself.
How can you expect
me to stay calm?
Stay here.
It would be better
if I handled this.
I'm coming with you!
[SHIRASU]
Tenka is no more.
That leaves you in
charge of the shrine.
Do you understand?
Soramaru.
You have your responsibilities,
and I have mine.
I'll bring Chutaro back.
Please, just don't
let him get hurt.
Ten, gen, myou, shin,
kai, ou, jin, tsuu, ryou.
Ten, gen, myou.
It's not like you
to drop in on me, sir.
Something must be
seriously off.
An astute observation,
as expected of an onmyo mage,
especially one of your pedigree.
Strange words from a man
descended from Abe.
[SOSEI]
Alas, magic isn't my forte.
I chose the sword.
Naturally.
[ASHIYA]
Right.
What can I do
for you, Commander?
[SOSEI]
I am in need of your familiars.
[ASHIYA]
What for?
[SOSEI]
Infiltration.
Gokumonjo.
I see.
[SOSEI] It's been the eye
of many a storm lately.
Just today, in fact,
the second Kumoh brother
reported an escaped prisoner.
Yet my personal inquiry into
the matter yielded nothing.
Their officials denied
any such incident.
[ASHIYA]
Business as usual.
[SOSEI]
The opium, however, is not.
[ASHIYA] I'll put the girls
on it right away, sir.
[SOSEI]
Thank you.
The information
about the escapee
came from Soramaru, didn't it?
So he hasn't been told, then?
About the Orochi?
Do you think he should?
Well, if my big bro was
strung up for no good reason,
I'd wanna know.
But that's just me.
Indeed it is.
Bear that in mind.
What does your clan
know of the sealing spell?
Do they, in their wisdom, feel
its properties were genuine?
[ASHIYA] Hard to say when
all you've got to go on
are old stories.
What I know is that the familiar
they summoned to enact it
represented everything
the Abe mages
had in their bag of tricks.
The spell is said to
have been so potent,
only she could wield it.
[SOSEI] And yet the
spell was lost during
the Orochi's manifestation
three centuries ago.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah. That's a damn shame.
Nonetheless. Her knowledge of
the Serpent would be a boon.
Do you want her summoned?
[SOSEI]
Can you?
[ASHIYA] You did hear
the part about her being
the alpha and omega of
Abe onmyo magic, right?
Meh. What the hell.
I swear on my family name
that I, Mutsuki Ashiya,
will find a way
to make it happen.
Don't disappoint me.
[FEMALE FAMILIAR]
That was quite a vow, master.
Are you sure it was wise?
[FEMALE FAMILIAR 2]
The infamous Abe familiar,
unlike us,
will prove to be a very
difficult entity to wrangle.
[ASHIYA] C'mon. What was
I supposed to do?
Tell my Commander "no"?
Besides, his modus operandi
has always been destroying
the Orochi.
Sealing it, per se, doesn't
really interest him.
I wanna know what he's
got up his sleeve.
How far the Ashiya and the Abe
have come from their enmity.
You're on such friendly terms.
[ASHIYA]
The past is the past.
It's not like I'm a
good will ambassador.
No. I'm just a man
caught up in the present.
All right, ladies.
Let's get to business.
[BOTH]
With pleasure, master.
[BOTH giggle]
You gotta wonder what in the
world all this is leading to.
[birds cawing]
The plan worked, sir.
Kagami has escaped and
is awaiting our signal.
Everything is in place.
We move at your pleasure.
--[birds chirping]
--[heavy breathing]
[SORAMARU]
It's all I can do
just crawling out
of bed these days.
My body aches.
My head's killing me.
Feels like I'm getting sick.
Well, for Nishiki's sake I'd
better keep my distance.
The last thing she
needs is to catch
whatever I'm comin' down with.
Except whenever I
leave her unsupervised,
she goes a little
nuts-o with the chores.
It's kind of ridiculous.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Just this morning,
as a matter of fact,
she's doing the laundry and
suddenly, bubbles everywhere--
[grunts]
Whoa, whoa! Watch it!
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Silence! I can hear you
talking to yourself!
Use your inside voice!
Nishiki this, Nishiki that,
blah, blah, blah.
Okay, we get it!
Did you fall on
your head, or--?
[TAKEDA] Stop looking at me like
someone who needs your pity!
If you don't wanna
hear about my life,
why are you running beside me?
[TAKEDA]
Because Takamine told me to!
Although he didn't say why.
Seriously? He's probably
just messing with you.
Ha-ha! Maybe he has
bigger things in mind!
[TAKAMINE] When that
happens, I want you ready.
There's a reason he's the
Commander's right-hand man.
If anyone gets my
respect, it's him.
There's a fellow you
could follow into battle!
[SORAMARU] Yeah, but
he answers to my teacher.
[TAKEDA] Laugh it up
while you can, Shorty!
--[SORAMARU] Shut up, Freckles!
--[TAKEDA] You shut up!
[SORAMARU] Why don't
you make me? I dare you!
Ugh, one of these days!
One of these days, what?
[BOTH]
Give it up, man!
I'm not losing to you!
[birds chirping]
Well, then.
Let's see what the Shiga
police are up to, shall we?
Hello.
Odd place for a manor house.
[gasps]
I understand Iwakura
is unwell as of late.
It seems so.
He'll meet with no one,
not even the Squad.
With one notable exception.
Shi.
[OKI] Precautionary measures
are called for, I believe.
If it's discovered
Tenka Kumoh was a proxy,
the uproar would
be tremendous.
[HIRARI]
Agreed.
[TAKAMINE]
A proxy?
The Commander needs
to know this.
Show yourself!
Who are you working for?
It's you!
[crickets chirping]
[gasping]
[choking]
[coughing]
Wha-- What's gotten into you?
[SORAMARU]
I don't know.
I just-- I--
I thought I heard a noise.
When I tried to
rouse you, you sprang.
Perhaps you were
having a nightmare?
Yeah, that must be it.
I don't imagine
you sleep well.
Not with Chutaro out there.
Why don't you try to
lie down for a bit longer?
Pardon the intrusion.
Master Sosei!
Good morning, sir!
What brings you here so early?
Ah, yes.
Your training might benefit
from a change of pace,
or at any rate
a change of scenery.
So you came all this way?
Hey!
Knock it off!
He's my teacher,
not an intruder!
Put that away!
[ASHIYA]
So he hasn't been told, then?
About the Orochi?
Well, if my big bro
was strung up for no good
reason, I'd wanna know.
Oh, have you eaten yet?
We'd be delighted to
make you breakfast, sir.
Master?
Yes. Sounds lovely.
Ryo, shin, ku, ban,
kai, sho, shiki.
[floor creaking]
Not again.
What is it with today?
Can I help you?
I rather wonder.
Hello, Master Ashiya.
What do you know
of the Orochi?
Uh?
[SOSEI] Historically there
have been vessels only
too well aware of their fate,
while others had no idea.
[SORAMARU]
Not sure I follow.
[SOSEI]
The Orochi is a malign spirit.
To be its host is to
subjugate one's memories,
one's sense of self,
until the evil within prevails.
Your brother chose
a swift death
over a slow and
agonizing surrender.
Yeah, I know.
Alas, I'm afraid his death
gave us no guarantee.
Sad to say.
[SORAMARU]
What? I don't get it.
What does that even mean?
[door opens]
[TAKEDA]
Commander!
[SORAMARU]
Takeda?
[TAKEDA]
Commander! I'm so sorry.
What do I do?
Calm yourself.
Tell me what happened.
He was attacked, sir!
Takamine was attacked!
He was found on the road
just a little while ago
and taken to the hospital.
It's unclear if he'll
regain consciousness.
Have they caught the
person responsible?
[TAKEDA]
No.
There was a townsman beside him.
It occurred near here.
[gasps]
[grunts]
You hear that? He was attacked
in your own backyard!
And on your watch!
Damn it, aren't you supposed
to protect people?
What are the Brothers
of the Cloud good for?
You're weak!
You're weak and you're a fraud!
Takeda, enough. Please.
I take it you've not
told the other members?
[TAKEDA]
No, sir.
I thought it best
to come to you first.
[SOSEI]
Inform them immediately.
Someone able to cut down
a man of Takamine's stature
cannot be trifled with.
I want him found.
Yes, sir.
[KAGAMI] Am I out of
shape or am I out of shape?
Time is a rat, kid, don't
expect it to treat you too well.
But, whatever, at least
my blade had a little drink.
So, uh, the person
you tested it on?
Is halfway across
the threshold of
the sweet hereafter
right about now.
This is yours.
Get ready.
Uh-oh.
Somebody gettin' cold feet?
Turn on the waterworks
for me, why don't'cha?
Cry loud enough
and maybe darling
Tenny'll come to the rescue.
[laughs]
[ASHIYA] You are some
piece of work, ma'am.
Three hundred years'
worth of scholarship
and nobody made the connection.
[BOTAN]
Oh. I have excellent sources.
Believe me.
In ancient times, the Orochi was
sealed through ritual magic.
In its last incarnation,
three centuries ago, however,
the serpent succeeded
in devouring the spell.
In the belly of the beast,
the incantation
was lost to time.
But, along with
the sealing spell,
two precious artifacts
were also swallowed.
[ASHIYA]
And those would be the Swords
of the Kumoh family, yes?
We will only know for sure if
you confirm it with your magic.
Master Ashiya, if you would.
Please.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah, yeah. C'mon.
What was I supposed to do?
Tell a legendary familiar "no"?
I would also ask that
you keep this a secret.
[ASHIYA]
Even from the Commander?
I'll tell him, at a
time of my choosing.
[ASHIYA] Look, I don't
pretend to know what went on
between you and the Abe.
But my boss is their
direct descendant.
He finds out I'm
keepin' this from him,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
Though, I suspect he's
got his hands full dealing
with whatever's going
on at Gokumonjo.
[BOTAN]
Does he really?
[ASHIYA] Lot of issues
with that place recently.
Even sent in my familiars.
Haven't heard a
peep from 'em yet.
Generally not a good sign.
Hope I'm not
bein' too forward,
but you'd do well
to be careful.
Excuse me.
Shirasu.
Please forgive me,
I thought you were
still out looking for Chutaro.
I was successful.
He's been found.
That's excellent news.
[SHIRASU]
Found, but not retrieved.
I will need help.
Whatever the Kumoh
need of me, my friend.
My apologies for the intrusion.
Master Ashiya,
might we pick up tomorrow
where we've left off today?
[ASHIYA]
No problem.
Time is short.
Right.
Listen to me!
True strength is laughing
in the face of your pain!
[laughing]
Oh, no. How the--?
[heartbeat]
What the--? What was that?
[gags]
[heartbeat continues]
[SOSEI] Historically there
have been vessels only
too well aware of their fate,
while others had no idea.
No.
[gasps]
[SOSEI]
The Orochi is a malign spirit.
To be its host...
is to subjugate
one's memories.
One's sense of self.
Little by little, until
the evil within prevails.
[gasping]
We must protect
the boys at all costs!
It was Tenka's
final charge to us!
Far be it from us to
disappoint the man,
even in death.
Say what you will, he was
an expert manipulator.
[BOTAN]
This is the least we can do.
To that end, I believe
I've found a way to
prevent the
Orochi's resurrection.
[SHIRASU]
Prevent it?
[BOTAN]
Exactly,
I think there is a way
to spare the vessel.
The Kumoh family swords.
If I'm right, they may
possess the means to dispel
the Serpent from
his chosen host.
[SHIRASU]
Is that possible?
[BOTAN] Those swords were
devoured by the Orochi
three hundred years ago,
along with the sealing spell.
They were later recovered.
The spell was not.
I believe the spell
fused with the swords
while inside the
Serpent's belly.
[SHIRASU] So the Kumoh
blades can seal the Orochi?
Shirasu?
I am impressed.
Clearly I underestimated you.
Can it be you have
a favorable opinion of me?
[blade puncturing flesh]
Oh, yes. Though, honestly I'd
have rather killed you long ago.
[grunts]
[SHIRASU]
Nothing personal.
I cannot allow you
to interfere.
[gasps]
It's over.
Do you understand?
[breath quivering]
[SHIRASU]
Lord Orochi will rise again.