What-- What are you?
It's over.
Rest assured, Lord Orochi
will rise again.
Why would you wish to
see the Serpent reborn?
[bird screams]
All necessary arrangements for
the exodus have been seen to,
down to the last detail.
Only those wardens
and inmates loyal to
the cause remain standing.
The convicts who've
survived the purge are
hopelessly addicted to opium.
We make the next move
at your behest, sir.
Wretched souls.
[SHIRASU]
Imagine the sheer number of
violent criminals running free.
No. No, don't tell me you're
involved in this travesty!
[SHIRASU]
Not just involved.
Responsible for it.
A plan like this one calls
for agents on both sides.
In and out.
But you-- You insisted on
calling yourself a Kumoh!
The Fuma have been Lord Orochi's
retainers for generations.
The law of the clan
dwarfs all else.
[MASKED MAN]
Comrades!
Why, I ask you,
must we suffer alone?
Are we not men?
Must we feed hand to mouth?
Must our freedom be
the prerogative of others?
Or shall we wrench it
from the talons of
our oppressors with a vengeance?
[PRISONERS cheer]
[bird screeches]
You stood by the Brothers of
the Cloud with such conviction!
Ha. You noted my
fervor, did you?
Well, it was simply a question
of protecting my lord's vessel.
You monster.
[SHIRASU]
Incidentally, it wasn't Tenka.
The honor goes to Soramaru.
But how did you--
how long have you known?
From the very start.
You bastard!
[whimpering]
[SHIRASU]
Ah, you're an Abe familiar.
I had my suspicions when you
survived a blade
through the heart.
[grunts]
Hmph.
What are you doing here?
Is this guy bothering you?
I don't know what your
deal is, but this is not
how you treat a lady!
Ugh, son of a--
[BOTAN]
Get away from here!
Look, this isn't
my first fight.
--I'll be--
--Do as I say!
Gotta love that fire.
Makes it worth
the wait every time.
If I go, my darling's
coming with me.
Mm?
Kill them both.
However you see fit.
Forgive me, Tenka.
Put me down this instant!
Yeah, because that's
a great idea.
[grunts]
Om shiro basara ei sowaka.
You see? I am not human.
These paper tigers
are nothing to me.
Am I not terrifying?
No. You're a thing of beauty.
That's not the effect
I was going for exactly!
Oh, just shut up!
How often must I hear
you spout off such
nonsense about me?
How often? Does that
mean you recognize me?
--Perhaps.
--Okay, this is nuts.
But I've been having
dreams about you since--
I can't even remember!
[BOTAN]
Poor Hirari,
condemned to chase
echoes of a former life,
led in circles
by visions of a woman
his heart yearns for
across centuries.
As long as the Orochi
lives, so do I.
So continues Hirari's
lonesome quest.
Yet by some happy coincidence
or outrageous fortune
he always finds the
woman of his dreams.
We have work
to do, you and I.
The Fuma must not
come into possession
or the Kumoh family swords.
[rapid footsteps]
[panting]
Master!
Yes?
[panting]
Out with it. I haven't
got all night.
Takamine's attacker
is still loose.
No, he's not.
You have to kill me, sir.
I'm the Orochi's vessel.
I've been losing time lately
and I have no memory of
where I've been, and I've
been finding evidence
of things I don't
remember doing.
Like clothes spattered
with blood in the closet.
I'd never just up
and attack someone.
You've got to
believe that, sir.
But I know it was me.
The evil's fighting to get out.
I'm begging you to cut off my
head before it's too late.
That smile's ridiculous.
And inappropriate.
It's annoying me.
This is what the
Yamainu is for!
If there's another way,
then I'm all ears!
Please, just--
--[heavy breathing]
--[grunting]
[gasping]
[grunting]
I swear you will not
take control of me!
[grunting]
[gasps]
Damn you, Orochi.
I'll find a way.
I promise you!
[sword unsheathing]
[SOSEI] Do you honestly
think death is the answer?
This is what you really want?
[sword sheathes]
And what of carrying the torch?
--What of your duty?
--Huh?
Do you forget
yourself so easily?
Let me ask you something.
Why have you not yet shed
a tear for your brother's fate?
Do you suppose
conceding a few moments
to grief would tarnish
the Kumoh pride?
Make no mistake.
Your strength has
inspired others.
But what good is that
strength if it gives
no quarter to human frailty?
[SORAMARU]
I'm not strong. I'm not.
'm weak and I'm a fraud.
I'm always depending
on everybody else
to keep it together for me.
I feel like if I give
in for a second,
the tears won't stop, and then
what good am I to anyone?
[SOSEI]
Rubbish.
Tears are no betrayal.
Quite the opposite.
Indulged quietly,
with dignity,
they are a prayer for those
to whom we owe our strength.
Honoring grief is the
measure of a true warrior.
[SORAMARU crying]
[SORAMARU] Tenka, you
were always out ahead of me,
always blazing a trail.
But when I was lost, you doubled
back to show me the way.
Maybe sometimes, being able to
cry is what makes you a man.
[crying]
Good. Nicely done.
Commander Sosei!
We've been surrounded
by the Fuma, sir!
Have we?
What do you know?
After all this time,
they're showing
their true colors.
[TAKEDA]
I don't understand.
Defend this young man.
To the death.
[SOSEI] Satisfied? I let
the Orochi vessel live.
It appears we are at last
in agreement, old friend.
This is certainly unexpected.
Just remain calm.
But, sir, they're--
Mortal creatures.
Who you have my
permission to kill.
[HIRARI]
Wait. Police?
What's going on here?
[BOTAN]
Is something wrong?
[KITAMURA]
Something wrong?
There's been a prison
break at Gokumonjo!
Everyone's escaped!
Our first instinct was
to ask Soramaru for help--
heaven knows we need
all we can get--
but he's nowhere to be found!
Where could he have gone?
Where are you going?
You heard them. They need help.
I'm getting reinforcements.
Right. I'll wait here.
Soramaru's bound to come back.
--[distant gunfire]
--[swords clanging]
[TAKEDA]
Halt, who goes there?
[gasps]
[SORAMARU]
Shirasu?
[TAKEDA]
What an entrance. Sheesh.
Ah, so we meet again.
[groans]
What the hell is wrong
with you? He's one of us!
You appear to have confused
me with Shirasu, comrade.
An all too common misconception.
[laughs]
You again! What are
you doing here?
And why do you
have Shirasu's face?
One could just as easily
remark that he has my face,
though I doubt our mother
would much approve.
You're twins?
That we are, as well as joint
orchestrators of this strategy.
You're a damn liar!
Do not imagine his loyalty
to you outweighs his
loyalty to the Fuma.
He is, in point of fact, the
undisputed leader of our clan.
Screw you! He's a
member of our family!
So you say.
Would you still grant him
that honor if you knew him
to have murdered your parents?
[growls] You bastard!
Ah!
I thought I made it clear you're
not to lay a hand on him.
Lest you forget, our lord
needs his body intact.
What's going on here?
Hail, Lord Orochi.
I am yours.
Let me introduce myself--
Tenth Chief of the Fuma Clan.
Kotaro Fuma.
I, too, am Kotaro Fuma.
Tis a title we share.
[BOTH] We pledge our all
to your glorious resurrection.
[SORAMARU]
No.
This isn't happening.
This isn't the Shirasu I know.
He'd never do
something like this!
[grunting]
[crying]
I pray thee, be calm.
[crying continues]
You deceived him for ten years.
This is to be expected.
Shut up! Go to hell!
Surely there is at least
some small degree of solace
in knowing your brother did
not live to see this moment.
Stop talking to me like that!
He was formidable
but a man in my position
couldn't hope for better pawns
than those he left behind.
--[blade slicing flesh]
--[thud]
[whistling]
They've retreated!
But why?
It can't be!
Commander, I--!
Idiot! Where is Soramaru?
I'm sorry, sir, but--
I'm afraid they have him.
[INUKAI]
You're saying he's the vessel?
We haven't the luxury of time.
Dispatch a unit to Gokumonjo.
We can only hope
that it isn't too late.
[INUKAI]
Sir.
The Fuma are not
to be underestimated.
We're dealing with people
capable of staging their own
massacre to win the
good graces of the Kumoh.
[KIIKO] That may be,
but what do they want?
To see the Orochi reborn.
But how did this happen?
Were there no defenses?
Brace yourself. They've
got the swords, too.
No! This is--
[ASHIYA] Sorry. I have
to get over to HQ.
Looks like things are
about to get pretty hairy.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Man, those clouds are
givin' me the creeps.
Do you think my mommy is
gonna be okay on the mountain?
Oh dear! She's not out in this?
Yeah, she went out with
some friends a while ago
to pick herbs.
[bird cawing]
Wow, the sky looks really weird.
I've never seen it
like this before.
Get your head out of
the clouds already, huh?
I'm starvin' here. Why
don'tcha go find us some food.
Quit ordering me around, okay?
You told me we'd be
in Kyoto by now!
So far all we've done
is hike circles around Shiga
tying ropes to everything.
Is that your idea of revenge?
Uh.
What about putting my
brother's soul at peace?
You've got family, don't you?
You think this crap'd
be enough for them?
[KAGAMI]
Who the hell said anything about
me having a family?
I've been on my own
from the get-go.
Damn it! Get him back here
now before somebody sees!
What's wrong? What's happening?
It's all right, sir!
He's gone, but
we're handling it!
Is your history with them
giving you second thoughts?
Of course not.
I'm reflecting on the
ability of these swords
to cleave Lord Orochi
from the vessel.
Interesting.
I imagine your stint
in Gokumonjo must've
been unpleasant.
What of it? My comfort
means nothing.
I would've endured
greater tortures still
to amass the army
we now command.
[SHIRASU] And I would have
exercised a thousand deceptions
in service to our lord.
[BOTH] For ten years we've
awaited this hallowed day.
[YOUNG KOTARO] All of our
clansmen who opposed
the Orochi's resurrection
have been slain.
[YOUNG SHIRASU] Spread word that
the Fuma have met their end.
[YOUNG KOTARO]
What delicious irony.
That our Lord would choose
a host from the bloodline
with whom we have
been at odds for so long.
[YOUNG SHIRASU] Alas, it will
be ages yet before the Serpent
can gather strength
enough to rise.
We shall retreat
to the shadows,
become but a rumor.
[SHIRASU] Such trouble
that meddlesome man was.
[KOTARO]
Taiko Kumoh?
His instincts were sharp.
Had he pursued them further,
the Yamainu would've
been at our throats.
How he clung to life.
[thunder]
[YOUNG SORAMARU]
Daddy!
Mommy!
Where are you?
[crying]
[thunder]
[KOTARO]
How swiftly his death
allowed us to win the
confidence of his children.
[SHIRASU]
True.
What of the prisoner's gambit?
Did the escape go as intended?
[KOTARO]
Yes.
That Kagami fellow
played his role admirably.
[SHIRASU]
Did he?
[KOTARO]
Envision it, brother--
Lord Orochi risen, exalted.
The word Fuma once again
synonymous with power.
[SHIRASU]
Not yet.
There is work to be done.
[flames roaring]
[SHIRASU]
Farewell, Shirasu Kinjo.
--[water splashing]
--[grunting]
Aw, c'mon, I had you! No fair!
[KAGAMI laughs]
I'm gonna go out on
a limb and say somebody's
never had to scrabble after
their own meal before.
Must be nice havin' brothers
waitin' on ya hand and foot.
They cart your butt around in
one of them chariots, too?
Fan you with palm fronds?
That's what you do if you don't
want your little brat growin' up
to be his own man.
[splash]
[laughing]
Keep talking about my
brothers and you'll be sorry!
You wanna say that again,
Your Highness?
Or shut your damn trap?
Now, you hear that sound?
We got ourselves some
unlucky villagers.
[CHUTARO]
That's the vegetable lady!
Well, she picked
a bad day to forage.
If you really wanna put your
brother's soul at peace,
you gotta show me
how serious you are.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[VILLAGER screaming]
--[BANDITS growling]
--Well dammit.
They beat us to the
punch, didn't they?
That's what you get for waitin'
so long to make a move.
Too bad, so sad.
[CHUTARO]
I can sneak up behind them--!
Ah, there we go!
That's what I need to see!
Get this through
that thick skull, kiddo.
Revenge is an
all-or-nothing proposition.
Period.
You're all alone.
It's all on you. Do or die.
No one's gonna feed you.
No one's gonna carry you.
[BANDITS laughing]
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
Hyaaaah!
[grunting]
Heh. Think you're
some kinda hero?
[grunting, screaming]
[birds chirping]
Now go!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[HIRARI]
Wow.
We can always count
on you to make a scene.
Take it easy! It's only me, man.
You're such a pain.
Next time you
decide to take off,
maybe run your brilliant
plan by me first?
People might get
the wrong idea.
[wind blowing loudly]