[WOMAN]
Year Eleven
of Emperor Mejii's reign.
Japan struggles to quell
the highest crime rate
in its history.
In Otsu, Shiga,
a great prison rises from
the center of Lake Biwa,
Gokumonjo.
Its "guests" are ferried
to their long home
by three brothers.
Scions of the
vanishing Kumoh line.
Legend will remember them
as Brothers of the Cloud.
[SHIRASU]
So, where are they now?
[TENKA]
Getting a little shut-eye.
[sighs]
Heavy day for
them, you know?
I made sure they were
tucked in and all that.
Figure we'll drop by the
clinic after first light.
That poor boy.
I certainly hope
his memory recedes.
[TENKA]
I think what came to him
when he was being
choked was pretty vague.
Just bits and pieces.
Damn shame that it's
still rolling around
in there, though.
Anyhoo. Sorry I keep
making you run back and forth.
However this family sees
fit to use me is my pleasure.
Come on, man. Why do you
have to say it like that?
We don't "use" you.
I do believe we're drunk.
Soramaru is going
to be cross with you.
[TENKA]
What's this "we're drunk" stuff?
[SHIRASU]
Oh, I'll catch up.
[SORAMARU]
Unbelievable!
He's a complete idiot!
Here we are falling all over
ourselves to make ends meet
and he's pissing
money away on booze!
[TENKA]
My little brother!
Such a lightweight
he can't hardly stand!
Stupid jackass.
[MAN]
Mhm.
Well, your arm will be fine.
[SORAMARU]
Whoopdie-do!
Meanwhile Tenka gets off
without a scratch!
Can't you make him hurt, doc?
Now, now.
Son, I really ought to
have a look at that neck.
Nah. It'll be fine.
I'm just a little weird about
people touching it and all.
Hm. I understand.
[SORAMARU]
Do you?
[SORAMARU screaming]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
anything by it, I swear!
You seemed down, so I
thought if I could tickle you
it'd make you laugh!
[SORAMARU]
Thank you, doctor. Goodbye.
[groaning]
[TENKA]
Didn't take long.
Must be a good sign, eh?
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Help me out. Has anyone found
the cure for hangovers?
[DOCTOR]
One moment.
I messed up, Tenka!
I tried to be funny and
now Sora hates my guts!
[TENKA]
Um.
Could you not do that, please?
Big brother would like to
keep his breakfast.
Thank you!
Calm down.
Look, Soramaru doesn't
hate you, okay?
He's just traumatized.
He needs a good laugh.
Well, yeah.
That's what I was doing.
Ah, but times like these
call for a special prop.
I think you know what I mean.
[CHUTARO]
Of course!
You're a genius, Tenka!
Hey, Sora, wait up!
[DOCTOR]
All three of you Kumoh boys.
So spirited.
Well? Are you still
recovering from last night?
I'm getting there.
Still got a little hooch
in my bloodstream.
Just bear in mind, my boy,
the bottle doesn't
help us forget.
It makes us remember.
[SORAMARU]
Get away from me!
Why do you always
do what Tenka says?
[CHUTARO]
Come on, give us a smile!
If you don't get away from
me with that thing, I swear--
D'aw, stop being
such a sourpuss.
You know this is hilarious!
Ugh. Seriously, man.
Leave me alone.
If he didn't hate me
before, he does now.
[DOCTOR]
What about your friend?
Hm?
Kinjo Shirasu.
It's been ten years since
you brought him here.
I still question your charity.
Taking a man like that
under wing was a huge risk.
It's not like he's
waiting to turn on me.
He's bad stock, Tenka.
The Fuma clan were butchers.
[TENKA]
How long have you known
those were his people?
[DOCTOR]
Quite some time.
White hair. Deep, violet eyes.
The ninja clans of old
are more than legend
to someone my age.
There was the Koga,
fierce advocates
of the wretched
and disenfranchised.
The Iga, who lived and
died by the contracts
of their wealthy patrons.
Such wild, cutthroat days.
Death walked quietly,
took indiscriminately.
And the Fuma--
Ended long enough ago now
that they might as well
have been a bad dream.
Yes, well. Funny
thing about dreams.
Sometimes you can't tell
them apart from what's real.
Kinjo Shirasu
is a trusted friend.
So, cut the guy a
little slack, huh, Doc?
But his family--
If you don't knock it off with
this talk, I'm gonna get angry.
[DOCTOR]
Forgive me.
I'm a worrier by
nature and by trade.
Hey, no harm done.
I appreciate the love.
Tenka, sir! We have a problem!
[TENKA]
Uh?
You'll probably want to
make haste for the shrine.
We have intelligence
that Naoto Kagami
is en route there as we speak.
Naoto Kagami?
[OFFICER 1]
The man's a lunatic.
He's carved a bloody path all
the way from the Choshu region.
Anyone in support
of the government
is fair game.
There won't be a lot of people
at the shrine this
time of day, but...
Soramaru!
Chutaro!
You're Tenka Kumoh,
is that right?
Sorry, but I'm going to
need you to stay here.
That's cute. You think I'm
going to do whatever you say.
[SOLDIER 1]
I am prepared to use
force if necessary.
[grunting]
I'm prepared to leave.
Do yourself a favor and move.
Oh, man.
Sora's so ticked
at me right now.
[KAGAMI]
Hiya, sport.
You're the youngest
Brother of the Cloud, right?
Uh. Who are you?
Just someone looking
to grease a palm
for a ride out to Gokumonjo.
I'm on a secret government
mission, you see.
I've been instructed to
deliver a special package.
Uh, sounds neat,
but Tenny said we're
not working today.
Huh. Well this is awkward.
I didn't realize you
gentlemen took holidays.
Can you work an oar, son?
No, sir.
Not without Tenny's
permission I can't.
I picked up quite a few stories
about you and your
brothers on the way here.
You're pretty strong, huh?
I don't know about that,
but Tenny sure is, sir!
Heh. He's amazing.
I'd be lucky to be
like him when I grow up!
Whoa.
Now Tenny's the oldest, right?
Uh-huh. Next oldest is Sora.
He's not as amazing as Tenny
but the food he
makes is delicious!
And now he wishes I were dead.
I thought poop would
make everything okay
but all it did was make
him madder at me.
Aw, there, there, kiddo.
Don't lose heart.
He'll come around.
Huh?
Imagine what'd he'd think if
you ferried me to Gokumonjo,
all by yourself
without any help.
I'd be impressed.
You've become a man, Chutaro!
I'm so proud I could cry!
No. No.
You know, I had brothers
of my own once upon a time.
Our family was torn
part years ago, though.
I haven't seen them
since I was little.
It's sad.
I can't remember
their faces now.
But deep down,
something tells me
we'll all be
reunited one day.
I shouldn't be
telling you this,
but the mission I'm on
might help me find them.
As a matter of fact,
you're in a unique position
to help me make that so.
I could help you?
All right then, I'll do it!
You can count on me, sir!
Excellent.
I had a feeling.
[CHUTARO]
Let's go!
[SORAMARU]
Chutaro!
[CHUTARO]
Oh, hey! You came back!
I don't know who you are,
but get the hell away
from my brother!
[CHUTARO]
What?
[SORAMARU]
Run and get Shirasu.
[CHUTARO]
Uh.
I have to take this
man to Gokumonjo.
Do as I say!
[CHURATO crying]
Oh boo.
Did you have to make him cry?
I'm gonna gamble and say
you're not from around here.
That weird accent
is pure Choshu.
Soften that tone a bit, huh?
I'm just a simple
traveler hoping to book
passage in your pretty
little boat, nothing more.
Spare me the act.
I happened to pass three
policemen on the way here.
Every one of them a corpse.
Coincidentally, you
reek of their blood.
I must be speaking
to the eldest.
I'm told you're amazing.
Must be hard living
up to that hype, huh?
Wouldn't want
to disappoint you.
[KAGAMI]
Oh-ho.
So you're Tenka?
The one and only.
Now what may I ask does
a filthy, murdering lowlife
want with a warrior?
Oh. Just a bit of fun!
Is that all?
You guys are supposed
to be the army?
Tenka, please!
You've gone too far!
Who says?
[OFFICER] You've taken
out a battalion, sir.
They started this mess.
My conscience is clear.
No retreat!
But, sir!
Do not mistake our
opponent for a man.
He is a monster.
Coming through, boys!
Nothing personal.
Who are you losers
taking orders from anyway?
From me.
Rakucho Takeda.
My squadron answers
to the government.
Well doesn't that sound fancy.
--[TAKEDA] You and me. Now.
--[TENKA] Meh.
[TAKEDA]
What?
I'm not doing this
for the hell of it.
I have somewhere to be.
So, sorry but some other time!
You dare to run from me?
Try to look at the bright side.
I would've totally wiped
the floor with you.
Of course you would flee!
Just as from your past!
Yes, I imagine it's
sensible to turn a blind eye.
Must protect your
brothers from the truth.
From what the Orochi--
I get it, you're a masochist.
[TENKA]
That do it for you?
Let's get one thing straight.
Whether you're military or not,
under these clouds, my clan
defends the common good.
You're not the law.
You're just pissing the law off.
That's rich.
You lecturing me
about the common good.
This squadron could've
used your strength!
Yet you fritter it away
in this backwater
while your country
is in shambles!
Charity begins at home.
Besides, what do you want?
It's all I can do to keep
the people close to me
out of harm's way.
Poor trees.
Your shrine won't
have any shade.
What is he?
I--
[MAN]
Naoto Kagami.
A fisherman from
the Choshu region.
Ambidextrous. Slim build.
Considerable
upper-body strength.
Combat training unknown.
Though he studied at Seizan,
where evidently the seed
of his ultra-nationalist
politics was first planted.
His methods are
bloody and merciless.
So much so he was
estranged from his own cause.
This is his idea of revenge.
His preferred weapon
is called Dodomeki,
a kind of sword.
Our latest reports place
him in the vicinity of Shiga.
That's all we know.
But why, if he's such
a bloody-minded
anti-foreign zealot,
would he bare his fangs against
the government of his Emperor?
It's not our job to
puzzle out the rationale
of a man driven mad
with devotion.
The point being,
he's in Shiga.
I say ignore it.
Let the police do their job.
I'd agree.
Except Takeda's already
moved in without authorization.
Our hand's forced.
Well, the Kumoh Shrine
is in that neighborhood.
Might be useful.
We'll scrounge for information
on the vessels
while we're there.
[WOMAN]
Where the Commander goes,
it's for us to follow.
[SORAMARU]
No! No running away!
You're killing me, champ.
What, ain't you got any pride?
You're the eldest.
Fight like it.
Heh. Word is you're looking
for the Orochi's vessel.
[SORAMARU]
Huh? Orochi? What the--
Tenka.
What have you gotten
yourself into this time?
Damn it!
Why do you always
keep stuff from me?
[KAGAMI]
Hello?
Anybody home?
Spoilsport.
What do we have here?
Who're you?
[SHIRASU]
That boy is vitally important.
I ask that you leave him be.
A Fuma?
[SORAMARU]
Wow.
They're so fast I can't
even see what they're doing.
[SORAMARU]
I knew Shirasu was strong, but
this is insane.
Whoa!
I never thought
this guy could fight
at the same level as Shiro!
Wha--?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Uh. I wasn't supposed
to come back?
They keep you on a leash, eh?
The ninja must be
hard-up for new masters.
Careful.
I wouldn't presume to
know the score if I were you.
All that skill and you're
just a glorified servant!
Shirasu!
It's not so simple
as all that, my friend.
[SHIRASU]
The Fuma are nothing.
Pale shadows.
Changeable ghosts.
We are but servants by choice.
Beholden only to the wind.
At peril scorned.
[SORAMARU]
Oh, no! You're wounded!
We have to stop the bleeding!
Chutaro, make a bandage! Now!
Yes, sir!
[SHIRASU]
But you'll ruin your clothes.
Don't be stupid, you're hurt!
[KAGAMI]
Isn't this adorable?
Seems everybody
wants a piece of me.
How sweet.
Now, this is what I call fun!
Shirasu, look out!
Hey. This guy bothering you?
You're running late.
[TENKA]
Sorry, got held up.
[KAGAMI]
Who is this?
[TENKA]
You been living under
a rock or something?
The name's Tenka Kumoh,
AKA, "He Who Laughs
Under the Clouds."
Ah! The genuine article!
What a relief.
[KAGAMI]
See, you look the part.
Shame you're a lapdog
for the Powers That Be.
Here we go.
Another day, another
anti-government thug.
Oh, you have no idea.
This regime makes
my blood boil.
[CHOSHU RONIN 1]
The Shogunate is helping foreign
interests make inroads on Japan!
[CHOSHU RONIN 2]
It's invasion, pure and simple!
[CHOSHU RONIN 3]
The Emperor must be protected!
[KAGAMI]
I made sacrifice upon sacrifice
for this country,
only to see my homeland rot,
my comrades abandon me.
The Emperor was my
whole world. My god.
My very soul was his,
and he seized it!
So what now? You want revenge?
[KAGAMI]
Isn't that a man's right,
when his loyalty is
repaid with contempt?
When the world is broken.
Its god must die!
This crazy bastard
wants to kill the Emperor?
Yes, that's why he wanted
access to Gokumonjo.
If he can free the criminals
interred within its walls,
Japan will be
plunged into anarchy.
So, rebellion doesn't interest
him. He wants chaos.
Yeah, that's the idea.
[TENKA]
Not on my watch.
Oh, very well.
What's a man to a god-killer?
I'll give you the
benefit of the doubt,
and take that as a compliment!
See, the trouble
is a guy like you
can't see the forest
for the trees.
You can't affect squat.
What do you know?
A lot more than you.
[TENKA]
Look,
hate on the government
all you want.
Just don't think
Japan owes anything
to someone whose
loyalty is so easily shaken.
The world is a big place.
There's more than enough
room for us to sort things out.
You got issues,
I got time.
[KAGAMI]
You're not going to kill me?
You'll regret this. I promise.
Because one day,
I'll steal your soul,
and all you hold dear.
[TENKA]
Talk is cheap.
You're not gonna reduce me to
whatever the hell you are, pal.
Try, and I'll make you
eat your words every time.
[KAGAMI]
Do it, then!
Nourish me on my own venom!
One would think
you'd have learned
not to turn your
back on an enemy.
Hello, Tenka Kumoh.
Hey! If it ain't
Commander Sosei!
I'm surprised a
jackboot of your rank
would put in an appearance.
Please tell me he
knows this guy.
They've something
of a history, yes.
See, his squad
is known as the Yamainu.
They report to the
Minister of the Right.
So, what brings
you out this way?
Not much. Least that's
our usual policy in this area.
But every so often, mistakes
must be handled personally.
Apologies. Takeda acted alone.
Threatening commoners is not
a tactic the squad condones.
It was cute, though.
[laughing]
Feeling kinda
forgotten about, boys!
Technically this isn't my job.
So stay down.
Ah! You and those
nifty vital-point attacks.
When I watch you
work I get chills.
[SOSEI]
Shut up.
Hm? Wow, nice. Miss you, too.
Thanks for dropping by.
Watch the sarcasm.
I don't gab with traitors.
[SOSEI]
Let's move out.
Well. Shall we go home?
[TENKA]
Sure.
[SORAMARU]
So that's the Yamainu Squad.
[MAN]
So,
you failed to secure
Tenka Kumoh's consent.
What does it say about us
if we can't cooperate
with a man formerly
of our own squad?
All due respect, sir, in this
case it speaks to our merit.
I cannot work with
him in good conscience.
I implore the 14th Head
of the Kumoh Shrine.
Tenka Kumoh.
[TENKA]
What is this? Who are you?
[BOTAN]
A searcher, as you are.
One who hunts the Great Snake.
Take heed, for you and I
are not the only seekers
whom Destiny leads to this pass.
[SOSEI]
Our goal is very simple.
[BOTH] Locate the Vessel
by any means necessary,
before the Orochi can return.
--[TENKA] And protect it.
--[SOSEI] And break it.
[BOTAN]
You mean what you say.
Protect the Vessel
of the Orochi?
[TENKA]
It's the Orochi
we should be hunting,
not the person who
serves as its vessel.
I'm not a big fan of
spilling innocent blood.
[SORAMARU]
The vessel of the Orochi?
I don't understand.
What's going on?