[TAIKO]
Tenka.
I'd like you to meet
your baby brother.
[BABY SORAMARU coos]
Now, he's very small, so it's
your job to protect him.
No! Soramaru! Chutaro!
[HIRARI]
Wakey wakey.
Welcome back.
[TENKA]
So, I'm in shackles now?
Don't look at me, man.
You're the one making
our job a pain in the ass.
[door unlatches]
That, and there's
somebody here to see you
who demanded to be let in.
You're alive.
Oh, Master Tenka, never
in my wildest dreams!
You were in on this
from the beginning,
weren't you, Doctor Ohta?
[OHTA]
Being in the government's secret
medical Research Division
does have its perks.
Eleven years ago,
this remarkable young man
sustained a grievous injury
protecting his brother.
His life hung in the balance.
But the Research Division has
its tricks and you had yours.
Isn't that right, doc?
You saved Tenka's life
at the eleventh hour.
Y'see, the government had
been running clandestine trials
on a compound made
from Orochi cells.
Nothing on humans, at first.
But then along comes a wounded
hero at death's door, and boom.
Perfect test subject.
Everybody's happy.
Tenka's injuries heal,
and the government
gets its miracle drug.
Please understand, he wished
to live whatever the cost.
Even if the cure left
him less than human.
[YOUNG TENKA] Look, I'm not
going anywhere yet.
I'm all the rug rats have left.
One day the Orochi will
take full control of you.
Yeah, but no worries.
I'll keep fighting
as long as I can.
Well, technically, I really
should've been executed.
As soon as the
Serpent took over,
they were gonna cut me
open and root around.
Why'd you see fit
to let me live?
Wasn't me. We got
orders from the brass
not to go through with it.
I guess you're worth more
alive and in one piece.
[TENKA]
How are Soramaru and Chutaro?
They okay?
I'm afraid not.
Chutaro went missing
several days ago
and still hasn't turned up.
What?
Things are that much
worse with Soramaru.
Wait, what do you mean?
Turns out he's the
actual Orochi vessel.
[gasps]
Please forgive me, master!
But Soramaru has been taken by
the remnants of the Fuma clan!
Shirasu Kinjo has betrayed us,
and is acting as their chief.
[grunting]
Hang on. What're you doing?
My brothers.
They need me.
But, sir! In your condition!
The Orochi doesn't have me yet.
I'm still a Kumoh, damn it.
Least for the time being.
Tenka.
Ah, what the hell.
Do what you gotta
do, my friend.
Go.
Just get outta here.
Hey, if I don't save 'em,
who else is gonna, right?
Chains are definitely not
that man's natural habitat.
You don't know
the half of it, doc.
He needs freedom
like he needs air.
It's uncanny.
Like we've known
each other for ages.
[heavy breathing]
It's nothing. Ignore it.
You've come this far,
so chin up.
Keep laughing.
[gong]
[TAKAMINE]
I've failed you.
I'm sorry.
[SOSEI]
Don't speak of failure.
You had no way of knowing.
Focus on getting better.
Sir.
That's good.
I'm glad Takamine's
on the rebound.
We'll marshal all of our efforts
to catch the Orochi alive.
I hope that's understood.
All due respect, sir.
Is that even possible?
[door opens]
I have it on good authority
that the Kumoh family swords
can separate the Orochi
from its host.
The second Kumoh brother
has them right now.
You'll wanna get them back ASAP.
[SOSEI]
Go.
Show no mercy
to those who resist.
Sasaki.
There's something you
ought to know first.
Mister Iwakura is convalescing.
I spoke with Shi earlier today.
It appears the Minister has
undergone major surgery.
I take it he's battling
some illness?
[SOSEI]
The operation was successful,
but I'm told the likelihood
of relapse is very high.
Also, Takamine believes that
the government is conducting
experiments with a treatment
involving Orochi cells.
[KIIKO]
That's madness!
[SOSEI]
Perhaps.
Nonetheless, such
cells are thought
to redouble a human being's
healing capabilities.
It is Shi's opinion that
Tenka Kumoh may have been used
as a test subject in
developing the treatment.
You think Iwakura would
go to such lengths?
[SOSEI]
Of course.
The man lives in fear
of his own mortality.
He'll grasp at
what straws he may
if it extends his interval
upon this earth.
[SHIRASU]
Lord Orochi.
The Yamainu Squad
is on the move.
[KOTARO]
They would ensnare you, my lord.
Time is of the essence.
It is in our best
interest to act.
We await your word.
Give us your orders and
we spring on the instant.
I believe he has his own ideas
on what's to be done next.
[wind howling]
[KOTARO]
Incredible.
So this is the Orochi's power.
I see now.
Our lord would
have his vengeance
upon the land
which subdued him.
[sword cutting]
[grunting]
Any luck yet?
It's no use, sir!
None of them will say where
the Orochi is being held!
That's the Head Warden
of Gokumonju.
Why in heaven's name?
Safe to say the man
is not on our side.
He's with the Fuma?
[SOSEI]
Seems so.
I doubt the grand prison break
could have been realized
without his blessing.
Yamainu.
You are all hereby
sentenced to death.
Last I checked, it was
your job to execute sentence,
not pass it.
Things are not as they were!
[grunting]
Cross swords with me and
you cross swords with the Abe.
[grunts]
Out with it. Where is
the Orochi being hidden?
[ORITA]
What good would it do you?
You're dead either way.
Look out!
Only a fool would
point a gun at me.
[slashing]
[grunts]
[SOSEI]
I lead by virtue of Empire.
We fight by virtue of right.
You have only your desperation.
[grunts]
[TAKEDA]
Takamine!
Sorry I'm late, sir.
Came as soon as I could.
We are bound together by
our devotion to this country.
Impossible.
[SOSEI]
We are the Yamainu,
the guard dogs of Japan.
If you wish to
sentence us to death,
summon your lord
and run like hell.
Ten.
Gen, myou, shin.
Kai, ou.
[grunting]
[ASHIYA]
Jin, tsuu, ryou.
A nasty bit of magic, as usual.
Surest means to a confession.
It can't be helped.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I've brought someone with me
you'll probably want to meet.
She's the Abe familiar
Ashiya was telling us about.
[SOSEI]
Ah.
Madam, you do us an honor.
--It's nice to meet you.
--Hey, there.
The name's Hirari
from the Shiga police.
How you guys doin'?
Hello.
It is the intent of the Yamainu
to catch the Orochi alive.
Can we count on your help?
[BOTAN]
Our goals are one and the same.
Do we know if the
creature has a weakness?
It is the sun,
in all likelihood.
The Serpent's rebirth is
facilitated by an overcast sky.
From this, we can surmise
that some quality of the sun
undermines his vitality.
I say we expose the bastard to
daylight and see what happens.
And how do we do that?
We use the Lake Biwa tunnel.
The canal system
connecting Shiga to Kyoto?
[INUKAI]
I remember,
the fundraiser gala.
The Minister's pet project.
Well, I know where
the Orochi is.
What should we do?
At this point, even the
smallest chance of success
is worthwhile.
We'll drive the enemy through
the tunnel beneath Lake Biwa,
and into the light of Kyoto.
The beast must see dawn!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
It is in our interest
to follow them.
So, we telling 'em
Tenka's alive, or is that
something we keep to ourselves?
I mean, these Yamainu
people are his friends, right?
[BOTAN]
I wish I could say.
Alas, friends are
all too hard to come by.
We must take care.
There is at least one person
in all of this who is untried.
Who she aligns with,
I do not know.
[NISHIKI]
I have been searching for you,
Master Soramaru.
[KOTARO]
He is not who he was.
Your search has been
in vain, my dear.
You are the girl who sought me
within the walls of Gokumonjo,
are you not?
My deepest apologies.
I had no inkling you would be
entitled to my allegiance.
But of course.
You are an Unfledged.
I would not expect you
to know who I was.
[NISHIKI]
Please.
Save me from this fate.
Let me serve you.
Peace is hell.
It plays havoc with my will.
I am a ninja.
A tool to be used.
Nothing more.
Without you,
without orders, I am
dust in the wind.
Such as I am, I humbly
pledge my all to you.
Soramaru.
[slashing]
[KITAMURA]
Chutaro!
Hey!
Just stay where you are!
Lookie here, somebody's
feeling brave.
[OWL hooting]
[SHIRASU] Why have you let
the aberration approach him?
[KOTARO]
She is half Fuma, brother.
Family is family.
[NISHIKI]
Master.
It is widely known that these
swords have protected those of
Kumoh blood for generations.
But less well known is that
they were once devoured.
These weapons and the spells
used to seal your lordship
roiled together in your belly
three hundred years ago,
until they became as one.
There are rumors, master,
that these swords can cleave
you from your chosen host.
Family or not, the girl's
loyalties lie elsewhere.
[NISHIKI]
Master Soramaru is what?
[BOTAN] Divulging this much
to you may well prove
to be ill-advised.
It just so happens
you're uniquely qualified.
The time has come.
Are you a Fuma?
Or do you serve the Kumoh line?
[NISHIKI]
I've never felt this way before.
Never acted without orders.
And here I am, defying my
own flesh and blood.
I do this for you, Soramaru.
For the chance of seeing
your smile again.
[slashing]
--[metal clanking]
--[grunting]
We don't have any
quarrel with these two!
They were in a position
to spare your Tenny
from the gallows,
and they did nothing.
So we just keep killing
till nobody's left?
Run, Chutaro! Go!
[slashing]
[groaning]
Stay down! Don't
try to fight him!
Enough of this.
Get out of the way, weakling.
Call me whatever you want.
If I abandoned them,
I'd deserve it.
Weak or not.
I'm making a stand!
[grunting]
Please don't be mad at me.
There's got to be more to
life than seeking revenge!
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll even catch fish.
Just stop this!
All I've done and this
is how you repay me.
It ever occur to you that
the Emperor is personally
responsible for the
monster I've become?
Take away my right to be
that and what have I got?
You're not a monster,
you're just alone, okay?
The path you're on
isn't the only choice.
There's another road!
[crying]
Easy for you to say, kid.
Try being forced to make
your way in the world
without a family before
preachin' to me about choice.
[roaring]
[CHUTARO]
What's going on? Wha--?
[grunting]
[footsteps departing]
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, go ahead.
Leave me behind.
I'm used to it by now.
[animalistic grunts]
Gerokichi? Is that you?
[GEROKICHI grunts]
When did you get so--?
Hey, be careful how you stop!
[grunting]
[CHUTARO]
Are you all right?
Hey, our swords!
[clattering]
Huh? Sora?
The swords you
requested, Miss Botan.
We are all in your
debt. I thank you.
Go!
Flee into the canal
tunnel while we can!
--We must go!
--I don't understand.
What the heck is going
on here, ma'am?
Get on Poko.
I'll explain to you as we ride.
[growling]
Uh, ma'am?
Sora's keeping up with us.
That isn't your brother.
He's been possessed
by the Orochi.
Seriously?
Listen to me very
carefully, Chutaro.
You must take the Kumoh swords
and lure the Serpent
through the canal
tunnel into Kyoto.
He'll be fine.
All you have to do is
lead him into the sunlight.
You've ever served this
family well, Poko.
I'm counting on you!
[grunting]
Stand your ground.
So, the leader
makes an appearance.
Knock it off!
What are you doing?
Miss Botan.
Where's Master Soramaru?
He's chasing his brave little
brother through the tunnel
beneath Shiga.
[leaves rustling]
[birds chirping]
There's no graver sin than
to turn one's back on blood.
[heavy footsteps]
We should almost be
there by now--
Ah!
Oh, no! It's a dead end!
[growling]
[crunching]
[screaming]
One can see why
he leads, I suppose.
Something tells me this
is going to be difficult.
[SHIRASU] I do hope you ladies
are prepared to meet your end.
[electricity crackling]
My name is Chutaro Kumoh
and I am the third son!
And I am the brother
of Tenka and Soramaru!
[grunting]
Please, you gotta
snap out of this!
It's time for us to go home!
[grunting]
[TENKA]
Chutaro!
Soramaru!
Enough of this screwin' around.
You're alive!
[growls]
[laughs]
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
History is forged
when the wisdom of old age
braids itself to
the fire of adolescence.
Youth shall be blacksmiths
of the coming era.
Seize the bellows
and craft steel!