[BOTAN]
You mean what you say.
Protect the Vessel
of the Orochi?
[TENKA] It's the Orochi
we should be hunting,
not the person who
serves as its vessel.
I'm not a big fan of
spilling innocent blood.
[BOTAN]
Then I've a favor to ask,
Master Tenka.
[KAGAMI]
Heh.
Word is you're looking
for the Orochi's vessel.
Talk to me.
What is the Orochi?
Eavesdropping. New low for you.
Is this "vessel" like
someone dangerous, or--
Oh, yeah. Actually,
it's Yamada from town.
Don't blow me off again!
Hey!
Please just talk to me.
Knock it off, runt.
You're killing me!
Sounds like somebody's
feeling a little left out.
Do you feel left
out? Huh? Huh?
Is him lonesome?
Aw, c'mon.
Lighten up. I'm kidding.
[SORAMARU]
Why do you always
keep me in the dark?
One day, I--
[TENKA]
Hm?
[SORAMARU]
Am I really that big
of a liability?
I'm going to get strong.
One day, I won't
be a kid anymore.
[SORAMARU]
Slow down.
Slow down!
That's enough, sir.
It's time for a bit of rest.
Not yet. I'll be all right.
Don't push yourself.
There's value in stillness.
I was beaten so easily.
Why can't I make any headway?
Have I hit the limit
of what I can do?
[dish clanking]
[TENKA]
Oh, sorry. My bad.
Not my scene.
[WOMAN]
Oh my.
Aren't we the proverbial
fish out of water?
Hey! Kiiko!
What on earth
are you doing here?
Your head must be spinning.
I guess it's an
occupational hazard
when you're the first born.
Gotta put on a monkey suit
from time to time.
[chuckles]
The more things change.
[TENKA]
Ha! You're looking good, though.
You're almost kind of
respectable in that gown.
Seriously. It flatters you.
Well, occupational
hazard, I suppose.
[TENKA]
You on duty?
Master Tenka,
good of you to come.
An honor, I'm sure.
[TENKA]
Old Man Iwakura?
It's been quite some time.
The old gang just isn't
the same without
you, sad to say.
[SOSEI]
The Gokumonjo rumor.
What do we know?
[TAKAMINE]
Right.
Well, sir.
As you know, the
underworld will talk.
Felons on route to Gokumonjo
are told to bring
something with them.
What that something
is, we've no idea.
But it seems to me the more
pertinent question is
who's collecting it?
And, being a rumor, local law
enforcement's uninterested.
So, we act on what we have?
No. Based on our intel
that would be unwise.
Then a closer
investigation's in order.
I volunteer, sir!
Request to infiltrate!
I think not. Request denied.
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
Tai-Yang is an option.
Tenka, huh?
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
His proximity to Gokumonjo
makes him the ideal candidate.
Does it not?
Why shrink from using him?
I won't repeat myself.
Let's just say
I have my reasons.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Hold it!
You can't go back there!
Huh? What's going on?
A moment, please, Commander!
[SORAMARU]
I throw myself on your mercy!
I beg you, teach me
the way of the sword!
[TENKA]
You came here all the way
from Tokyo?
That kind of surprises me.
[IWAKURA]
I have some business
with Kyoto's governor.
He and I have been consulting
on the design of
the new canal system.
The what?
Lake Biwa's slated
to be the hub.
It'll connect Shiga with Tokyo.
Canals are a keystone
of the Reconstruction Plan.
What did you think tonight's
ball was a fundraiser for?
Huh. I wondered why
I got asked to this thing.
[IWAKURA]
Your exploits
are spoken of far and wide.
The Yamainu Squad would welcome
you back with open arms.
Yeah, no thanks.
I got enough on my plate
with the fam as is.
Plus I'm nobody's dog.
Beg your pardon,
but the governor would
like to have a moment
to speak with you, sir.
Ah. Duty calls.
If you two would excuse me.
Old Man Iwakura.
Heh. Who'd have
seen that coming?
[KIIKO]
You really ought to
show him more respect.
Who cares? It's not like
I work for the guy anymore.
Thankfully so.
If you took up arms
with the squad again,
it'd be a disaster.
What was that you said
about the more things change?
Don't be smart.
We're different.
I doubt you'd even
recognize us anymore.
Do your brothers know
how it was in the old days?
No. Not a burden I'm
eager for them to carry.
[KIIKO]
They're Kumoh.
One day they'll have to.
[SOSEI]
Request denied.
I've neither the time nor the
inclination to educate you.
Don't do this to me!
I need to surpass Tenka!
Look, boy.
I'm motivated by profit.
It's as simple as that.
If I school you in the
ways of swordsmanship,
I expect a return
on my investment.
[SORAMARU]
I-- I'll work for you.
[SOSEI]
I have people working for me.
Not interested.
Goodbye.
[door closes]
Sorry about that.
Once the Commander
makes up his mind, he's a stone.
Even so, what was
the point of coming here?
Would it not be
better to find a dojo?
Probably, yeah.
But the way he stopped
Kagami dead in his tracks.
And, he looks-- well, he's not
all that much bigger than me.
[TAKEDA]
You have a good eye.
Gee, you think?
Watch it.
I don't care for
that casual tone.
Whatever.
Like I'm worried about a grunt.
I am a member of the Yamainu--
Ni hao.
Huh?
"Ni hao"?
Shi. Must you--
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
I am Shi Qian-Lang
of the Yamainu.
Master Shi, if you please.
Unless I mistake
your zeal, I believe
we may be of mutual
benefit to one another.
How far are you willing to go?
Try me.
You're going to go through
with this? I mean, for real?
[SORAMARU]
Yes. I promised I would,
but you can't breathe
a word of this to Tenka.
What do you mean
"a certain something?"
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
That is the question.
All we know is
that someone inside
the prison is collecting it.
We'd like to find out who.
[SORAMARU]
Why use me?
Your job provides
the ideal cover.
No one will suspect anything.
This is absurd!
The boy is untested!
Not 20 minutes ago
you were insisting
Tenka ought to be our man!
[SORAMARU]
I can do this!
Just give me a chance, please!
I'll take the burden!
My brother already has
more than his fair share.
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
Excellent.
So it's decided.
Sneak in. Bring back
some answers.
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
We profit, you profit.
[DOCTOR]
Your symptoms
seemed to have worsened.
[TENKA]
Yeah. Sure.
Blah-blah. I'm late
for breakfast, doc.
[DOCTOR] You should rest
a little while longer.
Sorry. Really wish I could.
But my brothers are
waiting on me, so...
[SORAMARU]
I'm counting on you.
Keep an eye on the real guy.
Do not let him loose.
Uh. Sure.
I'll be quick,
all right? No hassle.
[WARDEN]
Ah. It's the little one.
They got you working
by yourself today?
[CHUTARO]
Uh. Yes! Yes, sir!
Hello, loving household!
Welcome back.
Oh. Did Sora not
come with you?
Do what?
I felt certain that he--
Excuse me, Chutaro?
Any idea where
your brother's got to?
[CHUTARO]
Nope. No clue.
[SHIRASU]
I do hope he's not
been caught up in something.
Well, damn. Hold down the fort.
I'll go look for the idiot.
Hold on! I wanna come with you!
I am no one to be feared.
No? What are you, then?
My name is Botan.
I am your youngest
charge's teacher.
Kindly lower your blade.
[SHIRASU]
Why would I do that?
This is rather awkward.
Has Tenka said nothing?
[BOTAN]
I must know.
Will you or will you not
allow me to help?
I pledge all that I
have to your cause.
My prospects are few
and my allies even fewer.
But I will not disappoint you.
This I avow.
How could I say no to that?
Are you so quick
to give your faith?
[TENKA]
Sometimes.
Depends on the eyes of
the person asking for it.
You've got honest ones.
And that spark makes
'em irresistible.
So yeah, you got me.
Yes, well. You are not
the first to say as much.
Hm?
[BOTAN]
On my honor.
By my life and all
that I hold dear.
I shall never betray you.
Brothers of the Cloud.
[BOTAN]
I am a sworn ally
of the family you serve.
[SHIRASU]
So you maintain, madam.
Yet I find it a struggle
to believe you.
Your scent is not that
of a normal person.
My own is faint, to be sure.
But yours?
[BOTAN] What an un-chivalrous
thing to say.
You know the stare of
narrowed eyes, do you not?
You are,
after all, a Fuma.
[BOTAN]
One who put his own blood
before the lives of
master and countrymen
while the land thundered
to the stamp of civil war.
What it must be
to bear the contempt
of all but your
extinct clansmen,
and to be shunned
like a plague dog.
Of course, I can relate to
both sides of that sentiment.
The Fuma are ghosts
of an extinguished age.
But you may revile
phantoms as you will.
[SHIRASU]
That said.
Raise a hand
against the
Brothers of the Cloud
and you forfeit your life.
Your loyalty to
them is so strong?
[SHIRASU]
I learned well
to give none but my clansmen
the benefit of the doubt.
To suspect everyone.
But Tenka and his siblings.
They, in their innocence,
take the world at face value.
And thus I play the
skeptic on their behalf.
Such is my debt.
As you will.
[BOTAN grunting]
Our first order of business
is prisoner orientation.
Cause trouble or give me lip,
immediate grounds
for severe reprimand.
Say goodbye to
basic human rights.
You now have none.
The sole purpose of your life
from here on out is penance.
[SORAMARU]
What is that noise?
Is it the wind?
Wait, no. No, it's not.
Those are voices.
Welcome to hell.
[SORAMARU]
No kidding.
This really is hell.
Hey, what the--
Whoa. It's you!
[coughing]
Are you okay, man?
Oh, yes. The Master will
see to it in good time.
I'm fine. Better than fine.
Well, just take it easy.
You-- you still have your hair.
You're new here. Ah!
Did you bring it?
Don't wait too long.
You have to give it to
the Master at your first
opportunity!
Do you mean, like, the
thing from all the rumors?
Who is the Master?
You there! What's going on?
On your feet at once!
This man needs rest.
Better yet, a doctor! Now!
Who do you think
you're talking to?
You want a stint in
the Chamber of Punishment?
You haven't been
here long, have ya?
[WARDEN 1]
Stand up!
[WARDEN 2]
Degenerate.
[OFFICER]
All right. Get him back to work.
New guy.
Snap to and follow me.
[WOMAN]
Gonzo Gonda?
That was your name, right?
[SORAMARU]
Uh. Right! Yeah.
Your story. How did
you get into this place?
Wha-- What d'you mean?
[WOMAN]
Your crime.
Well, uh--
Actually, my memory
is kind of shot.
It's all a haze.
So you have amnesia?
Your entrance papers
gave no indication of it.
Well, it's only been
an issue recently.
See, for the past few days,
when I think about this
one time when I was five,
my throat closes up.
Gonzo Gonda.
You have three accounts
of armed robbery.
One count of attempted escape.
Hence the additional sentence.
That ring any bells?
[SORAMARU]
Yeah. Sounds about right.
Get used to being alone,
and only worry about yourself
at the expense of others.
You'll find camaraderie
very rare.
[WOMAN]
Gokumonjo is the home
of those with blood
on their hands.
Except,
for some reason,
I don't smell blood on you.
Whatever you're hiding,
I will find out.
[WARDEN]
Get out. Move.
[KAGAMI]
That was nice. I liked it.
Maybe you should change the
name to the Chamber of Reward.
[SORAMARU]
Kagami?
They brought him here?
[WOMAN] Wait here for
a moment. Don't move.
Uh.
[TENKA]
What the hell is going on?
Uh. I know this looks bad.
But it's not what
you think, I swear it!
[muffled grunt]
Who's this guy supposed to be?
I believe that would
be the criminal
we apprehended this morning.
Aw, come on, you guys!
Why would he even be here?
Next you're probably going to
ask me if Sora traded clothes
with him so he could
sneak into Gokumonjo,
which he didn't do!
'Cause that'd be
as crazy as me...
[TENKA]
Interesting.
...watching the guy while
he's gone, which I'm not.
One moment.
Your color isn't too good.
You're in no condition
to retrieve him.
I don't have much choice.
We can't just leave him there.
[SHIRASU]
Very well. Then use me.
What'd I say about that word?
You're not a damn
servant, you're a friend.
I am what I am, yes.
There's no shame in that.
Rootless, though
I am still a ninja.
You know the extent of my skill.
I can bring Soramaru home.
Whether as a friend
or no, give the order.
All right, you win.
I don't ask this because
you were a Fuma.
I ask because you're
someone that I respect.
Bring my brother home. Please.
Must you be such a mule?
I am what I am.
No shame in that.
[SHIRASU]
I shall return.
[KAGAMI]
Time flies
when you're cooped up in there.
I was expecting
something much worse.
Seriously.
Am I just too jaded?
Or is it called
death row because
they bore you to death?
I can think of so
many better ways to do it.
Not that I'm eager to die.
Way too many folks out
there I'd rather kill first.
[SORAMARU]
He's crazy.
Indulge me.
What on earth are you going to
do with a bunch of poppies.
What does that mean?
Like eavesdropping?
Why don't we listen closer?
Leave. Now.
Oh, give me a break,
Mr. Head Warden.
I've been in here
for all of five minutes.
Sorry, got a problem
with vermin.
Huh. This one looks kind
of familiar to me, actually.
We met somewhere?
I don't know.
It's a small world.
[WARDEN]
Clever.
Must have confused him
with this guy I saw once.
No one special.
Just a whiny
little middle child.
[door locks]
[MASKED MAN]
Make yourself at home.
Under this roof,
we are all family.
[SORAMARU]
That smell.
Is that--
[MASKED MAN]
Wretched souls
toiling long and hard...
[SORAMARU]
He's gathering poppies.
...to cleanse ourselves of sin.
[MASKED MAN]
Believe in me.
I know your mind.
Yes. I know your mind
and will help you.
As blood helps blood.
[SORAMARU]
Wha-- What's wrong with me?
Why do I feel--
[MASKED MAN]
What troubles you?
[SORAMARU]
No.
It was you, you--
you killed them.
You killed them!
Tenny, sir? It's starting
to rain real bad.
I don't know what's
taking Sora so long.
[TENKA]
Don't come in here!
Do me a favor, huh?
Bring in the wash?
Uh. Sure.
[TENKA]
Soramaru.
Nobody wants to
keep you in the dark.
It's just...
one of these days,
you'll find out how
strong you really are,
and sooner than you think.
'Cause you won't have an option.
The one in the dark
will be me.