Uhhhha...
[breathing]
What troubles you?
No, no... it was you,
you... you killed them!
You killed them!
[slamming noise]
[screams]
[punching]
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
I do not like to
reprimand family.
Calm yourself.
You're not my family!
[thunder]
Poor, tragic creature.
If it is your wont
to bear a grudge,
curse the day you
were born a Kumoh.
Your mother I did
not intend to kill.
Tenka. Help me. Please.
You bastard!
The eldest.
Tenka, I...
[baby crying]
Who are you? Show yourself!
I'm sorry!
Soramaru!
Idiot, you don't just
come out like that.
Oh... oh, no...
Hey, hey, hey...
It's okay.
You understand?
No worries. Look at me.
I'm all right. Nothin'
I can't laugh off.
There's no reason
to be afraid.
Remember, big brother's
here for you.
Your big brother's
always here for you.
Don't think about any of this.
Just push it all away.
Yeah? Give us a smile
so I know you understand.
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
Soramaru.
Hard to believe the size.
My god, how imposing.
Presumptuous punk.
Steal my thunder, will you?
This is my squad.
Greetings, Yamainu boy.
Oh, hello.
You serve the Kumoh
family, I believe?
What errand, might I ask,
brings you here?
Uh. Keeping watch.
Just double checking
the security.
Hm.
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Good, you're conscious.
Where?
Closest thing we
have to a clinic.
The head warden found
you passed out.
Took it upon himself
to carry you here.
Welcome back.
Passed out? I wish I could
say that's not like me.
Oh, man, I'm so pathetic.
Without Tenka, I'm nothing.
Just a scared little kid.
I couldn't do for him
what he did for me.
I need to know what you saw
in the isolation cell.
--What?
--A warden of my rank
isn't permitted to come
within 20 paces of the door.
I can only imagine
someone very dangerous
is on the other side.
--Who is it?
--I don't know, why can't you
just ask the higher-ups,
or whatever.
--I don't have clearance.
--Then maybe it's better
that you don't know.
--How's your head?
--Whoa! Hands off!
Well, what do we have here?
Looks like I'll have to tell
the higher-ups we've
got ourselves a spy.
All right, all right!
The guy was like...
I guess he wears a fox mask
and he has long, white hair.
His eyes were purple too,
so... well, you know.
The mark of the Fuma.
So, it is him.
Wait a minute? You know
who the bastard is?
What did he do to you?
--What do you care?
--I...
Do you know what it feels
like to lose your family
in the blink of an eye?
Ignore that. Slip of the tongue.
Please, sir! You want
revenge, right?
I can tell.
Call it what you like.
I intend to exact a price
commensurate with what I lost.
That is my right.
In my situation,
you would feel like I do.
I know. My parents were killed
by the man in that cell.
I want him dead.
But I'm just a kid, I'm
powerless to do anything.
Help me. And I'll
give you your revenge.
This position has its perks.
I have access to places
you do not.
We are the same. Let us demand
our price of him as one.
Wow, it suddenly
seems so easy.
It's been a while.
Aren't the higher-ups
expecting you back, sir?
You're... not gonna tell?
Your secret is safe.
Just stay sharp.
Thanks. I really appreciate it.
Tell me, how does
someone like you end up
in a place like this?
[explosion]
What the...?
Hey!
[WARDEN 1]
There's been an explosion!
[WARDEN 2]
Take cover! We're under attack!
Man your posts!
No one panic!
Sir, we have a situation!
The prisoners are
trying to escape!
--What?
--[explosion]
[prisoners shouting]
Stop this madness
at once! I order you!
[PRISONER 1]
Or what? You'll tack more years
onto a life sentence?
We got nothin' to lose, people!
[prisoners shouting]
[PRISONER 2]
Outta my way!
It's best if you all
return to your cells.
[PRISONER 3]
Says who?
--[blows landing]
--[PRISONERS groaning]
Someone who doesn't
care to repeat himself.
Wow. Who the hell is that?
Man answers to the
Minister of the Right.
He's doing some kind of thesis
on how we run things here.
[WARDEN 2]
So... he's a Yamainu?
What are gawking at?
Secure all the exits at once!
--Get to your posts!
--[WARDENS] Yes, sir!
Ugh... I'm here five
minutes and I get this.
--Are you coming?
--Yes... if it's not
too much trouble.
You'll carry more weight
with the guards than I will.
Perfect. This is what I
get for allying myself
with a ninja.
What's happening out there?
--Shhh.
--Wait, Shirasu?
I'm here to take
you back home.
Sorry I'm late.
Here. Change into this.
How did Tenka even
find out I was here?
Chutaro, I fear,
is an abysmal liar.
I do not pretend to know
your reasons for doing this,
but I suspect they
were compelling.
Regardless, Tenka will
be the judge, not I.
--Yeah.
--But first, let us
take advantage of the chaos.
Wait. You mean,
you did all of this?
I took every precaution.
Not a soul was injured.
Well, that's not
terrifying or anything.
Hey, Shirasu...
Hmm?
Before we go...
[door opens]
Why all the commotion?
You remember who
I am, don't you?
Tell me that you do.
--Hm?
--I was just five years old,
the day you murdered
my parents in cold blood.
You're speaking to one for
whom that might've been
any given day.
You took my family from me!
I will never forget!
I will never forgive!
Ahh... you've come
to be vindicated.
I suppose you want
to kill me, then?
No... no, you're wrong.
I'm not like you,
I don't kill people,
I protect them.
I won't stoop to spilling blood
to satisfy my hatred.
I won't throw away the family
I have left over you!
Better to let you live...
let you rot behind these walls
for the rest of your days,
but I'll be damned
if you brush me off.
I am Soramaru Kumoh.
The boy whose
parents you killed.
The young man who punched
you in the face.
Remember my name.
[door opens, slams]
Oh... I will.
Well done, my friend. That was
very much in character.
You knew all along?
You did, didn't you?
I was asked not
to say anything.
Tenka again, huh?
I'm sure he was just
worried about you.
Ah, whatever, he treats
me like a little kid.
Does he, now?
It's not like I can blame him
for that... look at me.
He knew everything.
Carried it on his back
so we wouldn't have to.
And still somehow managed
to cut up and make us laugh
all the time.
Wait! I'm so sorry.
There's something else.
Give me just a minute!
[footsteps departing]
[SORAMARU]
Up here!
What are you doing?
Hey, let me ask you...
when's the last time
you laughed?
No idea.
Not something I'm prone to.
Listen to me! True strength
is being able to laugh
in the face of pain!
Is that a fact?
Yes it is! Whenever you
give in to hatred,
the bastard wins!
Don't surrender your soul!
Laugh to spite what
he's done to you.
Is this a pep talk?
Why not?
Oh, and hey...
Here... you left this!
Thank you.
True strength...
that's what it's all about.
Helping people.
Hey... Tenka? Chutaro?
Sorry for all this.
I'm coming home.
Whaddaya say you
give us a smile?
In fact, let's all
have a good laugh.
I still can't believe I let
you take advantage of me.
It was all for an
excellent cause.
Oh, and nice work,
by the way.
It seems I underestimated you.
Yeah? Well, most of the credit
goes to your superior.
Hmph. Well, did you
find anything out?
[SORAMARU]
Little bit.
[TAKEDA]
You really want the Commander
to teach you
swordsmanship that badly?
Why, when there's an expert
living under your own roof.
[SORAMARU] My brother only
trains me when he feels like it.
Well, that and his idea
of giving lessons
is beating the snot out of me.
What kind of a man is he?
I've been hearing
all sorts of things.
Honestly? The guy's
kind of a jerk.
For one thing, he makes me
and Chutaro do all the chores.
If there're no
criminals to catch,
he just lies around
all day. He doesn't bathe,
he takes stuff without asking,
he'd be late to his own funeral.
[TAKEDA]
Sounds like a real joy
--to be around.
--Still though, it's not easy
bein' our brother
and dad at the same time.
Ahh... so you do
respect him, then?
[SORAMARU]
More or less.
It's hard not to, growing
up, looking at his back.
Ask him about it sometime.
He'll tell you.
Nah, at the end of the day,
he's a decent man.
Huh?
So... ra... ma... ru!
Wait, I--
Whine your way out of
this one, ya li'l pissant!
[TENKA]
'Kay. Guess that counts
--as a smile.
--Ow!
What a relief. Glad he's
home safe and sound.
Yes, ma'am, I think
we're all pretty glad.
I do hope Master Tenka
takes it easy on the boy.
I uh, I wouldn't count on that.
Hmmmmmmm....
Hey, I said I was
sorry, all right?
I know I screwed up.
I won't do it again.
And stop lookin'
at me like that.
I'm disappointed in you, man.
You break my heart.
Beggin' that Yamainu butt-stick
for swordsmanship lessons?
You'd rather learn from him
than your own flesh and blood?
Oh, no...
Am I not good enough?
Or do you wanna up your game
behind my back so you
can take me by surprise?
Either or, way to let
that Qian-Lang freak
get his hooks into you.
How'd you know about that?
How do you think I know?
Did it ever cross your
mind why they wanted you
inside Gokumonju
in the first place?
--Well...
--Look, just, point is,
stay away from
those people, okay?
I didn't know
what I was doing.
I-- I'll make it up to you.
One false step and
you'd have never seen
the light of day again.
I mean, hell, your
life was at stake,
you could've been killed.
I was ready for that.
Don't even go there,
you have no clue
what it means to
be ready to die!
D'you even care that
Chutaro was worried?
How 'bout the trouble
you put Shirasu through?
I thought I'd have to
barge in there myself
and make a big scene.
No. Screw that.
You don't get to talk
like a big shot.
Why the hell can't
you rely on me?
We're family, aren't we?
Look, don't say that.
I do rely on you,
I always have.
And that's the problem.
Because you take it
all on yourself.
The scar on your back is proof.
Hold up! You
remember that night?
It's all right,
I needed to.
I needed to remember
the sacrifices you've made
for us. Let me turn
your words around
on you... why can't
you rely... on me?
We are family,
after all, right?
[SORAMARU]
Chutaro could ask you
the same thing.
Yes, he's young...
but he tries.
And every day I practice,
proud to call myself a Kumoh.
Because one day, I'm gonna
live up to that name.
Aw, come on, don't cry.
[TENKA]
It's cool. I get you.
Big bro can read
between the lines.
[SORAMARU]
Are you listening to me?
[TENKA]
Little birdie's
leaving the nest!
Oh, Gerokichi...
Chutaro...
could you go inside
for a moment, please?
Your brothers might need you.
[TENKA]
Ohhhhh!
[SORAMARU]
Shut up! Stop it!
[TENKA]
Soramaru is going out
into the world on his own!
Sora, how could you?
I'm not letting you
leave without me!
Hm.
Whatever your knowledge
of the Orochi,
it would be best
if you stayed
out of Tenka's way.
I think he knows
what he's doing.
That came out of nowhere.
You'll have to forgive me.
It's odd to see a Fuma
so concerned with
another person
not of... "the blood."
[SHIRASU]
We've spoken of this.
The Fuma belong
to a distant past.
It was extinguished
a long time ago.
Slaughtered.
By a child.
One of their own.
One who saw his advantage
in the clan's diminished glory.
Its thinning stock.
Who, in a single
night, struck true
and folded my clansmen
into their common dust.
Alone, I wandered aimlessly.
Feared... despised.
Not even the cold solace
of revenge was mine.
[gunshot]
I lost everything.
And then... one day...
fate took pity on me.
Now, the world sees fit
to bless me with a home.
So... I say again,
the Fuma are dead.
I am a servant
of the Kumoh blood.
[TENKA]
Okey-dokey!
Bedtime!
--Yes, in the morning.
--Huh?
None of us has slept,
we've gotta catch up
sometime, right? Let's do it,
go crawl under those sheets!
Aye-aye, sir!
Sweet dreams, you guys!
--[rooster crows]
--I can't do this.
Ohh... what's wrong?
We slept like this
all the time
when we were little.
It's nostalgic!
[SORAMARU]
It's ridiculous.
--Nuh-uh! Come on, don't go!
--Please don't go!
This sucks! Ugh! It's cramped
and Chutaro thrashes
in his sleep like--
[TENKA]
Stop bein' a killjoy!
Dog pile!
[SORAMARU]
Get off me, you're too big!
[CHUTARO]
I'm the sumo champion!
[TENKA laughs]
Fine... if it's that important,
--get in bed already.
--[laughing] I knew
we could wear you down.
Ha!
[TENKA]
Seriously, man, why you always
wanna act so grown up?
[SORAMARU]
Somebody's got to.
[CHUTARO]
So grumpy.
[SORAMARU]
Go to sleep.
Tell me this ain't
the good life, eh?
Hm...
[TENKA]
Oh, right, by the way,
Soramaru? [laughs] Welcome home.
It's good to have you back.
Yeah. Thanks.
Good to be back.
[SHIRASU]
There, there. Time to eat.
Skittish creature,
will you never find it
in your heart to
see me as a friend?
Whoever's there,
you may come out.
Oh, my.
My long search ends today.
I've spent a lifetime
seeking you.
Master Kotaro Fuma the Tenth.