[OKI]
Preoccupied, my friend?
Oh. Why hello, sir.
And to what do we owe
the pleasure today?
Just a small formality.
The Justice Department wanted me
to file a report on Tenka Kumoh,
and now that the dust
has settled somewhat, I am able.
Good the storm's passed.
Nonetheless we must be on guard.
Hmm.
Naturally, sir.
Yes, naturally.
That man's nonchalance
gives me no small headache.
Pardon, sir. Who was that?
That's Officer Hirari
of the Shiga Prefecture.
Enlisted by the militia
during the Satsuma Rebellion,
despite his youth, and being
born with only one arm.
Yes, I've heard
stories about that man.
They say that he has visions.
Dreams, actually.
Curious ones,
as I understand it.
[SUBORDINATE]
How so?
[OKI] They involve some
mysterious woman or other.
[HIRARI]
Fleeting as a cloud on the wind.
[BOTAN]
Omi lies shrouded in darkness,
Beset by the wrath
of evil spirits.
The land is rife
with Onmyo magic.
Fanatics thrive in the maelstrom
of wickedness and fear.
Night has fallen
on Old Kamakura.
Ah. There you are.
Whatever you call yourselves--
lay a finger on this woman
and you answer to me.
Who, might I ask, are you?
[HIRARI]
You'll want to take a step back.
[thud]
You still in one piece?
[footsteps]
[HIRARI] I humbly ask
for your hand in marriage.
[BOTAN]
Excuse me?
Please, m'lady. I have
sought you for ages.
[BOTAN]
This poor creature must be mad.
[stones falling]
[BOTAN]
Oh, no!
They could've led me
to the identity
of the Orochi's vessel!
[SASAKI] We are profoundly
indebted to you
for saving our Botan, stranger.
I am the Guardian of Omi.
Kiyotsuna, of the ancient
Sasaki bloodline.
And this...
is Kagemitsu Kumoh,
head of the Kumoh Shrine.
Knock it off!
Forget it! I can't do this!
I'm not gonna sit here
and let some outsider
swoop in and whisk her away!
[BOTAN]
No one's whisking me!
'Kay. Would it be any easier
for you if you knew my name?
Hirari Abe, maybe
you're familiar
with the Abe clan
of Onmyo mages?
You're not serious.
Since when do mages
rely on swords?
Your reputation
precedes you, sir.
I've heard it said
that of all your clan,
you possess the least
aptitude for Onmyo magic.
Yeah. And that's about
the nicest way to put it.
I can't even muster up
a banishing spell.
Which qualifies me as
the proverbial black sheep.
Not an easy life.
Zero prospects make a
guy liable to reach out
and grab what he
wants out of life.
Keep your hands off! I won't
have you corrupt her!
Prodigal son or no,
your blood must commit you
to the same sacred
mission as does ours.
[HIRARI]
To eliminate the Orochi?
So, you are on our side.
Look, honestly,
I couldn't care less.
If you were the prize, though,
that'd make any mission sacred.
I prefer your virtue
be its own reward.
We welcome you as brother
to a common cause.
Sasaki, sir! Please!
[SASAKI]
In any event, you'd be wise
to lodge here for the night,
given the hour.
[HIRARI]
Will the lady offer sake?
I'll leave it for you
to pour yourself.
[HIRARI] Why was Botan attacked?
Who were those people?
A band of religious fanatics.
They want to see
the Orochi reborn.
Ugh. That sounds
like a handful, huh?
Well, they won't be touching
a hair on Botan's head,
I can promise you that.
So, uh, how'd you fall in
love with her so quickly?
[HIRARI] It was her eyes.
Without a doubt.
They're just--
they have that spark that
makes them irresistible,
you know what I mean?
And so compassionate.
They're definitely the
windows to an honest soul.
[KAGEMITSU] A soul that really
values the freedom to choose.
[HIRARI] Hey, either way.
I like 'em feisty!
[KAGEMITSU]
I'm sure you do.
[HIRARI laughing]
[water dripping]
[SASAKI]
Tell me, child.
What do you make of our guest?
[BOTAN]
I see no evil in him, per se.
[SASAKI]
And yet we must remain vigilant.
He may be the vessel.
[BOTAN]
It's possible, but...
surely not.
Show yourself!
[crash]
Hey! Botan! Tell me you're okay!
[BOTAN]
As luck would have it, I am.
Our enemies strike in darkness.
[KAGEMITSU]
Oh, great.
They have us surrounded.
Where is Hirari?
Out in the yard,
being an imbecile.
Ugh. The nerve of this guy!
A little too easy. It's like
knocking down corpses.
[MANGETSU]
Bravo.
Well deduced.
At least the Abe
gave you knowledge.
[HIRARI]
Mangetsu Ashiya.
Still peddling the old
cheap tricks, I see.
[MANGETSU] Oh, yes.
What about you, old friend?
I thought the concept
of duty repulsed you.
And I thought the Ashiya family
had more self-respect
than to serve the Orochi.
You dare speak to me
of self-respect?
On behalf of my
family, rot in hell.
Attack!
Om shiro dabija kangun sousa!
Wait a second.
You know Onmyo magic?
Sir, I advise you to
keep well out of the way.
Swords are useless against
creatures of this ilk.
The hell they are!
Let me be your shield!
Why are you so bent
on protecting me?
This isn't a game! Leave!
Those who can't wield magic
are a liability in a fight.
And besides, she
already has a shield!
I'm not letting you go.
I will not be bound by your
bloated sense of entitlement!
[HIRARI]
It's not about entitlement.
A man doesn't like to see
the woman he loves hurt.
Apologies, but I'm afraid you
fail to fully comprehend.
I was created to fulfill
a specific purpose.
I was made to serve the Abe.
I am not a human being.
I am a demon in service
to your father.
His familiar.
I know not pain nor love.
The subtle shades of human
feeling are wasted on me.
Uhh.
So you're a demon, huh?
It'll take a lot more than
that to get rid of me.
I won't be mocked!
Jaki funbaka!
Mister Sasaki, I shall leave
the gentleman to you.
[BOTAN]
What an infuriating man!
Now be honest.
Are these avowals to Botan true?
Do you believe I'd be risking
my life if they weren't?
She's at the Abe's
beck and call.
Explain to me how a familiar
can use Onmyo magic.
I assure you she is
no ordinary familiar.
Botan was summoned forth by
the full force of Abe's mages.
She alone possesses
the means to seal the Orochi.
The necessary ritual,
however, takes time.
It is the sworn
duty of the Kumoh
to guard her while
the spell takes effect.
The need for you is negligible.
--Spare me the speech, old man.
--Eh?
You can't argue with love.
This was meant to be.
I knew it then,
and I know it now.
Abandon all thought of living.
Do not shed tears.
Do not indulge hope.
Mercy is repugnant,
to yourself and to others.
You are a shadow.
[panting]
[HIRARI]
Those eyes.
The first to really see me.
But I don't kid myself.
No way she remembers.
Hmm.
[MANGETSU] Rin, pyou, tou, sha,
kai, rai, zetsu, mu, san!
[KAGEMITSU]
What just happened?
Why'd the bastard
run away like that?
You see the lesson
in all of this, yes?
Om shiro dabija
jaki funbaka. Free!
[HIRARI] Please. Don't ever
worry me like that again.
[BOTAN]
Let go! This is shameful!
That stupid little--
I suggest for now
we leave them be.
Love between a human
and a familiar
must, alas, be short-lived.
When Botan's sacred
duty is fulfilled,
her place shall
know her no more.
Let the heart beat while it may.
[HIRARI]
Wow. Breathtaking.
Omi has a beautiful view.
Poets have filled volumes
on the scenic tranquility
of this place.
Mister Sasaki feels
Omi's particular draw.
His loyalty to the land
preserves its beauty
for those who call it home.
Too bad about
the clouds then, huh?
It'd be great to see the sun.
[BOTAN] The Orochi's
presence obscures it.
Regret is foreign to me,
but if, when I go, these waters
have yet to catch gold,
I think I shall be disappointed.
[HIRARI] When you vanish
off the face of the Earth,
that's it for me.
I won't let you go alone.
How strange.
Is it not customary
for one in love to say only,
"I won't let you go"?
Nothing gets by you,
does it, my darling?
I'm not long for
this world myself.
[BOTAN]
Uhh...
[HIRARI] And if I gotta die,
I'd rather do it next to you.
Do not talk like this.
Botan, I want you to smile.
Do that for me
and I can be happy.
What are you...
Aaaah! What the hell, man?
I'm glad I came out here
to check on you when I did
or who knows
what'd you be up to?
Ugh, you're killin'
me here, kid.
We were just gettin'
in the mood.
[KAGEMITSU] In the mood
for what, exactly?
[HIRARI]
Wait. I see what's happening.
Hmm? What are you
talking about?
[HIRARI] You think I might be
the Orochi's vessel, don't you?
How did you know?
[HIRARI]
Are you wary of me, too, Botan?
Yes! It's her job to be!
[HIRARI]
Uh-huh.
It's sad there's
no trust anymore.
Hey! Wait! Where are you going?
[HIRARI] To try and wake myself
up from a bad dream.
What's with this guy? Seriously.
[insects chirping]
--[knock]
--[SASAKI] Hmm?
Hey.
Excuse me, old timer.
Hello, Mister Hirari.
[HIRARI]
I wanted to say thanks.
Ah, I see.
I take it you've thought better
of pursuing your heart?
Yeah, place is too laid back.
If I stay here,
I'll lose my edge.
[SASAKI]
Will you indeed?
I grant you Omi is lovely.
That's what compels me
to preserve it.
[HIRARI]
That what you tell people?
Nice. You get to have your cake
and eat it too, I guess.
Well, you just sit there
in your hot bath
and spin lies
all day, old man.
The truth'll catch up
to you eventually.
You know it isn't me.
The Orochi's inside
of you, isn't it?
Looks like it's got its
hooks into you pretty good,
but you're still human
enough to be scared.
Effective diversionary
tactic, by the way.
I mean, who'd suspect
the Orochi zealots
would attack the man
harboring their god?
Yeah. Good way
to earn the trust
of those who'd kill you
if they knew the truth.
Such a cavalier attitude.
You cannot know the horror
of what it means
to be chosen by the Orochi!
Is everything all right, sir?
[SASAKI]
This man is the vessel!
He really is?
Freeze! It's over!
[HIRARI]
No! Don't listen! He's a liar!
The vessel is him! Botan!
Ha! An obvious ploy!
Surely you take my word
over that of a stranger!
Please forgive me, sir.
Doubt comes uneasily
with regard to your word.
However...
a man like Hirari does not lie
to the woman he loves.
[KAGEMITSU]
What? Are you out of your mind?
[SASAKI groans]
Sasaki?
[SASAKI]
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no.
Sir!
[SASAKI]
So very sorry.
Get down!
[rumbling]
This isn't happening!
Botan! I need you to raise
a barrier, quickly!
Yes, master!
Om kiri kiri basara
basara jama.
Fuu shiki shinkin seimei.
Shinsui seimei. Shinmoku seimei.
Shinkin seimei. Shindo seimei!
Move it!
Don't be so rash!
Your business
is protecting Botan!
The Kumoh are shields!
Yeah, and what
are you gonna do?
[HIRARI]
"Abandon all thought of living.
Do not shed tears.
Do not indulge hope.
Mercy is repugnant.
You are a shadow.
Bait for the Orochi!"
That's what the Abe
drilled into the minds
of every kid they've taken in.
We're no more than bait.
This is my purpose. My destiny.
What an awful thing
for a child to hear.
Do your thing and leave
the stalling to me.
Where do you find
cause to smile?
Just work your magic, m'lady.
Be fleet and
be wise. Good luck.
Arrggh!
When I understood my destiny,
the future held
only fear and pain.
But then, for the first time,
someone looked at me
like I was a person.
I smiled because of you.
Because all of a sudden,
the world didn't seem so cold.
Please, you mustn't
let the man die.
Hmm.
Poko!
All right, let's
confuse it! Are you ready?
Yeah, just focus
on protecting Botan!
She told me to protect you.
I think I'll go with her.
Aaaaah!
[HIRARI]
Protect me?
Someone actually cares
if I live or die.
She cares.
This is too much.
[BOTAN]
Om kiri kiri basara basara jama.
We're almost there!
[BOTAN] Fuu shiki shinka
seimei. Shinsui seimei.
Shimoku seimei.
[explosion]
Don't lose heart.
Just keep on with the spell.
As long as I draw breath,
nothing is going to hurt you.
[BOTAN]
Don't die.
[HIRARI]
I thought I asked you to smile.
Don't be scared. I'm not
gonna die, all right?
And I would never lie
to the girl I love.
Kiyotsuna Sasaki!
You've fallen a
long way, old man!
Wait! It'll never work!
You'll be swallowed whole!
[HIRARI]
You used to love this place.
You really wanna see it fall
as hard as its former protector?
[SASAKI voice echoing]
Please. No.
I'm not ready to die.
Give me more time.
I beg you.
[HIRARI]
Do not falter now.
Protect this land
to your last breath,
Guardian of Omi.
Die with dignity.
I will take it on myself
to carry the torch
where you cannot.
You will survive in me.
I accept your burden as my own.
Aaah!
Whatever you've done,
the serpent is still.
The chant is complete.
Final spell begin.
Seal!
[coughing, groaning]
[whimpering]
[panting]
My purpose is served.
[HIRARI]
Botan!
Look at that.
The waters are catching gold,
just like you wanted.
It's okay. I'm numb
from the poison.
Can't feel a thing.
[BOTAN]
Thank you.
Because of you, the Orochi
has been sealed.
[HIRARI] If you go
by my training, I failed.
I disgraced the
Abe by surviving.
So be it.
I'm happy that little boy
outlived the weight
unduly put on him.
[HIRARI]
Wait, you remember me?
[BOTAN]
As though it were yesterday.
You've grown into someone
of which to be proud.
My heart has held out for
this very moment for so long.
And yet, the moment
is doomed to fade.
My duty is fulfilled.
My existence is forfeit.
I'm afraid you and
I shall meet no more.
[HIRARI]
You're wrong.
We'll meet again.
If oceans divide us,
we'll hoist our sails.
If death divides us,
we'll be reborn.
Next time, though, I'll try
to find you a little quicker.
You're either a hopeless
romantic or a hapless fool
to address a familiar this way.
Don't expect to catch me
in the next life
as easily as all that.
[HIRARI] Botan. Promise
you'll wait for me.
Please.
Yes, I will wait for you.
[HIRARI]
Was it real?
Or the mirage
of a summer's day?
Did we meet, or was
it all just a dream?
If my mind plays tricks,
let me be quick to laugh.
If what it shows me
is true, let us both be.
Another vision.
[sighing] Where are you?