[SORAMARU]
They're going to kill him.
Why are they doing this?
He's revealed himself to be
the vessel of the Orochi.
The government has no choice.
Tenka will be publicly
executed on the pretext
of having bombed Gokumonjo.
Why is right now the first
I'm hearing any of this?
Why would no one talk to me?
A few days ago, this
whole "Orochi" thing
was just some old wives' tale.
And now my brother's
being executed?
He knew what was going on
and kept us in the dark!
He lied!
Soramaru.
Tenka has tried to do
right by the Kumoh name.
With the blood comes a
host of responsibilities,
not the least of which
is protecting your future.
Oh, is that a fact?
And what is the Orochi that
Tenka has to lay down his life
for my future?
[BOTAN] The time has
come for you to know.
[chair slides back]
The information simply
won't take, it's too absurd.
The damned swiftness of
it all. I can't believe it.
No trial, no nothing,
and just like that.
It's wrong! We must act!
Precisely what
recourse do we have?
This falls outside
of our jurisdiction.
Of course there's no law
preventing you from being there.
We could manage the workload
for a little while.
You know, this'll be your
last chance to see him.
Just let the Commander
know where you're going.
Request for--!
[birds calling]
[indistinct conversation]
Good heavens! But why
must the boy hang?
What could he
possibly have done?
[BOTAN]
Six hundred years ago,
a brave and, some say,
foolhardy man
subdued the Orochi at
great peril to himself.
His name rings out still.
Kagemitsu Kumoh.
The sire of the Kumoh line.
Wait, do what? You mean he--
[BOTAN] Where Gokumonjo
prison stands now,
a great tree rose from the
depths of Lake Biwa,
soaring upward to the sky above.
It was there that the
Orochi's pride was wounded,
and his grudge toward the
blood of your family born.
Time and again,
the Great Serpent
assumes physical form
and dwells among us.
Time and again, the sky
darkens at his approach.
So, that's why the sky is
always so cloudy and stuff,
because it knows the
Orochi's coming back soon?
[BOTAN]
This is the Orochi's shrine.
These are the lands poisoned
by his recurring renewal.
It is written as follows:
"The Great Serpent
tightens its coils
round the arc of time.
a monster, a spirit,
striking out from the
abyss every 300 years
in the guise of man.
Take care, ye children
of such a day.
The Orochi is humanity's
greatest adversary.
To be found. To be
hunted and sealed away."
These are the words
of your destiny.
[thunder]
Botan! I need you to raise
a barrier, quickly!
Yes, master!
Move it!
Don't be so rash!
Your business is
protecting Botan!
The Kumoh are shields!
[CREATURE hissing]
Leave the stalling to me.
Be fleet, and be wise.
Uggh!
Please, you mustn't
let the man die.
Hmm. Poko!
All right! Let's confuse it!
Are you ready?
[groaning]
Don't lose heart. Just
keep on with the spell.
[BOTAN]
Don't die.
Wait! It won't work!
You'll be swallowed whole!
[HIRARI]
Do not falter now.
Protect this land
to your last breath,
Guardian of Omi.
Stand proud.
[BOTAN]
Final spell begin.
Seal!
[BOTAN] Yet even now, the
Orochi has taken a new host
and intends to rise again.
And the host he's
chosen is... is Tenka.
Why wouldn't you tell us?
You knew. You knew
and you said nothing.
And here we were, laughing
and carrying on like idiots.
Please. See it from his side.
He didn't want you two to worry.
I'm sick and tired of him
keeping things from me!
I'll never forgive him for this!
Tenny's the Orochi?
Snap out of it! Quit
staring off into space!
Let's go.
Sir.
Soramaru! Chutaro!
That kid doesn't even
have a mom and dad!
Whoa!
For your information,
I'm his mom and his dad!
Now either you little
brats shape up
or I throw you in
the sewer trench!
They were just
messin' around, Tenka!
Sorry. He takes things
too far sometimes.
See, Chutaro, that's gratitude.
He's apologizing for how cool
your parents happen to be.
Ohh!
Well, that's enough training
for today, I think.
But I can't-- ugh.
I can't even move.
Hey, hey, easy there.
Don't say "can't."
See, the minute you put a word
like that out there,
it starts to bind you.
Trick is, you gotta
think positive.
Right!
Right! I want you
to say "I can!"
Put that out there and there's
nothing you can't lick!
[TENKA]
These swords are special.
They're designed, not for
killing, but for protecting.
[SORAMARU]
I don't understand.
[TENKA] For the moment,
both of them protect you.
But one day, when
you're old enough,
the idea is for
you to wield them
in defense of something bigger.
The family. The shrine.
The Kumoh name.
Any and everything
under the clouds.
You'll understand in time.
You're my little
brother, after all.
Show me that you
can surpass me.
[SORAMARU] You never said
I'd have to do this without you.
I should have read
between the lines,
that's what you meant.
I don't accept it!
Things don't have
to be this way!
Hey. Come on, let 'em flow.
Sometimes being able to cry
is what makes you a man.
Don't worry about catchin'
up to your big brother.
You gotta let things unfold
at their own pace.
[SORAMARU] Is this your
idea of protecting us?
Just disappearing into thin air?
I don't think so!
Not on my watch!
[wind whistling]
[TSUCHIYA]
This is an outrage!
[OFFICER] Hey! You can't
just come in here!
--[KITAMURA] Tenka!
--[OFFICER] Stand down!
[TSUCHIYA] Please! He had
nothing to do with the bombing!
Damn it! Stop! You're
making a mistake!
[OFFICER] This is sedition!
Calm yourself, man!
[KITAMURA]
Shut up!
I won't let him die,
do you understand me?
[TSUCHIYA]
Clear a path!
[KITAMURA]
Run, Tenka! Make a break for it!
[sighs]
Wow, you guys are
a special kind of idiot.
Huh?
Uggh!
[TENKA]
What I owe you isn't lost on me.
Hey. Do a dead man a favor
and see to it these clowns don't
get the book thrown at 'em.
I can guarantee you
they're harmless.
[HIRARI]
Of course.
I can count on you
for that. Right, Hirari?
I knew you for an imbecile,
but this is beyond the pale.
Sosei.
What kind of sadist
comes all this way
to see a guy he doesn't
like kick the bucket?
Why didn't you say anything
when you realized?
How long have you known?
And here I thought
I'd go to my grave
before you guys
pieced it all together.
Guess I should've
had more faith.
It's been fun.
Damn you!
Why did you leave the squad?
It was your life's
goal to join,
your dream, and you walked away.
Hey. What can I say?
Dreams can go sour.
Hunting down the Orochi's
vessel was great at first.
It felt like we'd been entrusted
with something really special,
that we could be heroes
behind the scenes.
So in the beginning,
the squad was everything
I wanted it to be.
We were loyal to Japan,
to each other.
It was fantastic.
All the more because
I was with you.
Don't speak to me about loyalty,
after you betrayed me!
You had two brothers who
could've taken over the shrine
after your parents died!
You didn't have to
take it upon yourself!
Your zeal was everything to us,
and then you were just gone.
We all needed your guidance.
We needed you and
you left us to rot!
So yeah, you're damn
right dreams go sour!
Here's to being heroes.
I did what I had to do.
I'm sorry, but that's
just how I'm made.
I'll take "big brother"
over "hero" any day.
Uggh!
Then I guess you've made
peace with being alone.
Oh hey, that reminds me.
Soramaru's training
with you now, isn't he?
--He is.
--Yes.
You're not about to ask me
to look after him, are you?
Of course. How
infuriatingly typical.
Let's not fool ourselves
into believing
that you actually care about
the people you leave behind.
[OFFICER]
Hey, stop!
I said stop!
[CHUTARO]
Tenny!
--[OFFICER] What's this?
--[SORAMARU] Get off me!
[CHUTARO] Please, sir!
Where's my brother?
[OFFICER]
Out of here immediately!
Aw, hell, come on, you guys.
[SOSEI] Always soaring
miles above the herd.
Yet what of the loved ones quick
to put themselves in harm's way
in a desperate bid
to try and reach you?
Does the sun shine any brighter
for being untouchable?
More's the pity.
It profits nothing
from its own brilliance.
Uggh!
[OFFICER] Who are these
people? Halt or I'll--
Uggh! I said halt!
Step aside or don't,
it's all the same to us!
We're comin' through!
Stand firm! They're only kids!
Move.
We humbly object to
this man's execution.
I am Soramaru.
Second son of the
proud Kumoh line.
Chutaro, third son.
We will not leave this place
without our brother.
Who in the hell are these guys?
[TENKA]
Just two dumb, meddling brats.
Enough!
Just let him go!
[SORAMARU]
This is over, you hear me?
We're going home!
It's time.
Yeah, I know.
Sorry it came to all this
without a whole lot of warning.
Stop! What are you doing?
Get out of there!
We've come to take
you home. Please, Tenny!
[OFFICER] Knock it off!
He attacked Gokumonjo!
It wasn't him, it was me!
I bombed the damn prison!
If you wanna hang
someone, hang me!
No! Let him go!
If Tenny dies,
I wanna die with him!
Tenny, please.
[TENKA]
Easy now. Don't ever say die.
You two need to live.
You hear me?
Don't talk like these
are your last words, dammit!
Sorry, this is all she
wrote for me, kiddos.
I'm countin' on you two to pick
up where I leave off, alright?
No! No! This isn't fair!
You don't have to do this!
Stop joking!
Why do you have to act so
tough all the damn time!
You don't get to die
like this! Not today!
We're not the only ones
who depend on you!
[VILLAGERS shouting]
[MAN] This man isn't
capable of wrong-doing!
--He's right!
--There's been some mistake.
Believe us!
Give our big brother back!
[shouting continues]
Are you listening to them?
Whatever this is about,
we can still fix it!
Yeah! See? They're all
rooting for you, sir!
Oh, man.
Heh. I guess
people need a hobby.
--Shirasu?
--Miss Botan?
Make no mistake,
my friend. You are loved.
That's really nice
and all, but...
All of you. Get a life, eh?
I'm sorry we've gotta part ways
like this, but there it is.
Trust me on this,
eventually you crash head-on
into whatever you're
running from, ready or not.
This is the Shrine
of the Orochi.
The land where, every 300 years,
darkness prevails.
To some, at least.
To me, it's where I grew up.
I'm grateful to all of you.
Grateful I was born a Kumoh.
Grateful I was born here.
That's why...
even when I knew
in my heart of hearts
things weren't gonna
end well for me,
I could still laugh.
Soramaru. Chutaro.
I want you to know you were
the source of my strength.
As long as I could cut up
with you, I could do anything.
You were the best little
brothers a guy could ask for.
Remember that.
So long!
--Tenka, no!
--Tenny!
[SORAMARU] This isn't
happening. It can't be!
I'm not ready! He can't die!
[CROWD shouting]
Please don't go!
Tenny! Please don't go!
--Whatever you want me to do!
--You can't end it like this!
You were gonna watch us
grow up! You bastard!
We need our mom and dad!
You can't go!
Tenka!
[TENKA]
It'll hurt for a little while.
Not forever, though.
Go. Live your lives.
Cry.
Scream.
Be fierce.
But most of all...
...keep laughing!
[TENKA] Especially when
the clouds hang low.
[BOTAN] Year 11 of
Emperor Meiji's reign.
A turbulent time.
Behind the heavy clouds...
[thud]
...the sun sets.
[HIRARI] Where is he that kept
laughing under the clouds?
Where is he that wept
beneath the lowering sky?
Beyond my furthest reach,
perhaps, but not my thought.
Let then these words find you.
You are not alone.
One day, we shall meet again.
Only promise me...
...you'll laugh until we do.