[roars]
[gasps]
Hey, Sora!
Tenny took off again!
Why am I not surprised?
Way to treat us like
a couple of toddlers.
Let's go, Chutaro.
[CHUTARO]
Yes, sir!
[OFFICER]
Halt!
You're making it
worse on yourself!
You won't catch me alive!
I'd rather die than be
delivered to that nightmare!
Get out of my way!
Do not presume to
bellow orders, filth.
In this domain,
you answer to me.
Tenka, hey!
Excellent work as usual, sir!
Thank you.
Would it have killed you to
say something before you left?
[TENKA]
And wake up
the sleeping beauties?
You were in the
middle of a good dream,
judging from the noise.
We woke at dawn!
Tell him, Chutaro!
--Huh? Uh.
--[sighs]
Huh?
[MALE CRIMINAL]
That insignia.
Oh, hell.
[train whistle blowing]
[WOMAN] Year Eleven of
Emperor Mejii's reign.
The famed Edo
period's final act.
Japan foists itself
upon the World Stage,
casting off the
vestments of serfdom
in exchange for
the industrialized
sophistication of the West.
Gone is the age
of sword and shogun,
both stricken from the register
by Imperial edict,
the proud samurai
class now extinct.
Life plunges inexorably
forward into the modern age.
With great change, however,
comes great turmoil.
The government's sweeping
reforms left many
by the wayside,
and far too often, these
disenfranchised souls
turned to crime.
[CHUTARO]
Ah. He's awake.
Well, good morning!
[SORAMARU]
I hear you attacked
some poor guard while they
were escorting you to prison.
Not a very smart move.
They'll just add that much
more onto your sentence.
So you're the Kumoh brothers
everyone's been talking about?
[SORAMARU]
Everyone?
[CHUTARO laughs]
Guess we're becoming
local celebrities.
Oh yeah. You're the
talk of the whole town.
Like how the youngest
stand in the shadow of
their sword-wielding brother
and how they're not
good for much more than
pushing a ferry across the lake.
Use those fancy swords as oars?
Or are they just for show?
Does a runt like you
even know to take
them out of the sheath?
That's right, old-timer.
Get it all out of your
system while you can.
[SORAMARU]
Welcome to Gokumonjo,
your home until the
Emperor says otherwise.
Yeah. Kind of
imposing, isn't it?
They don't make them bigger.
Hey, at least you probably know
a few people in there, right?
[gulps]
[SORAMARU]
They built this prison
especially for escape
artists like yourself.
Even if the walls
can't keep you in,
you've still got to swim
across the largest lake in Japan
before you're free.
Sure it might be a bit extreme,
but as long as it's here,
we have a job pushing
our little ferry.
If you can really
call this a job.
The Powers That Be
pay us so little
we'd be better off trading
you in for day-old bread.
Please! I can't!
I can't go in there!
Look, I'll give you
anything you want.
Anything! Just turn
this boat arou--
[MAN screaming]
Sorry, old-timer. This is it.
Not much I can do for you.
[SORAMARU]
Word of advice?
Learn to love making atonement.
[grunting]
We're much obliged for the tea.
Thank you, Shirasu-san.
My pleasure, gentlemen.
This family's gracious
enough to tolerate me.
The least I can do
is entertain for them.
Well, it's nice of
you to entertain
a pair of fools like us.
I can't believe we let him
slip through our fingers.
[BOTH]
We're a disgrace to the uniform.
[grunting]
[SHIRASU]
Tenka.
Surely Soramaru has earned
himself a bit of a rest?
Why not tell him to come in?
Something's off about
the way Chutaro's acting.
[TENKA]
I can't put my finger on it,
but this morning...
[TENKA]
Study hard and make us proud.
Of course, sir!
Wait. What is that?
Oh. Uh.
Nothing! Got to go!
Have a pleasant day, sir!
See? You believe me,
don't you, Shirasu?
Something's wrong!
I can feel it!
Hmm. It's possible that
the boy's in love.
What?
He's got all the love
he can handle at home!
Bleh! Gross!
One mustn't fault
a vulnerable heart.
He's at that age.
I want to punch you in the face.
I'm liable to punch you back
out of reflex. That all right?
[shouts]
I need to take this
out on someone!
Goodness me.
Hey! If you want to spar,
I could use the practice!
Mmm?
Huh?
Soramaru and I are
going into town
to sabotage Chutaro--
I mean, chaperone
his courtship.
[humphs]
[YOUNG BOY]
Mommy, what's that?
[MOTHER]
Don't stare, it's rude.
Huh?
Do I even want to
know what's going on?
Hey, nix the
chit-chat, huh?
You can cry if you want,
but babies don't talk.
Oh, really?
They also don't happen
to come in my size!
Chutaro's head over heels
for someone in his class
and we're going
undercover to find out who
before things get serious.
Play your part or I'll
give you a spanking.
This is the opposite
of undercover!
Well, as I live and breathe!
Whatever are you
Kumoh boys up to now?
Oh, nothing much.
You know, I should run some
vegetables up to the shrine.
You're very kind, as always.
There can't be that
many to spare,
what with the fields
getting so little sun.
Be that as it may, lad,
for the peace of mind
you boys bring this town,
we're grateful rain or shine.
Yay! Sora's dressed like a baby!
Please put me down!
Uh-oh, sourpuss. I think I know
somebody who needs a new diaper.
Okay, that's weird.
[MALE TOWNSPERSON]
I admit, I envy those boys
their boundless energy.
[FEMALE TOWNSPERSON]
Yes, they're a lively bunch.
One hopes their
parents look down
from above with a smile.
[BOY]
Oh! Hi, teacher!
Let's play! Pick a game, Miss!
[chuckles]
So that's the object of
his childish infatuation.
I don't really know
about infatuation.
More like he enjoys
being spoiled rotten.
Of course.
He's too young
to really remember
what having a mother was like.
Tenka.
Stop! The only mother
you'll ever need is me!
Um.
Hey, Tenny.
What are you doing here?
[SORAMARU]
Excuse him, everyone.
[CHUTARO]
And you too, Sora?
You-- You two-timing runt!
Gnash your teeth!
[CHUTARO]
Yes, sir!
Don't listen to him,
he's just having a fit.
Heh. Made you look!
[CHUTARO]
Good one, big brother!
[SORAMARU]
You idiot!
Uh. Sorry for all the ruckus.
I'm Chutaro's big
brother, Tenka.
Pleased to meet you all.
Same here. I'm Soramaru.
Charmed. I feel
like I know you both
from all the stories he tells.
I'm Chutaro's teacher.
Oh, but please, you
can call me Botan.
[TENKA]
Ah. Nice to meet you.
So has he been keeping
up with his lessons?
Huh? Oh. Well, he's
working quite hard.
Right?
--Mmm...
--[TENKA] I believe she
just asked you a question.
Uh. Yes, very hard. Absolutely.
[SORAMARU]
Tenka.
I really think we
should go home.
We've caused--
[TENKA]
No.
We didn't dress up for nothing.
I'm gonna give this
place a once-over.
Whoa! You can't just
barge in! Tenka!
Perfectly all right.
No harm done. Why not
make yourselves at home?
[humming]
So your teacher seems
pretty nice. That's important.
[CHUTARO laughs]
Is there some reason you
blush when I point that out?
Oh, hey. What's
with the tanuki?
Is that the one that
hangs out at the shrine?
[calls]
It's Gerokichi.
Great. You gave it a name.
Well, I couldn't very well
let our family mascot
go without one, could I? No way.
The two of you kind of
resemble each other.
Huh. The funny thing is
Gerokichi likes
Miss Botan. A lot.
Lets her pet him and everything.
I've never seen him like that.
He's usually shy
around everybody but us.
Huh.
Hmm.
"Working quite hard," are we?
Not hard enough.
[gasps]
[BOTAN]
Something I can help you with?
[TENKA]
Oh, my bad.
Sorry. I got turned around.
The bathroom is where exactly?
Out and to the left.
You can't miss it, I'm certain.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Got to pee.
So, this is the 14th
head of the Kumoh Shrine.
Pleased to meet you, Tenka.
Oh, come on! You can't
just back away!
Step into your movements!
[SORAMARU]
I'm trying to!
[TENKA]
You couldn't slice
through a piece of
tofu with that swing!
Maybe that's what
I want you to think!
When you want to
fight, let me know.
Hey, but who knows?
Another trillion years
and you might beat me.
Wow! You're so strong, sir!
No one could beat you!
You're like the head of a crab!
[TENKA] And what is
that supposed to mean?
I want you to practice
on me next, sir! Please?
Your enthusiasm is admirable,
but don't be rash.
[CHUTARO]
I'll be fine! Promise!
--[OFFICER 1] Tenka, sir!
--Huh?
--What is it?
--We need your assistance!
[TENKA]
Let some more ruffians
slip through your
fingers, I take it?
Yeah.
Not again.
[OFFICER 1]
Apparently a master swordsman
got mixed in with the rest.
First chance he got,
he made off with my blade.
Please, you have to
help us. We're screwed!
If our boss catches
wind of this--
[TENKA]
Gents.
Always glad to be of service
for the right incentive.
[OFFICER 1, OFFICER 2]
Uh.
[TENKA]
Cold hard cash-a-roo.
There are people who'd
call this extortion!
[TENKA]
We're a little low
on funds at the moment.
I'm perfectly willing
to work for the money.
I say go for it, Tenny!
Cold hard cash-a-roo!
[SORAMARU]
Don't copy him!
I recommend coming
to a decision.
Your quarry is only
getting further off.
[SORAMARU]
We gotta do what we gotta do.
Let's go, Chutaro.
Yes, sir!
I'll handle this on my own.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TENKA] No lip. You two
are staying here.
[TENKA]
Hold on! I'm the second son!
And I'm the third, which means
I should get to help, too!
You really wanna help me out?
Keep a low profile.
Lead the way.
[OFFICER 1, OFFICER 2]
Sir!
[SORAMARU]
Damn it, Tenka!
[TENKA]
I don't need you
slowing me down.
[OFFICER 1]
We're going on 10 years now.
[OFFICER 2]
Hmm?
Since the skies
darkened over Shiga.
Hey, that's right.
Like all those old tales.
They say the clouds gather
every 300 years,
refusing to disperse.
Supposed to be an omen,
means bad things are coming.
[OFFICER 2]
The Legend of
the Great Snake, Orochi?
You believe that stuff?
[OFFICER 1]
No, of course not.
Why does he always
treat me like a child?
[SHIRASU]
Try to look at it
from his point of view.
After all, you are younger.
He feels obligated to act
as mother and father.
And he's a warrior,
so being protective
comes with the territory.
[sighs]
He's not my mom and dad.
He's my brother. Period.
[SHIRASU]
Which, like it or not,
makes you his responsibility.
[SORAMARU]
So what then?
He can't give me a
chance to prove myself?
I'm not useless.
I can help him.
He can rely on me.
Why else did he give
me the family sword?
That should mean something.
I thought he'd acknowledged
me as an equal.
Chutaro! Look alive,
we're going!
[CHUTARO mumbling]
[SORAMARU]
What are you doing?
I'm keeping a low profile
like Tenny told us to, sir!
Be your own person for once!
Ignore him!
Don't you want to pull
your weight in this family?
You bet I do, sir!
[SHIRASU]
You can't go.
I dare you to try and stop us.
Push comes to shove,
we're warriors, too.
[sighs]
[SHIRASU]
Oh my.
The Kumoh men are ever so
stubborn, aren't they, Tenka?
[rocks clacking]
Uh.
Why're you scraping
rocks together?
Heh, ignition.
Fire for the lowlife.
If he gives us any trouble,
we can turn him on a spit.
Okay, your mind is
seriously twisted!
[CHUTARO]
What's the big deal?
We can burn him a little bit!
[SORAMARU]
And you might incinerate
the forest while you're at it!
[SORAMARU]
Hey! Stop where you are!
Call it a hunch, but something
tells me this is our guy!
You're the fastest. Get up
there and cut him off!
Yes, sir!
[SORAMARU]
Stop right there!
We know you're a fugitive!
Pssh!
Well, well. Lookie here.
The toddlers of the Kumoh clan.
Go, Chutaro. Get out of the way.
Uh. Whatever you say.
Prepare to taste my blade!
[SORAMARU]
Stand my ground.
I've fought Tenka,
I can fight him.
Besides,
he doesn't step
into his movement.
His swordsmanship is crap.
I've got this.
Excellent, sir!
You really showed that
creep who's boss, huh?
[SORAMARU]
I'm so used to Tenka
kicking my ass,
I didn't even notice, but...
I'm not half bad!
[CHUTARO]
Hey! Look out, Sora!
An imperial lapdog
ain't gonna get the drop on me.
To think we were brushed
off to make room for you!
Do you know what it means for a
samurai to be denied his sword?
How it feels to be told
your glory days are behind you?
This ain't Japan no more.
The country's gone to hell!
[SORAMARU]
It's ronin like you
who're dragging it down!
Look what you've become.
You're a disgrace!
Sora!
Shame you can't
fight like you talk.
Your brother would've made
short work of me, I hear.
Must make you sick at heart,
not living up to
the family name.
Two Kumoh brothers,
and one's on his knees.
Put it down!
Tenka must be a real softie...
keeping deadweight
like you two around
in times like these.
Oh, you want this back?
I've got an idea.
I hock this on the black market
and see what your name's worth.
You wouldn't dare!
No one talks bad
about our big brother!
You hear me?
You're kidding,
it's just a boken?
It's mine.
[TENKA]
This sword is special.
It's designed, not for
killing, but for protecting.
[SORAMARU]
I don't understand.
[TENKA]
You will in time.
You're my little
brother, after all.
[TENKA]
Show me that you can surpass me.
Never question my
worth, you lowlife.
You are addressing the
Second Son of the Kumoh Shrine.
Show respect!
Take arms!
Brat!
You're addressing a samurai!
[SORAMARU] You're no samurai.
You're a criminal.
The samurai I know would
never stoop to your level.
He has pride. Dignity.
And strength.
[laughs]
[SORAMARU]
Yeah.
He's a real pain in
the ass that way.
[groans]
I don't swing this thing around
every day for bragging rights.
That was outstanding, sir!
You were just like Tenny!
[SORAMARU]
Don't celebrate yet.
Tie this guy up before
he gets his third wind.
Yes, sir! I'm on it!
[SORAMARU] Yeah.
He'll have to treat me
like an equal after this.
[TENKA laughing]
Could have done this
twice before breakfast!
Three times before lunch.
We are in your debt, sir!
There's a stout
fellow, too, yeah?
Um.
[TENKA]
No sweat.
The bigger they are,
the harder they fall.
[OFFICER 1, OFFICER 2]
That's the spirit!
Guess there were more bad guys
running around than
we thought, huh?
Way to go, Tenny!
Say goodnight, you punk!
He was only pretending
to be unconscious?
Oh no! Sora!
Run away!
[SORAMARU]
I can't breathe.
Tenka.
[gasps]
[TENKA]
Soramaru!
You're not hurt, are you?
Come on, talk to me.
[CHUTARO]
Tenny jumped in
at the last minute
and rescued you.
I think-- I don't know--
It's like I had dream or--
some-- someone was dead.
[SORAMARU]
It was--
I thought it was--
[CHUTARO]
Don't cry, sir.
The hard part's over
[TENKA]
Hey. You're all right.
Nothing to be afraid of now.
See? I'm here.
Everything's back to normal.
[exhales shakily]
[SORAMARU]
I'm useless.
If you hadn't been there
to save me, I'd be dead.
Huh?
[SORAMARU]
I am dead.
Dead weight.
[TENKA]
Heh. Uh-oh.
Make way for the waterworks.
[SORAMARU crying]
Leave me alone.
Sora.
Hey. Come on, let them flow.
There's no shame in a few tears.
Sometimes being able to cry
is what makes you a man.
[panicked breathing]
[OFFICER]
Given how scared you seem,
I'm guessing you know
what's said about this place.
Just a few things
here and there.
[GUARD]
Let's hope you caught the rumor
about what new inmates
are wise to bring with them.
This is absurd!
How can I be expected to
smuggle in something like that?
I see. That's too bad.
[door locks]
--[whimpering]
--[birds cawing]
Who-- Who's there?