[distant explosion]
Commander.
Something's happening
in the canal, sir!
Don't lose focus.
[TENKA]
Chutaro! Soramaru!
Enough of this screwin' around.
You're alive!
[slashing]
[thud]
[swords clashing]
Commander.
I think we can handle
these vermin ourselves.
You're the best one of us to go
head-to-head with the Orochi.
Let the Fuma be our concern.
It's Hirari, right?
Come with me.
Takeda.
It's your time to shine.
Get a move on.
We'll bring up the rear!
Right!
Best of luck, comrades!
I'll do my utmost!
This I promise you!
Tenny, sir. What're
you doing here?
[grunting]
Ha! The sun ain't doin' you
any favors, is it, tough guy?
[grunting, groaning]
Gerokichi!
Chase him down!
Am I dreaming
all of this, sir?
Nah.
It's really me.
Good work, by the way.
Do you mean that?
[TENKA]
Ha!
You're damn right I mean it.
Whaddya say we bring
Sora back to himself, huh?
All you have to do is take
a swing at him, alright?
Me?
Hey, there's nothin' to it.
I'll be right beside you.
'Kay.
Ready.
Now! Take your best shot!
[metal clanging]
[grunting]
He's too strong.
I'm gettin' pushed off!
Keep at it!
The trick's to wear him down!
Yah!
[rumbling]
[SOSEI]
Quite a lavish entryway.
What the--?
[TENKA]
Sosei!
Stay where you are!
Easy now. I gotcha.
Wait, Tenka?
[screaming]
It's over, y'hear me?
Give back my Sora!
What in heaven's
name is going on?
[TSUCHIYA]
Good people!
Please, we need your help!
Pathetic.
This is you lot
in peak condition?
Our lord has been
separated from the vessel.
The Great Serpent's
rebirth is assured.
Separated from the chosen host,
he's unable to be sealed.
[BOTAN] Are you certain?
I rather wonder.
The Kumoh family swords
are rife with his own magic,
and yet he is averse
to them as if to poison.
Can it be that the Orochi
is lethal to himself?
That's impossible.
[BOTAN] Is it? Or is the
vessel his deadliest foe?
C'mon, talk to me, kid.
How're you feelin'?
[gasps]
Tenka!
Oh yeah.
Wow, Sora! I'm so
happy you're okay!
Is this--?
Is this real?
Heh. Yes. It's actually me.
[screaming]
What the hell?
That really hurt, man!
[SORAMARU laughs]
You idiot.
You big, stupid idiot.
[CHUTARO laughs]
[TENKA]
Yeah. I know.
Okay.
There's still work to be done.
We cut the Orochi from
your body, but now he's free.
Ugly bastard can
still use Lake Biwa
to don his snake form.
If we don't put a stop
to this once and for all,
he'll keep comin' back.
But how do we stop him?
The Orochi's an immortal being.
As I understand it, he has
to be sealed, correct?
Only the vessel can do it,
and it won't be that easy.
[SORAMARU]
These swords protected me.
Now it's my turn.
I'm in.
Hey, whatever it takes, right?
My ancestors have used
this weapon to subdue
the Great Serpent
for generations.
May it serve you well.
Master.
[TENKA]
Here.
Can't forget this.
Watch me.
I'm about to make you proud.
Or jealous. One of the two.
Look alive, squirt.
Soramaru's gonna need your help.
But aren't you coming?
Yeah. I'll catch up soon.
Chutaro, come on!
[CHUTARO]
Yes, sir!
[GEROKICHI grunts]
[TAKEDA]
Wait just a minute!
I'm not about to let a couple
of brats hog all the glory!
It's early yet to fall into
a swoon, don't you think?
Gimme a break, man.
I'm kinda at my
limit here as it is.
Let a guy get some rest.
Where's the harm in that?
He miraculously survives
execution only to plea
for a moment's repose.
For the record, you might've
told me of Iwakura's bid for
longevity before now.
I know he's been
terminally ill.
Just as I know you're the
guinea pig for his Orochi serum.
Why keep that a
secret from me?
Why bother spillin'
the beans, huh?
It's not like I did this
with you in mind.
It was all for the rug rats.
Sorry to upset
everybody, though.
For what it's worth, that's
the one thing I regret.
[TENKA] Look. I acknowledge
you have every right
to hate my guts.
Answer me this, though...
What would you have
done differently?
On your feet.
I would've tried my damnedest
to do right by those
who looked up to me.
To honor my role as moral
compass by seeing to it
they knew where I stood.
Of course it's easy to apportion
blame in times like these.
But hypotheticals
are meaningless.
In any event, it's not
what I would've done.
It's what I plan to do.
Wait, Kagami?
[KAGAMI]
Room for one more in this posse?
[GEROKICHI growls]
It's okay, Sora! Go!
[heavy breathing]
Haven't you learned
anything, sir?
[KAGAMI]
Oh-ho.
Where was this high-and-mighty
attitude when you were helpin'
me organize the prison break?
That's right. I'm not
the only one here
with blood on his hands.
You're tainted.
I'll atone if it takes
me a hundred years.
But the bad things I've done
aren't all there is to me,
and the same goes for you.
As long as there are
people who love us,
it's never too late to change!
How sweet.
Are you crazy?
Why in the hell
would you protect me?
'Cause even you
deserve a second chance.
If you let go of this hatred,
if you learn how to laugh--
like, really laugh.
You can build a life for
yourself that's worth having.
[KAGAMI]
It's that simple, eh?
That sounds awful.
It's the Orochi.
And he's pissed.
Holy crap.
Look at him!
Ugh. He's hideous.
His power is immense!
[OROCHI roaring]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
He-- He's demolishing Otsu!
Let's stop him.
Okay.
My lord is furious
to have lost his vessel.
Miss Botan, you must
return to Master Soramaru.
I will see justice done to
Shirasu if it costs me my life.
I will not let such
a price be paid.
The Kumoh need you.
Om shiro basara ei sowaka.
Wood begets fire,
fire begets earth,
earth begets metal,
metal begets water,
water begets wood,
wood begets fire.
Om shiro basara ei sowaka.
Stop this! What are you doing?
Look out!
Om shiro basara ei sowka.
Om shiro basara--
Let it be done.
I'll catch you!
Jump!
Master Hirari, it's really you.
But how--?
You know.
Memory's a funny
thing sometimes.
I'm sorry to make you wait.
[BOTAN]
You are a fool, my friend.
Not that I am ungrateful but
you are needed elsewhere.
What are--!
This isn't the time--!
The Kumoh come
from good stock.
I'm sure Tenka and the
boys will be just fine
without yours truly.
I mean, Kagemitsu did all right.
If I may take a moment
to point out the obvious.
You being given the Abe
sword is unprecedented.
Do not take it lightly.
I won't.
Let not your fury be
indiscriminate, my lord.
Let thy wrath be centered
on the deserving.
[GEROKICHI grunts]
Hey, are you all right?
What happened with Kagami?
I'm okay, sir.
I wish I could tell you where
Kagami is but when I woke up,
he was already gone.
[KOTARO] Has Lord Orochi
regained his senses?
[SHIRASU]
Quite.
[KOTARO]
Excellent.
The plan is
unfolding beautifully.
In you,
our blood flourishes.
Shirasu!
What? Tenka?
[KOTARO]
The reins are yours.
Without you, brother, I am
no more than a pale shadow.
Whereas you are
whole unto yourself.
He's insane!
He's going to kill himself!
[KOTARO]
Silence.
You are the cause
of my lord's rancor.
Now rejoice with me
in its denouement.
Oh, no!
Tenny!
You bastard!
[groaning]
What's wrong?
[CHUTARO]
Sora!
It is finished.
The greater share of you
belongs to the Serpent.
In absence of him
you are a shell.
You and your allies
will perish.
[ASHIYA]
We can't keep this up.
[INUKAI]
There's just no end to them.
[SHI QIAN-LANG]
We have been beaten, my friends.
[shouting]
Think Shiga will
take this lyin' down?
[MALE VILLAGER]
Think again!
[blade slashing]
[thud]
So sorry.
We came as soon as we could.
Everybody.
Oh, wow! This is unbelievable!
[MALE VILLAGER 2] We may
not be much, but we can fight!
[MALE VILLAGER 3]
Yeah, we can!
Stand firm, brethren.
Strike fear into the hearts of
the rabble who oppress us.
Too long have we
languished in obscurity.
The hour has come to rise!
This is our ascent!
--[shouting]
--[swords clashing]
[MALE VILLAGER 2] We're not
just a bunch of helpless yokels!
[MALE VILLAGER 3] You wanna
mess with the Kumoh Brothers,
you gotta go through us!
This isn't a battle
I'm backin' down from.
--Gerokichi.
--[GEROKICHI grunts]
Get me as close to
the Orochi as you can.
Whatever the plan is,
take me too!
I need to do this alone.
Hey, that wasn't the deal!
Chutaro, run!
[blade puncturing flesh]
Damn it!
I told you two not
to hog all the glory!
Commander!
In case you hadn't noticed,
we still have an enormous
snake with which to contend.
Yes, sir!
You gotta admit
it's pretty cool,
watchin' the young'uns
pick up right where we left off.
Ha.
I'm not ready to pass
the torch just yet.
Yeah, y'know? Me neither.
No reason there can't
be some overlap.
[TENKA]
Good work!
Nicely done!
Can it really be Tenka?
Do I dare believe my own eyes?
We gonna bow to the Orochi,
or will we fight for our home?
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[TENKA] That's right!
Show me that Omi spirit!
[SORAMARU]
You know,
I almost feel sorry for you.
All that power,
and you've got no one.
No one to love.
No one to make you laugh.
I am Yamainu!
Lieutenant Rakucho Takeda!
I fight the good fight!
I am Chutaro!
Third son of the Kumoh line!
And I stand beside my brother!
I am Soramaru!
And I am not alone!
[ALL shouting]
Your time is at an end.
[water falling]
[TENKA]
So.
Got anything to
say for yourself?
Uh-uh! Don't just walk away!
You owe me an explanation.
Or was our friendship a lie?
Tenka, no!
Be careful!
You wish for closure.
Very well.
You have your family,
and I have mine.
We answer the call
of our blood.
Is that a fact?
[SHIRASU]
Tenka. Move!
Please. I'm trying to tidy up.
No dice, snowman. My body
is one with the floor.
C'mon!
Would it kill ya
to help us out?
[TENKA]
Ha! See, there you go again.
Yellin' like it's
gonna do somethin'.
It's all right. I can clean!
[SHIRASU]
Look, I know you mean well
and everything, but
you're like a cyclone.
Oh my.
I can't fathom what you
three would do without me.
Whoa! Hey, cut it out.
You ain't goin' anywhere.
You're a permanent
fixture o' this household.
[chuckles] Oh, is that a fact?
--[BOTH gasping]
--[gravel crumbling]
Don't you even think about it!
No farewells.
[TENKA]
Shirasu!
[BOTAN] Year Eleven
of Emperor Mejii's reign.
Japan struggles to quell
the highest crime rate
in its history,
as in a quiet corner
of the realm,
the curtain falls on a
drama of cosmic proportions.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Hey. So, uh--
Huh?
Well, how am I supposed to find
in my heart to forgive Shirasu
for what he did to us?
Good question.
Thing is,
it might be kinda
weird saying this, but--
but I miss the bastard.
He was a big part
of this family.
Yeah, I feel the same way
about him sometimes.
Me too.
Hey, jerk.
Thanks for bein'
a great big brother.
I mean it.
We love you, man.
More than anything, sir.
Took the words
right out of my mouth.
All right!
We ready to party?
[VILLAGERS cheer]
Hah! C'mon! Drink up!
Uh. I'm not old enough to, sir.
Master Hirari! Please!
Aw, don't be like that.
I think you've had a bit much.
No hooch. You're
still recovering.
You ain't a doctor!
[laughter]
Here. Try this, it's great.
You're gonna love it!
[whimpering]
[crying]
Uh. Oh crap! What did I say?
It's totally okay if
you're not hungry, miss!
[grunts]
Unacceptable! A gentleman
does not bring a lady to tears!
Ow! Leggo!
Hah!
You'd like that, huh?
Yay! Dog pile!
[grunting]
[CROWD laughs]
I'm starting to
see a resemblance.
Resemblance to whom?
Yo! We havin' fun yet or what?
Yaaaaah!
[groans]
The more things change.
Oh dear.
You're a catastrophe.
And you're a stick.
[giggling]
[SORAMARU]
Life goes on.
We cry.
We love.
We live.
And we laugh.
But no longer
under the clouds.
Keep laughing!