What is it?
Yeah, haven't heard anything
from her since that email.
Kaori says she hasn't been able
to reach her since
yesterday, either.
Oh yes of course I'll
let you know right away
if anything comes up. Take care.
So she's not back at
her parents' place then?
Yeah, that was a dead-end.
Could she be playing a prank?
No, I mean, Yuki may
tease me from time to time,
but I don't think that she'd
ever take anything this far.
Guess goin' to that location
and scoping things
out is our best move.
Sorry to drag you into
this on your day off.
It's okay.
Did I cross a line mixing
business with personal?
Eh, it'll be fine as long
as Gino doesn't find out.
This friend of yours,
she usually hang out
in places like this?
Not at all.
This is getting pretty strange.
It's most definitely strange.
I have no doubt this is a trap.
You're being targeted.
Wait, I am? By who?
Can you think of any
enemies you've made?
No way, I never make enemies!
Look, you do realize you're
a detective now, right?
Oh, great, thanks! Now you're
gonna give me that, too?
In any case I'll go in
check it out. You wait here.
But if this is a trap,
you'll be in danger.
That's why you stay out.
If we both got snagged in there,
no one would know
we're in trouble.
Should we call for
backup now, just in case?
If you feel that's necessary.
But first, I need
permission to carry.
Sure.
This is Akane Tsunemori,
requesting permission
for an Enforcer to carry arms.
Voiceprint and ID confirmed.
Level Two equipment use granted.
I'll leave the
navigation to you.
You've got the
location map, right?
Yeah. The data's a little old,
but should still work.
Do you see anything?
Nope.
In the back there...
Say again...
In the back there,
it's a dead end.
Mister Kogami. Mister Kogami?
Wait a minute! What is that?
What's going on here?
Inspector?
What's wrong? Come in.
I can hear you just fine.
Keep moving forward.
What the hell is this?
It's an abandoned subway line.
You should check the train cars.
Mister Kogami! Can you hear me?
Oh no! Please, come in!
Inspector! What's happening?
It's an abandoned subway line.
You should check the train cars.
It's okay. I'm MWPSB.
And you are ?
I'm Yuki Funahara.
You're Akane Tsunemori's friend.
Uh, yeah, how did you know that?
I work with her.
Not good.
Looks like the whole
bottom level's been flooded
and from the smell, I'd say
that's contaminated water mixed
with liquid waste.
Something like that gets dumped
on you, you're in for a bad day.
Yeah, but I was
tracking Mister Kogami
and he's already
moved beyond that point.
Actually, he went
back even farther,
going straight
through a wall.
Sounds like the
navigator went screwy.
It might be a software
issue, not the hardware.
Since this area's
been redeveloped
so many times
there's no real way
of knowing if the data we have
matches current conditions.
If anyone was deceived
here, wasn't it really you?
And you alone, Inspector?
Kogami managed to
escape your surveillance
and his location is now unknown.
Don't you think... it's possible
he might've staged
this from the start?
All so that he could
make a break for it?
Uh, Missy?
Suppose we trust the navigator
instead of this
expired map data.
Do you at least know
which direction
Kogami was headed in?
Or did his signal show any
kind of strange movements?
Well yeah now that you mention
it all of a sudden, his signal,
it started moving rapidly
in a straight line That's it!
He must've gotten in a vehicle
Isn't there a subway line
somewhere around here?
One that runs north-south?
Wait, let me check.
Yeah, there is.
It was called the Ginza Line,
but it was discontinued
sixty years ago.
I'm guessing it wasn't you
who sent Akane
that email was it?
What email?
What's going on here?
And what the hell am
I doing on an old subway car?
It appears that someone
must have abducted you
and brought you down here.
So you don't remember anything?
I don't know I got home
after working overtime.
I took a warm bath and
went straight to bed.
And when I woke up,
I was where you found me.
Who would do this?
I think you were used as bait
to lure Inspector
Tsunemori to this place.
Wait, no, it's an
abandoned subway line.
You should check the train cars.
Hey, is that Akane?
It's a fake, assembled
from voice samples.
Well-made, but definitely fake.
They must've known
that she wouldn't be
the one to come down
here to investigate.
They were counting on
someone else doing it instead.
So then their target
was never Tsunemori.
Does that mean they're after me?
Did we just stop?
I guess that means
they want us to get off.
Where are we?
They're jamming the signal.
Seems like they're
trying to isolate us
from the rest of the world.
Now they want us
to go through there?
I hate having to do
what they tell us to, but
At this point I don't
see other options.
Follow me!
The hell is this?
So far it's all
going as planned.
And these two
seem especially quick
to pick up on things,
don't they?
The smarter the prey,
the more enjoyable the hunt.
That's excellent.
Looks like this game
will be one worth watching
from the bleacher seats.
Then perhaps you might
like to take part
in the hunt for a change.
Oh, but I have a
vested interest in
what transpires during
this particular excursion.
So it'd be best if I merely
observed as a third party.
What are those?
Chemical lights.
But wouldn't a normal
flashlight work better?
If you're holding
onto a light source,
you'll be an easy
target in the dark.
Besides, these serve as a sign
we've been down this path.
Is Akane's job
dangerous like this?
Yeah it's gotten
really bad lately.
I guess all this time
I should've tried
to take her concerns
more seriously.
She's MWPSB.
She can't discuss details
of her job with civilians.
Is she doing okay at work?
She has faith.
I'll definitely say that.
She has an intuitive
understanding of what it means
to be a detective and
if there's one thing this world
desperately needs more
of it's people like her.
She was always special,
even when we were
in school together.
No matter how
bad the problem was,
as soon as she'd intervene,
it would get resolved.
I wonder about the other people
with the clearest
Psycho-Pass Hues
Do you think they're amazing
as friends like she is?
Wait a minute.
Are you the bad boy subordinate
Akane says always
leaves her at a total loss?
So that's how she talks about
me when I'm not around?
Interesting.
What? What's the matter?
A trap.
Even their traps
are old fashioned.
They've sure got
interesting taste.
Look at that.
A little to the right from
the floor you just checked.
The same bag we saw earlier!
Hold it!
I think I just saw someone!
Yeah. Now I know
what's going on.
We've been lured
into a foxhunt here.
A foxhunt?
Those Drones act
like hunting dogs.
When the prey gets
scared and runs,
then the hunter takes his shot.
Unfortunately,
we're the foxes here.
That's awful.
Don't panic. Don't get scared.
Just remain calm
and look for a way out.
If we freak out, we
play into their hands.
Where's that bag?
Uh, here
What's that?
Portable transponder.
We can communicate with this
even if they're
jamming the signal.
You mean we can
call for help now?
Well, we could
If it wasn't missing the
battery and the antenna.
I'm gonna go create
a distraction.
You just keep your
head down and wait here.
What are you gonna do?
We don't stand a chance
against two foxhounds.
Unless I take at least one
down, they'll surround us
and then we'll
really be done for.
Mister Kogami!
Let's go!
I got one of 'em.
And now all
I need's the antenna.
He's a cunning one.
He may be just a fox, but
that still makes him a canine.
Or perhaps a member
of the wolf family.
Mister Makishima,
I'm starting to suspect
you've introduced some
additional plot twists
into this game,
unbeknownst to me.
Am I correct in thinking this?
When a man is confronted with
fear his very soul is tested.
Everything that
he was born to seek,
everything that he
was born to achieve,
his true nature will be
revealed quite clearly.
Was that intended to mock me?
It's not just this
Kogami I have my eyes on.
I'm interested in you
as well, Mister Senguji.
An unforeseen situation,
an unexpected turn of events.
In the wake of such moments,
you too will be forced
to face your true self.
I know that that is the thrill
and experience you've
really been chasing here.
Indeed. You know, I have
to say I don't really mind
this habit of yours of
observing others from on high.
And now Shinya Kogami
let's see if you will come
to understand the true
meaning of this game.
I can't run anymore.
I can't! I just can't!
Hey! Are you listening?
Sorry. I was lost in thought.
Well, please, just say
something, anything.
When you're quiet you can be
a little creepy, you know that?
I was thinking...
With you as bait, they
knew they'd lure in Akane
but they counted
on her enlisting me
to come look for
you in her place.
They had it all worked
out when they set this up.
So it's really you they wanted
to play this game
with all along, isn't it?
ha Which means
that I'm just, damn it!
I'm just some stupid
pawn in all this?
I think that's right.
But once that email was sent
from your account last
night to bring us here,
you'd no longer be
necessary to them.
So then why did they
bring you down here
and put you on that subway car?
I think I know.
Doesn't my being here
make it much more difficult
for you to run away from them?
In fact, I'm the only
thing holding you back,
even as we speak.
If I wasn't here, you'd
be making a clean break
for it right now, wouldn't you?
It's fine. Just do
what you have to do.
This sucks.
The fox hunt...
it isn't just a
one-sided game now.
With this, I think
they're hinting
that I've got a
chance to win, too.
In other words,
I'm being tested.
And whether or
not I abandon you
I bet that decision
is one of the keys
to winning this game.
Hey, take off your clothes.
What, right here,
in the middle of all this?
Are you out of your damn mind?
Just give 'em to me.
This is insane!
I think you've got a
screw loose or something!
If you wanna make it out
of here alive, then strip!
Can't believe the MWPSB
hires pervs like you!
What? What are you looking at?
Wouldn't you normally
match your underwear?
That's weird. But why would...?
I'll need those, too.
You can at least
look the other way.
And there we have it.
The last item we
needed to beat the game
was hidden right there on you.
It's the transponder's
missing antenna.
I'm seeing some
pretty heavy jamming
throughout this area right here
though the range is limited.
Where's the source
of the jamming?
It's coming from the southwest.
But looking at the map,
there shouldn't be anything
in that whole section.
All right.
Let's go ahead and set up
a relay base right here.
Don't trust the map data.
Check every single gap
and corner thoroughly.
Also as soon as you see Kogami,
shoot him with the Dominator.
There's no need to warn him.
But we still don't know
if he was actually
trying to run away.
The Sibyl System will make
that determination for us.
If he did nothing wrong
then his Crime Coefficient
will be the same as the
last time you shot him.
And the Paralyzer
mode will knock him out
But if he really
wanted to fly the coop
then it'll mercilessly go into
Eliminator mode and that's it.
Yes, well, the cymatic
scan is never wrong.
It will reveal
Kogami's true intentions.
Are you really saying you'd
be okay with killing him?
You used to be his
friend, didn't you?
If he does end up dying,
Inspector Tsunemori,
it'll be due to
your poor supervision.
If you had any
control over Kogami,
then we wouldn't
be in this position
of having to potentially
kill the man.
Tell me: How does
it feel knowing
someone could die because
of your incompetence?
All right, Inspector.
That's enough, don't you think?
You're bein' a little
hard on the girl?
It's from Kogami!
Run a trace on my location.
We have a Code 108 in progress.
Requesting immediate backup.
I repeat: We have a
Code 108 in progress.
Send in the drones!
We don't know the right path.
Just pick them at random!
And make sure at least one
of those drones reaches him!
Hold on Kogami. We're coming!