Inspector Tsunemori,
take Masaoka
into those tunnels
and find Kogami.
Let us know when you do.
The rest of us
will search the area
for the source of that
jamming signal and destroy it.
Careful out there.
Yes sir.
To be honest. I have no
idea what's going on.
The powerful jamming.
This unmapped underground.
And a call for
backup from Kogami.
Well we know one
thing: it's serious.
Yes, it would seem so.
I've never heard Ko like that.
He really sounded desperate.
There's something bad down here.
I don't care much for
games of hide and seek.
They want to spoil my fun.
This must be it.
Take that!
User authentication,
Enforcer Shinya Kogami.
You are a valid user.
The Target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be
completely annihilated.
Please proceed
with maximum caution.
Aim carefully and
eliminate the target.
There's a pattern.
Silence after every two shots.
This guy must be using a
double-barreled hunting gun.
I've got bad news
Your time is up.
Seems they've destroyed
the jamming device.
According to protocol,
the main unit of the
MWPSB is about to rush in.
Lovecraft was
just blown to hell.
That bastard enforcer
destroyed it.
He finally got his nerve
and started to fight.
What will you do now?
When I was young I spent a
long time working construction
in developing countries,
mostly infrastructure.
The more dangerous the place,
the more the job would pay.
Conflict would
come out of nowhere,
and there was no way to
predict the next danger,
or limit the risk.
I remember our people
getting ambushed
once by guerilla troops.
That must've been seventy
or eighty years ago.
It was gruesome.
The colleague next to me
was shot with an incendiary.
He was a good friend, and
one minute he was shouting
and crying out in horror, and
then the next he was nothing
but a disgusting lump of
flesh melting in the seat.
His blood splattered
and dripped down my head,
and the smell of
his remains-- my god.
It stuck to me, stayed with me
no matter how I tried
to get rid of it.
I don't want you to get the
wrong idea when I say this,
but for me that's a
memory that I cherish.
That moment I felt awake, alive.
It was an indescribable
intensity
of existence I've never equaled
for the rest of my life.
But after all this time
I'm finally feeling
that intensity again.
My heart may now be mechanical,
but my blood burns in
a way I had forgotten.
And you're suggesting I run?
Not even you could
be that cruel of a man.
From here on, it won't
be a game anymore.
That's exactly right.
As an avid hunter,
I've shot down countless
prey over the years.
But now I want to
confront that Enforcer
as a duelist man to man.
Tell me the truth, Makishima.
Surely you didn't
invest all this time in me
because you thought I would
turn tail now, did you?
That wouldn't be
interesting to you at all.
Clearly you know me too well.
I'll witness the
splendor of your life
all the way until you
draw your last breath.
It'll be checkmate for you
soon enough, Enforcer hound.
Crime Coefficient, 328.
Enforcement action required.
Amazing. We did it!
We really beat that monster!
I'm sorry for putting
you at so much risk
Once we're out of this place
get therapy treatment
as soon as you can.
You saw way too many
things you shouldn't have.
I'm just sorry I couldn't
shield you from that.
That's okay.
Don't blame yourself.
You've been wonderful.
If you're what latent
criminals are like,
I wouldn't mind
being one myself.
Don't be stupid.
Stop it! Let me go!
I would love to
stay here with you
and talk the
whole night through,
but you don't seem to be
in proper shape for that
I'll see you again soon.
Stop! Mr. Kogami!
Don't let your guard down.
Calling this dangerous would
be an understatement.
There's bullet holes everywhere.
Must be a shotgun.
I think it's been years
since I've seen the
traces of actual gunpowder.
Do you see this blood?
Where are you Kogami
Someone help!
Yuki!
Do you know that voice?
It sounds like my
friend who went missing.
Please we have to
find her, let's go!
That's Kogami!
Kogami!
He's in bad shape.
Looks like multiple bullet
wounds from close range.
First aid.
Think you can you do it?
I've had my training sessions,
but I've never actually
done it for real.
Then you'll have
to leave it to me.
Akane.
There's a second man here.
He handcuffed your friend
and went that direction.
Try to stay out of the way.
I can at least
stop his bleeding.
Where the hell are
you going? Inspector!
This case isn't over yet!
Shit!
It's like a battlefield,
no, an execution ground.
Look at all this blood.
It couldn't have been
just three or four people.
I'd say several dozen, at least.
For all we know, a hundred
people could've died down here.
It seems Kogami was
lured into this place.
So many massacred.
And to what end?
What did the killer do this for?
Some kind of a game, maybe?
What?
I don't know.
It's just a feeling I've had
ever since we got down here.
This place looks like
the kind of battle arena
you'd see in a
fighting game online.
I could understand
if it were virtual,
but who would play a game
using live human beings?
This is Hound One.
Can anyone hear me?
This is Shepherd One.
What's your status?
I'm tending to Hound Three.
He's hurt so bad I'm
surprised he's still ticking.
A culprit is on the
run with a hostage.
Shepherd Two is
pursing him alone.
You have to hurry!
I don't think she's going
to fare so well by herself.
Dammit.
Message has been received.
Stay right where
you are Hound One.
We'll head there
to assist you now!
It sounds like this so-called
game isn't over just yet.
I want both of you
on high alert got it?
I feel so heavy.
It doesn't even seem
like my own body right now.
That's probably because
it's full of bullets.
If I try to pull 'em out and
my nervous hands hit an artery,
you could be finished for good,
so I'll save that for the pros.
Honestly I can't believe
you're even conscious right now.
And where is
Inspector Tsunemori?
Yeah that's what
I'd like to know.
She ran off alone.
Apparently she was
chasing somebody.
I've done all the
first aid I can,
and you're at least stabilized.
So I'm going after her now.
I'm coming too.
Are you an idiot?
I have to.
I hate to do that to a
guy who's already hurt,
but you're a stubborn ass
and I don't have the
time to argue with you.
I'd say If the people
responsible for this are strong
enough to mess you up,
that girl's in all
kinds of trouble.
Enforcer Masaoka!
Good of you to
join us, Inspector.
Hold down Kogami so he
won't try to follow me!
Don't know when
to quit, as usual.
What is it?
Looks like Ko shot
somebody really dangerous.
Toyohisa Senguji?
Oh, you have gotta
be kidding me.
Who's that?
Don't you watch the Ministry
of Welfare's recommended news?
Why the hell would
I watch that crap?
Stop right there!
This is the MWPSB!
Drop your weapon and surrender!
Crime Coefficient: 79.
Enforcement action not required.
The trigger is now locked.
Akane help!
Just hold on Yuki,
you'll be fine.
Oh, yes. I know your face.
You're the promising young
Inspector Akane
Tsunemori aren't you?
And you're the madman
who dragged Yuki into this.
I'm Shogo. Shogo Makishima.
Makishima?
Interesting. So you've
heard my name before.
That's encouraging.
Nice to know you're
not completely clueless.
We've got serious
charges against you
for multiple
crimes in this city.
Based on the Citizen's
Charter, I demand you come
with me for questioning and
the due enforcement of the law!
If we need to talk, let's
do it right here, right now.
We're both busy people, right?
You think you
can escape from me?
Don't they train you to buy time
for your backup
in this situation?
You should promote lively
conversation to distract me.
I'm sure a more experienced
detective would remember that.
Now when you
said multiple crimes,
which exactly were
you referring to?
Masatake Mido?
Or perhaps Rikako Ouryou?
Just as I thought.
I think people only
have real value
when acting on their own
impulses and desires.
So I've asked quite a few people
about their
suppressed free will.
I encourage them, I facilitate.
And then I watch for
the truth to play out.
Don't talk yourself up!
You're a criminal, nothing more!
There's a good conversation
starter--how do
we define criminal?
Maybe that Dominator
you're holding.
Shall we allow the Sibyl System
that which governs it
to decide what I am?
Crime Coefficient: under 50.
Enforcement action not required.
Trigger will remain locked.
By reading a bio-organism's
force field using
a cymatic scan some
very smart people
have found a way to
analyze a person's mind.
The intelligence of science
finally uncovered the
secret of our souls
and our society has changed
drastically because of it.
The problem is free will has
been stripped from the equation.
And if man is not
judged by their choices,
then how are we really deciding
who is good and who is evil?
What on earth are
you talking about?
I'm talking about seeing
the naked splendor
of people's souls.
I want to see our
precious lives played out
on the stage of the world.
But how can our
souls be precious
if they're not utilized?
If we base our lives
on Sybil's Oracle
and not our own free will.
Then can our souls have value?
Well since I'm here. I guess
I'll try testing you too.
Let's put your judgment
as a detective to the test.
Hold on. What are
you planning to do now?
I'm going to stand
next to this woman
named Yuki Funahara,
and I'm going to kill her.
Right before your eyes.
Crime Coefficient: 48.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
If you want to stop
me, instead of using
that useless piece of
scrap metal and circuits,
you can pick up the gun
I just gave you and shoot me.
Pull the trigger and a bullet
will fire, it's your choice.
I can't do that.
It's not my decision.
That isn't how it works.
You mean because I'm a
good upstanding citizen?
Because that's what
trusty Sibyl has declared.
Crime Coefficient: 32.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
What? But why?
That's a question I've
been asking for a long time.
Ever since I was a child
actually, my Psycho-Pass
has never been anything
but the purest white
It's never gotten cloudy,
not even for a moment I think
my body must be deluding itself.
Performing all sorts of vital
reactions as if I'm a saint.
Encouraging me to continue on
with a clean conscience,
doing whatever I want to do.
Help me! Akane. Do something!
Yuki!
You Inspectors just aren't
qualified to measure my sins.
If there are people
left in this world
who can judge me,
It is the fallen.
those who've shown
they have the freedom
to become killers
based on their own will.
I'm warning you now,
let her go! Or else!
Or else you'll kill me?
Get up off of the sidelines?
And for once lay
claim to your own soul?
That would be a rather precious
ending in its own ironic way.
Feel it? The importance of life?
Resting gingerly
against your fingertip?
As long as you're
Sibyl's puppet,
you can never experience that.
That's the weight of
decision and free will.
Crime Coefficient: under 20.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
René Descartes.
He said that those who can't
make a decision can't do
so either because their
passions are too great,
or because they lack
the sufficient intellect.
Find your resolve.
Unless you hold the gun
firmly, the bullet will miss.
Now. Aim with
the intent to kill.
Wha--? Akane
Not enough resolve.
How very regrettable for you.
Your failure has cost
your friend's life.
No! Help me ! Akane!
You've disappointed me.
So I have to give
you your punishment.
Don't. Please!
Regret helplessness, Akane.
And feel true despair.
Crime Coefficient: Zero.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
Yuki No!!!
That's Akane!
So you're awake.
Where's Inspector Tsunemori?
I let her die
without doing anything.
I let her die without
doing anything.
Tell me what happened.
The man from the
picture. It, it was him.
What man, what do you mean?
Shogo Makishima.
The Dominator won't work.
It won't judge him.