Our one rule in the Talisman
Saloon is that we're not here
to talk about ourselves,
only the affairs of others.
So careful with your phrasing,
okay, Lemonade Candy?
Okay. A friend of mine
has found herself in
quite the predicament,
so I'd like to get your thoughts
on her situation, Talisman.
Well of course, I'd be
delighted. I'll do my best
to help this friend of yours.
Tell me her situation
and we'll see
if I can't put the old
Talisman spin on things.
Yeah, Talisman!
Well, let's see... She recently
began a tough job right after
she graduated. A job with
a lot of responsibility.
But that's not the problem.
I know she doesn't regret
working there or anything.
Please continue.
The problem she's having stems
from one of her coworkers.
Well actually, he's more
of a senior colleague,
but he's ranked beneath her.
It's kind of tough to explain,
but they work together and
it's like she can't avoid him.
He's an important part of
her carrying out her job.
And he's difficult to work with?
Is that the issue?
His behavior can be
pretty erratic at times.
The thing is, she also
feels like there are times
that he makes a lot of sense.
And so she started to believe
that she might be able to
trust him at some point.
That's always a nice thought,
but there is still
the likely possibility that it
is nothing but wishful thinking.
So you think she's
being unrealistic?
It sounds like she might want
him to be something he's not.
She needs to look past
her surface assumptions
to understand
his true character.
Why don't you give this
advice to your friend
and see if it makes
things easier for her?
Step forward and share
your troubles with me, Talisman.
The difficulties of those cast
adrift may seem hopeless
but the answers
are already there,
hiding within the
stories you have to tell.
So I don't understand
his true character, huh?
You wanna ask me
about Kogami, don't you?
How could you tell?
The way you seem to be connected
by fate, I'd be curious too.
I just wish I could wrap
my head around
how I should deal with him.
Someone told me I should
try to understand him
and then someone else told me
that I shouldn't
consider him a human.
I can guess that advice came
from Inspector Ginoza.
It works for him. Dogs are
dogs and owners are owners.
But ya break everything
down to its basic nature
and I think it might
be easier for you
if you just stuck
to your own side.
If you really wanna
understand, Kogami the only way
to do it is to see
things the way he does
and think like he does.
And if you can manage
to accomplish that,
you'll find yourself
in the dog pound with us.
Your Pyscho-Pass will have a
reading identical to Kogami's.
"Gaze into the abyss and the
abyss also gazes into you."
Just ask Kogami. He stared
into the darkness too long.
So long that I don't think
he knows how to look away.
I get the impression that he's
convinced the only place justice
actually exists is within
the depths of that darkness.
If you really feel so
compelled to dive in after him,
well, that's
completely up to you.
There's nothing I could
say to change your mind.
I can't stop you if that's
what you really want.
I couldn't stop Ko, either.
Is that what...?
Something happen?
Looks like it.
Well I'm off duty now,
same with Kunizuka.
Kogami and Kagari
should be around.
So, What's the situation?
We got weird results from
the home security test.
The toilet in this
apartment has apparently
been broken for
the past two months.
And yet the tenant hasn't
filed a single complaint.
So the management
company got suspicious
and reported it to us.
Kimihiko Hayama 32 years old,
single, and unemployed.
He's unemployed?
In this day and age?
How is that even possible?
I checked the
records from his bank.
He was sponsored by an
affiliate service provider
and he was rather
well compensated.
Enough so that I'm positive
he lives in great comfort.
What a sweet deal.
Sit at home and get super paid
for being popular on the net.
Why the hell would you
want a straight job?
Only a chump would
turn that down.
Could he just be on an
extended trip somewhere?
Not possible. Not with
all the street scanners.
We would have a tracking
record of his movements.
There's no way a person
can get out of this city
without leaving some
kind of trace to follow.
Besides, his bank
account doesn't show
any activity for
the past two months.
This is easy. He's dead.
Clearly.
It's more difficult to
disappear than to get killed.
It's still too soon to
land on that conclusion.
Can we pull up the last interior
holo design for this room?
Hold on a sec.
What? Why's this
We all know you can't sit
on a hologram the whole point
of the holography design is to
line it up with the real couch.
To state the obvious: That
couch was over there originally,
but somebody had
a reason to move it.
Yeah, good call.
I think it's safe to say
they were trying to hide that.
Why worry about such
a small scratch.
Have one of the
Crime Lab Drones scan it.
Yep. Leftover
adhesive from tape.
And what does that mean?
That's the big reveal to
the magic trick they pulled.
The wand they used to
make Hayama disappear.
Of course they had
to murder him first,
probably poisoning or
strangling, something clean.
Some kind of bloodless
method to avoid any evidence.
Then they taped
down a plastic sheet,
and went to work
dismantling the body.
Chopped him up enough
to flush the pieces,
which probably
busted the toilet.
Hayama must've put up a fight
when they tried to kill him.
The struggle left the scratch
and the adhesive residue
is obviously left over from
when they taped the sheet down.
They're determined,
I'll give 'em that,
but it's an amateur job.
It can't be.
Bring in old Masaoka
if you don't believe me.
He would've sniffed it out
the moment he walked in here.
Trust me.
Can't fool a hunting
dog's sense of smell.
Let's check the plumbing
for any traces of blood.
We'll discuss more after that.
Alright then
Okay, it's open.
This is the online avatar
Hayama was using? Talisman?
The dude must've had a
pretty large fan base.
That's really the only way
you can make serious
money as an affiliate.
Talisman?
Y'know it?
Kind of... Yeah.
I spoke with him for the
first time just this morning.
Technology to the rescue.
Our precious Crime Lab Drones
have practically
built this case for you.
They managed to find the
remains of Hayama's body
scattered throughout the
sewers beneath his apartment.
A round of applause please.
So the guy's in countless
pieces but his CommuField
is still active and someone is
obviously posing as his avatar.
You got it.
S'like a horror movie.
A ghost haunting the forums
and chat rooms of the Internet.
I'd watch it.
So someone's
claimed his identity?
I'm really not sure.
It seems that way, but he was
apparently screwing around
with fake IPs back
before he went missing.
What about tracking
the access routes?
I don't know, but it's
worth giving it a shot.
It's tricky though, because
they're all running through
a variety of high
security proxy servers.
They've got all sorts
of paranoid measures
in place to hide their
client's footsteps.
We've gotta track 'em carefully,
or they'll notice us.
But luckily it
won't go past them.
They'll relocate the route
but they won't report it
so whoever's using
his avatar won't realize
they've aroused suspicion.
And that should give us
a fighting chance.
The suspect...
He doesn't even feel there's a
need to hide out and try to run.
He's practically walking
around beneath our noses.
If we play our cards
right we could very likely
get him to drop some clues
as to his real identity.
Right. Well let's hunt
down Hayama's avatar.
Making contact's a good
idea, but who does it?
Interesting.
This impostor's been
posing as him for two months
Running the Talisman
CommuField just as capably
as the real owner this whole
time and nobody's noticed.
Mister Ginoza, that's him.
Looks like he's heading off to
check out another CommuField.
Okay Let's follow.
Oh, yeah, this is Spooky
Boogie's CommuField.
This is a pretty
big community too.
Spooky Boogie!
We love you, Spooky!
You're the best, Spooky!
Woo, Spooky!
We've gotta be careful in here.
Spooky Boogie's notorious
for being an anarchist.
It could mean trouble if she
finds out we're detectives.
Good to know.
Does she have any
connections with Talisman?
Maybe. They're both
pretty famous,
although, that doesn't
necessarily mean they
know each other in real life.
Let's check their access logs
we can track their
visitations that way.
If they frequent each other's
CommuFields, then-Tsunemori?
What the... Ginoza?
Hello, there,
Miss Lemonade Candy.
I'm the hostess of this fabulous
CommuField, Spooky Boogie.
You're such an
unexpected visitor.
I had to invite
you to my chat room.
I hope it's not
an inconvenience.
Uh, no, it's not but
I'm curious, why me?
I've heard intriguing rumors.
That look on your face,
you really have no idea
just how famous you are,
do you, Lemonade Candy?
You are.
And I'm quite the fan
of yours, Akane Tsunemori.
How... Who are you?
Well If you really
want to figure that out,
you could start by scouring
the pages of your
old graduation album.
And if you guess who I am
I'll buy you a drink at
our next class reunion.
So, I can't help but
wonder why an Inspector
with the CID is
scoping out my CommuField.
I've got a funny feeling you
didn't just drop by to hang out.
So uhh.
I mean... Do you regularly
speak with Talisman?
Yeah, I have to.
We're rivals in the access
ranking, it'd be foolish not to.
Have you noticed anything
different about him?
Anything odd with his
avatar or his field?
Like, sometime within the
past several months or so?
Let's see.
Nothing that really
comes to mind as of late,
but there was a period
of time about, yeah,
it was about two months ago
he was acting strangely.
What? How exactly?
There were a couple of
things that really stood out.
He was speaking erratically
and he kept holding events
that were clearly intended
to get affiliate money.
It was fuel on the fire
for the Talisman haters.
He rubbed enough
people the wrong way
that it started to look
like the old timer avatar
was gonna have to call it quits.
But he bounced back.
You said he's not like that now?
Yep. He's back to his usual cool
and mellow self these days.
He's gone on record
and publically apologized
for his behavior.
It's pretty tough
for an avatar who went
into such a drastic decline to
make a full comeback, though.
So are you doing an official
investigation into him?
Did Talisman do something wrong?
I can't really talk
about the details.
It's complicated though we
need to physically track down
and locate him.
the person behind
the avatar, I mean.
That's kind of intriguing.
I'd be happy to offer
you some assistance.
What?
A PSB beaureacrat in debt
to little ol' me could
come in handy.
Infamous anarchist Spooky
Boogie working with the law.
Wasn't expecting that.
That's just part of my
public persona and besides,
we were classmates,
just leave this to me, okay?
Your attention please,
my dear and loyal guests.
To show my appreciation
for your support,
for all your love, and
for visiting my forum,
I'd like to invite you all
to a modest yet grand
party held in your honor.
It'll be a meetup in
Roppongi on the fourth.
In addition, I will challenge
my friend Talisman to a duel.
A chance to win the
White Crown I currently hold.
I hope to see all of you there.
A meet-up?
That's right
CommuField users gather
somewhat regularly for parties.
They wear Holo-Cosplay
that simulates their
online social avatars
It's completely anonymous.
The modern version
of a masquerade ball.
Alright, but the big question:
How can we be certain that
Talisman will actually show up?
He can't afford not to.
His popularity will
plummet if he backs out.
Whoever's been posing
as Hayama's avatar,
they've got no
choice but to be there.
They've already put
so much effort
into making sure his
CommuField runs smoothly.
They've gotta
show at this meet-up
if they don't wanna squander all
the work they've put into it.
He can't hide behind
his Holo-Cosplay.
The only thing we have
to do is get him in the
Dominator's sights
and his Crime Coefficient
is bound to give him away.
Right. Where's the meet-up?
At a club in Roppongi, Exoset.
Ginoza's team is on
the front entrance
and the drones are
positioned out back.
All we've gotta do is stand
back and wait for him to show.
I take back that masquerade
ball comment I made earlier.
It's a hell of a
lot weirder than that.
They're packed like
cigarettes into a place
with only two exits and
they don't even know
who's standing next to them.
How can they be
comfortable with this?
It's impossible to participate
in the social networks
if you're afraid of anonymity.
But this isn't virtual.
You can bleed and die in
here and any one of these
costumed freaks could be
carrying a knife on them.
And they're fine
with putting their lives
into the hands of strangers.
They're out of their
damn minds if you ask me.
That kind of thinking is exactly
what causes your
Pycho-Pass to get so cloudy.
Sorry, that was rude.
It came out the wrong way.
It's okay.
That's a legitimate point.
Take a look. It's him.
We can't get a read from here
Too many guests to clearly aim.
I'm gonna try to
get closer to him.
Dominator Suppression
System Online.
No way.
Now would I lie to you?
Well, crap I knew it.
Mr. Mido? You were
right on the money.
A Dominator was just
detected out on the floor.
There's definitely an
Inspector here. No doubt.
So it really is a trap.
Damn Spooky Boogie.
You better get out of
there while you can.
It'll royally muck things
up if you get caught.
I'm aware of that.
I've also got
unfinished business.
I'll help you get out.
Shit! What the
hell just happened?
Someone hacked all
the Holo-Cosplay!
The suspect's gonna run!
Dammit! Pull your Dominator.
We'll root him out by
his Crime Coefficient.
It's the CID!
Wait!
Crime Coefficient Over one-ten.
Over one-forty.
Target for enforcement action.
Crap, how many of 'em are there?
This went from covert
to full-blown raid.
Well this is great.
They spotted us.
Oh! Sorry!
What the hell were you trying
to pull with this meet-up?
My boyfriend got
busted by the MWPSB!
Are you gonna pay
for his treatment?
Please! Everyone just calm down!
I had nothing
to do with this raid!
I'm just as upset
about it as you are!
We can see right through
your lies, Spooky Boogie.
Judging by the way it went down
they must've been in the club
before the party started.
The only way that
could happen was
if the organizer was in on it.
You've always touted anarchism
as your guiding principle.
One of the reasons so many
love you and yet you've colluded
with the government
against your own followers.
A truly unacceptable offense.
Wha- That is not true!
From the way it looked to me,
you're the one they
were after, Talisman.
So if anyone's at
fault here, it's you!
You've betrayed your fans,
as well as your own character.
You have no right to call
yourself Spooky Boogie
and you certainly no
longer deserve the trust
and adoration of our community.
You... You have no right to say
that, you don't know anything!
I know more about you than you
could ever know about yourself.
Shut up, you creep!
What's his problem?
Talk about creepy.
Just who the hell
does he think he is?
I'm putting a block on
his access to my CommuField.
Screw that. He won't get
anywhere near me again.
There's really no point in that.
It's no longer your forum.
And Spooky Boogie is no
longer your avatar, either.
Did you kill her?
This woman had no right to carry
on acting as Spooky Boogie.
But Spooky Boogie shouldn't
vanish from the net.
She puts a smile
on so many faces.
With a little bit of crowd work,
Spooky Boogie can still be used.
The woman behind
her can be flushed.
Sure, I bet you'll make
a great Spooky Boogie.
Even better than
Shoko Sugawara herself.
Just look at what
you've done with Talisman.
You're leaps and bounds
better than Hayama.