Uh, hi, can we help you?
I need you to give me the
medicine written on this paper.
Sorry we can't give this to you.
Psychotropic substances
are only administered
at authorized facilities,
and besides
you'd need a prescription,
biological data
You don't get it, do you?
Help me!
Someone, please, help!
No one is coming to save you.
Come on, give me
the medicine, lady!
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
of the Public Safety Bureau.
For your protection,
access to this block
is currently restricted.
Please, keep moving.
Do not stop.
Hey, there.
I think I know what's going
through your head right now.
But Mister Kogami...
But today just focus
on the case at hand.
Okay. Got it.
All right, talk to me.
What do we have?
Well. Let's see uh.
The crime itself was
about as straightforward
as these kinds of things get.
The perp waltzed right through
the door like he
owned the place,
killed the two pill jockeys,
helped himself
to whatever meds he
came here looking for today
and then calmly walked out
as if nothing happened.
The security cameras were able
to capture the whole ordeal.
Someone, please, help!
What is up with that
freaky helmet there?
You know he's suspicious
just by looking at him.
Maybe, but just
looking suspicious
isn't enough to
set off any alarms.
From the moment he set
foot in the pharmacy,
his Psycho-Pass
showed a normal value
and his Hue remained clear.
The log is recorded
on the scanner, too.
Oh, great, does that mean
we've got another freak
like that Makishima
guy on our hands?
Someone who can commit
cold-blooded murder
while keeping his
Psycho-Pass normal?
I'm thinking the
helmet is the key here.
It must have some
bypass feature.
It's deceiving
the cymatic scans.
The man who got the jump
on Inspector Tsunemori,
this Makishima he might've
used a similar device.
Wait. Are you serious?
Are you saying that a
stupid helmet could be
all somebody needs to
fake their Psycho-Pass?
If it was simply blocking
the cymatic scan,
that would be tech
I could understand.
But, of course, that
alone wouldn't be enough
to get past security.
Because if someone who couldn't
be scanned tried to enter,
an alarm would
go off immediately.
The problem we have here is
that the scanner successfully
detected the
intruder's Psycho-Pass,
and yet somehow it determined
he had the clear Hue of a fine,
upstanding citizen who
couldn't even hurt a fly.
So did he crack the system then?
No, that's just not possible.
The attack didn't seem
to be premeditated
and everything happened
in a short period of time.
There's no way for
someone to alter the data
without leaving
any kind of trace.
The current security
system is founded
on the assumption that a
cymatic scan is reliable.
It's because of that
assumption that anyone
whose Psycho-Pass checks out is
considered incapable of causing
and is let in there's no risk.
Even when actual
assaults or thefts occur
the Drones' AI isn't
equipped with the ability
to identify such
actions as crimes.
Since everyone's
Psycho-Pass is scanned,
their judgment's based on that.
That means we don't
have any methods left
to prevent crimes like this.
Nothing. This whole
city is unprotected.
Yeah, exactly.
So I told him,
"That's not my job, okay?
Get somebody else
to do that for you."
After that, he just had
this stupid look on his face,
like he didn't know whether
to yell or cry it was awful
Hey. What do you want with me?
I detect that you
are experiencing
a high level of stress.
It is recommended that
you seek help immediately
from a specialized
mental health facility.
Are you distressed?
The Ministry of
Welfare's Urban Service
helps everyone lead a
happier and healthier life.
Has someone been injured
or suddenly become ill?
Would you like to
request an ambulance
from the nearest
emergency hospital?
Please be advised
that you will be charged
an uninsured service
fee at a later date.
Now that right there is some
phenomenal stuff. So brutal.
In the old days, it was normal
for people to physically
lock their front doors
because the doubting of others
was the basis for
maintaining order then.
Did you get that
from one of Mister Masaoka's
stories about the past?
Yeah. Guess they're
not totally useless.
Anyway, Now we
don't have to doubt,
or approach other people
with cautious skepticism.
You know that those
strangers you see
on the street aren't going to
hurt you because each one
of them has had their
Psycho-Pass verified.
This society maintains its
order based on that assumption.
But if, like that helmeted
man, people come
to find out that there's a way
to deceive the cymatic scans,
there'll be panic.
Yeah that's true,
or if word gets out about
the existence of Makishima.
What is it?
An elevated Area
Stress Level warning's
been issued in
the Setagaya Ward.
But shelving that for now
there's a rather
disturbing video
that's just been uploaded
on the net. Here, look.
What the hell?
What is going on here?
It's begun.
This is just. What's happening?
Makishima is behind this
crime. I'd bet anything on it
Of course
I'm not even sure what crime
is in this world anymore.
Ko, what're you thinking?
This isn't just some random act.
It's more like a seismic event
that shakes our very foundation.
Woah, that's crazy
When they said they
were gonna demo it,
they weren't messin' around.
We should go now.
Impressive how much
the Area Stress Level
has elevated in
such a short time.
Hello.
This will work.
The plan doesn't
need to be revised.
You're being ridiculous.
It's just one person
killing another, that's all.
Nothing particularly
serious has happened yet.
The really serious stuff
is yet to come.
Listen. You're the only one
who I've shared the
entire plan with.
I'm counting on you.
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department...
The victim's name
is Hiroko Fujii.
Hard to believe that goes down
in the middle of
a crowded street.
What the hell
happened to this city?
I tell you, it's outta control.
Do you think it's
the same perpetrator
from the pharmacy attack?
Well, I'd say
it's more than likely.
He's getting more
brazen, though.
Doing it in front
of all these people.
And how could they
just stand there?
The witness testimonies all
sound pretty much the same.
They say they
couldn't understand
what they were seeing.
I don't think we can judge them.
Someone getting killed
right in front of you.
You can't imagine it.
The idea wouldn't
cross your mind.
Every one of these
people had gone
through their lives
without ever considering it.
We all grew up believing
this wasn't possible.
And in the end, not a single
one felt the need
to report the incident,
so the elevated Area
Stress Level warning
was the only way we were able
to know something was wrong.
Yeah, but humans weren't alone
in missing what
was in front of them.
Of all things, he kills the girl
right under a
Psycho-Pass scanner.
So, does that mean any
change in the culprit's Hue
would've been
monitored in real time?
Yeah I'm pulling it up now.
He managed to maintain
a normal value yet again?
Unbelievable.
Even at the moment when
he's striking her dead,
it registers only
a minor fluctuation.
Is there any chance
that the value itself
could've been faked this time?
No way.
Fabricating a Psycho-Pass
just isn't possible.
Unless he's lugging
around a supercomputer.
Hey wait a second.
Now this is really bizarre.
Yeah, his value makes no sense.
It's more than that.
It looks too much like
an onlooker's reaction.
Check this out.
That graph there charts
the Area Stress Level.
It matches up perfectly with the
change in the murderer's Hue.
Whoa you're right.
If that's true,
this guy's mental state
was the exact same as the
witnesses watching him kill her.
I wonder if they'll be able
to see through that
little trick right away.
This is a simple
but impressive trick.
Although I'm afraid it can
be a bit limited, as well.
I think the reception range
is only about thirty meters.
But if there's even one
person within that range
who has a clear color.
Then it doesn't matter what
you're thinking
inside the helmet,
or what you do while wearing it.
The folks at the CID
will probably notice soon
that there was another
person in the vicinity
with the exact same Hue,
assuming they comb through
the scan data of everyone
who was at the scene.
Inspectors, we've got
another emergency.
What is it this time?
There are reports
that an armored car
was attacked on the freeway.
An armored car?
They must be crazy.
Hey, Shion, the
guys who did this
were wearing
helmets, too, right?
Excellent guess. Yes, they were.
There were three of them and
they were armed with shop tools.
This case is separate
from the one you're working.
How do we proceed?
We'll split up into
two separate teams.
Kagari and Kunizuka,
I want you to come with me.
You got it.
You guys keep looking
for the pharmacy attacker.
We'll go after the
armored car hijackers.
Hey, so these guys are
armed with real weapons, huh?
Which means that if this
thing doesn't work on them,
we're gonna be totally
outmatched and defenseless,
isn't that right, Gino?
Just focus on what
needs to be done here.
Now let's go.
I have to wonder, why would
our suspect do all of this?
Well the most
common reason would be...
What is it?
I can't believe we missed that.
Since the crimes are
so unusual of course,
they appear to be
totally random at first.
But the second attack...
Brutality like that
only makes sense
if the killer had a motive.
What now?
Don't they know I'm busy?
Can you check something for me?
I'm kinda in the middle
of checking a whole
lotta things right now.
It'll just take a second.
I'm only asking
you 'cause you're
the goddess of
information analysis.
Sweetie, when it comes to me,
flattery will get
you whatever you want.
What is it?
The victim, Hiroko Fujii.
She have any sort
of trouble in her past?
If she did, it wasn't anything
big enough to go on her record.
What about people she knew?
Anyone who hasn't
gone outside in a while?
You're looking
for a shut-in now?
Not a shut-in.
I'm looking for somebody
who knows he'd be sent
to therapy immediately
if he gets anywhere
near a street scanner.
Oh okay. I gotcha.
How about this guy?
Name's Jyunmei Itoh.
He's one of her
colleagues, or he was.
It seems he's been out
sick for about two weeks,
so he's been issued
a health care directive.
He lives in Tsurumaki.
That's not far from here.
He ain't home?
Bingo.
If this is the state of mind
this creep's been in lately
then it's no wonder he was
afraid to leave the apartment.
Crime Coefficient: Thirty-Two.
Target is a
registered Inspector.
We have to follow him!
Before we do that I need
to check something out.
Crime Coefficient: Thirty-Two.
Target is a
registered Inspector.
Warning: Any rebellious
conduct by an Enforcer...
Ah, so that's how they do it.
I figured out their
little magic trick.
Shion! Any uninhabited
blocks near me?
Why, what's this all about?
What's going on?
The suspect's able to copy the
Psycho-Pass of a nearby person.
The helmet itself is
doing a cymatic scan
of the people around him.
I see, so if we can
get him somewhere
with no people in
the scanning range
That helmet will
be useless. Hurry!
Let's see here.
There's a storage
building four blocks up.
It's fully automated
so nobody's inside.
We'll chase him to it.
Send any Drones in the area.
Yup, you got it.
You heard the plan right pops?
Go circle around
and cut him off!
Copy.
As for you, Inspector,
don't get too close to Itoh.
Otherwise, we'll have
the same problem as before.
Got it!
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
part of the
Public Safety Bureau.
We are currently...
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
part of the Public
Safety Bureau.
We are currently blocking
traffic due to an emergen
Keep it up, guys!
You're almost there!
We are currently
blocking traffic due
to an emergency situation.
Please take an alternate route.
Crime Coefficient:
two hundred eighty-two.
Target is a registered Enforcer.
Damn it!
Status, Enforce At Will Target.
Trigger safety now released.
Aw, gee, how kind of you.
All the way up to two hundred
eighty-two now, are you?
Yeah. The thought of killing
him may have crossed my mind.
How you like seeing someone
with your Psycho-Pass
getting shot down?
Hey, I'm just glad this thing
didn't turn into an Eliminator.
It looks as though you
were able to lose your tail.
Yeah, piece of cake.
When they can't use
their Dominators,
the MWPSB are harmless.
You wanna know something?
You aren't very smart.
I mean you gotta be
either stupid or crazy
to meet us here alone like this.
Now we know you
got goods and money.
And you know we're dangerous.
You shoulda' taken precautions.
This was merely a tool
to promote awareness.
To encourage those people
to live like human beings,
and to stop trudging
through their sad,
idle lives like livestock.
The masses have
been misled by Sibyl.
They've forgotten how to assess
the danger in front of them.
Well in that sense
they're like you.
You're every bit as naïve
as those pitiful sheep.
Oh, is that so?
Alas it really is
quite a terrible shame.