So that's it?
It's really that easy to adjust
the Ukanomitama virus?
Yes, the process itself
should be automated,
or close to it, as long as
the equipment still works.
I would guess that's why
they chose Ukanomitama,
because it is so easy to update.
A good virus, transformed
into a destructive disease.
We thought we'd built
the perfect iron wall
for our food supply.
In truth it was more like
a double-edged sword.
All right let's go.
And now we come to one
of my favorite stories
from the Book of Matthew.
Jesus told them another parable.
The kingdom of
heaven is like a man
who sowed good
seed in his field.
But while everyone was sleeping,
his enemy came and sowed
weeds among the wheat,
and went away.
The surest way to buy some time.
And yet, he didn't do that.
Security's still active.
I need another way in.
Well, well...
Damn it. This place is huge.
It has to be.
These machines centrally
manage the defense virus
and distribute it to
the entire Hokuriku area.
Hard to believe a
facility this big can be
fully-automated,
with no humans on site.
The bigger the prey,
the easier it is to hit
the target on their back.
Especially when you're working
with a poisoned needle
powerful enough to kill a whale.
These tactics are
just like Makishima.
It's probably from Kogami.
I'm guessing he saw us land.
He has to be somewhere nearby.
Tsunemori here.
Didn't think you'd
get here this fast.
Then you shouldn't be
underestimating the bureau.
You're not the only person
who can chase
Makishima into a corner.
He's already in the facility.
He must be using the
equipment Professor Kudama
left in the university's lab
to alter the Ukanomitama
virus as we speak.
And that's assuming
he's not already finished.
He won't pull this off.
We can't let him.
Then we've gotta be quick.
Before he distributes his
skewed version of the virus,
we've got to shut down
the entire facility.
You should be able
to cut off the power
to this place under the
authority of the MWPSB, right?
If we do that,
it won't just shut down
the factory's machines,
but the security system, too.
That's what you want, isn't it?
You're trying to use us
to lower the defenses,
so that you can get to Makishima
before we can and take him out.
Isn't that right Kogami?
We'll never let you do that.
That man wants to
bring down this society.
That means the MWPSB
has only one choice.
Cut off the power. Do it
and you save our country.
I'm gonna find a
way to save you also.
I will not make
Shinya Kogami a murderer.
Then we've got ourselves a race.
The security here.
Can't we have it
transferred to our control?
So that we can
shut down the plant
without leaving it undefended?
That process would
take some time.
Makishima could put us into
check-mate while we sit.
I'm afraid we have
no other option here.
We have to kill all the power
like Kogami wants us to.
Kunizuka?
I've disabled the
command to switch
to the secondary power supply.
All we have to do now is cut
off the main line and we're set.
There's something I'd like
to ask the both of you.
If you do encounter
Mr. Kogami somewhere in there.
And if his Crime
Coefficient is over 300
so it activates the Eliminator.
Will you promise to call me
in before you shoot him?
And what's the point
of you being there?
I've got a trump card
I can use against him.
Just trust me.
Let me handle this.
We're going after Makishima now.
This time you'll help me, right?
The Dominator will assist.
I'm glad to hear that.
Then lock this gun on
Paralyzer with the safety off.
You can do that
for me, can't you?
The Dominator determines
its enforcement mode based
on the measured
Crime Coefficients.
This is the basis for the system
that maintains the
current public safety.
It will not be
changed or violated.
Makishima threatens that public
safety on a massive scale.
To stop him and
protect ourselves,
we need suitable weapons.
If we can't use the Dominators,
we'll have no choice but to
depend on more primitive arms.
And that could be lethal.
Killing him would be worse than
paralyzing him, don't you think?
That would be a result of
your lack of resourcefulness.
It's a fact our resources
are limited in this case.
Our chances of
capturing Makishima alive
without someone getting
hurt aren't likely at all.
If you grant me an exception,
those chances get
a whole lot better.
Think of the end results,
and the justice you're
trying to enforce.
You're good at calculating
risk and reward, aren't you?
Beginning now, and ending when
Shogo Makishima is captured,
we will grant an exception on
the applicable terminal device.
Safety will remain unlocked.
Enforcement mode:
Non-Lethal Paralyzer.
Please exercise maximum
discretion when using weapon.
Do not allow other detectives
to become aware
of this exception.
I understand.
Something wrong, Missy?
Cause you haven't
been acting like yourself
ever since the
Chief called you in.
I know it's prob'ly
none of my business,
but some burdens can be
too heavy to carry alone.
Are you worried about me?
I am. You're reminding
me of Kogami.
I don't want to see the end
of another good
Inspector's career.
That's what happens
when you're in too deep.
Well if you're so concerned,
you want to check
my Crime Coefficient?
Hey, that's not what I-
No it's okay.
Go ahead and point
your Dominator at me.
I'll clear the record of it with
my authority as an Inspector.
Crime Coefficient: Twenty Four.
Target is a
registered Inspector.
See?
Right now I'm exactly
the kind of person
that the
Sibyl System wants here.
Guess so.
Please proceed Miss Kunizuka.
We're ready now.
Copy that.
I'm separating
the entire facility
from the main power grid.
Not bad at all for the police.
Yes.
Well we know one thing at least:
Makishima's bio-terrorism
plot has failed.
If he's the genius
everyone says he is,
won't he realize it's
over now and try to escape?
I'm not so sure.
It's true Makishima's put
a great deal of thought
into his plans and
executed them carefully,
but that doesn't
mean everything's
just a calculation to him.
You think he'll stick to his
plan even with the power out?
If he still thinks
there's a way.
Then he will try it.
Right now we're simply
preventing the emergency power
from kicking in
automatically, aren't we?
Yes.
Then it can still be
switched on manually
using the control board
inside this facility.
That would bring
the plant back online.
This isn't over yet.
That's in the
central control room.
Should we cast a net?
Hold on.
If he is thinking
rationally he'll try
to escape while he can.
We don't have
time for a side trip.
Okay then we should split up.
I'll check the control room.
Inspector Ginoza,
I want you to look
for him in the university's lab.
I'll go with
Inspector Tsunemori.
I can run a hard-patch into
the main security console.
And with Shion helping
from Headquarters.
We may at least
be able to control
the security cameras
so we can spot this guy.
And I guess that
makes us the lucky dogs
in charge of chasing him.
Come on, what are you
making that face for?
This is where we men get
to puff out our chests.
Damn it.
Did something happen at
the Ministry of Welfare?
Why do you ask,
am I acting differently?
Of everyone on this team.
I'd say you're
contributing the most.
Yet there's a cloud over
your head you can't shake.
I may want to give up, but
that won't resolve anything.
I just have to keep on moving.
No matter how small it is,
there's still hope.
And as long as I cling to that.
I can do my job and
see this to the end.
When you first joined
us as a new Inspector,
I admit, I had my doubts.
I thought you were
a naïve little girl
who couldn't possibly
handle this work.
You're right. I was so naïve.
No. You've proven my first
impression was completely wrong.
At this point there's
no doubt in my mind.
I know that I can put
my life in your hands.
You've earned that.
I think you're giving
me way too much credit.
Good. All clear.
Did we make it in time?
We're still assuming that
he'd be in this location.
You're right.
And it's strange
there's no one else here.
What?
He would've predicted
what Makishima
would do next a whole
lot better than me.
If this were the correct answer.
Mr. Kogami would've
made it here before us.
So why not?
I must be overlooking something.
You won't like it.
But I still need the answer.
That's my favorite
kind of question.
You did help him get away.
Isn't that right?
You're gonna keep up
your interrogation
at a time like this?
Your logic. Let Kogami
work outside the law.
Screw the system
if it gets the job done.
That's the crude,
selfish justice
of an old-fashioned
hunting dog like you.
Can you tell me
I'm wrong? Can you?
I know it's him.
He's the one you always rely on.
You don't expect
anything from me.
Like catching Makishima.
You never thought
I had a chance, did you?
Kogami's an Enforcer
and a latent criminal.
He and I have gone
down the same dark road.
But you're still
on a different path
and I'll do anything
to keep it that way.
So I did what I thought was best
from the bottom
of my heart, son.
You can make
justifications for anything.
Bad guys run and
detectives go after them.
That's the assumption we make.
Inspector?
But Makishima looks
at things differently.
He understands how
badly we want to catch him.
He knows how afraid we
are of letting him slip by.
And he knows how
desperate that makes us.
Ginoza and Masaoka!
Wait, please!
It's too dangerous!
I need you to stay here.
Someone has to be
sure that Makishima
doesn't access
the emergency power.
Don't let him get near it,
destroy the whole console if you
have to!
Inspector Ginoza!
Can you hear me?
Don't move!
Nobuchika!
Hold on.
Behind you!
You trying to blow yourself
up and take me with you?
You honestly believe I'd
do a stupid thing like that?
Don't let that
man go at any cost!
You're a detective!
Fulfill your duty!
That bastard.
You idiot!
Why did you let him go?
Why? What kind of
detective are you?
I'm no detective.
I don't deserve the title.
You are my son, after all.
Look at those eyes.
They look just the
same as mine used to.
Back when I was young.
Dad, no. Don't go like this!
Why? Why would you?
It's too late now!
So you finally ditched
that kangaroo justice,
and now you've got some
real bloodlust, haven't you?
In the end, you're everything
I always hoped you'd be.
Is that right?
That's funny 'cause I have
no hopes for you at all.
You can't feign indifference
after coming this far.
Spare me the arrogance.
You're nothing special to me.
You're just a bag of trash
the city overlooked,
and I'm here to finish the job.
I know you feel bitter
for being rejected
and left out of
society your entire life.
Beneath your bullshit you
just couldn't bear the solitude.
You're no different
than the little kid whining
because he isn't
part of the game.
You really say
some funny things.
My solitude? As if that's
only applicable to me?
Really, who isn't alone in
this society we've constructed?
The time when our connection
to others defined us is gone.
We've lost all sense of self.
In this world where
we're watched over
by the system and
live by its standards,
a community is no longer needed.
It's not even relevant.
We all live in our own little
cell, and the system tames us
by giving each of us
our personal serenity.