Beneath all of your bullshit you
just couldn't bear the solitude.
Really, who isn't alone in this
society we've constructed?
In this world where we're
watched over by the system
and live by its standards, a
community is no longer needed.
It's not even relevant.
We all live in our own little
cell, and the system tames us
by giving each of us
our personal serenity.
You're the same, aren't you?
Shinya Kogami?
No one accepted your justice.
Or understood your anger.
So you turned your back
on trust, and friendships.
You even abandoned
the only remaining place
that would tolerate you.
All so you could come this far.
Reach this moment where
you know you truly belong.
After all that? You try
to laugh at my solitude?
But I see you.
I value that trait.
He who doesn't fear solitude.
He who can turn
it into a weapon.
You never learn, do you,
Kogami? It's a shame.
Hold it right there.
Please, Kogami.
You need to drop the blade.
You realize that was
Makishima, right?
Yeah, I know.
I'll take care of him, also.
You gonna shoulder
all this yourself?
Handcuff me and go
after him on your own?
Surely you know I'm not
that reckless don't you?
This Dominator is
locked in Paralyzer mode,
with the safety unlocked.
So you should be
able to use it, too.
Let's do this together.
We're going to paralyze
Makishima and bring him in.
I'm not going to let
you do anything more.
Try and I'll blow out your leg.
I'm surprised.
I always thought this job
would make you tougher.
But I guess I figured
you'd still be nice about it.
You're trying not to kill
Makishima, no matter what. Why?
Because it's illegal,
and I can't overlook a crime.
Why are you going
so far to obey a law
that can neither
judge a criminal,
nor protect the
people from his wrath?
The law doesn't protect people.
People protect the law.
Humans have always
fought against evil,
and sought out a righteous
way of living as a group.
Those feelings the accumulation
of society's
feelings are the law.
They aren't just provisions,
or arbitrary rules.
They're the fragile
and irreplaceable ideals
we all carry in the deepest
recesses of our hearts.
Compared to the power
of anger and hatred,
they're something that
can easily be broken down.
People have prayed for a better
world since the dawn of time,
hoped for a better future,
sacrificed their own
freedoms for its sake.
In order for those
prayers to hold meaning,
we have to protect the law,
that promise of a better
world to the very end.
We can't just give up
on it because it's flawed.
If there ever comes a
time when everyone feels
the way you do,
the Sibyl System will disappear.
There won't be any latent
criminals, or Enforcers.
Because there won't
be any need for them.
But until then...
Akane!
I do wish you people
would stop insulting us
with your so-called efforts.
You're in our way.
Interesting.
That's fate.
No. Don't do it. Please.
This is between him and me now.
Kogami wait!
Everyone is alone.
Everyone's empty.
We don't really need
each other anymore.
With so much at our fingertips,
we can find a
spare for any talent.
Any item, any piece of
knowledge, any relationship
can be replaced with a
simple search and a click...
I'd become bored of
a world like that.
But for some reason.
Some feeling I can't explain.
The thought that someone
other than you might kill me.
That never even crossed my mind.
Tell me. What do
you think Kogami?
Once this is done will you
find a replacement for me?
I don't know.
I sure as hell hope not.
They must've realized
it the moment
they first laid eyes
on one another.
Realized that long
before they had ever met.
Destiny had planned
this encounter.
They were not two
ships passing in the night.
They weren't mysteries
that couldn't be explained.
They understood
each other better
than they understood themselves.
Their focus was solely
reserved for the other.
Kogami.
The outcome of the attempt
to capture Shogo Makishima
was quite regrettable.
So does that mean the
system is done with me now?
We have no choice but
to lower our evaluation
of your abilities, and
alter our expectations.
However, that does
not mean the value
of your existence
turns negative.
To the contrary, when it
comes to the macro-management
of the Sibyl System,
you remain an individual
of outstanding value.
Your role has simply changed.
And what's that mean?
You have a strong and
healthy Psycho-Pass,
combined with a clear mind
and superior judgment.
These qualities make
you as close to ideal
as can be expected
from an individual human.
You will serve as an example to
the citizens of the coming era.
Furthermore, you possess
an emotional antipathy
completely contrary
to your theoretical
assessment
of the Sibyl System.
This internal conflict has only
intensified after recent events,
making you an invaluable
subject for field research.
If we can establish a means
of winning you over to our side,
we will obtain crucial sample
data which will help us
take the governance of
society to the next phase.
What are you planning?
Due to current public
opinion, the true nature
of the Sibyl System must
be kept completely secret
from the masses.
While many safeguards are in
place to ensure that secrecy,
exposure of the truth remains
the most statistically
significant danger
to our stewardship.
In the short term,
this is a necessary risk.
But in the long term, this
strategy is not desirable.
To achieve maximum stability,
we should eventually
lift the curtain,
and make our true nature known,
thereby creating an environment
where every citizen enjoys
and accepts our governance with
full knowledge of what we are.
Only this can
solidify the health
and prosperity of
future human society.
But the individual human
mind is unpredictable.
To succeed at this transition,
further research is required.
Continuing to observe
and analyze your behavior
will provide us
with key insights
on how to build a
methodology for winning over
future citizens, and adapting
them to our system.
In short, we must
learn how to persuade.
You think you can control us?
As long as you don't
show any signs
of jeopardizing
our secret,
your life and your freedom
of action will be guaranteed.
We hope you will cooperate.
If you follow the root
instinct of self-preservation,
there is only one
choice you can make.
You're right. I don't
want to die in vain.
And I don't want to bring chaos
to a people that aren't ready.
Shutting down Sibyl now would
cause our society to collapse.
Knowing your mind, we believe
we can trust in your respect
for the law when you make
your future decisions.
Laws are a
man-made construction.
An agreement we all make
with each other in the
hope of a better life.
Enforcing laws
unworthy of protection
is a betrayal of that pact.
A shaming of that hope.
You shouldn't
underestimate humans.
We're always striving
for a better society
that meets our ideals.
And one day someone is
going to find that better way
and when they do.
They'll march into this
room and shut you down.
The Sibyl System has no future.
You're on borrowed--
no. Stolen time.
Your passion pleases us,
Akane Tsunemori.
Fight. Struggle. Only that
will help us to evolve.
Hey. It's been a while.
I came to see you today
because I decided what
I'm going to do next.
My Crime Coefficient is up
to a hundred and forty now.
They say there's no longer
a chance of recovery,
but as you know, it's not
in my nature to sit around
and mope in the
isolation facility.
So instead. I'm going
back to the PSB.
I know how much you wanted me
to take a different path.
And now that I've fallen
that dream is dead.
I'm guess I'm just a
bad son in every way.
But strangely enough,
I don't have any regrets.
Nothing's good about
living as a hound.
It's brutal work.
But it's necessary and some
poor fools have to do it.
That's us. Right, Dad?
All right.
Sorry for the trouble.
Not at all. It's part of my
job to chaperone Enforcers.
You taught me
that from the start.
At least my Dad got a grave,
I can't say the same
thing about Kagari.
Division Two's search.
They were told to stop right?
Yes.
I'm sure he was killed.
The top brass must know that.
But they want to sweep
any evidence they
have under the rug.
It's not the kind of thing
they'd want to go public.
And Mister Kogami.
I wonder where he is now.
When you take the collar off
a hunting dog as wild as he was.
Well then he's not much
different than a wolf.
And now that he's
out in the wilderness.
He may actually
enjoy his new life.
How could he? When he's
living as a fugitive.
I bet he's happier
running for his life
than living under lock
and key as an Enforcer.
He's a survivor. A cunning man.
Who never knew
when to call it quits.
No matter how bad the situation,
he'll always find a
way to pull through.
Wherever he is,
I think he'll be fine.
To be honest, Inspector, the one
I'm more worried about is you.
Are you serious?
Not everything's
changed, Mr. Ginoza.
You're still a worrier.
I'd rather not talk
about the old days.
Let's stick to the future.
A new Inspector's
being assigned?
That's right,
and she's a minor, too.
That's pretty unusual isn't it?
Well we're partially
responsible for her recruitment.
This is trivial and
none of my business,
but do you mind if I ask?
What?
Your glasses.
Did you wear them for show?
I never liked how
my face looked.
Especially my eyes.
But things I used to care about
don't seem to matter much now.
Division One has undergone
quite the sea change, hasn't it?
Shu. Masa. Shinya.
They're all gone.
It means old-fashioned guys
aren't suited for this job.
Adapt, or the changing
current pulls down.
Isn't calling them
old-fashioned kinda harsh?
I mean you could at
least call them romantics.
You really think that
would give them comfort?
Would anything?
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
part of the
Public Safety Bureau.
For your protection,
access to this block is
currently restricted.
Excuse me. Are you
Inspector Tsunemori?
I am.
You've got some awful luck
to get this assignment
your first night.
Inspector Mika Shomotsuki
reporting for duty.
Pleased to meet you sir.
I have just been assigned.
Yeah I'm sorry, but the CID's
short on man power tonight.
I don't have time to give
you the rookie treatment.
Yes, I understand, sir.
I'm looking forward to the work.
Good answer.
A paddy wagon?
The people you're about to
meet are humans, just like us.
But they'll handle crimes
with judgment criteria
different from yours.
Trust them,
but at the same time,
be careful, and
remember who they are.
Underestimate them and
you're bound to get hurt.
Those people are what
we call "Enforcers."
And they're all
subordinate to you.
Activating Dominator Portable
Psychological Diagnosis
and Suppression System.