Victim's Daisuke Shioyama.
Age twenty-seven.
He worked at
Hachioji Drone factory.
His co-workers found his
body at four AM this morning.
They say the drone he was
servicing dismembered him.
Could be just an accident?
That's what I thought at first.
Until I heard it was already
the third worker death
at the drone factory this year.
That's clearly not right.
The morning shift
found the body here,
in the Drone Behavior
Inspection room.
This area's the only
part of the production line
that uses human labor.
The factory has 50 debuggers on
the line, around the clock.
So those guys live here?
If the company's quota
is a thousand fully tested
drones a month, and they
want low-worker overhead,
keeping them on site in constant
shifts is the only option.
From what I understand,
by installing a sub-routine
in a drone before
it completes testing,
you can make it malfunction
in a way that looks
like an accident.
This sounds like.
A first-degree murder case.
Well, if there are
only fifty total workers,
it seems straightforward:
We just check each one
of their Crime Coefficients.
At this place, the
normal rules don't apply.
Inspector Ginoza.
Yeah, what?
I think I'm finally getting
the hang of how to work
with the Enforcers.
Are you talking about working
with the Enforcers as your
"friends and colleagues"?
Or do you mean working over them
as their "handler"
as an Inspector should.
Fools learns from
their experiences.
The wise learn from history.
I hope for all our sakes
you're not a fool, Akane.
Detectives, thank you
so much for coming.
Can you please show us
where you found him?
No problem, Inspector.
Follow me.
After the drones
come off the line,
we bring them here for test
runs and safety checks.
In this factory,
machines build machines,
but for the final checkout,
we believe humans can
and should play a decisive role
in the drone's qualification.
We can't deny that
it's dangerous work.
Have you observed
the pace of the work
having any kind of
strain on your debuggers?
From time to time.
It's very demanding and
doesn't allow much time
for relaxing like
in office jobs.
With no Internet, workers
don't have distractions,
but they also don't
have diversions.
So, this entire
facility is off-line?
That's correct, Miss.
There's not even an
old Ethernet cable here.
Plus, every structure
on the campus is built
as an anechoic chamber.
This means the walls
absorb reflections
of incoming and outgoing
sounds and EM waves.
We may be cut off
from the outside world,
but we're also a hundred
percent secure from hacking.
This place is creepy.
They're so isolated.
A clean up drone removed
the body during
the initial response.
Here's a recording of that.
He was alive as the attacking
drone ripped him
apart piece-by-piece.
Nasty.
Did Mr. Shioyama, have
any conflicts or problems
with other workers?
No, he got along with
everyone, and they with him.
And his Psycho-Pass was clean.
It had to have been an accident.
If three dismemberment
deaths are accidents
you should watch more
workplace safety videos.
Like I said, this
is not easy work.
The debuggers accept the risks.
I appreciate that
you have concerns
about this factory's
safety practices.
But please, relay
them at another time
to the appropriate
plant administrators.
Should we inspect the attacking
drone for any alterations?
I'm already having it
sent to headquarters.
Karanomori will be
analyzing it for us.
But early word is
not to expect much.
The Drone's memory
cells are destroyed.
For now, I need you
to go back to the car
and upload this recording to HQ
I have to ask Chief Goda
some more questions.
Will do, sir.
I think this file
should help complete
your investigation, Inspector.
The results of our
own periodic check-ups
as well as Hue
assessments conducted
by building scanners. Here.
Thank you, this helps.
Go over everything
with a magnifying glass;
you'll still find that no
worker's Psycho-Pass
ever routinely exceeded
his regulated value.
If you're still
suspecting murder,
I don't know which worker
would even be your suspect.
Well, we won't be
able to know for sure
until we run this data through
the Sibyl System for analysis.
Unfortunately,
that takes some time.
Unless, of course,
you're okay with us
using something unorthodox
on your workers.
And that would be?
Our Dominators.
If you'll let your workers
assemble outside
the anechoic buildings
we can use the devices
to check them, right now.
But that would mean we'd have
to suspend operations for hours!
Mister Goda, people's
lives are at stake here.
If you can find evidence that
Shio-yama's death is a murder,
we will cooperate fully
with this investigation.
We're not in business
to protect criminals.
But until then, we must assume
this was a tragic accident.
And need I remind
you, to interrupt this plant's
production would
require not only
that evidence but
also a signed order
from the Minister
of Economy himself.
Something I hear
does not come easy.
Ginoza may be a straight
arrow but I bet he really
turned the screws on
the shifty factory chief.
Guy's a pain in the ass.
Are they always like that?
Didn't you read the file
on this place, Akane?
This is a government factory
under the Ministry of Economy.
Ha, These kinda
places will do just
about anything to
protect their profit margins.
They don't want people like us
from the outside meddling and
causing a drop in productivity.
Even when some of their
own workers have died?
That's why they prefer to chalk
this up as another accident
and sweep it under the
rug as soon as possible.
Well, maybe an accident
is all that happened.
Their scanners never detected
anyone dangerous, right?
That's true, but then again.
Those automated
scanners aren't perfect.
In fact, the best
they can manage
is a quick Hue Check of
a person's stress levels.
If you really want
to use cymatic scan data
to check a potential suspect's
full mental state, job aptitude,
Crime Coefficient,
everything, you need to run
a dedicated analysis
through the Sibyl System.
Too bad there's always
a waiting list for it.
Unless our Dominators
find something.
Then, no matter
who's ahead of us,
we can jump to the front of the
line and receive an analysis.
With a Dominator and the
Sibyl System working together,
you can reveal a suspect's
entire mind in a second.
Most of the time.
Here, I'll show ya.
User authentication.
Inspector Akane Tsunemori.
Dominator usage approved.
Communication error.
System link cannot
be established.
To be hack-proof, these
buildings block all radio waves,
so as long as we're in here
we can't connect
to the Sibyl System.
The Dominators might
as well be scrap iron.
Nothing but fancy-lookin'
paperweights.
Still, what if the
death was, well, you know.
All just a terrible mistake? Ha!
I'm sorry; it's hard
not to laugh at that idea.
I'll say!
No offense, but if that
crime scene wasn't clear,
ya ain't much of a detective.
Just seeing pics would give
any Enforcer a gut feeling.
It was a murder, okay?
I wonder what the
perp's motive was?
Based on the thrashing
that poor victim took,
my intuition tells me
some kind of a grudge.
Food's good, but this is
such a sad place to work.
Imagine spending every minute
of your life totally off-line,
in this day and age!
But if it's as bad for
the workers as you say.
Why are their hues so stable?
Hey, don't underestimate
people's ability
to entertain themselves!
How's it going detectives?
Has your inspection turned
up any promising leads?
No, sir. Everything's
normal in your data.
Think fast, Yellow-Green!
You going to the crapper to
eat your lunch alone again!
Why are those guys
bullying him. It's mean.
Oh, that. He'll be fine.
Harmless teasing.
What?
Yeah it happens
all the time to him.
Since the guys here
aren't allowed any contact
with the outside world while
on shift, teasing someone
is the best way to let off steam
and get their minds
off things for a bit.
Yeah, but what
if that poor guy's...
If his Psycho-Pass
ever gets clouded
to the point that
it's a problem,
we'll just re-assign him to a
different part of the factory.
we take our workers' mental
states quite seriously.
He's not being bullied,
he's actually helping us.
For all we know, Sibyl
might have recommended
he work here because
he's naturally suited
to this kind of
whipping boy role.
And someone like you, who's
quick to laugh off abuse,
must be naturally suited
to a job like this.
Sibyl System always
gets it right.
You okay, buddy?
Yeah, thank you.
If the files the Chief
gave us are accurate.
There's only one employee here
who's Hue Check
slowly worsens over time.
And every time it changes,
that guy's transferred
to another part of
the factory to stabilize.
That said, it's been a year
since his last transfer.
Well, wait,
didn't Chief Goda say
that the first debugger's death
happened about a year ago?
And the same man for
the last year has been
the target of that
twisted bullying campaign.
The data we got leaves
no doubt about it.
I see a big board of
Psycho-Passes with clear colors,
and then one employee
who gets cloudy.
Mister Yuji Kanehara.
His Hue is yellow green.
So that's why they were
calling him "Yellow-Green."
I guess it's company policy
to put the Hue Checks out
in the open for
all employees to see.
That is a bad idea.
I'll say. But this guy's
most recent assessment
actually shows his
Hue improving a bit.
Yeah, the Hue looks like
it was at its most cloudy.
The day before Shioyama died.
Can't be. It doesn't
work like that.
The color of a person's
Psycho-Pass doesn't
just improve after
committing murder.
Don't forget, though, that
we're seeing this principle
at work when the other
debuggers relieve their stress
by beating up on Kanehara.
There's no mystery here guys.
Back before we
had cymatic scans,
desperate people getting pushed
past their breaking points
and then committing
crimes wasn't uncommon.
That's enough!
I'm tired of hearing
about your gut feelings!
You're just deluding yourself!
With that kinda
paranoia and aggression
it's no wonder you latent
criminals are society's garbage!
We can't go around
acting on hunches
from circumstantial evidence!
We maintain an orderly society
by using Sibyl to judge
Crime Coefficients.
If we change that, we'll
lose the public's trust!
You crow about order
and yet we're still here
investigating three dead people.
Gino, let me do it.
Let me investigate Kanehara.
If there's hard evidence,
I'll find it.
That's enough!
Sir, can we speak, please?
I agree with the Enforcers.
If going by the book means
ignoring certain possibilities,
I'd rather try Mr. Kogami's plan
Oh, come on.
You can't be serious!
Ginoza, why are you
acting so strange!
Did something happen
between you and Masaoka?
Uh, sorry.
I promise I'll do better
with the Enforcers, sir!
Well then,
if this is the path
you're determined to take,
I won't stop you.
You are still an
Inspector, after all.
If you think you can
control those hunting dogs,
you're certainly
entitled to try.
Thank you, sir?
You've chosen
the way of the fool.
So like a fool, you will have
to learn through experience.
Seems that's the only
way you'll understand.
Did something once happen
between Mister Ginoza
and Mister Masaoka?
Akane, tell me you did not
ask the Senior Inspector
that to his face!
Don't talk about that.ever.
What?
I count exactly two hundred
meters in communication cables.
Looks like the furthest
that'll reach is the elevator
hall on the second floor.
You sure you can lure
Kanehara up there?
No, but I'm certainly gonna try.
So...
The plan is just to
talk to him, right?
Yeah.
So this is where
you hide, Yellow-Green!
Do your meals taste better
after you kill someone?
Well? Hey! Answer me!
Shioyama, Asami, Koriyama.
Three dead this year.
You killed them, didn't you!
What? Why would you think that?
Lucky for you, as long
as you stay in here,
we can't prove
you're a murderer.
But Yuji.
Once I get a gut feeling...
Well, let's just
say we Enforcers
take pleasure in pushing
around other latent criminals.
First I'm gonna keep you trapped
in this hellhole of a factory.
so you have no where
to run to and hide.
Then my friends and I are
gonna put the word on the Net.
Yuji Kanehara is
a serial murderer
with a clouded Psycho-Pass.
Please. Don't.
Dammit.
I'm out of service
range in here. Oh, well.
Guess I'll have to
go out front for a bit.
You stay in this
bathroom on your knees,
trembling and crying
like a little baby.
And I'll get started
on bringing a three-time
murderer to justice.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Kogami, why'd you do that?
This is the quickest
way we got left
for seeing if Kanehara's
our murderer.
He doesn't have time to prepare
an elaborate method in advance.
I'm safe now.
So, if he's gonna kill me,
he'll have to do it the exact
same way he did Shioyama.
When he makes his move,
we'll have our proof.
This is crazy!
And if he's not
a murderous nut,
we'll walk out of this factory
without a scratch on us.
In that scenario,
everybody wins.
So inspector, which
ending would you bet on?
I don't...
This is all your fault!
Looks like we have
our answer. It worked.
Once I'm done
killing the two of you.
My Hue will become clean again!
Run!
Don't run.
You're just going
to make your deaths
that much messier
when I catch you!
No! God Dammit!
Why would you
gamble with our lives
just to prove a point to Ginoza!
It's not about proving a point,
it's about getting
justice for the dead.
Sometimes when you want
to uncover the truth,
you have to be prepared
to risk your life.
If we don't speed
up we won't make it!
You don't have to
tell me that, I know!
We're here.
I know. But right now
he's still in the act.
We gotta send a call for backup.
Suppression System, online.
Kogami!
Now you die!
User identification.
Enforcer Shinya Kogami.
Crime Coefficient at
Two Hundred Sixty-Five.
Suspect is target for
enforcement action.
Kogami, run!
Threat Judgment
of target is updating.
Enforcement Mode changed
to Destroy Decomposer.
Target is to be
completely eliminated.
Please be careful!
Here, too!
Kogami!
Man, those Dominators
kick serious ass
when they get fired up.
He said he didn't want
to be some hunting dog,
he wanted to be a detective.
But the look I saw in
his eyes that night.
Was more like that of
a wolf who had its prey
by the neck and couldn't
wait to taste blood.