I'm so sorry.
You seem to think those words
actually mean something,
so I'll explain
it to you like this.
If sorry was enough, we wouldn't
even need the police, would we?
After the complete outrage
your people managed to cause.
You still let Talisman get away.
Seriously. I don't
know what the hell
I was thinking cooperating
with the police.
But still.
There's not a single doubt
that Talisman is guilty
of a really serious crime.
Didn't you offer to help
us because you felt like
you couldn't just turn
a blind eye to that fact?
Who do you think I am?
I'm Spooky Boogie,
the notorious anarchist.
I slipped up once,
but under no circumstances
will I ever act as
your agent again.
But I...
Sounds like it might've put
a dent in your friendship.
Well. We were just in the same
graduating class together.
I actually don't
even know who she is.
You recorded that whole
conversation, right?
What? Yeah, of course.
Talisman Saloon's packed wall
to virtual wall
with guests as usual.
Yet another busy day for
the ghost of Kimihiko Hayama,
doling out advice
without a care in the world.
The guy knows the
CID is on to him.
And he's not bothering to hide.
He's even making
speeches about the raid.
It's time we figure out
just what his game is.
Is he trying to
convince the world
that Kimihiko
Hayama's still alive?
Seems like he'd at least
make a withdrawal or two
from Hayama's bank account if
he was trying to cover it up.
Do you think his only goal here
could be hijacking
Hayama's avatar?
There's gotta be easier
ways of going about that.
Unless he murdered him
just for the fun of it.
Hey. Don't try so hard
to understand the
criminal mind, Gino.
You'll wind up with us.
It's just too bad
you never bothered
to take your own advice, Kogami.
Hey, now.
Even if he's doing this
just for kicks, he's no fool.
He knew he was bound to
arouse suspicion eventually.
There's no way he could've
hacked the Holo-Cosplay
on the spur of the moment.
He was prepared for the chance
he was walking into a trap.
We've got no choice
but to teach him a lesson
if he thinks he can
outsmart us. Alright, Shion.
I want you to trace all of
Talisman's access routes.
He's bound to slip up
and lead us right to him.
You think it'll be that easy?
I mean the guy's obviously
pretty sure of his ability
to hide his tracks.
He wouldn't be popping
in and out of forums
if he wasn't confident
that he won't get caught.
So we should just sit
around and do nothing?
No, but I think that we
might have a better option
for getting a lead on him.
Not only that, I wanna
look into something else.
Well that's fine then.
Suit yourself.
But we're still putting a
trace on his access routes.
I just can't understand
this avatar stuff.
What's the point
of a virtual world?
I mean, what's wrong
with the real world?
Why can't these people just
go out and talk in person?
Spoken like a true technophobe.
You're part of an endangered
species, Mr. Masaoka.
Look at it this way.
Using the net is no
different than using a knife
for cooking or a
pen for writing.
It's just another helpful
tool for our lives.
It's not good or bad.
Simply enough, it's just there,
so we accept it and use it.
Well put. I like how
you explain things.
You'd make a good teacher.
You really think so?
Are you familiar with Rousseau?
Um. The philosopher?
That's right.
Specifically his work A
Discourse on Inequality.
Oh, hold on a sec.
I'll just look it up real fast.
There's no need for that.
I've got the whole thing
stored right up here.
For instance.
Suppose there are two
hunters in the woods.
Now they both
want the same thing,
so should they hunt
separately for rabbits.
Or should they work together
and go after bigger prey?
Which decision strikes
you as the better option.
Well the latter, of course.
That's basic game theory.
It's always best
to work together.
Precisely. Humans are
social creatures by nature.
Language, artwork,
currency, telephones.
Almost everything you can
think of is a communication tool
meant to strengthen
that social nature,
to help bring us together.
Now do you believe the
net fulfills that purpose?
That's the question.
Well I... Yeah, I think it does.
That's kind of intriguing.
I'd be happy to offer
you some assistance.
A PSB bureaucrat in
debt to little old me?
Could come in handy.
That's kind of intriguing.
I'd be happy to offer
you some assistance.
If sorry was enough, we wouldn't
even need the police, would we?
Seriously, I don't
know what the hell
I was thinking
cooperating with the police.
There it is.
You have something?
I don't know what the
hell I was thinking,
cooperating with the police.
Her choice of
words is different.
She says PSB at first,
but then she says the police.
Couldn't that be a coincidence?
Maybe, but let's run
a search through
as many of her
past logs as we can.
That's what I thought.
Going by this, you could count
all of the times Spooky Boogie
used the word
"police" on one finger.
You were speaking with a
different person this morning.
You were speaking
with the murderer.
That means he's now controlling
two avatars that we know of.
According to the tracking,
the Talisman avatar is
being operated from here.
This apartment.
Door breach.
Oh, shit!
It's always bound
to be terrible news
whenever I get a call from you.
Well, you might like this.
Looks like some hunting
dogs got caught in the trap.
That is good news.
I can get you as many
replacement proxy servers
as you need me to. As long as
you still plan on continuing.
Of course I
do. It's my duty, after all.
Well. You are
Mr. Makishima's favorite,
but a word to the wise.
Whatever you do, just make
sure you don't screw up.
How the hell are
you two not injured?
Geez, we'll make
sure to die next time.
Maybe you should learn
to duck a little faster.
What is it?
We've discovered
a second victim.
The user behind Spooky Boogie.
We searched through Inspector
Tsunemori's class records
and narrowed it down to people
who earned affiliate income.
Shoko Sugawara,
twenty years old.
The murder took
place in her home
in the exact same
manner as Hayama's.
We've found some of
her remains in the sewer
and yet her avatar is just
as lively as it ever was.
The estimated time of
death is before dawn.
They must've killed her shortly
after the raid last night.
Let's rendezvous at the office
and reassess our
plans with Shion.
If things keep up like this,
he'll have us right in
the palm of his hand.
Shit.
This is all my fault.
She got involved in
this because of me.
Don't talk like that.
But it's true, it's my fault.
She's dead because I...
Did you use Shoko as a decoy?
Was that your purpose
in accepting her help?
No.
Did you coerce her to cooperate?
Did you leak any of her
information to the suspect?
No.
Then what exactly is your fault?
Well yeah, but... she...
she got murdered.
Yeah, and if we had managed to
catch the suspect last night,
then Shoko Sugawara
wouldn't have had to die.
So we're all
responsible for that.
Let's stay focused on not making
the same mistake a second time.
Let's catch this guy.
Simply put: It's the
only thing we can do
to help the victims
rest in peace.
Looks like I've stumbled
across another phantom forum.
Rainy Blue, hosted
by Melancholia.
It's registered to
an 82 year old man,
but only because his
grandson begged the codger
to let him use his personal
info to create it.
But, the grandson
got into an accident
a little over half a year ago.
Yuichi Tokitou, 14 years old.
But of course, his avatar's
still kickin' around
the net just like
the kid had never died.
The grandfather
doesn't even know
how to sign in to
the social networks.
On top of that, he just
assumed the affiliate income
he was receiving was
part of his pension.
Rainy Blue is big, too.
It's a popular community.
Man, is anyone alive
on the internet?
Is it even possible
to simultaneously operate
multiple avatars like that?
It's not too uncommon for an
experienced, heavy user, right?
The most remarkable
aspect of this
is the suspect's
performance.
Three stolen avatars.
Nobody suspects
anything strange at all.
In fact, he's made
them more popular
than they were
in the first place.
Tens of thousands of users
and not one of them has
noticed that he's a fake.
It's 'cuz it doesn't
matter if he's fake or real.
These avatars are idols to them.
They're icons.
Icons don't become
icons of their own will.
They're like projections.
Neither Hayama nor
Sugawara established
their popular status
on their own.
Talisman and Spooky Boogie
are just as much a creation
of their fan's idolization, what
their fans wanted them to be.
The truth of the
person behind the icon
is rarely the same as the
truth of the icon itself.
It's not too surprising that
a fan could do a better job
than the actual user at
delivering what the fans expect.
They know what they want.
So you think this guy
was originally a fan?
Melancholia, Talisman,
and Spooky Boogie.
He knows each one of these
characters inside and out
and he can imitate
them perfectly.
This kind of behavior
is clearly driven
by the enthusiasm of a fan.
Great, how do we find him?
With all three of these avatars,
we've gotta be talking about
thousands upon thousands
of fans to sort through.
We can narrow things down.
We'll start with the
Talisman avatar first.
Bring up his top 100 fans.
All of his most
frequent visitors.
Draw up a graph of their
time spent there per day.
Isolate it to around the time
of Kimihiko Hayama's death.
Looks like it was more valleys
than peaks around that period.
The CommuField attendance
was pretty low then.
That's right around when
Talisman's reputation
was starting to sour.
But then, it makes an
almost full recovery
on this day two months ago.
And Hayama was
dead by that point.
Talisman had already
been hijacked.
But there were still
some regulars that stopped
coming to the
CommuField even though
his popularity was
back on the upswing.
It's these drop-off
rates that are the key.
Check the traffic stats
for Rainy Blue around
the time Tokito died.
the same with Spooky
Boogie's CommuField,
but check the day
before yesterday.
There should be one user
who shows the same pattern.
I see. We're pinpointing
the suspect's own avatar.
Yeah, exactly.
Once the suspect managed
to hijack the victim's avatars,
he no longer had
any reason to visit
their CommuFields
with his own avatar.
How's it look?
Any matching activity?
There's only one person
with those stats.
Masatake Mido, 27 years old.
Works at a virtual
sports management company.
He hasn't had a
Psycho-Pass Hue Check
since a routine scan
four years ago.
We don't even have a record
of a single street
scanner picking him up.
He must've plotted
out his daily routine
around specific routes that
avoided street scanners.
A pretty good sign that he's
got something to hide, huh?
Put a trace on his
recent access records.
One step ahead of you.
His last access was
just a few minutes ago.
From a flea-bag budget
hotel in Roppongi.
The Minato Ward.
And his home address
is in the same ward.
Inspector Tsunemori.
You've got the hotel room.
Take Kogami and
Masaoka with you.
Yes, sir.
I'll head over and check
out his home address
with Kagari and Kunizuka.
Let me remind you how
dangerous this guy is.
Not only can he crack code, he
can handle explosives.
Don't let your guard down.
Drinking on the job?
Heavy-duty booze is
the most effective tool
there is for handling
illegal holograms.
Yep. You'll find it useful
once you turn twenty-one.
MWPSB! Masatake Mido.
We demand to see your
Psycho-Pass at once!
Come out with your hands up!
What's going on here?
He's apparently got a talent
for cracking Interior
Holography as well!
Ko!
What do we do?
Crime Coefficient:
Three-Thirty-Five.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Must be on a
pain-inhibiting drug.
He's not gonna go
far with that wound.
We'll let Ginoza's
team box him in.
Welcome home, Mido!
We're glad you're back.
Welcome home.
Welcome home!
I made it. I'm okay
now that I'm home.
You're all eternal.
Freed from physicality.
Released from the
chains of your users.
And substantiated by
collective intelligence.
You're the embodiment of
Plato's theory of Forms.
No one could look down on you.
You stand above all life.
And I swear I won't let
anyone tarnish your nobility.
I swear.
I'll protect you no matter
what the cost might be.
Thank you, Mido.
Thank you, Mido!
Thank you very much, Mido.
There was a time
when each one of you
provided me with guidance.
But now, with the
three of you by my side.
I'll provide guidance.
I'll guide the entire world.
You're all eternal.
That's nice and all.
But don't you think you could've
tried a little harder, Mido?
Maybe done a better job?
How is this happening?
How are you...
There's something
that I'm searching for.
Something I'm
quite eager to know
and I did whatever it took
to succeed at this task.
I'm curious. Have you
read any Shuji Terayama?
What? T-Terayama?
You should check him out.
Read his play Saraba, Eiga Yo.
All of the characters are
agents for somebody else.
And all of the agents
communicate through avatars.
It's layers upon
layers upon layers.
Are you Makishima?
You have an impressive
knowledge of various avatars,
and imitate them perfectly.
You can become anyone,
which made me curious
about who you actually are.
Does such a chameleon
have a personality?
Once I asked, I had to know.
That's why I helped you.
Stop. Stop it! Give them back!
Stop speaking in their voices!
Sorry.
But we're approaching
the inevitable end.
No more ideas left
for you to borrow.
I'm afraid you'll
have to come up
with your own original way to
die, if you can even do that.
You bastard. Why're you...
You can portray any
character you desire,
just slip right
into their being.
But it turns out that you,
yourself, are nobody.
Your personality is a
complete and total blank.
It's empty. You don't even
have a face of your own.
And that's how you
were able to do it.
You simply slid any mask you
could find over that blank void.
Shut up! Stop it!
It's time to say
goodbye, Masatake Mido.
The hunting dogs
are at your door.
And they've come bearing death.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Trigger safety now released.
Aim carefully and
eliminate the target.
All clear.
He's the only one here, right?
It looks like it.
Well then who the hell
was he screaming at?
Gotta say. You did
quite well this time.
I can't really take any credit.
Mr. Kogami figured it all out.
It's incredible how he was able
to get inside Mido's head
and predict his actions.
That's just how Enforcers are.
They can do that
because they've got
the same psychological
profile as the criminals.
But he...
Mr. Kogami comforted
me after Shoko's death.
And he encouraged me.
I know he's classified
as a latent criminal,
but I have trouble believing
he has the same mind
as a maniac like Mido.
I just don't see it.
Fulfilling your
duties as an Inspector
is the only thing
you should think about.
Draw a hard line between
you and the Enforcers.
Is that an ironclad rule
for this job? Protocol?
No, but it's the rule I live by.
I used to have a partner
but I lost him due
to a mistake he made,
a mistake I couldn't
stop him from making
and I don't want to see
the same thing happen to you.
That's from the
Personnel Department.
Delete it when
you're done with it.
Shinya Kogami. Enforcer. Male.
28 years old. Former Inspector.
What?
While investigating the
previously unsolved
MWPSB Special Case One Zero Two,
Enforcer Kogami's Crime
Coefficient rapidly increased.
Despite repeated warnings,
he prioritized the
investigation over treatment.
His Crime Coefficient deviated
from the regulated value and
he was demoted to Enforcer.