♪ Trigger finger,
trigger finger ♪
♪ Destroy this façade
they have made ♪
♪ It's taken my place ♪
♪ Break it apart
and set me free ♪
Fuck Sibyl!
That looks painful. I thought
you took care of your nails.
Look! Isn't this cute?
This off-brand stuff works
just like the kind for
authorized rockers.
See? No difference.
Sit.
Here.
Yayoi!
Rise and shine, patients!
It's time to get up,
and start our day with a smile.
And for all our guests
who are latent criminals
Keep working to
purify your Hues!
A pure Hue shall set you free!
Rise and shine, patients!
It's time to get up
And start our day with a smile!
And for all our guests
who are latent criminals
Keep working to
purify your Hues!
A pure Hue shall set you free.
Rise and shine, patients.
It's time to get up and
start our day with a smile.
Me an Enforcer for the police?
The Sibyl System determined
that you would have a
high aptitude for it.
You're a latent criminal.
You won't get this chance again.
Does this mean
that my Psycho-Pass
is never getting back
to a normal Hue?
Utilize your talents
to the fullest,
and guarantee
yourself a stable life,
by taking the
Occupational Aptitude Test.
Help contribute to our
wonderful civilization.
Thanks to the O-A-T's
implementation,
any free civilian can
enjoy art, nature, and peace.
Loaning Service. Loaning Service
Hey, hold up.
Are you Miss Kunizuka?
The items you requested
to borrow and
purchase have arrived.
Please verify the contents.
Wait a second.
Yes?
It's too light.
Something I ordered
must be missing.
Where are my
Ernie Ball guitar strings?
That purchase was not approved.
Again?
How often do
I have to request them?
I'm sorry. Please submit
another request for them.
Come on!
I haven't been able to play
a guitar for over six months!
Look at my hands!
I'm already losing my calluses!
You expect me to play
with soft fingertips!
Your Hue has
changed to dark yellow.
Don't worry. Breathe it in.
Your Hue's been
pretty stable, lately.
Despite this setback, you should
still be able to leave soon.
And when you do,
you'll be playing
that guitar again that
you're always talking about.
It's a critical time
for you. Be patient.
I've leave some
supplements behind.
Loaning service.
You're wasting
your time asking me.
Actually, I'm here
for something else.
These are pictures of
street scanners vandalized
the last few months.
Each incident has
a different culprit,
and none of their
MOs are the same.
So naturally, we didn't
think they were connected
That is until we plotted
the culprits' movements
and noticed this:
They'd all come out of
Kitazawa in the Setagaya Ward.
Our theory. Some kind
of anti-establishment,
counter-cultural
insurgency's formed there.
We want to eliminate it.
So what.
We'd like you to help us.
A while back you were a musician
in Kitazawa, weren't you?
You played in the band, Amalgam.
Bet you know every
inch of that place.
What is it?
'Kay, I'll try.
Who is that?
Sasayama. He's
getting tired of waiting.
Hold on, where's Kogami?
Still talking to the girl.
Oh. And no smoking in the car.
Okay, okay. Why couldn't
you have stayed behind?
Sorry, I'm off the
clock the rest of the day.
So our candidate's a former
authorized punk rock guitarist?
Yep.
How does an authorized musician
end up becoming
a latent criminal?
Beats me.
I've heard of some cases where
authorized people's Hues change
Most of the time they're artists
who've become
consumed with their work.
Wow.
Things that arouse
strong feelings, like art,
can be a good thing
if they make you happy.
If not, they act
almost like a poison.
That's why going into the
arts requires authorization.
Work on a painting for too long
and the next thing you
know they've locked you up
and thrown away the key. Yikes.
So, you really think this
chick'll come work for us?
I heard she desperately
wants to return to society.
She does? Heh.
Guess she is crazy.
What makes you think
I'll be so good at this job?
I have to know why.
Are you saying I have
some hidden aptitude for it?
Yes. See, in this line of work,
you need a good nose.
The kind of nose
that sniffs out clues.
The Sibyl System's determined
that you have that nose.
Just what the police
are looking for.
This Sasayama
Hunh?
Is he the one who
was tired of waiting?
Yeah.
An Enforcer?
He is.
So you Inspectors do lead
them around like
they're pathetic dogs!
And you just want
another one on your leash
with a good nose,
don't you Inspector?
Well, I refuse.
I'm not doing anything
that'll ever cloud my Hue again,
Is it true, you want out
to play your music again?
That's none of your business.
Well I can tell you
miss your guitar.
You've put in purchase requests
for guitar strings
twenty-three times.
And you continue to
baby your fingernails.
Alright, that's enough! Get out!
And what if she doesn't
want to sign on?
Don't know.
But Kogami's good. Better chance
with him in there than me.
Is that your way
of finally admitting you're
a charmless bastard?
Shut up.
Yayoi!
What are you doing!
You can't hang with
unauthorized bands!
Your Hue will cloud up!
What?
I gotta go.
Sorry we didn't get to finish.
Here, you can have it.
Later.
Come with me, we're going home.
Hold on. I wanna
stay and listen.
An unauthorized
band's music is worthless,
you should know that by now!
The only thing worthless
is letting Sibyl decide
what kind of music to make,
if you want my opinion.
To be blunt, there's
no way to know of,
let alone check out,
every club in Kitazawa.
The area's full of
abandoned buildings
or just dumps with
absentee landlords.
It all leads to people pretty
much setting up stages
and venues wherever they want.
It's not uncommon to see a show,
and then a night later find the
place vanished without a trace.
So only those living
in the neighborhood
will know the specific dates
and venues of the really
underground events?
Yes.
But there are a few,
common venues
that everyone seems
to know and use.
And you can narrow
down this list further
by only looking at the ones
your vandals have visited
If this group exists,
this "anti-social" movement
of vandals and anarchists
Then it's likely they're using
either the Yellow Hood Club,
or the Two-Seven Club as
bases for their operations.
Two-Seven Club checking in!
Nothing suspicious here so far!
Everything's clear on my end!
This is Yellow Hood checking in!
There's nothing out of
the ordinary here, either.
Roger.
Except for these girls;
I gotta come here more often!
What is it?
Sounds like he's
having a good time.
He got used to
a new environment.
Stay put long enough and
you'll adapt to anything.
Your sub-conscious turns
the strangeness you see
into a "new normal" that your
emotions won't rebel against.
That goes for me, the Enforcers,
even Latent Criminals in
the Rehabilitation Facility.
What are you getting at?
Most don't come back
from the Rehabilitation Facility
with a normal state of mind.
Or I should say, no one does.
Some break down
from the confinement.
Some see their Hue get
so clouded they're executed.
But those are the extremes.
Most of the latent criminals
just become "accustomed."
To what?
To a life where things
are always being
taken away from them.
And then that emptiness ends
up swallowing them whole.
Of course, overcoming this
state of mind through will power
might be possible for
someone of your talents.
But there's a quicker,
easier way, too.
What is that?
A Dominator.
The Sibyl System only allows
Inspectors and Enforcers
to carry and use it.
It's the power
behind the takers.
"The power behind the takers."
If you wanna stop things
being taken from you
Then join the people
who do the taking.
The Dominator you hold
is what makes it possible.
Kunizuka. Your ID is
registered to that gun.
What? Why would you do that?
You never know what might
happen when you're on duty.
Always carry it.
I got eyes on possible perps.
They've been standing by the bar
a while, holding a brown bag.
I bet they're here
dropping something off.
Total amateurs. Piece-a-cake.
Don't be reckless.
That's Rina singing!
♪ Better learn to cast
my doubt away ♪
♪ The truth I could
not handle ♪
♪ My true self
being so fragile ♪
♪ But laughing doesn't
hide all of the pain ♪
Excuse me, fellas.
Yeah, what?
Mind if I take a look?
What the hell!
Bingo. You guys gotta
bomb in here Dontcha?
I'm an Enforcer.
Crime Coefficient:
over one hundred fifty.
It's the cops!
I told him not to
get reckless! Dammit!
Where's the fire extinguisher!
Emergency! Order all
drones to Club Two-Seven!
This is Ginoza. I'm an
Inspector with the MWPSB
I'm requesting a fire
department dispatch.
Listen up, folks: just
stay put. I have questions!
Kunizuka.
I'm positive that
was Rina's voice!
Don't move!
Or I slice her up!
Hostage Crime Coefficient:
Ninety-Eight.
Enforcement action not required.
The trigger is now locked.
Is she okay?
You guys gonna shoot
me or not? Come on!
You're nothing but a
fascist servant of Sibyl,
killing whoever
she tells you to!
Well, you are fired up.
He's using her to lock your gun.
Yeah, but she's
reading a ninety-eight.
That's practically
a latent criminal.
How bout we round up
and waste them both.
You can't go around
shooting everyone.
You're a nice guy, Ko.
Sure hope it doesn't end
up killing you one day.
What's going on in there!
Some guy threw a bomb!
It's chaos!
Do you know what happened
to Rina, from Prophecy?
The girl who was
just on stage singing?
She was up there right
when the explosion went off.
You're in our way!
You call this a
world where people
can enjoy nature and the arts ?
Sibyl won't even
let me play my music!
How lucky for you!
Ya won't waste your life!
Pursuing some stupid dream.
When you got no real talent!
Easy.
Shut up!
Rina!
Yayoi!
Are you okay?
Yeah, it went off
pretty far from the stage,
so I'm-- Hey wait what
are you doing back in town?
Did you get outta rehab?
It's kinda hard to explain.
I'm here with the MWPSB.
The cops?
Yo, Rina!
Thanks for waiting.
This is all we managed to save.
That's okay.
You tried. How many are left?
Are those...?
Rina, who is this chick?
No one. Go on ahead.
What's going on?
I said go. I'll catch up.
Yes, ma'am.
Rina. What is all this?
Drop your guns. Or she dies!
Crime Coefficient:
Three Hundred Fourteen.
You're gonna make a mess.
As you can probably tell,
we are attacking Sibyl.
We're rebelling.
If you do that, you become
worse than a latent criminal.
If you're captured,
they'll execute you.
Well then, you're a different
person than I thought you were.
Yayoi
You should join with us.
Rina, I can't do it.
Why not?
Because you're
an Authorized Artist?
No that's not it.
But you've seen how
messed up this world is.
You can't deny it.
They call this a democracy,
but the people
who win our elections
are nothing but
impotent figureheads.
This isn't a free country,
Yayoi, it's a farce!
The people who rule over
us are all chosen by Sibyl!
Every day people become slaves,
giving their lives to a program.
And they're all too
brainwashed to even notice.
But our music!
With that, we have power!
We can change people's
hearts and minds!
We'll turn the slaves of
Sibyl into free men and women!
And when enough people hear our
music the world will be reborn!
That's wrong.
It's not what I wanted.
Yayoi
The whole time I was away,
the only thing
that kept me going
was dreaming about
playing music again.
Just rocking out and being
on stage right next to you!
You should have dreamed bigger!
When you left I finally realized
how empty my life had become.
How little power I had.
Your way won't change
anything. Do you hear me?
It's totally pointless
without power!
It's pointless?
That's right!
We need a powerful movement
behind our music, Yayoi!
Rina. We used to have
such a good thing going.
But then it all
had to change, huh?
Is that...?
A Dominator. It's Sibyl's eyes.
You're really choosing
to side with them?
Don't do this, Rina.
Come with me It's not
too late, there's still time.
If you stay on this
path to a rebellion,
all you're doing is helping
sign your own death certificate.
Please, Rina, come with me.
Undergo a rehab program.
Or you shoot me? Is that it?
Yeah, if that's the only option
I have left for stopping you.
You don't have it in you.
No, Rina! Stop! I'll do it!
I'll shoot you, I swear!
Invalid user, Gun deactivated.
What the hell? Come on!
Shoot, damn it!
Rina, come back!
Wait.
Hey!
Alright. Well,
I'm glad it worked out.
You know, I almost
had a heart attack.
I can't believe
you gave a Dominator
to a latent criminal who's
not an official Enforcer!
That's gotta be a first.
Hey. Are you still there?
Sorry about that.
I thought it'd be a
necessary experience for her.
But the fact she was willing
to shoot means
Sibyl made the right call.
I gotta run. Later.
I'll do it.
I'll become an Enforcer.
What?
I'm in. I choose your side.