Shit!
You fought rather well
considering your wounds.
They must've
realized it the moment
they first laid
eyes on one another.
Realized that long
before they had ever met.
Destiny had planned
this encounter.
They were not two ships
passing in the night.
They understood each other
better than they
understood themselves.
Their focus was solely
reserved for the other.
You are... Shinya Kogami.
And you are Shogo Makishima.
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
of the Public Safety Bureau.
For your protection,
access to this block
is currently restricted.
Neighborhood
residents are required
to immediately
evacuate this area.
This message will now repeat.
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department,
of the Public Safety Bureau.
For your protection,
access to this block
is currently restricted.
Excuse me, sorry.
Excuse me. Do you know where
I can find Inspector Ginoza?
Right here. Well,
you've got some awful luck
to get this assignment
your first night on the job.
Inspector Akane Tsunemori
reporting for duty, sir.
Pleased to meet you, sir.
This is my first day.
I know.
I'm sorry, but the CID's
short on manpower tonight.
I don't have time to give
you the rookie treatment.
Our target's name
is Nobuo Okura.
A street scanner flagged
him during a Hue Check.
He was ordered
by a Security Drone
to receive therapy
but he panicked and ran.
His recorded Psycho-Pass
was forest green.
So we can expect his aggression
and compulsion to be high.
Why would somebody
choose to let their Hue
get so cloudy over
receiving treatment?
There's a strong chance he's
using incompatible narcotics.
Regardless, he's far enough gone
that we don't need to
wait for Sibyl's judgment.
Of course he had to pick an
abolition block to hide out in.
So that's the challenge.
The block's not wired
with a relay device
so we can't send
in any drones in.
On top of that.
We've got multiple
eyewitness accounts stating
that Okura took someone
captive while fleeing.
He's got a hostage?
According to the
witness reports,
it looked to be a woman
in her early twenties.
We still haven't
confirmed her identity yet.
The block's been
fully evacuated?
The city records
list it as uninhabited.
but it's become a
den for the homeless.
So be prepared.
A paddy wagon?
The guys you're about to meet,
don't think of them
as human beings.
Their Psycho-Pass
Crime Coefficients
are above regulation value.
They're all deeply disturbed.
They would normally
be completely isolated
as latent criminals.
But we allow them
into the outside world
for a single purpose.
To flush out and hunt down
criminals just like themselves.
They're nothing more
than hunting dogs.
The best way to track
a beast is with a beast.
We call them enforcers.
Each one of them
is your subordinate.
You said we were
gettin' a rookie,
but you didn't say
she would be so cute!
This is Inspector
Akane Tsunemori.
From today on, you'll know
her as your second owner.
Uh. It's a pleasure to meet you!
I'm assuming you've
already been briefed
on the target's data, right?
He's backed
himself into a corner
and we're gonna
tighten the noose.
We'll split into
two groups and zero in.
Alright, Kunizuka and Kagari.
You two are with me.
The other two are with
Inspector Tsunemori.
Roger that, sir.
Why do they get the babe and
I get stuck with your ugly mug?
Man, that guy has
no sense of humor.
'Cuz he knows you
weren't joking.
Have fun out there.
So, uh. What should I do now?
You could order us
to take a coffee break
and sit on our asses.
I don't think we'd
argue with that.
Why don't you try
earning your paycheck.
How's that sound?
No reason for ya to look
so nervous, little lady.
You've used a Dominator
before, haven't you?
Well I've received
basic training,
Then you know that
it's a gun that reads
the Psycho-Pass of the
target you're aiming at.
The safety is only released
when it registers the
target as a latent criminal.
All you've gotta do is follow
the Dominator's commands.
If it says shoot, then shoot.
That simple, huh?
The basic mode
is set to paralyzer.
As the name implies, it'll only
temporarily paralyze the target
so we can take
them into custody.
Go on. It's nothin'
to be scared of.
Activating Dominator Portable
Psychological Diagnosis
and Suppression System.
Now online. User authentication.
Inspector Akane Tsunemori,
Public Safety Bureau,
Criminal Investigation
Department.
Dominator usage approved.
You are a valid user.
You'll get used to that.
It's a directional voice.
Only you can hear it
since you're holding it.
Before long it'll blend right
in with your own thoughts.
What about briefing?
Shouldn't we have a meeting,
come up with some kind
of plan on how we're
gonna catch this guy?
The two of us'll hunt the prey
and you'll observe
our every move.
That's all there is to it.
I was thinking something
a little more strategic.
All he's saying
is leave it to us.
We may not look it,
but I promise you,
we know what we're doing.
Our methods work just fine.
But since you're the inspector.
You're responsible for us.
You decide that you don't
like the way I'm doing things.
Shoot me with your Dominator.
What?
We're latent criminals too,
no different than the target
so paralyze us if you have to.
I guess it might help
to know our names.
That stubborn bastard
is Shinya Kogami.
And this old bastard
is Tomomi Masaoka.
I'm lookin' forward
to workin' with ya.
I'm sure you'll do fine.
Oh. Thank you.
Well then. Should we head out?
Until today.
I've lived a more earnest
and honest life than anyone.
I've spent my whole
life walking on eggshells.
The perfect upright
nobody they want us to be,
not bothering anyone
and keeping to myself.
Then one time.
One time a street
scanner red-flags me
and just like that, they start
treating me like a criminal.
It's over for me.
There's no coming
back from this.
Basic employment, marriage,
it's all impossible now.
Well fine then.
I've restrained myself all this
time, but what's the point?
I might as well be
what they say I am.
I might as well just
kill anyone I feel like!
Pl-Please don't.
I'll let you in on one thing
I've always wanted to do.
I've always wanted to have sex
with a beautiful woman like you.
And not just a virtual one.
But a flesh and blood woman
I can feel screaming.
What about Kogami?
I didn't see which way he-
Crime Coefficient: under sixty.
Enforcement action not required.
The trigger is now locked.
Crime Coefficient:
over one hundred twenty.
Target is a registered Enforcer
status: Enforce at Will.
Trigger safety now released.
He doesn't act like one, but
he really is a latent criminal.
He seems just
like a normal person.
I've heard some rumors
floating around about you.
Is it true you were top of
the class in your training?
Yeah, I guess so.
Here's a piece
of friendly advice.
Wipe each and every
thing you learned there out
of your head as
quickly as you can.
None of that crap's gonna
help you on a real case.
Ya probably think that
sounds unreasonable, huh?
Well lemme tell ya.
All the time
I've spent on this job,
I have yet to encounter
a single reasonable thing.
Everything a person
thinks and wishes for,
we live in a time when a
man's own mind is wide open
to anyone with
the right machine.
Despite this universally
known fact, there's still plenty
of people wanting to
deceive or hurt other humans.
Now does that sound
reasonable to you?
All of the theories and
logic they filled your head
with don't mean squat
out here in the field.
I doubt it'll take you too long
to realize just how
pointless your training was.
So be prepared to be unprepared.
Do you think...
Come in, this is Hound 4.
I've found the target on the
fourth floor of the KT building,
what are your orders?
Okay. Hold your position
and keep an eye on him.
Hound 2 and I will box him in.
Sure. Although.
Considering how
worked up he is right now.
I don't know if the hostage
is gonna make it that long.
You sure you don't want me
to go ahead and capture him?
Fine. Don't mess it up.
Of course not.
Crime Coefficient:
over one hundred ninety.
Enforcement action required.
Trigger safety now released.
Well, now, you are a degenerate.
Kagari, what the
hell are you doing?
The Paralyzer didn't work!
He's gotta be hopped up
on stimulants or something!
The target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Shit!
Ah, great.
Is... Is this...
It's an Oracle
from the Sibyl System.
New judgment on Okura.
Seems he's overextended
his welcome in this world.
Elimination?
Just because he got flagged
by a routine street scan?
He probably drove himself into
a corner and it just got worse.
Nothing'll work on him anymore.
Not even therapy.
The judgment states
he's way outside
the realm of rehabilitation.
It's a damned shame
your first case
has turned out to
be such a nasty one.
Damn look at my Psycho-Pass.
I didn't even know it
could get this cloudy.
It looks like somebody
covered it in mud.
Hey. Take a gander
at your Psycho-Pass.
It almost looks
exactly like mine.
I guess you and
I are just alike now.
It'll be just as bad
for you if they catch us.
They'll lock you up
as a latent criminal
and torture you for
the rest of your life!
We better wrap this thing up
before the hostage passes
the point of no return.
You don't mean
Psycho-Hazard, do you?
I do.
It's a sad fact Crime
Coefficients can be contagious.
Young people these days are
rarely exposed to severe stress
so they're likely to break down
when confronted
with violent actions.
Yeah, I actually wrote a
thesis paper on the subject.
Well let me be the
first to tell you.
It could happen
to any one of us.
Enforcers for example.
You wanna know the reason we
became Enforcers in the fi-
Freeze!
Stay back!
Drop your guns or she dies!
Step back!
Die!
Why?
You have my deepest sympathies.
This is Hound 3.
Enforcement complete.
Using an old man and
a rookie as a decoy.
You've got a pair of cold,
stainless steel balls,
don't you, Ko?
Whatever it takes to
earn the paycheck, pops.
It's okay, we're with
the Public Safety Bureau.
I promise, you're safe now.
Just calm down.
Ma'am we're here to
rescue you, that's all!
No. You can't do this to me.
Please don't.
Mr. Masaoka?
Listen to me now.
You need to check
her stats on your gun.
Crime Coefficient:
over one sixty.
Enforcement action required.
Well. Nothin' we
can do about it.
Leave her alone!
What're you doing?
We're supposed to
be protecting her!
What the hell do you
think the Paralyzer is for?
We'll knock her out and
take her in to get help!
She's just frightened
and confused,
you don't have to use
the Dominator on her!
You know the Dominators are
connected straight to Sibyl.
The city's system
itself has determined
this woman is a
threat to society!
Think about what that means!
And you're just perfectly fine
with shooting an innocent woman?
I refuse to accept that's right!
Stay back. Leave me alone.
Don't come any closer.
Get away from me!
Kogami, wait!
Please, you can't do this.
Please stop.
She's the victim here
and we can't.
The target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Trigger safety released.
Aim carefully and
eliminate the target.
Please stop.
I said stoooooppppp!
That's enough now.
You've gotta put
the lighter down.
Cause if you don't.
Then I can't stop this
gun from killing you.
Please, I only wanna help you.
Throw the lighter down
and everything will be fine.
The target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Non-lethal Paralyzer.
Trigger safety released. Aim
calmly and subdue the target.
Inspector Tsunemori.
I want a thorough
explanation of your actions.
I expect a detailed report
first thing in the morning.
Good grief. Where the hell
do they find these rookies?
Talk about a piece of work.