[phone chimes]
[TOKAKU gasps]
[KAIBA] It's seriously
starting to get exhausting
dealing with such a child.
[KAIBA] Like hell there's
one correct answer
to such an ambiguous question.
The only right answer
would have to come from
the mouth of another.
An answer that you
would clearly never
come up with on your own.
Tokaku, have you
finally opened up
and let someone into your life?
[KAIBA] It's about time
you woke up, girl.
You can't sleep forever.
How much longer can it possibly
take for you to realize
that everything
I tell you is a lie?
[STUDENT 2A]
Oh, check this.
There's apparently some
mysterious Class Black now.
[STUDENT 2B]
Oh, yeah, I heard about that.
It's like a group of
super rich genius students
who transferred in.
[STUDENT 2C] Really? I heard
it was a secret class
full of nothing but
famous pop stars.
[STUDENT 2B, 2A]
Seriously?
Well good morning, everybody!
Let's get the day going.
We've got a few new friends
to introduce that just arrived.
Number 5. Shiena Kenmochi.
I'm happy to be here.
Hey there, I'm Student
Number 8, Otoya Takechi.
This is gonna be so much fun.
Suzu Shuto. I'm Number 7.
And I'm a big fan
of physical activity.
I'm Kouko Kaminaga.
My student number is 3.
As of today I'll be
the new class rep.
[HARU giggles]
[OTOYA]
Rep? Rep of what?
Well everything. Naturally.
For example, I'll represent
all of Class Black.
Would any of you care
to dispute the title?
Nope. You can go ahead
and take dorm rep too.
[MIZOROGI] Alright, excellent!
We're off to a good start!
Now let's keep getting along!
[INSTRUCTOR 2A] When rolling
a regular hexahedron die,
which is called a trial,
the possible event resulting
from that roll is one of
six values, one through six.
Giving us a total
of six outcomes.
Looking at the
ratio of how often
each of these events occurs...
[TOKAKU] Look at all of us,
acting like normal students.
Pshht. What a farce.
[INSTRUCTOR 2A]
What probability of outcome
is there that resulting
event is rolling...
[ringing]
[HARU giggles]
[NIO giggles]
[TOKAKU] Is everyone gonna
pretend to be friendly?
Knowing what we really are?
It's creeping me out.
[NIO gasps]
I was just admiring
your super cute hankie.
Oh, that's from me.
I noticed that you
didn't have one, so,
I slipped it in your
pocket last night.
[NIO]
Wow, you're so thoughtful.
[HARU laughs]
[HARU]
Wait, Miss Tokaku!
Here. You forgot this!
[PRINCIPAL]
All the arrangements
have been formally
taken care of.
[SUMIREKO] I appreciate it.
It sounds like everything's
in order for me to
attend Class Black.
[PRINCIPAL] You're the last
arrival, Mistress Hanabusa.
[SUMIREKO laughs]
Please.
There's honestly no reason for
you to refer to me as Mistress.
From here on out.
I'm just another
normal student of Myojo.
[NIO]
Students of Year 10 Class Black.
This is a formal announcement.
Now that we've
all finally arrived,
please join me at
midnight tonight.
We will convene for a secret
orientation in room 1908,
located in the tower.
If you would like to know
more about your mission,
I suggest you participate.
Oh, c'mon.
Please don't tell me you're
going to be our primary handler.
[NIO]
I'm an actual student here.
Who'd you expect?
Well that narrows down
our target, right?
[TOKAKU sighs]
[TOKAKU] Why don't I just
blow up the entire school
and get this over with?
It's not like I give a
damn about the reward.
And I could care even less
about Kaiba's assessment.
Hm?
[HARU]
Oh. Hey, Miss Tokaku.
So I found this spot
yesterday while wandering
around campus and made
a note to remember it
'cuz it had such a lovely view.
You're welcome to
have one of these.
Nio recommended them to me.
They're mini melon buns,
a Myojo specialty.
[TOKAKU]
I'm not hungry.
Our class sure did fill
up quickly, didn't it?
I hope I got enough of these
to pass out to everyone.
Yummy.
Could it be true?
Is she the one?
Huh?
[TOKAKU grunts]
I have to keep smiling.
Don't let them down.
[HARUKI] Are ya sure
ya don't wanna wait
for the orientation thingy
tonight, Mistress Isuke?
[ISUKE] I'd rather take care
of this and get home ASAP.
[HARUKI] Nothing good ever comes
out of being impatient, y'know.
[ISUKE]
And how many times you think
the early bird heard that one?
I'll be heading out
to get that worm now.
[TOKAKU]
Inukai?
[HARU] Yeah. She said she's
got some exotic tea blend.
Why don't you join us
if you're not too busy.
Is she coming over
here to our room?
Yeah, I'm sorry for not
checking with you first.
But you weren't here
so I kinda said yes.
I'll just go out for a while.
Okay, but it'd be really nice
if we could all be friends.
She's not my friend
and this is your room.
You can do whatever you want.
That's not true. This room
belongs to both of us.
It's just as much yours as mine.
[ISUKE gasps]
[HARU]
Hello, Isuke!
Oh, Miss Azuma.
Aren't you staying?
You've got a rancid stench.
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku!
[ISUKE]
Ooh. Think she's jealous?
[TOKAKU panting, grunting]
So, um. Why'd your parents
decide to name you Isuke?
Not to pry, but it is
a guy's name, right?
It's a boring story.
Your tea's getting cold.
Oh, sorry about that.
It has a nice fragrance.
Something wrong?
No, it's delicious.
[ISUKE]
So you asked about my name.
It's a variant of my mom's.
It's a pretty cool one,
don't you think?
[HARU] It is! But now I'm
stuck trying to figure out
what your mom's name
might be, like, Isuko?
[ISUKE]
It's Eisuke.
Huh?
Now you're wondering why
she's got a man's name.
Well that's because
my mom is a man.
And my dad's a
man too, of course.
Oh. Huh.
Full disclosure here,
I don't actually share a single
drop of blood with
either of my parents.
And if I don't need any of their
blood to be related to them,
then I don't need to spill any
of yours in order to kill you.
[HARUKI]
[HARUKI] I heard your
room was supposed to be
having a little tea party.
[TOKAKU]
Wasn't my idea.
[HARUKI] So you just left Haru
and Isuke all by themselves?
I wonder if Class Black's
gonna be ending early then.
What does that mean?
[HARUKI]
What, didn't Nio tell you?
Starting tonight,
Class Black's being activated.
Isuke is impatient.
She's convinced your
roomie must be the target.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARUKI]
Uh, bye.
[NIO]
Well, you're more of a schemer
than I gave you credit for.
The last thing you want is
Isuke beating you to the punch,
but you also know it wouldn't
be wise to have bad blood
between you and you roommate.
It might be too
late for all I know.
[NIO] Oh, don't go
doubting your plan now.
Haru Ichinose.
She's got quite the body
count under her belt.
All of her siblings, plus her
very own mother and father...
She went after her own
family? I doubt that.
[NIO] But she so did!
Took 'em out in cold blood.
She's a nasty piece of work.
Hey, wait, you've got a lot
of brothers and sisters
too, don't you?
[NIO yells]
[HARUKI] Leave my family
out of this, dammit.
[NIO]
Sure, roger that!
[ISUKE] Now, I just soak her
in the tub. And that's that.
You can try, but Haru won't die.
Huh?
[HARU]
Haru has an incantation on her.
A spell. It prevents
her from ever dying.
[ISUKE] Hm. Must be
talking in her sleep.
[KAIBA] C'mon, Tokaku.
How much longer can you sleep?
That beast clawing away inside
you can't hibernate forever.
Your keen sense
of smell comes from
that feral nature after all.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE] Just barge
right in, why don't you?
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE] I know, I couldn't
believe it either!
The scars on this
girl are incredible.
It's really kinda hot.
[TOKAKU] She didn't want
anyone to see those scars.
Oh don't tell me you're upset.
Once the target's revealed,
its first come, first served!
[TOKAKU]
She's just unconscious.
I should've guessed.
She's not as normal
as she seems.
[inaudible]
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE]
You're not stealing my kill!
[TOKAKU grunts]
[ISUKE] Why the hell
are you protecting her?
[ISUKE gasps]
You bitch!
[ISUKE grunts]
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Tokaku!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE gasps]
[ISUKE grunts]
Holy crap, you're a virgin.
[TOKAKU groans]
You haven't killed
a single person yet.
Have you, virgin?
[ISUKE laughs]
[TOKAKU panting]
Wow...
You sure you're an Azuma?
If that is true, then it
makes this even funnier.
[ISUKE] I'll do you a solid
and keep it quiet.
I'm happy to hold
onto this ammo.
No...
Wait...
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Hurry, Tokaku!
This way! There's no time!
If you ever think of
killing someone again,
just remember this shrine.
[YOUNG TOKAKU]
What'll that do?
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
You won't be able to kill.
Because inside that shrine...
[inaudible]
...will be watching you.
[TOKAKU] It's a curse.
It's still with me.
Ow!
Why were you leaning over me?
What do you think you're doing?
[HARU]
Jeez, I'm sorry.
You were just
sweating really badly.
I just head-butted you
and you hardly even blinked!
And I don't understand
how you can be conscious
after being drugged!
Where did you get
all those scars?
I wanna know who
the hell you are!
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku.
You're not the only one
with questions, you know?
For example.
Why didn't you just
let her kill me?
[TOKAKU gasps]
I've got a strong
resistance to chemicals,
so drugs don't work on me.
I was actually awake
most of the time there.
The students in our class,
they transferred here
to assassinate me, didn't they?
[TOKAKU]
Wait, you knew about that?
[HARU] So why'd you
really come to my rescue?
Was it a whim or a strategy?
Or maybe...
some other reason...
I promise you, I won't die.
No matter what happens.
Believe me.
They won't succeed
and I'm gonna graduate.
There's no way.
You're just too ordinary.
Not exactly.
You see, my family...
They were all a part
of a very large
and very powerful organization.
And there are a lot
of people out there
that want me dead just
for being related to them.
And my entire immediate family.
All of them died, for me.
My father... My mother...
Both of my brothers.
My grandpa...
Everyone.
So I can't say my life just
belongs to me anymore.
They sacrificed
themselves to protect me.
And the worst part is.
My mom...
I didn't even get the chance
to say goodbye to her.
Mother.
[HARU]
But she's always with me.
She's right here, telling me
what's right and what's wrong.
[TOKAKU]
It's a curse.
[HARU] Everyone in
my family always said
they loved to see me smiling.
So you'll never see me cry.
[TOKAKU]
It's a damn curse.
Basically, I feel like I was
put on this earth to smile.
[TOKAKU]
We're stuck.
Living beneath the suffocating
demands of the dead.
[YOUNG HARU sobbing]
[HARU]
So this is my final test.
And I will pass, just watch.
I am going to
survive Class Black.
[TOKAKU]
Impossible.
[HARU] And then I'll
make them proud of me.
I'll make sure they know none
of their deaths were in vain.
[TOKAKU]
Impossible!
You're up against
12 trained killers.
How can you survive?
[HARU] There have been a lot
more than 12 people
that died to keep me alive!
[TOKAKU] You do realize that I'm
after your life as well, right?
[HARU]
Yes, I'm aware of that.
[TOKAKU]
Aren't you afraid?
Why don't you run?
I mean, why stay?
The way I see it.
After what I've been through,
I know I wasn't born to die.
I was born to live
no matter what.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU] You're covered in
scars, and you know everyone
is out to kill you, so how
can you look at the world
with eyes like that?
Okay, I answered you.
It's your turn to answer me.
[HARU] Why did you risk your
life in order to protect mine?
[TOKAKU]
Uh...
Well I guess...
I guess I saved you because...
[knocking]
For you.
[NIO]
Welcome, esteemed assassins,
to the prestigious
Myojo Private School.
As you know, I'm Nio Hashiri,
the arbitrator of Class Black.
We're now set to
start orientation.
But before we do...
[SUMIREKO]
Hello, I'm student number 11.
Sumireko Hanabusa.
I have somewhat of
a frail constitution,
so I'm only comfortable
in my own furniture.
[NIO]
Hm. Whatever, sister.
As for the rest of you,
you've kept your word
and maintained your
patience while awaiting
everyone's arrival, and we're
genuinely pleased and grateful
for your composure.
Now from this point forward,
we ask that you strictly
adhere to the rules.
[NIO]
So... Will someone in this group
successfully eliminate
Haru Ichinose?
Or will Haru
survive your attempts
and safely graduate
from Class Black?
I know each of you has
already been fully debriefed.
But let's review the
rules one more time.
Do they seriously mean
anything we want?
[NIO]
They are completely serious!
The board of the
Myojo Private School will grant
any single wish
you can think of,
but only one of you can succeed.
So in other words, don't get
Teacher Man mixed up in this.
[NIO]
Precisely.
Mr. Mizorogi doesn't
know anything about this.
He's nothing more than
an honest, ordinary guy.
[SHINYA] Doesn't say
anything about not tangling
with other Class Black students.
[NIO] This is the
advanced kill notice.
You'll use this as the
declaration that you're
making your move on Haru.
You each get to use one
notice, and only one notice.
Once you send it out,
there will be no cancelling.
And I advise you to be very
careful with your timing.
After delivering your
advanced notice to Haru,
you'll have 48 hours
to kill her. If you don't,
you fail the mission, and you
will be immediately expelled.
Submit the notice at any time.
Overlapping with
other people is allowed.
Go ahead and be selfish!
[NIO laughs] Oh, no, Miss
Tokaku, you're a little late.
Here's your advance kill notice.
[NIO gasps]
If any of you try to kill her,
you'll have to go
through me first.
[TOKAKU] They got their
numbers all wrong.
There aren't 12
assassins, but 11.
And one protector.
So you wanna know
the reason I saved you?
That's easy.
It's because I'm
defecting to your side.
[TOKAKU]
And today, it truly began.
All of it. For me and Haru.
[KAIBA]
Hello, I'm Mr. Kaiba,
an instructor at
Private Academy 17.
Now that was a plain
and coherent introduction,
wouldn't you say?
So, Tokaku. How would
you describe yourself?
I'm sure other people
could answer that
more accurately for you...