[STUDENT 4A]
Oh, man, I'm tired.
[STUDENT 4B] I screwed up one of
the fill-in-the-blank questions.
[STUDENT 4C]
Yeah, that makes two of us.
That's one day
of mid-terms down!
Only two more to go.
We better hit the books
hard for tomorrow.
I'm determined to get a 100!
[TOKAKU]
Something wrong?
[HARU] I've hit an impossible
problem right off the bat.
[TOKAKU]
That sucks.
Look at this one.
Can you solve it?
It's not as tough as it looks.
You just need to
apply this formula.
Ah! Now I get it!
Thanks so much, Miss Kaminaga!
[KOUKO] It's not
really the kind of thing
that you need to thank me for.
Nothing is gonna get in
the way of me graduating.
I won't get a single
grade below an A!
[LIBRARIAN 4A]
Eh-hem.
[KOUKO]
You won't pass.
Because I cannot fail.
That is not an option.
[SUZU]
You need the bath? I'm stressed.
[KOUKO]
No, I'm okay, you go ahead.
Well, then I believe I shall.
I think I'll go with
Nobori-betsu bath salts today.
Although, Dogo Hot
Springs sounds nice.
[IRENA] Oh, wow! You're
doing a great job, Kouko.
Thanks so much, Miss Irena.
I'm trying really hard.
[YOUNG BOY 4A] Too bad you're
still a massive screw-up, Kouko.
Being good at drawing
diagrams is pointless.
Well, she did set off a bomb
the other day. On accident!
[YOUNG GIRL 4A]
What an idiot!
You might not believe this,
but it's better not
to be an assassin.
Huh?
It's okay. It'll be perfect.
[ISUKE sighs]
[TOKAKU sighs]
[bell rings]
All right! You guys heard
the bell, pencils down, please.
Turn your answer sheets over
and pass them up here.
These stupid tests are stupid.
They just make me sleepy.
I would so much
rather be in bed.
You still managed to sleep
through the whole thing.
My shoulders are all tensed up.
My eyelids are
too heavy to open.
I must've been thinking too
hard 'cause I'm starving now.
[MIZOROGI]
Now then.
Tomorrow's the long awaited
day three of midterms.
The final day!
So this is it.
Study hard tonight.
Review everything so
you have no regrets.
Right!
[HARU]
So how do you feel?
About today's test, I mean.
Think you passed? I bet you did.
It was easy enough.
I guess everything's
easy for you.
Hey guys!
Pretty hard test today, huh?
How do you think you did?
Alright, I suppose.
But how did you feel about it?
I guess it was okay.
Oh. That's awesome.
So, you know...
[BOTH]
Huh?
Why are you always holding
hands when we see you?
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku!
What, don't yell at me.
That's what you wanted
to ask them too, right?
Um, well, yeah.
Oh. I do this to make sure
Kirigaya doesn't get lost.
[HITSUGI]
I do appreciate it.
This place is just so
big it's like a maze.
This school...
I worry about girls
like Kirigaya and
Ichinose being here.
I just don't like it.
[HARU, HITSUGI]
Huh?
[CHITARU] I'm not here to
come after you, you know.
I transferred into Class Black
for my own personal reasons.
You expect us to believe that?
Really?
I'm not asking you
to believe me.
That's your decision to make.
Kirigaya. Let's go.
[HITSUGI]
'Kay.
I guess Miss Namatame's
all right. It's a relief
to hear she's on
our side at least.
Please. You better wake up,
before you get killed.
You wanna hear
something really crazy?
[HARU]
Huh? I do.
Look, we're trying to
study here, what do you want?
It's important
that you hear this.
You need to know about the
Seven Weird Wonders of Myojo.
Well yeah, we do!
Did you not hear me
say we're studying?
[NIO] You know the statue of
Beethoven in the music room?
He comes alive in the
middle of the night,
tossing his hair and
wildly conducting!
[HARU gasps]
[TOKAKU] That's a pretty
heavy embellishment.
I just heard his eyes
shine or something.
[NIO] There's also the anatomy
model in the science hall.
It rolls around laughing.
and then it quickly scoops up
all the guts that went
flying out of its torso.
[TOKAKU]
That's not quite so different.
I heard it just goes
running down the hallways.
Hey. I've been here
for years now,
I think I would know
better than you.
Oh. This one's cool.
Wanna hear about
a tome concealed away
in the library called
the Forbidden Book?
[HARU]
Ah! Tell us! Tell us!
[NIO]
Well...
One of the shelves
is actually a secret door
that leads to a hidden room.
In that room is the Forbidden
Book that must never be opened.
[NIO] But...
[HARU] Go on!
[NIO] They say that
if you write your name
on the checkout card
of that book,
it's supposed to grant
you everlasting happiness.
It makes you
happy forever?
That is what they say.
[TOKAKU]
That doesn't make any sense.
The book must never
be opened but then
you still have to open it?
That's contradictory.
Maybe that's why it brings
happiness to the person
who's actually brave
enough to open it.
[NIO]
That must be it!
But, you'd still have
to find the hidden room
before you could even
start looking for the book.
Studying's not this
loud, y'know.
Ah...
[LIBRARIAN 4A growls]
Right.
Ah! I am so stuffed!
I think I went a little
overboard at dinner.
No kidding. You probably
should have taken my advice
and skipped dessert.
[HARU] Yeah, but,
the strawberries looked
too good to turn down.
[HARU gasps]
[TOKAKU]
What's wrong?
I think that's one
of Luther's proverbs.
Okay, but what's
it supposed to mean?
[TOKAKU] What matters is
the clock's now ticking.
You've got two days.
We can expect an
attempt on your life
at any time in
the next 48 hours.
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku.
[TOKAKU]
A grenade.
[HARU sighs]
Thanks, that was a close one.
[TOKAKU]
Wait.
[HARU]
[TOKAKU]
So that's the main event.
Who could be behind this?
[SUZU]
Oh, hey.
I've already bathed
if you want a bath.
You look like you could
use some relaxation.
How about it?
I can fill the tub.
You're welcome to
my bath salts as well.
You prefer Kinosaki or Beppu?
No thanks. I think I'll shower.
Kouko. Have you heard this?
[KOUKO]
Heard what?
Death is not the end
of a person's life,
but the culmination
of a lifetime.
[IRENA]
Do you understand that?
[KOUKO]
Not really.
[IRENA]
Of course not. I don't know.
It's just something that's
oddly stuck with me.
It's always made me
wonder about death.
Maybe it isn't so much life's
conclusion as its pinnacle.
Okay. I've finished
rigging it up.
Five minutes
till target arrival.
[IRENA]
I'll complete the assignment.
You head on back now.
[KOUKO]
Yes, ma'am.
No, Miss Irena!
May God always watch over you.
[INSTRUCTOR 4A]
Our existence was nearly exposed
by your careless handling
of the assignment.
Your failure has
wrought calamity.
I'm so sorry,
please forgive me!
Next time! I promise I'll--
[INSTRUCTOR 4A] Enough.
Your actions have summoned
Ihrayna to the lord's side.
And unlike you, Kouko,
she was such a talented child.
It's a tragedy.
[IRENA]
You might not believe this,
but it's better not
to be an assassin.
It's always made me
wonder about death.
Maybe it isn't so much life's
conclusion as its pinnacle
If I hadn't screwed up,
you would still be alive...
Irena...
[KOUKO]
Remember her.
And know that failure
will never be an option.
[NIO giggles]
Oh, look at you go.
You've got something to prove.
[MIZOROGI] Okay! I have to
collect the answer sheets now.
[ISUKE sighs]
I am so over this.
Well, yeah, but all
you did was sleep.
So how'd you do?
I don't feel that
confident about it.
Well that makes
two of us, at least.
Oh, stop it.
Oh, man, my shoulders are stiff.
Finally. It'll all be over soon.
I'm really anxious.
I wanna see the results.
I was wondering.
Do you have any plans
for later tonight?
[TOKAKU]
Nothing in particular.
Then uh, you know
the library...
Alright, if you've got
something you wanna say,
just go ahead and
spit it out already.
The thing is...
I was kind of hoping
to sneak into the
library to check it out.
[TOKAKU] Is this about
that Forbidden Book?
[HARU]
I wanna try to find it.
But, I guess you don't think
this is a good time, huh?
Yeah, you guessed right.
Your life's in danger.
There are still over 24
hours left on that threat.
Is there something wrong?
Fine, if we take one look,
will you drop it?
Totally! Awesome!
Let's sneak in tonight
after everyone's asleep.
[TOKAKU]
Yeah, okay. Quit clinging.
Gimme a sec.
[HARU]
You're amazing! Wow!
[TOKAKU]
Hold on.
Were you planning
on breaking the glass?
Maybe...
Let's just get this over with.
[TOKAKU]
Alright then.
Where exactly is this
hidden room of yours?
Uh. Well...
It is hidden, y'know.
[TOKAKU]
You didn't do any research?
Why?
C'mon, what kind of fun
would it be to go searching
for a hidden room if we
already knew where it was?
Whatever.
[HARU]
Hm?
[TOKAKU]
It's this way.
[HARU]
Huh, really? Are you sure?
[TOKAKU]
This is it.
[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
Whoa, it really exists!
The Forbidden Doorway!
Wait. How did you
know where it was?
[TOKAKU]
By the smell.
[HARU]
Seriously?
[HARU coughing]
It does smell kinda moldy.
By the looks of it, this must
be the closed stacks wing.
Do you think the book's
really in here somewhere?
[HARU] ♪ The Forbidden Book,
Forbidden Book. ♪
Which could it be?
What the--?
How did one of
those get in here?
Wait!
Miss Tokaku! Are you okay?
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku!
[TOKAKU grunts]
[high-pitched ringing]
[TOKAKU grunting]
[TOKAKU gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Go hide somewhere-- hurry!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU] So you're behind
all this, Kaminaga.
You heard us talking about
the Forbidden Book, didn't you?
That's right. And I
almost succeeded.
I was so close.
There's no way I'm
going to give up now!
[KOUKO grunts]
No. I still have time!
[KOUKO grunting]
You can't understand how
I feel! How could you, Azuma?
I want out!
[KOUKO]
I can't take it!
I don't want to be
an assassin anymore!
You just want
out of the business?
Is that seriously the reward
you're doing this for?
[KOUKO]
Yeah, that's right.
So you're gonna kill
to never kill again?
Well that's ironic.
[KOUKO gasps]
[KOUKO]
I'm not an assassin.
I'll never be more
than a failure. Never.
[KOUKO sobbing]
[HARU]
Poor Kaminaga...
[KOUKO sobbing]
[MIZOROGI]
Miss Inukai. Miss Hashiri.
Miss Sagae.
This is crap. Who passes out
the worst grades first?
At least you managed
to write your name down
before passing out.
I don't even see the point
in looking at my results.
Now Miss Shuto.
And Miss Kenmochi.
Yep, that seems about right.
The biology portion of the exam
was staggeringly complicated.
[MIZOROGI]
Miss Azuma.
Miss Banba.
Did he have to
give these back?
I don't wanna see this.
Can't you ladies accept
failure with a little grace?
[MIZOROGI]
Here you are, Miss Hanabusa.
Oh.
[MIZOROGI]
Miss Namatame.
Miss Kirigaya.
Nicely done.
Hey, I got a 91.
Great job. Wow.
Thanks! There's no way
I could have done it
without your help though.
Of course they end up with
the best grades in the class.
It's always the ones
who are convinced
they completely failed.
Yeah, talk about obnoxious.
Drumroll please.
The highest score of
the midterms goes to:
Haru Ichinose!
[HARU]
Seriously? So that means...
I'm at the top of the class now?
[SHIENA]
Wow. Good job.
[MAHIRU]
Really. That's great.
[HARUKI] I'm not surprised.
Girl worked pretty hard.
[MIZOROGI]
Okay, ladies, settle down.
It's time to start class.
[MIZOROGI] I hope you do just as
well at your next school, Kouko.
It's too bad about Kouko.
I guess she just
wasn't really suited
for Class Black after all.
Is that...
It's the checkout card.
Maybe it'll help
Kaminaga find happiness.
[TOKAKU]
I don't see how it'll work.
She didn't write her name on it.
[HARU] It'll work.
The most important thing
about magic charms
is to believe in them!
[TOKAKU]
Is that right?
Yep!
[TOKAKU sighs]
[KAIBA] Baby pink, milky pink,
smoky pink, light pink.
They all look like the
same damn color to me.
Women make things
so complicated.
Not to name names, but if you
wipe your hands on your skirt
instead of a handkerchief,
you're a bit of skank.