Hey, Tokaku.
You don't have to stay here.
Come live with me in the city.
The city is a lot
of fun, you know?
and you'll have lots of friends
your own age at school.
We've also got sweet
candies and great books.
And your auntie won't make
you do this training stuff.
I know for a fact this isn't
what your mommy wanted for you.
[TOKAKU'S GRANDMOTHER]
Stop trying to fill her head
with that nonsense!
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Wait, mother--
[TOKAKU'S GRANDMOTHER] You're
a disgrace to the Azuma legacy.
I won't allow you to pass
on your selfish behavior
to the true heir
of our family.
You've visited the grave.
There's no reason for
you to stay any longer.
[YOUNG TOKAKU]
I killed it.
[TOKAKU]
Huh?
[MIZOROGI] I've got
some exciting news.
This month is the Myojo
Private School Annual Festival!
The whole school's
part of the celebration!
So I say we go all out.
How about we put on a play?
Our class is full
of beauties after all.
Which play you ask?
The classic of all classics.
Romeo and Juliet!
And I've worked hard
to rewrite the script.
I've given it a modern day edge!
I'll show you! Turn to page ten.
You'll know this scene.
"Oh, Romeo! Tell me, why
do you have to be Romeo?"
[MIZOROGI] "If it is--"
[ISUKE] Ugh.
So totally boring.
Go ahead and count me
out of this one, teach.
[MIZOROGI laughs]
Participation is mandatory.
This is so exciting!
Huh. Well, she seems pleased.
[HITSUGI]
O, Romeo, Romeo.
O, tell me, why do you
have to be Romeo?
Uh. If that is truly
the wish you ask of me,
then no longer am I Romeo!
Your one and only love.
From now on, that will
be the name I go by!
How exactly did you
come to be here?
If they see you, there is
no doubt they will kill you!
I'm far more terrified of
your gaze than their weapons.
Please. I beg of you to smile.
If only you'll do
that, then I will--
[SHIENA]
No, no, it's all wrong!
You are butchering this role!
Trust me on this one.
You need more sex appeal!
You have to use
your feminine wiles
to convince the audience
that you're a man!
Act more gracefully.
Try being sexy!
[SHIENA]
Give us some bedroom eyes!
Seduce us with your very gaze!
[MIZOROGI]
Uh. Okay, Kenmochi,
why don't you take
a little break, huh?
[SHIENA] With all due
respect, stay out of this.
If that's what you want.
[HARU]
Shiena really knows what's up.
[NIO] Yeah, I heard she was
into theatre at her last school.
This isn't really my thing.
It's just not me.
Maybe a different part?
You'd make a much better
Juliet than a Romeo!
Don't you think so?
You are a lady, after all.
These amateurs are
defiling my vision.
Got your own
directorial vision, huh?
Well aren't you a professional.
[HARU grunting]
[HARUKI]
There ya go.
[HARU] Jeez, you're strong,
Haruki. Thank you!
That's the only redeeming
quality I've got.
I'll grab that one too.
I'm so over this.
I think it goes without saying,
this work is
completely beneath me.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIZOROGI]
Oh. Great, that goes over there.
[HARUKI] Looks like we'll
get everything set up today.
[TOKAKU]
Looks like it.
Straight from the tests
and into a school festival.
[HARUKI]
It's kinda nice, huh?
It's like we're real students.
We're far from it.
I'm aware of that.
But look at this way.
Everyone's having fun.
How often can we say that?
It's pretty rare.
[HARU]
Hey Haruki! It's finished!
We couldn't have done
it without your help!
[phone ringing]
Sorry.
[HARUKI]
Hey, what's up, Fuyuka?
[FUYUKA]
I'm freakin' out, sis!
[SIBLINGS yelling, whining]
You just hang in there.
Don't worry, I'm gonna
take care of everything
before you know it.
'Cause I'm your sister.
It's my job, isn't it?
Okay. Later.
[HARUKI]
From the very beginning.
I've known what
I'm here to do. Fun?
The Festival? None of its real.
I have to do it.
[HARU sighs]
♪ Giant bath, giant bath. ♪
♪ A huge, gigantic bath. ♪
Hey, Miss Tokaku.
Look out!
Don't get too carried away.
I don't wanna run into anyone.
We're getting out soon.
No one else is
gonna take a bath.
It's way too late at night.
Hey. Come over here and I
can wash your back for you.
[TOKAKU]
I'm alright.
[HARU] Oh, don't be
so shy. Here, silly!
[HARU gasps]
Am I interrupting
something in here?
[HARUKI]
So I was talking to Nio...
[HARUKI] Having other people
die so you can live.
I'm curious what
that feels like?
[HARU gasps]
Letting someone sacrifice
their life for your life.
How exactly can you live with
that and keep on smiling?
[TOKAKU]
That's enough!
I will smile. Always.
[HARUKI gasps]
You're a twisted piece of work.
Ya hear that, Azuma?
She's just gonna keep on
smiling even if you die for her.
Oh, give it a rest. You're
starting to scare little Haru.
And you call
yourself an Azuma?
Look how tame you are.
What the hell happened to
you to reduce you to this?
As meek as you are now,
I could probably kill you.
[TOKAKU]
C'mon, Ichinose. We're leaving.
[HARU]
Wait, Miss Tokaku.
Are you okay?
What's with you?
Why aren't you mad at her?
The crap she was saying.
Doesn't it make you angry?
At all?
I just don't see the point
in getting angry about it.
[TOKAKU]
Tch!
Haruki. She isn't
usually like that.
I wonder if something happened.
[HARU] Is the Azuma family
seriously all that incredible?
Incredible doesn't even cut it.
In these circles,
the very name Azuma--
Man! It gives me the willies!
So they're famous?
[NIO] Are you kidding?
Everyone's heard of them.
They're part of a clan of
assassins that's reigned over
the dark side of Japan
since ancient times.
[NIO]
The Azumas of the East.
The Kuzunohas of the West.
They've served those in
power through every era,
secretly altering
the country's history.
[HARU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[TOKAKU]
Perhaps you've forgotten
the second rule of Class Black?
Oh! You're going for the
curry again today, I see.
You must really love that stuff.
No one's supposed to discuss
the history of other classmates.
Well, sure, but I'm
the class arbitrator.
[HARU]
She didn't say anything bad.
In the future, ask me directly
if you're curious about my past.
Just leave that
nobody out of it.
That's me!
Oh. Uh, so then...
What's your immediate
family like?
This sounds like a date.
Well I don't even know
what my father looks like.
And my mother...
She died right after I was born.
So I was raised
by my grandmother.
My other relatives are...
They're dead.
Uh, I'm sorry to--
Really? What a co-inky dink!
My entire family's
dead or missing as well!
[TOKAKU] No one asked you.
[NIO] Okay.
[HARUKI]
Hey.
Texting the fam?
[TOKAKU]
Not quite.
[HARUKI]
Sorry I was a bitch last night.
I just had some
weird stuff on my mind
and I lashed out at you guys.
[TOKAKU]
Don't worry about it.
[HARUKI] Man, another
peaceful day out there, huh?
If life was fair,
Haru would be out there
with all those other kids.
And not just Haru.
It's not like any
of us are really here
because we want
to go through with it.
I chalk it up to crappy luck.
Honestly, Azuma.
Wouldn't you rather give Haru
the freedom that she deserves?
The freedom to get
away from all of this.
We can give her that, you know?
Breaking away from
the rules of Class Black.
Is that what you're suggesting?
10 o'clock tonight.
Let's meet here. We can
talk more about it then.
I'll be waiting.
[ISUKE]
My, my.
I think I just figured out
why you got into this game.
Well at least they're cute.
The logical thing to do
would be to kill them all.
I know you live
your life your way,
but that's how I'd handle it.
You're only wasting your
time worrying about them.
Life is too short
to care so much.
You just have to get rid
of what you don't need.
Free yourself from that burden.
Hm. I was only trying
to give some advice.
[HARUKI] The reward I got
for the first person I killed
was measly. A tableful
of smiles for my family.
And a little something for me.
A bottle of
baby pink nail polish.
I'd always wanted it,
even though I knew
it wouldn't suit me.
[NIO] No need to tell me
your reward, Haruki.
I was given the details when
you were invited to Class Black.
You want enough money to keep
your family well-fed for life.
That's the gist of it, right?
That's it.
There's one other thing I
wanna make sure of, though.
And that is?
[inaudible]
That won't be a problem.
Miss Tokaku? Are you in here?
Oh, there you are.
[HARU]
Haruki?
Hey, have you seen Miss Tokaku?
She left a note saying for
me to meet her in here.
[HARUKI]
She's not coming.
It's just us.
What?
But don't worry.
I'm here to set you free.
[HARU gasps]
[HARU panting]
[HARU gasping]
[HARUKI grunts]
[HARU gasps]
[HARU coughs]
What a liar.
You were gonna
blow off our meeting
from the get-go, weren't you?
[TOKAKU]
You're one to talk.
[HARUKI] You got me there, but
I was still telling the truth.
I lured Haru here to
give her her freedom.
There's only one way
out of this hellish game
for her and that's to die.
[HARU weakly]
Miss Tokaku...
Don't worry, I got this.
[HARUKI] You may be
an Azuma, but just in name.
As meek as you are?
You can't kill me!
[HARU] Be careful!
[TOKAKU] Don't move!
[HARUKI grunts]
Look out!
[HARU whimpers]
[TOKAKU]
That's all I needed.
Now I've got you.
[HARUKI grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[HARUKI groans]
[HARUKI]
Ow... Dammit.
That was hard core.
Who'd you have to sacrifice
to get that strong,
you freakin' monster?
[TOKAKU]
Are we finished?
[HARUKI]
You've made our bad luck worse.
We both know there's no
backing down from this.
Not for you guys,
and not for me.
We can't escape this
no matter what we do.
[HARUKI] If we're ever gonna be
free then this is the only way.
Huh?
In other words...
...I win!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARU gasps]
That's it.
There's one other thing I
wanna make sure of, though.
And that is?
If I don't make it out
of this one, like I die,
my family will still
get the reward, correct?
[HARUKI] From now on, you'll
live with smiles on your faces.
Just like Haru.
[TOKAKU grunts]
[HARU]
How did we live?
Its Haruki's set.
[TOKAKU] It made a
pocket of space for us.
[TOKAKU]
Looks like no fatal injuries.
Thank goodness.
[HARUKI grunts]
Think you can stand up?
What is with you?
[HARUKI sighs]
Oh, jeez. I lost and I admit it.
I was trying to give us all
a clean death in one swoop.
Kinda botched
that one, didn't I?
We can't die yet.
Not that easy.
Because being alive?
It means that you've
been forgiven.
[HARU]
Forgiven to be here now.
[HARUKI sighs]
I swear, dying would be easier.
It's not like I
actually asked for this.
Life can be pretty
meddlesome, huh?
Well, it doesn't look like
I have much of a choice.
One way or another,
I guess I'm just gonna
have to keep at it somehow.
Aww, boy. Crap.
What's up with you?
That icy face of yours almost
looks relieved I'm not dead.
Well.
It looks like this means that
you can't die yet either.
So you keep at it too.
Hang in there, okay?
I miss our big sis.
I really hope she
comes home soon.
Me too.
[FUYUKA]
That makes three of us.
Having the family all here.
That's the best, isn't it?
No!
Do you still believe the world
is full of forgiveness?
After what you've just
been through with Haruki
and the rest of the class
trying to kill you,
think you'll be able
to forgive it all?
That's the thing about it.
Forgiveness is there for
those who commit crimes
and make mistakes.
And you can't just do it once.
We forgive as many
times as it takes.
[KAIBA] To be or not to be.
That is the question.
That's a famous line
from Hamlet, of course.
But they're putting on
Romeo and Juliet,
so you don't think
it's relevant?
Well don't get too giddy
about the festival.
You might get hurt.