[CHITARU]
Where are you trying to get to?
You want me to
help you find it?
Sure, if you don't mind.
I'm looking for
Myojo Private School.
Well that's bus number 6.
And you know what?
I'm headed there as well.
We can ride together
if you want.
That'd be great, yeah!
Thank you for being so nice.
[CHITARU]
Are you in grade school?
Don't you have a guardian?
[HITSUGI]
Huh? Oh, no.
I don't. Just me.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[HITSUGI]
Wow!
[CHITARU] The crowd seems
like they're really into this.
[HITSUGI giggles]
[DARTS BOOTH BOY 6A] Alright!
We've got a winner! Nice!
[HARU] That was awesome,
you're like a dart pro!
[TOKAKU] Yeah, thanks.
I'm not sure why you want this,
--but here you go.
[HARU giggles]
[HITSUGI gasps]
[CHITARU]
Uh--
[DARTS BOOTH BOY 6A]
And we have a winner!
[FOOD BOOTH BOY 6A]
Hot yakisoba!
[HITSUGI giggles]
I love it so much!
Thank you again, Chitaru!
You know... It still
really worries me
that a girl like you
is in Class Black.
Huh?
[CHITARU nervous laugh]
You don't need to worry,
I'll be fine.
So what about you?
You said that Ichinose
wasn't your target,
but if she's not, then who is?
She goes by Angel's Trumpet.
She's a coldblooded,
ruthless poisoner.
I know she must be here.
And I'm gonna find her
and take her down.
Me too. I'll do anything
I can to help you.
[HARU whimpering]
[SHIENA]
You can't be serious!
You have got to
get this part down!
We are opening tomorrow!
[HARU]
I know, I'm sorry.
Until you get this right,
we're gonna keep rehearsing!
Okay.
[TOKAKU]
C'mon.
Thanks for grabbing it for me.
[CHITARU]
Ichinose is quite helpless.
She's probably never even held a
sword before, wouldn't you say?
[SHIENA]
All right, one more time.
Let's take it from the scene
where Tybalt kills Mercutio.
So Azuma's playing a
character that murders Haru.
You've gotta love irony.
[SHIENA]
Alright, guys.
Hurry up with those
costumes and make sure
you can move around
in them, okay? Tell Banba
if you have any issues so
she can fix them for you.
Nicely understated design.
I'm playing the nurse,
so why the hell
am I in a maid's uniform?
[SHIENA] Careful, a maid
shouldn't speak so casually.
Actually, Nurse.
She's not a maid.
No, but don't worry about it.
People will think it's
an artistic choice.
Oh wow, you look
incredible, Miss Hanabusa.
Thanks. And your costume
looks great on you too.
Uh. Do you think so?
Fine feathers do
improve the bird.
Hey, be nice!
They sure seem excited.
[HARU]
Hey, everyone. Look over here.
[ISUKE]
Really, you're taking pictures?
[NIO] Totes, yo!
A snapshot of our youth!
[CHITARU]
Well, I'm off.
You feeling up to checking out
the main bath with me?
[HITSUGI]
Oh, no thanks.
I'm pretty worn out
from rehearsals.
No worries. Later.
[door slams]
[TOKAKU] Hold on a minute!
Can't you look for it later?
[HARU] No. I really
need to find it now.
[TOKAKU]
Wait!
[SUZU]
Really? Kirigaya's not with you?
[CHITARU]
She already went to bed.
[SUZU]
Well, huh.
I don't think I've even seen
the two of you separated
since Class Black began.
[CHITARU sighs]
Me too. I'll do
anything I can to help.
[CHITARU] Did I do the
right thing by telling her?
[HARU] I just don't get where
my script could have gone.
I thought it would be
around here somewhere.
[TOKAKU] We better not find out
it was in your bag all along.
That would be annoying.
[HARU] Give me some credit,
I looked in my bag.
Oh, hey. Did you
look over there?
Behind those trees?
[SHIENA laughs]
[HITSUGI] You are quite
dedicated to work so late.
[SHIENA]
Uh. Yeah. I guess so.
[HITSUGI] You're making
your move on Ichinose
within the coming day, correct?
[SHIENA]
Why would you say...
Oh.
[HITSUGI] That's why you really
care so much about the play.
I'm sorry, did you
forget something in here?
Oh, no. I'm making my own
preparations for tomorrow.
[SHIENA]
Uh?
[SHIENA whimpers]
[clatters]
[TOKAKU]
What do you think that was?
[HARU]
Whoa, wait!
It's Shiena!
Hey, stay back!
[TOKAKU]
Who's back there?
[HITSUGI] Of all the people
in class, it had to be you two
that come stumbling in.
Luck is not on my side tonight.
[HARU] But there's no way
that you did this.
[TOKAKU]
Why would you take out Kenmochi?
[HITSUGI]
She got in my way,
so I had to remove
her from the picture.
[HITSUGI] Oh by the way,
I might as well go ahead
and give you mine, too.
[HARU gasps]
You've got a full day tomorrow!
Is this for real?
[MIZOROGI]
Sad news, guys.
Miss Kenmochi was hospitalized
last night for food poisoning.
She worked really hard.
Let's do this right and
make this play a success!
The poor thing was so gung-ho
about putting on this play.
You know, Azuma, you really
could have at least waited
until we were done
with the show.
[TOKAKU, HARU]
Huh?
What're you talking about?
C'mon. Are you really
gonna sit there and tell me
that you didn't do
this to protect Haru?
[CHITARU]
Azuma took her out?
[NIO] The hospital tests
said it was a poison needle
that brought her down.
[CHITARU gasps]
[ISUKE] Huh. Poison. Really?
And Shiena had issued
her advanced notice too.
Pretty strange. Now that she's
suddenly been hospitalized,
guess you can cross
her off the threat list.
[NIO]
Here ya go, peeps!
Class Black's production
of Romeo and Juliet.
Trust me, you don't
wanna miss it!
[STUDENT 6A]
I heard that every student
in Class Black is super hot!
[STUDENT 6B]
Should we go see it?
[STUDENT 6C]
Well, duh!
[HARU] For both ours and
Shiena's sake, I really hope
we're able to successfully
pull off this play.
[TOKAKU] You realize
she wanted to kill you?
[HARU laughs] Well, she
had good qualities too.
[TOKAKU]
Our Juliet on the other hand,
she'll try to poison you.
Be sure to keep your
distance from her.
And don't eat
anything else today.
Think you can do that?
[HARU]
Mm-hm.
I promise that I won't
let her hurt you.
Thank you.
Anytime. Now let's go
have a good show.
[HARU giggles]
[HITSUGI]
You know, you're really
such a lovely lady, Chitaru.
You look so pretty.
[CHITARU] Uh, thanks,
but I'm playing a man though.
You look much lovelier.
[HITSUGI giggles]
Oh, stop.
You're the beautiful one.
So about Angel's Trumpet...
Do you mind telling me
why you're trying to find her?
[CHITARU'S MENTOR]
I'll never understand.
I constantly ask myself
why she was killed.
Why someone would want her dead?
It doesn't make sense.
It's silly, right?
I've spent so much time
chasing her and I don't even
know what she looks like.
[HITSUGI]
I don't think it's silly at all.
They were people that
you care about, right?
Yeah. I only had the opportunity
to meet her daughter once,
but she seemed nice.
[HITSUGI]
Huh? You only met her once?
So you're doing all of this
after only one meeting?
[CHITARU laughs]
[HITSUGI] You have a
genuinely kind heart, Chitaru.
[CHITARU]
I don't know about that.
I just want to see my
mentor smile once more.
You know, you told me yesterday
that you wanted to help me,
but you don't have to do that.
I want you to stay innocent,
to stay away from that darkness.
I think I can handle it.
I know that I may seem like
it but I'm not that weak.
[CHITARU]
If you say so.
Testing.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please take your seats.
Class Black's production of
Romeo and Juliet will now begin.
I hope you all have your
handkerchiefs at the ready.
Turn off your cell
phones and no talking.
If anyone causes
a disturbance...
Then it's your own fault
if you wind up dead.
[STUDENT 6D] That was a
really funny announcement.
Alright, Inukai. Now that's
how you get their attention.
[CHITARU] How're you feeling?
Starting to get nervous?
[HARU]
Yeah. I am.
[BOTH laugh]
[STUDENTS clapping]
[SUZU] I'll leave you be.
Good night, mistress.
[HITSUGI]
Thank you, and good night.
Oh, day and night,
through dreams and waking life.
My thoughts belong to him.
[CHITARU]
O, my most desired love.
Upon the wings of night
have I flown here this evening,
only to fall beneath the
weight of my passion for you.
The moon, so beautiful
this night,
but oh, lovely moon goddess,
your true nature is cruel.
[TOKAKU] If she's
planning to attack today,
that leaves less than ten hours.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HITSUGI] I feel like
a fool in some ways.
I speak to you
from this balcony,
even though I know...
[HARU]
Is something wrong?
It's coated in poison.
[HARU gasps]
We should check out
your sword, too.
[HARU]
Uh...
Don't touch it!
Who goes there?
What man are you,
hidden by night?
There's poison
all over the handle.
Poison.
She really is trying
to go through with it.
[HITSUGI]
Oh. Romeo, my Romeo.
O tell me, why do you
have to be Romeo?
[CHITARU] If that is truly
the wish you ask of me,
then no longer am I Romeo.
Your one and only love.
I shall take that as my name.
[HITSUGI] How exactly
did you come to be here?
[CHITARU]
Those two...
[CHITARU gasps]
[TOKAKU]
Wait!
C'mon. Are you really going
to sit there and tell me
that you didn't do
this to protect Haru?
The hospital tests said
it was a poison needle
that brought her down.
[CHITARU]
A poison needle?
Ah. I'm far more terrified
of your gaze than their weapons.
Please, I beg of you to smile.
[FEMALE STUDENTS shriek]
I need to know. What's up
with you and Ichinose?
Wha--?
Did you give her
your advanced notice?
[HITSUGI]
I ask that you leave.
You and I are sworn
enemies by blood.
Only pain can come from this.
[CHITARU] I refuse.
Your love is worth the pain.
[STUDENT 6E]
Romeo is so romantic!
[STUDENT 6F]
He's so passionate!
[CHITARU]
Be honest with me.
Do you know who
poisoned Kenmochi?
You can tell me.
Did you find out
Ichinose's Angel's Trumpet?
[HITSUGI]
Wait, where are you going?
[CHITARU panting]
[TOKAKU grunts]
[HARU]
No, don't touch it!
There's poison on it.
[CHITARU]
Poison?
This doesn't have
anything to do with you.
[TOKAKU]
Let's go, Ichinose. C'mon.
[CHITARU] I need to know if you
put the on poison that sword.
Just admit it, Haru.
You're Angel's Trumpet.
I don't get it.
What's Angel's Trumpet?
The person who assassinated
my mentor's daughter.
It was you, right?
What?
[SUMIREKO] Juliet. Oh, daughter,
what have you done?
I'm sorry, it's too late.
Please forgive me, mother.
My heart belongs to him.
[CHITARU] She was trying
to keep me from getting
blood on my hands.
Just come clean. Or else.
This sword's not a prop.
[TOKAKU]
Stay behind me.
[SUZU] The fault of the matter
does not lie with my mistress.
[STUDENT 6G]
What the--?
[STUDENT 6H]
Hey! What's going on?
[STUDENTS cheer]
[STUDENT 6I]
My darling Romeo!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU] Stay down here.
You'll be safe next to this guy.
What? "This guy"?
[TOKAKU] Sorry, but your
fight is with me.
If that's what you want.
Uh. Oh, wow!
That Romeo sure is determined.
It looks like he's
challenged Tybalt
to a fight for the
hand of Miss Juliet.
[BOTH grunting]
[CHITARU] Nothing can
make me forgive her!
If you're gonna defend her,
then I'll have to kill you, too!
[TOKAKU]
Where's your advanced notice?
That's not what this is about!
Then why the hell
are you trying to kill her?
The only one I want
dead is Angel's Trumpet.
And it turns out she and
Haru are one in the same.
[CHITARU yells]
You don't know what she is!
You don't know how many people
are dead because of her!
And how could you know
what she's been through?
Damn!
[CHITARU]
She's a heartless poisoner!
And I won't let her
get away with it!
[TOKAKU]
Poisoner?
[CHITARU]
[CHITARU] I figured it out
when Kenmochi was poisoned.
I know she did it!
No, that's impossible.
Kirigaya poisoned Shiena.
What was that?
[CHITARU]
Why should I believe you?
[TOKAKU]
Because I was there.
I saw it with my
own eyes. It was her!
[CHITARU]
That's a lie!
[HITSUGI]
I'm afraid it's true.
[CHITARU gasps]
Kirigaya?
I'm sorry,
but Angel's Trumpet is me.
Why are you telling me this?
My plan didn't
work as I'd hoped.
But it was my intention
for Haru to die on the stage,
exactly as her character
dies in the play.
So then, you're the one
who poisoned the sword?
I wish I could deny it.
But I'm telling you because
there's just no reason
for you to be risking
your life fighting Azuma.
Kirigaya...
[HITSUGI]
We should go back now.
I think we've kept the
audience waiting long enough.
[NIO]
Once you consume this potion,
you will appear dead
to the world, but...
[HITSUGI]
I care not.
I beg of you,
give me this potion, friar.
[HARU] I never would have
guessed that they were enemies.
Do you think they can reconcile?
I sincerely doubt it.
After all, they're both killers.
[NIO] In two and 40 hours,
you will awaken fully refreshed
as if rising from a
deep and pleasant sleep.
I-I have to.
I will carry out my mission.
[HITSUGI]
Romeo, I drink this for you.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Oh Romeo!
[BOTH gasp]
[STUDENT 6J]
So dreamy!
[CHITARU]
I found your poison.
[HITSUGI]
Life seems to be against us.
We can never be
anything but enemies.
Our fates just won't allow it.
Very well. I have
no other choice!
[STUDENTS gasping]
[HARU gasps]
What the--?
I don't want to do this,
but it's my duty.
This is just as it should be.
It's okay.
[CHITARU gasps]
[HITSUGI grunts]
[CHITARU]
No, please. Hitsugi...
[NIO] You were Juliet's
final wish, Romeo.
She told me that when
everything was said and done,
the only thing she wanted
was to leave here with you.
Living her life with you.
That is what this
child truly wished for.
[CHITARU]
No.
I'm sorry that I
never understood you.
That I only saw
what I wanted to see.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHITARU grunting]
[STUDENTS clapping]
[STUDENT 6L]
That was so much fun, huh?
[STUDENT 6M] That was so sad,
I was totally crying.
[STUDENT 6N] They almost had me
convinced that they really died.
[HARU whimpers]
[KAIBA] Did you know
there are official rules
to the split-the-watermelon
game? I hear it even covers
who cleans up at the end.
Seriously? That reminds
me of the saying
"the field trip isn't
over until you get home".
While we're on the subject.
I could go for some watermelon.