[BABY crying]
I've decided we shall
name the child Tokaku.
[TOKAKU'S MOTHER]
Mother?
[TOKAKU'S GRANDMOTHER]
It means "an impossible thing".
Fitting, don't you think?
Those who bear witness
to this child's strength
will be astounded. Her mere
existence will inspire dread.
There couldn't be
a more perfect name
for the heir to
the Azuma family.
Little Tokaku.
You're destined to grow
so strong that every soul
on this earthwill fear you.
[TOKAKU'S MOTHER]
I just-- I can't let it happen.
She can't be the Azuma heir.
I don't want her to become
a killer like we are.
She can't be like us.
I know, sis.
[TOKAKU'S MOTHER]
Mako, please.
Promise that if
anything happens to me,
that you'll take her,
you'll take her and...
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Hurry, Tokaku! This way!
There's no time!
Tokaku. If you ever think
of killing someone again,
just remember this shrine.
What'll that do?
You won't be able to kill,
because inside that shrine, your
mother will be watching you.
Huh?
[TOKAKU]
What the hell do you mean?
[ISUKE laughs]
Tell me! What was that sound?
And what about Banba?
You see, I made her
a little promise.
[ISUKE] If she let me beat you
to death, then she'd be free
to do whatever she
wanted with Haru.
[HARU gasps]
Tch!
[crash]
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU groans]
[ISUKE] Not so fast!
[TOKAKU grunts]
Move aside!
You realize this
is all your fault?
If you'd been able
to kill me before,
we wouldn't even
be in this situation.
[SHINYA]
Thanks, by the way.
[HARU]
Huh?
[SHINYA] Mahiru's got
herself some new treasure.
Wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for you.
And it's seriously an
awesome piece of treasure!
Awesome enough to fill
the emptiness inside!
[SHINYA cackles]
[HARU panting]
You dummy. You threw
your cell phone.
[SHINYA cackles]
How wonderful!
It wouldn't be any fun at all
if I just killed you right away.
[HARU panting]
[crash]
[SHINYA] Oh my,
where's your precious Azuma?
She's too busy to help you now.
Too busy getting
killed by Inukai!
[HARU gasps]
Nobody's coming to rescue you.
[SHINYA]
No matter how much you yell.
And yell...
And yell, and yell!
[SHINYA]
No one...
No one. No one.
[SHINYA]
No one watching!
No one there!
And right here and now,
there's no one to save you!
I hope you and Azuma
are happy on the other side.
Huh?
[HARU grunts]
[SHINYA gasps, coughs]
[HARU pants]
[SHINYA laughs]
[ISUKE]
First time I saw you,
I could tell you
were so full of crap.
Why would you even bother
joining Class Black?
You're such a freaking disgrace.
[TOKAKU grunting]
You're so determined
to protect Haru.
But you don't care about her.
It's just camouflage to hide
the fact you can't kill.
Talk about a raw deal for her.
[TOKAKU grunts]
[TOKAKU]
Keep your mind empty.
Don't think or feel.
Just keep on moving.
So much for all that infamous
"Azumas of the East" hype.
Does this mean I'll be
deemed the most powerful
after I kill you?
[TOKAKU grunts]
[phone vibrates]
Huh?
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU grunts]
[TOKAKU groans]
[ISUKE] You think this is
a good time to check that?
A little disrespectful
to me, don't you think?
[ISUKE laughs]
[TOKAKU grunts]
[ISUKE screams]
[TOKAKU coughing]
[TOKAKU pants]
[TOKAKU'S MOTHER]
Tokaku!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE grunting]
[ISUKE]
Hey, get back here! Stop!
[SHINYA pants]
[SHINYA giggling]
[SHINYA]
She's too busy to help you now.
Too busy getting
killed by Inukai!
[HARU]
She's okay.
There's no way Miss Tokaku
can get killed that easily.
[HARU gasps]
[metal scraping]
[HARU sighs]
[mop clatters]
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Now what was that?
Knock, knock. Anyone in there?
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Knock, knock. Anyone in there?
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Anyone in this room?
Anyone in here?
[crash]
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
How about in here?
[crash]
[SHINYA]
Anyone hiding in there?
[crash]
[slow knocking]
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Anyone in this--
[SHINYA groans]
[HARU panting]
[SHINYA laughs]
Oh, man, that was cheap!
You totally crushed my nose!
[SHINYA laughing]
[SHINYA groans]
I'd say it's time for
a ten minute break,
no reason not to take it slow.
After all, the night
is still young.
[TOKAKU panting]
Tch!
[TOKAKU]
Where are you, Haru?
Give me a sign.
[TOKAKU]
Maybe I can spot her from here.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[ISUKE chuckles]
[HARU panting]
[HARU]
What do I do?
Where should I hide?
I hope Miss Tokaku's alright.
[HARU gasps]
This is her phone.
[HARU grunts]
Aw, but it's no fun
when you dodge it.
[SHINYA] Oh, is that Azuma's?
So I guess it's already over.
Do ya see her corpse, huh?
You're still gonna run?
[HARU panting]
[crash]
[SHINYA]
How many times I gotta tell ya?
There's nowhere to run!
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Huh?
[SHINYA yells]
[HARU gasps]
I'm impressed you've
stayed alive this long.
I'll reward you by putting
you down with a single blow.
But I still won't die.
I promised Miss Tokaku that
I'd graduate no matter what!
Wake up, man.
Azuma's already dead.
Miss Tokaku won't die either!
She'd never die
in a game like this!
Your time's up.
[SHINYA whimpering]
[SHINYA screams]
[SHINYA sobbing]
[HARU]
Miss Toka--
[SHINYA sobbing]
[HARU gasps]
You do understand
what this means, right?
The fact that I'm here?
Tokaku Azuma is totally dead.
[HARU gasps]
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Hurry, Tokaku! There's no time!
[YOUNG TOKAKU]
Where are you taking me?
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
We're leaving this village.
Getting away from this
legacy of murder,
to the world of
broad daylight!
The world of broad daylight?
What does that mean?
It should never
have taken me so long
to get you out of here.
It's what my sister
wanted me to do.
But I was too damn weak
to make up my mind!
My mom wanted this?
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
It's all my fault.
I was her sister and I ran
from the Azuma legacy.
She had to bear
the burden on her own.
She had no choice but to fight!
Care to tell me
where you're going?
[BOTH gasp]
[TOKAKU'S GRANDMOTHER] You're
a disgrace to the Azuma name.
[YOUNG TOKAKU whimpering]
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
For... get...
[YOUNG TOKAKU gasps]
Forget it all. You have to.
None of this is your fault.
[YOUNG TOKAKU]
Auntie...
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Even if you don't remember us.
Your mom and I
will always be there.
We'll always look out for you.
[TOKAKU'S AUNT]
Watching from the shrine.
It's been you all this time.
You've been the one
calling out to me.
[TOKAKU]
You've been protecting me.
Thank you. But it's okay.
I'll be alright.
Tokaku...
[TOKAKU] I have someone
of my own to protect.
So from now on,
I'll make my own decisions.
I'll join you someday.
So please wait there for me.
Goodbye, Mother...
[TOKAKU grunting]
[TOKAKU]
Haru...
[TOKAKU grunting, panting]
[HARU whimpering]
[ISUKE]
Alright, c'mon now.
You've gotta try harder
than this to get away.
Unless you want me to kill you.
[HARU whimpers]
Jeez. What's up with you?
Don't tell me a few cuts
is all it takes
to quash that positivity.
I guess your guardian
angel "Miss Tokaku's"
early death really
took a toll on you, huh?
[ISUKE] Hey. Would it
make you feel better
if I killed you the same
way I killed her?
Spoiler alert. I tossed her out
a window and she went splat.
Way too easy, right?
It's her own fault for
being such an idiot.
She never even
would've had to die
if she hadn't bothered
protecting you.
[ISUKE laughs]
[HARU whimpering]
I think it's time
to complete this job.
[ISUKE gasps]
[HARU]
Miss... Tokaku...
[ISUKE screams]
[ISUKE grunts]
You almost made it,
Isuke. But you lose.
[ISUKE gasps]
Then kill me! Go on and try.
But we both know
you can't do it.
Wrong. I can kill now.
[TOKAKU] But. That doesn't
mean I'm going to.
[ISUKE whimpering]
[TOKAKU pants]
Are you okay?
[HARU sobs]
Tokaku!
[HARU] Tokaku! Tokaku!
[TOKAKU] Haru...
[HARU]
I thought they killed you!
That you died because of me,
and I'd never see you again!
[HARU sobbing]
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARU sobbing] Tokaku...
[HARU sobbing]
[HARU]
The rain stopped...
[TOKAKU] Yeah, we must be right
in the eye of the typhoon.
It wasn't a curse.
Huh?
For most of my life now.
I've felt like
I was suffocating,
trapped beneath the
wishes of the dead.
Like it was a burden preventing
me from living my own life.
[TOKAKU]
But I realized I was wrong.
All this time, I was
actually being protected.
[HARU gasps]
Haru. It's thanks
to you I realized that.
I wouldn't have without you.
[HARU] No matter what,
it's good to be alive.
[TOKAKU]
Yeah.
[SUMIREKO] You've all been very
courageous in your efforts.
It may seem the opposite
to the rest of the world,
but the truth is quite apparent
to me and I commend you.
Leave the rest to me
and sleep well.
You deserve the respite.
[NIO humming]
[beeps]
[NIO]
Are you serious?
Both Shinya and Isuke
have been eliminated?
That happened a lot
faster than expected.
We're finally down
to the last one.
Well this is
pretty damn exciting.
Oh, little Azuma of the East.
[KAIBA] Looks like there's
a tea party coming up.
The host is pretty high-society,
so I bet it'll be grand.
There's even a
formal dress code.
The finest tea and
every luxury imaginable.
Why don't you at least try
to enjoy yourself, Tokaku?