[phone ringing]
Hello, dear.
Is everything alright?
[ISUKE]
I know it's late, Mom,
but do you have a
quick minute to talk?
[EISUKE]
Of course.
I'm just tidying up right now.
So, what's the matter?
I expected you
to be home by now.
[EISUKE]
Here I thought
my daughter
personified punctuality.
The job's cake. It's in
the bag, It's just that...
Well, there's one
minor problem...
[EISUKE]
Really?
[ISUKE]
A real pain in my ass!
I can't decide if she's a
wolf in sheep's clothing,
or if it's just that her bark
is worse than her bite.
Well, either way, I guess
it doesn't really matter.
[EISUKE laughs]
[ISUKE]
What now?
It's funny. This is
just so unlike you.
Showing any fear at all.
[ISUKE]
I am not afraid of her!
It is through adversity
that children grow.
Although it is
a little bittersweet.
Your daddy is really missing
his baby girl, however.
So hurry home soon?
What, just Daddy?
[EISUKE] Of course,
Mommy misses you as well.
That's what I thought!
And just you wait, Mom.
I'm gonna bring home
tons of souvenirs
for you and for Daddy!
[ISUKE] Oh, hey, where would you
rather live after you retire?
Somewhere in the Alps,
or a beach in the Caribbean?
[CHAIRPERSON] This generation's
Class Black has proven itself
to be quite entertaining.
I have to say, your hard work
has truly paid off, Nio.
To think that only three
still remain. How sad.
Uh, there's four.
I'm still in there, too.
Oh, yes. That's true.
My apologies.
Eh. It's okay.
[CHAIRPERSON] Considering the
nature of Hanabusa's wish,
I don't foresee her making
a move until the very end.
The next play will then be made
by either Inukai or Banba.
Inukai desires money,
while Banba desires...?
Nada!
Oh, my! Then we're
in for quite a show.
So, any thoughts?
Haru Ichinose? Or Tokaku Azuma?
[CHAIRPERSON]
They certainly show promise.
As it stands,
there may very well rise
a new Queen Bee in the end.
But then there may not.
[NIO]
So then, you're still not sure?
[CHAIRPERSON] No. Who can say
what tomorrow will bring?
For that is the nature
of our little endeavor.
[CHAIRPERSON]
This does take me back though.
I'm reminded of my own time
as a young girl in Class Black.
How many days did it take
for you to graduate, ma'am?
Only six.
Hoo!
[CHAIRPERSON] I see
there's a storm on its way.
[HARU] It's gotten really lonely
these past few days, hasn't it?
Everywhere we go
is so quiet now.
It feels like we're
the only two here anymore.
[TOKAKU] And that's
exactly why we can bathe
without worrying now.
I'd call that a plus.
[HARU]
Jeez! That's cold.
[TOKAKU gasps]
Well! Look who's here!
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
Huh? Aw, no need to be shy...
[HARU whimpers]
Does it really look
like I'd hurt you?
[SHINYA] Must be my lucky day
to see you two at the bath.
You never really come
here much. It's such a shame.
To waste a good bath
like this one.
Then, uh, Mahi--
Shinya, you always bathe here?
You bet. Mahiru likes
'em big. Bigger is better.
[SHINYA] You know,
come to think of it,
Nio and Sumireko haven't
used this bath yet either.
Maybe they've also
got scars to hide.
What do you think?
[SHINYA laughs]
Oh man!
Mahiru has been
busting my ass lately!
I've been telling her she
needs to back off and relax.
[HARU]
Why? What's wrong?
You see, she'd been locked up
for a long time as a kid.
She never did nothing like go
to school and stuff like that.
So I was hoping she'd
get the most outta this
while she still could, you know?
[SHINYA] This is really
her first time to do
something normal
in life for a change.
But, hell. She might
have a point. It's time.
Okay! Night, night,
girls! Sweet dreams!
The next fight's
with her. Watch.
[HARU gasps]
[TOKAKU]
That's just how it is now.
[HARU]
Yeah, but...
[TOKAKU]
There're only three left.
But once we've dealt with them,
it'll be all over and done with.
Isn't it your dream,
living long enough
to graduate from Class Black?
[HARU]
What about you?
Huh?
Once we've graduated from here,
what are you going to do?
[TOKAKU gasps]
Let's go to bed.
[SHINYA] I really hate
seeing you like this.
After all, the whole
reason that I'm even here
is to make you smile.
[MAHIRU]
I want it. My trophy.
I have it already, but it
doesn't mean anything yet.
My trophy. I want my trophy!
I want it. I want it now!
It needs value! Please, hurry!
Please!
[SHINYA]
Alright. I've heard enough.
[MAHIRU gasps]
You've been real
patient all this time.
Well then. Like always?
[SHINYA]
You just leave everything to me.
[MAHIRU sighs]
[SUMIREKO]
Miss Shinya?
[SHINYA gasps]
[SUMIREKO] I just brewed
a fresh pot of tea.
Would you care
for a cup with me?
[SHINYA]
Yeah, sure.
My, what a surprise
this is! You've declined
all of my previous
invitations without fail.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
[SUMIREKO] It would
appear that the typhoon
is quickly approaching. Landfall
is likely tomorrow afternoon.
[SHINYA] That's cool.
It'll make my party kickass.
Ah. We're toasting
in your honor tonight.
Doesn't have to be
just my honor.
Parties are more fun when more
people show up to 'em, right?
Yes, but I...
[SUMIREKO gasps]
Right. You wouldn't get nothing
doing it that way, would ya?
But, there's no way I'm gonna
let that hold me back.
Um. My bad! I guess.
Sometimes I just don't
know my own strength.
Please think nothing of it.
[SUMIREKO] Everything is
destined for ruin in the end.
Thank goodness for free
nights and weekends, huh?
Your family must
be close if they're
taking your calls this late.
[ISUKE]
Of course they are.
After all, I am
their only daughter.
And such a devoted one.
Who'd have guessed?
You're parents sure
are lucky to have you!
But you can't really
pick your family, huh?
You said you wanna build
them a vacation home,
isn't that right?
[NIO] Oh, by the way, there's a
typhoon coming straight for us.
I'm kinda excited
about it, truth be told.
The big ones really get
the blood pumpin', you know!
It's like mother nature herself
is giving you a private show
from the safety of
your very own room.
[ISUKE]
So we're clear...
Hm?
Just because you bastards
have something planned,
doesn't mean it's gonna happen.
[NIO sighs]
[NIO laughs]
[MIZOROGI] As I'm sure
you're all aware, in nature,
all wildlife maintain various
relationships with one another
in order to coexist
as a population.
One such instance
of this is territoriality,
as exhibited by the sweetfish.
These guys lay claim to
territory within the river,
which thus enables them
to secure food and attack
any other predators that may
potentially invade their space.
It is because of this
behavior that sweetfish
decoy fishing is possible.
This process...
[HARU]
What about you?
Huh?
Once we've graduated from here,
what are you going to do?
[TOKAKU] I'm sure Haru
will return to the world
of broad daylight
after graduation.
[TOKAKU]
But, what about me?
Where will I return to?
[bell rings]
Alright, well that's
gonna be it for today!
You all be mindful
of the typhoon now.
Head straight
for your dormitory,
and don't make any
detours along the way.
[ISUKE grunting]
[NIO]
Haru!
Wanna get ice cream
with me on the way back?
I know a place that gives 30%
off when there's a typhoon!
But, Mr. Mizorogi said
we should all hurry back.
Oh come on, girl!
I live for these days!
The wind, the rain,
you gotta embrace the danger
with open arms!
[NIO]
I just had a great idea!
We're gonna test your might!
[HARU]
Wait, what?
[NIO] Out smack dab
in the middle of the storm,
with only a flashlight
and a raincoat.
It'll be fun!
And I know the perfect
spot for our little game!
It used to be this
creepy cemetery,
but then they tore it down
so they could build this huge--
You can play your
game on your own.
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku...
Oh, don't tell me
the great Azuma
is too afraid to play. You sure
do have a good poker face.
But there's always a
chance that this storm
is the manifestation of rage
from all of those
you've put away!
Don't make me laugh.
Hey! The occult is no joke, man!
After all, it does
totally exist.
So you had better be
on the look out...
...for the curses
of vengeful spirits!
[HARU whimpers]
[TOKAKU sighs
We'll pass, sorry, Nio.
We'll have to do it
some other time.
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku!
You guys suck!
[TOKAKU]
Honestly. Curses, my ass.
That chick seriously
needs a reality check.
That's just who Nio is.
Let's try to get back
before it rains.
You just leave the rain to me
and my old, trusty umbrella!
There's no way
that thing doesn't rip.
Hey, it's...
it's not that bad right now!
[TOKAKU, HARU panting]
The sun still hasn't set yet.
But once it does, that's
when Shinya will awaken.
Things are gonna get bad fast.
[TOKAKU] At least the typhoon
gives us an excuse
to lock ourselves in our room.
Good point. But you're
getting yourself soaked.
I'll be fine.
[ISUKE] Wow, it's really
coming down, huh?
Yeah, but, Isuke,
you're completely dry!
I sure am.
[TOKAKU]
Look out!
[HARU gasps]
[ISUKE gasps]
Nice moves!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARU gasps]
You're bleeding!
[ISUKE]
I'm impressed you noticed.
[TOKAKU]
You smell like filth.
You didn't give
an advanced notice.
You broke the rules.
Yeah, right. You can't
tell me you didn't get it.
[TOKAKU, HARU gasp]
[ISUKE gasps]
[TOKAKU]
Let's go!
[ISUKE laughs]
Blinding your opponent
and then running?
That's just pathetic!
Seriously! She's such a joke!
[ISUKE laughing]
It's hilarious.
My name is Eisuke Inukai.
Little one, your name
is now Isuke Inukai.
From here on out,
I will be your parent.
Do you understand?
[EISUKE]
You're going to be okay.
I know.
I get that that person was your
parent, but that doesn't change
the fact that they would
have left you to die.
So I really had no other choice.
[EISUKE]
Now, let's get going.
You don't wanna be here.
Come on. I'll keep
you close to me.
You can help me if you want.
Be Mommy's little helper. And
then, follow in my footsteps.
[YOUNG ISUKE]
Your footsteps?
That's right.
My work is very important,
being a professional assassin.
Being a killer for a living.
[ISUKE] Just wait
for me a little longer.
Please, Mom.
I promise you that
Mommy's little helper
will be coming home really soon.
[TOKAKU, HARU panting]
[TOKAKU]
That notice you got earlier
wasn't from Banba at all.
It really came from Isuke.
Nowhere in the rules
does it state that you can't
write down someone else's name.
Damn it.
Miss Tokaku! Your arm
won't stop bleeding!
And now we can't go back
to the dorms either.
Who knows what other
kinds of traps
she's got set up for us there.
Okay. Let me help you.
[TOKAKU]
It's gotta be tighter!
[HARU]
Right.
[TOKAKU grunts]
[HARU whimpers]
[HARU]
Well, how's that?
Let me see your cell phone.
O-Okay...
[TOKAKU] If anything happens,
text me right away.
Otherwise, you just
stay here where it's safe.
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku?
[TOKAKU] Don't worry,
I'll take down Isuke.
How can you say that
with that injury?
Why won't you let me help you?
You'd get in my way!
[HARU gasps]
[glass shatters]
[TOKAKU]
Even in that split second,
I could still see her movements.
So then, how did she
manage to cut me?
She read my attack. But how?
So now you had better
be on the look out...
...for the deadly curses
of vengeful spirits!
[TOKAKU]
Curses?
[TOKAKU gasps, groans]
[ISUKE] You know, I find it
kind of hard to be frightened
when I know that your
attacks have no chance
of actually killing me.
[TOKAKU gasps]
Kill shots? You avoid
them unconsciously.
You won't strike anywhere
that'd make a fatal wound.
'Cause you know that if you did,
you'd freeze on the spot.
[TOKAKU gasps]
Tch!
[ISUKE laughs]
It's so ridiculous!
You've got everybody
on edge just because
you're a great
and powerful Azuma.
None of them suspect
for even a second
that you're actually a virgin.
Just imagine the
looks on their faces
if they ever
found out the truth!
[ISUKE laughs]
When you're ready.
Prove me wrong, you bitch.
Miss Tokaku...
[knocking, banging]
[HARU gasps]
[SHINYA]
What's up, Haru?
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Absolutely perfect for a party.
Sorry about the wait.
Welcome to die!
Huh?
Hm. Well, it sounds like
the main even has just begun.
[TOKAKU]
Say what?
I really wouldn't have
guessed it myself,
but it seems she's
pretty punctual, too.
That Banba...
[KAIBA]
Well, Tokaku. It would appear
you've brilliantly
chosen the gate to Hell.
But truth be told,
that's where both gates
have been leading all along.
I thought you'd have
caught on by now.
There's no chance the
path you're on is ever
going to take you to Heaven.