[SUZU grunts]
[SUZU]
Dawn brings yet another day.
So many.
So many days.
[MIZOROGI]
Well, girls.
I'm pleased to say
that the Annual Festival
was an incredible success.
And Romeo and Juliet
went over like gangbusters!
You had your teacher crying
like a baby by the end.
Nevertheless! You may have
noticed more vacant desks
in the classroom today.
Yes, we've had more
unexpected transfers.
You can't let that
get you down though.
Believe me, I miss them
as much as anyone.
But the seven of you gotta
do your best to stay strong!
Poor naïve teacher.
Always cheerful. Unflappably so.
I cannot stand
people that happy.
It makes me feel sick.
Well, who else could work here?
I bet they hired him 'cause he's
so super positive, you know?
It's all gonna be
okay, Miss Tokaku.
We just have to
stay strong, right?
Like Mr. Mizorogi said.
[ISUKE]
Your blind optimism is pathetic.
I can't stand it. Makes me
wanna smash your face.
[TOKAKU grunts]
[ISUKE] Ooh, I'm so scared!
[SUZU] Alright,
[SUZU] calm down everybody!
[ISUKE] What?
[ISUKE]
Let's not fight over nothing.
We're just tense that's all.
I think now's a good time
to take a little breather.
A breather?
[SUZU]
That's right.
I stumbled upon
something wonderful.
So after class, what do you say
we all go and take a look?
[GIRLS giggling, gasping]
[ISUKE] That's Myojo
Private School for you.
Even got their own water park!
[NIO] Duh! We've also got an
Olympic sized pool for classes.
[SUZU] I had time reserved
exclusively for Class Black.
After the festival, I think
we've earned a little R and R.
Don't you?
And of course,
we have swimsuits too.
Thank you so much!
It's incredible!
C'mon Miss Tokaku,
let's go hurry up and change!
[TOKAKU]
Uh... Hold on!
Well. C'mon, ladies,
what are you waiting for?
A school swimsuit?
[SUMIREKO] Don't tell me they
expect us to wear that swimsuit.
[ISUKE]
So lame.
They think we're just a bunch
of toddlers, don't they?
If you're not a fan of the
school's designated swimwear,
well then, we have
more choices for you!
Pick whatever you like!
Um, do you intend on
going scuba diving, Nio?
[NIO] No way! I was going
for more of a bondage vibe!
[SUMIREKO]
Okay. I've made my selection.
Honestly. I think I like regular
old swimsuits the best.
What do you think?
Oh, my. Isn't that daring...
Something might even fall out!
She's got nothing there.
So there's nothing to fall out.
This one exposes too much skin.
It won't do.
It offers no protection.
A normal athletic swimsuit's
the practical choice.
[HARU]
The game?
[HARU gasps]
Hey, what are you doing?
Try to stay calm.
It'll explode if you attempt
to remove it by force.
It's a bomb?
[SUZU]
Correct.
A very small one, yes,
but that's all I need.
If it detonates while it's
strapped around her neck,
then she dies instantly.
I can't rely solely
on my physical strength,
so I intend to win through
this little game of mine.
The bomb is set to go off
at precisely midnight tonight.
If you fail to diffuse
it before then...
Well then, I win.
I'm gonna kill you!
I suppose you could
but you should know
that killing me won't save her.
You see Azuma, there's just
one way to disable the device.
[SUZU] You must enter
the 4 digit passcode.
Simple as that.
I'll even give you three tries
out of the kindness of my heart.
But if you get it
wrong all three times...
Oh my! Bye-bye!
You had better
tell me that passcode!
But figuring it out
yourself is the game. Look.
There are four cards,
each representing one digit
of the passcode,
hidden here in the park.
Find all four and
you've got the passcode.
To make it fun, included
with the advanced notice
are hints to their whereabouts.
[SUZU giggles] I just love
a good riddle. Don't you?
Well, what do you say we all
go enjoy this game together?
[TOKAKU]
Don't worry, it'll be alright.
We'll find the code and
get that thing off you.
Miss Tokaku...
"One card is in the forest."
[HARU]
Is that it over there?
[TOKAKU] It's the only
forest around I can see.
[HARU]
"One card is in the water."
I'm guessing that probably
means it's in the pool.
Go ahead and jump
on in if you like.
I wouldn't think of keeping
you from taking a dip.
That collar of yours
is water proof.
So don't you worry, the device
will still detonate under water.
[ISUKE] With all of
the rules they gave us
and the advanced notices,
Class Black was sort of
a game already.
Did she have to go and
literally make it a game?
[NIO] Bloody battle after
bloody battle just gets boring
after a while,
so I think it's super cool
to change it up this way.
Well, I'm starting to wonder
if Class Black's sponsors
actually want Haru dead.
You know something
we don't, don't you?
No... What could
I possibly know?
Whether or not it's all
some strange test, maybe?
C'mon, I know you can tell me
what the end game is here.
I don't know.
So you just gonna
sit around and talk?
You do realize that
if this kills Haru,
Class Black's game is over.
[SUMIREKO] If it ends like this,
then it wasn't worth playing
to begin with.
I, for one, prefer
a higher caliber sport.
For the moment,
though, let's relax
and observe from where we are.
Here. Please help
yourself to one of these.
Uh, thank you.
Man, this is nice!
It's almost like
we're at a resort!
Who's up for a game of
split the watermelon?
Anybody?
I just happen to have a
perfect watermelon right here.
My, how delightful.
Assassins engaging
in party games?
I do hope you'll
allow each one of us
to use our weapon of choice.
[NIO] Uh, just to be clear, do
you wanna do this blindfolded?
Because that sounds
ridiculously dangerous.
[SUMIREKO]
Well, of course blindfolded.
You'll find that it
won't be necessary
to guide me to the melon.
You can trust me on this,
my bullets will naturally
find their target.
[NIO]
Oh, c'mon!
That's not
"split-the-watermelon"!
That's "blast-the-watermelon
to smithereens!
[HARU]
What is it, Miss Tokaku?
[TOKAKU]
"One card is hidden in the dark
and only voices will
guide you there".
I think I know
where that card is.
[NIO gasps]
Alright, I found one card.
The 7 of diamonds.
Hey, bravo, you found it!
[HARU] That was so amazing!
How did you know?
[sighs] Were this task mine
alone, I would have already
identified all four cards,
and with much less drama.
Are you saying you know
where the other cards are too?
But of course.
The solution is
honestly all too easy.
[MAHIRU]
The cards. The remainder.
Mahiru, I take it that you've
figured it out as well?
How brilliant you are.
The remainder? Of what?
Oh. Hot on the trail?
Assuming all four cards used
were drawn from this same deck,
we don't have to find any
of your hiding places.
We just have to see which cards
are missing from the deck
to know the four digits.
Oh, I get it! That's so cool!
[HARU]
Four sevens missing.
So, the passcode
is just four sevens?
You can't be serious,
that's so easy!
That combination
might be the worst
possible passcode in history!
[SUZU giggles]
Okay, so now what will you do?
It's time. Now.
[HARU gasps]
Here goes.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[SUZU]
Oh no, what could've happened?
Oh right, I remember,
I set up that deck
to throw you off track.
And that made you waste
an attempt to boot.
You've only got two left now.
You better be careful!
Damn!
[MIZOROGI] If I want to prevent
any more sudden transfers.
I've got to take care of
my students any way I can.
No way. These two
have no family.
Maybe if we stay away from
conversations about home life,
they'll feel more comfortable.
[MIZOROGI gasps]
This is...
[TOKAKU]
The sun is setting.
[SHINYA]
And that means...
it's time for me
to come out and play!
[ISUKE]
Show up if you want
but there's really
nothing for you to do.
Not to mention, that swimsuit is
not a fit for your personality.
Just shut your trap already!
Mahiru has always wanted
to swim in a school swimsuit.
Let's go!
[SHINYA laughs]
So she had that prepared
the entire time.
Now that's forward thinking.
[SUZU] Okay ladies,
we still have quite some time
until we reach the
midnight deadline.
You should enjoy
yourselves until then.
[NIO] Check out our
awesome mood lighting!
"One card's in the light.
Before it becomes
too bright to see"
You think it's up
there with the lights?
Miss Tokaku! There!
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU grunts]
The second card.
[HARU]
A joker?
I almost forgot to mention.
In our case a joker stands
for the number zero.
[TOKAKU]
A seven and a zero.
[SUZU] I must admit,
you're doing very well.
Only two cards left.
[HARU]
"One card is in the forest.
In the best place to hide it.
One card is in the water.
In exchange for
something you care about."
Alright then.
There's the forest.
And there's the water.
So what's the best place?
Well, if you wanna hide a leaf,
the best place to
do it is the forest.
[TOKAKU] Yeah, but what we're
looking for isn't a leaf.
It's a card.
[HARU]
Where are you going?
[SUZU]
What are you doing?
You looked through those
cards earlier, remember?
I told you before
they're a red herring.
I found it!
The ace of spades.
[SUZU]
Nicely done.
So the remaining card
is in the water.
"In exchange for
something you care about."
I care about?
[bang]
[TOKAKU gasps]
Ichinose!
Whoa! Was that the explosion?
Happy Birthday, Shuto! Woo!
[ISUKE]
It's her birthday today?
[MIZOROGI]
You should have told us.
Then maybe we could've
planned a special party
for you or something.
It's not much.
But it's the best
I could come up with.
Hope you like flowers.
Sorry, sir. Technically,
men aren't allowed in here.
[MIZOROGI]
Uh!
[ISUKE] Oh! Was the birthday
magic trick just an excuse
to come and sneak a peep, teach?
Clever, Mr. Mizorogi.
That is ridiculous!
What are you talking about?
[SHINYA] Listen up,
you dirty old pervert.
Get lost, or else!
Hang on, Banba. Just relax.
There's no reason
for you to threaten me.
[MIZOROGI]
Hey! No! Stay back!
I just wanted to come
celebrate Shuto's birthday!
Is today seriously
your birthday?
I suppose.
[NIO]
Well, Happy Birthday then!
Oh, if you complete the
mission today the reward
will make the perfect
birthday present won't it?
It would actually be
a dream come true.
[NIO]
So what do you want anyway?
I haven't even
checked in with you yet.
My one and only wish
is to finally grow old,
and eventually die.
[NIO] Uh, what's that
supposed to mean?
[SUZU] My body is being
held hostage by a disease.
An illness that
prevents me from aging.
[NIO] I think I've
heard about this.
Oh yeah. It's called
Highlander Syndrome, isn't it?
It actually sounds
kind of awesome
because you'd get to
stay young forever!
[SUZU] Does that really
sound so appealing?
[NIO gasps]
Time always marches forward.
And I'm always left behind.
You see, I once
cared for someone.
[SUZU]
He...
He was only one year
younger than me.
And my birthday was
the day before his.
But before he could
catch up to my age,
my birthday would come
and I'd be another year
ahead of him again.
We used to joke and laugh
with one another about
how we would never
be the same age.
Before long, he grew into
a man right before my eyes.
And it became painfully clear
to me that I would never
grow out of this child's body.
He had outpaced me.
And in time, he disappeared
from my life to be with another.
[SUZU]
And so, my wish is to grow old.
To age normally and die
like everyone else.
[NIO]
Roger that.
We'll put together a team of
the best doctors and scientists
from around the world and
they'll tackle the problem
in no time at all.
Very good.
[HARU]
Miss Shuto...
[KAIBA]
There are only a handful left.
So why do you keep
dragging your feet?
Hm, Tokaku?
Here's the next riddle.
And if you don't answer
it soon, then someone else
is gonna beat you to the punch.
[phone vibrating]
[TOKAKU] Alright.
"One card's in the water."
Where is it?
[HARU]
In the water.
[TOKAKU]
Does this count as water?
No, it doesn't freakin' count!
Hurry up guys!
You're running out of time!
Are you gonna let her
explode in front of everyone?
[NIO giggles]
[TOKAKU]
In the water.
What does, "in exchange for
something you care about" mean?
[TOKAKU]
How could I have missed that?
There's water flowing top to
bottom through those slides!
Wha--?
Miss Tokaku!
[TOKAKU]
Damn it!
What's that? A key card?
Will it open the cage?
That's the fourth card.
Wait...
[TOKAKU]
"One card is in the water.
In exchange for
something you care about."
If I use this, I'll be saved.
But in exchange,
the card will be lost.
I have to sacrifice myself
in order to save her.
[TOKAKU] Ichinose! I've
gotta get her this card!
[TOKAKU]
No. Please don't do it.
[inaudible]
[TOKAKU gasping]
Made it! Are you alright?
I'm fine. But now we've
lost the fourth card.
And we're outta time.
[TOKAKU] We know three
of the four numbers.
Seven, zero, and one.
We have no choice now but
to guess the last number.
And there's yet another problem.
Even if you do
know all the digits,
you still don't know
which order to enter them.
Just leave it to me you guys!
I like to switch it up, but
today, my lucky number is nine.
You idiot!
That leaves only
one attempt left.
And I gotta think fast here.
We've got zero, seven, and one.
What's the last digit?
[TOKAKU gasps]
Happy Birthday Shuto! Woo!
[TOKAKU] It's her birthday.
Today is July 14th.
The passcode has to be
zero, seven, one, four.
She used her birthday?
That's like at the top
of the list of things not to
use for your password.
Have you got any better ideas?
We're just gonna
have to gamble on it.
[HARU]
Wait, Miss Tokaku!
[SUZU] You see,
I once cared for someone.
And my birthday was
the day before his.
Don't you remember
the gentleman in the story
Shuto was telling us.
She mentioned that his birthday
was the day after hers.
The way she talked about him,
I don't think the number
is her birthday.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU sighs]
[HARU]
Miss Tokaku!
You saved me.
[SUZU] His birthday
has come once again.
I have to hand it to you.
You're quite observant, Haru.
[HARU]
I guess so.
I can admit when I've lost.
[NIO]
Wait, Shuto.
[SUZU]
Hm?
How about it. You wanna tell
us how old you really are?
No one knows.
Not even me anymore.
[KAIBA] One gate to Heaven
and one gate to Hell.
And before them,
stand two gatekeepers.
One speaks only truth,
while the other, only lies.
You have just one chance
to get into heaven.
To pick the right gate,
what question do you ask?