[MIZOROGI] When it comes
to creatures that naturally
form highly organized societies,
there's no better
example than bees.
Take the queen bee.
She uses what's known
as the primer pheromone,
a pheromone that
only she produces,
in order to assume leadership
of the worker bees.
This shuts off their
reproductive functions
and lets her assign them tasks
like defending the hive.
In order to protect the hive
from their enemies,
honeybee workers will
go so far as to endanger
their own lives
during an attack.
Of course, they take some losses
as a result. But that sacrifice
is part of their instinct
to protect the group.
[MIZOROGI sighs]
[HARU]
Mr. Mizorogi?
[MIZOROGI gasps]
Oh, sorry.
I just got lost
in thought there.
[MIZOROGI] I want you all
to know you can count on me.
I'll teach this class
to the very end.
That's the one
promise I can make
as your homeroom teacher.
It's my job and I will do it.
[NIO] I just can't help but
feel bad for everything
we've put Mr. Mizorogi through.
I hope he gets to teach a normal
class next time, don't you?
[NIO] But forget about
that for a moment.
This is an
official announcement.
Tonight at midnight,
meet me in the tower
in classroom 1908 for the
real Class Black orientation.
If you wanna know the truth
about why we're all here,
I suggest you participate.
[HARU gasps]
[TOKAKU gasps]
Oh, but then again.
You already know the reason,
don't you, Haru?
That's all! This announcement
brought to you by Nio Hashiri!
Hey, um, Tokaku?
[TOKAKU]
What is it?
[HARU] Well, you see,
you know that stuff
we were talking
about the other day?
What Sumireko said?
[TOKAKU] What about all
those things Hanabusa said?
The queen bee? What was
she talking about?
[NIO]
What the hell are you thinking?
Talking about that
stuff in the open?
[NIO] I said everything will be
explained tonight, didn't I?
Try exercising a
little bit of patience.
There's no point
in spoiling the fun.
You've won already.
We've won?
[NIO] Did you forget that
you beat everyone else?
Tokaku sure did
risk her life enough.
I'm done eating.
[TOKAKU]
Take all the time you need.
There's nobody
left to attack you.
[SUMIREKO laughs]
How sad.
You don't even realize that's
the power of the queen bee.
[TOKAKU]
The queen bee?
The worker bee and the rabbit?
What the two have in common
is that they are willing
to give up their lives
to protect the leader.
[TOKAKU] She was just
messing with my head.
So why the hell am I
letting it get to me?
[NIO] Well then.
I'm sure the chairperson
will put a nice,
pretty bow on all this.
And you're related
to her, aren't you?
[HARU] I've never
actually met her before.
In fact, I've had
almost no contact
with other members of our clan.
All told, my life
has been pretty normal.
Girl, don't give me that!
There's nothing normal
about living with
a target on your back.
[HARU gasps]
[NIO]
Sorry, that was going too far.
[HARU]
All you did was say the truth.
I guess I'm not.
[NIO]
But you could be normal.
Because unlike us...
You don't actually
belong in here.
You belong out there in
the world of broad daylight.
[HARU]
Hey, Tokaku!
Sorry I'm running a little late.
[TOKAKU]
Come on.
[NIO] Now that the two of
you are here we can begin
the true orientation!
There's just one more
thing before we dig in.
A word from the
school chairperson,
Miss Meichi Yuri,
the sponsor of Class Black!
[BOTH grunt]
Pleasure to meet you,
Miss Azuma and Miss Ichinose.
I'm the chairperson
of Myojo. Call me Yuri.
[CHAIRPERSON]
You've both done a brilliant job
of overcoming Class Black.
So please accept this brief but
sincere offer of felicitation.
Congratulations.
Thank you, that's
very kind of you.
That's enough already.
[TOKAKU]
You're gonna explain, right?
What Class Black
is actually about?
Why did you assemble
all of us at this school?
And why did you put us
through this hellish game?
Just who are you people
and what do you want?
[CHAIRPERSON] Do you know
what a ritual initiation is?
It's a test to measure
the worth of an individual.
They're typically put
through this grueling ordeal
once they reach a certain age.
Our clan, specifically, requires
the girls of our lineage
to undergo such a trial
when they turn 15 years old.
It's rather apparent
what you're thinking.
And you're right, Miss Azuma.
The sole purpose
of Class Black was not
to murder Haru as you were told.
No, in actuality, the sole
purpose was to pit Haru
against 12 assassins to see
if she could survive.
[TOKAKU gasps]
It was all devised
to see if Haru
has what it takes to carry
the torch, to lead our clan.
[TOKAKU]
Your clan?
[CHAIRPERSON]
Yes.
A vast network of
families whose lineages
trace back to one bloodline.
[CHAIRPERSON] We reside in
all corners of the world,
and we are responsible
for everything that happens.
In politics, in finance,
military affairs,
education, culture, the arts.
Our hand guides
the course of history,
manipulating all matters
of power and influence.
And the one who unifies
our clan is the Primer.
She possesses a rare trait,
a kind of magnetism,
that's unique to
the women of our clan.
Whether they're
willfully acting upon it,
or it's an unintentional
and unconscious action,
these women draw people
to them only to charm them,
control them,
and manipulate them.
The more danger a Primer faces,
the stronger this
influence becomes.
And the more refined it grows.
And that's why the girls of our
clan are continually targeted
for death from the very
moment they are born.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[CHAIRPERSON] Haru has proven
herself to possess great power,
and she beautifully passed
the initiation of Class Black.
She's certain to become
an ideal Primer.
[TOKAKU]
She manipulates people?
[CHAIRPERSON]
Correct.
Although I couldn't honestly
say whether she did it
intentionally or not with you.
[CHAIRPERSON]
So that moment.
When you chose to step
forward and declare yourself
as Haru's guardian?
That was wholly
unsurprising to us.
It was actually
somewhat expected.
[TOKAKU gasps]
You're wrong!
Hm?
I don't have any
kind of powers at all!
I came here 'cause they
said if I went through this,
it would be all over!
They said I would
get to live a normal life!
So all this, this stuff
about controlling people,
it's just not possible!
Then tell me,
if you genuinely lack
these powers of persuasion,
how were you able to survive
against 12 highly trained
and motivated assassins?
You can't deny that many
people have died for you.
Willingly sacrificing their
lives in exchange for yours.
The people at the orphanage
who raised you as a child.
The hospital staff.
Close neighbors.
And of course your family.
[HARU gasps]
And I know they were
all happy to do it.
Giving up their lives for you
was a privilege to each of them.
No! Stop!
[CHAIRPERSON] You stand here
today after every attempt
that's been made on your life.
What further proof do you
need that you're special?
[HARU]
Stop saying that!
That's not me!
I'm not like that!
[NIO]
Wait, Haru!
[CHAIRPERSON]
No, Nio, leave her be.
She needs some time alone
to think things through.
Deep down, I'm sure
that she knows we're right.
As for you, Miss Azuma.
What is it that you most
desire in this world?
Desire?
[CHAIRPERSON] Haru wouldn't
have won without you
clearing the path for her.
So we acknowledge you as a
winner of Class Black as well.
Simply name your reward
and I'll have it prepared.
Congratulations.
There's no need to give
me an answer now.
You have plenty
of time to decide,
but make sure you
think it over carefully.
[NIO]
There you have it.
That concludes the
orientation. Thank you.
[HARU]
I'd heard all the stories.
I knew that special
people like that existed,
but I never thought
it would have anything
to do with me.
I mean, even in our clan,
my family was always
on the outskirts, like we
didn't even matter to anyone.
So there's just no way
that I could ever
have the ability
to rule the clan.
It's impossible. At least,
that's what I thought.
[TOKAKU]
You heard her.
She said the Primer
can exert itself
without you even
being conscious of it.
And it only gets stronger
the more danger you're in.
So...
Do you...
Are you saying that I
manipulated everyone
in Class Black to go easy
on me? That's ridiculous!
[TOKAKU] You didn't have
to manipulate everyone.
You just need control over one
person to make her protect you.
[HARU gasps]
If you don't want
me to believe that,
then prove me wrong.
But I...
I just didn't want you...
I just couldn't stand the
idea of us being enemies.
That's all.
[TOKAKU] So basically, you're
saying that you can't prove it?
[HARU]
Tokaku!
[KAIBA] I've been given the
details of what transpired.
A job well done.
I suppose this calls
for a celebration.
Congratulations on
winning Class Black.
[TOKAKU]
You knew, didn't you?
[KAIBA]
Hm?
[TOKAKU]
The true purpose of Class Black.
About the clan behind it
and about the Primer.
[KAIBA laughs]
Ah, Tokaku.
What's the point of
even asking me that?
[TOKAKU gasps]
If I were to tell you,
here and now.
"Why yes, I knew from
the very beginning".
What difference would that make?
What would it change for you?
[KAIBA]
Aw, man.
This is why I hate
dealing with kids.
Just hurry and wise up already.
You know all those riddles
I kept sending you?
You do realize there's no
correct answer to them, right?
[TOKAKU gasps]
The only answers
that matter, Tokaku,
are the ones that
come from inside you.
So dig 'em up and
take a close look.
Strain your fledgling brain
and figure out who you are.
Oh, don't get me wrong,
I am still gonna
grade you on them.
Just 'cuz you're in
Class Black doesn't mean
I'm not your teacher.
[knocking]
What do you want?
You know how late it is?
I need to speak with Yuri.
And in person.
[KOUKO]
I want out! I can't take it!
I don't want this anymore!
[SUZU] His birthday
has come once again...
[CHITARU] I'm sorry that
I never understood you,
that I only saw what
I wanted to see.
[HARUKI] There's only one way
out of this hellish game
for her, and that's to die.
[ISUKE] You realize
this is all your fault.
If you'd been able
to kill me before,
we wouldn't even be
in this situation.
[HARU sobbing]
Tokaku! Tokaku! Tokaku!
[TOKAKU]
I can't figure out why I did it.
Did I genuinely
want to protect Haru
or was she controlling me?
How can I prove
the real reason?
This is just another riddle.
Another damn riddle that
no one has the answer to.
[TOKAKU]
Tch!
[HARU] I've made up my mind
and I'm not joining the clan.
I know for a fact that
I don't have the power
to control people.
The only thing I want
is to live a normal life
away from all of this killing,
just like my family wanted
for me before they died.
[CHAIRPERSON] And are you
certain that that's your answer?
Yes, I am.
Do you honestly believe
that all of the people
who sacrificed themselves
so you could live
would be content
with that decision?
[HARU gasps]
Don't ask me that.
[CHAIRPERSON]
Haru, if you'll indulge me,
there's something
I feel you should see.
Please, Nio. You know
what I'm referring to.
Would you show
Haru the way there?
[HARU]
This goes really deep.
[NIO]
You'll understand why.
Only members of the clan
can enter past this point.
[NIO]
This is the cemetery.
Each and every person
enshrined here has given
their life in
deference to the clan.
Of course, it's not like there
are bones or bodies buried here.
This is only a
cemetery of names.
Our departed are engraved
here so that their loyalty
and sacrifice will
never be forgotten.
This was originally
an actual burial ground.
Myojo Private School
was later built in its place.
But why?
The one thing you can
always find in a school
is the laughter of children.
To console the souls of
the dead with the voices
of children living
on into the future.
"As our gift to you,
we will never cry.
Behold. Unto eternity.
As we carry on to
prevail in this world."
[NIO]
I know how lonely it must be.
Having been born with
a power such as yours,
this kind of life is
the only choice you have.
Haru, I get it.
I was all alone
in this world too.
Though someone cared
enough to save me.
And that was the chairperson.
Wait, Yuri did?
It's not uncommon for
the clan to use its power
to save people as well.
Please remember that, Haru.
Okay?
[NIO] Take some time to think
things over by yourself.
I'll come find you
in a little while.
[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
Dad. Mom. Big brother. Wataru.
[HARU'S FAMILY laughing]
[HARU'S FAMILY]
Happy birthday, Haru!
[YOUNG HARU]
Thank you!
[HARU'S MOTHER]
No, thank you for being born!
Haru, we couldn't
be more fortunate
to have you in our lives.
[YOUNG HARU giggling]
[HARU]
Mom, I miss you.
Did you give your life
to protect me
because you really loved me?
Or was it because I made you?
[HARU sobbing]
[HARU gasps]
Is everything okay?
[TOKAKU]
I've been doing some thinking.
Wondering if there's
a reason you and I met,
and what that reason could be.
Back before I met you,
I simply followed
whatever order I was given.
I was nothing more
than a puppet.
Things I cared about,
a purpose in life,
I didn't have that stuff.
And I wasn't even aware of the
fact that I didn't have them.
But then I met you.
And you showed them to me.
You taught me how
to actually live.
It's as if every day of my life
has been leading me to this day,
to this moment,
right here with you.
[HARU]
Tokaku...
So thank you, Haru.
Thank you for everything, I am
truly fortunate to have met you.
[HARU sobs]
But that's the reason why...
...I have no choice
but to do this.
[HARU gasps]
[KAIBA]
You finally get it, right?
Everything that comes out of
my mouth is a load of bullshit.
And there are
no correct answers.
So go ahead! Wield your
blade as you see fit.
That seems to be the only answer
you've arrived at
on your own in Class Black.