[GIRLS panting, grunting]
[STUDENT 1A grunting]
[STUDENT 1A groans]
[STUDENT 1B groans]
[STUDENT 1C gasps]
[STUDENT 1D groans]
[STUDENT 1A grunts]
None of you will
make it home alive
if you give up this easily!
[INSTRUCTOR 1A]
It's kill or be killed!
No target will just lie down
and let you assassinate them!
They will fight for their
lives and resist you
until they are dead!
Eradicate their life.
That is the only way to
neutralize their efforts!
And that is your job!
[INSTRUCTOR 1A grunts]
[INSTRUCTOR 1A groans]
[whistle blows]
[INSTRUCTOR 1B]
That completes the training!
We have one fit candidate!
Tokaku Azuma!
[KAIBA]
Tokaku Ahzuma. How perfect.
Year 10. Class Black.
You were practically
raised in this dark,
little world of ours, so you
must have at least heard of it.
You'll soon be transferred
to Class Black. Your objective
is to kill the designated
target before anyone else.
The target will be
another high school girl
chosen for ulterior reasons.
As for the rest
of your carefully
handpicked classmates...
...they'll also be assassins!
Their backgrounds run the gamut.
Some are trained
professionals like yourself,
some of them just find murder
to be an act of pleasure.
The student to complete the
assignment will be rewarded
with anything they
could wish for.
Money, power,
whatever you can think of.
So, Tokaku.
Just what is it you most want?
Nothing.
[TOKAKU]
I have nothing to distract me.
[TOKAKU] My only concern
is to kill what must be killed.
[TOKAKU]
Hm?
[phone rings]
[TOKAKU]
Yes?
[KAIBA] Got an answer
off the top of your head?
[TOKAKU] Torment.
[KAIBA] Bzzz! Wrong answer!
Torment? You're one
morbid bitch, huh?
Is that the only
reason you're calling?
[KAIBA]
No.
Y'know how I told you
you're getting transferred
'cuz you're the
most apt student?
Well, that was
a load of bullshit.
I simply chose the most
psychologically damaged
and messed up kid I could find.
Tokaku!
Your life's not worth
a damn to anyone.
[TOKAKU]
Big surprise. And I don't care.
So will you kill to live?
Or let live and die?
Those are two of your options.
[KAIBA] Unless of course, you
attempt to let live and live.
Tch. You're not making
any damn sense, moron.
[KAIBA]
Myojo Private School.
An immersive
institution accommodating
grade school through college.
The offspring of the world's
most elite comprise
the student body, children
of politicians and the rich.
It should take a couple
of days for everyone
in Class Black to arrive.
You'll soon be contacted
by the client on site
for a complete debriefing
on the assignment.
[TOKAKU]
And who's the client?
[KAIBA] Why, the chairperson of
the board of Myojo, of course.
[HARU]
Student number 1, Tokaku Azuma.
Number 2, Isuke Inukai.
Number 3, Kouko Kaminaga.
Number 4, Hitsugi Kirigaya.
Number 5, Shiena Kenmochi.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARU]
Number 6, Haruki Saguy.
Number 7, Suzu Shuto.
Number 8, Otoya Takechi...
And 10, Nio Hashiri.
11 is Sumireko Hanabusa.
12, Mahiru Banba.
Number 13. Me, Haru Ichinose.
No matter what. I'll
graduate with flying colors.
Are you in Class Black too?
I'm Haru.
Tch. Um yeah, I'm...
[TOKAKU gasps]
Whoa!
Uh. Class is starting.
I take it this is your homeroom?
[MIZOROGI] Good morning!
Welcome to Class Black!
I'll be your homeroom
teacher Mr. Mizorogi.
I've been teaching
for three years now.
And biology's my field.
But this is my first homeroom.
So it's nice to meet ya!
[TOKAKU]
He's just an average putz.
So how did I not notice him?
\As of today, Class Black
will be your home
for the next year.
So you girls just think of me
as your big brother, okay?
[ISUKE giggles]
You're so friendly,
Mr. Mizorogi.
The most pathetic trait
a person can have.
[MIZOROGI]
Uh. And what's your name?
[ISUKE]
I'll gladly introduce myself.
Class Black, student number 2.
Mistress Isuke Inukai.
And that's with 3 i's.
You're too young to be teaching.
I need a more experienced man,
40 and up, to teach
me anything new.
What? 40 years old?
That's like a senior citizen.
40 is nowhere even near old.
Maybe I should kill you.
Oh, c'mon!
Not tryna make you angry.
By the way,
I'm student number 10.
Nio Hashiri.
Play-ah.
[laughs] Hey, don't you two
ladies go fighting over me now.
So, next up we've got
student number 1.
I'm student number 1,
sir. Tokaku Azuma.
[ISUKE]
Huh? Azuma?
As in the?
[NIO]
Ya think she's related?
[TOKAKU]
Oh, and the name Tokaku?
It means an impossible thing.
I'm telling you now so
you don't ask me later.
[MIZOROGI] Okay, next on
the list is student number 12.
[MAHIRU whimpers]
Uhh, hi? Number 12?
[MAHIRU]
I'll do it later, in the dark.
[MIZOROGI]
Hm?
[MAHIRU]
I only...
...do things once
the sun goes down.
Don't make me say it again.
Uh, moving on.
We've got one more.
Me! I'm student number 13.
Haru Ichinose.
I'm sure we'll all get along.
[TOKAKU]
Haru Ichinose...
[HARU] Actually, I thought it
might be nice to have a token
of our new acquaintance.
So I made cellphone
straps for everyone.
I hope you all like them!
Uh. Well thanks, man.
Wow. That's desperate.
[MIZOROGI]
Alright.
We need to discuss the dormitory
that you'll all be living in.
If you're okay with it,
student number 1,
I figured it'd be easiest
to make you dorm rep,
temporarily, anyway.
[TOKAKU]
I don't want this thing.
Guess I'll toss it later.
[phone chimes]
[NIO]
Nice view up here, huh?
And it's not just
pretty, y'know.
It's got fun stories.
Like about how the workers
suffered nonstop accidents
while constructing the school.
Or how they're used
to be a cemetery here,
but they just built
on top of it.
Y'see, I've always gone
here so I'm in the know.
What do you say we team up?
I've got no problem
being your underling.
[TOKAKU] No thanks.
Has the target been confirmed?
[NIO] It ain't you, sister,
that much I know for sure.
You got the stink
of trouble all over.
[TOKAKU]
You think so?
The most likely target
is Haru Ichinose.
She smells like oblivious prey.
[NIO] Yeah, but I
don't think you wanna
let your guard down around her.
It's gotta be a GPS
or a listening device.
Not foolin' me.
[NIO gasps]
[TOKAKU]
It's not a big deal, really.
I don't think it's anything
more than a cellphone strap.
[TOKAKU]
That's weird. Why do I care?
It's wasteful to just
toss it like that.
You obviously don't want it,
so I'll keep it for myself.
[TOKAKU] I didn't even want
the one she gave me,
and now I've got two.
[ISUKE]
I don't want that crap either.
[NIO]
Dang, dude, you look scary!
[TOKAKU]
Take a look at her.
I'm not gonna hide
my true nature.
You see, I'm gonna
win this dumb class.
The target is clearly number 13.
Hm... You never can tell.
[HARU]
Uh. Do you...?
Yes, I love it. Thank you.
It makes me so happy.
Honestly.
Really? That makes
me happy, too!
[MAHIRU] It'll serve as
a relic. It's perfect.
[HARU]
Did you say a relic?
[SHINYA] A personal object of
someone exalted who's died.
[MAHIRU giggles]
[HARU]
Hey, Azuma! Remember me?
It turns out I'm your roommate!
Mind if I walk with you
on the way to the dorm?
[TOKAKU]
Yeah, sure. I don't mind.
[HARU]
Oh, awesome. Thank you!
This place is so sprawling
it's a little overwhelming.
Wow, you're kind of a
fast walker, aren't ya?
That's really cool
that you got selected
to be the temp dorm rep.
I'm jealous.
[HARU]
I'm gonna study with everyone!
It seems like a good way
to make friends with people.
I just wanna
enjoy life, ya know?
And I promise you this:
I'll graduate without fail.
You seem rather anxious
about that achievement.
Huh? Well, yeah.
[HARU] I haven't been to
much school before now.
Some stuff happened
when I was younger.
Long story, but that's
why I'm happy to be here.
[TOKAKU] I can't figure out
what she smells like.
[HARU gasps]
[NIO]
What's up, Haru? Tokaku!
[HARU]
Miss Nio!
Just Nio. I'm not a teacher.
Y'know, Tokaku,
you sure are lucky
you're roommates
with Haru, here!
Don't do that.
Huh?
There's no reason that you
should address me so casually.
Call me Miss Azuma.
[NIO]
What? Are you serious?
Dead serious.
[TOKAKU]
There's something off about her.
She's got a putrid ocean stench.
Miss Tokaku!
[HARU]
Uh. Let's compromise!
How about Miss Tokaku?
You can do what you want.
[HARU]
Uh. Hey, wait up!
[NIO laughs]
[HARU]
Wow!
Amazing!
It's so spacious!
Like a nice hotel!
[HARU] Which bed do
you prefer, Miss Tokaku?
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
I just flopped right down.
I'm fine with either.
Huh?
[TOKAKU] Those look like
scars from a dull blade.
Let me see.
No way! I mean--
They're not pretty to look at.
[TOKAKU]
Just lift up your skirt.
What? No, really,
I'd rather not.
They're just scars from a long
hospital stay after an accident.
Alright then.
[HARU sighs]
[HARU screams]
[HARU]
Okay. You're not very nice, huh?
And what's this?
Are you my roommate?
Yeah, I'm Haruki Sagae.
Nice to meet ya.
Perfect timing.
Do you have any--
[ISUKE]
Mistress Isuke Inukai.
[HARUKI]
Right, sorry.
Now that's out of the way.
Ya got any nail
polish remover, Isuke?
I spaced out and forgot mine.
Oh, this is off to a bad start.
You're pissing me off.
I'd rather you call
me Mistress Isuke.
[HARUKI] Sure. Mistress.
You got that remover?
The paint on my nails has
been chipping like crazy.
[ISUKE]
Too bad for you.
I use gel polish. So no remover.
[HARUKI]
What? You really use gel polish?
[ISUKE gasps]
[HARUKI] I always heard
this stuff thins your nails.
Doesn't seem worth it to me.
But they sure
are pretty, though.
Hey. You do know
Isuke's a guys name right?
Yeah, but who cares?
I think it's a cool name.
[TOKAKU]
I guess...
I better go check
the other rooms, too.
Okay, I'm done,
the bath's all yours.
What's that? The roll call?
I'll come with you.
[TOKAKU]
Not necessary.
[HARU] Roommates are supposed to
help each other with that stuff.
Not necessary.
[HARU humming]
Everyone from Class Black!
It's time for our
nightly roll call.
[HITSUGI]
Have a good night.
[HARU]
Thanks, you too.
Wait, are you in grade school?
What are you doing up here?
[HITSUGI]
Grade? I'm not...
[CHITARU] She's a transfer
student to Year 10,
Class Black, just like
the rest of us.
[HARU]
Oh, you're our classmates?
I'm sorry, nice to meet you!
[CHITARU] I'm student number
9 on that list of yours.
Chitaru Namatame.
[HITSUGI] I'm number 4.
My name's Hitsugi Kirigaya.
It's nice to meet
the two of you.
Hi, good evening.
Time for roll call.
[HARU grunts]
Hm?
[HARU]
Uh...
Jeez, sorry.
[TOKAKU]
I guess you've arrived.
I take it you're Saguy?
You already know who I am.
[TOKAKU]
Process of elimination.
You're not Inukai.
How perceptive. Mistress Isuke's
in the shower right now.
Now that seems like a sweet
little hand incapable
of doing anything bad.
[HARU] Well, yeah, I make a
point of not doing bad things.
Hungry? Ya want one?
I don't.
Don't be like that.
Go on and take 'em!
Whoa. Nice reflexes.
Uh. Haruki. It's rude
to throw food at people.
[HARUKI giggles]
Aren't you precious?
Right-handed, huh?
Who knows? I could
be left-handed.
Or maybe I'm ambidextrous.
[HARU]
I've got a question.
Why are you always so bristly?
Why don't you ever smile?
Try it.
Like this!
Your smell. It's so...
[HARU]
My smell? Do I stink?
Man! I just showered!
[TOKAKU]
No, that's not how I meant it.
It's this kind of dusty smell.
Makes me wanna sneeze.
[HARU]
Oh no!
[SHINYA]
What, you don't know that smell?
That particular smell?
That's what they call
the smell of sunny places.
Yo, the sun finally set
so I've come to do it.
[HARU]
Um, to do what?
[SHINYA]
To introduce myself, of course.
The name's Shinya Banba.
The daytime girl is Mahiru.
It's nice to meet you.
Not really.
[TOKAKU]
The smell of sunny places.
[SHINYA insane giggling]
[KAIBA]
Okay! Zip your lips, brats.
Talking is prohibited.
To put it simply,
people in different positions
don't understand each other.
Is that clear enough?
Why bother with them?
It's a waste of your damn time.
[KAIBA]
Look at it like this.
What's the point of
getting to know someone
if you're about to
put a bullet in them?
Trust me, there are
things in this world
you're better off not knowing.
[TOKAKU gasps]
Just look at this place.
She's about as messy as a boy.
Miss Tokaku. Please don't
end up hating me.
Even once you get to know me.
[TOKAKU]
Ichinose.
Uh, yeah?
[TOKAKU]
Got any idea how to solve this?
[HARU]
Is it like a riddle?
Are there any hints?
[TOKAKU]
No hints.
[HARU]
Hm...
Eh, never mind. Just forget it.
[HARU] Well, if I got to
decide my own answer.
I would say forgiveness.
[TOKAKU gasps]
[HARU] The world is full of
forgiveness. Isn't that nice?
[TOKAKU gasps]
[TOKAKU] But-- There's
no way. That can't be it.
[HARU]
Yeah, I figured.
I just meant that's the answer I
would want it to be, that's all.
[TOKAKU]
Is she? No...
No, that can't be right.
[CHAIRPERSON]
I'm dying to see how long
she can actually hold out.
12 bloodthirsty trained
assassins against sweet Haru.
Well, young lady...
I'm excited to see
what you've got in you.
[NIO] And there we go.
Finally time to get started.
[TOKAKU] And so, everything
would change today.
But of course,
I didn't know that yet.
[KAIBA]
Hello, I'm Mr. Kaiba.
I'm a teacher at
Private Academy 17.
Dice Man, Dice Teach,
that bastard with the dice,
call me whatever. Students
give teachers nicknames,
that's just what happens.
But not Tokaku, oh no.
She's not that sort of girl.