[beeping]
[RAMPO]
Huh? A security camera?
That wasn't here before.
Reality manipulation.
[RAMPO] Without a doubt.
The power of the page.
Which means...
...the camera's footage must
show me committing the murder,
even though I didn't.
[MILITARY POLICE A] You, inside!
Drop your weapon and surrender!
I repeat!
[TONAN]
I-I know who the perpetrator is.
Decay of Angels aren't
just the perpetrators.
They're the Armed
Detective Agency!
Tanizaki, snipers!
Hide us using your special
ability. We're running!
[LIEUTENANT] Sniper team
has lost the targets.
[CAPTAIN]
It's an illusion ability.
But they can't hide
their body heat.
Attention all units,
deploy your thermal goggles.
Infiltration squad,
normal bullets will not work
on the Gifted with their altered
healing and physical strength,
so you must equip yourselves
with gas grenades.
What's the risk of
intercepted communications?
Military encryption devices
have been issued.
Good. A band of
murderers disguised
as members of the good guys.
The time of your
reckoning has come.
[KENJI]
Kunikida, this way!
[DOPPO]
Those snipers must be from
the military's
counterterrorism team.
Which means they must have
us surrounded by now.
[JUNICHIRO] Let's surrender.
After all, we're innocent!
[RAMPO]
It's no use.
[DOPPO]
Rampo! You're safe!
[RAMPO]
Chief Taneda received treatment
to stop his bleeding
and is now in hiding.
He may testify on our behalf
if he regains consciousness.
But I don't have much
hope that he will.
Why not?
[RAMPO] This is the work of
the reality-altering book.
The chief said the book may
have been made by Gifted,
but I seriously have my doubts.
It's from a higher power.
No Gifted is able to
create a book like that.
Case in point, Mushitaro's
reality-altering ability
wasn't able to overwrite
people's memories.
But that's happening this time.
[KYOUKA]
I definitely have memories
of all of us abducting the
hostages and killing them.
So then, what happens
if we're caught?
The government has Gifted
who can read your memories.
If they catch us, we'll
be sentenced to death.
[MILITARY POLICE B]
Don't move!
[gunfire]
Rampo, run!
He's gone. Not Rampo, too.
What Rampo said about the
Detective Agency's demise--
this is it, isn't it?
[SQUAD A LEADER]
Infiltration Squad A.
We've arrived at
the target location.
[SQUAD B LEADER]
This is Squad B.
We've arrived at our point.
[CAPTAIN]
Understood. Begin!
[ALL gasp]
[DOPPO]
Knockout gas!
[SQUAD B LEADER]
Gas deployed.
They're going to
lose consciousness
in just over ten seconds.
Infiltration Squad C.
Confirm the targets' heartbeats
using your sensors.
[SQUAD C LEADER]
Headquarters!
One target's heartbeat
is weakened,
but the other four
cannot be confirmed.
What?
[SQUAD C LEADER]
We're going in.
Headquarters. They're all dead.
[CAPTAIN]
Shit! It's suicide.
Quickly, resuscitate the one
that had the weak pulse!
I want them to
confess their crimes.
[SQUAD C LEADER]
C-Captain!
[CAPTAIN]
What?
Welcome to the party.
[SQUAD C LEADER]
Impossible!
The gas should've
knocked them all out.
Did they bleed
themselves on purpose?
Lower blood pressure means
slower gas absorption?
[AKIKO] You see the thing
is, people can stay alive
for about two minutes after
their hearts stop beating.
And for Gifted, near-death
wounds are like no wounds.
Special Ability!
Thou Shalt Not Die!
Infiltration team,
what's going on?!
What is your position?
Infiltration team
has gone silent.
It seems that they've
all been taken down.
[SQUAD A LEADER]
To think you'd all die
just to avoid inhaling gas.
There's no way you
could've done it
without knowing about
our plan of attack.
How did you know?
[DOPPO]
Anything I've seen once,
I can reproduce
with my notebook.
We've used your encryption
devices several times
in our joint operations.
Now use that to call for help.
With prompt treatment,
you'll survive.
But I wouldn't wait too long
to do it if I were you.
All infiltration squads,
remove your masks now.
Given they're eavesdropping
on our communications,
you'll have to use
your own discretion.
[LIEUTENANT]
Captain, where are you going?
I'm off to the frontlines, too.
I can't let more
innocent civilian
or military lives to be lost.
[RADAR OPERATOR]
Captain!
A large warhead's in the air!
And it's headed right for us!
What? The enemy's
targeting us directly?
[OUCHI]
Man, oh man!
This aircraft really does
wonders for shoulder pain.
Never felt better. Huh?
Uh...
Permission granted to
stand at ease, men.
Which one of you is commander?
Raise your hands
and on your knees!
Are you with the
Detective Agency?
Any normal person colliding
with the ground at that speed
should have been incinerated!
You're absolutely right about
that. It's a horrible ride.
No room to even
scratch my own ass.
[JOUNO]
Hold your fire.
When did you get--?
Now, Captain,
did you miscalculate your
descent trajectory again?
I'm sure that I fired
right at him. How?
[OUCHI]
Jouno! You got here before me!
[JOUNO] How many times
do I have to tell you?
[JOUNO] Please don't give
our troops a heart attack
for no reason.
[CAPTAIN]
Hmm?
Did he just toss out a ballistic
pod for long-range insertion?
That can only mean that
he's the legendary--
All men, you can
lower your weapons.
These men are here
to back us up.
They're from the military
police's most powerful force:
The Hunting Dogs.
And here come the others.
It's open.
[TERUKO]
Damn it! Mine won't open!
Huh?
[TERUKO]
Ugh! Blood! Show me blood!
Show me the guilty's blood
and pleas for mercy!
Hurry up, or I'll
chop off your limbs...
Our gremlin friend
is angry again.
It's really not funny, Captain.
If the vice-captain goes
on another rampage,
we'll all be dead
before we know it.
[TERUKO]
Don't make me wait!
Hurry up and open it, damn it!
[TERUKO laughs]
You're lucky you came to my
rescue in time, my servants.
One second longer
and I would've gladly
chopped up your arms and
legs to make fertilizer
for my personal bonsai projects.
[BOTH]
She's a little girl?
[OUCHI] You are just as rabid
as ever, my dear Teruko.
I'm counting on you today.
You got it, Captain!
Teruko will always put
her life on the line
to be your loyal dog, Captain.
Are you sure that they're
the Hunting Dogs?
[CAPTAIN]
Yep.
The elite five-member team
comprised of the best
of all the forces throughout
the entire country.
They're the special
suppression squad A-Team.
The squad's leader and living
legend, Ouchi Fukuchi.
The blind king,
who comprehends all
with his superhuman senses,
Saigiku Jouno.
The most capable combatant in
the squad, Tetchou Suehiro.
Feared by her enemies
and allies alike,
the queen of bloody
thorns, Teruko Okura.
You said five, but there
are only four here.
Where's the fifth
member of the team?
No one knows who
the fifth member is.
[OUCHI] He's infiltrating
another organization.
Are you the commander on-site?
[CAPTAIN]
Yes, sir!
It's quite an honor to meet
you, Captain Fukuchi.
[OUCHI] You should go have some
tea and leave this to us.
Huh?
Vicious criminals
betraying human morals
will be shred by fangs
of the Hunting Dogs.
[YUKICHI]
Yeah, thanks. Please do.
Hmm...
[MILITARY POLICE C] Hands up,
Fukuzawa. We're arresting you.
You enemy of the state!
This is the end of the
Armed Detective Agency.
[DOPPO] Have we gained
some distance on them?
My phone isn't working out here.
[DOPPO]
Radio jamming.
They'll try to stop
us physically next.
Surveillance satellites,
search dogs, roadblocks,
military drones.
There's nothing the
five of us can do
with our special abilities.
[AKIKO]
It doesn't look good.
After all, the sheer
numbers and firepower
of organized militaries are
unbeatable in the modern world.
Damn! We can't be stuck here!
Right now, they might
be treating Naomi
like a common criminal!
Common criminals? Huh.
[KENJI]
Listen, everyone.
This is just like
the ten-year orchard.
When I was in the village,
we spent ten whole years
raising an orchard,
and then just like that,
it got wiped out overnight
in a big storm.
We never got to harvest
that orchard even once.
[AKIKO]
Well, that's an awful story.
What do you think
our village did then?
At first, we were dumbfounded.
We laughed about it
for a little while,
and then we planted
new seedlings.
We decided to rebuild
over the next ten years.
A storm has done really bad
things to the Detective Agency.
But it's okay.
In the end, a calamitous storm
and a blessed rain are
exactly the same thing.
Let's keep living.
Let's make it through the storm.
One thing we can't do
is decide that we don't
wanna live here anymore.
We've gotta stay on the
spinning rock we call Earth.
[DOPPO]
Kenji is right.
Let's weather the storm and
rebuild the Detective Agency.
And to do that, we all need to
come out of this storm alive.
The longer we wait, the better
equipped and staffed they'll be,
and the wider their
search radius.
From my experience, their
search radius will grow
by roughly 50
kilometers per hour.
Does that mean we
have to escape
at a rate of at least 50
kilometers per hour as well?
That's correct, which means
we're gonna need a vehicle.
The criminals have two options.
The first is the arterial
road to the south.
They may commandeer a vehicle
there to make their escape.
The second is the
station to the north.
They could hide among the
crowds and escape by train.
This special squad we
have is exemplary.
I could be screwing around
the base sitting on my butt
while the rest of you close
the case yourselves.
I don't appreciate your
vulgar figure of speech.
North or south,
a train or a car,
it's all a choice
between life and death.
Now then, which course will
those pathetic, starving dogs
finally decide to take?
[DOPPO]
We'll take a car.
[JUNICHIRO]
Why a car and not the train?
[DOPPO]
If they manage to somehow
catch up to us on the train,
it could get derailed and
cause a grave accident.
Too many innocent lives would
be lost. That's unacceptable.
So it's got to be a car.
Well, I'm onboard.
Good thinking, Kunikida.
Let's do it.
[JOUNO] So which way shall we
go? The trains or the roads?
[TERUKO]
Both.
We'll face the enemy's potential
ambush head-on and crush them.
That's how we do
things on this team.
All right then, Teruko and I
will head north to the trains,
and Jouno and Tetchou will
head south to the roads.
Above all, make sure
you don't lose them!
[CAPTAIN]
Captain Fukuchi,
the enemy has
destroyed our vehicles.
We only have one car left that
we can use for transportation.
[OUCHI]
Not a problem.
Huh?
Fail, and you will all
be punished severely.
I forgot, Captain, what
was the punishment, again?
[OUCHI] Uh, we haven't messed
up since we were formed.
Guess I forgot, too.
[JOUNO]
Well, then.
Huh?
[CAR DRIVER]
Hello, may I help you?
[DOPPO] Do you have
vehicle theft insurance?
Of course I do, why do you ask?
[DOPPO]
I see. Congratulations.
After this, you're getting
a brand-new car.
[TETCHOU]
We're here.
Tell me, Tetchou, why did
you cut down all the trees
instead of avoiding them?
Because the fastest
route to any destination
is a single straight line.
[JOUNO]
That's how an idiot would think.
Let's have a meal
before we start.
I'll have you know, Tetchou,
that of every single
member in our squad,
I most certainly
hate you the most.
[TETCHOU]
Hate? Why?
Because your soul is entirely
lacking in artistry!
You enjoy putting shichimi
spice on strawberries
just because you think similar
colors pair well together!
That also goes for
putting sugar on rice,
and soup base on youkan!
Uh! And now you're eating
a hard-boiled egg
with the shell on!
I wish you would
just die already!
You're completely useless
until we meet the enemy.
Just shut up and
don't say anything.
Also, your pulse and your
breathing are both annoying.
Please do your best to stop.
[JOUNO]
There.
Distance, 500 meters.
Four to five people on board.
Driving in a westward direction.
[ATSUSHI]
Just a little more.
I wonder what's happening
to the others right now. Huh?
Beware of any traps
set by the suspects!
[ATSUSHI]
Military police!
They've come to help
with the hostages.
Hey, help, I'm over here!
Help me out, please!
[MILITARY POLICE D]
Headquarters,
we've discovered
a remaining suspect.
Request permission to fire.
So now what do we do?
Next step is to hide out
and gather information.
That is, if we can find someone
who will provide shelter
to fugitives from
the Detective Agency.
I know a hideout we can go to--
somewhere that'll
be safe for us.
But I'll loathe being there.
[JUNICHIRO]
Really?
[KENJI]
Where's that?
[JOUNO]
I'm interested, too.
Please do tell us all about
this safe hiding place
you're going to.
[KENJI, JUNICHIRO gasp]
[JOUNO]
You're missing someone though.
Where's the girl in the kimono?
What?
[DOPPO]
He stopped Kenji's brute force!
[KENJI yells]
Asshole! Light Snow!
Go, Kunikida! Make a run for it!
[JOUNO]
Very impressive.
You erased the car and
messed up my sense of location
before pulling me
out along with you.
But Special Ability illusions
won't work on me.
I let you catch me on purpose.
We're going to finish
you two off first.
[TETCHOU]
Should I kill both of them?
Of course, you are the best
swordsman of the Hunting Dogs,
so at least go make
yourself useful.
Get ready!
It's not the idealist way
to leave anyone behind!
[MILITARY POLICE D]
Prepare to fire!
[ATSUSHI]
Wait!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
But, Kyouka, what--?
Don't worry, I only
knocked them unconscious.
We've been framed by an enemy.
The Detective Agency was labeled
a criminal organization,
so we had to escape.
Come on.
Where are we going? We have
to get outta here, don't we?
There's no getting
out of here now.
We're stuck down
here for a while.
Kenji! No time to
slow down! Grab on!
Well, that didn't go as planned.
We just went from bad to worse.
The Hunting Dogs are the
most formidable squad
the Military has.
Their bodies have been
augmented by Gifted experts.
They have many times
the physical capabilities
of the average person.
The next time they catch us,
they'll destroy the car,
and then we'll be
as good as done.
I can't believe it,
but you were actually
more useless than
ever today, Tetchou.
Have you considered
finding a new job?
I just needed a little warm up
fight to get my blood flowing.
[JOUNO] Ah, he's a bit pissed
about getting run over.
On some occasions,
evil goes unpunished.
Just as good can go unrewarded.
Without my blade,
one cannot wish for all things
to receive their proper justice.
One cannot begin to
hope for balance.
Plum Blossoms in the Snow!
[gasps]
[DOPPO]
What just happened to us?
[JOUNO] You came back
to save your comrade,
and you all went down.
It's hardly surprising when
you stop to think about it.
In my experience, that's just
the way life usually goes.
[KENJI]
Look out!
There is no escaping
from my sword.
[DOPPO] I still can't
comprehend his attack.
I have to do something.
Doppo Poet! Stun Grena--!
[DOPPO] I saw it!
The moment he drew his sword,
his saber grew far longer
than his scabbard.
And it turned.
[DOPPO] His blade, it's long
enough to catch a fleeing car.
There's no way we can
escape from that blade.
He's on another level.
Hunting Dogs, you're
certainly capable.
Now then, if you
please, Tetchou.
First, decapitate the doctor.
[ALL gasp]
[JOUNO] We can't have her
healing her buddies, after all.
Besides, she's an
angel of death.
[gasps]
The world is going to be
much better off without her.
No! Don't kill her!
All right, we'll surrender!
[JOUNO]
You have an interesting pulse.
Perhaps it's because
you're still
such an idealist, Kunikida.
You're relieved right
now, aren't you?
What do you mean?
[JOUNO]
I read up on you.
Your ideals are as lofty and
large as a hot air balloon.
But a hot air balloon
inevitably runs out of fuel
and returns to the ground.
You've lived in fear of
when that day would come.
Stop it.
[JOUNO] I'm really happy
for you, Kunikida.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll be free!
[CHUUYA]
Deploy Gravity Manipulation.
Hypersonic countermeasures?
But how? I didn't
hear any gunfire!
[CHUUYA] You've fucked up,
Detective Agency!
I'm here to save your asses,
on the boss's orders.