A transaction. You use
the healing ability for me.
In exchange,
I provide information
that will lead to the
Agency's restoration.
Let's meet in 20 minutes.
At Goban Street.
Information leading to
the Agency's restoration!
Now we have some hope.
It is odd, though.
How did Francis
discover the location
of this Port Mafia hideout?
I suppose he must have used
his Eyes of God or whatever.
[OUGAI]
That's the thing.
If he was able to
discover this hideout,
he might as well
have done business
with the military police
instead of us.
It would have been
more profitable
to do the formidable
Hunting Dogs a favor,
as opposed to the weakened
Detective Agency.
The Francis who I know
will always side
with the stronger,
more aggressive group.
This transaction might
be some kind of a trap.
[JUNICHIRO]
Yosano, where are you going?
To complete that transaction?
You think it might
be a trap, right?
Is that the reason you
won't join the Port Mafia?
[AKIKO]
Don't give me that bullshit!
I know you can help
prove our innocence.
You just don't want to
until we've heard your terms.
[OUGAI]
Correct.
The agreement with
President Fukuzawa
was that we would only help
the Agency in exchange
for transferring one of its
members to the Port Mafia.
Transfer a member of the Agency?
You think you're being funny?
You just want me
back in the Mafia!
Isn't that really what's
behind all this?
[JUNICHIRO] I can go.
I'll join the Mafia instead.
My ability of Light Snow
ought to be useful enough
to satisfy them.
But please tell me
what's going on.
What happened between you
and the Mafia boss?
Does it have to do with
the "Angel of Death"
that the Hunting Dogs
were talking about?
[AKIKO sighs]
All right then. I guess you
two deserve an explanation.
Fine. I'll tell you as we walk.
[AKIKO] A long time ago,
the boss and Mister Mori
were close allies in the
three-party framework.
As you know, they
wound up as enemies.
Why do you think that is?
Well, come to think of it--
[AKIKO]
It's because of me.
[AKIKO] The island Tokoyamijima
appeared out of nowhere
in the Pacific.
An unclaimed island where
it was only ever night
became the main battleground
at the end of the Great War.
Electromagnetic waves
from the aurora
destroyed electronic equipment,
resulting in pre-modern
close-quarters combat.
[SOLDIERs groaning]
[NURSE] Stay still. I have
your medicine right here.
I'm gonna wrap your bandage.
[AKIKO] Don't just lie there,
you lousy soldiers!
Special ability.
Thou Shalt Not Die.
[SOLDIER B] I can see!
Ah! My eyes are working!
It doesn't hurt!
I'm completely healed!
My leg. I have my leg again!
You get hurt
because you're weak.
Now stop loafing and get
back to the damn front!
[SOLDIERS gasping, laughing]
[SOLDIER D]
Amazing! It's a miracle.
[SOLDIER E]
You are our god!
[SOLDIER F]
Our savior!
[SOLDIER G] Let us use your
likeness as our emblem!
[SOLDIER H]
Please! Let us worship you!
[AKIKO]
Go away! Piss off!
[SOLDIER A gasps]
Are you that enamored
with my Yosano
that you're willing to
lose your life over her?
[SOLDIER C]
Ch-Chief Mori, we would never
disrespect her like that.
[SOLDIER B]
Oh, shit. He's gonna kill us!
[SOLDIER A] Oh, he's going
to pickle our organs.
Since when am I your Yosano?
Did you buy me at an auction
I wasn't aware of, Chief Mori?
How'd you like your
ears bitten off?
I'm your superior
officer, am I not?
I have the right to correct
your attitude and language
whenever I feel they
need correcting.
[AKIKO] I don't care
about military policy.
I was working at a candy
shop until last week,
when you dragged me out
here against my will.
[OUGAI] She's so strong
willed. I love it!
[SOLDIERS yelp]
[AKIKO]
Huh?
[AKIKO] Reading a novel?
After you nearly died?
No, it's not a novel.
It's a collection of poems.
Huh? Unbelievable.
I'm not telling you to thank me
with tears of joy or anything,
but don't you have any intention
of hurrying back to the front?
You know, now that
you're all better?
I want to thank you, for sure.
Which is why I'd like to
present you with this gift.
Hm? Is that one
of my butterflies?
[AKIKO]
No. It's... metal.
Thank you so much, my angel.
[AKIKO gasps]
A-Angel?
[OUGAI chuckles]
But how? How did you
do that just now?
Was that your special ability?
It's nothing that's
gonna change the world.
Certainly not in the way
that your ability is going
to impact people.
I'm going to change the world?
Your head must still be injured.
There are some things you notice
when you're nothing
but a private.
The Special Ability Doctrine.
[AKIKO]
Hm?
The great powers of Europe that
first started the Gifted wars,
they're all changing
the very concept of war.
If we are to prevail as victors,
we must prove this
to the military brass.
And we have to do so
as quickly as possible.
That's why Chief Mori
brought you into this unit.
That right, Chief Mori?
I can see that
you've been reading
my "Immortal Regiment" paper
without the proper authority.
[AKIKO]
What are you talking about?
[OUGAI] I was certain that was
a classified military document.
I don't know what the hell
you're going on about
with all this immortal stuff.
I just came here to save as
many soldiers' lives as I can!
[OUGAI]
Let's go, Yosano.
There are more patients
waiting for your ability.
Elise, the next chart, please.
Yes, Master Mori.
[SOLDIER C]
Dammit.
Those assholes have
set up camp so close.
They don't think we're a threat.
I hate to agree with them,
but we aren't.
We don't even have weapons.
None that will reach
that far, anyway.
[SOLDIER D] We're way outgunned.
And outnumbered.
Unless something changes.
Relax, we'll take them down!
After all, we have
an angel on our side.
[SOLDIER B]
You're right.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[SOLDIER C]
That's right, she's magic!
[SOLDIER B]
Pretty lucky at that, huh?
[SOLDIER C]
Absolutely. Heh.
[SOLDIER]
Shit! Get down!
[screams]
Huh? I still have my right arm.
[AKIKO]
Are you feeling all right?
[SOLDIER]
Hm?
Just tired, and you're looking
pretty tired yourself.
Of course I look tired.
I treated 80 people
all at once.
The worst one had half his
body blown off in battle.
I could heal his wounds
with my ability,
but I couldn't heal his mind.
He can't even say his
own name anymore.
[SOLDIER]
What about everyone else?
[AKIKO] The ones who didn't
die went back to the front.
They don't have enough men.
[AKIKO]
"Angel," my ass.
I'm basically healing them
just for them to die again.
[SOLDIER]
You're wrong.
[AKIKO]
Huh?
What's that?
Something I'm using
to keep count.
It's the number of times
that you've saved my life.
Today makes the fifth time.
I like to keep tally
with this character.
It's the character that
stands for "true."
Every time I count something
and finish writing "true,"
I get the sense something just
was created in the world.
This is your impact.
If it weren't for you, I would
never have had a chance
to see my brother
and my parents again.
I'm glad you're here.
[gasps]
Thank you.
Actually, I--
[SENIOR OFFICER A]
Private first-class!
The front remains dire!
If you're better,
then get out there!
Yes, sir.
[AKIKO] But, as if to laugh
in the face of our efforts,
the situation continued
to get worse and worse.
I was treating soldiers
once every three days.
All repeat customers.
Then it became once a day.
Soon, three times a day.
It was no longer appropriate
to even call it a war.
We were just standing
there, being brutalized.
A normal unit would have given
up and retreated long ago.
But that never happened.
Because I was there.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[SOLDIER B]
I can't fight anymore.
[SOLDIER C]
Spare me.
[SOLDIER D]
No more.
I don't wanna go to
the front anymore.
[OUGAI] That's a fracture
of the right radius.
Please treat him.
Father. Mother.
I'll be home soon.
[AKIKO]
I don't wanna fix them.
So you're just going to
abandon his wounds?
Yeah. That's right.
Let him fall back and get
treatment on his own!
[OUGAI]
I see.
You want to free him
from his obligations
on the battlefield as a soldier.
Quite the conundrum.
As your superior officer,
I'm obliged to dole
out your orders,
but for some reason,
I have a hard time saying no
to a young girl's wishes.
Not your wishes, though. Do it.
[AKIKO gasps]
[OUGAI] You know what happened
to the samurai, don't you?
They failed to understand
warfare using guns and cannons
and they perished.
In the war that followed,
the nation which recognized
tanks as beasts
that could ravage
enemy territory
was able to massacre and
completely annihilate its enemy.
In naval battles, the nation
which failed to realize
airplanes would be the masters
of the sea was the one to fall.
And now, special abilities
are changing war once again.
Your role is to
make the military
understand this
change is needed!
Do it. Or else the
nation will crumble.
I refuse!
I just wanna save the lives
of the people in front of me
who need it!
[OUGAI]
Very well.
There. He's dying now.
Fix him.
[AKIKO] No one could leave
the battlefield after that.
The soldier who drew
a picture of me...
The soldier who pat my head,
saying I reminded
him of his sister...
The soldier who made
me delicious coffee...
They all died.
If it weren't for me, they could
have left with mere injuries.
Do you know the word
"annihilation"?
It's used when half a
fighting unit of soldiers
becomes incapacitated.
Not when half of
the unit is dead.
In other words,
if half of an army is hurt,
it retreats,
and the battle ends.
But as long as I was there,
there was no retreat.
That's why they couldn't lose.
To lose is a human right,
but I took that right
away from them.
Deprived of that opportunity,
there's only one place
a military can go.
[SOLDIER F]
Stop him!
[SOLDIER G]
Take his dagger!
[SOLDIER H] Everyone's goin'
to die because of that bitch!
This isn't war!
Let me go, asshole!
Let me go! Agh!
Let me go! Let me go!
[AKIKO] It happened on the day
a soldier I was close to
tried to kill me.
[AKIKO]
My hair ornament's missing.
I must have dropped
it somewhere.
I can't lose it after
he gave it to me.
I have to find it.
[SOLDIER]
Yosano.
Huh?
[SOLDIER] I'd like to ask you
to deliver a message.
I know that voice.
[SOLDIER]
I promised I'd endure.
But your ability,
the truth of it,
has taught me every person
in this world has their limits.
Remember how I
called you an angel?
You're so much more than that.
You've descended on
the battlefield...
...as an angel of death.
Please tell my family
that I said goodbye.
[bang]
[screams]
[AKIKO]
My memory after that is vague.
From what I've heard,
I went crazy.
I was arrested for setting
off a series of explosives.
Something about trying to
blow up an aircraft carrier.
[KENJI]
Hm?
[AKIKO]
Even after the war,
I was kept in isolation
and under guard
in a mental facility.
Not that I imagine I would've
left even if the door was open.
[JUNICHIRO] So someone must
have rescued you from there.
Was it the Agency?
[AKIKO]
If only that were the case.
I was rescued by the
worst person there is.
It was three years after
the war had ended.
[OUGAI]
I finally found you.
[OUGAI] Come with me.
I need your ability again.
[YUKICHI] You would willingly
drag her back into hell again?
Have you decided you're
now the devil, Mori?
[OUGAI] She is the very pillar
of the three-part framework.
Of the city's peace.
An immortal army led by
Yosano's special ability!
She's the key to defeating the
formidable Port Mafia boss!
You really think she's the key?
Your reasoning lacks
all sense of humanity!
Humanity?
War is a game in which the first
to take humanity
into account loses!
[YUKICHI] In that case,
our alliance ends today!
No, it's your life
that ends today!
[RAMPO]
Ah, sheesh.
Grown-up fights are
always so pretentious.
Oh, about this?
I'm freeing you while my boss
is fighting your old boss.
That's my plan anyway.
Take me back.
[RAMPO]
Huh?
[AKIKO] Take me back.
I can't go outside again.
[RAMPO]
Why not?
[AKIKO] My special ability
makes it too easy to save lives.
I make the lives of
everyone around me
seem like they're
cheap and valueless.
Take me back. I can't be
allowed to live anymore.
[RAMPO]
Ah... That's so stupid.
I don't give a crap.
Why don't you give up using
your special ability, then?
[AKIKO]
If I could do that--
[RAMPO]
You're saying that you can't?
Why not? Because you have
a crazy healing ability?
Because everyone tried to take
advantage of that ability?
That's not it!
My Ultra Deduction is
the best special ability.
None of the others
matter at all.
With me on your side, I can
solve any problem you have!
[RAMPO] If you doubt me,
I can prove it to you.
[AKIKO]
It's-- But how?
I never told anyone about
this hair ornament before!
[RAMPO] I found it on
an old aircraft carrier.
See? I know everything.
Try asking me a question.
I'll answer anything.
[AKIKO]
Then tell me.
What should I do
with my life now?
The people I cared about
died because of me.
That's how it's
always going to be.
There will always be people
who wanna exploit
my special abilities
against my will!
There isn't one single
place in this whole world
where I should be
allowed to live!
Wrong.
[gasps]
[RAMPO]
There is one.
Just one place in the world
that doesn't need you.
That one place is the
Armed Detective Agency.
We don't want your
special ability.
We want that kindness of
yours that goes with it.
You didn't want anyone
to die, did you?
That's why you're
in so much pain.
I invite you to join us
because you feel that way.
I don't care about your ability.
It's your kindness
that means something.
[JUNICHIRO]
Yosano, what's wrong?
[AKIKO]
Nothing.
It's time to go.
The transaction takes
place through the door.
I'm saving the Agency no
matter what happens to me.
[RAMPO]
There is one.
Just one place in the world
that doesn't need you.
[AKIKO] The Agency is the
one place in the world
where I can be allowed to live.