[JUNICHIRO] The transaction's
supposed to happen
just up ahead.
We have to hurry, before
the Port Mafia notices
that we're gone.
[MICHIZOU]
Dammit, you old geezer, why?
Just kill the
freaking detectives.
[AKIKO]
They got here ahead of us.
Just remember what
the boss said.
Francis might be with
the military police,
so make sure you don't
go near their business.
Even though they ignored
the boss's orders
and went off on their own.
I can't believe how they're
disrespecting the boss!
Still not giving up your old
gangster habits, Tachihara?
The Port Mafia's actions
are not determined
by whether or not
it's disrespected.
But instead, whether or
not they're faithful
to the boss's wishes.
Don't let anyone
hurt the Agency.
Protect them with your
life if necessary.
That is the order we were given,
and we will follow.
To put it another way,
the boss knew very well
that they were about to engage
in dangerous business.
[AKIKO]
Mister Mori knew that?
There you have it, detectives.
Have you heard quite enough yet?
[AKIKO] Mister Mori sure
is a worrywart, isn't he?
Well, he doesn't need to worry.
Your deal with Francis
isn't a trap
like he suspects it might be.
[HIROTSU]
Oh? How are you so sure?
Because I know Atsushi
believes him.
Atsushi fought with Francis
when they were both
aboard the Moby Dick.
Once you bare your
soul to someone
by trading mortal
blows with them,
they won't be fooled
by your lies anymore.
[KYOUKA] We're almost
at the transaction site.
Yeah. Let's get ready to go.
You know, we might actually be
able to save the Agency now.
I feel hopeful.
The Agency always shows its real
strength when it's together,
not when it's spread out.
I can't wait to be
with everybody again.
[KENJI]
Their ambulance is here!
We've been waiting
for you, Atsushi!
[ALL gasp]
Kenji!
Do not move!
Targets surrounded!
Capturing the suspects now!
[AKIKO] Shit. I hope this
isn't what I think it is.
[JUNICHIRO]
Kenji!
[JUNICHIRO] What the hell?
An enemy's ability?
The ornamentation on that saber.
The Hunting Dogs!
Everyone, run now!
The transaction was a trap!
Francis has sided
with the enemy!
Damn it.
[ALCOTT] Lord Francis,
may I ask you something, please?
[FITZGERALD]
What is it?
[ALCOTT] Well, of the 78
strategy proposals I wrote,
74 of them involved
selling the location
of the Detective Agency
members to the government.
It seems to me like that would
be a good opportunity for us--
a way to make up for the
Moby Dick having crashed.
So my question is,
why didn't you make a deal
with the military police?
[FITZGERALD]
Louisa.
Do you remember the time when
we were reunited on the streets?
[ALCOTT]
I would never forget.
[FITZGERALD]
Me, neither.
Everything I ate
tasted just like sand.
Even breathing was strenuous.
Despair takes away
a person's ability
to get back up on their feet.
For the several months
until you came along,
I hadn't even thought of
rebuilding the organization.
But the Agency got
back up within an hour.
And now, they're fighting
for their lives.
I always side with the winners.
And in this fight,
the Detective Agency will win.
Therefore, I will side
with the Detective Agency.
[MILITARY POLICE yells]
Damn, the MPs are
all over the place!
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Squads A and B, advance!
Squad C, deploy thermal scopes.
Don't let the one with the
illusion ability escape!
[AKIKO]
Kenji!
I'm all right. This is nothing.
[AKIKO] A raincoat?
It's not even raining.
Something about this
suddenly feels off.
Kenji!
[screams]
I can't get the sword out!
[HIROTSU]
Move!
[yells]
[HIROTSU]
Listen up, everyone!
We're heading to a secret
Port Mafia escape route.
Let's go.
[JOUNO]
Understood.
[JOUNO] The squads on the ground
have requested that we move out.
[chuckles] Then let's move.
Let me see him!
I can fix him right up.
[MICHIZOU] Didn't I tell you? It
was all a trap from the start.
You were right, and I was wrong.
[AKIKO]
But something still seems off.
[KENJI]
Yosano.
I can't thank you enough.
You just saved my life.
The Port Mafia's armed forces
are returning fire now.
But their defenses are
falling apart quickly.
If the five Hunting Dogs
are called in, too,
then the first thing they'll do
is destroy this escape route.
[AKIKO] No. I suspect one
of them is already here.
That saber--it belonged
to the Hunting Dogs.
I'm told that they have
uncanny physical prowess.
Not to mention they possess
exceptionally powerful
special abilities for Gifted.
Each one of them has
the military power
of a thousand special
forces soldiers.
A thousand?
They're a bunch of super freaks!
And there are five of them, too!
[AKIKO] Tanizaki, Kenji.
We need to talk.
We should split up and run.
Huh?
We can't, Yosano.
We have to stick together!
I know we should.
But right now, only one of
the Hunting Dogs is after us.
If we split up, then two of
us have a chance to survive.
Mister Mori mentioned a hideout
as well as designated
vehicles for reaching it.
Whoever's still alive
will rendezvous there.
Have they been
prepared for us yet?
Both the hideout
and the vehicles.
[AKIKO]
Good. Make me a promise.
Whoever survives this escape
will put their lives on the line
to rebuild the Agency again.
Of course we will.
You have our word.
[HIROTSU] You're about
to enter a complex maze.
Follow this map meticulously
to reach your escape vehicles.
Please stop the ambulance!
[KYOUKA]
What's wrong?
There's fighting outside.
Lots of gunshots and combat
boots on the ground.
Also I hear familiar
footsteps from underground.
Wasn't there supposed to be
a secret Port Mafia passage
in this area somewhere?
Atsushi? Kyouka!
It's Yosano!
[AKIKO]
Special Ability.
Thou Shalt Not Die.
[ATSUSHI] I can't believe
Francis betrayed us.
[AKIKO]
The transaction was a trap.
I thought that you
two were both dead.
That you got blown up
in the explosion.
It couldn't be a trap.
Francis is arrogant, but he
looks after his employees.
Even if he was gonna frame the
Agency, he would only do it
after Margaret received
your treatment.
[AKIKO]
Good point.
So how did the military
police find out
where the transaction
was taking place?
[ATSUSHI] I think we should
get outta here now.
Listen, driver, we're gonna--
[gasps]
It's an ambush!
Everybody, get out!
[AKIKO]
It's him.
Go, Atsushi. I'm going to
deal with this guy by myself.
Don't do it.
The three of us together
might stand a better chance
of beating him than just you.
Winning isn't what's
important right now.
What's important is
protecting Margaret.
I already treated her.
Deliver her to Francis
before the military police
have a chance to
close the roads.
That's our only hope
for reviving
the Armed Detective Agency.
Believe me.
Get in. I'm gonna drive.
[AKIKO]
Don't worry about me.
I've never been
very good at dying.
Yosano. Please be careful.
Now then, for starters,
may I get a look at the face
of the person I'm fighting?
[SOLDIER] But your ability...
the truth of it...
...has taught me--
[MICHIZOU]
Stay back, you dumb shits!
Freaking hell,
that sword's tough.
[AKIKO]
What are you two doing here?
[MICHIZOU]
The boss's orders are absolute.
Old man, look out!
[HIROTSU] My life of evil is
little more than a clown show.
Thus I have no intention
of making way
for your pretense of justice.
Special Ability.
Falling Camellia.
Wow.
The escape boat is in the
underground drain ahead.
[gasps]
[HIROTSU]
Go!
I can't hold him off
for much longer.
[AKIKO]
But I can--
Go!
We gotta go!
Whatever happens, we can't
let his efforts go to waste!
[HIROTSU]
May my immortal soul
be as one with the Port
Mafia till the end of time.
[AKIKO]
The character for "true."
We're safe. Only the Port Mafia
can unlock this blast door.
I'm not so sure about that.
You're not, huh?
You seem to know an awful lot
about that Gifted we faced.
[AKIKO] The Hunting Dogs
are military veterans.
And that ability to
manipulate metal--
[JOUNO] Besides,
she's an angel of death.
The world is going to be
much better off without her.
[AKIKO]
If that man is a Hunting Dog,
it would make sense that
they knew about the name.
"Angel of death."
But that man was most
certainly dead.
[AKIKO]
I know better than anyone.
I tried so many times
to bring him back.
[MICHIZOU]
That should do it.
Even if the enemy uses a special
ability to open the door,
this proximity bomb will
blow their heads off.
Even a Hunting Dog
would be dead instantly.
[GIN] I've checked the
waterway bulkheads as well.
[GIN]
We're safe here.
[AKIKO]
You two take the boat to escape.
I'm gonna stick around
here a while longer.
[MICHIZOU]
What?
[AKIKO] That man is only
trying to get revenge on me.
I can't let any
more lives be lost
because of things
I've done in the past.
[MICHIZOU] Are you trying
to diss us or something?
I hope you understand that we
wouldn't be in the Port Mafia
if we were a couple of wimps.
I have a bad-ass older brother.
I used to hate being compared
to him all the time.
I turned to crime so I could
become his opposite.
No dice.
'Cause fightin' and
doin' bad shit
never relieved me of this
indescribable agony.
Then, one day,
I was caught breaking into the
safe of some serious crooks.
They told me they'd spare
my life, but in exchange,
I'd have to become
a grunt for them.
Work was fun, as strange
as that sounds.
When I was fighting
as part of something,
a powerful organization who
had my back and I had theirs,
I was neither my brother
nor his opposite,
but someone else entirely.
The boss's orders
made me who I am.
So if the boss's orders
wind up killing me today,
then I'd die having
no regrets whatsoever.
[GIN]
Tachihara.
[MICHIZOU]
Hm? What is it, Gin?
Did my story strike a chord?
[AKIKO]
Hey!
[GIN]
Run!
I can't control it!
I can't control the sword!
[AKIKO gasps]
[AKIKO]
Impossible.
The door was never opened
and the bomb never went off.
How then?
You finally became
someone you liked
when you joined an organization.
Well... I understand you.
Come on! You wretched
ghost of the past.
I, Akiko Yosano,
will make you regret
coming back to life!
[FYODOR]
Do you know who the fifth member
of the Hunting Dogs is?
That question certainly
came outta nowhere.
My answer is no.
I couldn't find anything about
him, no matter how hard I tried.
[FYODOR] The fifth member
of the Hunting Dogs,
master of metals and
executioner of the shadows,
is a man who has an old
and fateful connection
with the Armed Detective Agency.
How many of the Agency
members do you think
will survive against him?
[AKIKO]
Did he just stop the bullets?
His ability to control metals
is way more powerful
than it used to be.
Whether it's a gun or a sword,
all weapons are his to control.
I have no way of attacking him.
[rumbling]
[AKIKO screams]
[AKIKO chuckles]
[AKIKO]
Today's a good day.
President and Rampo both forgave
me despite knowing my sins.
I was the one who
couldn't forgive myself.
But today, you came to
take revenge on me.
And thanks to you,
I'm no longer lonely!
That won't work!
[AKIKO yells]
[AKIKO] I get the feeling that
you can't stop an explosion
with your ability, can you?
I'm gonna save the Agency!
And accept my punishment
at the same time!
Huh?
What in the world?
It's not a bomb!
[AKIKO]
A metal mannequin?
Was the enemy never even here?
No. He couldn't have
fought that way.
Not without seeing me.
So the enemy's been watching
from close by the whole time.
Hold on a second.
I remember this mannequin
from somewhere.
It's the one I saw
in the window.
[thud]
[screams]
[JOUNO]
Excellent work.
[AKIKO]
Hunting Dogs!
Suddenly, I understand.
Now I know how they were able
to follow me so accurately
through the underground
Port Mafia maze.
And how the enemy passed
through the door.
And why the bomb was fake.
There can be only
one possible answer.
As a former medic
in the Gifted War,
who knew better than you that
your superior, Ougai Mori,
was a dangerous man?
I never would've expected
that the undercover agent
we sent to watch over him
would prove to be
so useful to us.
You know, when you
told me earlier
that you had to work as a grunt
for some serious crooks,
I guess I just simply assumed
that the powerful organization
you were talking about
was the Port Mafia.
[MICHIZOU]
No.
I am the fifth Hunting Dog.
Undercover agent
Michizou Tachihara.
And the soldier you
killed 14 years ago
was my older brother.
[gasps]
That was your older brother?
You see, if it weren't for you,
I never would've had the chance
to see my little brother
or my parents ever again.
[MICHIZOU] When Sakaguchi,
the previous agent, left,
the military police decided
to send another agent
into the Port Mafia.
But I asked for this
assignment specifically.
I was sure that I could
get close to you
if I became a member
of the Port Mafia.
Revenge for your brother.
I see. Today truly
is a good day.
Do to me as you wish.
[gunshot]