[POLICEMAN] This is Kanagawa
Traffic Police Unit 205.
Arrest made at scene.
Middle-aged male.
Requesting identity check.
[RAMPO] Hey, officer,
are we there yet?
Very soon, sir.
Uh-huh.
[MITAMURA]
That was impressive back there.
I've never met such a great
little detective before.
You and the bodyguard would make
an excellent detective duo
if you decided to
team up for good.
Don't you think so?
I don't think that guy has any
interest in working with me.
[MITAMURA]
Oh. Why would you say that?
If you ask me, that bodyguard
is afraid of strangers.
[MITAMURA]
You've only just met him
and yet you seem to know
him so well already.
I guess you truly are Gifted.
From what I understand,
you have the ability to
see the truth, don't you?
You may say that,
but you don't actually
believe any of it.
I mean, you really gave
yourself away just now
when you said I'd only
recently met him.
That told me that
you had checked in
with your headquarters about me
and they'd informed you
that I only met Fukuzawa
after the president's
assassination.
And now you're testing my
abilities to see the truth.
Very impressive, indeed.
Shucks. I underestimated you.
I hate that you still doubt
that I'm a great detective.
Would you like me to prove it
to you that I'm actually Gifted?
[MITAMURA]
It would be quite an honor!
To get a front-row seat to
a Gifted detective at work
is a rare privilege.
All right, then.
This car isn't headed to
the police station, is it?
I'm sorry, I guess I
should've told you sooner.
I won't make that mistake again.
I received a dispatch
just before we left.
There's been an incident.
Headquarters wants me to
take the expert detective
to the scene right away.
Oh, I see.
But I don't think you needed
to use your special abilities
to figure out which way
we're driving, did you?
The police station's back there
near the train station.
Doesn't take much to realize
we're going the wrong way.
[RAMPO]
Let's do something else.
You can test me out again.
Ask me anything about
the last incident.
If I can't answer your questions
to your satisfaction,
then you win.
If you run out of
questions, then I win.
How's that?
Makes sense to me.
Okay, my first question is one
that I'm sure is
on everyone's mind.
You know the
gentleman in the suit
who was tied up and
arrested on stage?
How do you think he was
taken from his seat,
tied up, and placed
on the stage?
The answer to the
question is a rug.
[MITAMURA]
A rug?
That's right.
Remember the rugs that covered
the theater's lobby floor?
One of them went missing
as soon as the audience
started to panic.
Also, in the empty spot where
the rug was supposed to be,
I detected a faint odor
I couldn't quite place.
It was something like that
weird-smelling stuff they use
to make paint and plastics
and things like that.
[MITAMURA]
Organic solvent?
[RAMPO]
Yeah, that's it!
I caught a whiff
of the same smell
when I discovered the
gentleman in the suit.
Which means the attacker must
have wrapped him up in the rug
and taken him to the stage
while the police interviewed
people in the lobby.
The attacker used the organic
solvent to knock him out first
before wrapping the
man up in the rug.
[MITAMURA] There was certainly
a lot of commotion at the scene,
with the actors,
the audience, and the police.
A man in work clothes moving
a rug around the theater,
I guess it might not have drawn
that much attention from anyone.
Still, I suppose we're certain
the attacker was the playwright,
acting as the leading
man's accomplice?
[RAMPO]
It wasn't the playwright.
I think he was probably
murdered by someone
who didn't want him
talking to the police
before the performance
even began tonight.
Everyone else in this
world, besides me,
is thoroughly stupid, but
still worthy of compassion,
so I wish that I could have
saved the playwright,
but there wasn't much
I could do for someone
who was dead long before I ever
knew anything about the case.
But what still bothers me is,
why would they do all that
just to abduct one person
out of the whole audience?
You think that it
was an abduction?
[RAMPO] There's no other
way to describe it.
The whole project was
just an elaborate set up
to specifically abduct
the gentleman in the suit.
He was the attacker's only
target the entire time.
The playwright and the
leading man, Murakami,
were just pawns for the attacker
to use as a distraction.
Well? Did I prove to you
that I'm the world's most
Gifted detective, or what?
So come on, give.
I answered your questions,
so why don't you tell me where
this car is really going,
Mister So-Called Police Officer
who reeks of organic solvent?
[YUKICHI] Why can't you
get in touch with them?
We still don't have
any confirmation
that they arrived
at the station yet.
Nor can we connect to the
police radio in the vehicle.
[YUKICHI]
The playwright was murdered.
[YUKICHI] Judging from what
Rampo told Joshi Egawa,
this case isn't over yet.
The fact is, this crime involves
two completely different acts.
You could think of it like
a sea bream and a shrimp.
[YUKICHI] The real perpetrator's
still on the loose.
You could be satisfied
with the shrimp,
which is much easier to
catch than the sea bream.
[YUKICHI] He must be talking
about the actor, Murakami.
But if you decide you want
to catch the sea bream,
well then, you're going
to have to use the shrimp
you caught as bait.
[YUKICHI] So the true
perpetrator is plotting
an even larger crime.
Using the actor, Murakami,
and the playwright, Kurahashi.
Rampo is intent on
exposing that perpetrator.
[YUKICHI]
What was the name of the officer
who went to the
station with Rampo?
[DETECTIVE]
Senior Officer Mitamura.
We tried calling him. His
phone's been switched off.
[YUKICHI] What in the world
has happened to Rampo?
[YUKICHI]
Where could he have taken him?
[YUKICHI sighs]
[YUKICHI]
Hmm?
My card?
[RAMPO] I will see you later
for sure! Yes, yes, yes!
[RAMPO laughing]
That must be when he put...
[gasps]
[MITAMURA] Unbelievable.
Truly unbelievable!
To think that we didn't have
a single bit of information
on such an exceptional
Gifted on our research list.
Officially, this place is an
office for a shipbuilding firm.
But in reality, it's what people
refer to as a shell company.
[MITAMURA]
Anyway, have a seat.
[RAMPO]
A gun, huh?
[MITAMURA] Oh. Don't worry,
I have no intention of using it.
As long as you behave
and do as I say.
[YUKICHI]
Hm?
Is that the man's cane?
Could be a concealed weapon.
[YUKICHI]
Hmm...
Damn.
That was some gentleman.
[OCHI]
Have you changed your mind?
No, but I do have a request.
[RAMPO]
Well?
Where are we exactly?
I already told you.
This is one of our outposts--
it's a convenient place to chat.
"Our" outposts?
[MITAMURA] I don't mean the
municipal police, of course.
[RAMPO] There are four
career soldiers with guns
standing guard outside.
No. There are five guards.
[MITAMURA] Magnificent!
How did you know that?
[RAMPO] Because that's
my special ability.
[MITAMURA] Listen,
those men don't have
the slightest intention
of harming you.
I didn't even bring
them here to guard you,
to be perfectly honest.
Those men were assigned
to keep an eye
on my original target.
The gentleman with the cane
who you managed
to reveal on stage.
[RAMPO] And the gentleman
who managed to get away.
So then, why did
you bring me here?
[MITAMURA]
I'm sure you'll agree
that the plot at the theater
was pretty elaborate.
The brass is furious that their
deep investment has been ruined.
They're insisting
I catch the guy
who messed up all
their careful plans.
Make him tell me how he
saw through the scheme
and explain where he got
his information from.
Otherwise, we'll be forced to
follow our orders to hurt you,
even though I disagree
with that kind of decision.
You wouldn't want that
either, would you?
So I have a proposal for you,
Mister World's Greatest
Gifted Detective.
How would you like to work
with us instead of against us?
We have a vision
for our country.
A plan to rid this nation of
evil people once and for all.
An excellent Gifted
such as yourself
would be more than
welcome to join us.
What do you think?
[RAMPO]
Oh, sorry.
You were rambling for
so long I tuned out.
I guess I stopped listening.
[YUKICHI]
How do you like your jail cell?
[SAKUNOSUKE] Not bad.
There's air conditioning.
I told them I was bored, so they
gave me this book to read.
I guess it's their way
of telling me to repent.
[YUKICHI]
I'm here with a question.
Would you mind looking at this?
This is a memory device employed
by a certain government agency.
A device used by those in the
witness protection program.
It allows participants to
communicate with their agents.
Only high-priority people
targeted by crime organizations
would have one.
They would also have one
other thing in common:
They're all Gifted.
I'm sure someone
as capable as you
would've taken on external
clients from time to time.
Have you accepted any requests
to capture a Gifted recently?
You know well that I can't
talk about my clients.
[YUKICHI] Then let's forget
I used that word.
Have you heard
anything recently?
Perhaps you may have come
across some talk about
a contract regarding a Gifted
being captured alive.
The request may have been made
by someone who calls themself V.
[SAKUNOSUKE] I really don't
want to talk about them.
Do you know why
they're doing it?
No.
For their cause.
Killing for money or
killing out of spite,
those reasons make sense to me.
But to them, the killing
itself is their great cause.
I don't wanna get
involved with those types.
If you're killing
people for a cause,
it doesn't matter who you kill,
only the act itself
is important.
The kill is the ultimate
achievement.
[YUKICHI gasps]
[YUKICHI] I'm not asking you
or ordering you to fight them.
But they abducted an
acquaintance of mine.
Do you know where they
might be holding him?
I don't have any
reason to tell you.
[YUKICHI]
You're absolutely right.
if you do tell me,
I'll testify in open court
that you fired the
gun in self-defense.
And that you killed
him by accident.
That the secretary was the
one who attacked you first.
[OCHI]
Huh?
[YUKICHI] They'll let you
out of jail immediately.
[SAKUNOSUKE] I'm surprised.
You don't look the type.
You don't fit the description
of the kind of person
who would readily sell out on
the justice system like that.
[YUKICHI]
I didn't think I was, either.
[SAKUNOSUKE]
Let me tell you something.
As a hired killer,
I always thought it was
best to work on my own.
I've never wanted any
coworkers or superiors.
But if a skilled martial
artist such as yourself
would go against your principles
just to save your subordinate,
he's lucky to have you as
a superior and coworker.
I actually envy him a little.
[YUKICHI]
No. He isn't a subordinate.
[SAKUNOSUKE] I've heard rumors
about several buildings
they like to use for
their transactions.
Do we have
an agreement or not?
I could escape out of here
at any point if I wanted to.
The reward you're promising
isn't quite worth it to me.
However, the food at this
facility is god-awful.
If you happen to have
any sway around here
with the kitchen staff,
would you mind talking
to them for me?
Have any special requests?
[SAKUNOSUKE]
Curry rice.
[MITAMURA]
Listen up, great detective.
Our organization is
formidable and flawless.
It would be far more
rewarding to join us
than to team up with that dumb
bodyguard boss of yours.
[RAMPO]
Moo.
[MITAMURA]
Hm?
[RAMPO] Look, pal, I have
a hard time paying attention
to things I have
no interest in.
It just sounds to me like
cattle mooing all the time.
Moo! Moo! See?
[MITAMURA]
You're extremely fortunate
that I'm the one you're
negotiating with.
Anyone else might've
started sawing you apart
from your toenails up
to your eyebrows by now.
[RAMPO]
He's mooing again. Moo! Moo!
[MITAMURA] Looks like
we'll have to use this
to move the
conversation forward.
You can use your gift to see
through the truth, big deal.
You're still too feeble
to stop a single bulle
from going through you.
I only gave you my precious time
for the sake of our
organization's grand objective.
We'll wipe out the Gifted
rotting this country's values.
Starting with you,
if you don't get smart fast.
Okay, now I see.
V is an organization of Gifted
individuals brought together
to drive out other
Gifted individuals.
Wait! Give a guy a
second, would ya?
By my calculations...
...you have three seconds.
[gunshots]
Two.
[GUARD A screams]
One.
[MITAMURA gasps]
[YUKICHI] I took out one
of the guards outside.
Just how many more are there?
Four more!
That leaves one more guard.
Freaks!
[YUKICHI]
Are you all right?
[RAMPO]
Yeah, sure!
Wow, that went better
than I expected.
You arrived just
in time, just as I--
Screw you!
To hell with your
damn calculations!
When I got here, there was a gun
pointed right at your face!
That happened only because
I knew you'd save me!
[YUKICHI] Showing off
your abilities is fine.
Using your intellect against
powerful enemies is good.
But I want you to stop
wagering your own life
on your stupid risky gambles!
You're still just a child.
With a lot more to learn.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[sighs]
[YUKICHI] Looks like Officer
Mitamura was murdered
while in custody.
It seems he's been silenced.
So I guess the plot continues
for this complicated crime.
But who is the perpetrator
of the last incident?
I mean, V has to be
behind this, right?
[FYODOR chuckles]
Except it's not "V." It is five.
Remember your Roman numerals.
[RAMPO]
Oh.
[YUKICHI]
Hmm?
What is it?
Oh... I was just thinking
about the cityscape.
How it looks different
than it did yesterday.
Do you think so, too?
It's because you
understand now.
[RAMPO]
Hm?
You mean I understand now
about how I'm Gifted?
No, not that.
You understand what's
important, right?
[chuckles]
[SAKUNOSUKE]
Curry.
Spicy! But so good.
[YUKICHI]
Is this it?
[RAMPO]
Should be.
[NATSUME]
Welcome to Bankoudou.
Oh.
Why, there's my cane.
I thought I'd lost it.
[YUKICHI]
I happened to hear about you,
so I decided to take the
liberty of coming here
for us to discuss a
proposal in person.
[NATSUME]
Don't be so formal about it.
Please, have a seat.
[YUKICHI]
Thank you.
[RAMPO]
No way.
I didn't notice at the time,
but this man really--
[NATSUME] It seems that
I owe you one, boy.
[RAMPO]
Right.
You saw through their trap
from the very beginning,
before the play started.
But even still, you decided to
let them capture you anyway.
You flushed out the enemy
so that we would catch them
instead of the municipal police.
Though the sea bream
seems to have gotten away.
I have come here with
a request for you, sir.
As I'm sure you're aware,
Rampo Edogawa here is building
a reputation for himself
as a Gifted detective.
But it's taboo.
A Gifted is forbidden to
promote themselves publicly,
which Rampo's already done.
That's why I came here
to ask you for your help.
You want to acquire a
Gifted Business Permit.
So you intend to start your own
agency with him by your side.
Yes.
In order for me to obtain
a special permit of this kind
from the Gifted
Operations Division,
I require your vast knowledge
in that area, Master Natsume.
It will not be
an easy path for you.
But still, I think you can
make it happen if you try.
If anyone can,
it will be you two.