[MICHIZOU gasps]
I'd better take
this off for today.
[TERUKO crying]
Huh? Hmm?
You idiot! What are you
looking at? I'll kill you!
[JOUNO] Hello, Tachihara.
Nice seeing you here.
It turns out Teruko managed to
get Gilette to finally confess.
What? Jack Gilette of the
Seventeen Worldly Evils?
I thought he'd never break!
Me, too.
I thought he would be a chew toy
that would never fall apart,
but he finally broke.
And it only took about
half a year to do it!
[MICHIZOU]
I sympathize.
Sympathize with Gilette.
[JOUNO]
Anyway, Tachihara.
Thank you for all your hard work
on the infiltration mission.
And now I have a new
assignment for you.
Deal with that problem.
Carry me! On piggyback!
[TERUKO laughs]
I'll start by summarizing
my investigation.
Following the hostage
crisis four days ago,
we've determined that the
infamous Decay of Angels
was, in fact, the Armed
Detective Agency.
[TETCHOU]
Really?
What are their goals? Any intel?
[MICHIZOU] Their last sighting
was at the bank break-in,
and that was two days ago.
[TETCHOU] To think they'd
raid a bank. Despicable.
[JOUNO] No training in
the middle of a meeting!
[TETCHOU]
You're a perfect weight.
[MICHIZOU]
Why do you think we haven't had
any further sightings?
[TERUKO] They must've already
gotten what they wanted.
And we all know what
a criminal on the run
would want more than
anything, right?
A base and a command post.
The main objective of
our mission is to prevent
any terrorist attacks
prior to the other side
of the page being filled in,
as well as recovering said page.
But as wanted criminals, the
Agency can't act in plain sight.
That's where her special
ability comes in.
[chuckles]
[ANGO] Lucy will place the
two of you in Anne's Room,
which you will be
able to infiltrate
completely undetected.
Therefore, Lucy
will be considered
the heart of our operation.
Well, you heard him,
didn't you?
Right, tiger kitty?
I believe this ear is
saying that it wants you
to say thank you.
[ATSUSHI]
Sorry.
Hm? Why are you apologizing?
For getting you
mixed up in this.
Cooperating with us right now
is the crime of aiding
and abetting fugitives.
I don't think we can ever
repay you enough for your help.
Why not?
If I'm not mistaken,
I think I'm the one repaying
an impossibly huge debt
right now, aren't I?
[ATSUSHI, LUCY]
Huh?
[LUCY] Nothing, nothing, never
mind, forget I said anything.
I'm begging you to forget
this whole thing!
It's time to go.
[clears throat]
Well, it's time to go.
Take me to the airport
bus stop, please.
[BOTH gasp]
[OCHI] Don't let anyone
in until I say so.
[GUARD A, GUARD B]
Sir!
[OCHI] I trust that you
are ready, Fukuzawa.
[YUKICHI]
Yes.
[laughs]
Why would our reunion be
anything other than a drinking
contest between us?
You haven't changed
at all, Genichiro.
[OCHI]
What?
How is it you still
haven't gotten married?
[YUKICHI]
I've been busy with work.
[OCHI]
You stuck-up loner.
Heh. I never would've thought
you'd be the Agency president.
[OCHI] But now that you are,
you have responsibilities.
Make your men surrender
to the police.
That way, the case will fall
under the jurisdiction
of the prosecution,
and they will no longer be
targeted by the Hunting Dogs.
Because the Hunting
Dogs will never relent,
or stop trying to
tear you apart.
I appreciate the concern,
but not the advice.
[OCHI sighs]
Well, I suppose I might enjoy
duking it out with you again
just like the old times.
What's making you stop?
[OCHI]
You aren't fooling me, Fukuzawa.
You were going to make me
cut off your handcuffs.
And then you'd swipe my
own sword away from me.
[YUKICHI]
You got me.
[OCHI]
Fukuzawa, let's make a deal.
I assume that you want
to know what happened
to your Kunikida, don't you?
He fell out of a helicopter
and blew himself up.
But I happen to
know where he went.
[YUKICHI]
Don't bother.
I know Kunikida is alive.
If he were actually dead,
I would've sensed it the very
moment that it happened.
[OCHI]
Hm.
Well then, shit.
The lone wolf sure has
changed over the years.
[JOUNO] There's no way you
could possibly be the greatest.
Welcome to the cafe.
[JOUNO]
At the end of the day,
your strength is the kind
that screams to the world,
"Hey everyone, look at me, I can
beat up a ton of wild boars."
But the Hunting Dogs' job
is about investigating
and arresting.
So what?
So based on that criteria,
I am the greatest
Hunting Dog there is.
Seriously?
[TETCHOU chuckles]
I want to kill you so badly!
What can I get you two?
Caffe latte.
Soy sauce latte.
Very good, gentlemen.
Soy sauce?
Just give him the
same thing as me.
Let's you and I make a bet.
Whichever of us finds
the Detective Agency's
whereabouts first wins.
Okay, you're on.
So are you two with
the police department?
[JOUNO] Yes. We're
investigating a case right now.
Oh, speaking of which,
the heinous terrorist
organization,
the Armed Detective Agency,
had offices right above
this cafe, did it not?
[OWNER] Yes. I saw them here
on occasion now and then.
It's all so terrifying.
Here you go.
[JOUNO] This woman's a
waitress here, isn't she?
[OWNER] Yes. Today happens
to be her day off.
Do you need something from her?
[JOUNO]
According to our information,
she's very close with
the Detective Agency.
We have reason to suspect
she's aiding their escape.
They wouldn't get very far
depending on a lowly
waitress for their chance
at getting away from the police.
Fantastic.
I have true admiration for
people who can make good coffee.
I almost want you to come work
at the commercial
facility I own.
Sadly though, there's
only one problem.
At my place, I don't like to
hire dirty stinking liars.
Me?
[JOUNO] I can tell from the
sound of your breathing.
You just told me that the
Detective Agency
wouldn't get far depending
on a lowly waitress.
But that was a lie, wasn't it?
You know all about her
special ability, don't you?
I'm sorry, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
I understand you buy
half a year's worth of
coffee beans at a time.
Despite you doing that,
this coffee still has
such a nice fresh aroma.
How is that?
It's because you stock your
inventory in her room,
where time can be slowed in
a special ability space.
That way you can keep
a large quantity
of beans fresh all the time.
Hmmm? Would you
like me to continue?
You also told me that
today just happens to be
Lucy's day off from work.
That's also a lie.
In fact, she's taken
an indefinite break.
She doesn't know if she
can come back at all.
Yet you still let her ignore
her job, because you understood
that she's the only one who
can save the Detective Agency.
Now, here's the problem.
You are now an accessory
to an act of terrorism.
If you still refuse to
give up her location,
I'll make sure that you'll never
be able to make coffee again.
[JOUNO yelps]
Why did you stab my foot?!
[TETCHOU] You have a bad
habit of tormenting people
and taking pleasure in
seeing them squirm.
[JOUNO]
Hmph!
[TETCHOU]
Boss.
Is it wrong to want
to repay someone
you're dearly indebted to?
I promise you,
if you tell us where Lucy
is at this very moment,
she will not be questioned
for any crimes.
We have the authority
to make that so.
And a world in which a girl's
honest intentions are rewarded
is one that we ought to protect.
My problem is that Lucy
isn't the only one
I'm trying to protect right now.
The Detective Agency?
All I can promise you is that
they'll be given a fair trial
under the laws of the land.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
I just knew that this
was going to happen.
[TETCHOU]
I promise on my sword
that if my promise is broken,
I will cut open my gut.
Please.
[OWNER]
Lucy told me something.
She said she wouldn't regret
ruining the remainder
of her life.
But what I'm asking you to do
is please save her future.
This I promise.
She went to the Sky Casino.
That's where she'll be.
[TERUKO] What a ridiculous
construction this is.
[MICHIZOU]
Most people believe
the civilian entertainment
facility's just a front,
and that it was really built
by the winners of the war
for surveillance
and intimidation.
[TERUKO]
It would be both a physical
and political catastrophe
if this place
were to be attacked
by terrorists or something?
[EMPLOYEE A]
Sir, we have a problem.
[SIGMA]
Terrorists?
[TERUKO]
That's right.
We have reason to believe there
are terrorists in this facility.
[TERUKO]
And we have proof.
What kind of proof?
Sir, look here.
[TERUKO] That woman is
one of the terrorists.
She used her pocket
dimension ability
to bring them all in here.
Then send a search team
to scour the casino.
It's no use.
She can hide with them
in the pocket dimension.
[SIGMA]
What do we do, then?
[TERUKO]
We close the casino.
Unacceptable.
What did you just say?
Bastard! Do you have any
idea how serious this is?
What a silly thing
of you to ask.
[SIGMA] You're surrounded
by directed resonance guns.
They were made specifically
to combat Gifted.
The sound waves
affect the brain,
causing loss of consciousness
within one second
and death within ten.
Do either of you
care to try them out?
You dare to defy the government?
[SIGMA]
The government?
Under international law,
this casino is outside
the jurisdiction of
any country's police.
It's effectively an
independent nation.
Therefore, I am the law.
If you want to spend your
money here and then leave,
I'm delighted.
Otherwise, just get lost!
[TERUKO]
How dare you!
Did you actually just
tell me to get lost?
[MICHIZOU]
No.
Oh, shit.
This area is secured.
Careful who you tell
to just get lost!
[SIGMA]
Uh! What the--?
[SECURITY B] Sir, someone's
blown up the landing zone!
What?!
[TERUKO laughs]
I guess no one's gonna be able
to get out of this casino now!
We're gonna split up
and search this place!
And you need to figure out
what the Agency's next move is.
[MICHIZOU]
Yes, ma'am...
[SECURITY C]
An explosion?
By terrorists?
[SIGMA]
Stay calm.
Our top priority is to keep
our clients from panicking.
Tell them it's an
electrical failure
and escort them all back
to their hotel rooms.
Client A-4098, Lazarus,
is becoming unstable.
Assign him some security.
Client E-2988 has a
chronic heart condition.
Alert the medical staff now.
[SECURITY C]
Wow.
I heard he memorizes
all of his clients' names
and characteristics instantly.
[SECURITY D]
No wonder they always say
he was the perfect choice
to manage a casino.
[SIGMA] Such a mild incident
will be forgotten by next week.
If you see a situation...
deal with it!
[SECURITY]
Yes, sir!
[SIGMA gags]
[SIGMA] This couldn't
have gone any worse.
I should've kicked
the Hunting Dogs out.
They must be the ones
behind the explosion.
Which means they're going
to investigate the casino.
If they find out what this
casino really is in actuality...
...I will have to kill them.
[MICHIZOU] No signs of evidence
on this floor, either.
Huh? What's that?
A gold coin?
[MICHIZOU]
The Detective Agency.
They must all be hiding
inside of that room.
I don't sense anyone in here.
They must have noticed me coming
and escaped to the
pocket dimension.
[MICHIZOU]
The carpet has been cut.
There's something here
under the floor.
A safe?
Metal manipulation.
[MICHIZOU]
Currency from around the world.
All in coins.
How? How did they know?
How could the Hunting
Dogs have found it?
Impossible.
Did he just manage
to stumble into
that particular
room by accident?
Okay, stay calm.
Their communication
devices and weapons,
they were confiscated along
with the other customers.
Which means that if
I kill them both now,
I can still protect the secret.
[FYODOR]
Sigma.
I'll give you a word of
advice, as a colleague.
If you're ever found out
by the Hunting Dogs
in the middle of one
of their missions,
then abandon everything
and run away.
Believe me, you won't stand
a chance against them.
[SIGMA]
Abandon everything? The casino?
It's very odd.
Are all of these coins
completely hollow?
No. There's something
inside of them.
Some kind of impurity
in the metal structure.
I'm so sorry.
It's over.
From that distance,
he has to be dead.
A high-precision explosive
disguised as a coin.
It's the savage weapon at the
center of the Decay of Angels'
next worldwide terrorist attack.
Now that one has seen it,
I just can't send either
of them home alive.
[MICHIZOU] Whew! That was
a close one for sure.
[SIGMA]
What?
I managed to stop the shrapnel
with my special ability,
but the blast was still
able to knock me down.
Hang on for a second,
are all the coins in this
safe miniature bombs?
I didn't finish him!
Now what do I do?
Wait, I still have my
last resort available.
However, using it will cause
severe damage to the casino.
Believe me, you won't stand
a chance against them.
Maybe everything
he said was right.
When I think of
the Decay of Angels
and all the superhuman members,
I'm the one who has the
least combat ability.
If I'm not part of this casino,
I'm nothing at all.
[SECURITY C]
Wow.
I heard he memorizes
all of his clients' names
and characteristics instantly.
[SECURITY D]
No wonder they always say
he was the perfect choice
to manage a casino.
Everyone's got it all wrong.
I don't have the talent
they think I do.
I have to sacrifice sleep
to memorize things.
I obsessively study client
profiles and the casino layout.
I don't wanna lose the casino.
Therefore, I must--
[MICHIZOU gasps]
Are you serious right now?
An unmanned aircraft?
[MICHIZOU]
It's too big.
I can't stop it with my metal
manipulation ability!
[TERUKO]
Stand back!
I always knew you were weak.
[TERUKO laughs]
[TERUKO] It tried to challenge
me to a sumo match.
Silly airplane.
Oh, damn.
[thud]
[metal clanging]
[MICHIZOU]
You can't be serious.
Haven't you done enough?
Tachihara!
[grunts]
[yelling]
[CUSTOMERS gasping]
[CUSTOMER A] What was that?
Another explosion?
[TERUKO]
I see now. Coin bombs.
What an exhilarating
display of evil.
[MICHIZOU] The customers take
the coins out of the casino.
Then once they've been
traded around the world,
they'll all be triggered
at the same exact time.
This casino is actually
a terrorist itself.
That's why that manager was in
such a hurry to kick us out,
before we looked around
and found something.
This casino is where the trigger
signal is transmitted from.
A signal from such
a high altitude
would reach across
the whole world.
[MICHIZOU]
What do we do?
[TERUKO] We take the central
communication room
and expose the casino's
plans to the entire world.
[footsteps]
[TERUKO]
Are all you boys that desperate
to dance with little old me?
[gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
I hear fighting.
The Hunting Dogs
are on the move again.
[ANGO] And that is the Decay
of Angels' next plan.
A global act of terrorism,
targeting all of humanity.
But their true aspiration is
the panic that will ensue.
Currency, the basis of a
state's trust, will kill people.
Never mind a great depression.
It could very possibly
trigger the next world war.
This is it.
The worldwide terrorism that
the Decay of Angels will perform
before they fill in the
other side of that page.
[ATSUSHI] As the first step in
stopping this terrorist attack,
we'll have the Hunting Dogs
discover the coin bombs,
and while they're busy,
we'll take control
of the comms room.
By working with the Hunting Dogs
to stop a terrorist attack,
we'll prove once and for all
that we couldn't
be the terrorists.
And we capture Sigma,
who's a member of
the Decay of Angels
and knows where the page is.
That's exactly how Dazai's
plan will work.
[SIGMA] This is the Hunting
Dogs' combat power?
This is what it means to
be in a different league.
But us nothings have
our own way of fighting
when our backs are
up against the wall!
They'll see!
[OSAMU] Tell me, why
did you choose Sigma
to protect the casino?
[FYODOR]
What are you talking about?
[OSAMU]
Are you really gonna play dumb?
I discovered
something interesting
when I looked up
the Sigma character
you put so much faith in.
His life began rather recently
when he was arrested
by European police
three years ago.
He has no past to speak of.
He's sort of like a
novel that doesn't begin
until halfway through the story.
All I learned was
his special ability.
The ability to trade,
with anyone he touches,
the information each
person wants most.
He used that ability to steal
the location of the page
from Chief Taneda.
But you only needed
him for that instant.
So why did you leave
him to run the casino?
Why do you think
I left him in charge?
[OSAMU] First of all, I don't
think he's even close
to being a terrorist.
It's said that the Sky
Casino was built
following a secret meeting
of the victors of the war
13 years ago.
But no intelligence organization
had information about it.
That's when I realized.
The Sky Casino wasn't
built 13 years ago
like the rumors suggest.
It was built eight days ago.
It was then that it
emerged instantaneously,
having been written
about on the page.
Along with 13 years'
worth of history.
Now, I'll go back
to my first question.
Why did you assign
Sigma to the casino?
[FYODOR] Because he's
the most powerful of all.
[OSAMU]
Powerful?
In your opinion,
who would you say
is the strongest
person in the world?
A Gifted? A political leader?
Anyone you chose is wrong.
The most powerful one is the one
who has nothing else to lose.
[FYODOR] You see,
Sigma doesn't have a past.
In fact, he has amnesia.
[MICHIZOU] Sorry,
but guns don't work on me.
[SECURITY F]
Fall back! Retreat!
[TERUKO coughing]
[MICHIZOU]
Teruko! Are you all right?
[TERUKO]
Tachihara.
The heroes of justice are
gonna go save the world
while coughing up blood.
Don't you think that paints
an exhilarating picture?
[MICHIZOU] She got injured
when she stopped the plane.
[door opens]
[CUSTOMER B]
What was all that noise?
[CUSTOMER A] The security
guards are on the ground.
Oh, shit.
[WIFE] Is there something
wrong out here?
[MICHIZOU] Not to worry.
I'm with the police.
We're currently investigating
some terrorists.
This floor is now
completely safe.
[WIFE]
Oh. I'm glad to hear it.
[MICHIZOU groans]
[MICHIZOU]
What?
Tachihara!
[HUSBAND] Now we don't have
to pay for our losses!
[WIFE]
That's right, honey!
[SIGMA]
Attack! I repeat.
Attack these two
terrorists on sight.
I repeat. Attack!
You won't be accused
of any crime,
and your gambling
losses will be erased.
Plus ten grand for an injury.
One million if you kill them.
[FYODOR]
Unsure of who he was,
Sigma went looking
for a place to be.
That place was the casino.
This is why I have no doubt
that he'll torch
the Hunting Dogs
with hellish tenacity in order
to protect the casino.
The most terrifying thing that
ever existed on this planet
is a mediocre man
who is desperate.