[OGURI]
Dear Master Yokomizo.
How is it in the afterlife?
Knowing you, I suspect that
you're looking for ways
to manipulate divine powers
into allowing you an escape.
I bet if you saw me right now,
you'd be very jealous of my
current lavish lifestyle.
I'm not exaggerating.
The meals are extravagant
and exquisite.
[GUARD]
Meal time!
Thank you for this meal.
[OGURI] Even the Celtic
god Ruad Rofhessa
would envy my bounty
of reading material.
[OGURI]
You, guard.
[GUARD]
Hmm?
[OGURI] I wish to read
books on occultism.
Take me to the library.
You know you're not
allowed to leave.
[OGURI] Well, at least lend
me something to read.
If the rinse cycle
does not occur
during the washing process,
please see page 8 for more.
[OGURI] I get to read books
that I rarely do otherwise.
As a matter of fact, I never
even think about you
and that you no longer
exist in this world.
[OGURI yells]
[OGURI]
Oh, Yokomizo.
Unlike the fool that you are,
I am able to maintain
my composure
and grace during this crisis.
[OGURI yelling]
[screams]
[ATSUSHI]
We're here to help you.
We're from the Armed
Detective Agency.
Here's what happened.
The Decay of Angels framed
the Detective Agency.
While you were trying to
warn us about their trap,
the enemy captured you.
We used the Eyes of
God to find you
so that we can get
you out of here.
Kyouka, have you dealt
with the guards?
[KYOUKA] Demon Snow
knocked them out cold.
Well, Mushitaro,
it's time we all escaped.
[OGURI]
I refuse.
Huh?
You just want me because
of my knowledge
of the Decay of Angels,
isn't that right?
But I have no need for you
or your Agency at all.
But still, don't you wanna
get out of this prison?
I'm quite familiar with
being locked up by now.
Besides, there's nothing
for me anymore.
Not in the outside
world, anyway.
Even if I leave,
he's still not...
The manuscript.
Rampo told me that you wouldn't
be able to resist that word,
and it looks like he was right.
[RAMPO] It would be enough just
to publicize the true story
behind this manuscript.
[OGURI]
Is that a threat?
You've become a true criminal
organization now, haven't you?
That may be how it looks,
but I'll become anything,
and do anything as well
in order to save the Agency.
[growls]
I see.
Then you must be aware that
what you're doing right now
will be conceived as being
tantamount to bank robbery.
After all, we're inside
a government bank.
Breaking in alone
is a serious crime.
[OGURI]
Oh, whatever.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
I will do as you want me to.
You really mean it? Thank you!
[KYOUKA]
The escape route is this way.
[OGURI]
The manuscript!
[OGURI] That was the last
remnant of Yokomizo's life
with which he entrusted me!
How dare they use it against me!
Wretched bastards!
I ought to let the
guards take them out.
Which means, I need to make
us as noticeable as possible.
Ah! My stomach is killing me!
[ATSUSHI]
Are you all right?
[OGURI] Not at all!
I'm afraid I might be a goner!
[KYOUKA]
Okay, fine.
I know of an acupuncture point
that works on stomach pain,
and all it takes is a good
jab three centimeters
above the hipbone.
[OGURI]
Oh, I'm all better!
It works so well, you feel
better before you get jabbed!
[KYOUKA]
Glad to hear it.
[OGURI] Oh, you little brat!
I'm not done yet.
This way is bad!
This hallway is aligned
with the Kabbalistic
astrology sign Taurus!
Do not tread this evil path,
you foolish normies!
I know an acupuncture point
that works on Kabbala.
The alignment's all better now!
Such a powerful
acupuncture point.
[KYOUKA]
Glad to hear it.
[GUARD A]
Yes, this is Group C.
Yes. Yes. Understood.
On our way.
What's going on?
The guards are leaving.
What the--?
[MANAGER]
P-Please, no, detective.
[ANGO]
Manager, sir.
There's a wanted man hiding
somewhere within this building.
Please cease operations
immediately.
And grant us blanketed
access security authority.
[MILITARY POLICE A] Sir, the
bank has been surrounded.
Good work.
We've assessed the targets'
special abilities.
Now hunt them down.
[OGURI]
What's the problem?
The Special Operations
Division surrounded us.
[OGURI]
Uh! It's him!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
What is he doing here?
Who is that guy?
Ango Sakaguchi.
If that man manages to catch us,
we're all doomed for sure.
Are you aware of an organization
called the Seventh Agency?
They specialize in
cleaning up crime
and engaging in cover-ups.
I've heard of it.
When Fyodor was able to rescue
you from your confinement
and he demanded cooperation
during the Cannibalism
in return.
[OGURI]
Ango Sakaguchi
is the leader of that
crime organization.
That's impossible!
Ango Sakaguchi works
for the government!
Do you still not understand?
The government is the one who
created the crime organization!
The Seventh Agency is the
government's shadow.
There were documents on
political crime cover-ups,
using illegal tactics removing
any damaging rumors,
and it was my job to
delete the evidence
on all of these things.
There's no doubt if captured,
I will be held in captivity
until the day that I die.
And you two will
be erased forever.
[KYOUKA] If that's true,
then this trap will be brutal.
The Special Operations
Division team
focuses on dealing with Gifted,
and even the Port
Mafia fears them.
If found, they'll bombard us
with poison gas and explosives,
and that'll be it.
[OGURI] So then we just need
to avoid being found.
Huh?
You don't really know
who I am, do you?
[OGURI]
Walk with pride in your step!
[GUARD B]
Hm?
[GUARD C]
Somethin' wrong?
[GUARD B]
No, nothing.
Impressed?
If we walk with stolen goods
and use my special ability
to erase evidence of crime,
we magically vanish from any
kind of surveillance video
that's recording us.
That's cool.
[ATSUSHI] No wonder Rampo
struggled against this ability.
[gasps]
[OGURI yells]
[ATSUSHI]
Kyouka, hide!
The targets we're looking
for are in this area.
There are Gifted who can
dismantle walls and ceilings.
Secure the perimeter
with caution.
It's Ango Sakaguchi.
But how? My ability is
perfect at hiding us!
Well, this is not good.
The hallway ahead is a dead
end filled with vaults.
There's nowhere to run.
Wait, wh-what if we hide
in one of the vaults?
Too dangerous.
We'd be trapped like rats.
They're coming!
[OGURI]
There's no time.
If they find us, we're doomed.
What do we do?
[SEISHI] It's like you're
trapped in a room.
[OGURI gasps]
[SEISHI] One without an exit.
Just like a locked room.
It'd make for an
entertaining mystery
if the criminal somehow
vanished from here.
What do you think, Mushitaro?
Don't you agree?
[OGURI]
You two.
[ATSUSHI, KYOUKA]
Hm?
[OGURI]
Come with me.
[MILITARY POLICE B]
Targets acquired!
They're escaping into a vault!
Neutralize the enemy!
Gifted Combat Squad, advance!
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Explosives planted.
Breach charges set.
Detonate!
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Breach!
[MILITARY POLICE A gasps]
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Command, there's no one here.
The targets have vanished.
What do you mean?
[ANGO] There's no sign they've
dug through the walls or ground.
How can this be?
There isn't even a sign
they've used special abilities.
They've vanished
without a trace.
[OGURI laughs]
[OGURI]
See that, Special Operations?
[ATSUSHI]
Are you okay?
[OGURI]
That was nothing,
just the classic vanishing act
that I perfected years ago.
What they saw was the
moment Demon Snow
closed the vault door.
We were, in fact, hiding in an
open vault closer to the exit.
[ATSUSHI]
And in the moment of the attack,
Kyouka released Demon
Snow and we escaped.
It's psychological trickery,
taking advantage
of the expectation
that only a bunch of fools would
actually hide in an open vault.
The smarter you are, the more
likely you are to fall for it.
That was amazing.
How'd you come up with that
under so much pressure?
[OGURI]
Oh, well...
I didn't come up with it.
Years ago, someone
explained it to me.
Who was that?
[OGURI]
Hide in the room next door?
Ridiculous. Would it
even count as a trick?
[SEISHI laughs]
You couldn't figure it out,
could you, Mushitaro?
[OGURI] We debated thousands
upon thousands of times.
It seeped into the very
fiber of my being.
[OGURI] Yokomizo, were you
actually always there?
Can I always meet you in
a closed room somewhere?
[SEISHI] Life seems exciting
and fun around you these days.
I'm sure that this is much
better for your well-being.
Better than writing
dull letters.
Shut up, you lousy sell-out.
You okay, Mushitaro?
Now we just need to steal
a car and go on the run.
Of course, before we run,
we have to erase the evidence
of having stolen a car
using my ability.
That way, the footage
from the security cameras
placed throughout the city
will make any video
of us stealing a car
vanish into thin air.
You sure are somethin' else.
[KYOUKA] This sewer line will
take us to a parking lot
far away from where the
guards are stationed.
[ATSUSHI]
I'll handle it.
[ATSUSHI] I'm gonna go in first
and check it out to make su--
[OGURI]
Hey!
[KYOUKA]
A dummy grenade?
[ANGO]
Unacceptable.
I can't have you thinking you
can deceive me that easily.
[OGURI]
Impossible! How did you find us?
[ATSUSHI]
Ango, please listen.
The Armed Detective
Agency is innocent.
The real enemy is
the Decay of Angels.
I need you to understand.
Believe me!
[ANGO]
There, there. I understand.
I have special abilities, too.
My special ability allows
me to extract memories
residing in objects.
I used this bundle
of stacked bills
to determine your escape route.
My ability helps me learn
about the crime scene.
Therefore, I can be certain
the Detective Agency is guilty.
And a member stabbed
Chief Taneda!
[KYOUKA] Rampo said the
government has a Gifted
who has the ability to read
the memories of an object.
He also said if we're captured,
we're bound to be executed.
You'd really beg a secret
government organization
to believe you?
The Agency's jokes have
never struck me as funny.
[ATSUSHI] I underestimated the
Special Operations Division.
[gunshots]
[ATSUSHI groans]
Huh?
[MILITARY POLICE A] Commander,
where are the targets?
[ANGO]
They got away.
They escaped
through the manhole.
They're using the
tiger's special ability
to navigate west.
Secure the whole area.
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Yes, sir.
[ANGO]
This will convince Fyodor
that we are, in fact,
actual enemies.
So you believe me that the
Detective Agency is innocent?
Because you really
seem to hide it well.
Let me put it this way,
you saw Dazai's message
back when you were
in Francis' office.
I was actually the one
who sent that message.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh? So, then--
Osamu Dazai and I have
been cooperating
since the very beginning.
I'm Dazai's messenger while he's
in a European detention center.
But if he's locked up,
how's Dazai communicating
with the outside?
All of the prisoners at
the Mersault Detention Center
are implanted with
a vital signs monitor
in order to prevent escape.
We have a system.
Dazai has the ability
to encode his messages
within his heart rate,
which I then use my government
access to retrieve and decode.
You're saying he can control
how fast his heart beats?
It's the type of party
trick Dazai's so good at.
No one would suspect a thing.
[OGURI] I don't believe you.
You're an enemy.
What was the point
of your little charade
back at the bank anyway?
There's no telling where
Fyodor has his eyes watching.
With my ability to read
the memories of objects,
I can pursue any escapee that
leaves something behind.
If I lost you, the enemy
would be suspicious.
The enemy?
The cunning Seventh Agency
is afraid of an unseen enemy?
[ANGO]
That's the thing, Mushitaro.
I'm guessing you've been told
I'm part of the Seventh Agency,
or perhaps even that
I'm their leader.
And what if I have?
[ANGO]
It's simple.
I have absolutely nothing to do
with the Seventh Agency at all.
You don't?
[ANGO] Fyodor lied. In order
to keep you away from me.
That's how afraid he is
of you and I talking.
Let's continue this
conversation elsewhere.
I know a place we can go.
We'll be safe there.
What's wrong with you?!
Are you out of your mind
or something?
What do you mean
you're "wanted"?
What type of trouble did
you bring to my door?
Are you sure that this
place is really safe?
Only those that she decides
to invite inside can enter.
It's the safest place on earth.
[ATSUSHI]
Wait, Lucy.
Why are you suddenly
working with Ango now?
I... really don't think
that's any of your business.
[ANGO]
I'm protecting her.
[LUCY]
Hey!
[ANGO] One day, she barged into
investigation headquarters.
"Atsushi's not evil!
There's no way he's a murderer,"
she said maniacally.
[LUCY] Stop it!
Don't tell him what I said!
[ATSUSHI]
Wow, that's very kind of you.
Thank you, Lucy.
Can we put aside all
that for a moment?
As you might know, Ango,
I was once captured
by an organization
that forced me to help
cover up their crimes.
That evil organization was
called the Seventh Agency.
With that in mind,
can you honestly say
that you're not
currently with them?
I'm not.
All right.
Have you ever made use of their
services for any reason?
Yes, I have.
[OGURI] Then I have no reason to
cooperate with you any further.
Don't go. It was only once.
Four years ago,
in order to solidify a way
for Dazai to live
outside the Port Mafia,
I needed to erase
his past crimes.
Why just once?
Your hands were already dirty.
I tried to make amends
for a dear friend who
is now long gone.
For a dear friend long
gone, huh? Yeah.
Mushitaro, you are
absolutely correct.
The Seventh Veil Agency is evil.
Their scope, their members,
their hierarchy,
everything is unknown.
Even I had to go through
four levels of middlemen
to work with that government
crime organization.
I believe you.
So I'm guessing
that's the reason
why you prefer working
independently.
That's right.
What is all of this about?
The man in front of you
suspects that there's a spy
working inside the government.
[ALL gasp]
I can't trust anyone anymore.
I'm the only one capable
of avenging Chief Taneda.
So to that end,
I need to hear about
everything that you know.
The knowledge that Fyodor tried
so hard to hide from me.
I ask on his behalf as well.
I know you have no
reason to tell us,
but I'm asking anyway.
[KYOUKA]
Please, help us.
[OGURI]
Where do I start?
But just so you know,
in about five minutes
you'll be regretting it.
Anything you ask me,
all of my answers will
absolutely ruin your day.
[ANGO]
In that case,
I'll ask the most important
question first.
The Decay of Angels,
just what is it?
[OGURI] The terrorist
organization Decay of Angels
is comprised of five members.
The demonic Fyodor
and jester Nikolai,
as well as two more extremely
talented Gifted.
And then one founding member
who manages them all.
You mean there's
someone above Fyodor?
[OGURI] I don't know what
their ultimate goal is,
but I do know what
their current plan is.
I'm one step ahead of it.
The erasure of the state itself.
The erasure?
Don't you mean overturning?
That's impossible!
They could never pull it off!
Don't forget that
they have the page.
Yeah, but there's only one page,
and they used it when
they framed the Agency
in the murder of Tonan
and the other officials.
That was the first time.
They get one more go.
He's right. The other
side of the page.
[OGURI]
Exactly.
The page that makes
anything written on it
become a reality is activated
the moment it's written upon.
The page is blank on both sides,
and they've already
written on one.
They can use the other side
whenever they're ready.
So they have the power to
recreate that tragedy at will.
What are they waiting for?
Why don't they use
it right away, then?
In order for the page
to be activated,
a rule must be followed.
It needs to have a narrative-
like causal consistency
like one might read
in a novel, right?
[OGURI]
Correct.
And because of that rule,
a grand conspiracy
undoubtedly requires many
lines of text to complete.
So they'll only write the
important details onto the page.
They'll deal with the trivial
details themselves separately.
They won't waste space on that.
This is the current phase
of execution for their plan.
For the next step, they'll
engage in global terrorism
before using the blank
side of the page.
And then the state will
be erased. Is that it?
[OGURI] The other side of
the page will be written
on the night of the
next full moon.
Ten days from now.
Oh, shit.
You're right. I feel like
garbage after hearing that.
For now, let me escort
you out of here.
And then I will relay
this information to Dazai.
Hey, will you be all right?
You bet I will!
We actually did it, Kyouka!
Yeah.
[LUCY] Huh?
Wh-What has gotten into you?
Ten days until the other side
of the page is written.
In other words, they can't
write anything until then.
That's right.
It'll take them at
least ten days
to prepare their final step,
which gives us ten days to
try and stop their plan.
[ATSUSHI] The Detective Agency's
been made criminals
because of the page's
reality-altering effect.
We can't undo that.
Or so I thought.
But now that's not true.
We'll take the page back
and write that the Agency
is innocent of all these crimes.
And that'll finally
fix everything.
We'll track down
the Decay of Angels
within ten days and defeat them,
then take the page back.
Simple as that.
That's all we need to do.
Kyouka, let's do it.
We still have some hope.