[CHUUYA]
Deploy Gravity Manipulation.
Hypersonic countermeasures?
But how? I didn't
hear any gunfire.
[CHUUYA] You've fucked up,
Detective Agency!
I'm here to save your asses
on the boss's orders.
Okay, time for a gunfight!
Gravity manipulation!
Grab on to it!
It's impossible.
When did he become a Detective
Agency collaborator?
To think that one day we'd
be saved by the Port Mafia.
[CHUUYA]
Saved? Idiot.
The only thing that
happened was your boss
made a deal with my boss.
The price for your rescue
is the transfer of an Agency
member to the Mafia.
We've always got room for Gifted
criminals with useful abilities.
[DOPPO]
The president did that?
He couldn't. Could he?
But if not, we all
would've gotten arrested.
And Yosano would've been killed.
[DOPPO]
You're correct.
The president knows that ideals
alone can't save lives.
We need to be
practical about this.
[ALL gasp]
[AKIKO] You think Kunikida
hit his head or something?
Maybe it's because his
core got all chopped up.
His core? Oh,
you mean his notebook.
[JOUNO]
You have an interesting pulse.
You're relieved right now.
You've lived in fear of
when that day would come.
[DOPPO]
Is he right?
If my colleagues die,
do my ideals die with them?
Am I just waiting for that day?
[TETCHOU]
Get back here.
Seriously, dude? Come on!
Shit, he's outside the chopper!
Bastard's gonna
slash up the rotors!
[DOPPO]
Tanizaki.
I want you to expose
the actual murderer!
[TETCHOU]
Evil, begone.
Don't fail.
Plum Blossoms in the Snow!
[DOPPO yells]
You're a fool if you think
that I'm going to die
from this small height.
I'll just extend my sword again
and chase the chopper.
[DOPPO]
You're the real fool here.
I won't allow anyone
to mess up my schedule!
[JOUNO] Your ideals are as lofty
and large as a hot-air balloon.
But a hot-air balloon
inevitably runs out of fuel
and returns to the ground.
My name is Doppo Kunikida.
My ideals will not fail.
I will fuel them with my life so
they will fly on for eternity!
Kunikida!
Kyouka, are you okay?
Just tired, that's all.
Of course you are.
We've been sitting
here for two days
without anything
to eat or drink.
I'm going to go look
for food and water.
[ATSUSHI]
I wonder if it's true.
I heard the inspectors
speaking about it
while we were hiding up there.
They said the president
was arrested.
And Kunikida blew himself
up during his escape.
He may not have survived.
[ATSUSHI]
How did everything come to this?
[KYOUKA] Survival.
That's our priority right now.
[CASTER]
What a terrible incident.
A government-sanctioned
detective agency
turning out to be a
terrorist organization.
It's unbelievable,
but there is video evidence of
the crime and many witnesses.
It's likely that the crimes
they've solved in the past
were in fact their own doing.
This has rocked the nation's
trust in government agencies.
[KYOUKA]
Hide your face.
We need to secure funds
to leave the city.
Then we'll escape by train.
[ATSUSHI]
Escape? And then what?
I don't know yet.
The Decay of Angels
are behind all this,
and have an impeccable,
far-reaching plan.
We don't even have a full
picture of their plot,
let alone any evidence to
prove they're behind it.
[ATSUSHI]
She's absolutely right.
If the Decay of Angels
really was behind all this,
then Fyodor must be involved.
There's no way the two
of us could take down
that monster alone.
[DOPPO] The tiger is strong,
but you're weak.
[ATSUSHI] The Agency has
saved me time after time.
But I'm not capable
of helping the Agency.
Please don't tell me that
you're giving up already.
[gasps]
Is something wrong?
[ATSUSHI]
Think.
What would Dazai do if he
were in this situation?
Wait!
There's one lead
that could prove
the Detective Agency
is innocent.
[MUSHITARO] The Detective
Agency is about to get
a huge job offer!
Don't accept it!
Mushitaro Oguri?
[ATSUSHI]
Yeah.
He warned Rampo just before
everything happened.
Somehow he knew about the plan.
He must know who the
true murderers are, too.
Maybe even how to restore
the Detective Agency
to the way it was.
[KYOUKA] But the last I heard
he'd gone missing.
So how are we supposed
to find him?
[ATSUSHI]
There's always a way.
Hello?
[KYOUKA] Isn't this system part
of Francis' Eyes of God?
You think we're safe
coming here?
Francis was our enemy before.
He might sell us out
to the Military Police.
[ATSUSHI]
He's agreed to hear us out.
[ATSUSHI] Dazai was able
to get him to cooperate
during the cannibalism.
We'll have to try
to do the same.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
I smell blood.
[ATSUSHI]
Are you all right?
[ALCOTT]
It's you.
I'm hurt, but it's
nothing serious.
You've got to hurry!
Go help Francis!
[ATSUSHI]
Stay and take care of her.
[FITZGERALD] You seem to
have lost your religion
quite spectacularly, priest.
Death to my target,
for my beloved princess.
You'll pay for what
you did to her.
[FITZGERALD]
You're talking about Margaret.
How touching that you would
attempt a rescue for her.
Even though you've
lost everything.
But you see, the disrespect
of forgetting my face
is punishable by death!
Physical boost: 50,000 dollars!
He got away.
[ATSUSHI]
He's strong.
I see why he was the
leader of the Guild.
But why was an assassin here?
Enjoying yourself?
I hope you've been comfortable
in this Port Mafia hideout.
It ought to conceal you
from the Hunting Dogs
for at least a week or two.
[AKIKO]
Mori, sir.
Do you happen to know whether
Kunikida survived the explosion?
Unfortunately, the only
thing I was able to find
was where Dazai
had disappeared to.
Dazai had already been arrested
by the Hunting Dogs
prior to the hostage situation.
The military police transferred
him to Ministry of Justice,
then to Public Security.
His subsequent whereabouts
are currently unknown.
[FITZGERALD laughs]
The Detective Agency
is innocent, you say?
[ATSUSHI]
I swear on it.
[FITZGERALD] What about
all that footage on TV
of the hostages being
murdered, then?
It was a complete frame-up.
The Decay of Angels are
the masterminds behind it.
Fyodor is a co-conspirator.
[FITZGERALD]
Even if, hypothetically,
you're speaking the truth,
the Detective Agency is doomed.
Defeating Fyodor is
utterly impossible.
[gasps]
He's in Europe being held
in a detention center.
The facility is called Mersault.
Mersault's very existence
is a national secret.
Its location is known only by
high-level European
government officials.
Needless to say,
it is impenetrable.
In fact, it's the safest
hideout in the world.
[FYODOR] Now, then,
it would be a little annoying
if Eyes of God were used
by the Detective Agency.
I ought to eliminate
its owner, just in case.
[ATSUSHI]
But if he's imprisoned,
he shouldn't be able to give
orders to the outside.
Well, he shouldn't, but that
kind of thing is his specialty.
[ATSUSHI]
So basically,
he's impossible to beat,
just as you said.
[FITZGERALD]
It's like a giant game of chess
where he's the only one allowed
to move the pieces around.
There's nothing to do.
[ATSUSHI]
Spell Bullet!
[ATSUSHI] He must have
left his blood behind
when the fountain pen hit it.
[FITZGERALD] I won't be able
to boost my strength in time.
I'm dead.
[FYODOR laughing]
And now Eyes of God are
useless to anyone but me.
I've devised a perfect plan.
But perfection is boring. Hm?
A new prisoner arriving?
[gasps]
[KYOUKA] I activated
the sprinkler system.
It was the only way
to dilute the blood.
[ATSUSHI]
Kyouka.
[FITZGERALD]
You did this?
Interesting. How did you
know about the blood?
I was under the stairwell
when a warning showed
up on the display.
[OSAMU] I've stopped your
assassination attempt,
Mister Demon.
Very well played, Dazai.
You let yourself be captured
in order to save the Agency.
The only way I can see
through your schemes
is by sitting here where
I can keep an eye on you.
[FYODOR] I'm blessed
to have a chess partner
in a place like this.
[AOKI] The Chief is expected to
awaken within the next 40 hours.
That is, if the procedure
is successful.
[YACHIYO]
Damn it.
Why did the chief go after
the enemy on his own?
This wouldn't have happened
if he followed protocol
and let us protect him.
The criminal set the conditions
for the meeting himself.
They were both to show
up alone, or not at all.
How could we fall for such
an amateur move like that?
[ANGO]
We needed the information.
The chief's Gift allows
him to learn the details
of any abilities
activated nearby.
He had stopped violent
Gifted in the past,
so he felt confident in his
ability to do so again.
Alas, the criminal
was one step ahead.
Please watch over the chief.
I'll give directions on-site.
[AOKI] Wouldn't it be best if
you stay until he awakens?
[ANGO] No. I was never on very
good terms with the chief.
The chief quantifies human
lives. Sacrifice 1 to save 100.
I couldn't stand that.
[TANEDA] If you discover the
Decay of Angels, kill them.
[ANGO]
But what of legal justice?
[TANEDA]
Ango.
What's the Special Operations
Division mission?
Peace.
It is to bless the masses with
an ignorant, peaceful existence.
To hell with the law when
peace is on the line.
And if good men have to die
for it, I'd let them die.
[ANGO]
I was oblivious to his intent.
When the said
he'd allow good men
to die for the sake of peace,
he was including
himself in that list.
I'll report on the case's
closure after the chief awakens.
And as for the murderer?
I will kill him myself.
Time for happy group
counseling hour!
[OSAMU]
Hm?
Hi, everybody. I'm your host,
Fyodor Dostoyevsky.
[OSAMU] Okay, hold up,
stop right there!
What's the problem?
Exactly. What?
Exactly, what, what?
Ohh... Life counseling.
[FYODOR] Thank you for
your prompt understanding.
Due to our high levels
of intelligence,
we have the unique ability
to read each other's minds.
Although because of that,
we are not able to provide life
counseling to other people.
Unless they have our level
of intelligence, that is.
Which is why this opportunity
will be used to discuss life's
troubles with each other.
[OSAMU]
Sure. You go first.
[FYODOR]
All right.
My subordinates just wait
on my instructions
and lack their own initiative.
How might I get them to
become more autonomous
and effective without me?
[OSAMU]
Just sit around all day
and stop giving
out instructions.
Some of them will realize
things have to change
and take it upon
themselves to act.
Very good advice.
[OSAMU]
Okay, my turn.
[FYODOR]
Go ahead.
The waitress at my favorite
cafe won't respond
to my romantic advances.
How can I get her
to accept me?
[FYODOR] Initiate a way
for her to lose her job
and trick her family
into disowning her.
That ought to convince her to
turn to you out of desperation.
How I get you.
[FYODOR, OSAMU laughing]
Now we should both try asking
a question at the same time.
Okay, good idea.
[BOTH]
Ready, set, go.
Tell me how you manage to
contact the outside world.
[FYODOR]
I figured you'd say as much.
[OSAMU]
Sure you did.
Whichever of us learns
the other's method
of communication first will be
able to ask our associates
to terminate the other's
ability to communicate.
In other words... victory.
A pity you won't see through
my method of communication.
Of course I will.
That's why I'm here.
[FITZGERALD]
Indeed.
So the evidence you need to
prove the Agency's innocence
lies with this What's-His-Name.
Was it "Mushy Pharaoh"?
[ATSUSHI]
It's Mushitaro.
The vehicle transporting him
was found on the road.
Without him in it.
All that was found inside was
an officer who was shot dead,
but Mushitaro's blood wasn't
discovered on the scene.
The enemy must have
abducted him.
And you need the Eyes of God
to find him, is that right?
It could be arranged.
Though, naturally, for a price.
[ATSUSHI]
What's your price?
[FITZGERALD]
Well, I'd like to bring Margaret
back to her former self.
[ATSUSHI]
Margaret. Oh, your employee.
[FITZGERALD] You see,
Margaret is currently in a coma.
I want the Detective Agency's
doctor woman to revive her.
Your price is Yosano?
I've come to realize Margaret
is the only person alive
who can kill Nathaniel.
You saw the attack
earlier yourself.
Nathaniel has become
a pawn for the Rats.
But he still remembers Margaret.
His desire to save her
has compelled him
to commit incomprehensible
acts of violence.
We'll take advantage of that.
[ATSUSHI] But didn't she risk
her life to protect Nathaniel?
Isn't that why she was
critically wounded
in the first place?
Precisely.
You're going to force two people
who tried to save each other
once to now go kill each other?
And what's wrong with that?
I had forgotten.
You're the man who tried
to crash the Moby Dick
into the city and murder
hundreds of thousands
of innocent people.
Again, I ask your point?
[ATSUSHI]
I think I chose the wrong person
to do business with.
Are you sure?
I feel like the president
would rip me apart
if I actually made
a deal like this.
[FITZGERALD]
Have our negotiations failed?
Very well.
But there's something that
I would like to show you
before you leave this place.
[FITZGERALD] Allow me to
introduce you. This is Margaret.
[ATSUSHI]
No. Awful.
[FITZGERALD]
During the Guild's bankruptcy,
she was seen and treated by
several abhorrent doctors.
Her symptoms only worsened.
She only agreed to take on
many of the dangerous
duties of the Guild
to have the resources to
rebuild her family estate.
At this point, that's nothing
but a vain, delusionary dream.
If Margaret could somehow
speak to us right now,
she'd beg us to terminate
her life support
and send the money being
spent on treatment
to her ancestral home instead.
[ATSUSHI]
All right. I'll take your deal.
[KYOUKA]
Are you really sure about this?
[ATSUSHI]
It's hopeless.
Whenever I see that
someone's suffering,
all I see is my younger self.
I can't just abandon them.
I think that philosophy
works well for you.
[ATSUSHI]
Let's go.
[ATSUSHI] I hope Yosano
and the others are safe.
[AKIKO]
Don't give me that bullshit!
I know you can help
prove our innocence.
You just don't want to until
we've heard your terms.
[OUGAI]
Correct.
The agreement with
President Fukuzawa
was that we would only help
the Agency in exchange
for transferring one of its
members to the Port Mafia.
Transfer a member of the Agency?
You think you're being funny?
You just want me
back in the Mafia!
Isn't that really what's
behind all this?
[BOTH gasp]
And if that's the case,
what of it?
President Fukuzawa
understood that
when he made the
agreement with me.
The president would never agree
to that in a million years.
[OUGAI]
I accept your request
to protect all Detective
Agency employees.
Though combating
the Hunting Dogs
will be quite the
daring endeavor,
even for the Port Mafia.
[YUKICHI]
What are your demands?
[OUGAI] The transfer of one
Detective Agency member
to the Port Mafia.
[YUKICHI] That will not be
an easy price for me to pay.
I have one condition.
That you don't request Yosano.
She won't tolerate being
your assistant again.
[OUGAI]
So you're wrong.
See?
Fukuzawa said he would be
willing to give you up.
[gasps]
[HIROTSU]
Boss.
Pardon the interruption,
but something came up.
This radio was at the entrance.
[FITZGERALD] Hey, how are you
doing there, old sport?
I don't have time,
so I'll make it quick.
I sent the lycanthrope
boy your way.
Lycanthrope? It's Atsushi!
He's still alive!
And the reason
for his appearance?
A transaction.
You use the healing
ability for me.
In exchange,
I provide information
that will lead to the
Agency's restoration.
Let's meet in 20 minutes.
At Goban Street.
Information leading to
the Agency's restoration!
Now we have some hope.
It is odd though.
How did Francis
discover the location
of this Port Mafia hideout?
I suppose he must have used
his Eyes of God or whatever.
[OUGAI]
That's the thing.
If he was able to
discover this hideout,
he might as well
have done business
with the military
police instead of us.
It would've been
more profitable
to do the formidable
Hunting Dogs a favor,
as opposed to the weakened
Detective Agency.
The Francis who I know
will always side with the
stronger, more aggressive group.
This transaction might
be some kind of a trap.