Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[WANG LING]
This is our secret. Promise?
[SUN RONG gasps]
[XU JIAN]
He's only a primary phase.
How can he have so much power?
Wait, what? Reversing the
timeline goes against nature!
I wouldn't do that!
[WANG LING] I'm not you
and it doesn't matter.
[SUN RONG] Besides, I believe
that my feelings for you
transcend time and space.
So no matter how the
timeline is altered,
it'll bring me back to you.
[sighs]
[FATHER WANG grunting]
Lingling...
Thank God I made it in time,
otherwise the world would
have been destroyed!
[FROGGY 2 sighs]
You finally got your amulet.
With it, the world is saved.
But you've broken
the laws of nature.
You were reckless and now
nothing will ever be the same.
By restarting the
world so many times,
you've triggered an
unmeasurable decline
in its total spiritual force.
[WANG LING sighs] Why's it so
hard to save the world?
Morning, Chief.
We caught Liuying and
she'll be in jail soon.
[CHIEF A]
Hm. Thank you, Master Zhuo.
Because of your
tireless efforts,
we eliminated the
Shadow Faction.
[ZHUO YI]
My pleasure.
Although, one mystery remains.
Who hired them to kill Sun Rong?
We're still looking.
[phone rings]
[CHIEF A]
Hello? Hm? The Competition?
Yes, I understand.
[CHIEF A] That's not good.
You catch any of that?
[ZHUO YI]
More assassins?
[CHIEF A] No. The space station
detected a spiritual force
tsunami that spawned from
Faction Fifty-nine's arena.
Gross National Spiritual
Force Product has fallen.
Spirit energy vehicles
are losing power.
[ZHUO YI]
Do we know why?
[CHIEF A] We don't.
We're still investigating.
But my superiors aren't happy
and they're putting a lot of
pressure on us to figure it out.
You're kidding. That bad?
[FEMALE ANALYST A] The world's
force value has dropped
to four point eight.
That's way too low.
Is there a way we can fix it?
[FEMALE ANALYST B]
Liking and subscribing
should give it a signal boost.
[ZHUO YI] I'm on it. We're gonna
get to the bottom of this.
[CHIEF A]
Wait, before you go,
I need you to call off
the Sword Competition.
[ZHUO YI]
Huh?
[MALE STUDENT A sighs]
Man, this freakin' sucks.
We pulled ahead of Faction
Fifty-nine in the prelims.
If it wasn't canceled, we would
have actually made the finals.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
True.
At least we made it
into the Top Ten, right?
[MALE STUDENT A]
Yeah, I guess and that was even
with a Value Five on the team.
He hasn't said much
since the competition.
Wonder what's wrong?
He usually doesn't
have that many lines.
[SUN RONG sighs]
I hope he's alright.
I wish I could help him.
He's been like this
ever since we won.
[NARRATOR] Wang Ling is simply
trying to enjoy the splendors
of his quiet daily life.
But unbeknownst to him,
the wheel of destiny
is already turning.
[MALE STUDENT B]
See ya later!
[MALE STUDENT C]
Huh?
[PAN SHENGCONG]
Hm. Very good.
It seems everyone has turned in
their summer vacation homework.
That's what I'd expect
from Class Elite.
[sighs] Glad I was able to knock
it out last night, but I'm beat.
[PAN SHENGCONG] And, although
I believe that each of you
have worked exhaustively over
the summer, our curriculum
suggests that you
should have reached
the intermediate
foundation phase by now.
In the past, we lacked proper
academic disciplines.
After beating
Faction Fifty-nine,
the Department of Education has
focused their attention on us.
So today, we will hold
a Spiritual Force Test.
Anyone who fails to
qualify as intermediate
will be expelled
from Class Elite.
[STUDENTS]
No!
Which also means Students
from Class Ordinary
who do well on the test will be
transferred to Class Elite.
It's out with the old and in
with the new, as they say.
Huh? I'm confused, have none
of you reached the next phase?
[CHEN CHAO chuckles] Unlike you,
not everyone has the talent,
or family background
to lean on.
I worked my butt off all summer
and only just broke through.
Sounds about right.
Clearly everyone else
was lazy on vacation.
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO, SUN
RONG gasp]
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO, SUN RONG]
Wait. What about Wang Ling?
[WANG LING]
Huh?
[SUN RONG gasps]
Hey there!
I don't mean to pry, but I've
got energy to spare.
Let me perfuse you!
[STUDENTS]
No!
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
You know, my father taught me
some Mercy Palms this summer.
Maybe they can help you
with your breakthrough.
Time is short,
so we'll start with one.
[SUN RONG]
Hold it right there!
Forcing a breakthrough
could damage his meridians.
Heh! Well, that's how I did it
all summer and I'm just fine!
Perfusion.
Breakthrough.
[SUN RONG]
Perfusion!
[CHEN CHAO]
Breakthrough!
[GUO HAO sighs]
Guys, you can stop now.
Look you scared him away.
Master, what about the test?
[WANG LING] This one's
for status, not strength.
It'll be hard to lay low.
[GUO HAO]
Ahem. So that test, huh?
Bit of a shocker.
Thankfully, I'm here
to help you...
...because I learned how
to make foundation pills.
We'll work together
like we did before!
Make a handful of
these pills, then boom!
We take a couple of
'em and our energy
will be supercharged
for an hour!
I mean, that's long
enough to pass!
[WANG LING] Guo Hao, is this
because you didn't level up?
[gasps]
[GUO HAO]
Eh... How'd you know?
Wang Ling, help me!
If I get expelled from Class
Elite and my parents find out,
they're gonna break every bone
in my body! Help, please!
If we can just make those
foundation pills, we'll pass!
And both stay in Class Elite!
[WANG LING sighs]
[FROGGY 2 grunts happily]
[GUO HAO chuckles]
[FROGGY 2 gasps]
[intercom crackles]
[WANG ZUKANG]
Ahem. Phase two students,
you may now enter the field.
The Spiritual Force
test will begin now.
Since I can't find the dog
we were planning to use,
we'll be utilizing the Doomsday
protocol for today's test.
The student whose
number is called
will need to stand in the center
of the formation on the stage.
And then, concentrate
their force.
The formation will automatically
adjust its power
based on the strength
of the student's energy.
To pass...
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS grunt, shout]
...you must reflect the blast.
But if you explode,
then you've failed.
[MALE STUDENT F]
Explode?
[MALE STUDENT G] This is just
a Doom Breaking simulator!
[MALE STUDENT H]
Do I still have a chance?
[MALE STUDENT I]
In ancient times,
if someone failed this,
they died!
There's no need to worry.
Modern cultivation
has come a long way.
The voltage is limited to
levels deemed safe
by the Cultivation Council.
But just in case, we have
medics standing by!
[MALE EMT B]
You've got this!
[KU XUAN] I thought this was
at the end of the semester!
--I'm not ready!
--[LI HAO] Me either.
I only broke through last night,
who knows if it'll work.
[KU XUAN]
Huh? You traitor!
You trained behind
our backs, didn't you!
[LI HAO]
Maybe I'm sorry!
Today we'll begin
testing by class.
If you're not on the stage,
feel free to warm up.
Phase two, Class One Ku Xuan.
[ALL]
Huh?
[LI HAO]
Ku Xuan, no!
[SUN RONG]
Where's Wang Ling?
I wonder if he
knows they started?
[CHEN CHAO chuckles]
I wouldn't worry.
Guo Hao is trying to find him,
and our class goes last.
They've got time.
[PAN SHENGCONG]
Hmph!
[FROGGY 2 groans]
Whew. The pills are
getting pretty close,
all thanks to you
and Froggy Two.
Heh. We'll take 'em
right before the test.
They'll last an hour.
[WANG LING]
Hm.
Ah, feels like only yesterday.
This same room, last year.
You slipped your fully
formed vitality pills
into my furnace at
the last minute,
then claimed Chen Chao's
mistake as your own.
And right then, I just knew.
You and I would be
friends for life.
[WANG LING]
Mm?!
[GUO HAO]
Hang on. You hear that?
That's gotta be...
Professor Pan!
[yelps] Isn't she
supposed to be outside?
What is she doing here?
Holy crap, what are we
gonna do, man? Why me?
Hey, uh, what's that?
--[water splashes]
--[GUO HAO gasps]
[PAN SHENGCONG]
Hm?
Huh?
[PAN SHENGCONG exhales]
Everybody's on the field,
why are you in here half-naked?
Sorry, professor.
You see, we fell into a pool,
so we're drying our clothes.
Oh really? Then what's in the
furnace behind you? Huh?
Well, uh, we can't
tell you that.
[FROGGY 2]
Hm? Mm!
[PAN SHENGCONG]
Hm...
Please don't!
[PAN SHENGCONG grunts]
Why on earth is there
a dog in here?!
[FROGGY 2 grunts]
[PAN SHENGCONG]
Move.
[PAN SHENGCONG gasps]
Oh, what the hell is this?
Well, ma'am, we wanted
to dry our socks out,
so we put 'em in the furnace.
You better get to that test
as soon as these are dry!
[GUO HAO sighs] Man, I can't
believe she bought it.
Where'd you put the pills?
[GUO HAO]
They're, uh, in my stomach.
[GUO HAO yells]
[GUO HAO] They're being digested
and overloading my meridians!
[GUO HAO]
If the excess can't escape,
I think I'm gonna explode!
[CHEN CHAO]
Guo Hao, wake up! Guo Hao?
Come on, it's your turn, dude!
Uh? Wait, how did I get outside?
Where am I?
[WANG ZUKANG]
Class Elite, Guo Hao.
If you don't get up here,
you're gonna be disqualified.
[GUO HAO]
Here! Right here! I'm coming!
I have nothin' to fear.
I took those pills.
Just have to do this
within the hour.
[GUO HAO]
Damn it! No way!
I missed my freakin' window!
The pills are done. It's no use.
Get up, boy! You have
to stand for the test!
[GUO HAO]
I'm sorry, Mom, Dad, everyone.
I'll work harder next semester
and get back into Class Elite.
I promise!
[gasps]
[CHEN CHAO laughs]
Lookin' fabulous, man!
[GUO HAO] Have... have I
transcended my phase?
Am I an intermediate?
I didn't think those
pills were so trippy!
Great job!
Well, Master,
your boost worked.
It seems to have
nudged him along.
[WANG LING]
Hm.
Phase Two, Class Elite.
Wang Ling.
[GUO HAO]
Oh, no!
I swallowed
Wang Ling's pill too!
What's he gonna do?
[WANG ZUKANG] Since Wang
Ling's spiritual force
is below average,
we'll allow him to wear a
safety helmet for the test.
[GUO HAO pants]
Wang Ling...
Uh! Master, the stage is faulty.
How so?
[JINGKE SWORD] There's a limit
for the formation's voltage,
but they didn't set
a time threshold.
You're too powerful.
When they designed this stage,
they didn't anticipate
someone like you.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Is he gonna be alright?
[gasps]
Wait. What the...?
What? What is this?
[JINGKE SWORD] Careful, you're a
spiritual capacitor
with no limit.
I got it, Jingke.
How long will it last?
[JINGKE SWORD]
Until it's exhausted
all spiritual energy around it.
[WANG ZUKANG gasps]
[SUN RONG]
Wang Ling!
[WANG ZUKANG] Stop right there!
It's far too dangerous!
So what? He could be
killed out there!
[WANG ZUKANG grunts] Quick!
Help me unplug this thing!
[JINGKE SWORD] Master, you've
burned to much energy.
[WANG LING]
Eh. Unplug it and it'll be fine.
Spiritual Force Product
is dropping--
[WOMAN A gasps]
[FEMALE ANALYST A] Oh, no.
The force value dropped again.
[FEMALE ANALYST B]
What's gonna happen?
[FEMALE ANALYST A]
It stopped.
[ALL grunting]
Hey! Wang Ling!
You'll destroy the world!
Hang on.
Sun Rong, use 'im.
Peach wood is a buffer.
[SUN RONG]
Mm!
[GUO HAO] Sun Rong,
you broke the doom!
[CHEN CHAO] Dang, where'd you
learn to swing a sword
like that?
Wang Ling, are you okay?
Sir, did I pass the test?
[NARRATOR] This incident would
later be classified as
"The Breaking of
the Doom Breaker."
But, beyond that, it was the
beginning of something more.
Wang Ling's sword used
an amount of force
so excessive that it ripped
a crack in space and,
through this crack,
the spiritual impulses
of the human world began
to disperse into another.
♪
[GUO HAO] Now this is
Precision Craftsmanship.
The formation is destroyed,
but this thing survived!
[WANG ZUKANG] Why couldn't
we unplug it, though?
Perplexing.
[PAN SHENGCONG]
You're supposed to pull it up.