Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[LIUYING JIANG]
Why, hello there, handsome.
What's a girl gotta do for
a little bathroom break?
[LIUYING JIANG giggles]
[giggles]
[MALE GUARD A]
Heh! I'm disappointed.
For the leader of
the Shadow Faction,
you're trying some
pretty old tricks.
Don't waste your breath.
After your failed breakout,
we hired additional security,
and they see everything.
Also, don't do this.
Your new cage has
power limiters.
You can't seduce me.
When I get outta here,
I will obliterate all of you!
Oh yeah? Need these? Might help.
[gasps]
[LIUYING JIANG]
I know this evil.
It's the Ultimate Control!
[LIUYING JIANG laughs]
Thank God.
The universe always delivers.
♪
[ZOMBIES groaning]
Don't move. If we stay quiet,
they won't find us.
[SUN RONG] Mm. Wouldn't
surprise me. They seem dumb.
It's mind control.
[MAN A chuckles]
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG,
WANG LING] Mm?
--[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG gasp]
--[WANG LING] Great.
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG yell]
[WANG LING]
Hurry.
Now what? They're gaining on us!
Master, your full-powered
Trick of Forgetting
should break the curse,
so why not use that?
[WANG LING] If I do, they'll
suffer permanent brain damage.
[SUN RONG]
Oh no! This way's a dead end!
Hold on!
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG]
Huh?
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG gasp]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
No way! You're awesome!
Three people at once,
on a small sword!
Hey, now! I'm a magic sword
spirit, not just a small sword.
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[WANG LING]
We're safe.
Thanks, Wang Ling.
What do we do now?
Well, first off, we need to
know how to break the curse.
It's hard. Ultimate Control
is governed by nature.
Normal dispels won't work.
[SUN RONG] Hm? How'd you
avoid getting enchanted?
Maybe I'm not charming enough.
[WANG LING, SUN RONG gasp]
Who did that?!
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Oh God!
They're climbing each
other like a ladder!
[SUN RONG groans]
I can't take it anymore.
Master, you need me?
Wait... Look.
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
It's Chen Chao!
[ALL gasp]
So fast.
[CHEN CHAO]
Sun Rong!
Do you wanna go out with me?
No, I don't.
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
Wait. He's sick.
[grunting]
It hurts so much!
Where am I?
What happened?
[SUN RONG] Guys, look!
He's back to normal!
Guess the curse is broken!
I think I get it. Chen Chao
landed on his head, right?
They just need a
nice whack, is all!
No.
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
My chest. It hurts!
[SUN RONG gasps]
I see now!
Once I'd rejected him,
the curse broke.
Break hearts and you
break the control.
[CHEN CHAO] Huh? Hang on,
when did you reject me?
That's enough! I don't
like any of you that way!
[ZOMBIES sob]
[SUN RONG sighs]
They're finally free.
Yeah, these ones are.
There's a lot more, though.
True, but she could reach them
all if she did a livestream.
[SUN RONG]
Mm-hm. That's a great idea.
Huh? There's no service.
--[LIUYING JIANG laughs]
--[ALL] Huh?
Look, over there!
[SUN RONG]
Hold on. I know that laugh.
[CHEN CHAO]
It's Jiang Liuying!
You really are Sun's daughter.
You figured out how to release
those followers pretty quickly.
Unfortunately for you,
it wasn't quick enough.
[SUN RONG] What did she say?
Can you hear her?
[CHEN CHAO]
Eh...
And now, this cell
tower is mine.
So if you wanna use your phone,
you'll have to surrender
yourselves to me!
[XIAOYU LIN, CHEH CHAO,
SUN RONG shouting]
[LIUYING JIANG]
Huh?
[XIAOYU LIN] We get it,
you're the bad guy!
But we're trying to help you!
[LIUYING JIANG]
Huh?
What the hell?!
[ALL grunt]
Huh?
[CHEN CHAO]
Where'd that come from?
[XIAOYU LIN]
Zombies in the streets,
meteors crashing into the Earth.
Is this the apocalypse?
[SUN RONG]
You think she's alive?
[RICHMAN sighs]
Damn it all.
Missed the mark, yet again.
[SUN RONG sighs]
Great. The cell tower's gone.
Now I can't livestream.
[CHEN CHAO] Who cares?
We can just find another tower.
Ugh. I wish. My family
maintains this tower.
The next closest one is
thousands of kilometers away.
What do we do now?
[WANG LING]
We go there.
Oh yeah! Fort Skyloop is
Huaxiu's largest space station.
Up there, we can
stream world-wide.
True but, how do
we get up there?
Does your family have a rocket?
We're not that rich, okay?
[SUN RONG, XIAOYU LIN,
CHEN CHAO] Huh?
[SUN RONG] You have tickets
for a one-day Skyloop tour?
[CHEN CHAO] Dude, really?
Where'd you get those?
[REPORTER A] While the
performers work their magic,
we have some awesome
giveaways for our viewers!
The first prize is two
tickets to Fort Skyloop,
so don't forget to
leave a few comments!
[XIAOYU LIN whimpers]
I dunno. Can your little
wooden sword handle this?
Don't let go!
You do, and we all get
trampled by those zombies!
[JINGKE SWORD]
Please, Master.
Don't you think I'm a little too
old to be ferrying around
four people like this?
Crispy noodles.
You'll get two packs.
[JINGKE SWORD gasps]
[CHEN CHAO, SUN RONG,
XIAOYU LIN yell]
[SUN RONG, XIAOYU LIN gasp]
[SUN RONG] How are they
catching up so fast?
Listen. There's two
tickets and four of us.
Yeah, so? What do you mean?
[XIAOYU LIN]
Sun Rong,
only two people can get on
the train to the Skyloop.
Go with Wang Ling.
Hang on!
[CHEN CHAO] Wang Ling, this is
an order from your class chief.
Go save the world.
[SUN RONG] But if you stay,
you'll be overrun by zombies!
[CHEN CHAO]
Hmph! Just a hundred thousand.
We're good.
Roger.
[SUN RONG gasps]
No, Xiaoyu!
[CHEN CHAO]
Hm!
When we get to the Skyloop,
you can livestream there.
I know but, when it's all done,
will they remember me?
[SUN RONG] Wait a minute.
This atmosphere.
The way he's talking.
Do you think he's gonna...?
[WANG LING]
Sun Rong.
Yeah?
[WANG LING]
There's something... I just--
Don't hesitate. I mean, it could
be the end of the world.
[gasps]
Really, you sure?
[SUN RONG grunts]
Yes! Just say it!
You probably noticed...
...there was... no one
to check our tickets.
[SUN RONG]
Hm? What? You're kidding, right?
No, they could
have come with us!
These were pointless.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Good evening.
Our next stop is Fort Skyloop.
Please collect your
personal belongings
and prepare to exit the shuttle.
The next stop is...
[CHEN CHAO]
Well, looks like they made it.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Yeah. I'm not gonna lie.
I thought we were toast,
but they ignored us and
went after the train.
Yep. They all want Sun Rong.
You ready?
[SUN RONG]
Mm-hm. All right. Let's go.
[GUO HAO groans]
Hello, welcome to
my livestream,
and thank you for being here.
As many of you may know, I grew
up in a very prominent family.
When I was little,
I thought it was normal to
be the center of attention.
It wasn't until I enrolled
at Faction Sixty
that I realized the world
didn't revolve around me
and that I wasn't the
perfect daughter.
So I worked hard to improve
myself until we went broke,
and I sunk into a
profound depression.
Suddenly, I realized the things
I had taken for granted
my whole life were the
most valuable of all.
And then it became
clear to me.
People were only drawn to me
because of my family's status.
I just wanted everyone's love.
To get that validation,
I entered the
Sword Arts Contest.
And for reasons
beyond my control,
I got the love of
the entire world.
But, now I understand.
I was wrong. I don't
need all of your love.
I'm really sorry.
Just one man's love. That's it.
[gasps]
[CROWD sobbing]
[SUN RONG]
Wang Ling. It's done.
I rejected the entire world.
[WANG LING sighs]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
She was able to pull it off!
Hey, look! What's that?
[FEMALE ANALYST B]
Red alert!
A twenty kilometer meteor is
plummeting toward the earth!
[FEMALE ANALYST A gasps] Are we
due for another mass extinction?
[RICHMAN laughs]
[RICHMAN] I'll see this
one through to the end.
I will not miss again!
[RICHMAN laughs]
[RICHMAN]
If I'm going to die,
I'm dragging the whole
human world down with me!
[SUN RONG gasps]
I'm scared.
Don't be.
[RICHMAN gasps]
[gasps]
[CHEN CHAO, XIAOYU LIN laugh]
[SUN RONG]
Huh?
[WANG LING]
Hm?
[SUN RONG gasps]
♪