Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
♪
[LIUYUE JIANG]
"Routine Maintenance
of a Spiritual Sword.
Season Two."
[WANG ZUKANG]
Listen up.
The more we utilize our
swords in our daily lives,
the more problems they develop.
[WANG ZUKANG]
For instance, they become blunt,
[gasps]
[WANG ZUKANG]
or run slower than usual.
Not good.
This means that your swords
are unhappy, period.
[AUDIENCE]
Oh!
[WANG ZUKANG] The metal gets
dull after repeated impacts,
or when it's used
inappropriately.
An unhealthy diet can have
especially negative effects.
[WANG ZUKANG sighs] If you're
careless, you can cause
irreversible damage to
the sword and its spirit.
[LIUYUE JIANG] Whatever shall
we do, Professor Zukang?
Read my book!
Spiritual Swords and Me .
Available now!
[JINGKE SWORD] Master, you know
I haven't had any maintenance
since I was forged.
[WANG LING]
Hm.
[WANG ZUKANG]
Be ready.
This year's advanced spiritual
sword classes start next week.
Make sure to have
your swords ready
before those lessons begin.
[GUO HAO]
Hey, Sun Rong.
Did you ever get
your sword fixed?
Well, we finished
reforging the body,
but the spirit still needs time.
[SUN RONG chuckles]
It's fine.
So, you guys taking good
care of your swords?
[CHEN CHAO chuckles] Your boy
bought himself a maintenance kit
from the internet.
[SUN RONG] But the only tool
kits you can find online
are for Class C
swords and below.
Like Zukang said,
medium or large swords
have to be taken
to a Four-S shop.
Mine is a Class D, and it
needs service regularly.
Your sword is extra-large,
there's no way to
do that at home.
She's not wrong. Mine got rusty.
It could use some love.
Dude, you should really
take care of that.
And whaddaya know? My kit's
perfect for small swords
like yours, so let me
help ya out!
There's a shop near my house.
Appreciate the offer, though!
I can even get 20% off!
[SUN RONG]
Oh, you mean this shop?
You're looking at a VIP member!
Hey, Wang Ling.
If you're not too busy, would
you wanna hang out with us?
Oh, I forgot to ask.
How's your sword?
[WOMEN giggling]
[NARRATOR]
Wang Ling's sword, Jing Ke,
is technically a mature spirit.
Which means he gets his
maintenance without supervision.
[CHEN CHAO] Whoa, look at it!
It's beautiful!
Are all Four-S shops like this?
No, this is their
flagship store.
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO gasp]
[GUO HAO]
Whoa! Check it out!
The Legendary Fire's Joy,
I read about it in Popular
Blades magazine!
--[SUN RONG gasps]
--[CHEN CHAO] No way!
Is anyone strong enough
to use this thing?
[XIAOYU LIN] Ever heard
of the ancient Juque?
It's the pride of our shop.
[ALL]
Lin Xiaoyu!
[XIAOYU LIN giggles]
[XIAOYU LIN grunts]
[SUN RONG, GUO HAO gasp]
So cool. You're such
a professional!
[XIAOYU LIN]
Mm. I grew up around them.
As long as I can remember,
I was raised by a sword spirit.
[camera clicks]
Where were your parents?
[GUO HAO, XIAOYU LIN]
Mm?
I wish I could tell you.
They entrusted me to my sword.
[GUO HAO]
So where is it now?
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Uh.
When I was eight years old,
she left and never returned.
The last thing she did
was leave me a note.
[XIAOYU LIN'S SWORD SISTER]
I'm headed to Songhai
for maintenance.
See you in a few days!
[SUN RONG gasps] You think she
ran into trouble or something?
Who knows? I bet
she just got lost.
She probably has a terrible
sense of direction like I do.
[ALL]
Eh...
So, for all these years,
I've worked in
different sword shops.
Hoping one day
I'll see her again.
[CHEN CHAO whimpers]
A beautiful tragedy. She refuses
to buy another sword
until she can see her
sword sister again.
Actually, no. I'm poor.
That's why.
[XIAOYU LIN giggles]
What about our sword class?
Wait, someone from your school
can't afford a sword?
That's surprising even
for Faction Sixty.
[LIANG ZHENG, LIANG FEI laugh]
Ha! Great. Back for
revenge already?
I wouldn't get too excited, kid.
Our swords need love, too.
[LIANG ZHENG grunts]
Since she's good at her job,
I'll tip extra.
But I'm gonna need the whole
maintenance package,
sharpened and polished,
by tomorrow.
I would, sir, but this
is a large batch.
It'll take three days.
Excuse me. We already have her
booked for the rest of the day.
You'll need to find
someone else.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Uh! No, no, no, no, no!
It's fine. I'll stay
late and do both jobs.
Ha! That's it.
You're a smart girl.
Lin Xiaoyu, was it?
Just work hard and be better,
then you could get a bigger tip.
Maybe even afford that sword.
Don't patronize her!
I'll report you--
It's alright, Sun.
I make my money per-job.
This gives me a
chance to earn more.
Are you sure?
[TANG JINGZE laughs]
[TANG JINGZE]
Enjoy that paycheck,
you're really gonna
earn it this week!
[LIANG FEI]
Heh!
[CHEN CHAO]
Stupid Tang Birdie Two,
he's just a big bully.
She loves spiritual
swords so much,
but she doesn't even have one.
No wonder she's living
at the school.
Her life's pretty rough.
Would it be weird if
I just bought her one?
She wouldn't have
to work so hard.
[GUO HAO]
Mm. I don't think you should.
Might hurt her self-esteem.
[CHEN CHAO] What if we did
a really cool fundraiser?
Huh? That's the same thing!
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO]
Uh.
This is where you
build your own.
We could just...
forge one for her.
[CHEN CHAO] Wang Ling.
You're a genius, dude!
[XIAOYU LIN grunts]
[XIAOYU LIN hums]
[GUO HAO] She was here so late.
When does the poor girl sleep?
Sun Rong, are you sure we won't
get in trouble for this?
It's fine. I got the
manager's permission.
Works for me!
We got all the stuff?
Cool. Are you done
with the design?
Not gonna lie, that's pretty
twisted, dude.
What the hell, man? Let's go!
I'm so pumped, I can't take it!
[SUN RONG gasps]
Hold on.
We need to analyze
our materials first.
We can't skip this step!
[GUO HAO grunts]
[MALE ANNOUNCER A]
Spiritual beast bones.
Three point five ounces.
Grade A.
[laughs]
I yanked these teeth out of
a level three night devil tiger.
I pinned him down
with a sliding tackle.
Oh, come on, no one
likes a bragger.
[GUO HAO gasps]
[MALE ANNOUNCER A]
Phecda meteorite.
Approximately Ten pounds.
Grade S.
[GUO HAO gasps]
Where'd you find a Grade S item?
[CHEN CHAO chuckles]
[FATHER CHEN]
Hm. My Star of Fighters.
May you bless the Chens
and our martial prowess.
[yells]
[CHEN CHAO chuckles]
Uh, from home.
Sun Rong! What stuff
did you bring?
[MALE ANNOUNCER A]
Universal Hair Growth Lotion.
Grade S-Plus Treasure.
What is this thing?
That kinda item is totally
out of our league!
[CHEN CHAO] Sun, where can
I find one of these?
[GUO HAO gasps]
[SUN RONG gigles] That's only
for us girls to know.
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO, SUN RONG]
What's that thing?
I found it.
What's happening?
The meter's going nuts,
I don't think it's gonna stop!
[GUO HAO gasping]
Why are you smacking it?
Stop it. You're gonna break it!
[GUO HAO yells]
[GUO HAO]
What does that mean?
[CHEN CHAO chuckles] All right!
What do we do next?
According to this,
the next step is
taking all the materials and
smelting them in the furnace.
Right. How do we do that?
[GUO HAO]
We've come this far.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Mm...
One, two...
[XIAOYU LIN]
Hm...
[CHEN CHAO]
Yoo, hoo! Good morning!
You guys were faster than me!
Are you here to pick
up your swords?
[SUN RONG chuckles]
[SUN RONG]
For you.
[CHEN CHAO] Heh. Spiritual sword
class starts soon.
You didn't have one and
we didn't want you to get
left behind, so we thought...
[GUO HAO] Maybe we could
combine some of our stuff
and make you one.
--[XIAOYU LIN whimpers]
--[CHEN CHAO, SUN RONG gasp]
Is it no good?
We tried teaching ourselves in
the tutorial area. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too. I didn't control
the temperature very well.
[CHEN CHAO]
No, it was my fault.
I was kinda nervous, so my
hammering was shaky.
No, it's not that.
You did nothing wrong.
It just... looks so
much like my old one.
[ALL gasp]
Wang Ling designed it.
He must have known!
He's got such a gentle,
beautiful soul.
You guys, thank you!
This is the best gift ever,
and I love it!
It feels so great to
have a sword again!
[TANG JINGZE]
Congrats!
You made a sword so ugly
she started crying!
Ugh. You again?
Why? Hasn't she done
enough for you?
While you wasted your time
slacking off with friends,
I was having the store
manager take care of
the maintenance for me.
Ha! I'm sure it needed a lot of
work after I destroyed it.
Isn't that right,
Tang Birdie Two?
[GUO HAO laughs]
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
[TANG JINGZE]
Tell me.
She's one of your employees,
is she not?
Birdie-- Master Tang.
[TANG JINGZE]
As a VIP, aren't I allowed
to ask any employee to
help test my blade?
Excuse me. I'm a VIP too.
As such, I request her first.
[MALE EMPLOYEE A]
Eh... Sorry, Miss Sun.
He has an appointment
before yours.
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG gasp]
[TANG JINGZE laughs]
Valiant effort,
but none of your tricks
will work here,
[TANG JINGZE] because this shop
is operated by the Tang family.
Remind me again, Ling Xiaoyu?
Bring your sword.
Let's find out how well
your friends made it.
Don't go! Just stay here.
Sorry, but I don't
wanna lose this job.
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[XIAOYU LIN whimpers]
[GUO HAO] That's an insane
amount of armor.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
[gasps]
[TANG JINGZE]
Hm... Smooth and sturdy.
What masterful maintenance.
Your move, new kid.
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Lin no, watch out!
Hey, good sir. If you were
to violate the rules,
I would have to
ask you to leave.
Come on! This is too dangerous,
and you know it!
He's right. It is, but not
for the reasons you think.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps, groans]
Guys, what's happening?
Oh, that's her new blade
devouring the force
from Tang and his sword.
[TANG JINGZE yelling]
[gasps]
[TANG JINGZE groaning]
[groans]
[SUN RONG, CHEN CHAO,
GUO HAO gasp]
[CHEN CHAO]
You did it!
[TANG JINGZE gasps]
My Blowing Snow...
[CHEN CHAO] Over here!
Lin, are you alright?
[GUO HAO]
Lin!
[ALL laugh]
[SUN RONG] Lin, you almost
scared me to death!
Master, I'm done here.
The girls at the shop
were very enthusiastic.
♪
[DEMON COUNSELOR growling]
[DEMON COUNSELOR laughs]
[DEMON COUNSELOR gasps]
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
Huh?
[DEMON COUNSELOR shouts]
[gasps]