Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
Richman!
Would you care to tell me
why you're doing that?
It's because now...
I finally understand.
We've been wasting our time
on Sun's descendant.
Our real enemy is
her sidekick. That boy.
He's a cunning wolf
in sheep's clothing.
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
Yes, but we should be conquering
the human world,
not destroying it!
[DEMON EMPEROR] Counselor,
he may do what he must.
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
I-- Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, thank you.
[RICHMAN laughs] I'll see
this one through to the end.
I will not miss again!
[RICHMAN]
If I'm going to die,
I'm dragging the whole
human world down with me!
[RICHMAN gasps]
[gasps]
[WANG LING]
Hm?
[gasps]
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs, grunts]
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
Richman, no!
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Counselor, you must light
the dimensional lamps.
[DEMON COUNSELOR] Yes.
Right away, Your Majesty.
[SUN RONG] Hey, uh, we're pretty
lucky to be in Fort Skyloop.
We should stay a bit longer.
[WANG LING]
Mm.
--[SUN RONG] Let's go!
--[WANG LING] 'Kay.
Huh? Is it me, or does
something feel off?
What happened to us?
Look. we're three-dimensional!
[WANG LING] Hold on.
Things look normal out there.
[SUN RONG gasps]
♪
[MAN A shouts]
[CROWD shouting]
[roars]
[PREDECESSORS chattering]
[MALE PREDECESSOR C] Do you
realize I was on my vacation?
Do you?
What was so important we
couldn't just do this online?
What you did was dangerous!
You can't cut off a man's
treatments like that!
We tried to call you,
but the meteor shower
ruined our signal.
We're in a crisis!
Demons are here and all you can
think about is your vacation?
Well, send in the
Seven-Star Squad!
This is what the D-O-C
pays you for, anyway!
[ZHUO YI] Most of the squad
is evacuating civilians,
we don't have the manpower
to launch a counterattack.
[MALE PREDECESSOR D]
What, we're just gonna roll over
and play dead?
No, we've got a plan but--
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
Spit it out!
[ZHUO YI] Ahem. This portal
is above Faction Sixty.
To meet the demons as they're
breaching, I've had a doom
breaking formation
installed on the schoolyard.
A few months ago, a cultivator
used that spot to channel
massive lightning strikes.
That's the plan?
You're proposing we use
one of our best
practitioners as a conduit
so he can play doom breaker
and hope that kills them all?
[ZHUO YI] Yes, sir and we're
gonna need a lot of energy.
But we've lost contact
with the top practitioner.
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
Heh. He's a loser,
why would we send
that coward, anyway?
If you want the best, send me.
I've got boatloads of energy.
Sir, you're just not
strong enough for that.
[MALE PREDECESSOR C grunts]
Shut up!
I won't stand here
and listen to this.
If you want the best there is,
I'll show you what
I'm really capable of.
[SUN RONG grunts]
[SUN RONG]
Ocean go!
[gasps]
[SUN RONG]
It came back. What now?
We're not going to escape
by running in circles.
[WANG LING]
We could try the sides.
Wait, what?
I'm gonna break
through the walls.
[SUN RONG] You do know
we're in space, right?
[WANG LING]
It's fine.
The Guardian Light
will keep you safe.
Huh?
A way out. Awesome!
Huh? Hold on, who's there?
[SUN RONG gasps]
That's impossible!
How is this happening?
[WANG LING] We're trapped
in a spatial cycle.
Huh? What are we gonna do?
My sword. He could break
the cycle for us.
I could've, if you didn't
throw me so far.
[DEMON EMPEROR] Impressive.
You've managed to trap
the greatest threat
from the human world
using only 3,090
dimensional lamps.
Your technique is quite
remarkable, counselor.
[DEMON COUNSELOR] You humble me,
noble Emperor of Demons.
Aside from the occasional
dimensional spirit artifact,
there's nothing that can shatter
my three-dimensional seal!
I must admit, thirty of
the lamps were knocked
over by accident, so the
formation won't be able to reach
its full power potential,
but the remaining 3,060
should do the trick.
[DEMON EMPEROR] It's only
30 fewer lamps, right?
What difference could it make?
Tell me, how is the
war for Earth going?
[CROWD shouting]
[DEMON A growls]
[MAN B whimpers]
[FEMALE MAGIC MEMBER A]
Master Zhuo,
you managed to pull him away.
Is everyone out?
Almost.
[ZHUO YI] Is the doom
breaking formation ready?
[FEMALE MAGIC MEMBER A]
Not yet, but it will be soon.
[FEMALE MAGIC MEMBER A
gasps, shouts]
You there? Hey, A-Thirty-Four,
do you copy?
[FEMALE REPORTER A] It appears
that thousands of demons are
flooding through a portal that's
just opened up over Songhai.
Currently, the Seven-Star Squad
is fighting the demons,
in the streets. For your safety,
please evacuate the area.
Sweetheart, we gotta go.
My Lingling!
I'm worried about him.
But he's OP!
Oh yeah.
[SUN RONG gasps]
Right back where we started.
Wang Ling, are we gonna
to be stuck here
for the rest of our lives?
I guess it doesn't matter.
Even if we get out, we're not
gonna have a world
to go back to anyway.
[WANG LING]
Found it.
[SUN RONG]
Huh? Found what?
It's the control panel.
[SUN RONG] A control panel?
What does that do?
[WANG LING]
Polygons multiply!
[SUN RONG gasps]
No way! So cool.
We're high res now and our
movements are so much smoother,
it's insane!
[WANG LING grunts]
I bumped up the graphics
and removed the
frame-rate limit.
That's not good.
[SUN RONG gasps]
What's going on now?
[DEMON A]
Foolish humans.
We have you
completely surrounded.
Lay down your weapons
and bow to me!
Surrounded? Ha! I don't
think you understand.
You're the one who's surrounded.
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
Lightning come, empower me,
Bilibilelectricity!
[DEMON B growls]
[DEMON A growls]
[MALE PREDECESSOR C] Ha! Behold,
my doom breaking lightning!
To your weak demon skin,
this power's catastrophic!
[DEMON A grunts]
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
Heh! Huh?
[DEMON A growls]
Everyone rally to me!
Protect the Great Master!
[MAGIC MEMBERS]
Yes, sir!
[DEMON A growls]
[SUN RONG] With a great
master in the fight,
this should be over soon.
[WANG LING]
Maybe.
[SUN RONG]
Huh? What do you mean?
Look at that lightning,
how could we lose?
They put up the
rallying flags.
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Hm. How intriguing.
[MAGIC MEMBERS chattering]
Oh no.
[CROWD shouting]
[grunts]
[MALE PREDECESSOR C shouting]
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Huh?
[MALE PREDECESSOR C shouting]
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs]
[DEMON COUNSELOR laughs]
[MALE PREDECESSOR C shouting]
[coughs]
[ZHUO YI gasps]
It's gone. I-It's all gone.
The entire world, up in flames.
--It's hopeless.
--[WANG LING] No. Not yet.
[SUN RONG]
Huh? Really? What are you doing?
We already tried that several
times, and it hasn't gotten--
[WANG LING]
It's not what you think.
[SUN RONG gasps] Oh well, this
may sound like a dumb question,
but why are you
moving that mirror?
The demon seal.
It functions like a 3-D game
and what we're seeing is
being rendered in real-time.
Oh! No wonder.
I thought I saw it stutter.
I bet those were
frames dropping.
[SUN RONG gasps]
I have an idea.
If we overload the
graphics card,
I bet we could destroy the seal!
[WANG LING] That's the plan
and the best way to tank
performance is with
real-time reflections.
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
No! What's happening?
[gasps] You see it?
Your trick's working!
Frames are dropping like crazy!
[WANG LING]
All right. Call out Ocean.
[DEMON COUNSELOR gasps]
[SUN RONG]
She's making it even worse.
Her particle effects
are causing it to crash!
[DEMON COUNSELOR] Damn it!
Air cooling is insufficient!
[WANG LING]
Ray tracing... on.
[DEMON COUNSELOR gasps]
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
What?
This is impossible!
My thirty-sixty, no!
Wang Ling, we really did it!
We overloaded the system!
[WANG LING] Sun Rong, wait here.
I've gotta save the world.
[SUN RONG] If you go back now,
they'll know who you are!
[grunts]
Who cares? It's showtime.
[SUN RONG gasps]
[coughs, gasps]
[ZHUO YI gasps]
Master, I knew you'd come back!
[FEMALE REPORTER A] The battle
for Songhai took a sharp turn
after a mysterious practitioner
sunk one of the demon carriers.
[MALE MAGIC MEMBER J]
Who's that?
[gasps]
[FEMALE REPORTER A] This just
in, the practitioner disappeared
with what looked
like a butterfly girl!
Now what? He's just gone?
♪