Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
Are we live?
Oh. Hello, hello,
my little cubbies!
And welcome to your favorite
Fairy Fox's livestream!
So today, we've got a package
from a fellow cultivator!
Oh! And this one
comes from Li Chao!
Thanks so much, my cubby wubby!
Now who's ready to rip it open
and see what's inside?
[CHEN CHAO giggles]
[FAIRY FOX]
Huh. I don't know what it is.
Tongue of the Heavenly
Hound medicine?
[chuckles]
So, you like it, Fairy Fox?
How's your master been
feeling today? Any better?
[FAIRY FOX gasps] Thank you
for asking, my friend.
On behalf of my master,
I want you to know I
appreciate you, but...
...he's still
unconscious in the ICU,
so I wish I had better news.
However, thanks to your kind and
thoughtful donation of medicine,
I think my master will
feel better real soon!
[CHEN CHAO] I'll do everything
I can to help you
in your time of need.
[FAIRY FOX] I don't know
what I'd do without you.
You've been so generous.
How could I possibly repay
you for your kindness?
If it's okay with you,
I was thinking maybe
we could have a private chat,
just the two of us?
[shouts]
♪
[ZHUO YI] Ancestral leaders
of the past, thank you
for coming out of retirement
to be here, all of you.
Well, why are we here?
Must be of great importance,
to summon us old retirees.
The world's total energy has
dropped to four point seven.
We've got a crisis on our hands.
[MALE PREDECESSOR B] The same
thing happened last year!
So what? You gathered
us all up for that?
Not quite. The spirit shell
protecting the world
has weakened because
of the low energy.
In its fragile state,
a spatial crack has formed,
enabling demon spies
to infiltrate our world.
I've got an easy solution.
We could just build a wall.
A huge one. Frankly, I alone
can revive the energy
and then make the
human race great again!
[MALE PREDECESSOR D] We know
exactly what the demons want!
They've had their greedy eyes
on our world for an eternity,
and they're willing to go
to war to take it from us!
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
Hmph. That is fake news!
Trust me, I know demons!
A lot better than you!
You idiot! You think building
a wall will stop 'em?
We must take initiative
and strike them first!
Gentlemen, we don't know the
demon world coordinates.
If we attempt to find it now,
we could get lost
in spatial storms.
[MYSTERIOUS PREDECESSOR A]
Why bother?
We could capture a demon
and interrogate them.
Problem solved.
[MALE PREDECESSOR C]
The demons are good people,
just get in there
and make a deal.
They won't do anything reckless.
[MALE PREDECESSOR D] You know,
when you put it that way,
maybe we should keep
our ideas to ourselves.
[sighs]
Why'd they go offline?
[GUO HAO]
Wang Ling. Come on!
Hello! Earth to Wang Ling!
What's wrong?
It's Chen Chao.
His dad's here and
he's really pissed off!
Huh?
[STUDENTS chatter]
[GUO HAO grunts]
'scuse us.
[MALE STUDENT B]
Huh?
Stupid boy. What's the
matter with you?
Why have you dropped
down a phase?
Well, father, one of the
lessons you taught me
as a child was to be
kind and help others.
And as fate would have it,
I found someone that needs help.
Her master was hurt so bad that
he's unconscious in the ICU,
and now she spends
her time livestreaming
to raise money for him.
You gave your energy
to this temptress,
all in an effort to
save her master?
[CHEN CHAO]
Yes, father!
[FATHER CHEN]
Hm... You know what they say.
Good deeds will always
trump good intentions,
reckless or not. You did
this for someone in need.
I am happy those family
lessons were taken to heart.
You may keep your phone.
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
Thanks, father!
[FATHER CHEN] While I'm here,
do you happen to know
where our family's Tongue
of the Heavenly Hound is?
[CHEN CHAO]
Uh, well.
[FAIRY FOX] Since Li Chao
sweetly gifted this Tongue
of the Heavenly Hound,
today I'll return the favor
with a special live chat!
It's not what you think.
Sir, please let me explain.
[FATHER CHEN]
Enough!
You didn't care about her
master's well-being at all.
You did this to impress her.
Stupid boy, you're gonna
pay for this!
[CHEN CHAO yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[CHEN CHAO whimpers]
[CHEN CHAO]
Fairy Fox!
If I see you watching
another live stream,
you'll lose more
than your phone.
[SUN RONG]
What's wrong with him?
And how did watching
a livestream
knock him down a phase?
We live in the
seven-twenty-nine-G era now.
The bandwidth is so insane,
it even supports donations
of spiritual energy!
Uh. You can donate,
but not that much.
It's witchcraft.
Witchcraft?
Long ago, demons would
disguise themselves
as pretty women and then
drain their victim's energy,
leaving their bodies
frail and disabled.
I'm guessing Chen Chao was
seduced by the dark arts.
[SUN RONG]
How do you know all this?
[XIAOYU LIN] Oh, I dunno.
I guess I've always been
fascinated by the
more obscure magic.
Guys, he's fine.
When his Dad embarrassed
him in front of the school,
he learned his lesson.
[CHEN CHAO laughs]
--[GUO HAO] Huh?
--[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[FAIRY FOX yawns] Welcome back
to the livestream,
my little Li Chao!
Why'd you go offline and
leave me all alone?
Eh, dealing with family stuff.
Nothing bad.
[SUN RONG sighs]
That boy's a lost cause.
You think a demon's
involved somehow?
That would make sense.
Is there any way to
break the spell?
The quickest way is to
use a meta spirit.
Once inside the internet,
they find the demon's location
and disrupt their dark arts.
This method requires someone at
a golden pill phase or higher.
And, if they're powerful enough,
they could even transfer
their physical body.
[GUO HAO]
You guys can sit back and relax.
Infecting the demon's channel
should do the trick.
[GUO HAO chuckles]
Ooh! I love it! What is it?
[GUO HAO] You mean Trojan?
She's my digital spirit beast.
I've raised her for years.
Now it's time to shine!
And all I need to do is type
in the stream's web address.
Be free! Go get'em, girl!
[TROJAN neighs]
[gasps] Hm! There you are.
You can't hide from me.
[TROJAN neighs]
[FIREWALL A laughs]
[ALL gasp]
Trojan, no!
[FAIRY FOX giggles]
Whoops, just had a little
technical issue pop up,
but I hope you're still with me.
Are you ready for
our voice chat?
[CHEN CHAO]
Oh, you know I'm ready!
[SUN RONG]
Look at him.
He's drained so much,
he looks like a corpse.
If his father sees this,
he's gonna be in big trouble.
[WANG LING]
Hm. Thank you.
What about Little Wise Guy?
Right! We could use
a mind trick on him!
What's that?
[SUN RONG] It's an art of
seduction we learned last year.
I've used it on
Chen Chao before,
and it worked a little too well.
Oh, yeah! Out seduce her.
Fighting fire with fire!
Exactly!
[FAIRY FOX gasps] Oh my gosh,
you sound so young!
Did you graduate yet?
Not yet. I'm 18.
[FAIRY FOX gasps]
Hey, Chen Chao.
You want something to drink?
Yeah, thanks.
[FAIRY FOX gasps] Wow, you
didn't say you had a girlfriend!
Oh no, she's just
another classmate.
Wouldn't want ya to
get the wrong idea.
Oh, just another
classmate, huh?
That's it! He took the offering!
It's time! Not giving a part
of me to benefit the world.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Warning. Warning.
You have lost your connection
with Target Two-fifty.
Popularity falling.
I'm right here.
Please come back to us.
We're really worried about you.
You're right, guys. I'm sorry.
[FAIRY FOX gasps]
Fairy Fox, I'm going offline.
[gasps]
Aw, Chaochao.
Do you really have
to leave me so soon?
]This is the first time
I've chatted with a fan,
and it feels great.
I can't thank you enough
for helping with my master.
Because of your kindness, I just
had the best day of my life.
[SUN RONG]
What is she trying to do?
My only wish is that this moment
could have lasted forever,
but I understand you've
gotta get out there
and go live your life.
[whimpers]
I know what's happening.
You're leaving 'cause I'm
not popular enough for you.
I can return your gifts,
but it breaks my heart.
My biggest regret is not
meeting you sooner.
[CHEN CHAO]
Hm!
[SUN RONG]
Oh no, he's gonna break!
Listen to me! Don't give in!
You gotta snap out of it!
Please don't leave me!
--[SUN RONG gasps]
--[CHEN CHAO grunts]
[SUN RONG shouts]
We're done. Behave yourself.
[MALE ANNOUNCER A]
You lose!
[FAIRY FOX]
Hm! The plan's working.
Just a bit more,
and we're good to go!
Master, we'll have you up
and moving in no time.
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
[FAIRY FOX]
Four spirit-powered mini-TVs?
Aw, you shouldn't have!
[XIAOYU LIN] Not Sun Rong, too!
What are we gonna do!
[FATHER CHEN] Son, whatever
you've done, it's a sin.
[XIAOYU LIN yells]
[FATHER CHEN] When I was
his age, my hormones took me
on wild adventures as well and
I was just as stubborn, too.
The ancient Tongue of
the Heavenly Hound.
My wife gave it to me
as a token of affection.
That was long ago,
when we were dating.
It all makes sense now.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree!
Karma is inevitable.
Good or bad, it all comes back.
What grievous sins have
my family committed
to be trapped in this
endless cycle of depravity?
[SUN RONG gasps]
It's okay.
Wow, that was special.
A father connecting
with his son.
Aw! We got a family
heirloom from Chaochao!
[ALL yell]
Foul karma, be gone!
I've seen enough.
This ends today.
[CHEN CHAO]
Fairy Fox.
Chaochao.
[GUO HAO, XIAOYU LIN gasp]
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
No, no, please!
What have you done?
My son, we're going home!
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
What's this? You defy me?
[CHEN CHAO whimpers]
[SUN RONG gasps]
I do. You can't make me leave!
[ALL gasping]
What did he just do?
Meta spirit.
He can't! He'd have to
be a golden pill phase!
[FATHER CHEN]
Stupid boy, what have you done?
[CHEN CHAO groans]
[FATHER CHEN]
Huh? He's unresponsive!
[SUN RONG] Yeah, because his
meta spirit's on the internet,
his body's offline.
What's left is an empty shell.
Fairy Fox, I'm coming!
[FAIRY FOX laughs]
[FAIRY FOX] Now that we've
collected enough energy--
[DEMON A] I can get rid
of this awful disguise,
and finally breathe!
[DEMON A laughs]
[CHEN CHAO]
Where are you?
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
[CHEN CHAO]
I'm here!
[CHEN CHAO] Am I actually
in her room right now?
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
[CHEN CHAO]
Hang on.
This doesn't look like
her room at all.
Where am I?
[DEMON A] Oh, this is
Fairy Fox's stream-room,
I assure you. Can't you see it?
[CHEN CHAO]
Who the heck are you?
[FAIRY FOX]
I turned off my beauty filter,
and now you don't
even recognize me!
[CHEN CHAO]
No... No!
[FATHER CHEN]
Come on, son! Wake up!
It's no use. He's offline.
It doesn't work that way.
Well, how 'bout now?
No! You'll make it worse!
Hey, you've got the
web address, don't you?
[GUO HAO gasps]
Why do you need it?
Now's not the best time
to watch a stream.
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
[DEMON A] You may wanna
save your energy.
A meta spirit can't
attack a physical body.
Now, be a good boy and
climb into this cannister
so we can use you.
[CHEN CHAO] Ha! You said
I was a meta-spirit.
Which means you can't attack me!
[DEMON A laughing]
You sure?
[shouting] Stay back,
don't come any closer!
[DEMON A laughing] I thought
you wanted to help my master!
[SUN RONG]
You there, Chen Chao?
Chen Chao, can you hear me?
Are you there?
[DEMON A] Why didn't you
tell me your friend
was a descendent of Sun?
She can join us too!
Please don't give up!
We're here. We wanna help.
Please, are you there?
Chen Chao!
[gasps]
[CHEN CHAO gasps, yells]
[FATHER CHEN]
My boy!
[WANG LING pants]
Master Zhuo Yi of the
Cultivation Cruise Department
has cracked down on a massive
internet fraud scheme.
Armored Cruisers raided
the suspects' residence
and discovered a trove of energy
stockpiled in these containers.
We managed to recover
the stolen energy.
But, beware,
the perp's at large.
Hopefully, what we did today
will help prevent others
from falling for the same scam.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
And now, breaking news.
According to the Huaxiu Agency,
the long-standing Flower Fruit
Water Curtain Group has gotten
into some financial trouble.
The report states that
the conglomerate
was unable to pay its lenders,
and that its remaining assets
won't cover their debts.
According to legal statute,
the group is now bankrupt.
♪