Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[TANG] As the GM of Bp
Animation, I'd like to welcome
my fellow cultivators from
Faction Sixty's Class Elite!
With over 80 employees,
we are one of the largest
animation studios
in all of Huaxiu!
We do key animation,
backgrounds, 3D, action scenes,
photography, you name it,
we do it all in-house!
"Magical trinkets."
Oh, "High Above"!
"Mister Surprise."
Were those yours?
That was some of our early work.
Speaking of, we just
started production on
"Time Cuts Like A Knife,"
and "Impractical Magic!"
[CHEN CHAO gasps] Excuse me.
Can we try what you do?
[TANG]
Of course you can!
We have many institutes
across Huaxiu.
Visit a local branch
and try your hand
at the Art of Liver Bursting!
If you've got a real
passion for animation,
you can visit us any time!
All right, here we are.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Welcome, students,
to Bp Animation.
These are scribbles,
not a storyboard! Director!
[MALE EMPLOYEE B shouts]
Where's your project?
You've had 49 days!
[MALE EMPLOYEE E
chuckles nervously]
[GUO HAO]
We're finally here.
[CHEN CHAO] I guess this is
where the magic happens.
♪
[WONG grunts]
[FEMALE PHONE RECORDING A]
We're sorry.
The number you've dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
Damn it.
[TANG] Ah, there she is.
This is our best producer.
Every project is a
collaborative effort
between multiple teams, and it's
her job to coordinate them.
[WONG]
Geez, am I happy to see you.
As our company's producer,
she's capable of anything.
I'm not sure what
we'd do without her.
Hey, she's trying to
tell you something.
What's up?
[WONG] Uh... Our director.
Well, he just disappeared.
[TANG]
He did what?!
This project is slated to
go live in a few days and
you're telling me the director
suddenly up and vanished?
He was storyboarding offline.
I dunno, he was in some
sort of trance, and then...
...he just got up and darted
out of the room really fast!
Well, don't just stand there!
Go out and find him!
But, sir, somebody has
to keep the ball rolling.
[WONG gasps]
[TANG]
Well, Class Elite!
You said you wanted to
try what we do, right?
Well, who here's ready to
experience what it's like
to be a director?
[WONG gasps]
Ah! This is the best day ever!
Please! You can't do this to me!
[TANG sighs]
Relax.
Most of the work's been
knocked out already, anyway.
The only thing left for you is
the final content review.
[WONG] But, sir, you haven't
thought this through!
[TANG grunts]
Everyone, listen up.
As they say, the fans know our
material better than anyone.
Now, the director
may be absent,
but we have fellow cultivators
visiting from Faction Sixty!
As such, they'll be taking
over the director's duties
for the remainder of the day!
I hope you'll take their
suggestions seriously.
I know it's probably too late,
but can I quit?
[TANG] First up, let's check out
the key animation department.
With 12 episodes a season,
it's hard for the director
to check every detail.
So we have what
we call "conductors"
oversee individual episodes.
You can think of them as the
sub-directors for each one.
After meeting with the director,
they'll divvy up the work for
these amazing key animators!
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
This is so cool! It looks great!
Did you draw each frame?
Ha! That is what a key
animator does, right?
Are you satisfied, directors?
Not bad, I suppose. There is
one small problem, though.
Should I say it?
Fire away!
[CHEN CHAO]
There's some frame loss here
and these are just scribbles.
This doesn't look like the
animation I'm used to.
[MALE EMPLOYEE A sighs]
This is the first step.
Then, after I'm done,
the conductor and second
animator refine it.
A supervisor gets it next.
Then the assistants
fill out the frames.
If everyone's busy already,
who fixes the mess-ups?
We have limited manpower.
[SUN RONG] Huh? Some films have
a hundred and twenty frames
per second. Why does animation
keep getting lower?
[CHEN CHAO]
I'm pretty sure Disney cartoons
are all 24 frames per second.
Some others are only eight.
Cameras do the work in films,
but animations are hand-drawn.
You can't hold animators
to that standard!
[MALE EMPLOYEE A]
Shut up!
I'll show you 24
frames per second!
BiliBiliBoom!
Of all the martial arts,
speed is what I need!
[ALL gasp]
No way!
[WANG LING]
Liver bursting.
[TANG] That's right!
You sure know your magic, kid.
The animator enlightened his pen
and now it can draw by itself.
Only a golden pill
phase can do that.
Why don't they just draw
like this all the time?
[TANG] The art of liver
bursting is so intense that,
if they did it too often,
they'd end up in the ICU.
[SUN RONG gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[MALE EMPLOYEE A] Look.
Now it's 24 frames per second.
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
[XIAOYU LIN]
My goodness.
Is this what full-frame
animation looks like?
It's so smooth!
Director, are you
finally satisfied?
I do play a lot of
triple-A games,
so it still looks too low.
How 'bout 60?
[ALL gasp]
[MALE EMPLOYEE A groans, yells]
[crashing]
What are we gonna do now?
We just lost another
key animator!
[CHEN CHAO sighs]
I guess we won't be getting
60 frames per second.
[MALE EMPLOYEE E] You wanna
see 60 frames per second?
[TANG]
This is the print department.
After receiving the backgrounds
and key animations
you just observed,
the team uses a
post-composite software,
and they bring
all of it to life!
They're also responsible for
special effects, like blur,
reflections, you name it.
Composite and print
can't be completed until
materials are received from
the other departments.
These guys are basically on-call
and, when the time comes to do
their job, the producer
goes and wakes them up.
And done. You're about
to witness a miracle.
[ALL gasp]
[GUO HAO]
Is that magic, or what?
[MALE EMPLOYEE E] Nah. It's just
an interpolation plug-in.
This is nothin'.
I could do one-twenty,
even up to twelve hundred,
if you really wanted.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Huh? If that's true,
why would you ever
draw them by hand?
[MALE EMPLOYEE E] The AI in the
plug-in isn't perfect. See this?
But the frame-rate is so high,
it's hard to notice.
So, what do you think?
Satisfied now, Mister Frames?
[CHEN CHAO]
Hm.
I think these new animations
are kinda soulless.
Well then, you can
do it yourself!
Coming into my studio and
shaming the hard work we do.
Why don't you step over here,
and I'll show you
how much soul I have!
[JINGKE SWORD]
Master, do you feel it?
[TANG] Next, we're going to
swing by the art department.
[GUO HAO, CHEN CHAO gasp]
You think it's the main
character's homeland?
[TANG] They aren't
just drawing scenery,
they're influencing the
tone of the entire project!
Think about it.
When you have a hopeful scene,
you'll see a golden dusk.
But, if the project is sad,
you'll need a gloomy backdrop.
To develop a convincing setting,
it takes a lot of time
and effort, and years of
experience can help, too.
So if you have any other
suggestions, please--
[WONG]
I'm begging you. Please, sir!
We can't handle more feedback!
Mister Zhu's been working
for over half a year,
his liver won't
last much longer!
[TANG sighs]
All right. Thank you.
When you're done,
you can go back to your
hometown and get married.
[ZHU gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[WONG screams]
[WONG]
Mister Zhu, no!
[GUO HAO]
I didn't mean to, I swear!
[SUN RONG gasps]
Something wrong? What's up?
[WANG LING]
Uh...
Master, the world's spiritual
value is dropping.
[WANG LING grunts]
[WONG sighs]
There's nothing I can do now.
We've lost too many good people.
I don't think we'll ever
finish this episode.
[CHEN CHAO]
Don't give up just yet!
We're here to help you!
You're fine!
[WONG]
Uh? You?
Yes, ma'am! Not to brag,
but we're quick learners.
Which means we're basically
experts after that tour!
Yeah, but to be a key animator,
it takes years of training.
[TANG]
Miss Wong. Don't forget.
When we first started,
we were just like them.
So blissfully inexperienced.
But look at us now!
--[FEMALE STUDENT U] Right!
--[MALE STUDENT G] Good job!
Look at their sincerity
and enthusiasm.
That's real love of animation.
We must believe in them.
Because these kids...
They're the future of Huaxiu!
You should each have part of
a storyboard on your desk.
Draw your pictures as described.
[CHEN CHAO]
Hmph!
What is this?
[WONG]
The directors are pretty busy,
so the storyboard
might be kinda rushed.
[GUO HAO gasps] "Key animator is
requested to improvise here?"
What the hell?
[WONG] Some directors
don't draw action well,
so they may ask the best key
animators to make that up.
[GUO HAO gasps]
Oh God. Why is this so hard?
All I need to do is trace
the original picture.
It shouldn't be this difficult!
[WONG]
Of course it's difficult.
Beginners are required to
practice drawing solid lines
for their first three months,
then countless circles
and straight lines until they
can draw without squiggling.
[SUN RONG gasps] I'm afraid
I just don't have a knack
for drawing.
[ALL gasp]
It's moving... all by itself!
No way! If I can think it,
my pen can draw it!
Are they... liver bursting?
No. I learned the art
of enlightenment.
All right! No more shaky hands!
Man! Wang Ling, you're a genius!
[FEMALE SUPERVISOR A hums]
[WONG sighs]
[FEMALE SUPERVISOR A]
Hm?
Hey boss. They're ready!
Please take a look!
[CHEN CHAO] Uh, Miss Wong,
what does the supervisor do?
[WONG] Sometimes, animators
can draw the same characters
but with subtle differences so,
in a perfect world,
she just unifies the drawings.
But some animators
just aren't very good,
so she might have to spend
extra time on the details
and may even have to
edit the whole thing.
[GUO HAO] What happens if the
animation is too bad to correct?
[WONG] Then, she usually
gives them some feedback
and asks them to start over.
[CHEN CHAO] Geez. It takes
so long to pump these out,
I can't imagine having
to start over!
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
Did you just...?
There's no way I'm leaving these
twisted things on my computer.
[ALL gasp]
[XIAOYU LIN sighs] Making
cartoons is so much harder
than I thought. I guess there's
really nothing we can do, now.
Master, the world's force
value is almost gone.
The dimensions are
about to collapse.
What should we do?
[WANG LING sighs]
Not this again.
[gasps]
[grunts]
The Director. Where is he?
[WANG LING]
Hm. They're working hard.
Master, you ready?
The battle starts soon!
[giggling]
[WONG] You ever gonna
finish that storyboard?
[MALE DIRECTOR A]
Gimme a sec!
[hitting]
[WONG]
Hm?
The director's back!
[MALE DIRECTOR A] Conductor, how
are the key animations going?
Any unfinished scenes?
Try moving that back two frames.
[ALL gasp]
[CHEN CHAO]
So professional.
[GUO HAO]
This director's the real deal!
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO gasp]
[GUO HAO laughs]
[WANG LING gasps]
Thank you for creating
this beautiful world.
♪