Hey, guys. Do you feel like
we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[MALE REPORTER A chuckles]
Welcome to Songhai's
Spiritual Sword
Arts Competition!
[CROWD cheers]
[MALE REPORTER A] Students from
Songhai's top factions
are invited to showcase their
unique sword skills, live!
If you leave a comment
on the Bilibili webcast,
you just might win a prize!
Now, let's welcome
tonight's four judges!
Our first swordmaster is the
hero of Songhai himself,
captain of the Seven-Star Squad,
Master Zhuo Yi!
Next up, from Faction
Fifty Nine to our stage,
Professor Xie!
[MALE REPORTER A] Our last
two judges are from Bilibili's
most popular sword dance team.
Ling Yuan and Hanser!
[CROWD cheers]
[laughs]
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Hmph!
In ancient times,
spiritual sword cultivation
was judged on power alone.
But now, in these
times of world peace,
we can judge the style!
So remember, this is
not a contest of power.
Instead, we're judging
art and beauty!
[MALE REPORTER A] While the
performers work their magic,
we have some awesome
giveaways for our viewers!
The first prize is two
tickets to Fort Skyloop,
so don't forget to
leave a few comments!
So much for that
commercial break.
Let's introduce our
first performer!
You've seen her in
the headlines lately,
The Flower Fruit Water Curtain
Group's darling, Miss Sun Rong!
[CROWD cheers]
[chuckles]
♪
[CROWD chattering]
Hello, Professors, thank you.
I'm Sun Rong,
from Faction Sixty.
Hello, darling.
I thought you damaged all
your swords last year,
Little Miss Bankruptcy.
You even sacrificed
your sword spirit.
Yeah. It was difficult,
but I've been practicing.
That's why I'm here;
to challenge myself and learn
from the best. Thank you.
Wow! Very good!
What have you got for us?
My ancestral skill,
the Ocean Dance.
[CROWD cheers]
Now, that's a
multi-sword dance!
Yeah! Look at her control.
She's juggling well over
a dozen spiritual swords!
[XIE gasps] This dance has
earned its reputation.
It's special.
[chuckles]
[WANG LING]
Huh?
[CROWD murmurs]
[WANG ZUKANG]
Huh? Look out!
[XIE gasps]
[gasps]
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Kang Kang, my sweet!
I was worried about you!
[LIUYUE JIANG, XIE growl]
That's enough. Your maneuver
was quite dangerous.
Please, don't overdo it.
[MALE STUDENT A]
Really? Was that all she's got?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
That was so embarrassing!
[FEMALE STUDENT B laughs]
Typical Sun family.
[MALE STUDENT B]
Is she done?
[MALE REPORTER A] Thank you,
Miss Sun, for that performance.
Accidents can happen
to the best of us.
Now, let's move on to
our next performers!
[MALE STUDENT C] My five-year-
old niece could do better!
Hey, uh, are you okay?
Sorry, that was embarrassing.
Without my spirit,
I can't do it.
[XIAOYU LIN]
I have an idea.
Bring your sword to my shop.
I can calibrate it.
[SUN RONG]
Mm. Thank you... Huh?
You good?
[SUN RONG]
Mm.
[FEMALE ANALYST B]
Post an apology online.
It happened too
fast to cut away!
Hang on, after her accident,
the ratings skyrocketed!
[MALE REPORTER A]
They what?
The Spiritual Energy
Index is soaring!
I didn't think
anybody would watch!
[MALE REPORTER A] Ha! What a
blessing in disguise.
Keep rolling! Let's go!
[RICHMAN chuckles]
They don't even know.
[CROWD chattering]
[MALE STUDENT D] I dunno.
I think it's rigged.
[MALE STUDENT F] Attempted
murder is illegal, ya know.
[FEMALE STUDENT C] You guys
might wanna watch your heads.
[MALE REPORTER A]
She may have made a mistake,
but we appreciate
her all the same!
Let's move on!
Our next performers from Faction
Sixty are, "The Elite Duo"?
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL gasp]
[HANSER] I've gotta ask, what
brought you on stage tonight?
Were you boys looking
for a challenge?
Nah, we just wanted to
put on a little show.
[HANSER]
Huh?
Uh, this one goes out
to a good friend of ours,
'cause her life's been
pretty difficult lately.
And while she always
puts on a brave face,
we wanted to acknowledge
that we see the pressure
she's always under.
Sorry. While we can't
take that away,
we can take your mind off it.
And at least make you smile.
They're lucky to have
you as a friend.
Now, what are we about to see?
You've heard of
knife catching, right?
Well that's an easy
skill to master.
So instead of boring you
to death with that stuff,
I'll catch this sword
with my bare hands!
[laughs] Do you boys
know what year it is?
Even my grandfather
knew that trick.
Just wait.
Barehanded's one thing but,
I'll be blindfolded, too!
--[grunts]
--[CROWD cheers]
[grunts]
Wow, golden Buddha-arms,
that's pretty cool!
He summoned half a sword spirit.
Heh. Guess I failed to see
what's "cool" about that.
Chao! You ready for me?
[CHEN CHAO]
Hm!
[chuckles]
[shouts]
--[GUO HAO shouts]
--[CHEN CHAO grunts]
[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
And that was our demonstration
of The Great Chen Chao's
Iron Head!
[CROWD chatters]
[XIAOYU LIN laughs]
I knew he was hard-headed,
but not like that.
You see this? We have
over a million viewers!
The Spirit Index
set a new record.
[RICHMAN sighs]
Just a little more,
and I'll have all the
energy I'll need.
[MALE REPORTER A]
Uh, thanks to the Elite Duo
for their well-rehearsed
performance.
Now, let's welcome
our next performer,
hailing from faction
fifty-nine, Miss Yisha Bei!
[CROWD cheers]
You got this, Yisha!
What a formation!
It looks like hundreds,
no, thousands of swords!
Incredible!
Well, it is the age
of techno-cultivation.
Her advanced interface allows
her to control thousands
of spiritual swords with ease.
The times are changing.
Hang on to the the old way,
and you'll be juggling the
same ten swords forever.
[GUO HAO grunts]
Hey guys, you miss us?
Uh, Guo, is he gonna make it?
Oh yeah, the doc
checked him out, he's fine.
That's good, I was--
Whoa, hold on! Don't worry.
Did we cheer you up at all?
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
Where is everyone?
[MALE REPORTER A]
All right.
Thanks to Yisha Bei for
that spectacular show!
Now, let's keep the party
going for our last performer
from Faction Sixty, Lin Xiao Yu!
No way! Is that her?
[giggles]
Look at her without her glasses!
She's stunning!
[MALE AUDIENCE A]
She's a hottie!
[MALE AUDIENCE A] She's so cool,
it's killing me!
[MALE STUDENT G]
Just beautiful!
[MALE STUDENT H]
I like her!
[MALE STUDENT I]
I'm in love with this goddess!
[ALL gasp]
You're my favorite, now!
[MALE STUDENT J] Who is she?
She's so lovely!
[FEMALE STUDENT D]
How have I never heard of her?
[CROWD]
Huh?
[FEMALE ANALYST B] We're up to
five-hundred million viewers,
the most in human history!
[RICHMAN chuckles] Yes, my plan
is beginning to take shape.
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Is it supposed to be
burning like that?
Nah, man. Look at the
way she's circling it.
[gasps]
Oh no!
[shouts]
[gasps, grunts]
[SUN RONG shouts]
[CROWD gasps]
That was super cool!
Using nature, she made
the stage dreamy,
then burned it
all to the ground!
And they revitalized
it after the fire!
A dance with all five elements!
That was Rebirth from the Ashes.
Ha! I never doubted her.
That girl is one in
a million, just brilliant!
[MALE STUDENT L]
Their staging was fabulous!
[MALE STUDENT M]
What just happened?
[FEMALE STUDENT E]
I call it "Winning".
[FEMALE ANALYST A]
One billion? One billion!
You've gotta be kidding me!
[MALE REPORTER A gasping]
[RICHMAN] Outstanding
performances tonight.
Thanks to your viewers, I've
gathered the energy necessary
to unleash my magic.
Ultimate... Control!
[MALE REPORTER A gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[laughs] Your minds can't
fathom the effort it took
to harvest one billion spiritual
energies for this endeavor!
All humans are now
under my control,
for I am the puppet master!
Poor mindless saps. It's such
a shame you can't hear me.
My plan is genius, after all.
Sir. Do I know you?
Uh, hang on.
You can hear me?
[WANG LING]
They're not under your control.
How's that?
You're lying! My trick's huge!
How could you escape it?
[WANG LING]
I just moved your control key
about two meters forward.
[RICHMAN]
Huh?
[MAN A groans]
[CROWD grunting]
[gasps]
Who the hell are you, anyway?
How did you know my plan?
[sighs]
Damn you. Now I must
resort to violence!
[MALE REPORTER A grunting]
[RICHMAN yells]
Thanks for saving me!
Wait, something's
wrong with him.
[MALE REPORTER A laughs]
[XIAOYU LIN, SUN RONG gasp]
[CROWD grunting]
[SUN RONG]
Hm?
No! I can't release
them from my control!
This isn't your control.
They're infected
by a demon soul.
So these aren't normal minions.
No. They're zombies!
♪