Hey, guys. Do you feel like
we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[gasps]
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Hey, Idler, how do I look?
We're on a mission.
You shouldn't use
that trick in public.
[LIUYUE JIANG sighs] I wore this
itchy cheongsam just for you.
Try not thinking about
work for a minute.
[IDLER] Yue, do you feel like
maybe something's off, here?
[LIUYUE JIANG] The Seven-Star
Squad's been following us,
so maybe it's them.
[MALE PASSENGER B]
What was that?
[MALE PASSENGER C]
It's turbulence, calm down.
[MALE PASSENGER D]
I got coffee all over my pants!
[FEMALE ATTENDANT A] Good
evening, please return to your
seats and fasten your seatbelts
until we're clear of all
spiritual turbulence.
[gasps]
[FEMALE ATTENDANT A]
Excuse me, ma'am,
can you please
return to your seat?
[gasps] Ma'am, are you
listening to me?
I need you to return to your
seat and fasten your seatbelt.
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Shut it!
Ha! When you're this powerful,
you don't need seatbelts.
[PASSENGERS yelling]
[grunting]
[IDLER]
Yue!
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Idler!
[LIUYUE JIANG
grunting, shouting]
Yue!
♪
[GUO HAO] May I present the
world's number one assassin,
the Idle Beauty!
Ten years ago, he was on
a swordliner when it
mysteriously crashed, and he
hasn't been seen since.
This is the last
known picture of him.
Weird. Do you think
he died in the crash?
No. What I've heard is that
he was severely injured,
and he's been secretly living
in Songhai this whole time.
Get this, rumor is that
someone spotted him.
Said it was near here.
[gasps] Maybe he has a
hideout close by? No way.
[PAN SHENGCONG]
In case you weren't aware,
that sound was the bell.
[PAN SHENGCONG] Ahem. Minor
accidents aside, every student
was able to complete their
doom-breaking test.
A Class Ordinary
student performed well
and earned a spot
in our class.
Let's give her a warm welcome!
[MALE STUDENT A]
It's a girl!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
She's so cute!
[WANG LING gasps]
[gasps]
[SUN RONG]
Gosh, he's looking at me again.
That boy can't keep
his eyes off me!
Hi everyone!
My name is Lin Xiaoyu!
Her test scores are rather
extraordinary, but do be kind.
Her family is going
through a rough patch.
[JINGKE SWORD gasps]
Is it just me, or does the
new girl look familiar?
[PAN SHENGCONG] Professor Zukang
is currently busy,
so I'll be your
substitute for the day.
Please turn to page 58.
[ZHUO YI]
Zukang any updates?
[WANG ZUKANG] Hundred and
twenty meters to target.
Her spiritual energy
signature is just ahead.
Approach with caution.
She's dangerous.
I'm no slouch myself.
What? You think I can't
handle an assassin?
[ZHUO YI]
Point taken, carry on.
I found her. Cutting the comms.
[WANG ZUKANG] Jiang Liuyue,
we have you surrounded.
Trying to resist
would be pointless.
Time to give it up.
[sighs]
All those years,
where were you hiding?
[WANG ZUKANG, ZHUO YI gasp]
[LIUYUE JIANG laughs]
Does it really matter?
These cultivation quacks
couldn't find me
if they were using GPS.
I thought he was smarter.
I can't believe he fell
for such an obvious trap.
Hang tight, little sister.
Here I come.
[GUO HAO sighs]
[GUO HAO] I've also heard that
Jiang Liuying was captured
by the Seven-Star Squad...
and locked up on campus.
You're joking, right?
Our security is terrible,
I don't buy it.
[GUO HAO] We're talking about
the same school that had a
Giant Frog sealed
underground, remember?
Listen, the word on the street
is there's a massive prison
hidden under faction sixty.
Strong enough to
contain a demon king.
That was the lady
from the picture--
Don't just stand there!
[GUO HAO]
Hold up!
[CHEN CHAO]
Huh? Where'd she go?
[GUO HAO] Huh? This has gotta
be a storage room, right?
We just saw her.
She couldn't have gone far.
[WANG LING]
Someone lives in here.
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO gasp]
[CHEN CHAO] Is this Idle
Beauty's secret hideout?
I see.
Whoever's hiding here has made
themselves pretty comfortable.
Trash is full,
bed is a total mess.
Pretty lazy for the
world's best assassin.
[WANG LING]
Hm...? Somebody's coming.
[CHEN CHAO gasps]
The Idle Beauty's back!
Shut up and hide!
[XIAOYU LIN hums]
[XIAOYU LIN sighs]
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO gasp]
Who's there?!
Sorry, I know this
looks a little weird,
but we weren't trying
to spy on you.
[CHEN CHAO grunts]
Yeah!
[gasps]
You freakin' creeps!
No, no. It's not
what it looks like.
Whatever your name is,
I can explain.
Lin Xiaoyu, bro!
What are you doing
in my room?!
[CHEN CHAO gasps] This isn't
Idle Beauty's secret hideout?
[GUO HAO]
Guess not.
We didn't think your
room would be so messy.
[gasps]
Who are you to judge?
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO gasp]
[ALL]
Hm?
[ALL yell]
[WANG LING sighs]
[gasps] Wait, what are
you doing down here?
[LIUYUE JIANG] Is it a crime
to miss my baby sister?
I wanted to see how
you were doing.
[LIUYUE JIANG chuckling]
Where are the guards?
Doesn't matter,
they couldn't stop me.
Yeah, you're right. Now free me!
We can team up and revive
the Shadow Faction.
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Oh, sweetheart.
Do you honestly think I broke
into prison to rescue you?
[gasps]
In forty-three ninety-six,
you had a contract to
assassinate Sun Rong.
Did you fulfill it?
[LIUYING JIANG] Did they send
you here to take me out?
How did you get
involved with them?
You failed to complete
your mission, sis.
You knew there'd
be consequences.
[chuckles]
All for some demons?
I dare you to kill me!
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Ha!
Before I do that, you and I,
we need to have a little chat.
[GUO HAO, XIAOYU LIN,
CHEN CHAO yelling]
Sorry, carry on.
[GUO HAO, XIAOYU LIN,
CHEN CHAO yelling]
Master, I think I
found a safe place.
Good.
[GUO HAO, XIAOYU LIN,
CHEN CHAO grunt]
[GUO HAO grunts]
I thought we'd never land.
Where the heck are we anyway?
I can't see anything.
It's pitch black.
[XIAOYU LIN] You sicko,
get your hands off me!
[GUO HAO grunts]
You've got to be kidding me.
Guys, I think we found it.
[CHEN CHAO] Wait, is this
Idle Beauty's secret hideout?
Why this room?
The other rooms were filled
with creatures or full of traps.
This was the safest option.
[CHEN CHAO] This is the Li's
brand knife he uses to kill.
Crazy. Those rumors
weren't rumors after all.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Guys, check this out!
[CHEN CHAO, GUO HAO]
Hm?
[GUO HAO] Isn't this the
infamous "wall of clues"?
You think Idle Beauty's
investigating something special?
[GUO HAO grunts]
"Swordliner Crash Mystery,"
published ten years ago.
[CHEN CHAO]
"Leadership Change after
Shadow Faction In-fighting".
[GUO HAO] Hold on.
We definitely saw her earlier!
[LIUYUE JIANG]
When we first crossed paths,
I was on a mission.
How could I not fall
for that face?
[LIUYUE JIANG] We were an
inseparable force working
together near, far, wherever
business and life took us.
And eventually I became
Shadow Faction's boss.
I was on top of the world.
Of my hundred years
on this earth,
those were the best times of
my life, but they didn't last.
[LIUYUE JIANG shouts]
[LIUYUE JIANG] That day,
everything was taken from me.
For ten years, I endured my
imprisonment in the demon world.
I was ripped from
the one I love
and forced to live every
moment in unspeakable agony!
Confined in that
dreadful palace,
I translated documents from
the human to the demon tongue.
Which is how I stumbled
onto a contract
assigned to the Shadow Faction.
And I knew... it was you!
You destroyed the swordliner,
just to try and steal my
seat on the throne!
Yeah. Of course I wanted
your job, but that wasn't me.
Lies! The demon world sent me
to eliminate you, traitor.
Goodbye, sis. Failed leader
of the Shadow Faction.
[gasps]
No!
[WANG ZUKANG]
What you think you know about
the past is wrong, Yue.
[GUO HAO] Alright, let's see if
we can put the pieces together.
The timeline starts
ten years ago.
And we're right
where it all began,
here in Songhai's Faction Sixty.
Weird things happened that day.
Three, to be exact.
First, we have the
swordliner crash.
The Idle Beauty and the
leader of the Shadow Faction
were on board.
The Shadow Faction
boss was missing.
Allegedly, she was
thrown out of the liner.
[GUO HAO]
Mm-hm! Yeah, that sounds right.
Anyone remember the second
incident that happened that day?
There was an invasion!
The Giant Frog!
[GUO HAO]
You got it!
Which is also when the massive
portal opened above the city.
What's the third thing, then?
Master Zhuo beat the Giant Frog.
[GUO HAO, CHEN CHAO gasp]
I think I'm finally
starting to get it.
[MALE CIVILIAN A]
Look, what's that?
[MALE CIVILIAN B]
Oh no!
[MALE CIVILIAN C]
Run! Come on, run!
[FROGGY 2] Give all your
spiritual force to me!
[FROGGY 2 laughs]
Yes!
A side dish has unwittingly
delivered itself.
[FROGGY 2 groans]
[PASSENGERS shouting]
[grunts]
[IDLER]
Yue!
[LIUYUE JIANG]
Idler!
[LIUYUE JIANG gasps]
I hate being bothered
while eating crispy noodles.
[FROGGY 2 grunts]
[LIUYUE JIANG shouts]
[IDLER]
Yue!
[IDLER grunts]
[GUO HAO] After the crash,
the Idle Beauty went into hiding
in a secret base
below faction sixty,
waiting for his
beloved to return.
Guys, I think we've just
uncovered the truth.
[CHEN CHAO]
I can't believe it!
The world's top assassin was
a sweet, brokenhearted soul!
He really loved her!
He waited for ten years!
[WANG ZUKANG] My love,
I concealed my identity
and waited for you in
the last place I saw you.
Ten years... and I
finally see your face.
My sweet Kangy, y-you...
you put on a few pounds.
Losing you was difficult,
you know?
When the sadness consumed me,
I would devour my feelings.
This thick body reflects
the weight of the sorrow
that dragged me down.
Kangy.
[LIUYING JIANG] First, you try
to kill me on false pretenses,
and now you're torturing me
with sickening affection.
I'd rather be dead
than have to see this!
Sweetheart, you remember?
You said you were gonna take me
to see the moonlit stars
and fly around the world.
I didn't forget!
I'm taking you to see those
moonlit stars right now.
Let's fly away!
[LIUYING JIANG groans]
I think I'm gonna be sick!
Somebody, please, have the
decency to kill me!
♪
[GUO HAO sighs] I thought we'd
be trapped down there forever.
Thank God Wang Ling found
this top secret elevator.
[XIAOYU LIN sighs] At least you
didn't skip on your first day
in Class Elite.
[WANG ZUKANG,
LIUYUE JIANG giggle]
[ALL]
Huh?
Huh...