Hey, guys. Do you feel
like we're being watched?
[ALL]
Huh?
[FATHER LIN]
Relax. Take a deep breath.
Feel the spiritual force within.
Imagine it moving from your
extremities to your core.
Through your limbs,
into your back,
until it converges on
your shoulder blades.
That's it, you're doing great!
[grunts]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[sighs] It's okay.
You've almost got it.
[XIAOYU LIN] Daddy, am I
really one of the butterflies?
[FATHER LIN]
Why do you ask?
[XIAOYU LIN grunts]
All my friends could fly
when they were little, but I
don't even have my wings yet.
[chuckles]
When I was a child, like you,
it took until I was ten.
Then, one day, your
grandfather threw me
into the butterfly valley,
where I learned how to fly.
Huh? Why would he
do something so cruel?
Our wings are special.
We have the power to
travel through space-time.
This magic has always been
coveted by other demons.
So, if we weren't able to fly,
and got captured
by another race,
we would suffer a fate
worse than falling.
[XIAOYU LIN] Hm.
But, daddy, those bad demons.
Do you think they'll be
able to find us here?
Don't worry.
Daddy will save you.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Huh?
[XIAOYU LIN gasping]
I'm scared.
What are those things?
[FATHER LIN]
[XIAOYU LIN grunts]
Fly, now!
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Daddy!
[gasps]
[XIAOYU LIN] That's how I ended
up in the human world,
raised by my sword spirit.
It's also how the Demon Emperor
conquered my people.
To the butterflies,
it was the end of the world.
But to the demons, it was
just part of the routine.
They're driven by
one thing. Power.
When a dominant race
conquers a weaker foe,
they steal their spiritual
energy and amass more resources
to help them conquer
their next victims.
Did you fight back?
[XIAOYU LIN scoffs]
Are you serious? Come on.
What did you expect me to do?
The Demon Emperor has
conquered tens of thousands
of civilizations over the years.
He doesn't have
to lift a finger.
His legions will continue to
enslave anyone he conquers
and repeat the cycle forever.
The demon scourge
is unstoppable.
It's not a myth,
it's your reality.
We managed to crush
them ten years ago.
[XIAOYU LIN sighs]
Forget it.
You'll meet the emperor
soon enough, then you'll see.
See what?
[ZHUO YI gasps]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A] Warning.
Your delivery will soon be late.
[whimpering]
Master, where are you?
[phones beeping]
[DELIVERYMAN A]
Huh?
[ZHUO YI]
Fellow practitioners,
I'm a senior at Faction Sixty.
Sun Rong, and today is one of
the most consequential days
of our lives.
The demons have launched
their premeditated invasion.
They think that by beating
the Seven-Star Squad,
they'll also be
crushing our spirits.
But they're forgetting
something important.
Every one of us,
wherever we are,
whatever our social status,
whether we're a young student,
learning how life works,
or an elder who's seen it all.
We are practitioners.
Every one of us is a
scientific cultivator.
Sure, years of peace may have
diminished our combat instincts,
but we've been practicing.
We've managed to keep pushing
ourselves to higher phases
in case we needed to fight.
We grew up, practicing in
school and now,
we're all foundation
phase or higher.
As we face the enemy,
we'll prove that each of us
has the strength to
protect our homeland.
If they take our cities,
we will fight in the streets.
We will fight in the fields.
We will fight in the forests.
We will fight in the sky.
We will fight wherever
we must, at all costs!
Because we will never surrender.
Huaxiu calls on
every practitioner
to fulfil their duty, until
every invader is driven out!
We... will all fight
to the bitter end.
[ZHUO YI]
Hm.
Charge!
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs]
What a rousing speech, human.
You really are one of
Sun's descendants.
But you will fail. Your words
are the dying gasps
of an insignificant race
that's about to suffocate
on their own arrogance.
[FEMALE ANALYST B]
Oh no! What now?
They've surrounded us!
[DEMON EMPEROR] With my
infinite legion closing in,
let's see how long it
takes you to implode.
[XIAOYU LIN]
My noble Emperor of Demons,
I have delivered him
to you, as promised.
Please honor our agreement.
Free my sword spirit.
[WANG LING gasps]
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
On your knees!
[DEMON COUNSELOR laughs]
Your feeble kind hasn't earned
the right to stand before
His Majesty's throne.
[XIAOYU LIN whimpers]
[DEMON COUNSELOR]
Huh? You cheeky little brat!
You bow before the throne of
the great Demon Emperor!
[DEMON COUNSELOR gasps]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs]
[DEMON EMPEROR]
You know, I haven't risen
from this throne for
thousands of years.
Finally, someone has given
me a compelling reason
to walk yet again.
[DEMON EMPEROR] You must be the
boy Richman warned us about.
A mischievous little wolf,
masquerading in
sheep's clothing.
If I kill you,
would it end the war?
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Ha.
[DEMON EMPEROR] I don't fight
nameless practitioners, boy.
Go on. Who are you, really?
Songhai, Faction Sixty.
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs]
That all you got?
[SUN RONG grunting]
[FEMALE ANALYST B] Sun Rong,
we gotta do something, now!
If we don't take out that
carrier, they'll keep coming!
[gasps]
[gasps] Wait, aren't you
Wang Ling's sword spirit?
[JINGKE SWORD] Yeah! Thank God,
you finally remembered!
Do you know where he is?
You think he's in danger?
My master? I think whoever he's
fighting is in real danger.
♪
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
[DEMON EMPEROR] Who are you?
And why do you exist?
I don't understand where the
humans found a practitioner
like you and how have I
never heard of you before?
If I had noteworthy fights
on earth, it would be destroyed.
But we're not on earth, are we?
[DEMON EMPEROR gasps]
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
Really?
You think you're fast?
You can't compete with me, for I
am the master of the universe!
[DEMON EMPEROR shouts]
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Say goodbye while you still can!
[DEMON EMPEROR gasps]
No, that's impossible!
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
[DEMON EMPEROR shouts]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps] Come on, sis.
Let's get you home.
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
You're alive!
[DEMON EMPEROR grunts]
No, stop! Please!
I don't understand!
My demons, they've conquered
millions of worlds.
Eradicated countless
civilizations.
For eons, I've watched
as stronger races
crumbled under the weight
of my immense power.
And now, for reasons
beyond my comprehension,
a race as insignificant as
yours is doing what no other
has been able
to accomplish!
We've lived a long time.
Suffered many defeats.
Nearly collapsed
as a civilization.
But we never gave up.
Humans will never bow to
evil tyrants like you.
[DEMON EMPEROR]
Spare me your tripe!
I fell to your
unprecedented power,
not by the perseverance
of your race!
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
Wang Ling, look out!
[DEMON COUNSELOR] Finally,
a chance to end this mess!
Everything in the universe
has its vulnerabilities and,
while observing your daily life,
I discovered that you
had a spiritual figure
applied to your neck every week.
My dear boy, it's over.
You couldn't hide your
weakness forever!
[DEMON EMPEROR laughs]
Looks like the demons will have
the last laugh after all!
[WANG LING exhales]
[GUO HAO]
Huh?
They're disappearing.
[gasps] We just won.
We freakin' won!
[ALL cheer]
[GUO HAO]
Hm?
Spiritual energy in the rain!
[FEMALE ANALYST B gasps]
What's happening?
The world's spiritual
force keeps rising!
[JINGKE SWORD] There was an
explosion in the Demon World.
It's gone.
[SUN RONG gasps]
Wait. Where's Wang Ling?
[XIAOYU LIN gasps]
[XIAOYU LIN grunts]
I know I betrayed your kind
and, also, I saw your power.
So, whatever you do,
Please, let my sword go!
She's innocent!
[WANG LING] Xiaoyu, there's a
cell-phone in my right pocket.
I see. You're about to call
the police. I understand.
Call my dad now.
Tell him what's happening.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Huh?
Hurry... if you wanna
save the world.
[XIAOYU LIN]
Y-Yeah, of course!
[MALE NARRATOR A] In Huaxiu's
history books this event
would forever be known
as Demon War Two.
Humans proved that
the Demon Emperor
wasn't invincible after all and
Zhuo Yi became the hero
who saved the world again.
Under Sun Rong's
new leadership,
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain
Group regained its prosperity.
Timely and efficient
reconstruction efforts
helped repair the war-torn city.
And every-day practitioners
got back to living
their normal lives.
[GUO HAO] Don't you think
something weird was going on
with the demon invasion?
Halfway through the battle,
they just disappeared!
[CHEN CHAO] Hm! They were scared
by how brave we fought.
They just got up and left!
[GUO HAO] Who do you think
the mystery practitioner was
that sunk the carrier?
There's too much glare to
see anything in the picture.
I bet it was the world's
top practitioner.
He's legendary, bro!
Wang Ling. What actually
happened that day?
Huh?
[SUN RONG]
Wang Ling?
♪
[yawns]
Froggy Two, you're free
to go now.
Sorry for keeping you so long.
[FROGGY 2] It's all good.
I'm from the Demon World.
You'd be crazy not to
be suspicious of me.
Besides, I spent ten years
locked up under Faction Sixty.
What's a few extra days?
[FROGGY 2 inhales]
[FROGGY 2] Ah. Well, boy,
looks like you won the war.
[WANG LING]
Hm?
[FROGGY 2]
Now that's all over,
you wouldn't mind if I went
home for a bit, would you?
[WANG LING]
Sorry. Demon World's destroyed.
[FROGGY 2]
Huh?!