[OKIKU]
Through a darkened corridor,
where none were supposed
to have tread.
A child walks,
sounds of something dripping
on the floor and
dragging behind her
echo as she goes.
[OKIKU]
Her skin, as pale as alabaster.
Her cold, glass eyes stare out,
full of evil!
[CHILDREN scream]
[OKIKU]
Or so I thought.
[OKIKU] So then...
How did this happen?
[KIRI] Holy One, why do
you have a doll with you?
[PRIEST A] I was told it
was evil and asked to exorcise
the spirit possessing it.
But I wouldn't call it evil.
All it does is speak
and move on its own.
Its hair grows, too, but
that doesn't make it bad.
Hey, doll. Can you
make tables levitate
or plates fly through the air?
No doll with a shred of decency
would lower herself to
that kind of haunting!
So ya don't do ghost stuff?
Well that's no fun at all.
She's a doll, Natsume!
Don't be rude!
It's okay if you're
not a real poltergeist.
You're a great possessed
doll, just as you are.
[OKIKU]
Hang on...
Was that meant to try
and cheer me up?
Your attempts at kindness
don't always hit the mark.
Huh? What did I say?
Did I mess something up?
I'm sorry.
[NATSUME] Do you have a battle
mode where your arms and legs
come off and you morph
into a fighting doll?
[OKIKU]
Are you crazy?!
What's the matter
with these people?
Normally all I have
to do to make folks
scream and cry is walk
down a dark hallway.
This is humiliating!
Look at that hair.
It's gotten pretty
long there, Okiku.
Your name's Okiku?
That's so nice!
[OKIKU] Don't just make
up a name for me!
Sakura, you've got
scissors, don't ya?
Come here and give her a trim.
[OKIKU]
Wait a minute!
Children shouldn't play
with sharp objects!
Hold on, be gentle...
Don't worry. It's fine.
[OKIKU]
But her eyes...!
They have an evil gleam!
This may be the first
time I've ever seen
Sakura smile.
Careful not to move
or you'll get hurt.
[OKIKU whimpering]
Please, no!
Or at least, can't
someone else do it?!
[NATSUME] Didn't your little
niece do something like this
to her doll?
[SATSUKI] Uh, yeah.
It was quite imaginative.
Very avant-garde.
[NATSUME]
Well, you know what they say.
It'll grow back.
Don't say it like
I'm some dumb kid
who cut her bangs too
short before picture day!
[crying]
[REN] It's noisy in there.
What's going on?
[OKIKU]
I'm supposed to be an heirloom,
a one-of-a-kind doll
of the highest quality!
I was made by a
master craftsman!
What kind of a doll
am I if I'm hideous?
[REN growls]
[OKIKU gasps]
You are only ugly
if you think you are!
Listen to me,
if just being born a girl
automatically made you pretty,
life would be easy!
But becoming a beautiful
woman takes refinement
and hard work!
Sakura, hand over the scissors.
[SATSUKI]
She's doing her makeup, too!
[YUZU]
Wow! Such incredible skill!
[OKIKU]
Is this really me?
Hey! I'm supposed to
be a traditional doll!
Now she just needs a kimono.
What color?
Hey!
Hmm...
What she's got on is nice,
but this might look better.
[cutting noise]
You don't have
to do that for me.
[REN]
Natsume.
Could you please bring
me my sewing kit?
'Kay.
Feel free to use some
of my old clothes.
[REN]
Thanks, Kiri. I will.
You can also take scraps
from mine if you want.
Oh? Yours, too?
Hey! Don't forget about mine!
You don't even have
your own kimono.
Don't worry.
There's already enough.
[YUZU] Then can I maybe
help with the sewing?
[REN]
Do you know how to sew?
[YUZU]
Yes!
Sister Bikuni taught me
when I lived with her.
[REN]
Great.
Then here. Do these frills.
[YUZU]
Frills? Uh, okay.
[REN] Yuzu, you're
doing them all wrong.
Let me.
Sorry, Ren. I haven't
ever sewn frills before.
Well, you should have said so.
Still, your stitching
does seem to be
clean and straight.
Your eyes are so
life-like and beautiful.
The glass sparkles in the light.
And your porcelain skin
is so white and smooth.
[YUZU] Someone obviously
made you with a lot of care
for a girl who must
have been very special.
[MOM] Traditional Japanese
dolls are so creepy.
But dear...
My mother gave it to us
for her first granddaughter.
We have to keep it.
[MOM sighs] It's far too
detailed and intricate.
Especially in the eyes.
It's almost like
it's staring at us.
Put it away in the
closet or something.
[DAD]
Sorry, little doll.
[CHILD A]
Please, Mom!
[CHILD B]
Pretty, pretty please!
[CHILD A]
Buy me a new dress-up doll!
I want the one that's
in all the stores!
[CHILD B]
Me, too! Me, too!
[MOM]
All right, girls.
If that's what you want.
[CHILD A] Thanks, Mom!
[CHILD B] Yay!
[OKIKU]
Hey, girls.
I'm a doll.
[OKIKU]
Want to play with me?
[CHILDREN scream]
[YUZU]
Look.
She must have been very tired.
Apparently dolls sleep, too.
[URINOSUKE]
Oink.
Quiet, Urinosuke.
It wouldn't be nice to wake her.
[OKIKU]
Somebody.
Please play with me.
[KIRI] Sorry we weren't
able to do more.
[PRIEST A]
Nonsense.
You were quite helpful indeed.
So. What about the exorcism?
[PRIEST A]
Oh.
You mean for the
little doll I brought?
How come I have to
dress like a maid?
You are just full of complaints.
It looks so cute on you, though.
[SAKURA]
Heh heh heh.
[OKIKU screams]
[PRIEST A] I think your
staff has exorcised it
more than enough.
He left her here?
Well I guess I can't refuse
a request from a priest,
now can I.
So, doll.
What's your name?
I, uh, don't really have one.
Her name is Okiku.
[OKIKU]
Ah...!
--Okiku?
--[OKIKU] Yes...?
Good.
You'll start as a maid
and work your way up.
[OKIKU]
Staying here is one thing,
but why do I have to work?
We can't simply
allow you live here
at Konohanatei for free.
[OKIKU] But I'm a
traditional Japanese doll
made by a master craftsman!
[KIRI]
You don't look very traditional.
At least not anymore.
I wasn't meant to be a servant,
especially not a maid.
This is beneath me.
Would you prefer an
exorcism at the temple?
[OKIKU]
Definitely not!
Fine. Then welcome aboard.
Hey! Wait!
I never agreed to work here!
Where should I start you?
With... Yuzu!
With me?
What do you mean?
[KIRI] Would you take Okiku
and show her the ropes?
[YUZU]
Sure! Not a problem.
[REN] Hey, Yuzu!
Can you please bring me a towel?
[NATSUME]
It's coming down really hard.
[REN]
Yeah. It's miserable.
The rainy season can't
end soon enough.
It's already over
in some places nearby.
How come it's still so wet here?
[KIRI]
If you still need Yuzu,
she went out to
the shed with Okiku.
The shed?
Oh! That's right.
We have a guest in there.
[YUZU]
Pay attention, Okiku.
Delivering meals and
taking care of guests
is the most important
part of our job.
[OKIKU] Great.
Guess I'm stuck with that name.
But what's this guest
doing out here in the shed?
It looked like we had
plenty of open rooms.
Those won't work.
You see, this shed is special.
It's a weaving shed,
with a loom in it.
[YUZU]
Excuse me, Miss Iori.
[loom clicking]
[YUZU]
I brought some lunch for you.
[IORI]
Just leave it on the table.
Hey, Yuzu, look.
You see? She never
touched breakfast.
[IORI] And don't bother
tidying up the room.
You'll only get in my way.
In your way?!
Who do you think you are?
[YUZU] Of course.
Whatever you prefer.
[OKIKU]
What's with her attitude?
[YUZU] I don't know, but
she's so focused on her work.
She probably doesn't even
realize she's being that way.
That's still no excuse.
Also, her not eating
anything is really starting
to worry me.
[KIRI]
Now that you mention it,
she didn't take so much
as a bite yesterday, huh?
If this keeps up,
she'll get sick
or collapse from exhaustion.
I see.
Well, she's a very special
guest who came here to work.
Special how?
But...
I'll try to think of something.
Thank you, Miss Kiri.
[SATSUKI]
What's the matter, Yuzu?
--Oh. Nothing.
--[loom clicking]
[SATSUKI]
It's the perfect accompaniment.
--As in music?
--[clicking continues]
The sound compliments the rain.
[SATSUKI] They chose her
to be a priestess over me.
But I haven't given up
on serving the gods.
Once my job is done, I'll
try to join a shrine again.
[YUZU]
You're right. It does.
[OKIKU]
These are for Iori?
Onigiri will be
easier for her to eat,
particularly if she's busy.
[OKIKU]
You want me to take them?
Oh, no...?
You can't even handle
this little job alone?
You may end up stuck
as a maid for quite a while.
Just give 'em to me!
I can do it!
It isn't that hard.
[OKIKU]
I don't mind delivering meals.
But this one's
a different story.
[URINOSUKE]
Oink. Oink. Oink. Oink. Oink.
[OKIKU yelps]
[OKIKU screaming]
[YUZU]
Okiku?
[OKIKU] Here! Please
take these out to Iori!
[YUZU]
Uh... Okay.
[OKIKU]
Help! Keep her away from me!
I don't need another haircut!
[loom clicking]
[YUZU]
Hello, Miss Iori.
I, uh...
I brought you some rice balls.
I didn't ask for any.
[YUZU] The Head Manager
thought they might be easier
for you to eat while you work.
Just leave them on the table.
I'll eat them later.
[YUZU]
That's incredible!
Not yet. It's still
far from finished.
It'll be much more
beautiful when it's done.
[YUZU]
No.
Er, I mean, yes, the
fabric itself is lovely.
But the way you use your
hands is simply mesmerizing.
[loom clicking]
[YUZU] The sound is
just like Satsuki said.
[YUZU humming]
[humming continues]
[YUZU gasps]
Oh. I'm sorry.
The sound of the loom was
so rhythmic and calming.
It seemed so much like music,
I couldn't help but
sing along with it.
Please forgive me
for disturbing you.
--I'll go away now.
--[IORI] It's fine.
[IORI] I'm actually tired of
hearing nothing but the rain.
Could you stay and
sing for a while?
[YUZU coughs]
[YUZU (SONG)]
♪ La la la la la la la♪
[singing continues]
[YUZU (SONG)]
♪ La la la la la la la♪
[singing continues]
[YUZU] Watching it all come
together right before my eyes
is amazing!
But it's not good enough.
Huh?
I have two sisters.
The older one is
faster than I am.
She always finishes
her work before me.
The younger one is
more talented with her hands.
Her fabric is much
higher quality.
I'm not the fastest
one or the best.
I'm neither.
That's why I work so hard.
I want to become better
and faster than they are.
But wait.
You're both good and fast.
Your sisters may be
one or the other,
but can they do both like you?
I've never met
either of your sisters,
or seen them work,
so I don't really know
how you compare.
All I can say for sure
is that watching you work
has been so exciting.
Thank you for giving
me the opportunity.
[YUZU] Spinning threads out
of raindrops for weaving
must be difficult and
take a lot of practice.
Is it something you think
I might be able to learn?
I'm afraid not.
My sisters and I are servants
of the gods of heaven,
which means that we
alone can spin the threads
and make the cloth.
Wait a second. So all the
rain cloth you've been weaving
is a gift for the gods?
Is that why you've
been in such a hurry
to finish it?
Don't worry. It's beautiful.
They'll love it
when they see it,
and appreciate all the
hard work that went into it.
[IORI]
You're right.
They do know how
hard I've worked.
They'll like it.
However, this still
isn't finished yet,
but when it is I'll let
you be the first one
to see it.
Don't tell anyone, though.
It's our secret.
Sure.
[YUZU] Please don't overwork
yourself, Miss Iori.
Make sure you eat
when you get hungry,
and rest when
you feel tired.
Yummy.
[IORI] "Make sure you eat
when you get hungry.
And rest when you feel tired."
Don't overdo it.
Simple enough.
[IORI]
Okay. I'll try it.
[YUZU panting]
It's done? It's really done?
[YUZU]
Yay! Congratulations!
Here. Hold this end.
Be sure you grip it tight.
Ready?
And up!
[REN]
Hey, look!
[NATSUME]
The sky's clearing up.
[KIRI]
Finally.
Summer is here.