[YUBABA coughing]
[YUBABA] I think we'll be
lucky to get this cleaned out
by the end of next year.
Yuzu, could you take
that old box outside?
[YUZU]
Okay.
There's stuff inside.
Old papers.
What should I do with them?
[YUBABA] Oh. We haven't used
those old files in centuries.
Go ahead and throw them out.
[YUZU]
All right.
What could this be?
It's not a file.
Some kind of scroll.
Ren made us ramen for New
Year's Eve all by herself?
Because of the holiday,
we let the kitchen staff
off work early.
[YUZU]
You're such a good cook, Ren.
Whoever you marry is
gonna be really lucky.
Stop it. It's not a big deal.
I just bought some
noodles at the store
and threw them in a pot.
What are you still
doing here, Natsume?
Aren't you gonna go home?
Nah. My nephews would just
dogpile on me and beg for gifts.
[SATSUKI]
Sounds fun.
[door opens]
[KIRI]
Oh.
It looks like the snow's let up.
What do you think?
Should we go this year?
Oh, yeah!
That's a wonderful idea.
Uh, no.
[KIRI] And Yuzu hasn't
been there for New Year's.
[YUZU]
Uh?
To the shrine we go!
Oh, Yuzu. You don't even
have a haori jacket?
Come with me.
I have something
I can lend you.
Uh! Ren, are you okay?
Hardly. What is this thing?
Sorry, I was helping
the boss clean the attic
and I found it in an old box.
Ready to go?
Hey, I recognize that.
It's a k enzoku scroll.
Kenzoku ?
As in the servants of the gods
who work in their shrines?
The boss just said to throw out
all the files in an old box,
but when I saw it,
I got curious.
From the looks of it,
it's really old.
Why would she even have
something like this?
Good question.
Let's take it to the shrine
with us and find out.
It might turn out to be a
clue to her secret past.
She has a secret
past? What kind?
[REN]
Count me in.
[SATSUKI]
The mysterious kind.
That's what makes
it interesting.
[SATSUKI]
It's freezing.
The shrine here is open late so
everyone can celebrate together.
How wonderful!
[KIRI]
Hm?
That's a cute hood, Yuzu.
Red's your color.
Isn't it?
Hey! Not so fast! We have to
pay our respects and pray!
What should I pray for?
Riches or beauty?
You're even worse
than Natsume.
What? Why?
Listen to me. We're here to
offer the gods our gratitude.
They got us through another
year happy and healthy,
and we will thank them for it.
When you pray at a shrine,
you don't ask for
things for yourself.
That's what humans do.
[OKIKU]
All right. All right.
I've never seen so
many people this late.
It's like a slumber party
where everyone's awake!
[SATSUKI] I just wanna get
my feet under a kotatsu .
I hate the cold.
Well, it is chilly.
Hurry it up now. We don't
wanna miss our turn, do we?
[NATSUME]
I wanna ring the bell!
[REN] Not too loud!
The gods won't like it.
[KIRI] All right.
Come on. Make two lines.
[YUZU]
It's still hard to believe.
This time last year,
I never would've dreamed
a life like this
was even possible.
[YUZU]
Dear gods,
thank you for everything
you did for me this year.
Especially all the new friends
you brought into my life.
[bell tolling]
The New Year's Eve bells
are starting to ring.
[OKIKU]
Aren't they ringing them here?
The bells are over
at the temple.
We're at the shrine.
I brought this like
Natsume said,
but who should I go
to to ask about it?
Wait! Come back!
[gasps]
What the--? Where am I?
Hello? Is there
anybody else here?
[MAN A]
I'm so busy.
[PEOPLE chattering]
'Scuse me, sir? I'm lost.
Could someone please
tell me where I am?
[TSUBAKI]
Ugh!
Don't just stand in the
middle of the road.
What's wrong with you?
You got in my way.
Oh! I'm so sorry!
[TSUBAKI] You must be the
other new girl. Come with me.
Uh. What?
Wait. Slow down.
[WISH GRANTER A]
Welcome back, Tsubaki.
[WISH GRANTER B]
You're late, Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI]
I know.
But it's only because
I picked up the new girl.
[WISH GRANTER C]
New girl, can you take these?
[YUZU]
These scrolls.
They're just like the one
I found at Konohanatei.
[YANAGI]
Hachibei from Nichome again?
"My only wish is that my wife
might come back to me."
Well, she would if
you quit drinking
and went out and
got yourself a job!
What does he expect
us to do for him?
Turn down the
prayers of all those
who haven't made
their offerings?
Ignore those who don't clap
and don't help those who
won't help themselves?
[KOZUE] Maybe you should
try and lighten up a little.
[BOY A]
Um, gods?
Could one of you please
stop my mama's coughing?
Please help her.
That's all I want, really!
I think the good cough medicine
is on the third shelf, isn't it?
But he hasn't made
an offering yet.
And he didn't clap
his hands, either.
[YANAGI]
Shut up!
[WISH GRANTER G] We're back
from the mortal realm.
We fixed the dried-up well
in the village of Icchome.
Great job.
[YUZU gasps]
You-You're servants
of the gods!
You answer people's prayers
and grant their wishes!
Didn't you already know that?
I thought you worked here, too.
That's incredible!
You're practically saints!
I guess so. If you want
to put it that way.
But it's not like we answer
just anyone's prayers.
What?
[TSUBAKI]
We kenzoku must first determine
whether or not a person
deserves our help.
Then it depends on
what they want
and if it's for someone else.
Someone else?
So people aren't allowed
to wish or pray
for things for themselves?
Of course they aren't!
If they pray for themselves,
they must answer
their own prayers.
[gasps]
[TSUBAKI] People need to work
together and help each other.
That's the foundation
of the human world.
Our job is merely to
help them do that.
[YUZU]
That's-That's so beautiful!
You're saving the world
and you're so humble about it!
What is this girl?
She's not one of us.
[TSUBAKI] Well, she had a
scroll, so I thought she was.
That's why I brought her here.
That's right! The scroll!
I brought it to the shrine
hoping someone could
tell me about it.
This scroll looks just like
ours, but it's got a seal on it.
Only the person who
sealed it can open it.
And I don't know
whose seal that is.
[YUZU]
I see.
[YANAGI] Okay, I think
I've got the gist of it.
You found the scroll in a box
at this place
called Konohanatei,
and that's where you work.
[YUZU]
Mh-hm.
[TSUBAKI, YANAGI]
Hmm...
[YANAGI]
What do you think, Tsubaki?
[TSUBAKI] It doesn't sound
to me like she's lying.
And the scroll is real.
Which all means...
I messed up big when
I brought her here.
So then, what's your name?
You can call me Yuzu.
Well, Yuzu, afraid
I've got some bad news.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[TSUBAKI]
This Konohanatei you mentioned
doesn't exist in this world.
[YUZU]
Huh?
[TSUBAKI]
I'm saying... it's not there.
You can't ever go home.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[SATSUKI]
Yuzu!
Hey, have you seen Yuzu?
No, but it is crowded.
Don't worry, though.
I told her just to go back to
Konohanatei if she got lost.
She's not a baby.
She'll be fine.
[SATSUKI] I know it's not
like she's helpless.
But something
doesn't feel right.
[YUZU] What... What do you
mean I can't ever go home?
[TSUKUSHI]
Uh! Kozue!
Are you all right?
Sorry for collapsing on you.
We're so busy right now,
this is the last thing you need.
We'll be okay.
You've been working
non-stop for far too long.
[KOZUE] But if I can't keep
going, how will you manage?
There won't be enough
record keepers.
[YUZU]
Uh. Excuse me.
If you're a bit shorthanded,
perhaps I could help out.
I know how to read and write.
I can fill in for her.
[TSUKUSHI]
Sit here.
[YANAGI]
This is your ink and brush.
Write the people's names and
what they ask for on the scroll.
[TSUBAKI] Be quick! They're
gonna come one after another.
Uh, okay.
[WISHER A] Get rid of him.
Then I can get promoted.
[YUZU] I hear people's
voices in my head,
what they're wishing
and praying for.
They're so angry and selfish.
[clapping]
[BOY A] Thank you for
helping my mommy.
She's all better now!
[WISHER C] My daughter-in-law
safely delivered a healthy boy.
[WISHER CC] Thank the gods,
I found a new job
and we didn't lose the house.
[WISHER D] Thank you for
getting me through finals.
[WISHER E] Thanks for helping
my dad quit smoking.
[TSUKUSHI]
We're done!
At last, we can finally
get some sleep.
Rest while you can.
Tomorrow it starts
all over again.
[KOZUE]
I'm so sorry.
You got dragged into
this becauseof me.
It's fine. Don't worry.
How are you now? Any better?
Yes. Better than before.
You kenzoku have
such a tough job.
I could barely keep up.
It's difficult. That's for sure.
But for most people
who come to the shrines,
they've run out of options.
We're their last hope.
So what else can we do?
[YANAGI]
Your brushwork is good.
Where'd you learn to read and
write? Did you go to school?
[YUZU]
No. I was tutored.
Sister Bikuni taught me.
[INARI]
Sister Bikuni you say?
I know her well.
She is very devout.
My lady goddess.
Goddess? As in the
one you serve?
Inari Okami. Goddess
of rice and agriculture.
And who is this little fox?
Are you Sister
Bikuni's kenzoku ?
[YUZU]
Oh, no, lady goddess.
I'm not a kenzoku .
I work at a hotel.
A hotel?
So she was lost,
and somehow wandered onto
the "path of the gods."
That's when you, Tsubaki,
bumped into her,
and thinking she was a
kenzoku , brought her here?
[TSUBAKI]
Correct.
One thing.
What is this "path of the
gods" she's talking about?
I've never heard of it.
There are dozens of holy
shrines all over the country.
The "path of the gods" is a
passageway between them.
It's a quick way for the
gods and their servants
to get around.
Unfortunately for you, the path
also connects different times.
In other words, at this moment,
at this point in history,
Konohanatei doesn't exist.
Or at least, I've never
heard of a hot-spring hotel
for the gods.
[INARI]
Hot spring?
[TSUBAKI grunts]
Great idea.
Let's go and dig one.
We can't just go dig one!
It's complicated!
[INARI] There are too many
Inari shrines these days.
Managing them all is exhausting.
I just wanna sit in a hot spring
and relax for a little while.
Is that so difficult?
Please don't give me a guilt
trip, my lady goddess.
Sorry to interrupt.
But if this is a different
time, what do I do?
What are you talking about?
Fate brought you to us.
So there must
have been a reason.
Therefore, you should stay here.
[TSUBAKI] I knew she
was gonnna say that.
Yes, my lady.
She'll remain here.
But if she must stay,
could we at least keep her
as one of your kenzoku ?
She's well-educated,
and she learns quick.
We could definitely use her.
[TSUKUSHI]
Absolutely!
We'd love to have
Yuzu on the team!
[YUZU]
Huh?
[WISH GRANTER O]
Join us!
Not just anyone can
work for the gods.
It's a prestigious job.
But-But I...
[KOZUE]
You won't have to clean
that grubby, old
hotel ever again.
I can't!
[ALL]
Huh?
I-I can't stay.
I wanna go home to Konohanatei!
[YUZU]
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
You're fine. There's
no need to apologize.
Sorry for calling it
a grubby old hotel.
If you miss it so much, your
job there must be important.
[YUZU] No. I started
less than a year ago.
I don't handle the
important stuff.
I just, uh...
[YANAGI growls]
If you're just a new girl,
why would they care or notice?
Why're you so
desperate to get back?
[YUZU] You're right!
They don't need me at all!
[YANAGI]
Please don't cry.
I shouldn't have
said that. Sorry.
But... even so...
Konohanatei is more than
just the place I work,
it's my home!
And the people I work with,
they're not just friends,
they're like family!
[TSUBAKI] You're close
to them. I understand.
But say you were
able to go back,
it's still just a job.
Your friends won't
be there forever.
Eventually, you'll all
want to go your own ways.
[SATSUKI]
Once my job is done,
I'll try to join a shrine again.
[TSUBAKI] In the end,
you're not going to be together.
So why are you so determined
to get back to them?
[YUZU]
I guess...
Because I know them now.
And I can't go back to
the person I was before
because now they're part of me.
Such a rude old man.
He'd never talk to me like that
if I served the Inari shrine.
[YUZU]
They've changed me.
Everyone I've met at
Konohanatei has changed me.
They've made my life richer.
I can't help but love them.
Plus, if I suddenly vanished,
I think they'd be worried.
You are so dumb.
Did it not occur to you that
if you wanted to go home
for the sake of your
friends and not yourself,
you could just
write it on a scroll?
No. That never occurred
to me at all!
And it goes to show
how useless I am.
Maybe I shouldn't go back.
They might be better
off without me.
[YANAGI]
Although, sending you home
through space and time is
a bit beyond our abilities.
But don't despair just yet.
We'll figure something out.
As young kenzoku ,
we're not powerful
enough to take her back,
but I'm pretty sure
I know someone who is.
Sure. You take her
wherever she wants to go.
[TSUBAKI]
Which means you're distracted
and not going to help.
So, you guys know any older,
more powerful kenzoku ?
Thank you for trying so hard.
Tsubaki understands.
She's had trouble
finding her home, too.
She's actually new here.
A lifelong kenzoku ; she's
bounced from shrine to shrine
since she was a child.
The last one was
destroyed in a landslide.
So, she never really had
a home to begin with,
much less one to go back to.
There goes me and
my big mouth again.
She's gonna yell at me.
We don't know anyone?
Time travel is real tricky.
The kenzoku would have to
be hundreds of years old.
[TSUBAKI] Where are we
gonna find a fox like that?
Does she even exist?
[URINOSUKE oinking]
[YUBABA]
It's late. Where did they go?
They better be back soon.
[YUBABA]
Come... Come back.
[gasps]
Yuzu, the old scroll you found!
[YUBABA]
Come back home.
[TSUBAKI]
Did you hear that?
Sounds like someone over there
is wondering where you are,
and wants you to come home.
[TSUBAKI chuckles]
[TSUBAKI]
Get going.
[ATTENDEE D]
Maybe next year.
Hey. D'ya think should
we write something?
Um. If you want.
You shouldn't eat so
much this late at night.
It will make you get fat.
What do you mean? How the
heck can a doll get fat?
[SATSUKI sighs]
That idiot.
Where could she be?
[KIRI]
Less than a minute to go.
It's almost New Year's.
[WOMAN H]
One hundred and seven.
[SATSUKI] Hurry up and
get back here, Yuzu.
[click]
[gasps]
[FESTIVAL GOERS]
Happy New Year!
[screams]
[SATSUKI groans]
Why are you always falling out
of the sky and landing on me?
[YUZU]
Oh, Satsuki!
I was so scared!
You can't imagine how much!
Satsuki! I thought I might
never see you again!
[NATSUME]
What's all the fuss about?
You've gotten lost before.
Still, you shouldn't
wander off, Yuzu.
We were worried.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to worry you.
I'll be more careful
from now on.
This was fun.
We should do it again!
[ALL]
Happy New Year!
May this year be the best yet!
[KIRI]
This year, let's work hard
and make Konohanatei
better than ever!
It's one o'clock.
Where were you?
At the last minute, we
decided to go to the shrine.
Sorry. I hope you
weren't too worried.
Ha. I wasn't worried.
Don't flatter yourselves.
Happy New Year, boss! May this
year be the best one yet!
Happy New Year,
and the rest of it.
Hm.
Yuzu?
Is that your hood?
No. It's Ren's.
She just let me borrow it.
I see.
Well, anyway,
we've got guests coming bright
and early, so don't sleep in.
[YUZU] Uh. Wait, boss!
Just one more thing!
Thank you for bringing
me back home.
[YUBABA]
Sure. Welcome home.
[URINOSUKE oinks]
[INARI]
We'll need food.
I won't be able to
relax in the hot spring
without something to eat.
[TSUBAKI] Are you still
planning to dig that thing?
Please don't go through with it.
You'll hardly ever be there.
[INARI]
When I'm elsewhere,
we can let other
gods come use it.
Perhaps we could make
it a hot spring hotel.
I think it's a terrible idea.
[INARI]
Come on. Can't you picture it?
It would be fun. And once
it's built, you could run it.
Whatever you want.
[TSUBAKI]
A hot spring hotel?
[YUZU] I'm not a kenzoku .
I work at a hotel.
A hot spring hotel for the
gods called Konohanatei.
[TSUBAKI]
It couldn't be.
[gasps]
[YUZU] I wish for a warm
home for Tsubaki.
Yuzu.
[TSUBAKI] That little minx.
I can't believe this.
But how could she have known?
Yanagi must've said something.
[TSUBAKI] If the fox girl who
first wrote on this scroll
should ever become lost,
may she always be able
to find her way back home
to those who love and miss her.
Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI] I've got a hunch
this might come in handy.
[YUBABA] It was such a long time
ago, I'd completely forgotten.
The little fox girl
I met that night.
I don't remember her
name or her face,
but I think she was
wearing a red hood.
Just one more thing.
Thanks for bringing
me back home.
Sure. Welcome home.
[YUZU] I wish for a
warm home for Tsubaki.
[NATSUME]
It's so cold!
[KIRI] Our New Year's Day guests
will be here any minute!
[REN]
Natsume, hurry up!
[NATSUME]
Coming!
Yuzu, could you meet them
at the top of the stairs?
Sure. I'll go right now.
[SATSUKI]
Thanks.
Welcome to Konohanatei.
Thanks for coming.
I hope you enjoy your stay.