[YUZU humming]
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
You startled me.
Good morning, sir.
Welcome to Konohanatei.
May I get your bag for you?
Sir? Hello? Where
are you going, sir?
[KIRI]
Don't worry about him.
He's going to find Sakura.
He's one of her regulars.
You sure I shouldn't offer him
some tea or anything like that?
No. They're all right.
Best leave them to it.
[gasps]
[squeals]
[KIRI] Lately, he comes
here just to see Sakura.
He enjoys spending
time with her.
[YUZU] So he likes the
kind of hospitality
only Sakura can provide?
[KIRI chuckles]
Yes.
And speaking of regulars,
some of Ren's will
also be arriving today.
Go help her greet them.
Yes, Miss Kiri.
[YUZU] I wonder what
Ren's regulars are like.
[REN] Oh, Princess,
your hair smells divine!
[IMAGINARY GUEST A] You
noticed? It's my new perfume.
[YUZU]
Probably something like that.
Oh, my! Look at you.
Are you new here?
Uck. She's the plainest
fox I've ever seen.
Perhaps we should
give her a makeover.
Yuzu's a work in progress.
And she's sensitive,
so please don't tease her.
Goodness! We didn't mean
to tease the poor girl.
[GODDESSES]
Much.
We think she's
absolutely adorable!
[REN]
Yuzu, these are my regulars.
They're gods of entertainment.
Aren't their outfits
and makeup fabulous?
[REN giggles]
You both look amazing!
Just like always!
Originally, there was
supposed to be
a third member of our
party joining us today.
But she had a local festival,
so I'm afraid she's a no-show.
How nice for her.
To be a local god in a town
where she still matters.
Nobody bothers to make
any offerings or pray to us
except at New Year's.
These days, people
only call on the gods
when they're in trouble.
[BOTH]
"Help me!"
[GODDESS GUEST A]
Back in the old days,
there were festivals
all the time.
Tons of different gods got
invited to the mortal world.
[GODDESS GUEST B]
So true.
Ah, the good old days.
Since Konohanatei
sits on the path
between heaven and
the mortal world,
it was right smack dab in
the middle of all the action.
The place used to be packed!
Oh! You should've seen it!
Do you know why they
stopped having
as many festivals, Ren?
I don't.
You two are gods.
Do you know why?
We have no idea how the
mortal brain works,
but there are several
Western celebrations
that now seem to
be all the rage.
[GODDESS GUEST B] That
Halloween thing where children
dress up as ghosts and
ghouls is rather popular.
Goddess, that would
be perfect for you.
You wouldn't even
have to dress up.
Speak for yourself, Sister!
[GODDESS GUEST B chuckles]
Well, hello, Sisters.
Long time no see.
[GODDESS GUESTS chattering]
[GODDESS GUEST A]
We should have our own festival,
the three of us!
[REN gasps]
[REN] Ladies, wait! You're
rooms are actually this way!
Ladies?
[WOMAN]
Sounds wonderful, Sisters.
Are they gone yet?
Where have you been?
And why were you hiding
in the break room?
Those sisters are a
bit too fond of me,
and they like to kiss me
until my whole face is wet.
But anyway, you seen
Sakura around?
She seems to have ditched
her chores and disappeared.
One of her regulars is here.
Last time I saw her, she was
playing in the garden with him.
The master's here?
Yay! Then tonight I'm gonna
ask him to teach me kendo!
He's a kendo master?
Kiri didn't say anything
about him at all.
[NATSUME]
Well...
He's an old battle god.
And since there
haven't been many wars
in the mortal world lately,
he's got a lot of spare time.
[GODDESS GUEST A]
Back in the old days,
there were festivals
all the time.
Tons of different gods got
invited to the mortal world.
[GODDESS GUEST B] These days,
people only call on the gods
when they're in trouble.
[FORMER BATTLE GOD]
Hmm...
[gasps]
[YUZU] Wait! You don't
have to do that, sir!
I can go to the tool shed
and get you a hatchet
and a small knife!
Please don't damage
your precious sword!
It'll only take me a s--
It's all right. Don't worry.
Unless I do something with it,
the blade will remain in its
sheath and will only rust.
Besides, if it's not carved by
a katana, it won't fly as well.
[GODDESS GUEST A]
Fantastic! What a...
[GODDESS GUEST B]
Wonderful!
[GODDESS GUEST A]
Almost as good as the old days!
Natsume, get up there
and dance for us.
Or I'll have to kiss
that adorable face.
[NATSUME yelps]
Okay. I'll do my
fish-scooping dance.
Could you take a few more?
[laughing]
[GODDESS GUEST A, NATSUME]
And scoop, and scoop,
and scoop, scoop, scoop, scoop!
[GODDESS GUEST A]
Not so...
[WOMAN]
Seeing the place like this...
...makes me feel like I'm
back at the old Konohanatei.
[gasps]
You're the guest who came
in after Ren's two regulars.
[YUZU] Years ago, did
Konohanatei used to always have
big, loud parties like this?
Yeah.
The mortal world was a lot
livelier back then, too.
Sure, there were wars
and other hardships,
but the gods would come visit
far more often than they do now.
This inn was the place to be.
It was a grand old time.
Well, I can't say anything about
what Konohanatei was
like in those days,
because I wasn't there...
...but it's still
a special place,
and there are some things
we can offer our guests now
that back then we couldn't.
[WOMAN]
Huh.
You've grown pretty
wise, little fox.
Who'd have thought?
And if it's all
about the service,
you'd best get a move on.
[gasps] Yeah!
[GODDESS GUEST A] What, no fish?
You need to scoop some more.
I'm very disappointed
in you, Natsume.
They must be drunk.
We've opened three whole
barrels of saké just for them.
Satsuki, who is she?
Do you know her?
[SATSUKI]
The woman in the dark kimono?
No, I don't.
Didn't she come with
Ren's regulars?
[GODDESS GUEST B] Hello,
we're out of saké over here!
[REN]
Yuzu, can you get some more?
[YUZU]
Yes! I'm on it!
Thank you for staying
with us again.
Until next time. Safe travels.
You don't need to
see every guest off.
We can handle things.
Get some rest.
From the looks of it, you
were up drinking till dawn.
Almost.
But they're gods, it's not
like I could say "no."
[REN, NATSUME]
Who's she?
No idea. I thought
she was a guest.
Her voice does sound
familiar, though.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you all staring at me?
Well, to be fair, they
may be confused, boss.
They've never seen
you like this.
What the--?! It's you?!
You're kidding me!
Come now. You're that surprised
to see me in makeup?
[GIRLS shouting]
Huh?
The two of you want to
watch me put on my makeup?
That's a strange
request, but all right.
[YUBABA]
First, I put on my powder.
Then next..
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSUME, REN shouting]
[OKIKU sighs]
I am so bored.
[URINOSUKE oinks]
I finished all my chores,
so there's nothing left to do.
Maybe I'll go find those stupid
foxes and play with them.
[URINOSUKE oinks]
We're going to have
divine guests again today.
A very large group of them.
How large a group
you talking about?
It seems like we're
getting a lot of gods lately.
[NATSUME] New Year's is
a very busy time for gods.
So they like to get in some rest
and relaxation right before.
[OKIKU]
Uh...
Kiri's put me in charge
of giving everyone
their assignments.
Stay on your toes.
It'll be pretty hectic.
Right. Got it.
We can handle it.
[NATSUME]
Uh. Hm?
Okiku? Something wrong?
No. There's nothing
wrong. I'm perfectly fine.
And besides, why do you
keep calling me "Okiku"?
It's not my name.
Just because you say it doesn't
mean that's what it is. Jeez.
[OKIKU] I think I'll
go to town for a bit.
I know they don't want me going
too far from Konohanatei.
But it can't hurt if it's just
for a little while, right?
[URINOSUKE oinks]
Great. Glad you
agree, Urinosuke.
[URINOSUKE oinks]
[OKIKU] Then it's settled!
To town we go!
[OKIKU] Why do I have to
stay here all the time?
What does it matter?
They prob'ly won't even notice.
It's not like anyone cares.
It's busy. Must be
the year-end rush.
[MOUSE 1]Outta the way! Unless
you wanna get seriously hurt!
Move it, pig!
What's up? Do you smell
something, Urinosuke?
[URINOSUKE oinks]
[OKIKU]
Come on. Wake up.
Think you can move
your arms and legs?
Where am I?
[OKIKU]
Konohanatei.
Urinosuke and I found
you in the trash,
and decided to bring
you home with us.
The trash.
I see. So I was thrown out.
[OKIKU]
You were!
Therefore, starting today,
you'll be my doll and
you'll play with me!
But first, we're going to
have to do something
about those shabby
clothes of yours.
Don't worry, though.
They'll be an easy fix.
You see, here at Konohanatei,
there are all these foxes.
One's very handy.
Another's good at sewing.
And there's one that'll
do whatever you ask.
Basically, they're
all my servants,
but don't tell them I said that.
[giggles]
[OKIKU]
Ren!
What do you want? There's a
lunch banquet today. I'm busy.
Think you could stop
what you're doing
and whip up a new dress for me?
No. Not right now, Okiku.
[OKIKU] I can fill in for you
and serve at the banquet,
if it'll help.
[REN]
No thanks.
We have some very important
guests here today.
You and Sakura need
to not be in the way
and stay out of trouble.
That will help plenty.
[OKIKU] Uh! Forget it!
I don't want your crappy dress!
Well, clothes aren't
that important.
You're body is actually
a bigger issue.
We should probably get
that fixed up first.
You're full of chips and cracks.
If we don't do anything about
it, you could fall apart.
Just who I wanted to see.
Hey, Natsume, could you
come help me with s--?
Oh, how ya doin', Okiku?
Everything all right?
Like I said, my name
is not Okiku!
And you just decapitated
me, you moron!
Of course I am not all right!
Well, I can't leave ya headless.
There we go.
That's better.
At least for right now.
[OKIKU] Don't just glue me
back together with rice!
[NATSUME] Sorry, I'm busy,
so it'll have to do.
I'll fix you up for real later!
Ugh. Everyone's getting
on my nerves.
And this isn't even on straight.
[YUZU]
What's all that noise?
Hi, Okiku.
Oh? Who's this lovely girl?
Is she your little doll friend?
It's Yuzu.
[OKIKU]
What should I do?
This one's not too useful.
More like a total klutz.
[SAKURA humming]
[gasps]
Yuzu, help me out.
[YUZU]
What is it?
I need you to distract Sakura
while my friend and
I get out of here.
Uh. Sure. Okay.
Hey there, Sakura. What are
you up to? Is it something fun?
[YUZU screams]
[OKIKU]
She is totally useless!
[URINOSUKE squealing]
[OKIKU] Whew! Thank
heavens. We lost her.
I don't get it.
Why did we run away?
'Cause she's a menace!
That girl is an enemy
to dolls everywhere!
[LILY]
What's so bad about her?
Doesn't she just
wanna play with us?
Don't be naïve.
She doesn't wanna play with
us, she wants to scalp us!
I get traumatized just looking
at a pair of scissors.
But that's what children do.
It's what we dolls
were made for.
You only think it's
what we were made for
because that's how
you've been treated.
That's all over with.
You're safe now.
The foxes that work
here are good people.
Except for Sakura.
Think of this as
a new beginning.
You can start a whole
new doll life right here!
Now you're free to do
whatever you want.
Even curse the humans
to your heart's content.
What? Curse humans?
Does that mean you hate them?
Of course! I hate every
last one of them!
I was made by a
master craftsman,
supposed to be
a family heirloom,
and my humans went
and ditched me
for some dumb mass-produced
hunk of plastic!
So I put a curse
on that ugly thing
so it would forever be
losing one of its shocks
and one of its shoes!
You hid that doll's shoe
and sock, didn't you?
Curse the humans!
May they get leg
cramps every night,
which force them
to get out of bed
and walk the halls till
dawn! May they be...
Okiku, nobody's ever played
with you, have they?
That's why you're still
so pretty, isn't it?
No child has ever touched you.
Look at me.
My body's all
cracked and beat up.
The color on my arms
is faded from the sun.
And my shoes were lost long ago.
[LILY'S OWNER singing]
[LILY'S OWNER giggling]
But each scratch and
chip is precious.
They're memories
I share with her.
But she... she threw
you in the trash.
That's what happens at
the end of a doll's life.
[LILY] Eventually, all children
discover something they like
more than playing pretend.
They find someone they like
more than their dolls.
They grow up.
As dolls, our entire purpose
is to be a child's friend.
So when they're
no longer children,
that's the end of our life.
Bye. I have to go now.
What? Where are you going?
'Cause you don't have
to go anywhere, ever.
You're free now.
Don't ya get it?
You can stay here.
I'm sorry. I wish I could
be your friend, but I can't.
[SATSUKI]
Snow.
No wonder. It's been so cold.
Autumn was long, but
Winter's finally here.
[REN] Why are you sitting
around sulking?
I'm not sulking.
Are you still mad that
I wouldn't make you
a new dress earlier?
[OKIKU]
No. That's not it at all.
Ugh! Here.
Your very own furisode .
Happy early New Year.
I've been working
on it for days.
That's the only reason I said
I wouldn't make you
something earlier.
Understand?
Okiku, nobody's ever played
with you, have they?
Come on. Why are
you crying, Okiku?
Cheer up.
My name isn't Okiku.
Please stop calling me that.
[REN]
Okay. Fine.
[OKIKU]
But thank you for the furisode .
[BOYFRIEND A]
When did it get thrown out?
[LILY'S OWNER]
I don't know.
My mom put her in the
trash without asking me.
[BOYFRIEND A]
Any luck?
[gasps]
[LILY'S OWNER]
Yes! I found her!
Oh, Lily. Thank goodness!
[BOYFRIEND A] That doll's
pretty old and beat up.
[LILY'S OWNER]
Yeah, she is.
I've had her ever
since I was a kid.
My parents gave her
to me for Christmas.
[BOYFRIEND A]
So are we taking her
to get repaired or something?
[LILY'S OWNER]
Nope.
We're gonna get
her some new clothes.
I'm sure she must've
been lonely without me,
so I wanna make up to her.
[BOYFRIEND A]
Make it up to a doll?
[LILY'S OWNER]
What's wrong with that?
Lily's my best friend.