What's the big idea?
Yuzu's doing well.
She's gotten pretty
good at her work.
Therefore, I'm telling
you to go take a break.
You need it. You're enough
of a workaholic as it is.
What does that matter?
It's my choice.
I'm not tired at all.
I am perfectly fine.
And while I'm on this "break"
who's gonna cover for me?
Your temporary
replacement is not your choice.
[SATSUKI]
Hmph.
Listen to me.
You are taking tomorrow off.
Satsuki. I understand
how you feel.
But just because you work
yourself especially hard,
doesn't mean you'll get
out of this place any quicker.
[SATSUKI gasps]
--[door slams]
--[KIRI grunts]
[YUZU]
Um, Miss Kiri?
[KIRI]
Hmm?
[YUZU] Is there anything
wrong with, uh, Satsuki?
[KIRI] Just because you work
yourself especially hard,
doesn't mean you'll get out
of this place any quicker.
[SATSUKI] I know that.
You didn't have to remind me.
But... I feel like
the more time I waste,
the further behind her I get.
[SATSUKI gasps]
Hey! What the hell is all this?
[YUZU]
A cherry blossom bath!
The others said that
this pool was going to be
drained tomorrow morning.
So, I figured why not?
[SATSUKI] I've never had saké
in the hot spring before.
Though Kiri does
it all the time.
[YUZU]
Why not? Don't you like saké?
Yeah, but not at night.
I'm usually busy planning and
preparing for the next day.
Well then, tonight you can
and get a good night's sleep.
[SATSUKI] She's right.
I don't work tomorrow.
Tonight, I don't need to
worry about anything.
[SATSUKI] I didn't realize it
was almost the full moon.
[SATSUKI]
How'd I miss that?
When did I stop
looking up at the sky?
Time marches on
no matter what we do.
The Earth goes around the
Sun and the Moon keeps on
going around the Earth.
[YUZU] Everything can
change in a heartbeat.
You have to be careful
not to blink or stare
at your feet too long.
Otherwise, you could
end up missing it.
And when that happens,
it's a real shame.
[SATSUKI] It would be
a shame to miss it, huh?
This ancient spring has already
changed several times
while I've stared at my feet.
What else has passed me by?
[SATSUKI] You sure you
want to be putting in
all this work pampering me?
You must be tired yourself.
Oh, it's fine.
I've got the day
off tomorrow, too.
So, I can sleep in real late.
--[SATSUKI] Is that so?
--[screams]
--[YUZU] Merlion!
--[laughs]
Come join me!
Screw the pampering!
Uh... Okay.
[SATSUKI laughs]
[YUZU]
Is she drunk already?
So, you've got
tomorrow off, too, do ya?
Perfect. Then you're
comin' with me.
[YUZU]
Huh? Where to?
To town. Where else?
You haven't seen it yet, right?
I'll take ya and show ya around.
And I'll treat you to
something nice as thanks
for the flowers and saké.
[YUZU] But, Satsuki,
you don't have to do that.
Also, I don't have anything
I can wear into town.
[SATSUKI] You can borrow
one of my kimonos.
See you in the morning.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
My first time going out in town!
[REN yells]
You are unbelievable!
Are you seriously
going to go out in public
with that bedhead, Satsuki?
Who cares? It's my day off.
Why shouldn't I?
[REN] Because it's
completely unacceptable.
Go fix it. And as for you,
that obi's the wrong color.
Come with me.
I'll lend you one of mine.
If there's one thing I
can't stand, it's when women
are indifferent and don't
care about how they look.
[YUZU gasps]
Something wrong?
Oh, no. Nothing.
I've just never heard you be so
loud and demanding
before, Ren, that's all.
Ahh! Please pardon me.
A lady must always remain
demure and graceful,
even if her house is on fire.
[YUZU] Oh, my gosh!
She's cute and funny!
Satsuki? There's a
hole in your sock.
Are you just gonna leave it?
Yeah. It should be fine.
It is not! Change it, now!
[YUZU] Nobody's ever
scolded Satsuki before.
--Not that I've seen.
--Ren?
[YUZU] I get the feeling there
are a lot of different sides
to Ren I don't know about yet.
The two parties
will arrive by six.
[NATSUME]
Got it.
Satsuki is an
attractive young woman.
I wish she'd be more
mindful of her appearance.
And once she's a priestess,
she'll have to be.
It's practically a requirement.
Huh?
Oh. That's right.
You probably don't know.
Satsuki plans on leaving
the Konohanatei one day.
She wants to become a priestess.
[YUZU] Satsuki's panning
on... leaving Konohanatei?
[KIRI]
What a lovely day.
Perfect for a leisurely
stroll about town.
Wouldn't you agree?
What's up? You're being weird.
I thought you
didn't even like Yuzu,
yet you're taking
her out on a date?
[SATSUKI] I'm just showing her
around town today because
I have nothing else to do,
thanks to a certain someone.
[YUBABA]
Kiri! Kiri!
[KIRI]
Yes, boss? What is it?
There will be
two additional guests.
At the banquet.
[KIRI]
Understood.
I'll be sure to let
the kitchen know.
[YUBABA]
Thank you.
Hey. If you need me, I could--
[KIRI ]
Absolutely not!
We won't have that many people,
so everything's covered.
Go to town!
[YUZU gasps]
Why did Ren have to
hold us up like that?
We left so late.
She did it for a reason.
Look at how pretty you are!
[SATSUKI grunts]
[SATSUKI] Does she really have
to keep saying things like that?
[YUZU]
Satsuki! Over there!
Look it! How cute!
[FORTUNE CAT meows]
[YUZU] So many Maneki-neko !
They're adorable!
We have any expression
you could want.
Come take a look
at our fine selection.
A neko with its right paw
raised brings good fortune.
[SATSUKI] Are you really
that big a cat lover?
--[YUZU] Yes!
--[SATSUKI] But why?
Cats aren't that tasty.
[YUZU, BAKENEKO gasp]
[SATSUKI]
There are more shops over there.
Why don't we go check those out?
[YUZU]
Okay.
[YUZU giggles]
That's mitarashi dango ,
right, Satsuki?
They look good.
They smell good, too.
May I have a bite of one?
If you want.
[SATSUKI] I guess most
people do like dumplings.
[YUZU] Would you like
to have some of mine?
Me? Um. Okay.
All right. Here you go.
--[SATSUKI whimpers]
--Try it.
See? The shiratama
is all jiggly.
Isn't it just delicious?
[SATSUKI] Nobody's
staring at us, are they?
This is a busy town, isn't it?
The temple I used
to live at was remote,
and way out in the mountains,
so I was shocked
when I first saw it.
[SATSUKI]
People don't bother you, though.
You seem comfortable enough.
[YUZU] Lots of visitors
would come to the temple.
All kinds of folks and more
than a few humans, too.
[SATSUKI]
I see.
I was wondering how she knew
so much about human things.
It's not often, but we do
sometimes get humans here.
They really come here?
[SATSUKI] This town is a
stop on a main travel route.
You can expect to see
just about anyone here.
[MOUSE 1A]
Step aside! Coming through!
[YUZU]
I think it's wonderful.
All the people
passing through here,
with all their own
secrets and stories,
and the adventures
they've been on.
It's exciting!
[SATSUKI]
Is it?
Thanks for inviting
me out, Satsuki.
It's a day I don't
think I'll ever forget.
[SATSUKI sighs]
Whatever. I guess that means
you're enjoying yourself?
I am.
[SATSUKI] I just had time
to spare, that's all.
I didn't do anything special.
She didn't have to thank me.
Though I suppose it's
easy enough to say.
[YUZU giggles]
[SATSUKI] So why can't I seem to
say it back to her?
[SATSUKI] Don't go
getting weird ideas now!
[SATSUKI] I've got no problem
saying anything to Kiri.
[KIRI]
Oh, Satsuki.
[SATSUKI] But this girl.
She throws me off somehow.
[MAN A]
Hey, Tome! Long time, no see.
Have the cherry blossoms
bloomed up at the shrine yet?
[MAN A]
Sadly, no.
Cherry blossom
season came and went,
and the tree never
sprouted a single bud.
I suppose it's just too old now.
Aww. That's such a shame.
I never saw a finer sacred
tree in all my travels.
It was lovely.
So then, where do
you want to go next?
I think I'd like
to stop by the shrine!
[SATSUKI gasps]
The shrine?
[SATSUKI] There isn't anything
interesting to see up there.
[YUZU] I just wanted to pay
my respects to the local gods,
and I heard something
about a sacred tree.
So, I was curious.
And I want to see
where you'll be working
after you leave Konohanatei.
'Scuse me? After I leave what?
[squeals]
[SATSUKI]
Ren told you, didn't she?!
That big blabbermouth!
She's gonna pay!
[YUZU]
Please! Don't hurt her!
This is my fault!
I know I probably shouldn't
have said anything, but...
Honestly. I think you would
make a wonderful priestess.
I can picture you leading
the ceremonies.
Well, you can forget about that!
Wait, where are you going?
[SATSUKI]
To the bathroom!
I'm really sorry...
[YUZU] What did I say
that upset her that much?
Think, Yuzu, think!
[SATSUKI]
Listen up.
Stay right there.
Don't move, or you'll get lost.
[YUZU] Even when she's mad,
she still worries about me.
She's got a kind heart.
[GHOST GIRL grunts]
[YUZU]
Hey, are you okay?!
[GHOST GIRL]
Thank you for your help.
I was with my sister,
but we got separated.
Have you seen her?
I've been looking for her
for five days now.
[YUZU]
Five days?
She and I still have so much
work we have to do.
This is such a predicament.
[YUZU]
Oh, no!
Um... I'd like to
help you look for her,
if that's okay with you.
[GHOST GIRL]
I'd be very grateful. Thank you.
[YUZU] Sorry, Satsuki.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I promise.
[SATSUKI] Guess I should
head back to Yuzu.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER]
Hey! You there! Girlie!
[SATSUKI]
No matter how irritated I was,
I shouldn't have snapped at her.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER]
I'm talking to you.
[SATSUKI] She's young,
and new, and she didn't know.
--I could've cut her some slack.
--Hey, Girlie! I'm lost.
Show me where to go.
[SATSUKI]
And it being Yuzu,
she'll pretend she's forgotten
about it when she hasn't.
Don't act like you
don't hear me, Girlie.
Damn. This brat won't go away.
You do not get to
call me "girlie."
I'm your elder. Now go buzz off.
Why, you--!
That's no way to talk to
a poor, lost, little soul.
If you keep being mean
to me, I'll throw a fit!
I'll roll around on
the ground and cry,
until everyone in town knows
how horrible you are!
[SATSUKI]
Is that a threat?
[rasps]
[SATSUKI]
Dammit. Fine. I'll help you.
Whatever.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER giggles]
Glad you understand.
[SATSUKI] Sorry, Yuzu. I'll
buy you a maneki-neko later.
So, where exactly
do I need to take you?
To go find my older sister.
Then you're a "lost child"?
Don't say it like that!
When my sister wasn't looking,
I went off to have some fun,
and now I can't get home.
[SATSUKI]
Then you deserve to be lost.
You're gonna end up alone in
life pulling stunts like that.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER]
That was uncalled for.
And... there was more to it.
I was tired of my big sister
constantly teasing me
just because I'm younger.
It's not fair.
I'm not a little baby anymore.
Yeah. Older sisters
do tend to be pretty selfish.
That's right! Do you have
an older sister, too?
--[SATSUKI] Dammit!
--We're gonna get along well.
[SATSUKI]
I beg to differ.
[BYSTANDER 2A] I'm sorry. I
haven't seen anyone like that.
[YUZU]
That's too bad.
Thanks anyway. Sorry to trouble
you. I'm not from here.
So, I'm afraid I
don't know the area.
That's quite all right.
Nevertheless,
I appreciate you trying.
[YUZU gasps]
Where were you headed to?
Maybe we can look there.
To the north.
Every year, we follow
the celestial bridge
from the southernmost point,
slowly northward.
All the others we were traveling
with have already gone on ahead.
My younger sister
and I fell behind.
What? Aren't you worried that
you need to catch up to them?
[GHOST GIRL]
A little, but not really.
Throughout the years,
this journey has been
undertaken countless times.
[GHOST GIRL] Better to try
and stay calm, then to panic.
One can never outrun
the passing of time.
That's beautiful and very wise.
[REN] Satsuki should be more
mindful once she's a priestess.
[YUZU] I was sad when
I first heard that,
but it's not like
we're parting for life.
There's still so much
I don't know about this city
and its people,
about Konohanatei,
and about my new friends
that I work with there.
But I want to learn
as much as I can,
and grow to love
it all even more.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER] So, you
think we'll be good friends,
or maybe best friends?
[SATSUKI]
Would you shut up already?
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER]
What's your older sister like?
Does she act like the world
revolves around her?
[SATSUKI]
Definitely.
She's self-centered
and tactless,
and really great at
everything she does.
[HIIRAGI] I have no interest
in becoming a priestess.
Let Satsuki do it.
Serving the gods
is her dream, not mine.
She's awful. A terrible person.
Wow. My sister may not
think about others,
but she's not that bad.
[SATSUKI] Good grief.
Can I just smack her?
I like you a lot more
than my sister.
What if you come
north with me instead?
[SATSUKI]
No way!
Why not?
Serving the gods
is noble and dignified.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER]
And not just any gods,
like the local ones
of a small town.
We serve the gods
of Takamagahara.
Ensuring the well-being of
Nakatskuni also falls to us.
It's important work.
You could give your sister
a run for her money.
[SATSUKI gasps]
[SATSUKI'S DAD] We'll send
Hiiragi to work at Konohanatei.
[SATSUKI'S MOM]
But dear, she's the eldest,
and she has so many gifts,
everyone expects her
to become a priestess.
[SATSUKI'S DAD]
You're right.
Satsuki should go
to Konohanatei instead.
I've got you now.
[SATSUKI gasps, screams]
[CROWD screamin]
What's going on?!
Where did this
sudden wind come from?!
I don't know!
[YUZU whimpers]
I know where she is.
By the sacred tree.
[GHOST GIRL'S SISTER] If I make
the cherry blossoms bloom,
my sister will finally
see what I'm capable of.
I wasn't able to do it before,
all by myself, but now
I have someone to help me!
[SATSUKI]
Wait a sec! Help how?
You're not planning to use
me as fertilizer, are you?
[YUZU pants]
[SATSUKI]
Somebody? Anybody?
Flowers of the sacred tree.
Blossom!
[YUZU gasps]
It just bloomed!
[BLOSSOM VIEWER A] The sacred
tree has flowered at last!
This calls for a celebration!
A banquet, too!
Satsuki! I found you!
[YUZU] I was worried you might
be stuck in the bathroom
and missing all this!
[SATSUKI]
Yup. There you go again.
Acting like I was
never mad at you
and nothing even happened.
[YUZU grunts]
Are you all right?
Yeah. I think so.
You should've pulled
me down more carefully.
[AYAME]
Satsuki?
[YUZU]
It's one of the priestesses.
Ayame.
Well, this is a surprise.
It's not very often that
I get to see you here.
How are you?
Yeah, uh, I'm fine.
[AYAME] Come on! I'll
find you a seat right up front!
[SATSUKI]
Hold on a sec, Ayame!
[AYAME] Don't worry.
I'll make sure I snag one
for your little friend, too!
[YUZU]
Hey! Wait for me!
What's wrong?
Oh. I was with somebody
looking for her younger sister.
Her sister?
Yeah, it's awful.
She said she'd been
looking for her for five days.
It seemed like she
really needed help.
I'm sorry I moved.
No, don't be.
I kinda did the same thing.
[YUZU]
Huh?
And anyway,
they found each other.
[YUZU gasps]
[SATSUKI] See the one
with the silver hair?
[YUZU]
Huh?
The pretty priestess
over there in the middle.
[YUZU]
Ah.
Believe it or not,
that's my sister.
She was going
to work at Konohanatei,
but she's older than me,
so I went in her place.
They chose her to be
a priestess over me.
[YUZU gasps]
But I haven't given up
on serving the gods.
Once my job is done,
I'll try to join a shrine again.
And I'm self-conscious
about this,
so keep your mouth shut.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
She's such a good person.
Satsuki's kind,
and a little awkward,
and she doesn't like to talk to
people about herself that much.
Yet she told me
something very personal.
[YUZU whimpers]
[YUZU] She trusted me
enough to confide in me.
I never knew something like
that could make me so happy.
Hey. What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm so glad...
that I came to Konohanatei,
and got to meet everyone there.
Especially you, Satsuki.
I'm just...
so happy we're friends!
Come on.
There's a banquet
in the main hall tonight
and they'll need us.
So, let's get back to work.
All right.
[YUZU] Ever northward,
two sisters travel.
Leaving only footsteps and
cherry blossoms behind.
They're on their way,
so let us go home,
back to our Konohanatei.