[YUZU]
Miss?
Hello? Can you hear me?
You all right?
[gasps]
[BOTH scream]
[YUZU]
Hello?
Are you sick? Did
something happen to you?
Uhh. Yeah, sorta.
You see, I was shipwrecked.
Shipwrecked?
[REI]
It was terrible.
The boat I was on
sank in a storm.
After it went down,
I grabbed a piece of wood
and drifted for days.
I guess I must've passed out
because the next thing I knew,
I was washed up here.
Uh?
I'm sorry.
The only thing that
I have is this manju .
But please, take it.
You need it more than me.
Keep it. I was kidding
about the shipwreck.
[YUZU]
You were just kidding?
That's good. You scared me.
Yeah. Storms aren't
a problem for me.
'Cause I'm really a mermaid.
Like you have a tail
and live in the sea?
Yup.
I got separated from
my mermaid friends.
In fact, I'm looking
for them right now.
Your poor friends must be
so worried about you.
I know I would be.
I can shout real loud.
Is it okay if I help
you look for them?
[REI]
Huh?
[YUZU]
Mermaids! Mermaids!
Are you on this beach somewhere?
[YUZU yelps]
Is this a tail?
Yeah. That's a tail.
And it's my tail.
Okay, so why do you have it?
[YUZU]
Uh...
Now that you mention it,
I don't know.
I'm not actually sure
what it's used for.
[chuckling]
Sorry. That was weird.
I shouldn't have asked.
[REI] I didn't expect you
to answer so seriously.
[YUZU]
Hm?
Why not?
Forget it, cat girl.
It's not important.
But I'm not a cat.
I'm a fox, and it is important.
Mermaids, where are you?!
--I lied about being a mermaid.
--Your friend is-- Huh?
[YUZU]
Wait, you did?
I'm not out here looking
for my friends, either.
The truth is I don't
have any friends.
I lie all of the time.
So pretty much everybody
I know hates me.
[REI'S MOM]
Lying is so childish.
Are you doing it just to
get people's attention?
[REI] When it comes to my mom,
things are difficult.
And my step-dad's a
stubborn workaholic
I've never been close to.
School's not any better.
Since I'm a liar, nobody
listens to me there either.
They just walk away.
I know I'm not fooling anybody.
No one pays attention
to my lies anymore.
But still, I keep doing it.
I try to stop.
But reality is so damn
boring I can't stand it.
You really think so?
I work at a hot spring hotel,
where I get to meet
all kinds of people.
They're all so different and
have such interesting stories.
It makes each day exciting.
You lucked out.
Life doesn't feel boring to you
because you have a job you like.
I don't have any dreams
or goals for my future.
So you don't know
what you want.
That's tough.
But there has to be
something you like.
[REI]
Mm...
I guess when I was a kid...
I did like picture books.
[REI] And drawing whatever
random stuff I felt like.
[YUZU gasps]
How cool! It looks just like me!
Doodling's one thing.
But I'm not that good,
so I can't I'd become
a painter or anything.
I go to school, read my
books, take my tests.
And when I grow up,
I'll get a job in an office.
Stuck in a routine
day-in-day-out
for the rest of my life.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[REI grunts]
Don't worry about it.
Really sorry for deceiving you.
Bye, fox girl.
You don't need to say "sorry."
You didn't deceive me.
When I offered you my manju ,
you didn't take it.
[REI]
What?
Deceiving someone isn't
merely telling lies,
it's using those lies
to get something.
Your lies aren't like that.
They're just fun stories.
I mean, in the course
of only a single day,
I've met a survivor
of a shipwreck,
a mermaid from the ocean,
and finally, you.
My lies are fun?
[YUZU]
Uh-huh!
[REI]
Guys! Guys!
I just saw an alien out
back behind the school!
Look up! There goes
its spaceship!
[BOY A]
I see it! Cool!
[GIRL B] Huh? You do?
I don't see anything.
[GIRL A] I hope it comes
back. I wanna see!
[REI]
You're right.
Back when I was a kid,
telling stories was fun,
even if they were made up.
Reality is dull if
it's nothing more
than repetition and routine.
But fantasies and daydreams
are part of reality,
so it doesn't have to be boring.
I'm so glad I met you.
I wish I knew someone
like you back at home.
You do know someone.
[REI]
Huh?
There is someone
you know already,
who would love to
hear your stories.
Who needs you and won't
turn their back on you.
I promise.
I was once like you and didn't
know what friendship was,
but then I got to make
some true friends.
Please keep on
telling your stories.
Go and share them with as
many people as possible.
[TANABE]
Matsumoto.
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto! Please wake up!
You were unconscious!
Are you all right?
[REI grunts]
Who are you?
[TANABE]
What? It's me! Tanabe!
We're in the same class.
I sit right in front of you.
[REI]
Oh, yeah. Her.
You almost scared me to death.
Since you've missed
so much school lately,
I thought I would bring
you your homework,
but when I got here...
I saw your shoes on that ledge
and my heart nearly stopped.
Sorry. It was the fish.
You see, they were
rare flying fish,
and I was trying to
catch them, and I fell.
But managed to swim to shore.
[chuckling]
[TANABE]
What? That's hilarious!
You think so?
There is someone you
know already,
who would love to
hear your stories.
Well, yeah. I'm so
glad you're alive.
[REI]
I may have yanked her tail,
but she wasn't pulling my leg.
[TANABE]
What are you talking about?
[REI chuckles]
[REI] The dream I just had.
You gotta hear it.
So, there was this fox...
That kid's not from
anywhere around here.
He must be a human
who wandered over.
It happens sometimes.
A human?
[YUZU] That must've been
what happened to her.
Humans occasionally
wander in and out.
Most of them don't
even realize it.
He'll find his way
home eventually.
What are those things? Mice?
Ooh! Fluffy!
Owie!
Watch it! Don't go
around picking on girls!
Hey, let go of me!
What's this shrimpy
guest doing here?
If that kid were a guest,
I would've stopped you
before you hit him.
She's mean!
What's your problem?
I only wanted to play!
Sakura doesn't have
time to play with you.
Unlike all you spoiled,
little, rich kids,
she has a job that
she has to do.
[yelps]
I'm going to have a very
important job when I grow up,
'cause I'm special.
At least, that's
what everyone says.
Everyone?
Dad, Mom, and Mr. Takahashi.
Takahashi? Is he your teacher?
He's the one who first
noticed I was special.
"You're a special one,
Kaito. And smart.
When you grow up, what you
do will be very important."
See?
So I'm not a spoiled kid,
and my work's way more
important than hers.
[YUZU]
But, Kaito.
As someone who is destined
to do great things one day,
shouldn't you be more
respectful of others
who are working hard
in what they do?
How would you feel if
someone belittled your job?
He must've hit a nerve.
I've never seen her angry.
What? This is Yuzu
when she's angry?
How can you even tell?
Sorry for what I said.
[KAITO'S FOSTER MOM]
Kaito!
[KAITO]
That's my mom calling. Later!
What does "later" mean?
Does he plan on coming back?
He disappeared.
That can't have been real.
I must finally be
losing my mind.
Kaito, are you awake?
[KAITO'S FOSTER DAD]
Feel like going for a walk
with your Mom and Dad?
[KAITO laughing]
[KAITO]
Yay! I win!
[KAITO'S FOSTER DAD panting]
Kaito. You've gotten
so big and fast.
My little boy. You've
grown so much so quickly.
Can't believe today's the day.
[KAITO]
Huh?
What's wrong, Dad?
Why are you crying?
[KAITO]
Uh! Mr. Takahashi!
Yo!
[KAITO] Hey! Come on!
Come on! Let's play!
Hey, there buddy.
So, Kaito! How ya been doing?
[KAITO]
I'm good.
Mom and Dad are over there.
[TAKAHASHI] Your mom
and dad did a great job.
Now say goodbye to them.
[KAITO'S FOSTER MOM]
Bye, Kaito. Study hard.
I know you're going
to be amazing.
You're new family
is waiting for you.
I hope you'll be happy there!
[YUZU] What is it?
Did you find something?
Kaito! What are you doing here?
What's wrong?
[KAITO]
I was at school, and I ran away.
You did?
I wanna go home! I hate it here!
But you can't.
That wasn't your real home. And
those weren't your real parents.
It was true! I wasn't theirs!
I didn't belong to them,
so I couldn't go home, not ever!
We're very special.
That's why we have to study.
'Cause one day, we'll have
important jobs helping people.
It's the reason
Mr. Takahashi chose us.
[KAITO]
I was chosen.
I didn't have the right
to choose for myself.
Oh, Kaito.
[KAITO] Come with me!
We can run away together!
I heard that, you brat!
Now you're just being
manipulative. Go!
It's time you went home!
Never! Never! I'm never going
to go back there again!
[SMOKER STEPFATHER] I'm never
going back there again!
What the--?
It's past your checkout date.
You have to go home.
Enough is enough.
I can give you more money.
Go on. Tell me how much
you want, Cat Ears.
What's it gonna take?
I'm a fox, thank you!
And this is in no
way about money!
It's okay. Let me.
[REN]
All right, Kiri.
[KIRI]
With all due respect, sir,
I need to inform you of
something you're unaware of.
You see, what you call
"money" is nothing more
than worthless paper here.
Now I get it.
When I woke up
after the accident,
I couldn't figure out where
I was or why I was here.
I'm dead. And this
must be the afterlife.
Oh, no. You're still
very much alive.
So if you don't mind,
please get out now.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER] Give me a
break, lady! Then I nearly died!
What the hell?
How heartless are you?
My deepest sympathies, sir.
It would seem Hell didn't
want you just yet.
Better luck next time.
You say that like I
failed a job interview.
"Hell didn't want me yet"? Tch.
And besides, even
if I did go home,
I still can't go back
to my old life.
It's impossible.
[KAITO]
I don't wanna go back either.
So I know how you feel.
[YUZU]
Careful, Natsume.
You're throwing him really
high. Don't drop him now.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER] They weren't
your real folks, huh?
And ya didn't like this
school, so you took off?
I didn't know what
being special meant.
I thought I could be
anything when I grew up.
But it turns out my
future is on a track
someone else laid down for me.
That's a rather sophisticated
way of puttin' it, kid.
Me? No track.
I started out as a truck
driver, worked hard,
and managed to end
up the president
of a small transport company.
I had an awesome wife and kid.
Can't say life was
always smooth sailing,
but I couldn't
complain about it.
Then it happened.
I got into an accident.
One wrong move turned
my life upside down.
In the end, we're
all in God's hand,
just dancin' away in his palm.
You seem like a good kid.
You're healthy, able-bodied,
and you've got a bright
future ahead of ya.
Those are all things
I don't have.
But you've got a family, Mister.
I don't have that.
I wasn't theirs.
My mom and dad weren't
my actual parents!
We weren't a real family!
Then we got somethin'
else in common.
[KAITO]
Huh?
My daughter isn't my real kid.
My wife had her
before we got married.
She didn't like me
much at first.
Either she was distant
or we'd end up fighting.
Teenage girls are
so damn complicated.
Seriously, why is that?
You're asking me?
How would I know?
It took a very long time
for her to accept me
and think of me as her family.
Is she why you don't
wanna go home?
[SMOKER STEPFATHER]
Don't be stupid!
You think I hate her for that?
She's my daughter!
I raised that girl
like she was my own.
I paid a fortune for her to go
to some cockamamie art school.
Now she's out of the house,
enjoying her life,
and I'm very happy for her!
Then why? Why don't
you wanna go home?
Your daughter's probably
waiting for you.
[gasps]
[KIRI chuckles]
What do you know?
How can you ask me to go
home in the state I'm in?
When we became a family,
I vowed to provide for
them and protect them.
I'll be nothing but
a burden from now on.
They'll have to take care of me.
How can I do that to them?
Hey, come on back.
You've slept long enough.
It's time to wake up.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER]
I wasn't a perfect man,
but I kept my vow.
I was a good husband and father.
If it all ends here, I can
still hold my head up high
and call it a good life.
Right?
We're all in God's hand,
just dancing away in his palm.
Isn't that what you said
just a few minutes ago?
Sometimes you have to deal
with what life gives you.
Huh. Usin' my
words against me?
You sound like my wife.
I'm sure.
I can hear her grumbling
even here in Konohanatei.
She's a patient woman,
and she's loved you,
stubborn fool that you are,
since the day she married you.
Trust me. She has
you all figured out.
Surrender and go back to
the palm of your wife's hand
where you belong.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER grunting]
[KIRI chuckles]
Damn you! I'm outta this place!
[KIRI]
Goodbye, sir.
I hope you enjoyed your stay.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER]
Stay outta trouble, kid.
You and me aren't
all that different.
Bye, now. See ya around.
I'm gonna go home, too.
Does that mean you're
feeling better about things?
I still wish that I had a
little more say in my future,
and that I had a family,
but I'm gonna study hard, so
that one day I can help people.
[OKIKU] I told you! My hair
hasn't grown out yet!
It doesn't need to be cut again!
[SAKURA]
Come back!
Listen up, you can
have fun out here,
but don't wander into
the guest rooms!
Speaking of people
who wandered in,
do you guys remember that boy
who pulled Sakura's tail?
No. What boy do you mean?
Yuzu!
[gasps]
Hi, Kaito! You came back!
I did. It feels like
it's been forever, Yuzu.
You're so small now.
I think maybe it's you
who grew up and got tall.
Have you been doing well
since you were here?
[KAITO]
Mh-hm.
I have a new family
I really like.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[KAITO]
Uh.
Sorry. Seems like Dad
wants to leave now.
I better go.
Thanks, Yuzu. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, huh?
So, guess he's not
coming back this time?
Then you do remember him.
Good for him.
He must've found what he needed,
or someone who needed him.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER]
Kaito.
Kaito!
You awake, my sleepy boy?
Whaddya say we go out
and do some shoppin'?
[barks]
[REI'S MOM]
Adorable.
These are all of Kaito
when he was a puppy?
[TAKAHASHI]
Yes.
His foster parents took
lots of pictures for us.
He had a hard time
when he first came to
the training center.
We weren't sure
he'd make the cut.
But then something clicked
and now he's a real pro.
After the accident, my husband
completely shut down.
He couldn't cope.
Losing his eyesight
affected him deeply.
But ever since Kaito came,
it seems like he's
truly happy again.
We've been lonely since
our daughter moved out,
but now we have a
beautiful golden boy.
It feels as if he was meant
to be with us all along.
All right, bud, you ready?
Remember, I'm countin' on you.
[SMOKER STEPFATHER]
Let's go.