[YUZU growls]
[BIKUNI chuckles]
[YUZU cries]
I think I know
what I'll call you.
From now on, your name is Yuzu.
[KIRI] Once upon a time
there was a very lonely girl.
She didn't have any
family or friends,
and spent all her
time by herself.
She did everything she
could to try and make friends,
but the other girls excluded
and shunned her.
Not one soul really
cared about her.
[LONELY GIRL]
Why won't anyone love me?
Is it me?
Am I not good enough?
Is it something I can change?
Or should I just
become someone else?
[KIRI] And so she decided
to erase herself.
[crashing noise]
She believed it was the
only way she could become
a different person.
[LONELY GIRL]
Hey, guys, look!
That girl you
didn't like is gone.
Is this better?
Can we be friends now?
[LONELY GIRL (MONSTER)]
Why are you running away?
Didn't I fix it?
Please, just love me a little.
Then we can be together,
and you can become
this way, too.
[YUBABA] What are you
all still doing awake?
[GIRLS scream]
[REN]
Oh.
--[NATSUME] We...
--[SAKURA] Were...
--[KIRI] Just...
--[YUZU] Uh...
[GIRLS]
Sorry, boss.
[YUBABA]
Ugh.
Don't they realize that
staying up this late
will ruin their complexions?
She got us good, didn't she?
The boss is five times
as scary at night.
[KIRI]
Should we call it, then?
And go to bed.
That was so much fun.
Satsuki and Okiku
should have come, too.
They really missed out.
[KIRI]
What is it?
[NATSUME]
Uh...
There are five of us,
but six shadows.
[KIRI]
Uh...
[MASKED GUEST A]
Huh?
[COOK A]
[GIRLS scream]
[NATSUME laughs]
Awesome!
Stop that! It's not funny!
You guys know what's going on?
The lights went out
all over the building!
[NATSUME]
Yeah!
We were all telling
scary stories,
and then a real ghost showed up.
Can we please
not talk about that?
[KIRI]
All right, ladies.
Mysterious shadows aside,
we still have a hotel full
of guests to take care of.
So let's split up and
make sure everyone's safe.
Got it?
[GIRLS]
Got it.
Satsuki. Oh, that's right.
Don't give me that look!
I can handle it.
[SATSUKI] Yuzu and I
will take the first floor.
[YUZU]
Uh, sure.
If we see a ghost, you kill it!
[NATSUME] But wouldn't it
be more fun to catch it?
[KIRI sighs]
Just get going.
[LONELY GIRL (GHOST) laughs]
It's really quiet, huh?
When I was little,
sometimes I'd nap too long
during the day and then not
be able to sleep at night.
[SATSUKI]
Huh?
[YUZU] But it got lonely
being awake by myself,
so I asked Sister Bikuni
to stay up with me.
[BIKUNI] When the grandfather
clock strikes twelve,
that's when today ends
and tomorrow begins.
[YUZU] You know how you
go to bed one day,
and then when you
wake up in the morning
it's "tomorrow"?
[SATSUKI]
I think once you've woken up,
then the day is "today."
Exactly.
"Tomorrow" suddenly
becomes "today"
and we hardly ever notice.
So what?
I don't get it.
Where does tomorrow come from?
Is there someone whose job
it is to switch out the days?
[YUZU] I thought it was a
strange and impressive trick.
I felt like I had unlocked
a great mystery
and seen one of
our world's secrets.
On a night like tonight,
when the moon is full.
I feel like there's
another secret out there
just waiting to be revealed!
Sister Bikuni.
Isn't that the woman
who raised you?
She's a human, right?
Yeah.
She adopted me.
[SATSUKI]
So you're adopted.
[SATSUKI gasps]
Is something wrong?
You're kinda cutting off
the circulation in my hand.
No. Nothing's wrong.
Uh, you sure about that?
You're not afraid of ghosts
or anything are you?
No!
If you say so.
Stop being stupid. Come on.
[YUZU chuckles]
Is someone there?
[SATSUKI screams]
[YUZU screams]
[crashing noise]
[SATSUKI whimpering]
[YUZU]
Satsuki?
Ghosts?
I'm not afraid of them at all!
Not one bit!
[YUZU]
Aw. Poor thing. She's shaking.
It'll be okay.
[YUZU] Satsuki's always so
strong and commanding,
but she's got her fears, too.
No. Of course you're not.
And that's all right.
Are the two of you cuddling?
[SATSUKI]
It's not what you think!
Give me that!
[YUZU giggles]
Hey. Get up, Yuzu.
We've got guests to check on.
What the heck is so funny?
[YUZU giggles]
Oh, it's nothing much.
[YUZU]
I was right.
There was another secret.
On special nights,
when the moon is full,
who knows what you'll discover!
Hey. Have you guys seen Ren?
We got separated.
We haven't. Sorry.
[sighs] Not good.
She was so scared
she told me not to let go
of her hand, but uh...
[REN]
Remember, Natsume.
Don't you dare let go
of my hand, okay?
Yeah, sure.
And walk a little
bit slower, will you?
You're going too fast.
Okay.
[REN] I said slow down.
You didn't have to stop.
What is it?
[REN gasps]
Tell me.
Do you love me, Ren?
Whoa, do I love you?
Why on earth would you ask
me that here in the dark?
Well? Do you?
[REN] What's happening?
What's happening?
Wait! We can't!
We're working!
But I do kind of
like this feeling
of being a little naughty.
Why are her eyes
all glazed over?
Did she get food poisoning
from the miso mackerel
we had for dinner?
[whines] We ate fish!
And I haven't brushed
my teeth yet!
Ah! Her face is so close!
Her lips are just
inches from mine!
My heart's pounding.
Darn it, Ren, just go for it!
[REN]
I...
[REN laughs]
Um...
Sorry for making so much
noise and disturbing you.
[MASKED GUEST A]
It's fine. It gave me an idea.
[REN]
An idea?
She got me all worked
up and then ditched me?
Then again...
It's not like I'm disappointed
she didn't go through with it.
Well, maybe a little.
[OKIKU] Going around and
re-lighting these lanterns
one-by-one is such a pain.
--[footsteps]
--[URINOSUKE] Oink.
[OKIKU screams]
No! Not again!
--[URINOSUKE squealing]
--[OKIKU whimpers]
--[OKIKU screams]
[OKIKU]
Stay away from me!
It's better with the lights on.
Not that I was afraid
or anything like that.
I just don't care for it
when it's dark, that's all.
Kiri?
[KIRI (GHOST)]
Hm?
--[SATSUKI grunts]
--[KIRI (GHOST) grunts]
You're that ghost Natsume
mentioned, aren't you?
[GHOST A]
How'd you figure it out?
[SATSUKI]
Well, for one, you just told me.
But it's also not
like your disguise
was super convincing anyway.
You got gross, so I socked you.
[NATSUME]
What's going on?
Natsume, I found your ghost.
Let's catch it.
Yeah!
Catch me?
But I thought you
were afraid of me?
Well then joke's on you.
I'm not afraid--[coughs]
It's not ghosts I don't like.
What I hate is the dark.
--[SATSUKI, NATSUME scream]
--[NATSUME] Seriously?
Why would you tell an
enemy your weakness?
You're despicable!
How could you do this with
her after what you almost
did with me?
Uh... Ren, what are
you talking about?
[REN]
You're a two-timer!
We're all just notches
in your obi, aren't we?
[NATSUME]
Uh, no?
Obis don't have notches.
[KIRI]
What's all the commotion?
It's late. People are sleeping.
Try to keep it down.
--[KIRI] Huh?
--[KIRI (GHOST)] Huh?
What...?
Wait. How come
there are two Kiris?
One is real, but which is it?
We could both get
naked and compare.
The thought of strip
searching my own body
is mildly titillating.
That's our Kiri.
An egotistical pervert.
[SATSUKI]
Hurry! It's getting away!
Aw. It's late. Do we have to?
I mean, it's just
one little ghost.
Tis the season.
There's not much we can do.
Ghosts are seasonal?
That's in the fall.
This happened because you
were telling scary stories.
[OKIKU]
Help! Somebody stop her!
She's gonna make me bald!
Hold on. Where's Yuzu?
I don't know.
She just disappeared.
[YUZU]
Hey.
Where exactly are we going?
[SATSUKI (GHOST)]
Someplace happy.
You're coming with me, right?
I promise you'll like it.
Sure. I'll come see
your happy place.
But first, would you mind
telling me who you are?
How long have you known?
Did you realize I was an
imposter and came anyway?
Of course.
I'd never seen anyone
more in need of a friend.
I couldn't say "no."
[SATSUKI (GHOST)]
Were you really adopted?
[YUZU]
Yeah.
Sister Bikuni found me stuck
in the snow and took me in.
[SATSUKI (GHOST)] So you were
alone, and she saved you.
Do you think if I was her,
you could love me?
Or it doesn't have to be her.
I can be anyone, or change
in any way you want!
Tell me how to be
who you love, and I will.
Who do you love?
And what's the reason
you love them?
I don't know.
Do you have a reason?
Let me think.
[YUZU]
I hate him! I hate him!
Are you talking about Yohei?
He always makes fun
of me and calls me slow.
[YOHEI]
Well.
If it isn't Yuzu, Sister
Bikuni's little errand fox.
Or should I say errand snail.
Careful now.
Or your face might
freeze like that.
[laughs]
Such a rude old man.
He'd never talk to me like that
if I served the Inari shrine.
Yuzu.
Are you capable of reading
other people's minds?
Well, no.
Then explain to me
how it is you're so certain you
know what someone means.
You must start listening
not just to the words
people say, but also the
feelings behind them.
[YUZU]
Sorry, Sister Bikuni.
[YOHEI laughs]
Better hurry up there, Yuzu,
or one of these days
you'll get kicked out.
[YUZU]
That's crazy talk!
Sister Bikuni would
never just get rid of me!
[MAN A]
Good day, Sister.
The Inari shrine in
my village is a bit short
on manpower.
Or should I say "fox power"?
Do you think it would be
possible for young Yuzu
to go serve there?
Perhaps.
I will consider it.
So I was just about to
say to the young man--
Well, hey there, Yuzu.
You're working up a sweat.
Hmm... That's strange.
You see the look on her face?
Something seems off.
[BIKUNI]
Hmm.
[crashing noise]
What happened?
What was that crash?
[BIKUNI]
Yuzu!
I was trying to clean
the Buddha and it fell.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
Did you hurt yourself?
[YUZU]
I'm sorry, Sister Bikuni.
I promise I'll be more careful.
And I'll work even
harder from now on.
So please, let me stay.
Please don't make me leave you!
[crying]
Now, why would I make you leave?
I'm slow and always
messing things up.
So you're going to send me
away because I'm useless!
[crying]
Take a look outside, Yuzu.
Do you think the flowers on
that tree there are useless?
No.
Flowers are pretty and
they have a nice smell.
They can also soothe
a troubled mind.
Excellent, that's right.
But the flowers'
appearance and scent
isn't there for our sake.
The blossoms and
nectar attract insects
so the plants can propagate.
The flowers themselves have
no idea they ease our minds
and make us smile.
They're worth more
than they know.
This is too complicated.
I don't understand.
Perhaps you forgot
what you said.
Didn't you tell me that if
you served the Inari shrine,
no one would make fun of you?
[BIKUNI] I thought if serving
there would give you
more confidence,
it might be a good idea
for you to go.
However, I don't
think you're ready.
So as far as I'm concerned,
you are not going anywhere.
All right?
[crying]
[YUZU]
I love you, Sister Bikuni!
[crying]
[CHONMAGE] Past those hills,
there's a large town
along a trade route.
And high atop a mountain there
is a wonderful hot-spring hotel.
[BIKUNI] Are you perhaps
referring to Konohanatei?
Yes, I am indeed.
Do you know of it?
Actually, I know
the place's boss.
She happens to be an old friend.
I've only been there one time.
But wow. It was incredible.
Thank you, dear.
Is this that little
fox child you adopted
way back when?
[BIKUNI chuckles]
Yes.
She's grown up.
And she reminds me of the foxes
that work at Konohanatei.
They all looked to be
around the same age, too.
There are foxes there
the same age as me?
[CHONMAGE] During a conversation
with the Head Manager,
I said "It must be tough,
dealing with different guests
every day."
[KIRI] But all those guests
are what make it enjoyable.
Let's say it's been
years since your visit,
and you're tired or in pain,
yet you still think back
on your time here
like a wonderful dream.
That means Konohanatei
has become a part of you,
and will remain etched
in your heart forever.
If I can help you
make such a memory,
I consider it an honor.
And there's nothing
that makes me happier.
[CHONMAGE]
So she said.
[YUZU] Past those hills
and high atop a mountain.
Yuzu. Yuzu!
I'm sorry. I got distracted.
Could you please repeat that?
[BIKUNI] True knowledge is
not merely what you learn
from books or sitting
at a desk taking lessons.
It also comes from
going out into the world
and learning from others.
And you'd be able to
do that at Konohanatei.
You really mean it?
[YUZU]
I can go to Konohanatei?
You may.
Remember what I said
about the flower?
You are all those flowers.
You're worth more to me
than you will ever know.
That's why I'm sending
you out into the world.
[YUZU crying]
So you can bloom
even more beautifully.
[YUZU]
Oh, Sister Bikuni!
Whoa.
Was I just dreaming,
even though I'm standing up?
I've waited patiently.
Give me an answer.
Who is it that you love?
[YUZU]
Lots of people!
Sister Bikuni, the people
who came to the temple,
the guests and staff
at Konohanatei,
and everyone I've met
since I've worked there.
Had there been a
simple twist of fate,
I might never have gotten
the chance to meet
any of them.
But I did meet them, and
I'm so grateful that I did.
To me, it feels like a miracle.
And today, the person
I got to meet was you.
If only I'd gotten to meet
you a little earlier.
[YUZU]
Is that a boat?
Are you coming?
Next stop: The fields
of eternal happiness.
Yuzu.
If I didn't want to let go
of your hand right now,
would you come?
[YUZU] Sure. I'd cross
the river with you,
and then come back.
[SATSUKI (GHOST)] Sorry for
taking a peek at your memories.
[YUZU]
You did?
Yeah, a little.
I hope next time I can
be a flower like you.
Let's meet again, okay?
[YUZU]
Absolutely!
And with a smile like that, I'm
sure everyone will love you!
[YUZU]
You're perfect as you are.
You don't need to
be someone else.
[KIRI]
Oh. Really?
And that's why you didn't
come back till morning, huh.
[YUZU]
Uh-huh.
I gotta say, you have way
more guts than I thought.
How come you're not
afraid of ghosts?
Ghosts?
What do you mean?
Oh! Are you talking about
how she could shape shift?
Yeah. She was pretty
good at that, wasn't she?
[SATSUKI]
Uh, no.
That girl was dead.
She was a ghost.
An evil spirit. Get it?
Yeah. You had a
bit of a close call.
You know that river she
almost took you across?
Yes?
Well, that was the River Styx.
[YUZU] So, that's the
story of the lonely girl
and a slightly odd night I had
my first summer at Konohanatei.
[OKIKU]
The end.
[URINOSUKE]
Oink. Oink.