[NATSUME]
Brrr. My hands are so cold.
Oh, stop. We didn't even
have to draw that much water.
[REN] Who knew I'd still
be putting up with her
after so long.
So very long.
--Boo.
--[screams]
[YUBABA grunts]
[REN gasps]
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[YUBABA growls]
[NATSUME]
Pfft! [laughs]
[YUBABA]
Hmm?
Sorry to laugh, boss.
But your head's so big the
bucket won't even fit on!
Ah! Did you forget
who you're talking to?!
You two are gonna pay for that!
[NATSUME, REN]
Sorry, boss!
[sighs]
Dumb Natsume, and her pranks.
Though, come to think of it,
she's been surprising me
and scaring me like that,
ever since the day we first met.
[REN]
I can't take it anymore!
I'm so sick of Natsume.
Can't I work with Satsuki?
[KIRI] Hmm. I don't know
about that idea.
I'm not sure partnering
up my two best workers
would be quite fair.
[REN gasps]
Me? The best?
Oh. Thank you.
I do try to work hard.
But I never realized
I was one of the best.
You're right. It wouldn't
be fair to the others.
[KIRI]
Too easy.
[REN]
The best, me?
[KIRI] I could pair you up with
Yuzu for a bit, if you like.
[gasps]
No. Thank you.
I'll stick with Natsume.
'Kay.
[NATSUME]
Man. Today was exhausting.
[REN] Well, thanks to someone,
we started off the day
with a surprise run.
Oh, please, you were
laughing, too, Ren. Come on.
[REN]
I assure you, I wasn't.
Why were you running?
What happened?
It was so funny.
I scared Ren and
she screamed and--
[REN]
Don't blame it on me!
[NATSUME] Anyway, the
water bucket went flying
and landed right
on the boss's head!
--[YUZU laughs]
--[REN sighs]
[NATSUME]
Uh-oh. Careful, Yuzu.
Laugh too hard and
your butt might break open!
[YUZU gasps]
Really? Oh, no!
Don't pay any attention to her.
That's such an old joke.
[NATSUME]
I'm serious! Look!
--It's got a big crack in it!
--[REN] What an idiot.
--[YUZU screams]
--Ha! You're so adorable!
[REN] Natsume, always
acting like a moron.
--[leaves rustles]
--[gasps]
Hello? Is someone there?
Stay back! Go away!
But you're a complete mess.
You can't go home like that.
[REN]
Oh! She's a girl.
She was so tall and skinny,
and her arms and
legs were so long.
Honestly, she could
have been either.
--Turn around, 'kay?
--[REN sighs]
Go on. I'll get your
back cleaned up.
[REN sighs]
[NATSUME]
Stay still. All right?
[REN sighs]
Let me guess, a boy bullied you
and beat you up, didn't he?
[REN gasps]
[REN]
She was like a magical nymph.
More beautiful than any other
creature I'd ever seen.
[NATSUME snores]
[REN]
Then again,
first impressions are
sometimes deceiving.
[GIRLS]
Goodbye. Safe travels.
We hope you enjoyed your stay.
May I fix your obi?
--Sure.
--[KIRI] Natsume! I need you!
--Coming.
--It's coming undone,
and we can't have that.
Oh. I'm sorry, Ren.
I was just in a hurry.
Even so, when you're
in front of the guests,
you mustn't appear unkempt.
[REN]
There. You're all set.
[YUZU] Thank you.
It's nice of you to help me.
You're so considerate.
[REN gasps]
[REN] Really, Yuzu,
I'm not being considerate.
It's something anyone would do.
Oh, wow!
So this is the kind
of modesty it takes
to be a refined lady! I get it!
[REN]
No, you don't!
Just be more careful
from now on, okay?
[YUZU]
Okay.
Great. See ya!
I'm gonna go rake some leaves.
[REN] Naive, little,
sparkly-eyed Yuzu!
I hate your stupid face!
Stop looking at the world
through rose-colored glasses!
Not everybody you meet
is sweet and kind
and wants to be your friend!
Someday, somebody is going
to take advantage of you,
and then you're gonna cry!
[sighs]
Don't get
the wrong idea, Sakura.
[SAKURA]
Shh.
Found you! Found you, Sakura!
You can't hide from us!
Found you! Found you!
I've been found.
[BIRD A]
Okay. This time, you're it.
You count and we'll hide.
--1, 2, 3, 4...
--[BIRD A] Hurry! Hide!
...5, 6, 7, 8, 9...
More saké over here! We're dry!
Be patient, please.
Some more will be out very soon.
Send some here, too!
[YUZU]
Yes, sir. Right away!
I don't know you.
Are you new here?
Yes. And, my name is Yuzu.
[GUEST B chuckles]
Well aren't you adorable.
[REN]
Coming through.
[GUEST C]
Hey, you! Cutie!
Get me some saké, too.
[REN] Sorry, sir.
But I'm bussing tonight.
One of the others will help you.
I don't want
one of the other girls.
I want you!
[REN whimpers]
--[GUEST C chuckles]
--That looks heavy.
I'll take it.
You go make more hot saké.
Oh, sure. Excuse me.
[GUEST C chuckles]
[REN gasps]
--[REN screams]
--[GUEST C yells]
--Ren!
--[GUESTS gasping]
--[YUZU] Ren! Stop!
--He's the one who started it!
--What are you doing?!
--Let go of me, Yuzu!
[REN]
Oh, no! I struck a guest!
What have I done?
How dare you--
Pardon me...
...but this is Konohanatei.
A reputable establishment
you seem to have confused
for a brothel.
I think you may have
had a bit too much saké.
We will arrange for a car
to escort you home.
Please leave quietly
and go sleep it off.
[REN gasps]
[GUEST C yelps]
This is outrageous!
How dare you be so impertinent!
You're the boss!
Make her serve me!
Inappropriate conduct
will not be tolerated.
Please leave quietly,
as she requested.
Otherwise, I shall be forced
to bar your entire party
from ever returning to
Konohanatei again.
The decision is yours, sir.
Barred from here forever?
[GUESTS]
Leave! Right now!
[gasps]
[KIRI] Don't let the door hit
you on the way out.
Goodbye!
[GUEST C yells]
[REN] I dislike
drunk men to begin with,
but no matter how rude he was
I shouldn't have made a scene.
Don't let it bother you, Ren.
He deserved it.
He was in the wrong.
[YUZU gasps]
Um... Hello,
Ladies and Gentlemen.
I'm Yuzu, and I would like to
dance for your enjoyment!
[REN gasps]
Sure! You can dance for us!
Good idea! I'll come dance, too!
Excellent! Let's get everyone
back in a party mood!
[NATSUME, YUZU]
Dance. Dance.
Dance, dance, dance, dance!
[KIRI]
Looks like fun. Wanna join them?
[gasps] No. Dancing for
the guests is beneath me.
In other words, you're
saying you've got two left feet.
[gasps]
No single person
can handle it all.
If each of us could
do everything ourselves.
We wouldn't ever
need to ask for help,
and we wouldn't have
friends to help us.
Now, then. I think
I'll pour some saké.
[REN whimpers]
There, there, Ren.
He's gone now.
You're okay. You're okay.
[gasps]
[NATSUME]
There, now. All clean.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You scared me, ya know that?
[NATSUME]
When I first saw you,
I thought you were the
prettiest girl I'd ever seen.
I thought you were a
fairy, and might cast a spell.
[REN] You said almost the
same thing I'd been thinking,
so I couldn't say it back.
But somehow, I didn't need to.
I knew I wanted
you to notice me,
and as long as I was beautiful,
you always would.
Thanks again, Natsume.
I should thank Yuzu,
too, for dancing.
And try to give tonight's
guests my happiest,
most heartfelt send
off just like she does.
[REN] I should also thank the
boss and the others for having
my back, and getting
things done when I was upset.
I'll get up early tomorrow
and do extra cleaning.
As for you.
When you open your eyes,
I hope I'll be even
more beautiful than
when you closed them.
[REN]
Absolutely not!
No! I refuse to sit and watch
while practically naked men
grapple with each other.
Picturing such brutishness
makes me shiver.
That's a pretty
narrow-minded view.
[SATSUKI]
What's narrow-minded?
What are you talking about?
Hey, Satsuki!
You want to go to the
sumo match with me tomorrow?
[gasps]
[SATSUKI] No way. I see
your ugly mug enough at work.
Why would I want
to see it on my day off?
[NATSUME]
Uh, ouch. Come on.
[REN] Well, at least I don't
have to worry about anything
ever happening between
Natsume and Satsuki.
They fight like they're sisters.
I'd be happy to spend
my day off with Natsume,
if we were shopping
or something.
[KIRI] Ren! There you are.
Hurry up! We have guests.
Coming, Kiri.
I'm Ren and I'll be
taking care of you.
Welcome to Konohanatei.
It's been quite a while
since we've been
to a hot spring, hasn't it?
Oh, my, yes. I'd say
a hundred years at least.
[REN]
What a cute little old couple.
Oh? Is that your grandchild
over there, all in blue?
[GRANDPA A]
Indeed it is. That's Aoi.
One of our great,
great grandchildren.
[GRANDMA A] No, dear,
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
Aoi is one of our great, great,
great, great grandchildren.
Aoi came along to keep
the two of us company.
Such a sweet child.
[REN]
How precious. I'll get her.
[NATSUME, SUMO GUY grunting]
[NATSUME yells]
[AOI gasps]
[REN]
Natsume!
If it's all right.
Can Natsume be the one
who takes care of me?
Please, Grandmother?
[REN]
That brat!
[GRANDPA A] The view here is
absolutely stunning.
[GRANDMA A]
It certainly is.
[GRANDPA A]
I'm so happy we came.
[REN] Konohanatei
gets mostly older guests.
I can't believe I let
my guard down.
If a cute girl like that
liked Natsume,
would she like her back?
[NATSUME]
Don't worry Aoi.
You'll be bigger
before you know it.
[REN] Bigger? Why do you
care about getting big?
[REN coughs]
You seem to be having fun.
What are you talking about?
[REN] She's not even
going to talk to me?
By the way, Natsume.
Who were you
fighting with earlier?
It was sumo wrestling.
Not a fight.
Whatever it was.
That's not the point.
[REN]
What if that man was a guest?
What if you'd injured him?
You shouldn't be
so rough with people.
But, Natsume is awesome, though.
So strong and fast.
Really?
You flipped that huge guy like
he barely weighed
anything at all.
I think you're totally amazing.
Aw, shucks. You'll embarrass me.
[laughs]
About tomorrow-- Hey, Ren!
Guess she must not
have heard me.
Can we go to town?
Tomorrow. If you don't
already have any plans,
would you take me somewhere?
[REN gasps]
Yeah, sure.
Tomorrow's my day off.
[REN]
They're going out?
Just the two of them alone?
[REN]
Do something, Kiri!
That guest is taking up
far too much of Natsume's time.
No work is getting done!
You mean your work?
No, Natsume's!
[KIRI]
Even so...
[GRANDPA A]
My joints are sore.
[KIRI] A young person
probably would get bored
just sitting in the hot
spring with an old couple.
Yeah, I see
your point, but still.
You're not actually
worried about Natsume's work,
are you, Ren?
Try being a little
more honest next time.
[NATSUME] All right. I'm gonna
take Aoi to town for the day.
[laughs]
Goodbye, Grandmother!
Goodbye, Grandfather!
Be good, Aoi, and don't
you give Natsume
any trouble now.
Bye, Ren. See ya later!
[REN]
Hmph.
Oh?
[REN]
Why did I do that? I'm terrible.
[YUZU]
Ren? Are you okay?
[REN]
Hm?
You're not smiling
and seem kinda down.
I haven't the faintest
idea what you mean.
If there's anything
bothering you,
you know you can
talk to me about it.
[REN sighs]
[REN] Yuzu's the
last person I'd go to,
but I've gotta tell someone.
Um, my friend...
She's got a problem,
and it's really bothering her.
[YUZU] So it's not your problem,
it's your friend's?
[REN] You see, she's
got this old friend that
she's been really close
to since they were little.
But now there's this new
girl that just came along,
and she completely
adores the old friend.
The old friend
and this new girl talk
and hang out together.
That's all, but my friend
is beginning to feel
really jealous of the new girl.
She feels guilty for
resenting the new girl, though.
So I told her to
stop and get over it.
[YUZU] Are you sure your friend
actually resents this new girl?
What if what she's
feeling isn't guilt?
What if she's actually sad?
[gasps]
Um... Well, you see...
Let me explain with this
yummy steamed bun
that I've been saving.
[REN]
What?
[YUZU] It's my last one,
and I'm really looking forward
to eating it.
[YUZU] But what if somebody
came and stole that bun?
[YUZU gasps]
You're mean, Sakura!
[YUZU] Anyone would be
upset by that. Even me.
I might be angry for a
second or two at the person
who took the bun and ate it.
But the thing is, I wanted
to eat the steamed bun.
So I'd be more sad
and disappointed
that I couldn't have it.
Then, if it were you,
you'd be sad?
I would. Very sad.
So instead of scolding your
friend and making her feel worse
for resenting the new girl,
I think maybe it's better
to comfort her and support her,
so she won't feel so sad about
something she can't control.
[gasps]
Are you crying?
Oh, no! I'm sorry, Ren!
Please forgive me!
I didn't mean to make you cry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Should I not have said that?
Was it a bad story?
[REN] You're really frustrating,
you know that?
[YUZU]
Eh?
[REN] Stop saying
"sorry" all the time.
[YUZU]
Hm?
Still, thank you.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[REN]
She's nice. Weird, but nice.
Maybe your friend should
tell her old friend how
she really feels and not keep
her emotions so bottled up.
What do you mean,
"how she really feels"?
Oh, like she's sad, ya know?
And, maybe that she's feeling
left out and could use
some more attention?
[REN gasps]
Have you gone
completely insane, Yuzu?!
That would come off as
totally needy and annoying!
But Ren, Natsume would
never be annoyed with you.
[YUZU gasps]
[blows landing]
[YUZU whimpers]
I'm sorry.
[REN] I should've known
that wouldn't work.
[REN]
"How I really feel," huh?
We'll see.
[REN] Natsume's already
back from town?
[REN]
Hey, Natsume, it's Ren.
[NATSUME]
Good. Harder. Harder!
Could I maybe talk to you?
[AOI] You mean like this?
Is this better?
[REN gasps]
[screams]
Get away!
Natsume's mine!
Hands off, Aoi!
[REN]
What? The little brat is a boy?!
[screams]
Please! Look away!
Ren. It's not polite to stare.
Me? I'm the impolite one?
What? What is going on?
[NATSUME] Aoi wants to become
a great sumo wrestler someday.
That's his dream.
I'd half given up.
I thought I was too small.
But then I saw Natsume,
and I realized it
wasn't hopeless.
Even someone as skinny
as me had at least a chance.
Natsume's been so encouraging.
He's like the big brother
I never had.
So please, Natsume, teach me.
I know I can do it
if you're my coach.
[REN]
Uh, hang on.
Before this goes any further,
let's go over a few details.
[AOI]
Huh?
First off, Natsume is
actually a girl.
Oh... What...?!
And I'm not sumo coach.
That's the main reason I agreed
to take you into town, Aoi.
So you could meet and talk
to a real sumo wrestler.
[REN sighs]
Get it, now?
[gasps]
Oh. I misunderstood.
Sorry. Also, I've never really
talked to any girls before.
[REN]
So he wasn't ignoring me either.
He's just shy.
That's a relief.
Serves me right for
getting ahead of myself.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
[NATSUME]
I got ya a little something.
This is the comb
you wanted, right?
I tried to
double check with you
yesterday before you left.
But you didn't seem
to be able to hear me.
[sighs]
Sorry about that.
Thanks, Natsume.
[AOI sighs]
[NATSUME]
Ah. There's the smile.
[REN]
Ah?
I haven't seen it
since yesterday.
You've been so down.
You were in a bad
mood this morning, too.
When we were leaving, you
wouldn't look me in the eye.
I'm sorry.
I mean, hey.
Not liking sumo wrestling is one
thing, but we are still friends.
Ah?
Please join me next time.
I was sad not seeing your face.
[gasps]
[YUZU] Maybe your friend,
should tell her old friend
how she really feels.
[REN]
Hey.
[gasps]
I was lonely.
I missed you, too.
Ah. Really? It wasn't just me?
[REN]
Mm.
[NATSUME]
See ya in a bit.
I'm gonna go take a bath.
[REN]
Honestly, Yuzu.
Again with your obi.
You're greeting our guests!
[YUZU]
Sorry. I'll keep trying.
I'm pretty sure none
of our guests would notice
one loose obi.
Nope. You're wrong.
Girls must be beautiful. Always.
[YUZU whimpers]
Sure. Whatever you say.
[REN]
Hey, Yuzu.
[gasps]
Thanks for today.
Ah?
What?
Never mind. Forget it.
Now come on.
Turn around and face front.
[YUZU whimpers]
[SATSUKI]
Idiot.
[YUZU]
I'm very sorry.
[NATSUME]
Aoi? Whatcha doin'?
[gasps]
[AOI] Ren is a really pretty
young woman, isn't she?
And once you get
to know her a little bit,
she's sweet and good-natured.
And wonderful, and perfect.
And not for you.
And not for... me?!
Ren isn't for you.
Why not, Natsume?
Is she already dating
someone else?
You think she won't like me?
[NATSUME]
Oh, no, particular reason.
She's just not.
Because I said so.