[HIIRAGI]
"Dear Satsuki.
I was happy to see you
at the celebration of
the sacred Cherry Blossom
Tree the other day.
I'm glad you haven't given up on
your dream of serving the gods.
Please, Sister."
[growls]
[bells ringing]
[YUZU screams]
[gasps]
[NATSUME snoring]
[snoring continues]
[REN sighs]
[REN screams]
Who's hurt? What's going on?
[REN]
Natsume! Why?! How?!
You sick pervert!
What have you done to me?!
I'm a pervert? Why?
What do you think I did?
Come on! It's too
early for this!
[REN]
This is all your fault, Natsume!
[gasping]
The two of us sleep in
the same room every night!
So who else's child
could it possibly be?
[SATSUKI]
Wait! Explain your logic!
Well. I'll take responsibility.
You will?! Do you even
know how babies are made?
[REN gasps]
--It's...
--...an...
...egg?
[NATSUME grunting]
Get it off. Get it off!
[NATSUME groanin]
What do you think
could be in there?
[NATSUME] If we let
it hatch, we'll find out.
Regardless, you can't
work with it attached to you.
What? You can't be serious!
[SATSUKI] You're gonna
help guests with an egg
stuck to your stomach?
[REN] So I'm just supposed
to lay around all day
and do nothing but incubate
this mystery egg?
Hang in there, Ren.
It'll probably come off soon.
Just rest up, and don't worry
about it hatching, okay?
Whatever's in there
grew inside of you.
So it's ours, and we'll
raise it together.
[gasps]
[KIRI] Really? Ren is
taking the day off?
Yeah. She's in bed
with a stomach ache.
[SATSUKI] Ugh. I hate
how she lies so easily.
Poor Ren must be miserable.
I'm gonna work
real hard today to help Ren.
And help her egg baby, too.
Great. But don't repeat
that to anyone else.
Oh. Satsuki!
Come over here a second!
[SATSUKI]
Hmm?
This guest wanted
to talk to you.
He says he saw you
at the celebration
back when the
sacred tree bloomed.
[SATSUKI]
Mm. Oh. He did?
Well, I thought one
of the priestesses who danced
was simply spectacular.
Someone told me
her name was Hiiragi
and that you might know her.
[NATSUME] Oh, of course
Satsuki knows Hiiragi.
That's her older sister--
[grunts]
[GUEST A whimpers]
--Please excuse me.
--Are you all right?!
Why'd she do that?!
What I say?
[chuckles] When it comes to
Satsuki and her older sister...
Let's just say it's complicated.
[NATSUME]
Mm.
[heartbeats]
Where am I?
Who are you?
Oh. It's you.
Why are you dressed
like that, Natsume?
You look silly.
[NATSUME]
It's over, Ren. We're through.
[gasps]
[NATSUME] I never told you,
but I'm a prince from the stars!
And sadly, I can no longer
remain here on Earth!
[REN gasps]
Farewell, Ren. Bye.
[REN]
No, wait! Come back!
I promise I'll eat
all your carrots for you,
since you hate them.
And I'll stop getting mad at
you when you wake me up.
I swear.
Just please don't go!
[REN whimpers]
[NATSUME]
Don't cry.
[REN]
Huh...?
Hey. I'm right here.
[NATSUME]
Ren!
[REN]
Ah?
Wake up, Ren! You okay?
You were having a nightmare.
[REN yelps]
[YUZU gasps]
Hey, look! The egg fell off!
How ya feelin'? Anything new?
[SATSUKI grunts]
[SATSUKI screams]
What? Why's it stuck to me now?
Damnit! Why won't it come off?
Take a nap!
It came off Ren after
she'd been asleep for a while.
[SATSUKI] Don't be stupid!
I can't take a nap.
I've got work to do.
Enough of this nonsense!
[YUZU]
Wait! Stop!
When you're with child,
you need to rest
and be good to yourself.
Yeah, Satsuki.
That body's not just
yours anymore, ya know.
Knock it off! I'll do
whatever the hell I want!
What's going on?
It's awfully noisy in here.
[KIRI]
I see.
Well then. Get some sleep
and we'll see what happens.
[SATSUKI]
Ah.
[KIRI] You're taking
the night off, Satsuki.
No arguments.
[SATSUKI sighs]
And, uh, be sure
to let me know
when you go into labor, 'kay?
[SATSUKI]
Don't say things like that!
[NATSUME]
Hey, Ren?
[SATSUKI] Why did this
have to happen to me?
[REN]
That goes to the Akebono room.
[YUZU]
It can't be the Akebono room.
I just brought them food.
[NATSUME] Well, who
the heck's it for, then?
--[crashing]
--[GIRLS screaming]
[SATSUKI]
I'm never gonna get any sleep.
[REN] What happened now?
There's food all over the place!
[NATSUME]
Slow down! I've already got one!
Okay, egg.
What the heck are you and
why are you really here?
[KIRI]
Are you okay?
[NATSUME]
Oww...
[HIIRAGI]
Satsuki.
[SATSUKI]
Hm?
Look. It's my new kimono.
Am I pretty?
[SATSUKI]
How could you not be?
You're beautiful
no matter what you wear.
Everyone looks at you like
you're a flower in bloom.
[SATSUKI'S DAD] We'll send
Hiiragi to work at Konohanatei.
[SATSUKI'S MOM]
But dear, she's the eldest,
and she has so many gifts.
Everyone expects her
to become a priestess.
[SATSUKI'S DAD]
You're right.
Satsuki should go to
Konohanatei instead.
Satsuki. What do you think?
Um. If that's what you want.
[SATSUKI]
It didn't matter what I wanted.
They wanted my sister
to be the priestess.
So I agreed.
[HIIRAGI]
You just agreed?
You gave up your spot
without saying a word?
You didn't object or protest?
And now you're blaming me?
[SATSUKI]
No.
What anybody else
wants doesn't matter.
[SATSUKI] But if I'd
said no, that wouldn't
have changed anything.
All it would've done is
hurt you or our parents.
But what about you,
Satsuki? How do you feel?
I could never bring
myself to actually say it.
I thought it would be selfish.
But if it didn't really matter
which one of us it was.
If it didn't matter who...
...then why couldn't
I have been the priestess?
[SATSUKI]
What the...?
[YUZU]
But who went to the shrine
and who to the hotel did matter.
[SATSUKI gasps]
You had to be the one, Satsuki.
You... We needed you.
Konohanatei needed you.
It couldn't have
been anyone else.
[YUZU] You ended up
where you needed to be.
[SATSUKI whimpers]
[YUZU]
Satsuki.
Satsuki! Satsuki!
[gasps]
Are you all right, Satsuki?
You were having a bad nightmare.
Yuzu.
It's okay. I'm fine.
It was only a dream.
[YUZU gasps]
The egg's hatching!
[SATSUKI]
Now what?
[PIG squeals]
Okay.
Do you think
it's some kind of pig?
It can't be a
pig. It's all fuzzy.
Yeah, like a winter melon.
So we should call this
little guy Urinosuke.
I'm just glad he's
hatched and it's all over.
So it's back to work with you!
[gasps]
[NATSUME]
Thank heavens!
Practically nothing gets done
without you around, Satsuki.
Kiri's completely useless.
[KIRI]
Excuse me, I'm what now?
[NATSUME]
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[gasps]
[HIIRAGI] "Don't be afraid
to visit here more often.
Come say hello.
And bring your
friends from the hotel.
I'd like to meet them.
Hope to see you soon.
Hiiragi."
[SATSUKI]
Hm.
By the way, I meant to ask.
You were having a bad dream
right before he hatched,
--weren't you?
--Uh-huh.
Or at least I think it started
that way, but I can't remember.
I only remember the
good dream it turned into.
Same for me.
I can't remember the bad
part of my dream either.
Really? That's good.
Nightmares and bad dreams
are better off forgotten.
So, what was the good
part of your dream about?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
I don't remember.
Huh? But you just said--
[SATSUKI]
Drop it! I said I forgot!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Speaking of nightmares and such.
Isn't there some sort of
beast god that's supposed
to eat bad dreams?
[YUZU]
What was it called again?
I used to know.
[SATSUKI]
Ya got me.
[URINOSUKE squeals]
[YUZU]
Good morning!
--I'm back and I got everything.
--[BABY wailing]
Yuzu! Thank
goodness you're here!
You have to make
this baby stop crying.
[gasps]
[REN]
Whose could it be?
I don't remember any
guests with babies.
[SATSUKI] And we
don't have any right now
young enough to be the mother.
[URINOSUKE snorts]
[YUZU]
No, Urinosuke! Get down.
Looks like he's
not interested in
the baby after all.
There he goes, running
around like he owns the place.
It's good that he's settled in.
And it's not like the boss
has complained about him.
[crying stops]
Someone gave me a steamed bun
while I was shopping earlier.
I thought the baby could eat it,
since it has teeth.
Perfect! Let's find the mother
quick while it's not crying.
Wha..
[YUZU] Ma'am? I bought the
thread and fabric you asked for.
Wow. That's such
a beautiful kimono.
It's for a little
three-year-old girl's
Shichi-Go-San celebration.
I hope that my Shino
will like it.
[YUZU] Shino? I wonder if
that's her granddaughter.
Do you know where
this tradition came from?
You see, long ago, children
were said to belong to the gods
until they were seven.
Not their own parents?
[OLD WOMAN] No. They
wouldn't even become human
unless they survived
for seven years.
Shichi-Go-San celebrates
their reaching that milestone.
That's beautiful.
And I'm sure Shino
will love her new kimono.
[YUZU gasps]
Satsuki! Where's the baby?
What happened to it?
I took my eyes off it
for a second and it disappeared.
[YUZU]
What?
I'm pretty certain
its mother probably just
found it and took it back.
Seems possible.
I hope you're right.
Hey. Did something
just walk behind me?
[BOTH gasp]
[GIRL gasps]
[SATSUKI yells]
Aw. First a baby, and now a kid?
Wait! I think I know who she is!
[SATSUKI]
Huh?
[YUZU]
I recognize that kimono.
This little girl must be Shino.
Her grandmother's staying here.
I was just in her room,
talking to her.
That's a relief. Nice job.
Let's get her
back to her granny.
[grunts]
[SATSUKI]
Damn it. Today is cursed.
Are you my Mommy?
Since I don't remember
giving birth to you,
I'd say "no."
[SHINO whimpers]
Satsuki! She's a little
girl, don't make her cry.
Honestly.
[SATSUKI]
Hey! I didn't do anything!
Shino, ready to come out?
[YUZU screams]
[yelps]
[YUZU]
Merlion!
[SHINO laughs]
Oh. Look at that.
She's laughing.
[SATSUKI laughs]
You can wear this yukata
until your kimono's dry.
[gasps]
Hee!
Wait! Shino!
Bye-bye!
Don't you wave and run off.
Dammit. This kid
is such a handful.
[YUZU] The way Satsuki
smiles when she laughs.
It makes her look so adorable.
[SATSUKI] Hmm? What are
you grinning about?
Something funny?
[YUZU]
No. Nothing like that.
My Shino, there you are.
But where did you leave
your kimono, dear?
Whatever am I
going to do with you?
Ah. What a nice day.
[NATSUME]
What are you doing up there?
[whimpers]
Oh. I see.
Your ball's stuck there
on that high branch.
[NATSUME grunts]
You shouldn't go
around climbing trees,
little one.
[sighs]
You're going to
get that pretty kimono
of yours all dirty.
Um... Okay.
And...
Big Brother.
Thanks for your help.
But... I'm a "Big Sister."
[OLD WOMAN] Goodness.
What's the matter, Shino?
You're all red.
Are you in a hurry
to grow up that fast?
[chuckles]
Of course you are.
Don't worry, my dear.
I'll make you a
lovely furisode next.
It won't be long before you're
a beautiful young lady.
[sobbing]
[REN] What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
My mother made me a furisode
because I'll be grown up soon.
That's great!
It looks so pretty.
No, it's not.
My mother's fashion
sense is ancient!
I can't go around wearing this!
[gasps]
[REN]
There.
That's a bit
better now, isn't it?
Don't just cry and complain.
You can come up with
a style all your own.
Thank you.
Do you think if I keep working
at it, I can be pretty like you?
Wait! What are
you talking about?
You... You're already
a pretty girl.
Maybe not as
pretty as me, but...
[NATSUME]
Ren! Have you seen my pajamas?
I can't find them.
You mean the ones
you tossed on the floor
and forgot about?
Yes. I washed them for you,
since I knew you wouldn't.
[NATSUME]
Ah! Thank you, Ren!
I love ya! You're the best!
Man. What's wrong with you?
Other people are watching us!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[REN]
What happened? She's gone.
Who was that girl?
I've got no idea.
She prob'ly came with
one of the guests.
[NATSUME]
Maybe that was her older sister.
[URINOSUKE squeals]
[YUZU]
Excuse me, ma'am.
It's Yuzu again.
I brought you more
pretty fabric and thread.
Come in, Big Sister.
Please sit down.
Ah?
[OLD WOMAN]
Sorry it's such a mess.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll make some tea.
Uh, ma'am.
I'm not--
Are you planning on
making another new kimono?
[OLD WOMAN]
Yes, Mother.
And I know; I just made one.
But Shino keeps
growing so fast,
as soon as I finish them,
they're already too small.
[KIRI chuckles] She must be
going through her growth spurt.
[OLD WOMAN]
Beyond that, it seems she has
fallen in love, as well.
Oh, but don't tell
Jirou someone's stolen
his little girl's heart.
That man is attached
to his children.
He loves them so.
I can't imagine he'd
ever give her away.
He'd try to keep you.
Right, Shino?
[gasps]
[OLD WOMAN] So, for now, I think
it's best we keep it a secret.
[YUZU gasps]
[KIRI]
We'll be back later.
Yuzu.
You were raised, at least in
part, by humans, weren't you?
I was.
[KIRI] Then perhaps you've
heard about an old custom.
A mother, whose daughter
has died young, keeps a doll.
And she dresses it in
wedding clothes the way
she would have her child.
She does this so
her daughter might marry
in the afterlife.
Now, then.
What do you think
of this custom?
[YUZU sighs]
Do you think that
lady is wasting a lot
of time and energy on ghosts?
Do you feel sorry for her?
I think... if she wants
to see things a certain way,
then the world she
sees is real for her.
And besides.
Our guests are our gods.
It's not my place to judge.
[KIRI]
Hm.
[chuckles
[SHINO sighs]
[KIRI]
Is anything the matter?
Because you don't look happy.
There you are, you tanuki.
Except, I am not
a tanuki. I'm a fox.
Whatever you are. I don't care!
You've been lying to
my mother. Now stop it!
[KIRI] You seem to be in a
rebellious phase, Shino.
You couldn't have chosen a more
difficult age for a human to be.
You're keeping her here.
When are you going to set
her free from this place?
[KIRI groans]
[KIRI]
Your mother is a guest.
She came to Konohanatei and
walked through the front door
of her own free will.
I cannot simply kick her out.
Relax, Shino.
Why don't you try to
enjoy your time here, too?
You may like it.
[SHINO]
How am I supposed to do that?!
All of this is nothing
but a cruel dream!
And when my mother wakes up,
she'll be even more miserable!
[KIRI] There's something
you don't realize.
[GASPS]
The fleeting dreams one
has at Kononhanatei
can easily comprise the
entirety of a human life.
And they've become as real
to us foxes as they are
to your mother.
If she says "Oh, my!
What a lovely dream!"
Isn't that good enough?
Or, at the very least, if
she doesn't mind it's a dream,
isn't that all that matters?
[SHINO WHIMPERS] You're right.
She should be happy.
Please don't tell
anyone what I said.
[SHINO] I can't seem
to stop making mistakes
and embarrassing myself in front
of everybody who works here.
But, Shino, that's
what growing up is,
and no one ever
said it was easy.
You make mistakes.
You regret all kinds of things.
But you learn from it all,
and you grow.
You grow until you
become a beautiful woman.
Wow. She's such a pretty bride.
I don't remember her.
What room's she in?
[YUZU]
The Kasumi room.
With her mother.
[SAKURA grunts]
[gasping]
No harm done.
Are you sure you're all right?
Why, thank you.
Aww!
Her mother finished her
wedding kimono this morning.
She said it was the last one.
What a fine and lovely day.
The Spring sky is fresh
and perfectly clear.
Just like the day you were born,
my darling daughter.
You look so beautiful...
...Shino.
Ever since I was
a baby, you said that
I belonged to the gods.
But I'm not theirs.
I've always been your daughter.
My life has been...
rich and full,
like a wonderful dream.
Thank you, Mother.
I love you.
[OLD WOMAN] I don't think I
can ever thank you enough.
All of you took such good care
of me and made me feel
so happy during my stay.
Truly, it was just like a dream.
Except that it wasn't a dream.
[OLD WOMAN]
Hmm?
[KIRI] From now on, you'll
always be with your daughter.
You'll never have to
say "goodbye" again.
The two of you will
be together for a long time.
Much longer than you were apart.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Finally...
I'm so happy... What a
truly miraculous day...
[YUZU]
Ma'am? It's me again.
I brought your lunch.
I'm afraid you're too late.
Our guest has already left.
She has gone to go
be with her daughter.
Without eating first?
She must have been
in a terribly big hurry.
[chuckles]
I'm disappointed
I couldn't see her off.
She was so nice.
Before she went, she did
want to thank all of us.
She said everyone
took good care of her and
the past few days
were like a dream.
[gasps]
[KIRI] Now, then, we've got
another banquet tonight.
It's going to be
a big job, Yuzu.
You ready?
[YUZU]
Yeah!