[CROWD murmuring]
[YUZU gasps]
There are so many people!
[BIKUNI]
Yuzu.
[YUZU sighs]
--[BIKUNI] Yuzu!
--[gasps]
Careful not to
get too distracted.
I don't want you
getting lost, okay?
Right. Sorry. I'll stick close.
[MALE MOUSE A]
Coming through!
Everybody out of the way, unless
you want to be seriously hurt!
[MALE MOUSE B]
Move it, missy!
[YUZU]
Oh. Pardon me. Sorry.
[MALE MOUSE A]
Hmph!
This being your
first time in the city,
you must be so curious
about everything.
[YUZU]
Uh-huh!
[YUZU] The cherry blossoms
here are so beautiful.
Look ahead, Yuzu.
You can see it.
We're almost there.
[YUZU gasps]
[gasps]
This is it.
The hotel and hot spring
where you'll be working
starting today. Konohanatei.
[YUBABA]
So... Is this her?
Little fox kid that you
said wants a job here?
Yes.
[YUZU coughs]
Well. She doesn't
look like much.
but since you and I have
known each other a while.
I'll take her on.
--Kiri.
--[KIRI] Yes, boss? I'm here.
[YUBABA]
This is our head manager, Kiri.
She'll teach you how
we do things here.
[gasps] I'm pleased
to meet you, Miss Kiri.
I look forward to
working with you.
[KIRI giggles]
[YUZU whimpers]
[YUZU gasps]
[KIRI] All right! That's
enough sentimentality.
Time to get to work.
Natsume! Satuski!
She's here. Yay!
Girls. This is Yuzu.
Let's get her started.
You heard her, Natsume.
Go on and get the
new girl all cleaned up.
[groans]
That's just Satsuki for ya.
Don't take it personally.
You'll get used to it.
[YUZU]
So pretty.
She reminds me of Sister Bikuni.
[NATSUME]
Okay, clothes off.
[gasps]
[screams
Come on. Don't be so shy.
[YUZU]
Really. I can wash myself!
[KIRI] Oh, my. Such
big breasts for a small girl.
[NATSUME] Hold still.
Or this will take a lot longer.
[YUZU]
What are you scrubbing me with?
--Is that a rock? [squeals]
--[NATSUME] Stop squirming!
It's just a pumice stone.
--I really want to get out now!
[REN] Morons.
[KIRI]
Next, we'll get you dressed.
[REN] I've prepared some
kimonos for her that I think
will go well with
her hair and eyes.
You're really on
task, Ren. Excellent.
[YUZU]
Look at her! She's so cute!
And you can call me Ren.
Good to be working with you.
Why, thank you.
Good to be working
with you, too.
Though it's only
been a few seconds.
[REN]
Ah--
Is she serious?
Does she really not understand
a turn of phrase?
I was just being polite!
What's wrong with you,
you silly fox?
Thank you, Ren.
You can get back to
your usual work, now.
--[YUZU wails]
--[REN] Yes, Kiri.
She has to be slow or something.
[YUZU]
There's more?
[KIRI]
Hush now. Just come with me.
Take a look out there, Yuzu.
After the shrine to the
gods, Konohanatei is
the second highest point
in the entire city.
So what you see is
a rare privilege
we're very lucky to have.
[YUZU gasps]
It's amazing!
The city's so big,
and there are so many
people down there.
I've never seen
anything like it.
[KIRI] You and Sister Bikuni
always lived way out
on your own, didn't you?
Yes..
Heh.
And now that that's over with.
You'll be partnered up
with Satuski here
till you know the ropes.
Happy working, ladies!
[SATSUKI]
Hold on.
Shouldn't she be apprenticing
under Natsume or Ren?
Why should I be the one?
Oh? Don't think
you can handle it, huh?
If our brilliant Satsuki
isn't up to the task,
what shall we do?
Hey. I never said I couldn't--
I'm sure your
older sister isn't having
any difficulties supervising and
instructing the staff members
she's working with right now.
[SATSUKI]
Hmph!
Let's go, shrimp.
There's work to be done.
[YUZU]
Okay. Coming!
[YUZU grunts]
[SATSUKI sighs]
[KIRI]
Welcome, gentlemen.
[GUEST B]
Hello, Kiri. Is the boss well?
[KIRI]
She is, indeed. Maybe too well.
[GUEST A] Think we might
be able to eat a little early?
[KIRI]
Of course. Not a problem at all.
An early dinner it is.
[SATSUKI] Hurry up and
finish that. We have guests.
[YUZU gasps]
[FURRY GUEST]
Pardon me, ladies.
Is this the way to
the outdoor baths?
Yes, sir.
They are located just at
the end of the path there.
Please relax and
enjoy your stay.
Yes. Please enjoy your stay.
Idiot.
Always make sure you're on your
feet when a guest approaches.
I'm sorry.
Remember, the guests
are what's most important.
So never get in their way.
[YUZU]
Got it. Understood.
[YUZU sighs]
[NATSUME] A big group
of unexpected guests
sure is a pain.
[YUZU grunts]
[NATSUME]
Wow, that looks a lot cleaner.
Oh. Thank you.
But be sure not to
polish it too much,
or you'll slip.
[YUZU]
Huh?
[yelps]
[NATSUME giggles]
[YUZU]
I went overboard..
[FURRY GUEST]
Oh, my! What an excellent bath!
[YUZU]
He shrank!
[FURRY GUEST gasps, yells]
[YUZU gasps, yelps]
[YUZU groans]
Are you hurt, sir...?
Is anything broken?
No, dear.
Are you injured at all, child?
[SATSUKI]
I'm truly, deeply sorry, sir!
We'll let the manager know
what happened and come by later
to make a proper apology.
[FURRY GUEST]
That won't be necessary.
I'm sure the little one there
was hurt far worse than me.
[YUZU] I'm sorry.
That was all my fault.
Just be more
careful from now on.
Apologizing won't
always fix everything.
[YUZU]
Yes, but...
Shouldn't I tell Kiri and go see
the guest later, by myself?
You're missing the point, moron.
We all share responsibility
for what happens here.
Regardless of who messed up,
I did what needed to be done.
[gasps] Okay. Thank you
for having my back.
[SATSUKI sighs]
You're always so fiercely
independent, Satsuki.
I never knew you had
such team spirit.
I was saving
my own face, not hers.
Where any guests are concerned,
if one staff member
here makes a mistake,
it's everyone's mistake.
I know, someday,
I'll be quitting this place,
but until then, I'll do my job.
[FURRY GUEST]
Truly, I'm fine.
No apologies necessary.
[SATSUKI]
Thank you, sir.
And what about you?
Are you all right?
No broken bones, I hope.
No! I only have a
little bruise on my bottom.
--That's all.
--[SATSUKI growls]
Dear me. You poor girl.
That sounds painful.
[FURRY GUEST]
Here. Use this compress.
It will make you feel better.
That's very kind, sir.
Are you a pharmacist?
[gasps] Please, sir.
You must let us pay for that.
And we'll buy other
medicines as well.
It's the least we
can do as a token of apology.
[YUZU]
Can we afford that?
A token of.. apology?
[SATSUKI]
Yes.
We would like to make amends
by helping your business.
[YUZU] But medicine is to help
the injured or treat the sick.
It's not something you should
buy as a way of apologizing.
--[FURRY GUEST] Actually...
--[gasps]
If you would
like to help my business,
there is something.
[FURRY GUEST] This is
a very special medicine,
used to treat a wide
variety of ailments.
[SATSUKI]
Sugar candy?
[FURRY GUEST] And I'm
afraid I don't have enough
of the stardust
I need to make more.
Stars are so high.
Could you knock
some down for me?
[SATSUKI]
But that's just ordinary candy.
Does he think we're that naive?
With all due respect,
sir. What you are--
[YUZU]
Of course, sir!
We'll knock some down for
you as soon as it gets dark!
[YUZU gruntin]
Idiot! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
I'm trying to get some stars!
[grunts]
Almost.
[SATSUKI]
Shut up and stop it already.
[YUZU yelps]
Just one more!
[gasps]
I got it! Did you see?
I hit it and it fell!
It looked like it landed
out past the mountain.
So all you have to do is
go over there and pick it up!
[SATSUKI snarls]
You moron!
Don't you understand?!
He's just messing with us.
I wouldn't exactly
call it "messing with you."
I would more describe it as
"playfully pulling your leg."
And I must say,
it's been quite entertaining.
Thank you both
for a lovely time.
Take these for your trouble.
But we haven't
been able to help you
or do what you asked of us, sir.
I cannot accept these.
You have a strong sense of duty.
However, life is more
than just responsibility.
You ought to loosen up and
let yourself have a bit of fun
once in a while.
That medicine is special.
It will help you learn to relax.
[SATSUKI]
Am I really too uptight?
No. He was just a
weird, old pharmacist.
Still. That stupid brat's
quick thinking did save us.
[gasps]
[FURRY GUEST]
That medicine is special.
It will help you learn to relax.
[SATSUKI sighs]
[SATSUKI]
Fine...
[YUZU sighs]
[YUZU] I've never been
in a hot spring before.
[water splashes]
[YUZU]
Huh...?
Hey there.
[YUZU yelps]
Watch it! Idiot! Be careful!
[YUZU]
Sorry, Satsuki. I'll try.
It's just...
Well, this is my first
time in a hot spring sharing
a bath with someone
around my age.
It's new to me.
[YUZU]
And a little embarrassing.
[SATSUKI sighs] You...
You did good earlier, kid.
Our guest seemed to be
very pleased with you.
With me?
But I didn't do anything for
him to be pleased about.
If he gave us praise,
it belongs to us both.
[gasps]
You're sharing it with me?
[YUZU] It's like you said when
I over-polished the floor.
We all share responsibility
for what happens here.
We're a team.
We have each other's backs.
Since now I'm a
part of that team,
any praise I get is yours, too.
I, uh...
[SATSUKI] I was saving
my own face, not hers.
[water splashing]
[SATSUKI yells]
Idiot! Did you really want to
drown in that hot spring?!
[YUZU]
Sorry you had to rescue me...
[SATSUKI]
Here.
But, that's yours.
Don't argue with me, dammit.
Just have some and go to sleep.
[SATSUKI]
Night, Yuzu.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU sighs]
[SATSUKI]
Night, Yuzu.
[YUZU]
Mm.
[KIRI] Please come
see us again sometime.
[FURRY GUEST]
Oh, I will.
But for now I'm off to explore
the other side of the mountain.
After all, I do need
to pick up that star
a certain someone
knocked down for me.
No, sir! I was just being silly!
I didn't actually knock
down a real star!
Please don't waste your time on
the other side of the mountain!
It won't be there!
He knows that, dummy.
[FURRY GUEST]
Do I? I'm not so sure.
[SATSUKI gasps]
Perhaps there's a
fallen star over there,
or perhaps there isn't.
I won't know for certain
until I go see for myself.
[gasps]
[FURRY GUEST chuckles]
[GIRLS]
Goodbye. Safe travels.
[YUZU]
This is amazing!
I hope I get the chance
to do it every day!
Seeing guests off on new
adventures is wonderful!
I'll make you proud,
Sister Bikuni.
I'm going to work
hard here at Konohanatei.
With Miss Kiri, and Satsuki, and
Ren, and Natsume!
[KIRI]
Oh, yes! That's Sakura.
I forgot to
introduce you to her.
[SAKURA grunts]
[YUZU sighs]
[YUZU]
Correction.
The four I mentioned,
and Sakura.
[SAKURA sighs]
[SATSUKI]
What's the matter with you?!
Quit slacking off!
If you finish something early,
don't just stand around!
See if there's someone else who
needs help and go help them!
Do as we do, even if
you don't understand it!
--[YUZU] I'm sorry!
--Satsuki sure is noisy as ever.
[SATSUKI] How many times
do I have to tell you?!
[YUZU sighs]
You look absolutely beat.
[NATSUME]
You don't need to do everything
that she says, you know?
[YUZU] But Satsuki spends so
much time and energy teaching me
how to do things here.
And she still does all her
own work on top of that,
without missing a beat.
That's why I need
to be strong, learn fast,
and work hard, so I can
stop slowing her down.
You're such a good girl, Yuzu.
[REN] By the way, did you blow
your nose on your obi Natsume?
[NATSUME]
So? Who cares?
We're washing it anyway, right?
[REN]
I care!
[YUZU] You want us
to work with other people?
[KIRI] Uh-huh. Today, Satsuki
will partner up with me.
And, Yuzu, you'll be
teaming up--with Sakura.
[YUZU] Uh, it'll be good
to work with you, Sakura.
[SAKURA]
Hmm.
[YUZU]
Ah-- Wait up! Hey, Sakura?
Wh-Where are you going?
[FROG snores]
[SAKURA]
Hm.
Uh, Sakura? I'm done sweeping.
What job should we move
onto next, huh?
--[SAKURA] Hm.
--Wait! What are you doing?
I don't understand.
Do as we do, even if
you don't understand it!
[YUZU sighs]
I... will!
[yelps]
[YUZU screams, whimpers]
[YUZU]
Hmm?
[whistles]
[YUZU whistles louder]
[loud whistling continues]
[SAKURA blows]
[loud whistling]
--[whistling]
--[gasps]
[weak whislting]
[gasps]
Sakura?
[YUZU pants]
[YUZU gasps]
[gasps]
[gasps] Thank you, Sakura.
How nice of you.
[YUZU] I was so busy trying to
work and get better at my job.
I never noticed where I was or
what was around me.
There's so much beauty here.
[YUZU] I fell asleep!
I have to get back to work!
How come?
It's still lunch break.
[YUZU gasps]
You and me don't
have any need to hurry.
[YUZU gasps]
Amazing! You're amazing, Sakura!
Time passes so slowly
when I'm with you.
It's like you're magic!
It must be
because you're so fun,
and you find so many
interesting things to do!
You think I'm fun?
Yeah! I think
you're lots of fun!
I love working with you!
[bell clanging]
Lunch break's over.
Shall we go back then?
It's for you.
What? For me?
But you worked
so hard making it.
Don't you want it?
[SAKURA]
Not really.
It's just string covered
in flower pedals
[gasps]
Thank you, Sakura!
Thank you very much!
I promise I'll take
good care of it!
[YUZU whimpers]
[KIRI]
So, how'd it go today?
It went great! The forest,
the grass, the streams,
and even the cherry blossoms,
all look so different with her.
She made me realize I've been so
focused on doing just my work,
that I've been missing
the beauty all around me.
Good.
Let's just hope you can do
something constructive
with that.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
I will. At least I'll try to.
[KIRI]
That reminds me.
You two are going to have
to be roommates for a bit.
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRI] Good luck!
See you in the morning.
[YUZU whimpers, gasps]
Being roommates...
This will be fun.
[SATSUKI sighs]
Yeah.
[SAKURA]
That girl is weird.
She said working with
me was interesting and fun.
[laughs]
That sounds like her.
How do you feel, Kiri?
Is working with me fun for you?
[KIRI]
Hm?
Mmm... I'm not sure
I'd call it "fun."
But, it is comforting.
When I'm around you, I can
relax and let my hair down.
[SAKURA gasps]
You should sleep
on your futon, Kiri.
[KIRI] Oopsie! I mistook
you for a high-quality pillow.
[SAKURA] You're getting old,
you know that?
[YUZU whimpers]
[SATSUKI]
We're about to go to sleep.
Why on earth are you so hyper?
[YUZU]
Sorry. I'm just so excited,
I can barely stay in my bed.
I've never shared a room
with a friend before!
We should have
a pillow fight tonight!
--Not a chance.
--[YUZU whines]
[SATSUKI]
She seriously wanted to?
If it's no fun
being in here with me,
then go and bunk with Natsume.
What? But here with you is fun.
[SATSUKI]
I do not get her.
[YUZU]
Goodnight, Satsuki.
It's nice having someone to say
that to... before...
...I go to sleep.
[gasps]
She fell asleep fast.
[BIKUNI] True knowledge, is not
merely what you learn from books
or sitting at a desk
taking lessons.
It also comes from
going out into the world
and learning from
many other people.
Understand?
[YUZU]
Yes, Sister!
[BIKUNI]
Hm.
Yes, Sister Bikuni,
I understand...
[SATSUKI sighs]
[SATSUKI]
Goodnight, Yuzu.