Run faster, damn it!
We can't let him get away...
Does Tim even know
how hard we worked
to steal that thing...?
Let's go get it back!
No one else will have it...
This is my ring now...
No, I don't think so...
You do not deserve that ring.
The Hope Piece is in search
of a worthy master,
you see... You do not
fit that description.
He jumped off the bridge!
That fool.
Ladies and gentlemen,
gather round!...
The Frost Fair hasn't happened
in almost eighty years...!
Don't miss your chance!
Impressive. "Frost Fair"
certainly is
an apt title for this.
A large gathering held at the
foot of the London Bridge
when the Tehmz freezes over...
From what I'm told,
it hasn't been held
for several decades now...
Not since 1814, apparently.
My lady, please...!
Slow down a bit!
Careful... You're going to
crack the ice if you keep
stomping about like that.
Please understand, my lady...
If your parents learn
that we took a detour,
they'll be terribly angry.
I'll be in a lot of trouble.
But Harrods and Liberty
were utterly useless...
They had nothing to offer!
I was joking. It won't crack.
Excuse me, my lady... but
there seems to be something
specific you've been searching
for. Might I ask what?
Something special...
I need a present for Ciel.
It's almost his birthday...
The perfect present.
One that will make him happy...
I mean very, very happy!
Oh, Lady Elizabeth...
that... that is
absolutely adorable!
I understand now.
You have my word...
I pledge to help you
in whatever way
I can in this endeavor.
Thanks, Paula... How sweet.
Well...? Any word on Tim?
They found his body in the
ice. It appears the ring
wasn't on him.
Which means one thing.
Aye. The ring is in the Thames.
Step on up, ladies and gents...
I've got bargains that would
blow even Jack Frost away.
Buy something
for someone special.
Is there something amusing?
Those goods are all
of dubious quality.
Funtom should set up a stall.
Any of our products
would be better than
what that man is selling.
Like that, there.
Ah...! Hello there, noble lad...
You have a good eye.
That piece is one of a kind...
It was manufactured by the
Funtom Toy Company years ago...
back when it was still only
just a small craft studio.
No... that is a blatant fake.
The Funtom Arks are rare...
only three were ever made...
My predecessor employed
the talent of an artist
incredibly skilled in his craft.
Since our estate burned down,
even we no longer possess one.
One most certainly
wouldn't turn up here.
Noah's Ark... You know...
it reminds me of this country.
Why is that?
Think about it: a boat
captained by a single person.
One filled with
only the select few who
have been chosen to be saved...
Rather arrogant,
don't you think?
Is that?...
A Scotland Yard inspector has
time to attend to the fair...
London must be very peaceful...
today, anyway.
It's not...
I'm on duty right now!
Oh ...well, then, I'll
leave you to earn your wages
in faithful service
to the queen and country.
Good day, Inspector.
Wait, come back!
I have some questions
I want to ask you, Ciel!
Pardon me... my master is a
touch fragile at the moment...
er... I mean, sensitive.
Perhaps you could try to be
a trifle more gentle
when you're approaching him.
Now... what is an inspector
from the Yard doing here?
What's your business,
Abberline?
Murder. A man's corpse
was found this morning,
trapped in the ice on the Temz.
We learned he was a member of a
certain criminal organization...
I'm here because Scotland Yard
wants to hunt down
that man's killer and
we also want to recover
a ring that he stole...
a blue diamond, one supposedly
worth around two thousand quid.
The diamond... The ultimate
symbol of eternal radiance.
A stone that bewitches all
those who see its sparkle...
What man wouldn't be inspired to
pursue such an exquisite prize,
even knowing all that
awaits him is total destruction.
Impossible...! How do you know
about the Hope Piece?!
You're after the Hope Piece?
Oh...? Interesting...! Such a
gemstone really does exist?
Oh my.
Wha--... Hold on...!
But you were sayin'--
It's best to ignore him...
He was blathering...
Anyway, Lau... what in the
world are you doing here?
I own this place,
my lord. Nice, eh?
Yes, of course you do.
This 'Hope Piece'
you were talking about
sounds fascinating, my lord...
Perhaps you could
tell me more about it?
Have you never heard of it?
A blue gem known
as the Hope Diamond...
Named after the man whose
collection it was a part of...
Henry Philip Hope.
Don't know it.
It passed to Louis the Sixteenth
and Marie Antoinette...
We know how they ended...
The diamond is said
to be a cursed stone
that brings ruin
to all who possess it...
At one point it was stolen
and cut into smaller pieces
to disguise it...
Rumor has it that
two such pieces still exist.
Those shards of diamond
would certainly be valuable.
Tell me, Abberline... is that
what you're searching for?
The diamond was
being moved as evidence...
It's carriage was attacked...
It was stolen.
Intriguing...
Give me details...
I would like to lend you
a hand in this case.
Of course, I can't force you...
But then... if you do
decide to refuse me...
I can see to it that
Sir Arthur finds himself
in a rather awkward position.
Oh, look at these...!
Aren't they simply wonderful?!
No...those won't do at all!
Oh... You...
you don't think so...?
I thought they'd be an adorable
gift... Jingle, jingle!
You don't understand at all,
Paula... Very well...
I'll search on my own!
Please, Lady Elizabeth!
Give me another chance!
Lady Elizabeth... Please!
You're sure this
is the right place?
Yes...it is...
He set up shop here
because so many people
have been freezin' to death
during the Frost Fair.
Inspector... you can't be
serious... Not him!
Yes Him and you lot can
wait right here outside.
You are lucky I let you
accompany me at all.
What a hopeless fool.
One of the privileges
of youth, my lord....
So... what is this place?
It's the Undertaker's parlor!
You met him during the Jack
the Ripper case, remember?!
Oh, right!
Abberline won't last one
minute in there.
Sebastian... prepare to--
I assure you, man, you're
in the wrong profession!
That was hysterical.
You could be
a world renowned comedian!
What did you say to him?
I have no idea. I was just
talking to him normally...
He began laughing
like a madman.
How unexpected...
You aren't without talent.
It seems you're a man
to be reckoned with...
Most interesting.
But... I didn't do anything.
Tell me more about the ring...
I want to know it all.
The man you pulled out of the
river was the last to have it.
Perhaps it was frozen
in the ice near where
the body was found...
You are a citizen of our great
country, Mr. Undertaker...
Please give us
your help in this matter.
As I said before, I'm
profoundly impressed with you,
Inspector.
I'll tell you everything...
Where is the ring, you ask?
You see... right there.
It appears that a sculptor must
have happened upon the ring
and then designed
a beautiful ice sculpture
to complement it.
Our mystery has been solved.
Collect the ring right now!
Right!
What do you think
you're doing, thieves?!
That dear lady will be awarded
to the contest's victor.
You wouldn't want
to defile her, now would you?
Viscount, Lord Druit!
They're holding some contest?
Why is he a judge?
Yes, wasn't he just arrested
for human trafficking...?
What a naughty man.
He was released a few days ago.
Must've paid well.
Excuse me...
but this statue is now under
the charge of Scotland Yard.
Oh, no...! I don't care if you
are from Scotland Yard sir...
The Frost Fair is
an event for our citizens;
I will not let you disrupt it.
Just look at her beauty...!
Such an exquisitely noble lady!
We could never allow her
to be violated by anybody!
You're one to talk.
If you insist on
possessing this lady...
you should offer
something of equal beauty.
A well-spoken pronouncement
from a true lover
of art and beauty...
As he says... if you want
this statue, win the contest.
There's merit
to your argument...
The ring belongs to whomever is
the winner of the contest...
Nice and simple.
Really, Ciel?
Don't worry, Inspector.
I'll get the ring.
But it's stolen property...
Not to mention the fact
that it's our key evidence
in serial kidnappings
of young girls!
I see... That's why the Yard
is so frantic to find it.
The legend is true. Every person
who has owned the ring
has met a horrible end...
It's a cursed stone, and
you'd still try to win it?
Cursed, eh?
Then it sounds like
the perfect ring for me.
Come to think of it...
isn't that family ring you wear
set with a pretty
blue stone as well, lord?
Yes.
Perhaps you should be careful.
Diamonds are quite hard...
because they're hard,
they're also... brittle.
If you go too far...
you may be shattered as well.
I'm not concerned.
My body... along with
my family ring...
Both have already been
shattered and then reborn.
I've been through too much
to worry about that anymore.
Win the contest...
That's an order.
Indeed... Young master.
It's settled, then...
go fill out an entry form.
Seriously?!
Are you an Irishman,
or aren't you?
We know more than the bloody
English about ice and snow!
R... Right!
And if all else should fail...
Welcome, one and all
to the Thames Frost Fair...
Now, it is time
for the traditional
Ice Sculpture Contest.
You have until three p.m.
All right...
You may begin sculpting!
Oh, look at that!
Something's happening there...
it sounds excititing!
Ciel...
I hate this ring!. Take it!
Forgive my master,
Lady Elizabeth,
but that ring was something
very important to him.
It's a precious
heirloom passed down
from the head of
the Phantomhive family...
He's grown quite attached to
it... It's truly one of a kind.
I'm sorry, Ciel...
I'm so sorry.
But I'll make it up to you...!
I'll find you
an amazing present.
That ark...! I want it!
And now, folks...
the judging shall commence!
First up...
We have Scotland Yard and
its Merry Men
with their sculpture...
"Guardian of London."
Judges' scores...
One, two, one, one, zero...!
For a total of five points.
Next team...
Who's name is "All Women's
Dresses Should be Tiny."...
And their entry....
For obvious reasons... this ice
sculpture has been disqualified.
But why?
How could you possibly think
that was proper to display?!
You know, when they hide
bits like that,
I think it only
makes it more erotic.
Win this...You can, right?
Of course I can. You explicitly
ordered me to do so.
and I exist only to fulfill
your orders, my lord.
And next, from the team
known as Queen's Puppy,
we have... The Ark of Noah!
What a sculpture!
I've never seen its like!
That is art in
its highest form!
An amazing piece...!
Let's see the total scores--
One moment...
My apologies, but you haven't
seen all of the sculpture yet.
Wow!
They look like living animals!
Brilliant...!
He deliberately made
the seam of the roof weak
so it would melt
and fall apart in time.
Our ancestor!.
The brave man who stood
fearlessly against
the flood of God's wrath:
Noah...!
He is depicted here with
the pairs of animals
he was ordered to rescue...
awaiting rebirth from the sea.
Astounding work, young man...
It's high art...
I declare you an ice sculptor
of the highest caliber.
No, Sir...You're too kind... I
am simply one hell of a butler.
So, uh... I don't think
we're gonna beat that.
Damn... Then on to plan B.
Is everyone ready
for the final scores?
Hold it right there.
Hate to break up the party,
but this ring is ours...
We're taking
what belongs to us.
Hold on...! That means
that you're the--
That's right...! We're the team
of thieves all of London's
been talking about.
Maybe you recognize these?
You have ten seconds...
Anyone who doesn't want
to die should get
the hell out of here... Ten...
Master?
Nine!
My orders remain the same...
Do it now, Sebastian.
Indeed... Young master.
Eight!
What are you doing...?
Hurry up.
We need to get out of here!
Seven!
You can go if you want to...
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Six!
I can't leave you here!
I joined Scotland Yard
to protect our citizens...!
That includes
noblemen like you Ciel!
What a fool.
Stay back, inspector!
You only have
three seconds left...
A sweet little boy like you...
shouldn't you be running away?
I see no need for that.
Look behind you.
What the--?!
Impossible! He spun
four whole times in the air.
A noble swan
flying through a world
of silvery-white snow!
Lured by that devilish smile,
the maiden is enfolded
in his midnight-black wings!
Ten, ten, ten, ten, ten...
That's it! A perfect score!
Damn you... Little brat...
I'm gonna blow you away!
Again...?! I hate this guy.
Please Boss, stop doing that!
Have you forgotten?
Look down...!. We're
standing on top of ice!
Sebastian!
Where is he?
My lord is stubborn as ever.
The ship sails on...
leaving human despair behind!
The ship sails on!
Carrying the future
of the world...!
The ship sails on despite the
raging flood of icy waters
seeking to drown it...
The ship sails on!
It's the ark... Truly
a recreation of Noah's Ark...!
We've seen a miracle
on the Thames!
Was tossing me about
like that really necessary?
My apologies sir... But we did
have an audience, after all.
I thought it might add
a bit of flair to the show.
The Hope Diamond
will sleep safely
at the bottom of the Thames.
Not a bad end.
But won't it curse
all of London now?
Somehow I doubt
that will happen...
Besides if a ring
can destroy this city,
it wasn't meant to survive...
After all...
We Phantomhives have lived on.
Grab my hand! I've got you.
Tell me something...
Earlier, you had accused
Noah of being arrogant...
But he was only
trying to save a few...
Wouldn't the desire
to protect everyone
be even more arrogant?
Yes, it would seem so.
Ah, well...
An arrogant fool like
that every now and then
might not be so bad.
Ciel... Who exactly are you?
What's the matter?
My father... he said
this was obviously a fake.
It's awful... I thought...
I thought I'd found
something to make Ciel happy!
I'm so sorry...!
Please cheer up! here,
I have just the thing!
Jingle, jingle, jingle--
Leave me alone!
Ciel... I'm sorry.
I just... wanted to
give you a wonderful gift.
So I thought to myself...
Why not let
the hope diamond find
a new owner on its own...
Eh, master?
The ring's stone flickers
like a blue abyss...
an inescapable
promise of death...
Meanwhile, the organ
plays a broken melody,
its tune faltering.
Listen well, young master...
You must not trust bad men...
No... I'm sorry...
What I meant was red men.
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler,
However You Please."
You see... I am simply
one hell of a butler.