The Funtom Company
is celebrating its third year...
In honor of this,
they are presenting a play
for orphaned children...
...a presentation of Hamlet.
Well, well, it seems
as though we're
getting a fair bit
of press for this.
I never expected
charity from you...
I have to admit, I do admire
your philanthropic
spirit, master.
Philanthropy...?
No, love breeds money...
You do know what
they'll say, don't you...?
"The Funtom Company gives
love to children in need."
A comment easily used
to our advantage.
[people crying]
[BARDROY] Love for
the poor orphans...!
How noble...!
It brings tears to my eyes!
Of course our master
understands how they feel...!
He lost his own parents
just like the orphans!
Stop this crying...!
Didn't you lot hear
anything that I just said?
An appropriate choice, sir...
Hamlet...
Exactly what I would
expect from a child.
[SEBASTIAN]
Shakespeare's great work.
One with much significance.
[SEBASTIAN] After Prince
Hamlet's father, the king,
is murdered, Hamlet
vows to avenge him
even at the cost
of his own life...
The play might as well have be
written for you, young master.
Don't get carried away.
Hamlet was simply in the
repertoire of the troupe...
I don't care about the plot.
[Mey Lin cries out]
Master!
What's wrong...?
What on Earth happened?
[MEY LIN] Sir...!
The ship carrying the actors ran
into some trouble at sea...!
They won't arrive in London 'til
next week, no they won't!
But the performance
is three days away.
Do you have any idea how
much it's been advertised...?!
Bloody press is
going to be all over us...
We can't possibly reschedule!
What shall we do?
What we have to...
Now...
Sebastian...
...your orders:
Make the show a success...
It must be worthy of
the Phantomhive name.
Indeed, my young Lord.
♪
My dear Ranmao...
...tell me, what part
do you want to play?
Seaweed.
I know my
part already...!
Obviously, I'll be
playing Ramakrishnna!
Oh, my prince...
You'll be fabulous!
You'll be the star of the show!
Oh, and I want to
be a gorgeous princess...!
And I'll wear a pretty dress
with at least three petticoats!
[Undertaker cackles]
Only three, princess?
Oh no dear, I won't be caught
dead with less than five.
What, are you serious?!
You're going to
be a princess, too?
That wouldn't be cute at all!
We have seaweed,
a mystic, and two princesses?
[CIEL] Didn't I explain:
we're doing Hamlet?!
Sebastian...!
Why all these amateurs?
Were you intending to
put on a school play?!
This is as it
should be, master...
A charity play really ought
be staged by its host.
One oughtn't pay a
theatrical troupe to do it.
And besides...
I have some faith
in this particular group...
I believe they'll all take well
to a bit of harsh direction...
They know better than
to argue with certain people.
And naturally, you'll have a
part to play as
well, young lord.
I'm sure it's not a problem...
Of course you
know you, too,
must rise to the occasion
in a time of crisis.
Or are you
indeed a child, master?
[piano chord struck]
It's time for us to begin...
...so, it will start
with vocal exercises.
[Sebastian vocalizes a scale]
[group attempts to mirror
scale with some off key]
[moaning the scale]
[Sebastian vocalizes a scale]
[SEBASTIAN]
There will be none of that.
[piano chord struck]
[SEBASTIAN] Go!
[group attempts scale]
[SOMA] Yes!
So perfect!
So wonderful!
[SEBASTIAN]
None of that, either.
[SOMA] Why not?
But, there's
plenty to go around...
Please do feel free
to help yourself.
No, thank you.
And now...
...we work on acting.
[CIEL]
"To be, or not to be.
That is the question...
Whether 'tis nobler
in the mind's eye--"
Master...
...put a bit more heart into it?
[CIEL] "To... ...to
be or not to be.
That is the--
[GRELL] Not to be, of course.
That's a DEAD certainty.
Oh, what pathetically
horrible acting...!
Do us all a favor
and drop dead this instant,
my dear little Prince Hamlet!
No, Grell...?!
What're you doing here?
Who is that...?
I have the strangest feeling
I've seen him before.
[GRELL] You have
absolutely no heart.
None at all...! Don't
you want to convey
all the anguish
Hamlet's feeling?
It has to echo
throughout the theatre!
Come on now, try it like this!
[GRELL]
To be or not to be...?
That is the question...!
Whether 'tis nobler...
♪ That's no question,
no, none at all...! ♪
♪ No,question at aaallll! ♪
[ALL]
♪ No, not at all! ♪
♪ When I met you,
there was no question, ♪
♪ no question at all... ♪
♪ To be, to be
with you...! I would do ♪
♪ anything that I
had toooo! ♪
You know...
...if you aren't careful, you
won't be for much longer at all.
[GRELL] Oh, my Bassy...!
Love and death coincide...!
Can you not see it...?
Don't you understand
the beauty?!
I must admit...
...as melodramatic
as his style may be...
...perhaps it could be useful
for our current purposes.
[SEBASTIAN] Anyway...
...no one's putting forth
sufficient effort...
Try harder, people!
And I said, no curry!
[SOMA] It's really good!
[RANMAO] Seaweed.
[ELIZABETH] Yeah.
See...?
Pink hats, there definitely
the cutest, aren't they?!
Excuse me, Sebastian?
[SEBASTIAN] Hamlet.
[SEBASTIAN]
Nothing but pain in its plot.
Othello...
King Lear...
And Macbeth...
Combined with Hamlet,
and his greatest tragedies.
[SEBASTIAN]
You have to understand Hamlet...
You have to understand
the Phantomhives...
They are two blood tragedies
inextricably intertwined.
[group cries out]
[GRELL] My...
...my Bassy...!
You're terrifying!
[dog makes a questioning sound]
[WOMAN] Oh...!
It's the viscount!
[FINNIAN] Look at that...!
There's so many people!
I'm so ready!
Finally, I can show off
my prowess as an actress!
[ELIZABETH] Oh, my...!
This costume isn't cute at all!
[SEBASTIAN] Where is he?
[MEY LIN] Oh, I...
I think he went
to the restroom...
[SEBASTIAN] So this
is where you've been...
Master.
[SEBASTIAN] A bit too
late to decline the part...
Terribly sorry.
[CIEL] I am a young prince...
I lost my father
and burn for revenge.
I know you...
You didn't give me this
part on accident, did you?
You lack acting
experience, sir...
And I'm afraid you scarcely
possess the dexterity required
to button your own shirts.
[SEBASTIAN] I didn't
want to cast you in a part
too different from
who you are...
I thought it might be
too difficult for you.
Really?!
Why shouldn't we
proceed this way, master?
There is bloody revenge coming.
Should this not then
be its prelude?
[SEBASTIAN] Master...
are you ready?
The curtain is rising
on this tale at last.
[PLUTO] So, they're on holiday.
[PLUTO] Which also means...
I get a holiday as well.
[PLUTO] Crunchy and delicious!
[PLUTO] And here I go!
[Pluto howls]
[PLUTO] Inukko: puppies love it!
[FINNIAN] The King
of Denmark has met
with an
untimely death...
He is succeeded
by his young brother...
Claudius has been crowned king.
And the late king's
wife who, until now,
had seemed to love
him unconditionally...
...has scandalously become the
bride of Denmark's newest ruler.
[LAU] Oh...!
What happened to my brother
is such a terrible tragedy...!
But we're both still alive,
so shouldn't we enjoy
ourselves, huh?
[UNDERTAKER]
Absolutely, my dear!
[LAU] Pardon my reach...
Ah...
how lovely you are...!
Your bosom... like a
pair of new, ripe apples...
Simply heavenly... heavenly,
heavenly, my darling--
[Undertaker laughs]
[LAU] Tickle tickle...!
You know you like it,
don't you, darling?!
Your Majesty, you're
getting a bit handsy for me...!
I am a lady, after all!
[FINNIAN] And then, in
a startling development,
the late king's son, Hamlet,
encounters him as a ghost.
Oh, no...!
My father...!
What can this mean that
thou appearest so before me?
[grunts three times]
Is that so...?
It was my vile uncle...?
That man... the devil,
Claudius, did this to you...!
He poured poison
in your ear, Father?!
[grunts three times]
I understand what you ask...
Yes, you bid me to
take revenge in thy place.
I will do
as you ask, Father.
[BARDROY] That's funny,
I didn't hear him say that.
[MEY LIN] Tanaka can convey
all of that just by being there.
[SOMA] What I'd
like to know is why
I'm sitting here playing
a stagehand, huh?!
It might help if you
weren't eating curry.
I promise you...
...that my hatred shall
live along with yours...
I will avenge you, though it
may mean the fires of Hell.
I swear it
here and now...
...in your name,
vengeance shall be mine!
An enthusiastic performance,
don't you think?!
[BARDROY] Come on now,
can't you do better with
that light than that?!
[SOMA] It isn't like I
volunteered to be a stagehand!
[SEBASTIAN] Then maybe
you should stop eating...
Now then...
How is the audience?
[SEBASTIAN]
I don't know that children
can quite understand Hamlet.
Hamlet must somehow
deceive his uncle...
Thus, he makes a plan...
He will seem to
be hurt by Ophelia,
and he will appear to go mad.
Oh, I'm simply terrible...!
Terrible!
[AGNI] Ophelia...
there you are!
[GRELL] Hello, Father!
Oh, goodness...!
Now I've gotten a better
look at thee, yes I have...!
And how handsome
you are, my darling father!
[GRELL]
I know it's forbidden,
but what a beautiful
love we could have!
I cannot even begin
to fathom such depravity...!
Who could forgive such heinous
acts between father
and daughter?!
[GRELL] But...
please...
[FINNIAN] And one
thing led to another.
Ophelia as well met
an untimely end.
No...!
It's not time...
Ophelia isn't supposed
to die this early!
And she did not
receive a proper burial!
[ELIZABETH] This'll be easy!
Let's toss her in the river.
[GRELL] Oh, my dear father...
Seaweed, seaweed...
...oh, how lovely it is...
Seaweed, seaweed,
oh how lovely it is!
Oh my...
I dare say she seems
to be quite a hit.
[KID 1] Seaweed!
[KID 2] Heck, yeah!
[MEY LIN] Sounds like
she's popular with the kids!
One more reason I ain't
never gonna understand kids.
Finally,
we've broken through
to our audience...
The master's scene
is here at last.
To be or not to be...
that is the question...
Whether tis
nobler to suffer...
...the slings and arrows
of outrageous fortune...
...or take arms againt
of a seas of troubles
and by opposing end them...
...to die to slumber and
by slumber to end.
I don't want to die!
Hamlet, must you be
such a pathetic coward...?!
You are a most
unworthy hero...!
Your soul is far too weak!
This is my sworn vow...
There's no taking it back.
No matter what,
I can never turn away!
[CIEL] But...
I must be off now...
...before my blood begins
to rises any further.
[BARDROY] Bloody hell.
Amazing...!
He's just amazing!
Indeed, he is...
Very true to life,
don't you think?
Oh, how he trembles
with such honest fury...!
His slender limbs... are
like such fragile branches--!
[KID]
Shhh...
[DRUITT] Oh, sorry...
Pardon me...
Look at that...
Even the children
were able to feel the
anguish in his performance...
And now...
Looks like it's
time for my turn...
Now, following this
unfortunate turn of events,
Hamlet and Ophelia's brother,
Laertes must meet blade to
blade in a fencing match
arranged by the king.
[FINNIAN] However...
...the tip of Laertes' sword
has been coated with poison...
...one that will kill a
man with a single drop.
[KID 1] Okay,
I'm getting scared now!
Thou art Ophelia's
esteemed brother...
I've heard much of
your skill with a sword.
I've heard the same of thee...
Perhaps you will see
fit to take pity on me.
Yes, yes...
...that's about enough
chat for now, I think.
We'll have a ten-point match...
Ready...?
Let the match...
...beg--
[KID 3] Hamlet, no...!
Don't do it!
That old guy's cheating...!
His sword is poisoned!
"Old guy?"
It's the king...!
He lied about the
match being fair!
Don't you see, Hamlet?
They're trying to kill you!
[KID 1] You should stop.
Stupid revenge isn't worth this!
[KID 3] Yeah, you don't need it!
They don't want me to die...
Master...!
Just remember your line!
What's my line...?
It's hopeless!
What do we do?!
[SOMA] Hurry up!
Draw the curtains!
Yes, of
course. I'll--
Mey Rin... hold on!
[SEBASTIAN] How dare
you stop our fight!
This farce is over...
You know the
truth, Hamlet...!
My dear sister's
life was cut short...
You are the one to
be blamed for it.
She's dead because of you!
Stop it...!
This isn't in the script!
I shall have
my revenge...!
I will see that
you die as well...!
For my Ophelia!
[GRELL] Oh please,
stop your fighting!
Please do not shed
your blood over me.
[BARDROY]
What the bloody hell?!
Yes, and why
is there a gondola?
[SOMA] That diva wants
to hog the spotlight!
Well, I'll show hi--
[BARDROY] Come back here...!
You'll ruin it!
[SOMA] Not fair!
Not fair! Not faaaiiir!
[CIEL] Ophelia...?!
Isn't this a
pleasant surprise...
I thought we'd lost you!
I was lost 'til my brother
came back for me...!
But his love is strong...!
Strong enough to
revive the dead!
Oh, my darling brother...
...you must know,
you truly are the one for me!
So this is where
you've been
spending all your time...
Reaper Sutcliffe.
Will!
[WILLIAM] This is an outrage!
You've deserted your place,
and you're putting on a play...
...with that demon!
My, all these handsome
men fighting over me!
Whatever is a girl to do?
[SOMA] Stop this now!
End your useless fighting...!
Leave the rest to me,
Ramakrishna, avatar of the sun!
I'll save the day!
Yes, Prince Soma!
[KID 6] Look,
Ophelia came back to life!
[KID 7] Go get 'em,
Rama-whoever!
What a perfect
mess this is...!
Utter foolishness!
[SEBASTIAN] Yes, it is foolish.
Revenge is
foolishness, master...
A very brief release...
...and then nothing but
confusion, chaos, and pain...
When the curtain falls on
such a sad performance...
...what does anyone
really have left?
What?
Would you not agree...
...my Prince of Denmark?
But... you...
I never thought you
would say that.
[SOMA] Yes, I agree!
In the end,
revenge has no meaning...!
You know I speak the truth,
for I am Ramakrishna,
avatar of the sun!
Wh... What?
[SEBASTIAN]
If you can't adlib...
...what kind of a demon's
master would you be?
You can do it, Hamlet.
Yes, you're right.
From now on, I vow...
I'll forget revenge--
I will forget it.
And I will live, instead!
[crowd applauds]
[DRUITT] How magnificent...!
This is Hamlet as it
ought to have been seen...!
Brilliantly transcending
a revenge play...!
Hamlet, you should be wrapped
warm in arms of tender love...!
Hammy, Hammy, my Hamlet!
[TANAKA] Thank you very much...
And if I may say...
"All the world's a stage...
...and all the men and
women merely players."
[TANAKA] We meet one another...
...and we begin our drama.
But sooner or later,
the curtain closes.
As it must.
[TANAKA] Thank you...
Thank you...
Thank you.
♪
[KID 2] That was so much fun!
[KID 3] Hamlet was adorable!
We put on an excellent
show for those orphans today!
Seaweed.
Hey wait...
Does anyone know what
happened to Ophelia?
[SOMA] That old man with
the scissors took her...
He beat her black and blue, too!
The performance
was quite a success, master...
Why do you seem so out of sorts.
The bit about
forgetting revenge...
I hope you know, I won't do it.
Of course I know, my lord.
We see beauty on the stage,
but in the end, it's a dream...
Besides, what would
I have to gain if
you forgot about revenge,
young master?
[ELIZABETH] Ciel!
There's going to be a big
party at your manor now, right?
What...?
A party?
[SEBASTIAN]
I've seen to everything...
I went back during
intermission to prepare.
You see, sir...
I'm one hell of a butler.
[CIEL] Forget about revenge...
...forget, and live on.
Hang in there, please!
You have to!
I'm a fishmonger,
not some bloody canary.
Maybe you
should start thinking
about getting out of my town.
[LAU] Only a matter of time
before Tanaka Sushi goes down.
[CIEL] Really...?
Interesting.
Outside talent...
I'm curious to see
what you've found.
Looky here...
Freshly caught
and still floppin'!
My specialty...?
Oh, it's human hearts.
Tanaka's lackey...?
Well, good luck!
Sebastian...?
I suppose this
will be interesting.