This is the second fire
we've had since
I began my service
with the Phantomhives...
All I can do, in the end,
is document the story
of this grand estate.
That is my role...
However... I suppose...
That role...
is coming to an end.
That's a strong wind
a-blowing, eh?
Aye, and it's warmer
than it ought to be.
We'll see rough waters.
I hope we'll make port
in London soon.
I found you... Lord.
The Undertaker?
That tiny, whiny bloke
Will was the one who
brought me into
this expedition.
Apparently he'll be
shorthanded in London,
so he roped me into it
by promising to waive
my library fines.
Will's coming to London?
Yes... There's much work to
do... We have a great many
souls to collect
in London this evening.
Look at that!
What is it?!
Ah... seems that it's begun.
My... They certainly put on
quite the show, don't they?
And now I must be on my way.
Hold on! Tell me...
Why did you come here?
You and I have our
share of history together,
don't we? In light
of that fact...
I thought I would
give you fair warning.
My young Earl...
before much longer...
...you'll die.
I'll die... what do you mean?
No!
You'll die.
Sebastian's gone...
He isn't with me anymore,
which means the death
waiting for me is...
it's useless... wrong.
The hatred... my pain...
They're burning out.
Everything is burning.
Burning away...
You're hurting... I well
understand. I'm quite sorry...
but I'm simply not at liberty
not to finish you off right now.
So much to do.
Ugh... that's revolting.
Majesty, the holy flame
has begun the salvation
of your land.
Ah... I see.
Isn't it wonderful?
We shall finally
be greeting the unpolluted
England of the new century!
Something's wrong, Majesty?
Ever since we returned
from Paris, you seem to be
in poor health.
Ashe, come
...see this. It hurts.
It hurts so much.
Forgive my touch.
His body is
beginning to rot.
Please allow me
to perform a cleansing.
No!
I can't lose him!
Leave me this at least...
Leave me his body...
just as it was.
Majesty...
He doesn't need to be
cleansed... He's perfect
just as he is. Please
do something Ashe!...
Save him for me!
You smell.
You are... unclean.
Yes, she may be the queen, but
she's only human... and a
foolish human at that... How
terribly sad for her Majesty.
The pain, and all the tears
that have fallen in
this corrupt land...
their genesis...
was when humans were divided
into male and female.
We can show great mercy...
but still...
The humans can't be saved.
No salvation.
My dear Albert
is falling down...
falling down, falling down.
Albert, my... dear...
is falling down my...
cherished... husband.
I'm going to die... soon.
Will it be on this ship,
or somewhere else?
What are you doing?!
We can't go back to London
when it's in this shape
now can we?...
We'll have to do circles
around here.
But why?!
We're practically there now,
aren't we?!
Fine. I'll get on that one...
Get me a row boat!
For one little boy? Tell me
why should I even bother?...
Now, if there's money
changing hands...
Ruddy fool!... I have
to return to London!
Do I really?... For what?
In the end... I didn't
kill Her Majesty...
No... I couldn't kill her.
If I let go of hatred...
then the person I've been
since that day
disappears with it.
That's not me!... Not me!
But darling...
I will not let it go.
I will not lose... my hatred!
If I let go of my hatred...
then I don't exist.
But... Then...
Who stands here now... who'm I?
Wake up, kid...
I'm a busy man, you know...
So maybe you should--
Bloody hell!...
What's wrong with you?
Are you mad?
Take this.
That's incredible!...
Just look at it shine!
It's a blue diamond.
You don't see
one of these every day.
Wait, what's a kid like you
doing with something like that?!
Take it... and give me a boat.
Look, here he comes!
Are you a Frenchman?
Come on!
Let go!... What're you doing?!
You bloody Frenchmen!...
You started this fire
in the first place,
didn't you!
You want to start a war
wif England, don't you?
Yes... It would appear that
your beloved Queen
is trying to plunge Europe,
not to mention
the rest of the world,
into full-scale war.
Just wait a moment...
I'm not--
Quickly men!
Another frog!
Stop it!... Please just stop!
What is this?...
What are they doing?
Such a fire!
Stop this!
I'll take that.
Where am I?...
Is this Hell?
He's here.
So the boy has made his way
back to London.
Impressively done.
Tell me... what do you
think of the view?
Look out!
You must have
a death wish, yes sir!
M-... master!?
Mey Rin?!... But what
are you doing here?
Oh! Oh dear!... I'm so
very sorry, my lord...
I know it's my duty to
protect the estate, but...
But... I just... had to...
Calm down...
You're not in trouble.
Just tell me
why you're here.
It's... it's Plu-Plu!
What about Pluto?
What are your thoughts?
Next to the Great Fire
of London in 1666...
this one... well, it seems
to burn rather slowly.
Indeed, you're right...
This city is so unclean...
It takes time to burn filth...
It will be long
before London is
utterly purified.
Even so... good
shall prevail.
This fire will burn everything
out... And then at long last...
a cleaner land will
be able to emerge.
The door will be open...
to a new century.
It seems that checkmate
is fast approaching.
What will you do with
your pawns... master?
The damn tranquilizers
don't work!
Plu-Plu...
So... you really think
we did the right thing,
chasing Pluto out here?...
The reason we were hired
in the first place was to
protect the estate, isn't it?
Doesn't even look like we
can even do anything
to help here.
The house itself isn't what
I want to protect.
I want to protect the
relationships in it...
...all the good times
we had together!
For us to have that...,
everyone...
everyone has to live...
including Pluto!
Master!
What were you thinking,
bringing the master here?!
He said to! It's not
my place to say no.
Pluto!
An ironic world, isn't it?
You fought against me
for your master's sake...
And now here you are...
standing beside me...
watching his
little tragedy play out.
I cannot act at the moment,
not without my master's order,
and for now...
for awhile, at least...
I have no master to follow.
Through all of this,
I've thought to myself...
I might not mind joining
forces with you...
We can rule the newly
reborn world.
The clean world...
When it springs from the fire.
How would that work?...
I thought I was the epitome
of the uncleanliness
you so detest.
When you look
at them closely,
all things are two sides
of the same coin...
Morning and night...
man and woman...
light and darkness.
But when they are put
through purifying flames,
they become one...
They return to the
essential existence
beloved of the Father.
You want a doll...
another artificial thing
to satisfy
your hunger for power.
No.
Is there something
else you want?
If you hunger...
I can come to you
as a woman, as well.
What are you up to here?
Well... it's just... we wanted
Pluto to be how he was...
We're sorry!
And I'm already out
of tranquilizers.
Are you idiots?
You have real bullets,
don't you?
Master, are you telling us
that we should shoot him?
Take a look at his eyes.
His mind is
already long gone.
That up there isn't the
Pluto you and I knew...
It's just a beast.
A beast...
You three know what
it's like, don't you?...
To have even your pride
stolen away from you...
to be left behind, hollow...
It's a tragic way to live.
I order you... Mey Rin...
Finni... Bard...
Kill the demon hound...
any way you can.
Yes, sir.
He's everything I would
expect from someone
who would employ
a demon such as you...
Unfeeling and ruthless, a soul
forever beyond redemption...
As I said before,
you and I should join--
So that's it, then...
No matter how much time
goes by Angels and demons
will forever be on opposite
sides of the coin.
Let's go!
Now... all I can do is run.
If I'm going to die,
I will die with
the soul he craves...
Only then... only then
can I regain my pride.
I am the Earl of Phantomhive...
Ciel Phantomhive...
I request to see--
Time is standing still...
A trap?... No time
to decide that!
Her Majesty!
What's this?!
What happened?
Who's that?
It's Her Majesty!
The Queen's been murdered!
Who did it?
Who's responsible?!
Who is this murderer?!
I'm Ciel... I am the
Earl Phantomhive...
as my father was!
Phantomhive?... You mean to
say the queen's guard dog
has turned against her?!
I've cast off that title...
and no,
I'm not the one
who killed Her Majesty.
You think to talk your way out?
No... I'm certain
I can't... but still...
No matter what
you do to me, I will not
be stopped now!
I'm hit... bleeding...
Think... the gates
of Heaven will forever be
out of your reach.
Do you wish to form
a contract with me?
This is... my death...
This is... my soul...
No... no... forget it!
I... I won't end here...
Not like this!
I see you've awoken,
young master.
Fire!
You came... back.
It is exactly as
you said, Master.
You won't end...
Not here. Not now.
Master... I ask your
forgiveness for taking
unauthorized leave.
What... was so important?
Oh... I was seeing
to the preparations
for the Last Supper.
Spicy... bitter...
but sometimes sweet...
It's a multifaceted meal,
indeed... Braised to perfection
Thanks to you, this Last
Supper will be delicious...
I will be able to enjoy
the ultimate soul.
I order you...
take me right now to this
angel of massacre!
Yes sir.
He can't be a human!
Oh no... Indeed, I'm not.
I'm simply...
one hell of a butler.
Can they do it?
Assuming the servants fight
with all their might...
I believe they'll be an
even match for Pluto.
They should have a good
chance of winning.
Well, whoever loses...
Before much longer...
I'll see them... I'll be
seeing them again in Hell...
It's beginning.
It's coming to me...
The despair of the unclean
must ultimately be
transformed into
divine hope!
And it feels... good.
I've waited a long time
for this, my young master.
Combing your fine dainty locks,
gingerly fastening
the buttons of your
shirt one by one...
it was all I could do
to keep the surge
of emotion in check.
But now at last
the moment has come
there is no need to hold
back. Bon appetite.
Next time, on Black Butler:
"His Butler, Fluent."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.