Believe it or not...
T'weren't so long ago
people could bathe
in this 'ere river.
Might as well be
a sewer now, though,
what with the filth
all of London has poured
into it these past years.
Mr. Havock, look there...!
What's that?
Oh, aye... That
there is Cutty Sark.
They say she was built
to import tea from China,
for the nobles and such -
like who could afford it.
Is she faster
than a steamship?
Heh... F'you listen to
the crew what sails her,
with a stout wind she can
beat anything that floats.
Why is she the "Cutty Sark?"
Old Bobbie Burns tells of a
witch by that name, my boy.
Says if you stare
at her too long,
she'll have you by the tail.
She could take me
away from here...
Some place that no one's
ever heard of...
Could be...
But that new canal in Egypt's
clipped her wings a bit.
Put her out of the tea trade
for good, so I hear.
The age of the clippers
is over, I'm afraid...
It's the beginning
of a new era now.
That's her...! Cutty Sark!
What is it, boy?
We haven't been able
to find anyone who
can identify him, inspector.
I see.
Simple robbery, then...
He was murdered elsewhere
and then dropped here...
not much left for us to do.
But see here?
The victim was killed by a
single, well placed blow...
That seems a bit neat
for a common thief
if you want my opinion, sir.
Perhaps there's some sort of
Mafia infighting going on, then.
Who knows what the Italians
and Chinese are up to...
I've heard tales of
a new drug on the market.
That could cause
some territory dispute...
Doesn't matter. Won't know
anything 'til he's identified.
That won't be necessary.
We know his identity.
His name is John Stanley...
Sebastian has the rest
of his particulars for you.
Inspector.
And what is
your interest in this?
Doing my civic duty and
cooperating with the police...
Isn't that what you've
always told me to do,
Sir Arthur?
Spare me the
noble protestations...
What is it you want
with this case...?
Out with it,
Phantomhive.
A bit gauche, but if
you prefer it that way...
I'm happy to oblige...
I need to see any belongings
left on the victim.
Well... Actually
there were none.
Not even any
identification papers.
In that case... I'm happy
I could be of service...
Thank you, Inspector Abberline.
Sebastian.
Sir.
Nosy brat...
I'll never understand why Her
Majesty puts her trust in him.
Because he's
her guard dog... Sir.
Is something wrong,
my lord...?
I must say you seem
even more taciturn
than usual this afternoon.
And I should look pleasant
while investigating a murder?
You're far too modest, sir...
You misheard me...
I would never say that
you don't look pleasant.
This case just makes me
a bit uneasy...
Clearly we don't have
all the information.
This morning a body
washed up at the
Regent's Canal Dock... The
man's name was John Stanley...
by profession he was a merchant
in the shipping business.
And?
He was an operative in
the criminal underworld,
on top-secret assignment
for Her Majesty.
Not unlike you,
Lord Phantomhive.
Her Majesty wished me
to convey this:
"Find the thing he carried on
his person, and destroy it..."
That is all.
Think you're up to it?
And his killer...
shall I get rid of him too?
No... You've been
given your orders...
Find this object...
and dispose of it.
Fine... Just tell me what
I should be looking for.
Oh, no... That's a secret.
Then how on earth
am I supposed to find it?
You're a loyal dog... Even so,
Her Majesty hesitates to
share this bit of information
with you... And who are we to
question any decision of hers?
I suggest you do not attempt
a closer examination
of the item in question.
First, we need a better
understanding of the situation.
Meaning what, precisely, sir?
We need to know why Stanley
was murdered, obviously.
Was it simply that he was
in the wrong place
at the wrong time...?
Or was he killed as a result
of his work for the Queen.
Alright then, how do we go
about locating witnesses?
Assuming there are any.
We'll leave that part
to the Yard for now...
If you want to know about
Rome, you ask a Roman.
We know in whose territory
the murder occurred.
This place is foul.
I see you've finally
found your way
to my humble place of business.
It feels so strange that
we should meet under
such questionable
circumstances, my young lord.
And yet, inevitable,
don't you think...?
I must say, I always knew
someday it might come to this.
It might come to what??
Welcome...! to my humble
House of Pleasures...
darling Earl.
If you're trying to push
your wares... forget it...
The only thing you have
that I want is information.
So impatient for
such a young man...
If you think I know
something that would make it
worth your while to
venture so bravely
into my den of sin...
then you're quite right...
So you've already heard
what happened, then...
I thought as much...
But what should I expect
from the head of
the English branch
of the Chinese trading
company... Kunlun?
Much less from an officer of the
Shanghai Mafia's "Green Gang."
Oh dear, I never have
cared for fancy titles
such as that one...
They're so stiff and formal...
Don't you agree? Ran Mao?
I left you in charge of
the dealings in this area
for a reason... So...
I assumed you'd stay
informed about any disputes
that occurred
in your territory.
Naturally...
As per your original
instructions, my lord...
I could hardly forget about
the "protection fee"
I pay in order to be allowed
to conduct my business.
Well, then?
More importantly... I have
something to ask you.
What exactly are you
talking about?
Damn it, Lau!
Just talking through
his hat again,
it would seem...
How droll.
What do you say we go upstairs
for our little chat...?
It's a little bit stuffy
in here, don't you agree?
Perhaps if you found
another source of income...
you wouldn't have that
problem quite as often.
"One night, Zhuang Zhou
dreamed he was a butterfly...
a happily fluttering
butterfly..."
You know the rest.
There are people in this
world... lord Phantomhive...
Who find reality a bitter, and
unforgiving place to live,
if you can believe it.
I merely sell them dreams
of a less painful existence.
You know I'd help you
if I could, dearie,
but I'm afraid I've never
seen that fellow before
in my life.
God rest his soul.
Now, enough
about business.
How are you and Maria
doing these days?
Oh... Well, Ma'am...
Actually...
Goodness! Aren't you a quick
one! oh Congratulations!
Putting that horse
a bit before the cart...
but I suppose I understand...
Not everyone will, mind,
you being an inspector and all.
Best make an
honest woman of her soon.
Yes, ma'am,
I've already proposed.
And she said?
Wonderful news...!
You'll finally have a family...
After all those years as
an orphan with no kin
to call your own,
you must be overjoyed.
Thank you, ma'am.
And you're right.
That has affected my life.
That's why I'm determined...
to make the world safe
for children everywhere.
Oh, enough...
You'll make me cry... Now go.
I'll let you know if
I hear anything new, I promise.
Thank you, ma'am...
I would appreciate it.
Let's see... Nowadays,
I suppose all the gang fights
in the area have been
about drugs.
There's a new product that's
appeared on the market...
Somebody's been spreading
it around town
quite liberally
for a while now...
Frankly, it's becoming a bit
of an inconvenience for me.
A new product?
Yes... Apparently it is
cheaper, more effective,
and far easier
to transport than
common opium...
It goes by the name
of "Lady Blanc."
The white lady...?
Do you know why it was
given that name?
Is it important?
No...
What's the name of
the man they found
at the Regent's Canal Dock...?
Perhaps I will have
heard of him.
It was John Stanley...
I'm afraid it's likely that
was an alias, however.
He doesn't look
familiar to me...
And to think I flattered
myself I knew all the
small time drug pushers
in the area...
What about you...?
You recognize him?
Well, there you have it.
I'm looking for something this
man was supposed to've had.
He was carrying it
on his person.
Just "something?"
Yes... And it's possible this
'something' is the reason
he was killed in cold
blood... which is why...
there's something I'd
like you to do for me.
And what is that...?
My dear Earl.
I want you to spread
a rumor about me...
Let it be known that
I'm in possession
of something valuable
I took from the man
who was murdered.
Darling, that couldn't
be easier...
And may I be permitted
to know why?
If we spread that rumor
far enough,
the killer is sure to hear
it... and he'll have to doubt
the authenticity of
the article he stole
from John Stanley...
Then he'll be forced
to come after me for
the real thing.
Oh, I see... You're
using yourself as bait,
you clever thing, you...
A courageous act, indeed,
from the Queen's
loyal guard dog.
Speaking of which, my lord...
I've always wanted to
inquire about something...
How is it that you
remain so loyal to
your lord and master?
It seems to me she makes
unreasonable demands
of you.
I doubt you could
ever understand it.
You left your country
for another...
If you never put down roots,
you couldn't possibly
comprehend the depths
of mine, Lau.
You've got me there.
Now then, Cáo...
Let's do as the Earl
requested, shall we...?
and dangle a few little
rumors about him... So...
It seems he obtained
a document from
the dead man they found at
the Regent's Canal Dock.
A document, sir?
My dear Earl...
Of all the lovely games
we've played together
over the years,
this one may just prove
to be the most entertaining.
Hello there... young man.
Just now... I was talking
to my good friend,
Mr. Havock...
He said... you were
collecting rubbish
from the Canal
this morning and you saw
something odd.
Yeah...
Why don't you tell me?
I love a good story...
Especially one
about witches...
Did you really see the
"Cutty Sark."
Here we go!
Alright... I think
that'll do us.
Perfect. I've got it...
Oh, Mey Rin, I've been
meaning to ask,
you work at the
Phantomhive manor right?
Yes, I do...
Do you... think you
can get me some?
Some what?
Lady Blanc... Sebastian...
do you think the drug is named
after the woman in white
from the last case?
You're quite like a little
lost puppy sometimes...
You know that, don't you?
I may be one hell of
a good playing piece
to maneuver...
but I am still merely
a pawn in your game...
Would you ask a pawn
for advice on strategy?
I'm still alive, which can
mean one thing...
My wish is unfulfilled,
and our contract is in
full effect.
Yes, my lord... That's true.
In the meanwhile,
I will play the guard dog
like the Queen requests,
as so many have before...
As the Phantomhive heir,
it is my duty...
To follow in the footsteps
of my ancestors.
Yes... Just as
it's always been...
Nothing has changed at all...
Except this feeling.
Bad dog... No, get off me!!
Stupid mutt...! Let 'er go!
Pluto, you bad boy! No!
I said let go, you rabid cur!
Sebastian...! Do something
about that horrid creature.
Certainly.
Pluto... Kennel.
Can anyone tell me
what that was all about?
Can't be certain,
but maybe he's rutting.
Rutting after me?!
Was it me, or did he
seem to be concentrating
rather intensely on what
Mey Rin has in her pocket?
Oh...! Did he now?
Well that's it...!
You've got one of the
Funtom candies on you!
Forgot about this...
A nice lady gave it to me,
yes she did...
Said they're becoming
the rage all over London.
When we said we'd never
tried one, she insisted...
She was a really nice
lady, right Mey Rin...?
Said we had to try
one for ourselves...
Apparently they're so good,
even adults can't get enough...
And they make you
feel wonderful all over!
She says it's addicting!
Well... give us a ta--
Hold on just a minute!
Lord Phantomhive...
I think it is fairly safe to say
this sweet was not made
by the Funtom company.
It wasn't?
This wrapper is genuine...
but our quality control
is not so lax as to permit
a shipment of candies
so unshapely. I guarantee
you that, my lord.
This is...
Oh no! He ran out of time!
It's some kind of narcotic.
I believe it is derived
from opium. Perhaps
further refined, however.
I assume this is the
new drug Mr. Lau spoke of.
We've found Lady Blanc.
A visitor...? To see me?
You there! Get up...!
What are you doing
in my chair, sir...?
This is the outside of enough!
That desk is reserved
for the Commissioner
of Scotland Yard!
It's quite comfortable,
Sir Arthur...
I see why you guard it.
It's you...! What are you
doing here?
I bear you a message
from Her Majesty...
It's... quite delicate...
to say the least.
Get me to the sweets
factory...! And quickly!
Damn...! What are those
drugs doing in my product?
And the orders
from the Queen...
how is this all connected to
the dead man at the docks...?
Where's the link?
We're missing something here...
Some vital piece of the puzzle.
Ranmao,
Tell me, which do
you think is worse?
To be unable to wake
yourself from your dream...
Or to be unable to dream
of anything at all?
But of course, all things
that seem eternal...
whether waking or sleeping
must someday come
to an end.
Shi-dagu
Surrender!
Halt!
You are a reckless man...
Had anybody else been driving
you would have been trampled.
I knew full well who
you were and thats...
why you were stopped.
What goes on out there,
Sebastian?
I have stopped you,
Lord Phantomhive...
Please step down...
You're under arrest in
the name of her Majesty..
For violating the
Pharmacy Act.
Allow me, master.
So... You would dare detain me?
Do you have any idea the
magnitude of the insult
you offer the house
of my family?
And you, an untitled
police inspector, no less.
I'm afraid
that's correct, Ciel...
You're suspected of
collaboration with
that drug pusher,
Lau... We know
you've been distributing
a new form of narcotic.
With Lau...?
Hah! That's just ridiculous...
I'll admit that I've been
using him as a pawn
for some time...
But Randall knew
full well he was
running an opium den, and
he's never said a word.
If that's a problem,
then arrest Lau...
He knows I would
never protect him.
Lau runs his business
at his own risk,
and by his own hand.
You own a warehouse, yes?
Located down by the docks?
Yes.
That's where we found it...
A large hidden cache of the
opiate known as Lady Blanc.
Far too great an amount
for you to claim
recreational use...
Some of it already inside
Funtom sweet wrappers.
And Lau?
He's on the run...
The team we sent after him
suffered great casualties...
Practically an
admission of guilt.
What would you
have me do my lord?
Should I let them take me in
for now...? Or not?
Sebastian... My order--
Shut your mouth now...
you brat!
Abberline...
I thought I told you...
You were to separate the
boy Earl from his butler.
Randall...
I wonder that you would
choose to point a gun
at me, knowing what
it means to do so.
Well now, if you'd like to
resist, please be my guest, sir.
but I assure you,
that will be the end
of the Phantomhive
family name...
sullied as it is by now,
perhaps that's for the best.
You would dare?!
My orders come directly from
the Queen's representative
and he made Her Majesty's
intent quite clear.
Only the criminal
responsible would've known
what the Queen was seeking...
The rumor we heard
spoke of a document,
you see, and so we knew.
Therefore, please detain Lau...
and his benefactor, Phantomhive.
Oh... And don't worry
about having to conceal
what the charge is...
We'll find a suitable pretext.
Right...
And what shall I do with
them after the arrest?
Ciel Phantomhive,
you are under arrest...
In her Majesty's name...
and I do hereby suspend...
all of your privileges
and authority.
If you defy the law
in this matter...
you shall be stripped of
your title for high treason.
Furthermore... The man known
to the state as Lau...
Opium smuggler and head
of the English branch
of Kunlun...
shall be summarily executed for
his crimes against the crown.
Lord Phantomhive... will
you confess to knowledge
of Lau's whereabouts
or the whereabouts
of the letter we know
you have concealed?
I'm afraid... I can
tell you nothing.
A letter...? That must
be the missing piece.
I should very much like to push
you on that bit of evasion...
Sadly, Her Majesty forbids
torturing a peer of the realm...
However there are no such
rules about butlers.
Offer no resistance.
When the time is right,
I'll call for you...
And then we will show them...
what becomes of those
who humiliate me...
Do you understand?
Yes, my lord.
If your intent is to torture me,
you'll need better technique
than that.
The only pain I truly feel is
when I instruct my master
on the concept of dancing.
I'm fairly certain the
prase "two left feet"
was invented precisely for him.
So a beating of two
compared to that...
all I can do is laugh
at your attempts.
Next time on Black Butler,
"His Butler, Escaping."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.