Bloody hell...
this wire's done for.
Oh, not the rats again!
This is getting ridiculous,
I mean I heard they'd
been plaguing London lately,
but I never expected
them to be such a problem
this far out of the city.
Now I've got you...rat!
Uh oh!
Looks like it got away...
Hee-hee!
What're you laughing for...?!
Are you trying to kill us,
too, you idiot?!
Look! There's another one!
Catch it!
Quite the commotion
going on out there...
It seems you're experiencing
a rat problem as well.
Speaking of which, how long
will you let the vermin
run wild? Filthy monsters...
Someone really ought
to take care of them,
don't you think?
And 'someone' will...
He's just waiting
for the opportune moment.
Indeed... He prefers
to settle things with one blow.
Will you pass on this turn,
too, Lord Phantomhive?
I'll pass... It's my policy
not to shoot if I know
that I'll miss.
That's all very well...
But when will you
handle the problem?
Anytime you like.
The rats will soon come looking
for their forbidden cheese...
And I hold the key
to the storehouse.
Even so... Locating the nest
and eliminating the vermin
promises to be a tedious task...
you should concentrate on
preparing me a suitable reward.
You're a vulture.
Sir Randall... I'd be careful
how you smear my family name.
Heh, you're
in trouble now, Randall...
What next, Lord Phantomhive?
It's time to put an end to this
worthless game, don't you think?
How soon can you
secure the payment?
Tonight...
I'll have it by then.
Then I'll send
a carriage for you later.
We can even prepare some
light entertainment for you...
Does that sound good?
You passed your turn twice,
and now you're after them
all in one go??!
Naturally.
Careful, or your greed
will undo you.
Am I undone?
Your tea. We have a special
Darjeeling blend to offer
from Fortnum and Mason today.
Smells lovely... Tea can
be excellent when made well.
Grell.
Yes, my lady?
Learn something
from Sebastian.
Yes.
Just look at him...
I mean... this physique...!
You should quit
this country job
and come work for me
in the city!
Madam Red...
Oh, sorry...!
I couldn't help it...
He looked like
he needed a physical...
Just a doctor's habit.
So, do you believe the
drug trafficker you're after
was one of your guests today?
Perhaps.
Why not leave
the extermination to Lau...?
A rat knows best where
a rat's nest is, doesn't he?
I'm but a tame guinea pig
dedicated to my lord.
If the earl instructs me
not to act...
I'm bound to do nothing.
Watch it...! You'd best
keep your filthy paws off
my darling nephew!
You wound me...! I would never
paw at him in his own home,
dear Madam!
Are you saying you would
if you were elsewhere?! Careful!
You're on thin ice now, sir!
Master?
You'd better be! I hope you
understand how protective I am
of my dear nephew!
The rats are here.
It went that waaaay!
And here, too.
Master? Today's dessert...
It's a deep dish pie prepared
with fresh apples and raisins.
It will be ready soon...
Would you like to eat
with your guests?
Bring it to my study...
I'm done here.
Certainly, my lord.
That's enough of that.
Now stop playing
and get to work.
Sir.
Finally, some peace and quiet.
Young Master...?
I've brought your pie
and afternoon tea.
This is terrible.
The refreshments will
all be wasted now.
The policeman
of England's underworld.
One of the nobles who have done
the royal family's dirty work
for generations.
"The Queen's Guard Dog," tasked
with disposing of anyone
who disagrees with her.
Just how many nicknames
do you have...?
And how many families
have you crushed...
Ciel Phantomhive?
I thought it would be you...
You shame your family,
Azzurro Vanel
Come now... my little
Lord Phantomhive...
Do you know how hard it is
for the Italian mafia here?
You Englishmen have nothing
but tea on the brain.
It's difficult to penetrate
those small minds of yours,
so we have to think
outside the box to make money...
So we found the drug trade.
The Pharmacy Act of 1868
listed opium as
a restricted substance...
It is the Queen's decree...
and I will eliminate those drugs
and the vermin who sell them.
Oh-You know, this is why
I hate all you Englishmen...
The queen this, the queen
that- The way you act,
you would think
she was your own mother.
You line your pockets while
pretending the whole time
you're better than the rest
of us... but in the end,
we're no different
from each other...
Why can't we get along?
I've left orders about your key.
If I don't come back,
my servants will make sure
the authorities get it...
I'm sorry... I have no
interest in 'getting along'
with someone like you.
You brat
don't underestimate me!
My men are already waiting
at your estate...
Where's the key?
Spit it out soon, or your
servants will start dying
one by one.
Oh, I think
they'll be all right...
but you had better hope your
lap dogs know how to fetch.
Did you hear that...?
Time for talk is over!
Oh dear...
This is most troubling.
Where could the master
have been taken?
Sebastiaaaaaan!
I just found a letter,
yes I did!
Addressed to whom?
Uh... to the servants...
of the Earl of Phantomhive.
Mey Rin, the letter please.
Letter...? Oh! Yes sir!
If you want to return
your Master safely,
come to Nova Garden Bethnal
Green as soon as possible...
Goodness, what a
dreadfully written letter.
Sebastian!
What is going on here?
Sorry for the noise, my lady...
I assure you, nothing's wrong.
Please don't concern yourself.
Nothing? Are you sure?
Everyone, I have
business to attend to.
Would you mind
cleaning this up?
So when you say 'clean', uh...
That means we can eat it...!
Right...? Sebastian?
Sorry, I missed.
What do you mean you missed...?!
You are complete idiots!
I should have never
hired scum like you...
Just get back here!
Um, sir... something's off...
I see something...
What's that?!
Aw, what's wrong...?
You little girls
see a bear in the woods?
What's happening-
did someone find you?
Talk to me.
Hurry it up!
It's coming... closer!
That's it- I've had enough
of your games already!
No good...it's here!
Ah... Hello...? What happened?
That's too bad...
Sounds like your little
game of fetch is over.
Just shut-a your mouth,
you damn brat!
You listen to me...!
If one you
don't answer right now,
I swear I'll kill you!
Hello.
Who's this?
Pardon me, but I represent
the Phantomhive estate...
I was wondering if my master
might be available.
Hello...?
Is anyone there...? Hello?
Woof.
Very good, young master...
I will come to get you
momentarily.
Thank you for the use
of your field telephone.
And now, there are a few things
I'd like to ask you about,
if that's alright.
First... I'd like to know
who you work for.
Hurry up, now... I'm not
exactly what you would call
a patient man.
And you do remember what
happened to Humpty Dumpty,
don't you?
Ou-our employer's name
is Azzurro Vanel...
He has a hideout
up in the city.
It's in the East End.
We just work for him!
But of course. I understand...
I'm very sorry to have
interrupted your work gentlemen.
I'll let you go now.
Have a safe trip.
Oh dear... Look at
how late it's gotten.
If I don't move quickly,
we shall never have
dinner ready in time.
Are we certain nothing's wrong?
If that butler says
everything's fine,
I'm inclined to believe him.
He's been in the earl's
service for so long...
and it's quite plain to see
there's some sort
of unshakeable bond
between those two.
You can always find him at the
earl's side... Like a shadow.
'So long'? But Sebastian didn't
arrive until two years ago.
That's not much time at all.
Oh, really...? How odd...
My memory is so unreliable...
Isn't that right, Ranmao?
Useless.
Listen up the Phantomhive boy
has help on the way.
Move it! Tighten security
at the gate...!
Not so much as
a single rat gets through.
My, my... what a splendid home.
'Ey! Who the hell's this guy?!
Ah, my apologies...you see...
I represent
the Phantomhive household.
Oh dear... We need
Sebastian here.
Where did he go now?
I wish I knew!
I don't care where he is
right now or what he's doing.
This is all
I'm worried about...!
Does 'clean it up' mean
we can eat the pie or not...?!
I have to knoooow!
I'm sure just one bite each
would be okay.
No, Finny...!
You know how Sebastian is!
If we eat something
we're not supposed to,
he'll bake us into
his next pie!
You need to
calm yourself down, Bardroy...
A soothing drink might help...
Here, give this a try.
Milk...! Like
that's gonna help me!
Milk is an important part
of your diet...!
It'll help you grow strong
bones, yes it will!
My arm...!
He shattered the bone!
Pardon me...but I'm in
a bit of a hurry. 5:34.
Move, damn it...!
Call in the boys
from the west tower...!
We need to rip
this bastard apart!
An entire swarm of rats...
I'll get nowhere at this rate.
That's it...!
I'm going to eat it!
Mey Rin, tea...!
Finny, go get the silver!
Sir, yes, sir!
It should be right in here...
What the--?
Is somethin' wrong?
I don't understand...
The silver's supposed
to be here... But I don't
see a single knife or fork.
Who the hell is he?!
Now, now. If I couldn't
do this much, at least...
Then what kind of
butler would I be?
Oh dear... That took
longer than I thought.
Already 5:43.
I have come
to retrieve my master.
Is this a joke...?
I was expecting a giant
and instead I get
some scrawny dandy
in a tailcoat.
Who are you anyway...?
There's no way
that you're just a butler.
No sir...You see,
I'm simply one hell
of a butler... I promise.
Yeah, sure...
It doesn't matter anyway.
I have no intention
of fighting you.
Not yet...
But you better have
what I asked for.
Yes I do... It's right here.
Wha--
Aw, sorry, dandy...
I really am...
This round's mine.
There's no way I was
going up against Phantomhive,
lord of games, without
a trump card hidden.
I damaged the goods
a little bit,
but that's all right...
I'm sure you'll fetch a pretty
price even in this condition.
Don't worry.
You have so many enemies.
I doubt you'll be alive
all that much longer.
All right... I'm tired
of messing around.
How much longer are you
planning to play dead?
Not long.
But how-...how are you-...?
You just...
Guns today are much more
efficient than they used to be.
They can shoot
so many bullets now.
Perhaps you'd like these back?
What are you doing?! Kill him!
Oh dear,...What
an awful thing to do
to a perfectly good tailcoat.
You could have
avoided that... Idiot.
Master... How unfortunate.
They don't seem to have
taken good care of you.
No...! Stay back!
You look like a helpless little
child all bound up like that...
But then, I guess
that's appropriate.
I-If you come any closer,
I'll shoot him!
Can we move this along...?
His breath smells awful.
But if I come any closer,
he might kill you.
Well then?... Are you saying
you want to break the contract?
No, of course not...
Nothing has changed.
I remain your
faithful servant, lord.
What the hell kind of nonsense
are you two talking about?!
Master, you know what
you have to do...
now just say the words.
This is an order...!
Save me, now!
No! It's oveeeeer!
What the--
...But that's impossible!
Are you looking for this?
Here then... let me
give it back to you.
I must say, the game wasn't as
much fun this time, Sebastian.
No, wait, come back...!
Work for me!
Be my bodyguard and I'll pay
you ten times what he does...
All right then...
twenty times...!
And you can have all the liquor
and women you want too!
I'm sorry Mr. Vanel...
It's an attractive offer,
but I have no interest in such
materialistic things...
You see...I am simply...
one hell of a butler.
Uh... Right...ok...
As long as my master
holds the contract...
I am his loyal servant.
A wish. A sacrifice.
And this... All of these things
keep me bound
to Lord Phantomhive.
Until the day
I swallow his soul.
Unfortunately for you...
...this game is over.
You're awake, master?
Master! Welcome home, sir!
Oh-dear!
Master Ciel, you're injured!
I just tripped and fell...
It's nothing to worry about...
What...? You don't believe
what your master tells you?
Oh, no...we do!
It's just, you look so cute,
being held like a baby and all!
Put... me... down!
Stop looking at me like that...!
Honestly...
Master...
I'm so terribly sorry.
I've committed
a blunder unacceptable for
a Phantomhive Butler...
How can I ever atone?
I hang my head in shame...
dinner is not ready.
At the suggestion
of Lady Elizabeth,
Master Ciel's betrothed,
we will be holding a ball...
Unfortunately, my young master
cannot dance
to save his life...
His attempts are so
pathetic that calling in
a dancing master
would be too embarrassing.
It seems as if I shall
have to rid my lord
of his two left feet myself.
Next time on Black Butler...
"His Butler, Omnipotent."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.