Maria...! Maria, are you there?
Oh, Hello there Ms. Luida...
I've brought you
some beef stew dearie...
It seems I've made
far too much...
Maybe you'll be sweet and
help me finish the rest...?
What is this? Where did
all these gifts come from?
Oh my, that looks
like a baby's rattle.
Who could have
sent you all this?
Finni, help me with this!
Yeah, okay!
Oh! ...Don't forget
his under clothes!
Tanaka. How is it coming?
Young master...
Everything has been carried
out to your specifications.
My lord Pardon me...
I've taken care of our lodgings.
Very well Sebastian.
I say, young master... where
exactly are you two going
on this trip of yours?
You mean to tell me
you've been helping out
with the packing all this
time without knowing that?!
Paris.
Her Majesty arrived in
Paris three days ago...
She should be viewing
the Exposition now.
I'm sure the hotel will be
heavily guarded, so we--
Master?
Yes, what is it?
Well, sir... your mind
seems to be adrift.
It's what Lau said.
That the Queen wants
to plunge Europe,
no, the entire world into war.
Is that why you seek an
audience with Her Majesty?
No.
Well then... Is it
because your heart
was so moved by
the death of Abberline?
It isn't... They have all been
my pawns from the beginning.
You should keep your
distance from me...
If you want to live.
He was a pawn...
A disobedient pawn who
ignored my will and kept
sticking his nose in.
The same goes for Lau... If you
can't control your pawns...
well then,
you can't play the game.
That's all there is to it.
The Eiffel Tower marks the
entrance to the Exhibition...
Then there is the
Champ de Mars, which houses
the Palace of Fine Arts.
Then we have Machinery Hall,
where one can see the pinnacle
of modern technology.
There's an exhibition
on horticulture.
The Esplanade des Invalides
features a colonial exhibition.
From what I've heard,
it features a reproduction
of the ruins of Angkor,
along with some lively
folk dancing.
Additionally,
I understand that
Buffalo Bill's Wild West
Cowboy Show
is here all the way
from the States.
This is quite a
special occasion...
Perhaps we should look
around some more, my lord...
as research for the company.
You're sure?
Yes, they say there's
a stuffed angel at
the Palace of Wonders!
That I must see!
A stuffed angel? Really?
Pathetic. It's nothing more
than a stuffed monkey...
What a bore. Let's move on.
What's happening?!
What is that thing?
Calm yourself,
young master.
But this--
You're used to living
in the darkness...
This should be nothing... The
lights have only dimmed a bit.
You should leave here now...
Master, please entrust
this situation to my care.
He's right... I'm used
to living in the darkness.
My soul has been mired
in this darkness...
for a long, long time.
Ciel...
Since that day...
Forever after...
I've been running...
In the dark.
It's so bright. Can it be...?
Is this really
the world I live in?
My, you're in a hurry,
aren't you?
Is it you?!
Ciel... It's been a while.
Your Majesty!
Quite a view, wouldn't you say?
As we face the next century,
Europe is on the verge
of change... However...
We are stained.
We are stagnating.
We are unclean.
The state must be wiped clean.
No creation without
destruction. The new century
must be pure... and so I
have cleansed the house
that has seen fit to sully
our great country.
The house of Phantomhive.
How very tasteless.
What's this?
London Bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down.
Lon--
She's here.
I know it now. It's her...
Might I ask
you something?
What is it?
You didn't simply kill them...
Why did you have to make it
a slaughter?
You should watch how you
speak to your queen, Ciel...
I cleansed them.
Burning your subjects alive?!
That's what you
consider cleansing?!
And you don't?
Never!
But Ciel... I was only...
Only paying tribute
to the Phantomhives for the
loyalty they showed me
for so long.
You what?!
Terribly surprised, aren't you?
Her Majesty is the
absolute picture of youth.
Ashe!
Her great loss, the loss
of her beloved husband,
ended Her Majesty's happiness.
She was a truly wretched
creature, pained and mourning
her husband's death to
a degree that threatened
even her own survival.
Indeed, her grief was
so great that she tried
to end her life.
In an attempt to save her,
I joined his body with hers
that they might live
together forever.
You what--?!
I can tell that my late
husband is pleased with
what I have done
to keep us together...
I can feel his body still...
His heart beats inside me.
Thump... thump...
the throbbing of life.
Truly, what greater joy
can there be than
being made one with the
person that you love...?
I did the same for your
parents... They left this world
together as one. So it
wasn't such a ghastly death
as you imagine... Come Ciel...
Surely you must agree?
The Queen and her husband
firmly intend to guide England
to a world of perfect light...
a world of beauty and harmony.
That aim has purged Her
Majesty of her impurities...
And now she is the
chaste girl that you see.
Hers is a truly noble goal...
She is indeed a most worthy
master for an angel.
You? An angel?
Surely you're joking!
It's time, Ashe...
Unsheathe your blade...
Ciel deserves to see
the end of it.
Ashe's blade is a thing
of true beauty...
It will usher forth the
brightness and purity of
a new century.
I shall draw my sword
against thy wisdom...
and I shall punish the
beast within thee...
And then I shall bring thee
down into the pit.
May the great beauty of Heaven
greet you, Ciel Phantomhive.
An impressive sword... but
utterly useless if you're
unable to land a blow.
Master...
I think this may be
the end of our journey.
Now... my orders?
Ciel, no...
Sebastian... Kill Ashe.
Is that all...
young master?
No, also... kill the Queen!
Ciel!
Yes, my lord.
No stop... This is dreadful...!
Please stop him...!
Do something,
please! Ciel!
Oh dear!
Watch out!
No...! Sebastian, stop!
Oh? Why?
We're starting to
attract attention...
At this rate, the entire
city will be out here soon.
And why should we worry? They're
only puny humans, after all.
No...! We are withdrawing!
He has angel wings!
Master... Why did you stop me?
I told you, we were attracting
too much attention...
that's all.
All right. I see.
You want to
say something?
What you wanted from me...
was vengeance against the ones
who dragged you into hell.
Did it mean nothing... the
vow you swore to me then.
You have summoned
me here today.
That can never be changed...
and nothing sacrificed
can ever be regained.
Now choose.
I order you.
Kill them!
I will become your sword...
I will carry out your
revenge... In exchange...
You want my soul...?
You are welcome to it.
You have no doubt?
None at all.
On that day,
I thought you had
no doubt in your mind.
Will you maintain your
loyalty to the Queen,
even after learning the truth?
I never even felt a scrap of
loyalty to her to begin with...
Never... I merely
acted as the head
of the Phantomhive
family that's all.
Very well... so you
value your soul now?
My soul? What would
I want with that...?
You're being stupid...
Do you honestly think that--
You seem a bit
tired... my lord.
Perhaps it would be
a good idea now
to return to your room.
What a loathsome city.
Since that day...
you've spent your time
buttoning my shirts...
I never imagined having
a demon for a butler...
But you've done
remarkably well.
After all what kind
of butler would I be?
That's quite enough
for tonight sir... now...
You really should get some
sleep... young master.
Please just let it all go. May
your dreams be pleasant ones.
You do have a chance,
Ciel... to move forward,
and build a future for
yourself from the wreckage
of your past...
Don't ever forget that...
Promise me, you won't...
I have no future.
Give up your title as her dog.
You don't have to keep it.
It's not you!
Sebastian...?
Sebastian!
Hey, Sebastian,
where are you?
Come on, don't you hear me?
Sebastian!
I'm Earl Phantomhive.
In room 702.
Do you know
where my butler is?
One moment, please, my lord.
His mark wasn't gone...
but still....
Please just let it all go. May
your dreams be pleasant ones.
He would never wish me
pleasant dreams.
And then he said 'let it
all go.'... Was that...
A farewell?
London isn't that far...
I'm certain I can
get there on my own.
Please take me
to the Port of Calais.
Really...?
And may I ask what exactly
you're willing to pay?
How much do you want?
Here we are.
Pardon? I asked for
the Port of Calais.
So sorry, but I live elsewhere.
Let me down!
Well kid I'm sure you'll
eventually hit the port
that you need...
That's assuming you keep
walking straight, of course.
Get back here...!
Do what I paid you for,
you bounder!
I would like a room
for the night.
You'll be paying?
I can't right now...
but I'll be sending money
from London later.
Are you toying with me?!
I am Ciel Phantomhive...
Everyone knows that name...!
What kind of business
are you running?
Haven't you ever heard
of my company?!
Take a look at this ring...!
This ring has been passed
down through generations!
All right,
I'll take that, then.
In exchange for the ring,
I'll let you stay...
The gem isn't bad kid...
so I'll throw in breakfast, too.
Excuse me?!
You honestly think I would
give this to rubbish
like you?
I'm so hungry.
It's cold... Would you
like to come here?
Now even you're trying to
make a fool out of me?!
Get back here!
Oh, it was right here...
I was this close.
I wandered everywhere...
unable to find it.
But it was right here...
all along... so close to me.
Oh, no!
Water! Water!
Get some water!
The infernal cries of a
soulless beast echo through
the smoldering streets
of London...
and I find myself
without a master...
would you by chance
wish to enter into
a contract with me?...
why not... when the
moment of truth comes,
I shall plunge you
into a deep fathomless
soothing darkness
as gently as possible...
the pain shall be brief...
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler,
Up in Flames."
You see I'm simply
one hell of a demon.