Think carefully... Should you
reject the faith even this
once, the gates of Paradise will
forever be out of your reach.
Do you think...one who
was among the faithful...
would ever go so far as to
summon someone like you?
I'll ask but once more... Do you
wish to form a contract with me?
I do...! Now, stop asking
these tedious questions,
and let me know
if we have a deal!
Master... It is time
for you to wake up.
For breakfast today, we have
a lightly poached salmon
accompanied by a delicate
mint salad. I can also offer
toast, scones,
or pan de com pahn yah...
Which dish would you
care for this morning?
A scone.
Today you have a meeting with
Mr. Hughes, the authority on
the history of the Roman
Empire... and this evening,
Mr. Damiano of
the Poseidon Company
will be paying you a visit.
Oh... Is that the man I have
in charge of stuffed animals
at my factory in India?
Yes. I'm told he's Italian...
We will, of course,
offer him all the hospitality
the estate can provide.
I know this smell...
Is this tea Earl Grey?
Yes... from Jackson's
of Piccadilly.
I shall wait for you
at the dining table, master.
Well thrown, my lord. Even so...
let's save the games for later.
Yes... I suppose
you're right, Sebastian.
My butler is an able man.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! What was that
for, Master...? What did I do?
Nothing... I don't need
to justify my actions.
There you are. Have you finished
weeding the courtyard, Finny?
Mey Rin... have you
washed all the bedding?
Um, well...
Bardroy... shouldn't you be
preparing for tonight's dinner?
Mr. Tanaka...
Well... I suppose
you're all right as you are.
Now all of you...We have
no time for thumb twiddling
this morning...
So get to work!
Yes, Sir!
Simply hopeless.
The silver is polished
to a spotless shine.
The tablecloth is crisp,
clean, and wrinkle free...
There is not a single bruised
blossom among Master's
favorite white
roses. And finally,
the highest quality ingredients
have been gathered to prepare
a first-rate dinner.
The table is perfection...
This will be an elegant
Phantomhive welcome.
Still so much to do,
and he calls me now?
A guest is comin'? All right,
then this is our chance...
Sebastian looks
down on us all the time...
today we'll be so perfect,
he won't even know
what hit him. Yeah,
that's what he's gonna say!
AAAH!
That's for him to say, not you.
Ooh! That's a good idea!
Right, we have to stop relyin'
on Sebastian for everything.
It's settled, then.
We got a plan of attack!
Let's get to it!
I'm a bit hungry... I'd like
something sweet to eat.
You shouldn't eat now, Master...
You don't want to spoil
your appetite for dinner
with your guest this evening.
I don't care about that...
Make me a parfait.
I'm sorry, sir.
Fine then... about the portrait
in the hallway...
Yes?
Take it down.
I am Ciel Phantomhive,
son of Vincent
and I am the head
of the house now.
Consider it done, my lord.
Now...
How exactly... Did
this... Happen?
I thought things
would go faster if I used
extra-strength weed-killer
on the garden!
I was trying to reach
the tea set we use for guests,
but I tripped
and the cabinet fell!
There was a lot of meat
to be cooked for dinner,
and it was going
to take a long time...
so, uh, I used
me flame thrower.
We're so sorry!
We didn't mean to!
Our guest will arrive just
after six. At most, we have
two hours left. Not enough time
to replace the tea set
or find premium meats.
What should I do?
Calm down, all of you.
Perhaps you should try taking
a page out of Tanaka's book
and start behaving like--
Everyone... listen closely
and do exactly as I say,
understand?
We must be quick about this.
We might save this night yet.
How impressive!
Hello. Welcome, sir.
This is called
a stone garden...
It is a traditional
feature in Japan.
Ah, prodigioso...! Wonderful.
Truly, an elegant garden.
We thought it appropriate
to serve dinner
al fresco this evening...
Allow me to escort you inside
until the meal is ready.
I should have expected
this from a Phantomhive.
I cannot wait to see
what else is in store.
Whew, we actually did it!
Who would have thought
a dozen bags of gravel
could turn into an
amazing garden?!
Naturally we were able
to handle this...
We serve the Phantomhive family,
after all. There's still
work to be done... Let's take
care of it while the master
is talking business with
his guest... Look sharp, now.
Right!
The progress we've been making
with the East India factory
is quite astonishing...
We already have the makings
of a top-notch staff.
"Bewitched by the eyes of the
dead." What terrible luck...
It appears I lose a turn.
Right now is the perfect time...
We should begin expanding
the company and building
a strong labor f--
Go on. It's your turn.
Oh, yes... I just
spin this, then?
Okay, there. Five spaces...
Now, what I wanted to ask you...
Perhaps you could contribute
another 12,000 pounds
to support our expansion?
I believe it would be
quite a profitable venture
for you, my lord...
and I would consider it
an honor to help expand
the Funtom Company into--
"Lose a leg in the
enchanted forest."
Huh?
And it's your turn again...
I lost a turn, remember?
Oh... I see...
Right... I move six.
You don't... That's three.
What? But...
You lost a leg,
if you'll recall.
Now you only move
half the number of spaces.
Oh my... This is a gruesome
board game, isn't it...?
Is there no way for me
to restore my leg, then?
I'm afraid once something
is truly lost, sir...
That one can never
get it back again.
"Your body is burnt
by raging flames."
How is it going?
I'm doin' it like you said to...
This really what you want?
Yes... that looks excellent.
Sebastian! Found em!
Oh, honestly... How many
times have I told you
not to run inside
the manor, Mey Rin?
I'm so sorry, sir...!
My glasses cracked,
and I can't see a thing!
These are the last items
we needed for dinner.
Splendid work, everyone...
And now, I believe you can
leave the rest of it to me
and relax for a bit...
But I need you to do well--Very
well--during dinner tonight.
He said it twice.
Ooo, that's serious.
Pardon the interruption,
but dinner is served.
Ooh... dining out in that
exquisite stone garden...
Shall we go, my lord?
Very well.
We'll finish the game later
Oh... Is there any
real need to finish it?
It's obvious I'm going to lose.
I'm not in the habit
of abandoning games
halfway through.
How childish.
Uh...I...I mean,
sometimes it takes
a child's eyes to see
what's really important
...It's a true gift.
Maybe that's what's made
the Phantomhives
the nation's foremost toymakers.
It certainly impresses me.
On tonight's menu is a dish of
finely sliced raw beef donburi,
courtesy of our chef, Bardroy.
"Don"...?
A pile of raw beef...
and this is dinner?
Yes. But surely
you have heard of it...?
This, good sir, is a
traditional Japanese delicacy,
a dish offered as a sign of
gratitude to someone who
has accomplished important
work... That, sir...
is the wonder of donburi!
Oh, donburi!
This is a token from our
master... to show his thanks
for all of your hard work
on the company's behalf...
He wanted you to know that
it's much appreciated.
Now that's our Sebastian,
for you!
He saved the day!
Excellent! What an inspired
idea! The legendary
Phantomhive hospitality
in action.
The vintage we are pouring
tonight was specially selected
to complement the flavor of soy
sauce...Mey Rin...Now, Mey Rin.
Why are you just
standing there...?
Pour the man a glass of wine.
Of course, yes sir!
'ey...Is it just me, or is
Mey Rin acting a little strange?
Sebastian's watching me...
I can't take it.
Don't look at me that way!
Mei Rin, stop it...! Can't you
see you're spilling the wine!?
Huh...? Where did
the tablecloth go?
A speck of dirt...
most unsightly...
I had the cloth removed
so it wouldn't distract us...
Think nothing of it.
Please accept my apologies,
sir... Do continue...
Enjoy the meal
at your leisure.
Oh...oh my!
Lord Phantomhive,
once again you have
truly impressed me.
What an able butler
you've acquired.
Pay him no mind. He merely acted
as befits one of my servants.
My master is quite correct
about that... Naturally.
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.
That was a thoroughly enjoyable
dinner, my lord. Now then...
about the contract.
Before we discuss that,
we must finish the game.
Yes, of course... I do have
a pressing appointment...
Perhaps another ti--
Children can be very demanding
about their games...
Surely you wouldn't
want me to get upset.
No...no, of course not.
Perhaps you would permit me
to use your telephone?
I've brought some tea
for you and my lord.
I'll be right back.
What is this...?
It smells terribly weak.
Out of consideration
for our guest,
I've brought some Italian tea.
Italian?
Italians drink more
coffee than tea, sir,
so finding high-quality Italian
tea can be difficult...
This particular selection is
not to your liking, master?
No, it is not...
I don't like it at all.
I'll see to the
dessert preparations.
Good... We must show him
every available hospitality.
The Phantomhive family
is known for its courtesy.
Yes... my young lord.
I'm tired of babysitting
this child Earl...
Yes, I've already sold off the
factory... Now all that's left
is to pocket the extra cash...
I'm trying to squeeze
more out of the brat right now.
The employees...?
Who cares about them?
Never mind... The rest
of the formalities
are for you to deal with...
No... it'll be easy.
Please... he's only a child.
Impossible...
I'm seeing things.
"Bewitched by the eyes
of the dead."
No, that's ridiculous.
Huh.
Not here either... or here.
This manor is like a giant maze.
I can't even find
the drawing room.
"Bewitched by the eyes
of the dead."
Stay away from meeee!
That's odd... Was that
our guest I heard just now?
Hey! We need to move this
or Sebastian'll start
yelling again!
Right!
How embarrassing...! I really
messed up this time...!
Ooh... But at least I was able
to get close to Sebastian!
Ooooh! What a shameful,
dirty thought...!
What kind of
lecherous maid am I?
You lose one turn.
Sir, are you all right?
His right leg!...
It's twisted 'round!
What happened to it?
Hey, what's wrong?
Our guest!
Something happened!
"And now you lose one leg
in the enchanted forest."
Sir... Um, sir...come back.
Surely you aren't
leaving the manor yet, sir.
We haven't given you the full
Phantomhive treatment yet...
We still have to serve dessert.
You've lost a leg, remember?
Now you can only move half
the number of spaces.
So why not just relax a bit
and make yourself at home?
Damn... it's too dark.
Is this a cupboard?
Damn... These are really
tight quarters. What's this?
It smells like sugar.
What an impatient guest
we have... You couldn't even
restrain yourself until the
dessert was out of the oven.
The...the oven?! Open up...!
Please open the door!
Perhaps the Italians aren't
familiar with our customs...
There's plum pudding...
Mincemeat pie...
There are many traditional
desserts in England
that make use of meat...
I find them all quite tasty.
"Your body is burnt
by raging flames."
What was that...?
Someone screamed.
Dunno... Oh...! Hi Sebastian!
Thank you for your hard
work today... As a reward,
how would you like some
lemon meringue pie?
The sugar will
give you energy.
Pie for us, Sebastian?!
You're such a nice person.
You're not all bad! Who knew?
Thank you so much, Sebastian!
Oh yes... and Bard...? A workman
will be by in the morning...
When he arrives, kindly let
him know we'll be needing
our oven thoroughly cleaned.
Huh...? The oven?
Mr. Damiano... I hope
you enjoyed your stay
and the Phantomhive
family hospitality...
all the way down to your bones.
Mamma miaaaa!
What an unattractive scream...
He sounds almost like a pig
taken off to slaughter.
What presumption!
First, he sells the East Indian
factory without telling me...
And then he dares
to ask for more money.
Did he think to
retain my trust?
I'm afraid once something
is truly lost...
one can never
get it back again.
It would appear we'll be needing
to hang new wallpaper as well...
Mama! Papa!
The new head of the
Phantomhive estate...Huh.
My young master, Ciel,
has another name...
He is also known as
the Queen's Guard Dog
for his role in policing
England's seedy underground...
His small body houses
great determination...
You will marvel at the bravery
he displays when dealing with
a drug trafficking ring...
Also, feel free to admire
my notable skills
with the silver,
upon which I stake my honor as
a Phantomhive butler.
Next time, on Black Butler
"His Butler... Strongest"
You see, I'm simply
one hell of a butler.