Ciel...
He disappeared
for a while after
the estate burned down
and his parents died.
Eventually,
he did return home.
But by then he had
stopped smiling.
I love him... My Ciel.
And I love his smile.
But... For some reason...
We keep going in circles.
What can I do?
How can I help him?
How do I get
his smile back?
Ciel.
You lost your parents....
Your home...
And this time... you stand
to lose Lady Elizabeth?
Sebastian!
Take that back...
right now!
What do you mean?
I don't like you taunting me!
Master... earlier you informed
me you had some business
to take care of.
This business of yours, did it
include endangering yourself
in a misguided effort to
rewrite the past, I mean?
Do you remember what you said
at the Frost Fair...?
About your body...
about your ring.
What you said... was both had
been shattered and reborn...
And that you no longer had any
fear of being broken yourself.
I remember... You don't
need to remind me.
Build it up with iron and steel,
iron and steel, iron and steel.
Build it up with
iron and steel--
This means
they defeated Grell?
Interesting... They appear
to be controlled
through the singing of that
song. In which case...
Iron and steel
will bend and bow...
Bend and bow,
bend and bow.
Iron and steel will bend
and bow, my fair lady.
Iron and steel will bend and
bow, bend and bow, bend and bow.
Iron and steel will bend
and bow, my fair lady.
Who are you calling a lady?!
Now my young master...
Let us go.
I think not.
Ciel Phantomhive...
You are now the
property of my master.
Property...?!
Who do you think you--
The proof is there... You
are marked by the very ring
you're wearing.
I know what it is.
That is a Hope Piece...
The same gem my master
sends as a token to those
who are destined
to become his dolls.
What master?
It's been decided.
Ciel Phantomhive is going to
become a doll. An exquisite
doll made up of silver and gold.
Silver and gold will be stolen
away, stolen away, stolen away.
He was indeed stolen away.
However, I am
thinking to myself,
Ciel Phantomhive will return,
Whether he wants to or not.
There we are... You're safe.
What about Lizzie...?!
She's still in there!
Did I order you to solve the
recent string of kidnappings,
or didn't I?
Lizzie is one of
the kidnap victims...!
Saving her is the first pri--
If an order negates the
contract... I cannot obey it.
Your first priority is always
orders from the queen...
Similarly... my first
priority is your life.
I've devoted myself to your
service and protection...
It's been more than
two years now.
I can't very well let
someone steal you away
after all this time,
now can I?
Master?
Apparently the
Hope Piece is what marks
the 'master's' next target...
And I have two of them...
I guess that means I've
been doubly marked...
Protecting me will
be a difficult task.
I'm not afraid
of hard work.
Pluto?
I searched the mansion,
top to bottom...
I wasn't able find any sign
of Lady Elizabeth.
That leaves one place. She must
be in that sealed up tower.
Hey, now, calm down...!
What's wrong with you, puppy?
That's a surprise.
You're still alive?
Wait a second...
A demon hound...? Really?
You're just now noticing?
Ooh la la! A night with
a demon hound! How sexy!
You really have no standards.
Now... I've been
waiting for you, Pluto.
That door has been sealed
with unnatural power...
Only a demon hound
can open it.
Look, his collar's shining.
And so's the door.
He's so big!
He's run off again.
No need to worry.
We'll follow him in...
He should prove to be
a serviceable guide.
Lizzie!
Lizzie?... Lizzie!
Oh my, it looks like
we're too late.
Wake up. Lizzie...!
Lizzie, wake up! Lizzie!
Where?
Lizzie... You're okay.
That's the ring.
So you did like it...?
That makes me happy...
So happy.
That was her gift for you...
The one you didn't open.
How foolish...
She didn't have to.
Then why did she?
Why is her body
moving without her control?
And why...
Is she going to hurt the
one person she loves
most in the world?
What's happening to her?!
No!
No...! No...!
No, no, no!
Look sharp, Grell.
Can't you see
what's happening?
I suppose so...
But I would hate to chip
one of my blades, so...
Please do help us out, Grell.
Oh, Bassy...!
How could I deny you...?
Well then... when we kiss...
can there be...
just... a little bit...
of tongue?!
I have no idea what
you're talking about...
but I can in fact tie
a cherry stem in a knot
using my tongue.
Oh, myyyyyyyy!
I cannot allow
a little girl like you
to wield a better blade
than I do. Unforgivable.
No, Grell...! Stop!
Is she alright?
What happened?
A puppet string.
Only a death scythe could
have cut it with such ease...
Well, Sebastian...?
Aren't I amazing...?
Tell me how good I am!
Well done...
Perhaps you should run
with scissors more often.
Oh...! I am just
flattered to death!
Now let's see...
where does the string lead to?
So then, I began
thinking to myself...
"I have two new dolls
at my disposal.
What materials
shall I use this time?"
Indeed...? And of what
materials are you made?
Me...? Huh... I don't know...
What am I made out of?
Well... I'm not sure... but
whatever materials were used
don't seem to be of
the highest quality.
Oh my. So then
I thought to myself...
"I have always believed
that I was human...
but... lately...
I often find termites
crawling out of my ears.
Isn't that strange."
Now, Grell.
Oh, Bassy...!
We'll work together as one!
United by love!
You are utterly lacking in
style... You're no butler!
I'd never lose to someone
so hopelessly inferior.
Aww! That's my Bassy.
So stylish!
So he was a doll, too?
His name was
Drossel Keinz...
His soul was collected
five years ago...
but we still detected
signs of his existence.
He must have been fitted
with a transient soul
by somebody...
His master, maybe.
Ciel...
You're awake...!
Let's get you home.
I want to give you... a real
birthday party... Can I?
Okay... we'll have a party.
You can rest easy now
Lizzy... It's all over.
It appears that it's not.
So then... I thought...
To myself... I still
have a task... I...
Must report...
to my... master.
What's wrong with this loon...?
He's all torn up and he still
wants to serve his master?
Perhaps I judged him
too hastily.
He may be...
one hell of a butler.
Master... It's me...
Why is he here?
And why... is he so friendly?
I'm terribly sorry.
My butler's incompetence
prevents me
from offering
you hospitality.
You're the one
behind this...?
Why would you want to turn
little girls into dolls?
Perfection is so
difficult to attain...
And when it is achieved,
it is fleeting.
Doll making is noble work...
It preserves that which is
most beautiful in this world...
A doll is a perfect little
person, forever frozen in time.
I have to disagree...
Those little brats
of yours were anything
but lovely--
Why are you after me? You won't
win. I'm no one's doll...
And I will never be a part
of your collection...
Here's your ring!
You ought to learn
your place, boy.
What?
My butler's head
was filled with straw...
With such limited intellect...
I don't imagine he could
understand why I wanted you.
Ciel Phantomhive...
the manner of your death
has been fated
since the day
of your birth.
That body you wear...
is unclean.
But how... how could
you know about that?
I cannot allow someone like
you to live in this world...
Your existence
is a desecration.
Unclean... unnecessary...
unwanted...
That is why I intend
to erase you.
What?!
Snuff him out. He is unclean,
unnecessary, unwanted...
End him! End him! End him!
Stop talking!
It's a puppet.
Sebastian...!
Go catch that thing!
The person pulling the strings
is elsewhere my lord...
It wouldn't do us any good
to give chase.
Now I see...
There were hidden strings woven
throughout the entire room.
How very unpleasant.
Bassy...! My love!
It's time for our kiss!
Well, young master... what now?
Would you like me to
avenge Madam Red for you?
Okay, on second thought, the
kiss can wait until next time!
Bye-bye, Bassy!
Wait Grell!
No, leave it... Not today.
Elizabeth's here...
I don't want her to see
any more bloodshed.
Look at that...
It's little Lord
Phantomhive's birthday today.
Somehow I doubt he's
celebrating the occasion.
I'm sorry, Sir Arthur...!
I was looking into
the Hope Diamond,
and I became sidetracked.
It's not a bad idea
to investigate him.
Huh?
He receives special
treatment...
including access to information
even we at the Yard
can't obtain.
He wags his tail
for the queen...
marking all territory as his...
The queen's damned guard dog.
Guard dog...?
Well, whatever this
kid's secrets are...
There can't be a child
in the whole world
who wouldn't want to
celebrate his birthday.
Happy birthday, Ciel!
Happy birthday
to you, master!
This is fun... see!
Best birthday party
ever... hooray!
Master, shall I serve
the pudding now?
What a bother...
You could have just
cut it in the kitchen.
What is this?
Well, the season
is almost upon us...
so it is a traditional
Christmas pudding...
Whoever's piece has the ring
in it is guaranteed happiness
throughout the new year...
It seems you've found
the ring, Maste--
Did you hear that...?
You can finally be happy
again... I'm so glad!
I don't think--
Paula!... The bells!
Yes...! Right away...!
Jingle, jingle, jingle,
jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle!
How ridiculous.
All I cared about, all I
wanted, was to see Ciel smile.
I want him to be happy...
like he was before...
Always.
You have such a good heart.
Sleep well my lady.
I cast this ring away...
And now here it is again.
Today's events aside... It's
still a present Lady Elizabeth
went to great trouble to
acquire for you. Besides...
Cursed ring or not...
I will always protect you.
What do we know
about the mansion?
Well... It's been empty
for quite some time...
Its owner,
the Earl of Mandalay,
currently resides
in a sanatorium.
In all likelihood, he has
nothing to do with this, then.
Yes... so it would seem.
But still... that crest we saw.
Is there something
bothering you?
Nothing... I'm going to
retire now... I'm tired.
Yes... as you wish, my lord.
Snuff him out. He is unclean,
unnecessary, unwanted...
Snuff him out.
He is unclean,
unnecessary, unwanted...
End the unclean.
End the unnecessary.
End the unwanted!
Snuff out the unclean...
the unwanted...
Snuff out the unnecessary...
snuff out the unwanted.
Snuff out the unclean.
End him.
An odd fellow has
come to visit us
all the way from
exotic India...
Prince Soma's immaturity
rivals even that of a certain
Earl I know.
He is personally attended by a
competent butler named Agni...
Young master...
That particular pairing
seems to be rather popular
as of late.
Next time on Black Butler,
"His Butler, Freeloader."
You see... I am simply
one hell of a butler.