Is this really the time
for a game of chess?
Obsessing about it won't
help you solve the case...
Why not just leave it all
to Sebastian, dear?
Because he's simply my chess
piece... I'm the one who
moves him by giving orders.
But he's no ordinary piece.
He can move as many squares
as he needs to...
Like that.
That was against the rules,
you know.
Indeed... It would be
if this was a game...
But rules such as that have no
true meaning in the real world.
There are always knights
who break the rules...
and pawns who betray.
If you let your guard down...
It's checkmate.
You must've had
other options in life...
besides policing
England's underworld...
I'm sure my sister, your mother,
wanted something else for you.
And yet, after their deaths
you returned to be
the queen's guard dog...
Is it because you're trying
to avenge your parents' murders?
The need for revenge
is a funny thing...
It won't bring the dead back...
nor will it bring
them happiness.
But then--
To answer your question,
I didn't return to
the house of Phantomhive
for my parents.
I did it for myself.
I want to find the people
responsible for what happened...
and I want to
make them experience
the same pain and humiliation
that I suffered.
I still remember
when you were born...
though it seems so long ago.
You were so tiny and fragile,
I remember thinking...
"No matter what,
I have to protect him."
You know I was never
able to have children...
But then there was you...
and I've come to think of you
as my own son...
which is why I wish
you would quit this.
This is a task
I've freely chosen...
It's still my choice to make...
and no one else's.
I don't regret my decision and
I won't be coddled by anyone.
I have it now... thank you.
My lady.
Promise me... say you'll
never leave his side.
This is a dangerous world
for a boy...
Make sure he doesn't
lose his way?
Fear not... I swear...
I shall stay by his side
until the very end.
I'm here to escort you
back home... my lady.
Well, then?
No matter how I look at it,
the result is still the same.
Yesterday's murder...
the viscount didn't do it.
Exactly... none of the people
in his mansion could have
done it either.
Indeed... No person could
move that quickly...
Anyway, tomorrow we'll start--
Sebastian... ! You didn't....?
Of course I didn't, my lord...
I told you, I never lie...
Now... Involved in medicine...
ties to secret societies
or black magic...
lacking alibis for the nights
the bodies were found...
The only human who fits our
criteria is the Viscount Druit.
You know more about this than
you're letting on, don't you?
But I'm simply
one hell of a butler...
As you well know, I only
carry out those orders
my master has
directly given me.
You need only say
the words, my lord...
and I become either your pawn...
or your knight.
Now... master...
move me to check.
He'll show if we stake out
this place, right?
Yes.
You know... I've realized
the murdered prostitutes
had other things in common
besides their profession.
The most beautiful,
glossy black hair.
But I still don't understand
why he had to kill them all.
So very lovable...
it could almost be a sin.
And what's more, I--
So soft... Ah, so soft...
Listen when I'm talking to you!
Oh... I apologize, sir, but
she's so beautiful... and soft.
How could somebody
have gotten past us?
Let's go, sir.
Come away!
You've made quite a bloody mess
of things in there...
Jack the Ripper...
or, rather...
Grell Sutcliffe.
No... ! No, you're wrong... !
I...I heard the scream
and rushed to help... but...
You can drop
the innocent act, Grell...
It's over. You know, this
is actually the first time
I've met someone like you
in the human world.
You played the role
of helpless butler well...
Your act had almost everybody
completely fooled.
You... you think so?
How... kind!
That's great to hear.
After all... I am an actress.
And quite a good one at that.
Of course... you're not really
"Sebastian" either, are you?
Sebastian is the name
my master gave me...
So that is who I am...
for now.
Ah... you're playing
the faithful dog...
Well, you're handsome enough
to get away with it.
Anyway, here we are
Sebastian... No...
I'll call you Bassy.
Let me introduce myself...
The Burnett butler, Grell
Sutcliff... What do you say... ?
Let's get along!
Ah, it's so nice to
talk to you in my true form!
I admit I was surprised
when I first met you.
I've never seen
a demon playing a butler!
But I could say
the same about you...
I never thought I'd
find one of your kind
playing a butler either.
You're supposed to be
an intermediary
between man and god.
A grim reaper.
Why would a divine being
like you pretend to be
a servant?
Why, indeed... for now
let's just say that it was
out of love for
a certain woman.
And that woman would be?
You don't really
need to ask, do you?
Madam...
Well, I hadn't
counted on this...
I didn't think anyone would be
able to see who Grell truly is.
Naturally, you were
on the suspect list
from the very beginning.
But all of your alibis
seemed flawless.
You mean you actually
suspected your own aunt?
I was looking
for a murderer...
Degree of relation to me
didn't matter.
None of the humans
on the suspect list
could have been responsible
for all the murders...
but if one had
an inhuman accomplice,
that would change
the game completely.
It had to be someone who
could enter and leave a room
without being noticed,
someone who could
travel from the viscount's
home to the East End
instantaneously...
In the end, you two
were the only ones who
could be Jack the Ripper...
You, Madam Red...
and Grell Sutcliffe.
I began to look into
what else the victims had
in common besides
prostitution... and then...
I noticed they'd all undergone a
certain surgery at the hospital
where you work...
We made a list of
all the patients...
One... the only one
who was still alive...
was a woman by the name
of Mary Kelly.
We knew if we waited
around here,
you would
come for her eventually.
But we were... too late.
My darling nephew, how
unfortunate this turned out
to be. If you had let it go, we
could have played chess again.
But now...
You've taken everything!
What... is that?!
Grim reapers use tools
for harvesting souls...
that is his reaper's scythe.
Don't you dare call it that!
This is so much more
than a scythe!
I worked very hard
to customize it.
This is a special death scythe
of my own design...
It can hack anyone into tiny
pieces. I've been far too
well behaved. I'm getting out
of shape. I would love to
exercise my skills.
So... shall... we... play?
Perhaps you could be a bit more
respectful of my position... ?
I'm on duty, after all.
What a stoic man you are!
That makes you
even more irresistible.
You know, red is
my favorite color.
It's perfect for hair...
for clothes... for lipstick...
So I painted all those women
with pretty, pretty red blood.
So, Bassy, now I'll
make you even better looking
than you are. I'll tear
you up from the inside
...and trust me
I'll make you like it.
You'll be as lovely
as scattered rose petals.
You're a grim reaper...
Your job is to quietly harvest
the souls of the dying.
And as a butler, your job
is to follow your master
like a shadow.
You have violated both
of these expectations...
And, quite frankly,
I find it sickening.
Bassy... you wound me.
You know... I'm more deadly
efficient than I seem.
In my name and that of the
queen, I order you, Sebastian...
Put an end to them.
Indeed... my young lord.
Oooh...! Yes! Please, run
away...! We can play tag, Bassy!
But see what happens if you're
not fast enough? You get cut.
It's more fun when it hurts
a little bit though isn't it?
You're still the queen's guard
dog... which means that now,
I'm your prey.
But if it's hunt or be hunted...
There's only
one thing I can do!
You're a doctor.
How could you do it?!
You wouldn't understand if I
told you! You're just a child!
You...
You brat...
You shouldn't have been born
in the first place!
Sister...
Master!
Stop, Sebastian!
Don't kill her!
Your arm...
How sweet you are, Bassy...
Really, what a prince!
Sacrificing your own poor
limb to save that kid.
On the other hand, you're
a disappointment, Madam...
Come now... Hurry up
and kill the brat already.
I loved my sister. I loved her
husband. I loved their child.
I can't.
I can't kill him... I can't
kill their beloved son.
Really? You're getting
soft-hearted on me all of
a sudden? After all those
deaths? If you don't end him,
he'll end you.
Madam...
But... This dear boy...
This child is my--
Too late for that...!
How disappointing.
What use do I have for you
if you're just another woman?!
Is that her--?
A part of the reapers' job
is to replay and examine
the memories of those
who are on the To-Die list.
From that we determine what
kind of person they were...
We see from their own
perspective what kind of life
they've lived. And we decide
whether they should live or die.
Their lives flash...
right before their eyes.
Ugh, please, that's such
a pedestrian term!
It is so much more than that.
This is the reaper's true power.
The Cinematic Record.
Rachel...
Angelina come say hello to our
guest, Lord Phantomhive.
I had hated the red hair
I'd inherited from my father.
Your hair is
very beautiful, An.
The color of spider lilies.
Red suits you very well.
But I came to love it after all.
I came to love the color red...
I came to love him.
Ann, I have wonderful news!
My sister...
Once again...
I hated the color red.
But...I could never
bring myself to hate them.
Eventually, I, too,
met a man and got married.
What do you think?
A boy or a girl?
Men are so impatient...
How would I know that yet?
It didn't happen at all
in the way I'd wanted it to...
But still, I thought
I'd found happiness.
That carriage hit someone...!
Call a doctor, quickly!
Then it all slipped away.
Your husband died
instantly... and in order
to save your life... We were
forced to remove your uterus...
and your unborn child
with it... I'm sorry,
but we had no choice.
Everything... everything
slipped away from me.
I lost the man
I had learned to love.
And the child I loved so dearly
before it was even born.
The stain spread.
It covered everything...
That color I so hated...
The color red.
My sister was buried
with the man she loved...
If only... if only my heart
had been buried in the ground
along with them.
Honestly, a child
would only be in the way.
I don't know who the father is,
and my customers wouldn't
like a child hanging around.
I had lost everything in my
life. That woman had what
I wanted most... What I
would never get the chance
to have again. And she threw it
away without a second thought.
I wanted to stain her, too.
Hello... you're that doct--
Wha- What are you doing... ?
No... ! No, wai--!
I decided to stain everything
red... with my own hands.
My, my... ! That was
quite a little show!
That's when I met
my blood-red grim reaper.
A few months later... my missing
nephew suddenly reappeared.
Oh, Ciel!
With him he brought
a butler dressed in black.
You're really safe.
I got at least one thing back.
Thank goodness...
At least we still have you...
Let me take a look
at your darling face.
The child of the man I loved...
and my sister.
If this child could come back
then why couldn't my beloved?
Why wasn't I the one
he chose to marry... ?
I finally decided that
I would right all the wrongs
I had been dealt.
You've taken everything!
How beautiful you were
dyed crimson, covered in
your victims' blood...
I loved you so.
What a disappointment you
turned out to be in the end.
You don't have what
it takes to wear red.
Your cheap little
melodrama ends now.
It's... over,
Madam Red... Goodbye.
Well, what are you waiting for?
I thought I ordered you to
put an end to Jack the Ripper.
It's not over yet.
One is left... Stop standing
there and kill him!
Certainly.
I was going to spare you...
Professional courtesy and all
that... but if you insist...
I'll send you and the boy
to Heaven together!
Heaven? You're joking.
I know nothing of Heaven.
You would kick
a lady in the face?!
Where are your manners, sir?!
Terribly sorry... You see, I'm
simply one hell of a butler.
You think a demon like you
can beat a reaper?
Certainly... You see if
my master tells me to win...
then I shall win.
You care a lot about that
puny little brat, don't you...?
I'm jealous.
Demon or not, you'll still
be destroyed if I reap you
with my death scythe...
Aren't you frightened?
Not at all...
I belong to my master...
My soul and my body, down to
the last hair, are his.
The contract remains... so
I follow his every order...
That's what it means
to be a butler.
The red spider lilies
blazing in the fields...
the red cardinal singing in the
trees... all must eventually
wither and die... falling prey
to the deadly laws of nature.
Please excuse me...
I cannot allow myself to be
affected by such vulgarity...
I shall have to dispatch him
in a deadly efficient way.
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler, At the Funeral."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.