Ciel... Ciel...
Ciel Phantomhive:
Look. This is your past.
Some of it shines brightly...
and some of it...
remains shrouded
in darkness.
Ah... so that is
the past you choose?
No, Father!
I know you!
Master?
This is
the Grim Reaper Library.
I don't know if you're aware,
but this is where
the Cinematic Records
are housed.
Ah, as I suspected, it is you.
I thought I smelled a rat.
Will!
To think a demon would have
the nerve to set foot in here.
No, hold on Will...!
I'm looking for
the Doomsday Books
like you ordered.
What a shame,
a Grim Reaper and you
invited this filth into our
territory. You're a disgrace...
Are you actually trying to
be demoted even further?
What.... What will
you do to me now?
You call me
an invading rat...
but I do believe that you
have another infestation
to be worrying about.
The angel.
That's right.
Excellent... looks like I'll
have more overtime tonight.
So, you're awake now,
are you?
Really? It was you...
Angela Blanc?
How did you enjoy the
record of your past...?
Did it feel like being
wrapped in soft velvet...
or perhaps...
sandpaper against your skin?
Shut up!
The hand I saw...
That hand was his...
my father's hand.
You killed them,
didn't you? But why...?
Why did you kill my parents?!
What did you stand to gain--?
"Killed?" What a
disturbing thing to say.
I'm not the only one
who harmed your parents...
But you know that...
don't you?
It was your butler...
No, It was you, wasn't it...?
It was you who gave them
their second death.
You were rather brilliant.
In the face of such
a distorted past you somehow
managed to remain sane.
How could you?
You are a truly
unclean human.
But... underneath all
of those impurities,
there is a glow it would be
such a shame to extinguish.
Well, Ciel...
Shall I alter your unsightly,
impure past for you...?
Would that help you
find peace at last?
An angel she would
indeed have the ability
to tamper with a
Cinematic Record.
You mean they can
change the past?
I don't think even a deity
could manage that...
but still, an angel can give
a false sense of peace.
Nice try...! But you're
the reason I'm impure!
Someone who has experienced
trauma great enough
to break his soul may
wish for all memory of it
to be obliterated. However...
it will haunt him forever...
no matter what.
Ciel... it's all right.
You don't need
to mourn us anymore...
You can abandon your grief.
That's right... Ciel...
We hate to see you
suffering needlessly like this.
An angel's powers
leave the past unchanged...
They simply manipulate
a person's impression of it,
offering a rosier view
of things than before.
You're lying... Liar...! My
mother and father were killed--
We were... but in that moment
we saw a bright light.
It was a tranquil peaceful
glow wrapped in love...
In death your father
and I were finally able
to become one
in body and spirit.
Yes... that's right... and now
that we are truly joined...
now... we can embrace
your body and spirit as well
and join you to us
completely, son.
Come, Ciel.
Our son.
We love you so much.
I love you too...
Mother, Father...
Master!
His past is being rewritten,
being cleansed.
Soon, he will be as pure
as the driven snow.
Cleansed?
Hatred is painful...
No one wants to harbor it
in their hearts.
Ciel is no different.
Master!
Don't be hasty.
You can't stop her right now...
If you do, the child's past
will be horribly changed...
and as a result, he'll become
something less than human.
Yes, pure as
the driven snow.
My young master...
being purified?
That's right,
Ciel... Keep going...
We don't bear any grudge
toward anybody.
Yes... come closer, Ciel.
Don't be led astray by
things like hatred and pain.
Free yourself from
all such emotions.
Unnecessary... unclean.
What is it, Ciel?
What's wrong?
N- No... no.
What, Ciel?
No, I... don't want....
What are you saying...?
Please, Ciel!
Maybe you never bore
a grudge, but still...
that has nothing to do
with me. Nothing.
It cannot change my hatred!
But Ciel... How could
you say that?
Please think about what
you're really saying!
I thought you loved us, dear!
I do love you... I always will.
And that's why it hurt
to lose you...
It hurt so much!
After that...
hatred was all I had left.
Why don't you just let it go?
I can't!
Why, Ciel...
If I let go of hatred...
then the person I've been
since that day
disappears with it.
That's not me...!
It's not me!
But darling....
Please, Ciel...
I won't... let go.
I will not let it go.
I will not lose... my hatred!
What...?! He's rewinding
the Cinematic Record
all on his own?!
Master!
What the hell
were you thinking?
Sebastian... good catch.
Always surprising. You
are forever exceeding
my expectations.
You have a worthy soul.
Indeed, truly worthy, master.
Such a horribly
unclean heart... Depraved...
stagnant...
trapped in the dark.
I should never
have shown you pity.
So here and now...
I shall purify you.
We'll see about that.
A crime in the library
is our jurisdiction...
Let us join the fight...
now come with me Grelle.
Oh, my!
We will march into
battle together, then:
a, passionate,
fighting trinity!
Pardon me. Please move
aside. I'm coming through.
Let's see here... Number
eight... number eight....
Undertaker?
Hi!
Hey you...
what are you doing he--?!
Mind your manners, idiot...!
He's a legend.
He passed judgment
on Robin Hood and sent
Marie Antoinette to hell
The Grim Reaper who makes
even crying children
willingly give up their souls.
No, not fair!
He doesn't look
anything like the chap
in the sequence just now!
How could this
creepy old man be
a legendary
Grim Reaper...
Take me!
You seem busy...
I suppose I'll have to
start my purification
in the abbey, then.
Running away, coward!
You shall see...
I'll show you all
what happens to a world
ruled by impurity...
I doubt you'll like it, though.
What... was that?
An angelic seal.
What are we supposed
to do now...?
Our leader is gone!
You don't have to grieve.
The time has come
to use the coffins...
The moment is at hand at last.
A... An angel?!
Give up everything to me.
Including... Your sullied
Doomsday Books...
They have no future
to offer you...
There is nothing left.
It won't open!
Oh, dear.
Unfortunately, it looks as if
we're locked in.
What is this...? It looks
like the Cinematic Record
of someone who
is in that abbey.
Seriously?
Interesting...
"An angel of massacre
is descending...
in an abbey that
is near Preston."
What? An angel
of massacre?
All you who have gathered
here. Your souls are impure.
they are dependent,
leaning on others.
You have forgotten
how to take the future
into your own hands.
The unclean... end them...
The unwanted... end them...
The unnecessary... end them.
Ah, yes... I see it now.
Stop her now.
Ooh master... how charitable...
I thought your intent
was to put an end to this
cult once and for all.
I don't want to help them,
but I don't want her
to have her way... That is all.
But what are we
supposed to do...?
We can't even
find a way in there.
No... not true.
There is a way... We have
a tool... the ultimate
Reaper tool to which we
managers have access.
This tool... is the
Death Bookmark.
A bookmark?
And it's pink.
Isn't that lovely?
If we use this
to halt the story,
we can make some
editorial changes.
The woman in this story happens
to be Matilda Simmons...
It says here that she is
purified in the abbey
by the angel Angela.
But the sentence
just ends there.
Oh, yes... but now
I just add that
Sebastian Michaelis
appears suddenly...
Oh no...! Bassy!
That woman there...
she smells like a demon.
Yes
You see... I've
already marked her.
It's you!
You wish to die at the hands
of an angel, do you...?
A pious demon indeed.
Sebastian Michaelis.
You think a demon can
compare with the purity
of a winged angel in flight?
A creature like you... is
chained to the earth, forever.
Really? ...is that so...?
then I suppose that
you are forever chained
to the heavens.
Let's get to work!
A brand-new
Death Scythe!
Well done!
You shall wash and
return it when this is over.
Uh... so cruel.
But suddenly, there's a
dramatic turn of events...
Grim Reapers William T.
Spears and Grell Sutcliff
appear before Matilda
in the abbey.
That's a useful tool.
Indeed, but even it
has some limits.
This looks like
it could be fun.
Do you know what...?
I think we should have
ourselves a game of darts.
Oh dear... I missed...
Now... whatever do you think
I should aim for next?
Pick me, I want to play!
A demon, all right.
What's this...? Does she
mean to die along side us?
Snuff out the unclean...
Snuff out the unnecessary.
Uh, boys... see the ceiling?!
You're all free to go now...
It might be
the best option for you.
Yes... yes, okay!
It is our turn now... We will
retreat, Grell Sutcliff.
Seriously! Never mind
the overtime!
I want a day off!
Is it over?
She plunged me into
a bottomless abyss...
And I don't even know why.
A promise...
is a promise!
Why, Sebastian?! Why are you
not taking my soul?!
She has to be dead!
Doesn't she?!
Someone else...? Is there?
I'm sorry. I'll be serving you
a while longer, Master.
Out of curiosity, why were
you in the library?
I was under the impression
that you'd retired
from active service.
Well... This fellow here
reminded me of something.
There were some Cinematic
Records I'd neglected
to return.
You must be kidding.
Certainly not. In fact,
now that you mention it,
two of the books I
checked out were about
an Earl Phantomhive
and his lady wife.
Their true Cinematic
Records: ones that had never
been touched by
avenging angels...
Would you like to know
what they said, my lord?
No... Now...
Let's go... Sebastian.
Yes, sir.
That was interesting.
Are you sure
that was wise?
I'm sorry, master... but
if you read the books,
you'd know who
deserved your revenge.
It's done.
Feeling sentimental?
Not that...It's just...
Seeing them again... being
near them once more...
You can only disgrace
the dead so much...
Master, lately you seem
to have made quite a friend
of inspector Abberline.
Making new friends
is lotable, naturally
but one might air on
the side of caution.
I would advise you
not to become
so deeply involved
that you put yourself
at risk.
Share a short conversation
now and then
but always be
on the lookout.
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler, Imprisioned."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.