Noooo!
Oh dear oh dear oh dear!
Ahhhh!
Hot! Hot hot hot hot hot hot!
Ah! I'm so sorry!
I'll wipe it off!
Master... why did you agree
to take in such a useless idiot?
You're one to talk, Bard.
It didn't seem like
such a bad idea.
Oh Ciel, darling.
I have a problem.
Grell is hopelessly incompetent.
Could you do me a tiny favor
and have Sebastian train him
to be a decent butler?
Can't refuse your
favorite aunt, can you?
I thought Sebastian would be
the only one inconvenienced...
I never expected that I would
be affected by it as well.
Ho ho ho.
I'm so sorry for causing
all this trouble...!
I simply don't know how
I can apologize enough.
Wait that's it! The only
thing I can do now is die!
I shall atone with my death!
Whoa...! Calm down a second!
Um...Should we take
the knife away?
There is no need for that.
Just think of the horrible
mess you would make...
It'd take hours to clean up
all of the blood.
Thank you, Sebastian...
You're so very kind.
That was kindness?
Now, what I'd like to know...
is how you could think it was
ever acceptable to serve
the master such weak tea.
Watch me... a spoonful for
each person and one more
for the pot.
Finally... add a half-pint of
boiling water and let it steep
until dark.
Master... Are you ready?
It is almost time...
I have the carriage waiting
for you in the front drive now.
Fine.
As for the rest of you...
I want this place absolutely
spotless, understand?
Grell... perhaps you should
just sit there and relax
so you don't cause
any more trouble.
And... If you do decide
to seek your eternal rest...
please see to it outside,
would you, and try not to make
too big a mess.
What generosity...!
What great kindness!
Get your paper here...!
All the latest news!
Prostitute
mysteriously murdered!
Oh, hello, boy...
Did your father send you
for something?
Actually, he's here
on his own business.
We need to pick this up.
Oh...you're here
for that walking stick.
I was wondering who would have a
use for one as short as this...
Naturally...
I didn't think a chi--
Straight as an arrow...
a magnificent stick,
indeed, good sir.
Keep the change. Good day.
That ridiculous strength
of Finny's is a menace...
How could someone accidentally
break a walking stick...?
It's a pain to
special order a new one.
Certainly- what a pity to go
to all that trouble...
you haven't even had
a growth spurt in years.
And speaking of trouble,
I don't know how well
Grell is going to work out...
We shouldn't stay away
for too long.
Look, Mama! It's the brand new
rabbit toy from Funtom! See?
The Funtom Company. The maker
of toys and confections
has grown rapidly
in the last three years.
And this estate testifies
to the company's prosperity.
The manor is magnificent,
don't you think?
You know, it's only been around
for about two years now.
Odd...? But it looks
so stately and dignified.
Of course it does...
That was the intention.
Look! It's the real Tanaka!
We haven't seen him in months!
This manor was specifically
built to be an exact replica
of the previous one...
It is identical in every single
detail, from the windowpanes
to the stairways and even
the cracks in the pillars.
Identical?
The original Phantomhive manor
burned down three years ago...
The entire estate
was engulfed in flames.
It was a great tragedy.
Oh...oh, I see...
Forgive me for asking...
but Master Ciel's
parents... did they...?
Yes... Sadly, they both
perished in the fire.
How terrible--that poor boy.
Oh, no! Tanaka!
His energy and stamina levels
are way below a normal person's.
Bein' Real Tanaka exhausts him.
He just needs to rest himself
for awhile.
Oh. That's interesting.
Why're they all skulls?
No! Not again! I've made yet
another unacceptable mistake!
I can't go on any longeeeer!
Quit tryin' to die all the time!
But I have to...! It's the
only way to redeem my honor!
Grell!
I'm sure you're tired, master.
I'll prepare tea for you
immediately.
What's the matter?
My mansion?
What happened to this place...?
Why it's a disaster!
Sebastian! Sebastian!
What is going on here...?
And why on earth are you all
dressed like lunatics?!
She's crazy...! Crazy!
Who is crazy?
What are you doing now?!
At the moment, I believe
I'm in the process of dying,
Master Ciel.
Get him down, Sebastian.
Yes, sir.
Ciel!
Ciel...! You're back!
I missed you so much!
Elizabeth, what a surprise!
Oh...! How many times do I have
to tell you call me Lizzie!
Aww, you really are
just the cutest thing ever,
aren't you, darling boy?
I could just eat you up!
Lady Elizabeth.
Oh, hello Sebastian...
How are you?
Aww... you took him down?
Yes. He detracted from
the beauty of the room.
But I made such a lovely
decoration out of him!
A decoration?
Yes! Just look at it all!
Isn't the salon so cute now?
My mansion... It's so pink.
From now on, only the
cutest things belong in
the Phantomhive manor!
Don't you agree, Antoinette?
Ho ho ho.
Oh, And Tanaka?
And I have
a present for you too.
Here. You're always dressed in
black. I thought this would be
a nice change.
What do you think?
I am deeply honored that
you went to so much trouble
for a humble servant... Your
generosity overwhelms me.
Happy to help!
In any event, Lizzie.
What are you doing here...?
Auntie didn't let you
come alone?
I sneaked away because
I wanted to see you, silly!
You... sneaked away...?
Don't you think
you'll get into trouble?
Um, Sebastian...
who is this girl?
She... is the daughter
of the Marquess of Scotney...
Her full Christian name is
Lady Elizabeth Ethel Cordelia
Midford of Scotney.
Scotney-ethel-elizabeth-
cordelia-mid--
She is actually my young
master's betrothed,
of several years.
Ah... his fiancée,
yes of course--
Master...!
Marrying...?!
Her?!
Lady Elizabeth is of
the nobility, after all.
She is the daughter
of a Marquess...
Nobles marry other nobles...
That's how it works.
Oooh...! I know! Now that the
manor is decorated so prettily,
why don't we have
a ball tonight!?
You can be my escort,
and we'll dance around
all night long!
Isn't that a wonderful idea!
A ball...? No!
You'll wear the clothes
I picked out for you, won't you?
Pretty please!
They'll be so cute on you!
Listen, I don't want t--
And of course, I'll be
dressed to the nines as well!
You come with me. I want
to make you even cuter
than you already are!
Wait, I said no baaall!!
I believe the wisest
course of action is to
go along with her plan...
I don't think she is
going to listen to reason.
Can't you just give her
some tea or something
and get her out of here...?
I don't have time
for a stupid ball.
My lord... Lady Elizabeth
would like a dance.
You cannot refuse her.
Master...
What now?
I know I've never
seen you dance before...
but I assume that you can?
Oh, I see...
Well, that explains
why you're always such
a wallflower
at social engagements.
I have too much work to do...
I don't have time
to waste on dancing.
With all due respect...
Dancing is a necessary skill
for a person of your position
to possess. In your line
of work, Master...
social contacts are
important to maintain.
The world expects
any noble gentleman
to possess at least
rudimentary dance skills...
If you turn down too many
invitations simply because
you cannot dance, your
reputation in high society
will suffer greatly.
Fine, I'll do it...
Now stop the lecture...
Call me in a private tutor
or something...
Mrs. Bright or Mrs. Rodkin
should work well enough.
We don't have sufficient time
to call in a tutor for you,
my lord...
There's only one option.
With your permission,
I will be your dance instructor.
Don't be ridiculous...
I'm not going to take
dancing instruction from a man!
Besides, do you even know
how to dance?
The Viennese waltz is my
specialty... I was a guest
at the Schonbrunn Palace
in Vienna from time to time.
Now, if you would do me
the honor, my lady...
May I have this dance?
Let's begin. To lead, you start
the first step on your heel...
Be sure to keep your hand
firmly upon the lady's back.
When the music starts,
lead with your left foot. Now.
Next, we'll try a Natural Turn.
Slide your foot forward,
like this.
Your natural ability for dancing
is not so much lacking--
as it is nonexistent, my lord...
You cannot simply cling
for dear life
onto your dance partner.
You're too tall.
It's not working!
Most importantly... You need
to wipe that gloomy look
off of your face.
The lady will
take it as an insult.
Now, let's have a smile...
Pretend that it's fun.
Let me go!
Master!
I can't smile! I forgot how.
I don't know how to pretend like
I'm having fun...
Not anymore.
How... awful...! This is the
most humiliating outfit ever!
I think you're going to have
to make peace with it.
This dress... it's atrocious!
So white and girly and frilly!
If I have to dress up
why can't it be in
a sexy shade of red,
with a waistline that
would flatter my figure?!
That's your problem with it?
I can't live with
a shame as deep as this!
No...! I'd rather die!
You aren't going to try
to stop me this time?
Blue is definitely
Ciel's color!
It will look so good on him.
You should see
the clothes I found!
I got them today in
London. They're great!
He'll look dashing!
Now... time to get you
dressed up...!
I'll make you look so adorable!
I'm really farsighted!
I can't see anything without
my glasses, my lady!
You don't have to see
at a ball to have fun...
Now hand those over, silly!
No, no, no, please!
Just leave her alone.
Ciel! You look adorable!
That outfit
is absolutely perfect!
Ciel... Why aren't you wearing
the ring I brought you...?
It matches your clothing
perfectly. Now where did it go?!
The ring I already
have on will work.
No! I went to so much trouble
and that ring isn't cute at all!
Why won't you wear the ring I
picked out specially for you?!
You're so cruuuuel!
I just want everything to be
perfect for our lovely ball!
That's not it... Lizzie,
this ring is--
Hah...! Fooled you!
It's mine now!
Lizzie!
This is far too big for you.
The one I bought
will fit perfectly.
Just put it on and--
Give it back!
Give me that ring...
Now, Elizabeth!
Wh... why are you
so angry at me...?
I just... wanted...
What's wrong? I just wanted to
make everything look adorable,
that's all...
So why-why are you so angry?!
I hate this ring! Take it!
Master, you forgot the walking
stick we went to so much trouble
to get.
Forgive my master, Lady
Elizabeth, but that ring
was something
very important to him.
It's a precious heirloom
passed down to the head
of the Phantomhive family.
He's grown quite
attached to it.
It's truly one of a kind.
Please try to understand...
Why this upset him
It... it was that important...
and I destroyed it...?
Oh, Ciel... Please, I--
Ciel, wait! What are you doing?!
It doesn't matter. It was
nothing but an old ring,
after all. Even without it,
I'm still the head
of the Phantomhives...
And that won't change!
How long are you going to cry?
I... I'm so sorry!
Your face is a mess! Completely
unsuitable for a lady.
How could I possibly ask
a lady with a runny nose
and puffy eyes to dance?
To dance?
He's incredible!
He plays the violin?
Is there anything he can't do?
Ah...! I'll join him!
What the hell...?
He can actually sing!
So then, we are agreed...?
We'll forget our cares
and dance the night away...
It's decided.
Yes!
Don't worry, I'll make sure
she gets home safely.
You can count on me.
Are you sure?
Indeed. I'm more deadly
efficient than I appear.
Thank you so much, Sebastian...
I'm in your debt-
you've taught me a lot about
what it means to be a butler...
They say that before
a person dies his life
flashes before him.
and I know that when
I see the light of death,
this momentous evening
is what will appear to me
in my dying vision.
Interesting that
you would say that.
That's true. He hasn't been very
good at dying so far, has he?
It's finally over.
What a horrible day it's been.
You seemed to be enjoying
yourself for awhile there,
my lord.
Don't be so foolish.
Am I the fool here?
I know the importance
of this ring...
and yet, you put on
that act for Lady Elizabeth.
If I couldn't do this much
for my Master...
well, then what kind
of butler would I be?
But you should take care.
It is precious.
This ring...
It has seen so much.
That is true.
It's always there.
This ring has seen
the death of many masters.
My grandfather...
my father... and eventually,
the ring will witness
my own death as well.
It's heard the dying screams
of the Phantomhive family
for generation upon generation.
When I close my eyes,
I hear them too...
voices echoing in my head...
"If I throw the ring away...
I won't have to listen
to them screaming anymore"
...at least that's what I
believed. Ridiculous, yes?
My... look how high
the moon has risen.
You must get some rest, sir.
Don't want to make yourself ill,
do you?
Sebastian... stay with me...
until I fall asleep?
Goodness... Are you displaying
weakness in front of me now?
Just a simple order.
I will stay here... I am
by your side forever, master.
Until the end...
I'm still the head
of the Phantomhives...
That won't change!
Stay with me...
Now...I must
prepare for tomorrow.
The mysterious
prostitute murders
are getting out of hand...
Unfortunately,
in order to solve them,
my master may have to
do something with which
he is not quite at ease...
Now, now, my lord,
don't be shy...
You look quite fetching
in a dress...
Remember, it's for
a good cause, after all...
Besides, you have to admit,
it's pretty comfortable.
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler, Capricious."
You see, I am simply
one hell of a butler.