Young master...
he has made his move.
Good. Let's follow him.
Take me with you!
You? Why?
I know that Agni's
been sneaking out
after I fall asleep...
I want to know
what he's been up to...
That's my right.
A nice place.
Who lives here?
This estate belongs
to Harold West Jeb.
He imports a wide range
of goods from India...
He also owns various
stores, coffee houses,
and the like...
I've met him once. He's
disgustingly obsessed
with his social status.
People at one of
his businesses
have been found trussed-up
and hung upside down...
Mr. West happened
to be away at the time,
however, so,
fortunately for him,
he managed to
escape unharmed.
My, isn't he lucky.
Shall we have a look?
Indeed.
Why not relax with
a nice Scotch?
An excellent one from
Justerini and Brooks.
They hold the
Royal Warrant, you know.
Our plan has been perfect so
far. You've done well for me,
Agni. I think we've
done all we need to...
Stringing up anyone else
won't be necessary.
With this blessed
hand of yours...
the Royal Warrant
may as well already be
in my pocket.
A Royal Warrant...?
That's what this is?
If I carry out the plan as
promised... Then Mina...?
Where's Mina?!
What the--?
My prince!
West is almost certain
to recognize us....
We must stay back.
What is this...?!
You've known where Mina
was all along, Agni?!
I see... This intrusive
young man is your master?
And you are the man
who took Mina away...!
Get him...! Do you hear me?
What are you waiting for?!
Let's grab that idiot
prince and
get out of here
right now.
But West'll recognize you
as soon as you walk in.
I'll take care of it.
Well, Agni...
are you going to take
care of this brat for me?
This brat?!
Well?
Agni!
Deer?
A deer-man?
What's going on here?!
Yes, thank you
for stating the obvious.
I am a deer...
I've come for the prince.
He's a foreign spy... Get him!
No... I am simply
one hell of a dee--
Kill him!
Do something or
our agreement is over!
Now!
Since I was reborn...
I have had only one
god and master...
I vowed that I'd never swing
my fist for anyone but him...
I am guilty of betraying that
vow... Please forgive me!
Don't do it... Agni!
The crystal glasses I bought
at Thomas Goode!
Do you know what
those are worth?!
Her Majesty specifically
granted them a warrant!
Sounds like trouble...
Perhaps we should leave now.
Come my lord,
it's time to go.
Hey...! We're drawing
too much attention...!
Grab the kid and get out
of here, Sebastian.
Yes, sir.
With that kind of punch...
this fellow is no
ordinary human being.
It's a mental technique he
uses called Samadhi...
When he gets like that,
no one can touch him.
Never heard of it.
I imagine it's
a type of trance...
Agni has absolute faith
in his master...
Consequently, from that faith
he is able to produce
superhuman power.
His skills are born of
something we can never
understand: the power of
complete love and trust
in another person.
But this betrayal...
why would he do it?!
Why do the people close
to me always leave?!
Prince Soma!
All of them... but why?!
Oh... just look at the
Haviland tea set I ordered...
So well suited to my master...
Children...! It seems
this one in particular
will require some
personal disciplining.
You careless pig!
I'm the careless one?
You're in England,
at the estate of my master,
Lord Phantomhive...
What you childishly don't seem
to recognize is that it stands,
your presence in
this house hold announce
a little more than a nuisance.
You're a helpless child
who can do nothing
without Agni at his side...
And now your pillar of
strength has left you.
You're right... I've
lost everyone now...
everyone who mattered to me.
Lost?... You're more of
a child than I thought.
You haven't lost anything,
prince... Don't you understand?
You can't lose what you
never had to begin with.
Status from your parents...
a palace from your parents,
a servant from
your parents...
Never before in your life
has anything actually
belonged to you...
Isn't that right?
It's not!
Some part of you must have
known the truth about Agni...
But you were too much of a
coward to face that truth,
weren't you?
You're wrong...
You're wrong!
You know I'm not wrong...
You're finally
seeing the truth...
and now you want to play
the tragic hero.
What a hopelessly pathetic
brat you are.
They said they'd be with
me forever.
And you actually
believed that?!
You are so naïve.
Why on earth would they
stay when they got
nothing in return?
That's something most
three-year-olds understand.
Time to face facts.
Nobody ever loved you.
That's enough of that.
Master?
Who knows?
I could have ended up
the same way as him...
If it hadn't been
for that month.
What're you talking about?
My family...
They were killed and my home
was burned down...
I was treated worse than you
would treat any animal...
I was helpless... just a
child... But I came back...
To make the people who
did all that to me
suffer the same
humiliation...
And I will find them.
My parents were killed
for a reason...
If I remain the family head
and make myself
a nuisance to the people
who hurt them,
they'll target me.
That's what I'm waiting for...
Someday they'll come
to take my life, too.
But why...? Why do it?
Because the alternative is
grief and melancholy...
If I stand still then
I might as well
be dead with them.
But I'm alive and
still standing...
moving on my own two feet.
I'm going to die someday,
and I'd rather do it
without regrets...
I'm not going to pretend that
I'm doing anything noble...
This is no grand revenge.
It's just a game... I'm
waiting to see who wins.
However far I fall,
as long as there's so much
as a thread left to me,
I'll use it to climb...
I'll take hold of it....
and refuse to give up.
I am still human...
I can do that much.
But every person must to decide
on his own whether to grab it.
Enough of this idle
talk... Sebastian...
We need to talk about
West now... Come.
Yes.
Every person must decide
on his own to grab it.
Ciel!
I'm seventeen,
but you're right.
Compared to you
I am still only a child.
I'm nothing more than
a spoiled brat.
I knew there was something
that had been bothering Agni,
but I didn't bother
to ask, did I?
Now I want to know...
I want to see them in person
and ask why they left me.
I'm begging you...
let me come!
Don't think so.
You're a naïve idiot. I don't
want to chaperone you...
Of course... It's not like I'm
going to go to the trouble
of locking you in here.
Thank you!
Get off!
I'm sorry I lost my
temper earlier and
destroyed your tea set.
Please forgive me.
Oh yeah, and you too...
I'm very sorry.
It's all right... I find
you entertaining.
I didn't realize West was
after a Royal Warrant...
Though, given his
obsession with status,
it does make sense.
I was wondering, what exactly
is a Royal Warrant?
It's an endorsement bestowed
by the royal family
upon their favorite vendors.
Royal Warrant holders
are official purveyors
to the Crown.
Yes, indeed...
and in one week,
a curry exhibition
will be held as part of
the festivities at the
Crystal Palace.
I'm told it should be
quite the event.
Curry?
What's more... From what
I've heard, Her Majesty,
who is widely known
to be a lover of curry,
will be in attendance that day.
Nothing more
than rumor...
Ever since her husband,
Prince Albert, passed away,
Her Majesty rarely
condescends to make any
public appearances.
What do the curry exhibition
and the recent crimes
have to do with each other?
The connection is the curry.
It's the specialty at
West's coffee house...
If he obtains a Royal
Warrant for his curry,
his sales are sure to
increase dramatically.
My guess is he was using Agni
to target specific men...
They were probably his rivals
for the curry exhibition.
When he hanged the men,
he included notes that
insulted the English...
That was done to make it
seem as if the attacks
were carried out by
a bitter Indian...
Likely...
Mina was West's bait...
She's probably the only
reason Agni got involved.
I'm guessing he
did it all for you.
You worship Kali,
a goddess who is depicted with
her tongue sticking out...
Agni worships you as
his god, along with Kali.
The connection
seems obvious...
He signed those letters as
a way of apologizing to you.
He may indeed have left...
but everything he does is
still for you, no one else...
Agni lives only for you.
He is a fine butler.
Agni!
My, my, my, I do love
a happy ending...
It looks like
everything's wrapped up.
No need to get
more involved...
I'm sure the Yard
can handle the res--
Wait, no...!
There's Agni and Mina...
What will happen to them?
We know the criminal underworld
isn't involved in this...
Which means it has
nothing to do with us.
You're right...
This is my problem...
I need to be strong
and find a way to handle it
on my own.
That's the right attitude...
and it affords me
the liberty to look after
my own agenda.
I was called to the
city during winter
for this idiotic case.
I think I deserve
to be compensated
for the inconvenience,
don't you?
Thanks to West's
nefarious activities,
the competition at the
curry exhibition this year
will be considerably slimmer
than it normally would be.
So perhaps the Phantomhive
Company should
enter its own curry...
We'd only have to beat West...
Then the Royal Warrant
would fall into our hands.
I was already considering
expanding into
the food industry anyway...
Winning a Royal Warrant
for our curry would
generate some buzz...
It would be an excellent
way to get started.
But you only have a week
before the contest...
Can you find an adequate
curry chef and
gather equipment in time.
I don't think that
will be necessary.
Isn't that right... Sebastian?
If I couldn't make a good
curry for my master...
then what kind of butler
would I be...?
I shall secure
the royal warra-
Impossible.
There's no way
you can win...
They have Agni
cooking for them.
And his hand was blessed
by the goddess Kali.
Yes, I'm willing
to admit that Agni is
a remarkable fighter,
but this is a cooking
competition... It's not combat.
That's what I'm saying...
None of you have even
glimpsed Agni's
true power yet.
You don't know
real curry... No!
What is this
'real curry'?
The key to curry is the
mixture of spices...
The possibilities
are infinite...
Choosing the right one
is a very difficult task.
It is... like trying to find
one truth in a vast universe.
But Agni can do it...
He creates worlds
out of nothingness.
His power is on the same
plane as the gods'...
That's why he's known as...
The Godly Right Hand of Kali.
Never in my life have
I tasted a bowl of curry
that could even begin
to compare to his.
How interesting...
Agni's true power is
creating the curry of Kali.
Well, what do you think?
Fascinating indeed...
It sounds like a challenge.
You, uh... you made all
these yourself, really?
Yes...You're the only
one on the estate
who's ever tasted
Agni's curry before...
I'd like you to perform
a taste-test for me.
Which one should we use
to defeat your butler?
Yes, okay. I will...
If I can repay your
kindness by eating curry,
I'll eat as much as
you want me to!
Thank you. I
appreciate it.
I'll do it for Mina and Agni!
Thanks to you,
every lost one of our rivals
has withdrawn their entry.
The only ones left
are third-rate brands
I've never heard of before...
and some company that
makes children's toys.
The Funtom Company...?
Does that mean...?
No need to worry... With that
'godly' right hand of yours,
we're sure to win
the Royal Warrant.
My prince...
Pardon me, sir.
For today's tea, we have
gâteau au chocolat.
I'll need proper dress
for a royal audience.
You insist she won't come,
but you dress up anyway...
How amusing.
The Queen's guard dog is
a well trained little pup, eh?
Have you concocted a curry
better than Agni's yet?
No.
According to Prince Soma,
something is still lacking.
Then get back
to the kitchen and
stop wasting your time
baking cakes...
You have more important
things to do.
Yes, I understand, my lord.
And anyway,
I'm not in the mood for
chocolate right now...
Drop it into the curry
or something.
Indeed... my young master.
Until that day, I wasn't
a religious man...
I was born into
the Brahmins...
We were the highest caste...
people meant to serve
the gods... But I saw
the greed and snobbery
of the men
around me...
and I couldn't bring myself
to believe in
our righteousness...
I committed many crimes...
until finally...
The man you were
is dead now...
You will be reborn with a
new name and a new life!
I finally found something
divine... It was in him.
Now... you are Agni.
I vowed to use this
hand only for the god
I found in him.
Is this outfit fit for a
royal audience, my lord?
Yes, it's fine.
Now drop it... Anyway...
are you certain you can
beat Agni's curry today?
Of course.
I swear it on the
Phantomhive name.
I shall win a Royal
Warrant without fail.
Well... I have certain
preparations to make.
I must excuse myself.
You can do it,
Sebastian. Good luck!
Why are you here?
Mina!
Was that...? Prince Soma?
Mina...! I'm so glad...!
Agni got you back.
You don't have
to worry now...
We can go back
to the palace!
Highness?
How stupid are you?
Go back with you...?
Don't make me laugh...!
Why would I ever want
to go back there...?
I already went to so
much trouble to escape.
People born into royalty
can lounge around,
never doing a day
of work in their lives...
But because I was born
into a lower caste,
I was forever doomed
to be a servant.
I don't want to spend
my whole life trapped
by the caste system!
You went with him willingly?...
It was your decision--
Yes that's right! A lowly
servant or a rich man's wife?
Even a child would know
which one is better!
I spent my life taking
care of you,
you selfish brat...!
I'm done with it.
I promised
I would not tell you...
but now, here you are.
You're old enough
to know the truth.
Mina and I came
to an agreement...
If I obeyed West...
she would reveal nothing of her
true feelings to the prince...
He can't know the truth...
He's still too young for that.
So that's what this is about.
Don't you see... This is for
my prince. I can not lose!
Funny you say that...
Neither can I.
I'll never win
with this swill...!
Something is still missing...!
But what is it?
You seem quite troubled.
Perhaps using this
would help you.
What the...?
Thank you all for waiting!
Welcome to the
Curry Festival...
and the best curry
London can offer!
Great... this guy again.
Attention-seeker.
Prince Soma...
you can't stand to look at
my face anymore, can you...?
No...! I have to focus
on the competition!
And now,
let the cooking begin!
What is it?
It sounds like...
Her Majesty!
Spice is nice!
I'm sorry about that...
I was talking to myself.
A Phantomhive butler
who can't make curry
isn't worth his cumin.
Even the strongest
detractor will be hoping
to curry favor with me.
Next time on Black Butler:
"His Butler, Competing."
You see... I am simply
one hell of a butler.