The murderer's distinctive
style of killing
has earned him
a unique nickname
from the press.
"Jack the Ripper."
Yes... the uterus is missing...
which is quite... odd.
Exactly... none of the people
in his mansion
could have done it either.
Sebastian! You didn't...
In the end, you two
were the only ones
who could be Jack the Ripper.
...You, Madam Red...
and Grell Sutcliffe.
You brat...
You shouldn't have been born
in the first place!
I can't kill him...
I can't kill
their beloved son.
Too late for that...!
How disappointing.
What use do I have for you
if you're just another woman?!
Here we are.
A demon... And a reaper.
I suppose we'll
never resolve this.
These feelings that we have
are forbidden...
Oh, my! It's just like
Romeo and Juliet!
O my dear Bassy,
Wherefore art thou,
my sweet love, Bassy?!
If you would deny thy master
and refuse thy name...
I know that we could be
happy together.
The moment my master
uttered my new name,
that word became
our solemn contract...
I was rebaptized as his...
and his alone...
From that day,
I have been "Sebastian."...
By yonder moon, I swear it.
To swear by something
as inconstant as the moon...
How can I believe your words?
Yet I see your eyes
and know that they do
what your lips
and hands long to do.
You caress me softly with your
unworthy, devilish gaze.
Oooh!
It's almost too much, Bassy...!
I would bear your children
if you'd only let me!
Please stop that...
It is revolting.
Oh... you treat me so coldly.
Beautiful tyrant!
Fiend angelical!
My dove-feather'd raven!
Oh, Bassy! Bassy... my love...
If only cruel morning
would never come...
Then the two of us might
go on like this forever,
our love permanently lit
by the moon's seductive glow.
But no...
I'm afraid our
adventure ends here.
Shall we part with
a passionate kiss...?
No? Then good night, my love.
A thousand times, good night!
There now...!
Surely your Cinematic Record
will be be far more
interesting than any human's!
No...! No no no
no no no no...!
Who are these people?
What the hell is this?!
That's what my life has been for
the past two years, after all.
I'm not interested
in seeing your daily chores!
I know all that! Come on,
show me the good stuff!
So sorry...
I'm afraid I charge
for the juicy bits.
Skinflint!
Look at that.
My clothes are ruined again...
This is past mending.
You must be pretty confident
to worry about your clothes
right now... But of course...
You know, I always appreciate
a sharp looking man...
Well done, Bassy.
There was one technique that I
absolutely did not want to use.
but I have no other choice.
So at last you're going
to fight me seriously?
Shall we send the curtain down
with the next blow...?
I'll miss you terribly,
but perhaps we'll meet again...
Farewell!
What the hell?!
That was my finest tailcoat.
It was made of the
highest quality Yorkshire wool.
Wool is a very tricky fabric...
Once it becomes
caught in something,
it is exceedingly
difficult to remove.
How could you do this to me?!
I acquired that coat at
the manor and I certainly
didn't want to use it
for something like this...
But...you had already
ruined it, after all.
So then...
Fistacuffs yes...?
That suits me quite well...
I do have some
expertise in that area.
No...! Please,
just one request...!
Not... my face!
I said no face!
Please... just stop!
I'm sorry...
I seem to have misjudged
the distance, my lord.
You look terrible pretty awful.
He caused me a little bit
of trouble actually.
I'll...show you someday.
Oh, dear...
I suppose one can't kill
a reaper with bare fists alone.
Well then...
I'll just try this...
His very special reaper scythe.
There... that's unstuck...
now it should
cut right through you.
What... what are you doing?
No don't...! No... no--!
I must say, this is much
nicer. I prefer kicking
to being kicked.
That hurts!
Master... He's revolting,
but still a divine being...
Are you prepared to accept
whatever consequences come
of killing him?
Sebastian, do you need me
to repeat my order?
No, sir.
We've finally found
something you're good at:
screaming...
Very well done...
And, as a reward,
I shall kill you with
this cherished toy of yours.
No, please stop...!
Don't kill me!
So sorry.
I can tell you who killed
the kid's parents!
I apologize for interrupting.
Let me introduce myself.
I am William T. Spears,
an administrator
at the Grim Reaper
Staffing Association.
I've come to retrieve
that reaper there.
William...! Oh, William!
Did you come to save me--
Attention,
reaper Grell Sutcliffe...
You have violated
several regulations.
First... you killed people
not on the To-Die list...
Second, you used a death scythe
that had been modified
without authorization...
And finally ,
you offered someone
strictly classified information
regarding the identity
of his relatives' murderer.
I apologize for
all of the trouble
this wretch has caused.
Here, please accept my card.
Honestly... I never
thought I'd see the day
when I had to bow my head
to demon scum like you.
This is a disgrace
to all grim reapers.
Then perhaps you should keep a
better eye on your minions...
so they don't trouble us.
Humans are so easily tempted...
They will do anything when
in the grip of utter despair...
They will grasp at
any thread that promises
to save them from unhappiness...
No matter the consequences.
You should know that.
That's a charming bit
of hypocrisy.
You demons capitalize on that
quality more often than we do.
That I cannot deny.
Right now you seem
to be a tame dog...
That makes you
far less dangerous
than the rabid mongrels
running around free.
Now... come with me,
Grell. We're leaving.
We're already short-handed,
and here you've gone
and landed me
with even more overtime.
The Board is not
going to be pleased...
I assume you'll
want that, yes?
Yes, thank you.
Now, if you'll
please excuse us.
I'm sorry, my lord...
I allowed half of
Jack the Ripper to escape.
It's all right...
it's... done.
You're chilled
to the bone, master...
Let's hurry back
to the house now...
I'll make some hot tea
to warm you up.
That's a good idea.
Sir!
But master...?
No! Stay back...
I can stand on my own.
I'm fine... Just a little
tired... that's all.
Hey, look... The church
is really crowded today.
I wonder why?
Don't know.
But you're older than us.
Doesn't that mean
you should know?
You're stupid!
'ey, I'm still only twelve!
It's not like I'm supposed
to know everything yet!
You have a point.
At only twelve,
it would be a shame
if you did understand
what's happening...
Let me explain it...
Today is a special
noblewoman's big day.
What do you mean, mister?
Well... it's the ultimate
ceremony of any person's life.
The funeral.
She has departed
from us now,
as all mankind
must the earth,
as someday we all must....
Her flesh shall turn to ashes,
but her spirit will remains
with the lord....
Goodbye Auntie An...
You're here!
Is that the Phantomhive boy?
With a scarlet dress?!
How inappropriate!
Not so. Think of how
she loved the color red.
White flowers and plain dresses
didn't suit you in life,
and they don't now.
You belong in red...
the color of passion...
the color of spider lilies.
Farewell, Aunt An.
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady
London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down,
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady
London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down,
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady
London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down,
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady...
Rest peacefully...
Madame Red.
The funeral must be
going on right now.
Madam Red won't be coming
to visit anymore...
It'll be so quiet here.
Everyone, we need to
get it together...
A time like this
is when the young master
needs us the most,
you know.
--Yes, you're right!
--You bet!
Ho ho ho
So you've left us,
my lady...
You'll be with
your loved ones again now...
May you find peace.
What're you still doing here?
The investigation is over.
Are we sure?
How can we be certain...?
The circumstances are all
so shadowy.
I feel it's our duty
to investigate further.
Our country has
a long and rich history...
and with it comes a certain
number of secrets...
secrets from which I would
advise you to stay away.
It has been decided, boy.
This case is part of
the underworld,
and it will be solved
in the underworld.
Decided...? But by whom?
If you want to know,
get yourself promoted...
but I guarantee
you'll regret finding out.
Some rocks are
better left unturned.
Trust me on this, Abberline.
You're not going
to report the true identity
of Jack the Ripper
to the Queen?
I don't think it necessary...
She simply instructed me
to stop the incidents...
And now I have seen to that.
Your world is full
of quicksand...
and you keep letting yourself
sink further and further in.
But even if you reach
the point of no return...
and all looks lost...
you'll still never
call out for help.
No, none of us will hear
Lord Phantomhive's
pathetic screams.
The Queen's guard dog
is too proud for that.
Which makes you
a formidable opponent.
I'll have to be
careful around you.
Now that you mention it,
opium dens are beginning
to become a problem...
If you want to get out,
now's the time.
If I did that, I'd have to think
of another business to run,
and that sounds like
more trouble than it's worth.
Well...
You could always go back
to your home country.
Oh, but I haven't
exhausted my interest
in this country quite yet.
Or, for that matter,...
in you, my lord.
I fully expect more interesting
challenges from you.
We have somewhere
to go... Come.
This is her?
Yes, indeed it is... My last
customer from Jack the Ripper.
Apparently she
was an immigrant...
She had no family in the
country to claim her body.
So our kindhearted earl here
hired me to pretty her up.
Even had this gravestone
erected. A truly noble act
on his part, eh?
This isn't noble at all.
The noble thing to do would
have been to save her...
And... I could have,
If I put her life first.
But no... I had to
catch them...
Apprehending Jack the Ripper
was more important.
I knew they intended
to kill her.
I knew...and I let her die...
along with my aunt.
You regret what you did,
my lord?
No, I don't.... Jack the
Ripper is gone forever...
and I've done exactly
as her majesty asked of me.
Victoria, eh?
I don't much like her.
She just sits back and
watches while you do all
her dirty work for her...
It doesn't seem fair to me.
That's what the Phantomhives
do. It's our duty...
Passed down through generations
along with this ring.
That ring reminds me of a collar
a master puts on her dog...
You're forever tied to the queen
by the leash of duty.
I chose this life... Stop!
Lord Phantomhive... You
should be wary of the path
down which duty will take you.
That collar may choke you yet.
And we wouldn't
want that now, would we...?
Do come by if you should need
my assistance again.
You and that hilarious butler
of yours are always welcome.
It was noble.
Don't make me repeat myself...
What I did wasn't noble.
I thought it was.
But if you think not...
Then maybe...
it was weakness.
What?!
Tell me...
Why didn't you kill her?
Your own aunt
was threatening you...
It seemed like she
was going to take your life.
You could have stopped her...
You could have
defended yourself
if you wanted to...
But you wavered... Even then...
you refused to draw your gun.
Why, master...? Were you afraid
of killing Madam Red...
with your own hands?
Would it have been easier
if she was a stranger
instead of someone who
was your own flesh and blood?
I held back because
it was your job.
I knew that you would
protect me even at the cost
of your own life... That's why
I didn't draw my gun on her...
Our contract demands
that you serve me...
and that you protect me
with your very life ...
until I achieve my goal.
Until that time I'll not worry
for my safety... I imagine
you demons know nothing
of principles or loyalty...
but you do know about deals,..
And so, because of the deal we
have made... you'll protect me,
no matter the circumstance...
Am I wrong?
Of course not.
But you stopped me
from killing her as well.
When she moved to kill me, there
was hesitation in her eyes.
I didn't think she'd be able to
do it, not to me, her kin,
her sister's son. One wrong
move can cost you your life...
just like chess.
She hesitated and lost sight
of her next move...
That's all there is to it.
That's why I don't hesitate.
Now that's what
I expect to hear...
Always skillfully
manipulate your pieces...
That's how you survive.
Use me... and Madam Red...
and any piece
within your reach.
Even if the bodies
of your pawns
pile up at the foot
of your throne...
Because if the king falls...
this game is over.
I won't hesitate... I won't
regret the moves I've made.
Sebastian... You... you
you're the one person
who can never betray me...
And you can never leave
my side. That's an order.
Yes ...my young lord.
I will be there... Anywhere
you wish me to follow.
Even if your throne crumbles...
your brilliant crown rusts...
And a mountain of bodies
piles at your feet...
I will stay beside you...
We will sit side by side
atop your fallen pawns.
Until the last bell tolls...
I will be there.
My young master has been
ordered to develop a certain
village into a recreational
estate for the queen.
What a petty task...
Maybe there's something to that
revolting nickname of his.
The Queen's guard dog...!
Perhaps it's truer
than I thought.
Wag your tail...!
Fetch...! Good boy!
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler, Merrymaking."
You see... I am simply
one hell of a butler.