So, young master...
you wanted to speak with
us about something?
Yes, I have a little job
for the three of you
to take care of.
J
O
B?!
See, we didn't
have to worry!
When he called us, I thought
for sure we were fired,
yes I did! Whew!
This is a camera from the
famous Talbot collection...
It has a story
behind it.
It had been missing from
the collection altogether
for some time...
When it suddenly came up
for auction,
I bid immediately.
Who's Talbot?
Full name William Henry
Fox Talbot...
Let's see...
He was a renowned
English scientist
and one of the inventors of
photographic technology.
There were some strange
rumors about the last camera
he used...
the one our young master
has acquired...
Legend has it that if you
use this camera
to photograph someone...
whomever or whatever that
person cares about
most in the world
will appear in the
photograph as well.
Oh, my! That sounds too
incredible to be true!
Can such a camera really
exist, or is it just rumor?
Perhaps we should take
a picture and find out.
Don't move... The exposure
takes ten seconds.
Uh...what exactly
is 'exposure'?
Basically, the camera is
copying down an image of Finni.
Stay still or the
image will blur
and we won't get
a good picture.
8... 9... 10...all done.
You didn't have to hold
your breath the whole time.
Wow! Look at that...!
It's my bird!
Huh? Since when do you
have a pet bird?
Aw, it's so cute!
I gave it food
every day...
Eventually it started
eating out of my hand...
I was so happy, I went to
give it a gentle pat and...
My little friend
never moved again.
Are you saying that he...?
Yes, I forgot to
mention something...
The camera has one other
unique attribute.
The new soul that it will
show is not of this world...
To put it plainly...
the dead appear.
Only the dead?
You mean ghosts?!
You can see why I would be so
interested in this camera...
Not only does it know who
you care for the most
but it reaches into the other
world to photograph them.
But this is the
nineteenth century.
Surely nobody believes
a story like that now.
That sounds amazing...!
What an incredible
camera, master!
I miss my poor little birdie!
Take a picture of Sebastian
with this camera...
but do it discreetly.
I don't what him to know
what you're up to.
You want us to take
a candid photo?
That's right.
Really? The photograph
will show us
who Sebastian
cares for most?
That's something
I'd like to see.
Bloody right Finni.
He's always bossing us
around and mockin
my artistic
cooking methods.
He's as human
as we are!
He's got to have at least
a weakness or two...
and now's our chance
to see 'em!
You'll handle it?
As you wish,
young master!
Yeah...! That was a pretty
good impression of 'im, eh?
Just like him!
There's no telling
what will appear
if we take a picture of him
with this camera.
This should be interesting.
Let's see...
at this time of day
...he's in the library.
He needs to stay still.
For a full ten
seconds, yes.
I hope this works!
He's fast!
He's so fast I can't
even see him!
Damn, we'll never
get that photo!
Look...! He stopped.
Great...! Let's go!
I forgot to take
the picture.
He's so wonderful
to watch!
And next...
He'll straighten up
every room.
Look ooooouuuuuuuttt!
And after that...
He'll work on records
in the office.
Come in.
Yes? Did you need
something, master?
It came undone.
Of course, my lord.
He's beautiful in profile,
too, yes he is!
All right, now
just stay there!
Four... five... six...
Let's air this room
out a bit, shall we?
This is turning out
to be a lot harder
than I thought
it would...
Getting one measly photograph
shouldn't be so tough.
There you are. I have a task
for the three of you.
What is it, Sebastian?
Over there.
The mangy pooch?
What do you want us to do?
We'll be receiving a guest
this afternoon...
That thing is offensive...
You are to transfer it out of
sight before our guest arrives.
He's kind of a big fella.
Where should we put him?
I'll let you three
figure that out.
Oi...! We've got our own jobs
to take care of, too ya know.
You do have until
this afternoon...
I'm sure you can
take care of it
in between your
other tasks.
Maybe now I can do my own
job without interruption.
Plu-Plu...! Come here!
Up you goooo!
Oh, wow.
Now there's a surprise...
Who knew Pluto
could breathe fire?
Well, that's a demon hound
for you...
Hold on! We don't have time
for standing around!
Honestly, what's
taking them so long?
Something wrong?
No...it's nothing...
I think I'll take
my supper in here today.
Of course, my lord.
They couldn't handle
one simple task...?
I'm beginning
to think those three
would be more useful
as dog food.
How lovely.
A lithe, supple body...
And paws...
Such soft paws.
Cats are perfect.
Interrupted again...
Can a butler get
no peace around here?
We're so sorry, master.
B-But Bard thought up
a really good plan,
yes he did.
The idea came to me earlier when
I saw the dog breathe fire.
I hope this new plan doesn't
involve a flamethrower.
Damn.
My lord. Hello!
Oh, it's Mr. Lau!
And what are you
doing here?
I heard what
you were up to.
I thought I might assist.
Go away.
My lord, please
don't be so hasty...
Why not relax and
leave this up to me?
I have already woven a
spider's web to trap him...
and the more he tries to
struggle... the more entangled
he'll become.
Escape is impossible.
Against me... no prey
stands a chance...
It is only
a matter of time.
Very well... But I will
not tolerate any failure.
Is that understood?
Yes... of course, my lord...
I would not allow failure to
sully the Phantomhive name...
I would surely be booted out
of the country
if I did such a thing.
So...what are you up to?
Welcome, sir.
Hello I'm the writer from
Brit Business...
Paul Jones sir.
Indeed, Mister Jones... We've
been awaiting your arrival...
If you'd follow me inside.
Now... our plan begins.
That was your big plan?
Quite odd... How could it
have failed...?
Just look at her, my lord.
I was sure even the butler
would stop a moment to stare.
I was fool for
ever believing
you could handle
something like this.
I have only
begun to fight!
Not her...! Now,
where's Sebastian?
Coming, sir?
Oh...! Yes, of course!
How strange...
I don't understand.
What a spectacular waste
of time that was.
If I may sir,
allow me to introduce
Funtom's General
Director Tanaka.
Ho ho ho
I'll start in on my
questions then.
What's wrong...? Why is he
in there all by himself...?
Is he sulking
or something?
He said he wanted
to take a little time
to think things
over alone.
He seems to be taking this
quite seriously.
We need him to stand still
for ten full seconds.
This is the one thing
I didn't want to resort to.
But he's left me with
no other choice.
And now...
Could you please tell me
about Funtom's business
strategy moving forward?
Ho Ho Ho
Huh?!
Allow me to explain...
Currently we are focusing
on toys and confections...
but we intend to expand
into other areas as well.
As I was saying, sir...
Oh... yes?
The company is working on
plans to build outlets
across Europe.
We'll begin with branches
in Paris, Vienna,
Berlin, Rome, Amsterdam,
and Athens.
We intend to expand
into thirty countries
over the next
five years,
including those in
North America.
We'll also build a
confection factory
in Provence in
the south of France
and a toy factory
in Salzburg, Austria.
This will ensure that an
ample supply of our goods
is available.
We at the Funtom Company
always strive to maintain
and improve the quality
of goods and services
supplied to
our customers.
No item leaves one of our
factories without first
being subjected to numerous
quality assurance tests.
Only then can a product bear
the name "Funtom."
Our motto is "The customer
always comes first."
Our delivery system
allows us
to arrive at your business
or residence,
product in hand,
in record in time,
however remote the location.
Customer satisfaction
is guaranteed. That is the
Phantomhive way! See?
That's everything.
Th-Thank you very much...
But before I go, I would like
to get a photograph, if I may.
Photo?
I'd like to have you
in the shot, too.
I'm afraid
I must decline.
You see, I'm simply
one hell of a butler.
Today we are serving
Demon Hound Bean Cakes...
Manufactured in Houndsworth.
Why are you serving me
this rubbish?
Bard and the others purchased
quite a few of them.
How was the interview
this afternoon?
I only wish that you could
have been there, my lord...
Tanaka was
quite extraordinary.
That's good...
A distinguished
old man makes
a suitable face
for the company.
Yes...
The interviewer deigned to take
a photograph before he left.
Did he?
Apparently portrait photos
are all the rage
among the nobles lately.
Are they?
I know, young master...
why not try your hand
at it yourself?
No.
It's almost time...
Let's go.
Are you sure
this is okay?
Yes.
I don't know...
Do it, Finni!
Right!
Look out, sir!
What a charming picture
the two of you make.
You're late.
My apologies, sir...I was
making dinner preparations.
For the entrée
this evening,
we will have Canard
a la Rouennaise.
That's nice.
You could have just told me
to pose for a picture.
What?
Had you ordered me to...
I would have had
no choice but to do so.
I don't know
what you mean.
We finally got
the photo.
At last, we'll see the fruits
of a hard day's labor.
The young master will
be happy, yes he will!
Okay... I can
almost make it out.
Plu-Plu!
What's wrong, Pluto?
I wonder what all
the noise is about...
Do you know, my lord?
Good.
My lord has
outdone himself...
That was an elaborate piece
of mischief he concocted.
You do know you're
sleeping outside?
Excuse me, lord... We
should prepare you for bed.
Falling asleep slumped in
your desk chair...?
How irresponsible of you
But typical, I suppose.
Once again you have given
me unnecessary work.
Whoa.
Sebastian's in the picture!
That means the young master
cares most about Sebastian...!
That is how Tanaka said
the camera works, right?
Interesting.
Aw, they're
good friends!
That makes the master my
rival... What do I do?
Hey, it's Plu-Plu!
Huh...?! Hold on just a
second... That means...
Does this mean Sebastian's
in the picture
because the one who cares
the most about him
is Pluto?
I don't know!
Or is it the young master
like we thought at first?
Which one?!
I'm honored, master.
Oh, shut up.
It's your own fault
for falling asleep
so defenselessly like that.
How dare you!
The image in a photograph isn't
real... only an illusion...
But... that is
humanity's way...
seeking vainly to preserve
the image...
because you fear one day
it may be forgotten.
Hold on a second...
I thought the images the
Talbot camera showed...
were only of things
like my dead bird.
Weird... If that's true,
then why is Sebastian in
the photograph...? huh...
Finni!
Plu Plu!
Well...who cares?
The season has arrived
for the annual frost fair
on the River Thames.
My master claims to be
'inspecting the market,'
...But in truth, I know he is
enjoying himself immensely...
Watching his innocent,
childish joy makes my heart
feel positively tepid...
No, wait, warm...
I mean warm.
Next time on
Black Butler:
"His Butler, On Ice."
You see, I am simply
on hell of a butler.