Ooh...! What a nicely
mangled corpse this is...!
Maybe instead of covering
up the wounds,
I could accentuate
them with pink dye,
like the petals
of a lovely flower.
So much fun! So much fun!
What a great job I have.
Now let's see...
Who do we have next?
No, I don't like this one bit.
This is most unsatisfying.
Not a single wound
anywhere on the body...
How pathetic.
Excuse me, but what
did you just say?!
This morning
you have a dance lesson
with Mrs. Bright...
This afternoon an appointment
with Lord Wensler,
an import exporter... are you
listening to me, my lord?
I told you, I'm sick
of dancing lessons...
It's not for me.
You are too modest. Your
dancing soothes the heart
of everybody who
sees it in action.
By making them laugh...?
Is that what you mean...?
It is isn't it?
No, I would never say that.
Look, Tanaka!
Three upright tea stalks.
I think it promises
to be an excellent day.
Wait, I know you!
You're the queen's butler!
Greetings, Lord Phantomhive...
I do apologize for this
embarrassing display.
Why is the Queen's butler here
sipping tea at my estate.
So sorry, I thought you
were aware of his role,
young master...
This entire time...
Ashe has been her
personal messenger...
His job is
to deliver the orders
her majesty sends out
for you my lord.
That's not a job for a butler.
Forgive me,
but I beg to differ...
If I couldn't consult
the Doomsday Book
for those requesting an
audience with her Majesty
and travel here
to deliver a simple message
and then stop for
an elegant tea break,
what kind of butler would I be?
Yes, well...
having a tea break is
hardly a duty for a butler.
Well... if I may...
to what do we
owe the pleasure?
Oh, indeed.
Outside of Preston
there is a Catholic abbey...
It was burned down
during the Reformation
and is no longer in use.
A cult practicing the
Isna religion has begun
gathering there.
We have received word
that the cult's leader
is in possession of
the Doomsday Books
of all its many followers.
You mean the land registers...?
Where all livestock and
property is recorded...?
I don't understand. What could
he possibly want with that?
Oh no... their
Doomsday Books are
quite a bit different
than that...
They aren't the normal
records you're used to.
They don't cover property.
These are the records required
when you stand before
the Lord in Heaven
on Doomsday...
the Day of Judgment...
All your sins and
your good works are
supposedly recorded there.
I'm getting weary
of the occult.
There have been most
distressing rumors circling.
Apparently,
they're planning a coup
against the government...
Their activities as of late
have made the people
of Preston quake with fear...
Her Majesty worries...
She wants her people safe.
So what...?
Are you asking me simply
to make sure this cult
is disbanded...
Or is it more...?
Do you want them
completely eliminated?
That decision is yours...
We leave the choice up to you.
All right. Understood.
Pluto?
Who exactly was that?
Oh, he's a servant,
nothing more.
Is that so...? He seems an
interesting sort of servant.
Well... what next?
According to Ashe, the abbey
is heavily guarded...
That is something to consider.
So we can't just waltz in
through the front door, then.
Incidentally, he did
mention one more thing...
Apparently a large number
of coffins have been delivered
there in recent days.
Coffins, eh?
I'm coming in.
Welcome, little lord.
Listen up, Undertaker... I
have something to ask of you.
In that case....
I demand the very best
loving that Bassy
has to offer!
Wait, Grell?!
Hello, my lord.
What are you doing in there?
The bounder told me
he wasn't afraid
of grim reapers,
so I buried him in salt.
Yes he did!.
All the moisture in body
is being sucked right out
of it as we speak...
It's a great feeling.
An interesting opinion.
Tell me, what are you
doing here?!
Will gave me a job
to investigate, that's all.
But I couldn't find
any information...
It was getting late,
and I was tired.
So I laid down
in a field of flowers...
The next thing I know,
I'm waking up here
in this shop.
I should be careful
in the future not
to stop breathing
while I sleep...
but I was waiting
for a certain prince
to come along
and revive me with his kiss.
So, what are you
investigating.
Oh, nothing much...
It's the Grim Reapers' store
of Cinematic Records.
Some of them have been stolen.
Cinematic Records?
What're they?
Not something a kid
needs to worry about.
They are reels of film
containing all memories
from someone's lifetime...
Grim Reapers extract
them from the To Die list...
Then they decide whether
the person go from there.
That's basically it,
though you should be aware
that you humans can only
see them when you die.
And these records...
How exactly is it that they
were allowed to be stolen?
Well, you see... they're
stored in the library when
we aren't using them...
Good and evil...
the full past of everyone
who is destined to die...
all of their lives
are stored there
in the form of books.
So you reapers have
a group of books written
in preparation for Doomsday?
This is something you've
heard of before, isn't it?
Undertaker... If you will,
there is something
I need your help with.
Well then...
you do know the price
for that, don't you?
Ah well... on second thought,
I guess I'll do it for free.
I'm here to deliver the
coffins that you ordered.
Coffins...?.Are you certain
sir...? I don't believe
I have been informed
about a delivery like that.
I have the order right here.
My, oh my, where did I
put it? No. Maybe here?
All right then. Perhaps you
should come in, after all...
Your friends there
are welcome as well.
In that case, I believe I'll
take my leave of you...
I've accomplished
what I came here to do.
I understand. Thank you
for all your hard work...
I wish you only the best... May
your soul be truly cleansed.
Hey... I thought it was
supposed to be difficult
to get in here.
Yes... That is what
I thought as well.
They have such perfect
smiles... don't they?
Perhaps you should
be learning from them,
considering that you've
forgotten how to smile yourself.
Don't be stupid...
Those smiles were fake...
And you know it.
What is it my Lord?
Good evening!
Another gorgeous day
today, wasn't it?
Aw, well, look... aren't you
just the cutest thing...?
I really don't do well
with kids, though.
Hello there unclean one,
I can see every bit
of your impurity.
Say what?!
What's wrong...?
Is something bothering you,
unclean one...?
Are you not feeling well?
Ya Brat...!
What right do you have
to be calling me unclean?
Wah! An unclean one touched me!
We need to go
and be cleansed!
Another unclean one!
I'm sorry about that.
After a certain age,
everybody is
considered unclean.
I see from your clothing...
you're a new convert...?
Don't worry...
If you study the teachings
of our leader,
then you, too,
will be cleansed.
What...? How dare you!
Unclean...?
What a bizarre thing to say.
I can't believe a lady as
beautiful as you is impure.
We really don't know
anything about the religion
you practice yet...
Perhaps you would be so kind
as to tell us
a bit more about you?
Yes... but then
what are you doing here?
There was a bug.
Now, you'll tell me
everything I need to know,
won't you?
Oh no, stop...!
You'll make me impure!
Whatever--do you mean?
I've never known him to use
this approach before.
That's it...!
I'm going to put that wench
on the To Die list!
She's done!
Calm down.
Oh... I can see them...!
I can see the gates
of Heaven now!
I doubt that...
something is fishy here.
The Doomsday Books of those
who live a long life
are impure. Our great leader is
trying to cleanse the impure
passages... And make them clean
again but that isn't all...
Apparently... the Doomsday
Books contain more than just
our past. Our futures
are there as well.
Can you believe that?
The future... Interesting...
You don't say.
It's true... but only
the chosen children
of the heavenly choir
eligible to hear the words
of the future
written in the books.
What is this
'heavenly choir'...?
Do they all sing
hymns or something?
Well, I... I'm not sure...
singing might not be
the right word, exactly.
But I hear beautiful
sounds... They come from
our leader's bedroom.
If only boys are chosen
for this heavenly choir...
that means you're
the only one of us
who can get close
to this priest.
Rubbish! Just look
at this outfit!
They'll let me
into the choir for sure.
Well boys?
How do I look?
Wah! He's making me impure!
I hate this guy.
The time has come now
for the cleansing ceremony!
Cleansing, eh?
I was right... something
here does smell.
And what is it?
Nothing sir. Nothing more
than a rotten apple...
Dead fruit from a fallen tree.
Tonight... the unclean
will be made pure again...
It is time for the cleansing.
I suppose those books
are cinematic records?
I'm too far away to tell.
I shall read the Doomsday
Books of these impure,
lost children.
First Jill Fesant...
The second child of a farmer...
She conceived a child in sin.
Then we have
Thomas Atkins...
He has committed no evil
deeds per se but
he has spent his life
meaninglessly...
And that is
a grave sin to us.
I say!
What's happening?!
Snuff out the unclean,
and the unwanted,
and the unnecessary!
Snuff them out! All of them!
And now... despite
what they have done,
these people are
no longer unclean...
Our brother and our sister...
Now as pure as snow!
Our Leader!
What a great blessing this is.
Something's wrong here.
Those books that
the Priest had...
They were definatly
not Cinematic Records.
They weren't...? Does that
mean he doesn't have
the power to see
the past or future?
Ah! you're still here.
I'm so excited!
The heavens have truly
smiled upon you this day!
No, stop it...! I can
do it myself, okay?!
Nonsense. You've been chosen
for the heavenly choir,
so we have to cleanse
you from head to toe.
Oh my...!
What amazing skin you have!
Don't touch me!
You don't need to worry...
We can touch you.
We've already been cleansed.
That isn't my issue!
Pardon me. I can
take care of this.
No you can't...
You are still unclean.
You can't help here.
My goodness...
You think I'm impure?
Maybe you aren't
unclean after all!
No, he is!
Aren't you getting
a little carried away today?
No... I just want to
handle things smoothly.
My lord, I have
no intention of allowing you
to get yourself in danger.
I never thought I'd hear you
say that, Sebastian.
Quite so, but even if the
Doomsday Books are fakes...
I still believe they hold
some sort of power.
Unclean, he said.
That's what
the doll called me...
And there's this. This mark.
It's all I have
to cling to now...
The only thread the spider
has left me to grab onto...
It's my only clue.
And by grabbing hold
of that thread...
you'll be able to drag
yourself out of hell.
Is that what you truly
believe at this point?
No... I'm not
pulling myself up...
I'm dragging them down...
to suffer in this
awful hell with me...
Well that's my plan, anyway.
I would expect
nothing less from you.
There's only one thing I want
to hear from you now...
and you know it.
"Indeed... my young lord."
Leader... we've brought him.
Well done. You may
leave us now.
You look very... clean... Ciel.
Very good. Come this way.
Thank you for choosing me.
I... understand
it's quite an honor.
Very good.
And now there is something
I would like to read to you.
May I ask you, what is...
a "Doomsday Book," really?
For our purposes...
it's a story I'll read to
you for as long as you want.
Tonight is a treat, isn't it?
Mother said that
since it's my birthday
I can sleep in
the same room with her
and father tonight... and
she's going to read me
as many stories as I want!
Tell you what, I'll read to
you until you fall asleep...
Tonight's a treat, isn't it...?
It's your birthday.
What the...?
That hand... it's his.
Cleanse yourself.
Cleanse yourself of the
sins you've committed...
Right here and right now.
That's right.
It can't be. It can't!
Sebastian, this is an
order! Kill this man!
Yes... my young lord.
I thought it was you.
And I was right... Angela.
Uh... Bassy, what the hell's
an angel doing here?
Master!
Oh, look...! That's a real
Cinematic Record right there!
Do something, Grell!
Use your death scythe!
Give me a second, okay.
I'm working on it!
What are those sad things?
Well, what do you want
me to do...?!
Will just took my other
death scythe away from me!
I will show all of it to you...
all the light and darkness
Every moment in your past.
Master!
I cut it!
Here we go!
Master, you must do
your best not to look
into the past.
I know it's call is sweet
and it's lure addictive.
To avoid is to avoid
a part of yourself
that you may feel
that you're missing.
But you are fragile yet
and dipping even one toe
into that pool of nostalgia
could mean drowning...
you must see it.
Next time, on Black Butler...
"His Butler, Transmitted."
You see... I am simply
one hell of a butler.