[GOATS bleat]
[MALE OPERATOR]
Losing altitude, sir.
[MALE GENERAL]
How's the engine?
[MALE OPERATOR]
Seems normal.
[MALE GENERAL]
Is the load too heavy?
[MALE OPERATOR] No, sir...
It shouldn't present a problem.
[MALE GENERAL huffs]
What does he expect?
The armor is somehow going
to rise from the dead?
[MALE LOOKOUT]
What the hell?!
[MALE OPERATOR]
Can't stabilize altitude.
We'll go around the
mountain and fly over Sasu.
[MALE COLONEL]
General?
[MALE GENERAL]
We have no choice...
Possession of that
armor is essential
to the preservation of our clan.
Whatever must be done,
I intend to see that it's
delivered to Commander Folken.
[VAN yells]
[MALE OFFICER 1 groans]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[VAN, MALE OFFICER 2 grunting]
Stand down.
He's only one man.
[BOTH grunting]
[MALE OFFICER 2 yells, groans]
[MALE OFFICER 3 grunting]
[VAN growls]
Finish him!
[VAN chuckles]
[MALE OFFICERS grunting]
[MALE OFFICER 5 yells]
He's one man! Put an
end to it, already!
[MALE OFFICER 5 groans]
[MALE OFFICER 6 grunting]
--[VAN yells]
--[MALE OFFICER 6 screams]
[MALE OFFICER 6 groans]
Impossible... One man
can't kill so many!
[gasps, gurgles]
Well, then. You're the Dragon
we've heard so much about.
I'll slay anyone who
stands in my way.
[VAN laughing]
[VAN]
Dragon Armor...
You've slumbered long.
It's time to awaken.
Hear your name
and rise, Escaflowne!
You are my armor.
[STATION CROWD chatters]
Huh?
[SORA singing]
Who are you?
[STATION CROWD chatters]
[station bell rings]
--[watch beeping]
--[STUDENTS chatter]
[BIRDS chirping]
[YUKARI] Hey Sleeping Beauty...
You spend a lot of time napping
instead of going to
class these days.
You interrupted a dream.
What about?
Something that happened
when I was younger.
Oh... I think you
told me about it...
When you saw that man
at Tokyo Station, right?
[HITOMI] A strange man
in strange clothing.
Yeah, I remember.
[HITOMI] I wonder why I'm
having that dream again now.
'Cause you've become
pathetic and lonely?
Hey!
You could try
finding a boyfriend.
That might help.
[HITOMI sighs]
[YUKARI] I'm serious.
You're probably just bored.
You could drop by and say
hello to the team sometime.
[HITOMI]
I can't do that.
Of course you can!
In case you forgot,
I don't do track anymore...
It'd be weird.
Then just rejoin the team.
Problem solved!
I'm tired. My leg hurts...
It sounds like too much trouble.
You're pathetic.
[HITOMI] Yeah...
you've got that right.
[YUKARI gasps]
Hey, what's that?
[HITOMI]
What's what?
[YUKARI]
This letter.
--It's addressed to me.
--[HITOMI gasps]
Give it back!
[YUKARI giggles]
It's for me.
--Why can't I read it?
-- I'm serious!
[HITOMI]
Because I need to rewrite it.
[YUKARI] That's okay.
I'll just read it now.
[HITOMI]
Please, I mean it!
Don't open it!
[YUKARI]
Let's see here.
Ta-da!
"Dear Yukari. If you are
reading this, then I'm dead.
I hope you have a
good life. Farewell.
Sincerely, Hitomi Kanzaki."
[HITOMI grunts]
That's really terrible.
No imagination!
The prose was abysmal!
Shut up, would you?
Those can't be your
last words. For my sake!
I'd be embarrassed to
be known as your friend.
[HITOMI]
You don't have to worry.
Looks like I'm too much of
a coward to do it, anyway.
[YUKARI]
If you're going to die,
let me know before,
instead of after.
Who knows, I may even join you.
[HITOMI]
You won't need to do that.
I'm sure I'll live
a long time...
...until I'm wrinkled and gray.
Probably die in
my sleep, of old age.
[YUKARI] Oh! You're coming
with me tomorrow, right?
You promised, remember?
[HITOMI]
Oh, yeah...
Just give me a
wake-up call, will you?
[YUKARI] You're always
napping during class,
and you can't drag yourself
out of bed in the morning.
What's up, are you staying out
late at night or something?
[HITOMI]
It's nothing like that.
I'm just... sleepy all the time.
[HITOMI]
I'm always so tired...
I wonder why.
[HITOMI]
What's wrong with me?
Am I sick or something?
[HITOMI]
I mean, I feel okay but...
Everyone looks so happy.
I'm not.
That's why I sleep so much.
So I can just fade away.
But it doesn't
change anything.
I could fade away forever...
...and no one would notice.
It wouldn't change anything.
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT] There's been
an accident at Yoyogi station.
We apologize for any
inconvenience this may cause,
but we will be held
here momentarily.
Again, we apologize
for any inconvenience.
An accident, huh?
I wonder what happened.
Does it really even matter?
[footsteps]
[YUKARI, HITOMI giggle]
[HITOMI]
C'mon! Stop it!
[giggling continues]
[HITOMI gasps]
[SORA singing]
What's the matter?
Someone's calling...
Hitomi... you've been
acting really strange.
I, uh, still don't get why
you dropped out of track.
I am the team manager,
don't forget.
When people drop out,
Coach comes asking me questions.
[HITOMI] It's nothing.
Don't worry about me.
Hitomi...
This is getting annoying.
I'm tired of explaining myself.
Just leave me alone.
Forget about me.
Oh, okay.
[HITOMI]
I'm so tired...
[YUKARI]
Well, I've got some stuff to do.
So, I'll see you
at school tomorrow.
Just fade away now...
...you stupid girl.
Just fade away.
You're no good for anybody.
Just fade away...
Can it all be over?
[FOLKEN]
Yes... Let everything fade away.
[HITOMI gasps]
[FOLKEN]
This whole sad world...
...let it all just... fade away.
[FOLKEN]
Come, my kindred spirit.
[FOLKEN] I hear you
from the world beyond.
Come join me.
You are the Chosen One.
Are you talking about me?
[FOLKEN]
Yes.
You are the Wing Goddess.
You shall travel to our world...
...to fulfill our prophesy.
[FOLKEN] I bid you welcome,
Wing Goddess.
Welcome to the world of Gaea.
[gasps]
The Earth?
[HITOMI]
Is this all a dream?
Or is it a vision?
No... It's really happening.
What I wished is
actually coming true.
[OXEN moo]
The Mystic Moon,
so beautiful!
How gracefully
you adorn the sky!
[MILLERNA] No wonder it's
called accursed armor.
Possessing it seems to be
detrimental to one's health.
Everyone is nearly
in place now.
The Dragon Armor
is coming alive.
[gasps]
[HITOMI screams]
[VAN grunting]
[GADDES]
Millerna! The flying ship!
The Black Dragon Clan?
[GADDES]
Headed for us.
See? Precisely as I
predicted it would happen.
I hope you're planning to
reward me well for this.
Of course.
Can we talk actual numbe--
Are we really going to
shoot the ship down, Boss?
Don't waste your time
worrying about Van.
[MOLE MAN grunts]
[GADDES] You might be
overestimating him, you know.
[ALLEN]
Hm.
[VAN grunts]
He'll be okay. He'll be okay.
[MERLE]
King Van!
All right. Take it down.
Reeden! Fire now!
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN grunts]
It's alive.
[gasps] We stopped.
What's happening?
[yelps]
[gasps]
[HITOMI grunts]
What is this?
What's going on? Hello?
Can anybody help me?
[gasps]
--[HITOMI yelps]
--[VAN grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[grunts]
You look familiar.
Are you her?
Are you the Wing Goddess?
Have I found you?
[FOLKEN]
You are the Wing Goddess...
Wing Goddess?
What does that mean?
I'm a descendant
of the Dragon Clan.
My name is Van.
As a citizen of Gaea, I would
beseech you to allow me
the great honor of
serving you, Wing Goddess.
Serve me?
The Dragon Armor lives.
I will use Escaflowne
to fight for you.
Eliminating any who oppose
your will, any and all.
Just fade away now.
[gasps] I'm confused.
I don't know what's happening.
Where are we?
Escaflowne?
What is it?
What's happening to you?
[gasps]
It's gone.
Escaflowne's gone.
What happened?
[BATS chirping]
What is this strange place?
[chirping continues]
[gasps]
Some kind of jewel?
[VAN]
It was you.
You were the one
who sent it away.
[HITOMI]
What do you mean?
Huh?
Why did you do it?
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN]
Who the hell are you?
Why were you hiding
inside the Dragon Armor?
[HITOMI whimpers]
Answer me!
[gasps]
I think you should
answer him, Hitomi.
[VAN]
I bet I know.
You're a spy from the
Black Dragon Clan.
In that case... you die!
[ALLEN]
Hold it, Van!
[VAN huffs]
[gasps]
Allen! Don't interfere!
Why such a rush to kill her?
Aren't you being a
little bit impulsive?
I saw her! She sent
away the Dragon Armor!
Maybe. Maybe not.
But let her live.
She might be useful.
And besides...
I don't really care to see
a woman's blood spilt.
[VAN]
You can't order me around!
[ALLEN]
Hm.
[growls]
[VAN grunts]
I'll kill anybody
who gets in my way.
Yeah? Let's see it, then.
[VAN grunting]
[VAN yells]
What are they doing?
Are they really trying
to kill each other?
[VAN yells]
[VAN grunting]
[ALLEN chuckles]
[VAN grunts]
--[VAN yelps]
--[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN growls]
That's enough.
This is pointless, Van.
You know the
chief isn't serious.
If he was, then you
would be dead.
[MILLERNA] And you thought
throwing knives around
would help the
situation somehow?
I didn't hit
anything important.
[MILLERNA]
You'd better not have!
[REEDEN] Ooh! Is Captain Gaddes
being scolded by the princess?
[GADDES]
Reeden, get down here!
Sorry, sir. I was only jokin'.
[ORT chuckles]
Hey! Is that a
woman over there?
--[ABAHARAKI FIGHTERS murmur]
--[ORT] A woman?
Yeah, you're right. I thought
she was a man at first,
with short hair like that.
[TEO] Where'd you find her, Van?
Can you get any more?
[ABAHARAKI FIGHTERS catcall]
[MOLE MAN laughs] She is
the legendary Wing Goddess
whose coming has been
predicted since ancient times!
With her guidance,
Gaea will become a new world!
We should celebrate this day!
Praise be! Praise be!
Whatever, you crazy
fortuneteller!
[HITOMI whimpers]
Well, is she the one?
Probably, yes.
[MILLERNA scoffs] This is the
great and powerful Wing Goddess?
She doesn't look all that
different than the rest of us,
clothing aside.
You all right, Van?
[VAN]
Tsk!
[grunts]
Thanks for that.
[chuckles] Anytime you
want a fight, I'm game.
Just ask.
--[MERLE] King Van!
--[GADDES] Huh? Uh...
You jerk, stay away
from him!
[GADDES grunts]
[ABAHARAKI FIGHTERS laugh]
Girl can kick!
--[MERLE] How bad is it?
--[HITOMI gasps]
[MERLE] Oh, look at you!
You're bleeding!
You prissy bastard,
always making Lord Van
do the dangerous work!
I swear, one of these
days I'll get you!
[HITOMI whimpers]
[ALLEN] There's no need to look
so frightened, Wing Goddess.
Despite Van's unfriendly
greeting, we welcome you.
You must be weary after your
journey from the heavens.
If you'd like to come with us,
you can rest at our caravan.
Would you Please grant
us the Dragon's power
and the shelter of your wings.
Come... will you not join us?
[HITOMI gasps]
[WARRIORS yelling]
[FATHER FANEL]
So, it was you, Dune?
You were always a fool.
A reckless fool!
That's why the oracle
didn't favor you.
Favored one or not,
Van will die, Father.
I will see to that.
[SORA sings]
Time to wake, Commander.
[FOLKEN gasps]
Has the Wing Goddess
finally descended?
Yes...
However, she has descended
to another Dragon.
It's not as if there are
many to choose from.
[FOLKEN]
Van, then...
I find it hard to believe
the Wing Goddess
descended to that bastard.
Be aware, I cannot sense the
Dragon Armor's vibrations.
[FOLKEN]
I see...
Without resonating with both the
Dragon and the Wing Goddess...
the Dragon Armor will
not come alive...
And I am the only one who can
resonate with the Wing Goddess.
I wonder if that is so.
It's foretold that
the Dragon Armor
will lay waste to all of Gaea.
That includes you, Folken.
So be it.
That's precisely
what I wish for.
[WARRIORS yelling]
[MALE MESSENGER 1]
Gentlemen!
The King of Salas asks
that his life be spared.
The Black Dragon clan
has no need of slaves.
We will proceed as Commander
Folken has instructed.
Kill everyone. Burn everything.
[JAJUKA]
Such senseless cruelty.
They aren't content
to burn down villages
but have to slaughter the
innocent beast creatures
who inhabit them, as well?
What's left to conquer?
[gasps]
Finally. You're awake.
[HITOMI gasps]
[MILLERNA] I was beginning to
worry that you'd died on us.
[HITOMI]
Um...
We can't let you die.
At least not yet, anyway.
Who are you people?
I'm obviously dreaming.
I'm asleep right now.
I just have to wake up.
Then it will all be over!
[HITOMI gasps]
That hurt.
Oh? This must not
be a dream, then.
[gasps]
Come with me.
Wait! Please don't!
I'm sorry! No!
[grunts]
[HITOMI gasps]
[MILLERNA]
Well?
Did some sun on your
face perk you up a bit?
[HITOMI]
Yes.
[MILLERNA] We need you
to stay here for a while.
Um, why?
Well, we have to make sure you
really are the Wing Goddess.
I'm sure you understand.
No, I don't understand at all!
None of this makes
any sense to me.
To be honest,
you're not exactly
what I imagined a
goddess would look like.
Sorry...
[MILLERNA]
Enough about that.
What's your name?
You have one, right?
'Course...
My name's Hitomi.
I'm Hitomi Kanzaki.
Hitomi, huh?
That's a pretty
cute little name.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
My name is Millerna.
This world is Gaea,
and we're the Abaharaki.
--[HITOMI] Huh?
--[MILLERNA] We're survivors
of the nations destroyed
by the Black Dragons.
That's why we've
sworn to fight them.
Who're the Black Dragons?
[MILLERNA]
Escaflowne is the god of battle.
He will fight on our side
and ensure our victory.
[MILLERNA scoffs] That's what
the bard of Freid told us.
"Escaflowne will be resurrected
by the Wing Goddess,
who will arrive from
the Mystic Moon."
So says the prophesy, and then
you emerged from Escaflowne.
It's too much.
I just can't take it all in.
I'm really sorry... but I...
I just don't understand
anything that's happened.
I really am sorry.
Heh. I bet you're hungry, huh?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
We don't have a lot, but would
you like something to eat?
Oh, no, that's okay.
You're hungry,
aren't you? So eat!
Well... actually...
Yeah?
If it's not too
much trouble...
Uh-huh...?
I'm thirsty.
Can I have some water?
Or whatever it is you drink.
[MILLERNA laughs]
You're thirsty?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry.
If the Wing Goddess
really exists,
you know what I'm gonna ask for?
Better food!
I'm sick of the slop
we gotta eat every day.
Well, I'd rather be blessed
with good booze.
[TEO]
Does the boss really believe
in all this stuff, you think?
Hell if I know... maybe.
What do you think, Kio?
[KIO]
Don't ask me!
I've never seen a
real Wing Goddess.
--You haven't? Huh.
--[TEO, KIO gasp]
[grunts]
[PYLE]
What's with you?
[yelps]
[ALL gasp]
--[KATZ yelps]
--[HITOMI gasps]
Jeez. I don't really
look that strange, do I?
She is a little odd...
And that hair...
I think it's possible
she's from another world.
If she is the real thing,
the Black Dragon Clan will
find out. They'll want her.
Well then, whatever happens,
we can't hand the Wing
Goddess over to them.
Van, you're going
to keep her safe.
[VAN]
I don't think she's the one.
[ALLEN]
Are you afraid?
[grunts]
[ALLEN]
Well, shouldn't you be?
If she's the real
Wing Goddess,
the Dragon Armor
will appear again.
And If the legend
is indeed true,
Escaflowne will
be seeking blood.
The blood of the Dragon Clan.
You're the last of the
Dragon Clan kings.
It'll seek your blood, Van.
I took a wrong turn somewhere.
I'm definitely lost.
What do I do now?
[gasps]
Excuse me!
--[HORSE neighs]
--[HITOMI yelps]
Oh, sorry!
Is anyone there?
[MERLE]
Who is it?
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry...
[shouts]
Uh, excuse me.
I'm looking for water.
--I don't mean to bother you.
--Oh, yeah? Huh!
If it's water you're after,
then why aren't you
in the galley, huh?
I don't really know
my way around.
[MERLE]
Hmm. Hmm?
Hmm!
[HITOMI sighs]
You look weird!
I'm weird-looking? I don't
think you're one to talk!
[MERLE]
Are you really the one?
The one?
--[MERLE] Here.
--[HITOMI gasps]
I mean, are you
the Wing Goddess?
I don't know.
You should know who you are!
I used to...
But something crazy
happened to me,
and I'm still pretty confused.
Ah! Don't make excuses!
[sighs]
It's been a long day.
I'm exhausted.
You didn't look so
tired a second ago!
[MOLE MAN yawns]
[MERLE, HITOMI yelp]
[MOLE MAN]
Upsy daisy...
[MERLE]
Mole Man!
What're you doing
lurking in the straw?
[MOLE MAN] Is there any
better way to wake up
than to the sweet chirping
of two ladies' voices?
Such a sweet, cheerful sound!
Oh, shut up!
[MOLE MAN snorts]
[MERLE]
Huh?
Excuse me, my lady. Do I detect
the scent of a fine stone?
Fine stone?
--[MERLE] Hm?
--[HITOMI] Oh...
This thing?
[MERLE]
Hm?
[BOTH yelp]
[MOLE MAN] Oh! Ah, yes!
Exceptionally beautiful!
If I were you, I would
want to take good care
of a stone like that.
Perhaps you would allow me...
[HITOMI]
Mm-hm.
[MOLE MAN giggles]
Wow!
I wouldn't have thought you'd
be so good with your hands.
Good with his yakker, too...
Most quack fortunetellers are.
Must you always be
so cruel to me?
[MOLE MAN]
There. All finished.
Wow! It's perfect! Thank you.
[HITOMI]
Uh...
Now, the matter of
my compensation...
--[MERLE grunts]
--[MOLE MAN groans]
No doing business
down here, greedy paws!
--[neighing]
--[MOLE MAN yelps]
[MERLE]
When King Van was young,
his country was destroyed
by the Black Dragon Clan.
It's a common story here.
Isn't that the same
for the others, too?
So they're all fighting
on the same side.
[MERLE]
They met on the battlefield.
They've been
together ever since.
They must be
pretty close, then.
[MERLE] Not really...
King Van doesn't do "close."
He always fights alone.
It's his way.
That sounds pretty lonely.
[MERLE] King Van was
destined to become king.
His country may be gone...
his clan may be dead...
but he will continue
to fight his enemies
for as long as he lives.
That's the duty that
every ruler is born with.
I know he can seem fierce.
And even frightening.
But, deep down...
He's a kind, gentle person.
I know. I've seen it in him.
[GADDES]
Huh?
Ah! It's the king.
[REEDEN] Hey! How're things
going with the new girl?
[GADDES] I guess he
can't even be bothered
to make conversation.
Not with lowly men like us.
He's a king, after all.
Is that it there, Jajuka?
Is that the vessel from
which Commander Folken
wishes us to extract
the precious cargo?
Ha, ha. Well, Shesta.
What's the layout like inside?
[gasping]
I... can see...
on the lowest deck...
...starboard side. The stables.
A girl in white... I see her.
[DILANDAU] A girl in
white in the stables.
[JAJUKA]
Lord Dilandau.
it's important that
this plan succeed.
[DILANDAU] And all that requires
is snatching the Wing Goddess.
Yes, I'm aware. But, you know...
...I would rather kill them all.
Can't we do that instead?
The Abaharaki are
professional fighters.
If we lose men because
we ignored orders,
we'll have lot to explain.
[JAJUKA grunts]
Enough of your prattling.
You're worse than an old woman!
The sun's setting.
Heh. Now... It's time
for us to go hunting.
[MILLERNA]
Incoming.
Allen. Heads up, It's the
Black Dragon Cavalry!
This is going to delay
our arrival in Torushina.
[OXEN bellow]
[CAVALRY BEASTS growling]
[CREW grunting]
[JAJUKA]
Lord Dilandau,
this is supposed to be a
feint-and-grab mission!
Please remember that!
Charge!
[JAJUKA]
Wait, sir!
Kill anyone who approaches!
Don't let them inside
the transport!
[DILANDAU]
Let's go!
[GADDES] Stay close!
Hold your ground!
[DILANDAU grunts]
[ABAHARAKI FIGHTER 2 groans]
--[MIGUEL shouts]
--[ABAHARAKI FIGHTER 3 yells]
[grunts]
[GADDES growls]
[HITOMI] What happened?
It feels like we stopped.
[MERLE] Can't you hear?
There's a battle going on!
[MERLE gasps]
[NUKUSHI growls]
[BOTH scream]
Hey! Let us go!
Am I going to die?
[JAJUKA yells]
[DILANDAU laughs]
Damn it!
They're moving too fast!
[PYLE]
Huh?
[gasps]
[MIGUEL grunts]
[DILANDAU]
Huh?
[CAVALRY BEAST growls]
[VAN grunts]
[CAVALRY BEAST groans]
[gasps]
[VAN]
Merle!
Talk to me!
Come on now, open your eyes!
Please, Merle!
[MERLE whimpers]
Hitomi... He took her...
[VAN growls]
[VAN]
Hyah!
[yells]
[ABAHARAKI FIGHTER 4 screams]
The order called for a
feigned attack only!
Hyah!
[JAJUKA]
He's pursued.
[gasps]
[NUKUSHI]
Don't move!
[HITOMI gasps]
Who are you?
Stay still and keep quiet,
and I won't kill you.
[grunts]
[HORSES neighing]
[VAN grunts]
Are you hurt at all?
I-I'm fine!
Get back but
stay close to me.
[VAN]
Go away, Nukushi!
[NUKUSHI]
Huh? Your Majesty?
King Van of Adom! Is that you?
Why are you involving
yourself in a human fight?
Doesn't that go against
your clan code?
Just leave now and
we'll forget this!
Humans dragged us into
this fight! We had no choice!
[gasps]
The Black Dragon Clan.
They've destroyed
your lands, too.
[NUKUSHI]
Our village is in ruins.
And those who survived
were taken captive.
We forest creatures are no match
against battle-hardened humans!
We made a deal with
the Black Dragon Clan.
It was the only way
to save our people!
In exchange for their lives,
we agreed to take the
girl from the Abaharaki.
I beg you, sire!
I must bring her back!
[grunts]
I can not allow you to do that!
Now go, Nukushi! I have
no desire to fight you.
Forgive me, sire.
[grunts, coughs]
[VAN]
Nukushi!
[HORSE snorts]
Aw. It seems I've hit the
wrong target. Oh, well.
No matter.
The mangy creature had already
outlived his usefulness.
Jajuka. All we need is
to snatch the girl, right?
We don't need the man, do we?
So I can do whatever
I want with him.
[HORSES neigh]
[VAN growls]
Van?
[VAN grunting]
[DILANDAU grunts]
[DILANDAU screams]
[JAJUKA] Spread out!
This one has magical powers!
Keep your distance.
[panting]
[DILANDAU]
Oh, yes. That's right.
I forgot you were
with the Abaharaki.
[cackles]
You're him, eh?
The Dragon I've been
hearing so much about.
His strength is undeniable.
Hurry, get behind me.
It's you these guys are after.
Oh! Right!
[DILANDAU laughs]
[DILANDAU]
Oh, no. This is terrible.
I'm positively drenched.
I hate the rain,
It's so depressing.
Not to mention uncomfortable.
[DILANDAU] One of my soldiers
just died. Do you know why?
Because he was weak.
Foolish and weak.
Are you stronger than he was?
How long will you live?
Well, I think we
should find out.
It's playtime.
Let's have some fun.
[gasps]
Van!
[DILANDAU yells]
[VAN grunts]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[HITOMI shrieks]
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
grunts
[VAN groans]
[grunts]
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI screams]
[SOLDIERS yell]]
[screams]
What are those? White wings?
Van...
Are you all right?
[gasps]
I think so...
Thanks to you, anyway.
Hang on tight. Things could
get a bit bumpy up there.
[VAN grunts]
[HITOMI gasps] Van!
What happened? What's wrong?
They're disappearing.
[gasps]
Van!
There's so much blood.
What am I going to do?
Wake up!
Please, Van , wake up! We have
to stop this bleeding somehow!
Come on, Van. Hear me!
Open your eyes!
Someone help me!
Is there anybody out there?
Anybody? We need help!
Please, he's going to die!
Anybody!
I can't do this myself.
Someone please help him.
[JAJUKA]
Kinder to let him die.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[JAJUKA] That's the only
way to set him free.
To rescue him from the
sorrow of fighting alone.
Can't you see that death
is what he wishes for?
In death, there is peace.
[HITOMI]
What do you mean?
Sorrow does not cease.
It is a permanent
part of us all.
Until death ends it.
You're saying that
he wants to die?
Why would he?
Is his life that hard?
Is he suffering that much?
Van, why? Why do you
insist on suffering alone?
You don't have to do
it all by yourself.
I want him to live.
Even if he does want to die!
[HITOMI]
I'll wait.
I'll stay with him.
Until he realizes
he's not alone.
I'll stay by his side
until his grief ends
and his sorrow fades away.
There is no sorrow that
doesn't fade with time.
That's what I want
to believe, at least.
Just as, eventually...
...the rain will stop...
...and the sky will be
blue and clear again.
[FOLKEN]
I'm disappointed, Dilandau.
Why didn't you follow my orders?
I instructed you to
acquire the Wing Goddess
and bring her to me.
Instead you got yourself
mired in a useless battle.
--Disobedient fool.
--[DILANDAU gasps]
[grunts]
[DILANDAU yells, groans]
[FOLKEN] Who was
the one who saved you
from a life roaming the
wild with feral dogs?
Who was it?
[bone cracks]
[screams]
It was you, Commander.
[FOLKEN] And who gave you
command of the Dragon Cavalry?
I'm waiting...
[bone cracking]
[yells]
It was you, Commander.
[groans]
[DILANDAU]
Commander Folken!
[grunts]
[whimpers]
[FOLKEN] You will not disappoint
me again... Understood?
[yells]
[DILANDAU grunts]
There aren't many like you left.
Men who have Dragon Clan
blood in their veins.
That blood contains magic,
despite your inferior birth.
I have great expectations
for your magical power.
Yes, sir.
As a matter of fact, in spite
of your disobedience,
I am prepared to bestow
upon you a new power.
one that better
befits your status
as a scion of the Dragon Clan.
I want it. I want the power.
[MALE WORKERS chatter]
[MALE WORKER 1] It looks like
another of Commander Folken's
predictions has come true.
Hey. Let Mr. Dryden
know our status here.
Tell him the armor's
coming together.
[MALE MESSENGER 2]
Right.
Damn that thing.
The longer I look at it,
the creepier it gets.
[ALLEN]
A new armor in Torushina?
[GADDES] That's the news
Dryden's messenger brought.
Still have no idea where
Hitomi and Van are?
[ALLEN]
No.
Folken will be on his
way to Torushina soon.
We have to move quickly.
I bet that they're still alive.
And Van knowns
where we're headed.
He'll show up in
Torushina with Hitomi.
Have some faith.
[OLD WOMAN]
How did you find the meal, dear?
Was it to your liking?
[HITOMI] Uh, yes!
It was delicious, thank you.
[OLD WOMAN] I'm afraid your
clothes are still being washed.
It will be a little while
before they're ready,
if you don't mind waiting.
I can't thank you enough
for all you've done.
I don't know where
we'd be without you.
The people of Adom never
refuse someone who is in need.
It's not our way.
Sorry, but do you
think I could see Van?
[OLD WOMAN] I don't know
what good it will do.
It will be a while
before he wakes.
I understand. I just
want to see him.
[OLD MAN]
Hm?
--[rustling]
--[murmurs]
Come in, come in.
[OLD MAN]
No need to worry now.
We've driven the evil out.
The wound still needs
some time to heal, however.
He cannot travel
anywhere just yet.
[OLD MAN]
Until he is,
please feel free to
rest in our village.
Make yourself at home here.
Thanks.
[CHILDREN singing]
[MALE ADOM VILLAGER] Come on,
everyone! It's almost time.
[ADOM VILLAGERS murmur]
There he is!
King Van's coming out!
[ADOM VILLAGERS cheer]
[CHILDREN singing]
[VAN] The man who destroyed
my country is named Dune.
His Black Dragon Clan name
is Folken... He's my brother.
[HITOMI] Your brother?
But, why are you...?
[VAN] In my country, an oracle
decides which of the king's sons
will become the
heir to the throne.
It indicated that I would be the
one to rule, not my brother.
[HITOMI]
And for that he killed everyone?
My clan is gone. I'm a king
without anyone to rule.
I live for one reason only...
..and that's to kill my brother.
Sometimes life can feel
like a burden, can't it?
That's how it seemed
to me, at least.
I didn't know what
to do anymore.
I had lost all sense
of joy and purpose.
I was hurting all the time,
so I lashed out and hurt
anyone who tried to help me.
I was confused and adrift and
I just wanted to fade away.
Because then,
the pain would stop.
We're from different worlds,
but I think we're a lot alike.
We're kindred spirits,
so I think...
...I think I should stay
by your side, Van.
Maybe... you've been
alone long enough.
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Thanks for everything.
Take care of yourself, Ruhm.
Sure. The same to you.
The reports I hear say
the Black Dragon Clan
has Torushina under siege.
Yes, I've heard that, too.
But that's where my
friends are, so...
May the Dragon protect both of
you, always, wherever you go.
[GIRLS giggle]
Hitomi! Come back
and visit us, okay?
And say hi to Merle for me!
You hafta come back!
We had so much fun!
I had a lot of fun with
you, too. Thank you all!
You have such a
beautiful village.
We should go now,
if you're ready.
[HITOMI]
Hm.
[GIRLS]
Goodbye!
--Ride safe!
--We'll miss you!
Come back and see us soon!
Goodbye!
[HITOMI]
Mr. Dryden?
[VAN]
Right.
He's from a wealthy
family in Torushina,
and he's the Abaharaki's
financial backer.
We can find out where
Allen is from him.
--[song plays]
--[MEN murmur]
[ERIYA, NARIA sing]
[VAN]
What are you doing? Sit down.
Right.
[HITOMI]
This is such a beautiful song.
A ballad of the
Ancient Dragon Clan.
[HITOMI]
Huh? So you've heard it before?
Yeah... When I was young.
My mother used to sing it.
[VAN] In the darkness,
the Dragon wakes.
To the heart numbed cold,
the Dragon roars.
With you by my side,
the Dragon sleeps.
When the Dragon gains wings,
our hopes will
leap into the sky.
[MEN cheer]
You know, it's funny.
It sounds kinda familiar.
[MAN]
Hello there, strangers.
Are you enjoying our
music this evening?
I'd prefer something
a bit more upbeat,
to be honest with you.
But nobody seems
to be in the mood
for cheerful music these days.
Not with nasty soldiers
lurking around every corner.
I would like to see Dryden.
Dryden, was it?
Sorry, never heard
of him before.
[VAN] You must've.
He owns this tavern.
And what about you folks?
You wouldn't be Black
Dragon spies, now would you?
No! We are here to meet
Allen of the Abaharaki.
Hey, careful now.
Watch what you say around here.
It can be dangerous to
speak of the Abaharaki.
They're wanted
fugitives, you know.
Well, you're exactly as Allen
described you, King Van.
Right down to your quick temper.
[VAN grunts]
[MAN] And this lovely
young lady with you
must be the Wing
Goddess, Hitomi.
Huh?
I'm Dryden, the owner
of this establishment.
It's nice to meet you.
[MERLE]
You're here!
[VAN chuckles]
We are.
Hi, Merle!
You're alive and
still in one piece!
I've been so worried about you!
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[ABAHARAKI WARRIORS chuckle]
[HITOMI]
The whole crew!
[DRYDEN] Sorcerers have begun
the rite to resurrect the armor
that was retrieved from
the bottom of the lake.
It's just a matter of time
before they give it new life.
And we all know
what that'll mean.
If they bring the
damn thing back to life,
we don't stand a chance.
We're finished,
along with all Torushina.
We've still got one card
left to play, though.
Don't forget Escaflowne.
Maybe we should be
consulting the Wing Goddess.
I'll do whatever I can.
I don't know if I really
am the Wing Goddess,
but if I am, I would
certainly like to help you.
Oh! Exactly as the
Gadarasarai song tells us:
"Upon her arrival,
the Wing Goddess will
resurrect the Dragon Armor.
When her work is complete,
Gaea will be a new world."
That's part of it, but if
I remember correctly,
there's more to the song.
It also says "The Dragon Armor
will lay waste to all
of Gaea and vanish."
After all, it was
the Dragon Armor
that destroyed ancient Gaea.
Legend says the Wing Goddess
is the one who
summons Escaflowne.
Put it together,
and it sounds like you came
here to destroy the world.
[MALE MESSENGER 3]
All troops have been deployed
in Torushina. The tunnel
entrances have been sealed.
No Abaharaki soldiers
can penetrate our defenses.
[FOLKEN] We must speed
the armor's resurrection.
[MALE MESSENGER 3]
Yes, sir.
A newly-risen armor...
How many troops do you already
have under your command?
And yet, that power isn't
enough to satisfy you.
What of the Wing Goddess?
Has she arrived in Torushina?
Yes.
Very well, then.
I want you to use your power.
Summon her to me now.
As you wish, m'lord.
[JAJUKA] So, impure Dragon's
blood will be used
to resurrect the ancient armor.
[DILANDAU grunts]
This is vile,
Folken, even for you.
Has there been any word from
the commander yet, Shesta?
None so far, sir.
If something should happen to
Lord Dilandau, I swear.
Those sorcerers are
going to pay for it.
[DILANDAU groans, screams]
[booming]
You guys hear that noise?
It's coming from the airshaft.
[metal creaking]
[MERLE]
I noticed something.
[VAN]
Oh, yeah? What's that?
Your eyes are different.
They're a lot softer
and kinder looking
than they used to be.
[VAN]
Are they?
Absolutely!
Trust me, I can tell.
[MERLE]
Uh...
Ah! Thank you!
[VAN] Merle... after the
battle is over...
...let's go home to Adom.
Do you mean it, King Van?
[VAN] Heh. Yeah...
This'll put an end to it all.
One way or another.
[DRYDEN] Put it together, and it
sounds like you came here
to destroy the world.
[glass shatters]
[gasps]
What was that?
[SORA sings]
[SORA]
Please, Wing Goddess...
[HITOMI gasps]
Who's there?
[SORA]
The future is in your hands.
Please choose the path
of Gaea's destruction.
Only the end of everything...
can cease all suffering.
Destroy Gaea?
I could never do that.
[SORA]
I beg of you...
End the suffering
of this world...
..and Commander Folken.
I beg of you.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
He's calling me.
Van! Hitomi's gone!
--Where is she?
--[MERLE] Huh?
Not in her room?
Where could she have gone?
I don't know, but I
don't like this at all.
[gasps]
I feel a presence...
...It's Folken!
Hey!
[singing]
Over there.
[FOLKEN] You cannot know
how long I have been waiting
for this moment.
[HITOMI]
You're Commander Folken.
[FOLKEN]
Only I can end all suffering.
But in order to do that,
I need the power of Escaflowne.
[gasps]
No!
I'm coming!
[FOLKEN] You desire
the end of the world.
I've seen it in your heart.
[HITOMI]
That isn't true. You're wrong!
That's not what I want at all!
[FOLKEN] It is... The very fact
that you descended upon Gaea
proves that you
responded to my call.
[FOLKEN]
Come...
Together, we can do this.
We can end the suffering.
You're trying to kill Van.
That's all what you really want!
--[VAN] Folken!
--[FOLKEN gasps]
Take your hands off her!
Van! You're here!
[FOLKEN gasps]
So, you came.
Again? Once again,
are you going to take away
what is rightfully mine?
[gasps]
[FOLKEN]
So be it, then.
But you shall suffer
the consequences, Van.
[HITOMI gasps]
A trick all along!
--[booming]
--[VAN gasps]
What's that?
[DILANDAU'S ARMOR growls]
[MALE WORKERS chatter]
[MALE WORKERS scream]
This is amazing!
Like there's fire flowing
through my veins!
[DRYDEN]
And so it begins...
The future of Gaea
is being decided.
Will it be destruction,
or survival?
Which destiny will the Wing
Goddess choose for this world?
Now, Van, where are you?
It's the armor!
I have wings too, now.
What do you think of them?
No! It's coming!
Get it! Fire!
What?
Please, no! Stay where you are!
[VAN]
Hitomi!
Stop! Don't come near me.
[gasps]
[DILANDAU'S ARMOR growls]
Van... Please go.
Hitomi...
[DILANDAU]
Damn all of you!
[VILLAGERS murmur]
[gasps]
Damn you to hell!
[VAN]
Look out! Get back!
[HITOMI]
No, don't descend!
[HITOMI gasps]
It's Escaflowne.
[HITOMI]
Wait! Stop! Just stay back!
Please, you shouldn't do this!
If I use Escaflowne,
I'll be able to destroy
that other armor.
It's not worth the price!
Please, Van, I'm begging you!
It's okay. I have the Wing
Goddess on my side now.
Van...
Escaflowne! I offer
my blood to you!
Van!
[grunting]
It took his blood.
What will happen now?
[groans]
[HITOMI screams]
[MILLERNA]
This way!
Escaflowne! It descended,
just like the legend said.
King Van's in there.
All right, go!
[HITOMI grunts]
[grunts]
So, that's the much
vaunted Dragon Armor.
[MILLERNA] What are you doing?
It's dangerous! Get back!
He might need help!
I'll cut you down!
I'm going to destroy you!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Damn you!
[screams]
You did summon
the armor, didn't you?
Well, don't lose faith now.
You have to believe he
won't destroy the world.
I know...
[grunts]
I will burn you!
Burn!
[panting]
Burn until you're
nothing but ash!
[panting]
[VAN screaming]
Mom!
[trembling breaths]
[FATHER FANEL]
Keep fighting, Van!
The King of the Dragon Clan
never runs from his enemies.
You must fight!
Destroy the enemy!
[gasps, yells]
[grunts]
What the hell is he doing?
How is he...?
[VAN]
I'll kill you!
[grunts]
Stop! No!
I will kill you!
[screams]
I will destroy you!
[screaming]
I will crush you.
[gasps]
[DILANDAU grunting]
[DILANDAU]
What the hell is that thing?
[ESCAFLOWNE shrieks]
Boss, what's happening
to the armor?
So, this is the true
nature of the Armor.
Van...
[ESCAFLOWNE shrieks]
[FOLKEN laughs]
[FOLKEN] It has answered
Van's call and not mine.
So be it.
My younger brother can be
the one to destroy Gaea.
[SORA]
I wonder...
I sense the vibrations
of the Wing Goddess.
The desire she holds
within her is strong,
and it seems to be
reaching the Dragon.
What of it?
The legend of the Goddess
says that her desire
has the power to
change the world.
[FOLKEN] Her desire is
rooted in anger and hatred.
She doesn't wish to change
the world, but annihilate it.
Do you understand that?
She wants destruction...
and Van will give it to her.
[SORA] Commander Folken,
you poor soul.
[VILLAGERS scream]
[MOLE MAN] And now the Dragon
Armor will destroy everything.
I have to go to him.
Hitomi! What do you think
you're doing? Come back!
--[KIO] No, princess!
--[REEDEN] Please, stay back!
[MILLERNA]
Let go! I have to stop her!
[HITOMI]
Van!.Answer me!
Is this really the end?
And if it is... can I at least
see you one more time?
Let me see your face!
I want to stay by
your side. Please!
[HITOMI]
Van!
Hitomi...
[gasps]
[VAN whimpers]
[HITOMI]
Van?
[VAN cries]
Where are you?
Over here?
[VAN cries]
Where are you?
Van!
--[VAN crying]
--[HITOMI panting]
[HITOMI]
I can't find you! Help me!
[VAN]
Just leave me alone.
[HITOMI]
Please come out.
Don't leave me here by myself!
[VAN]
I can't go back!
I can't escape this fight!
I think you can!
[VAN]
You don't understand.
I'm always alone.
I was always alone, too.
[HITOMI]
It's sad living that way.
Lonely and painful.
[HITOMI]
I do understand...
But if we're together...
Even though we may hurt
each other sometimes...
...even though we
may have to part.
It will be okay.
Because I will never
truly leave you.
I'll always be here, with you.
[ESCAFLOWNE shrieks]
[ESCAFLOWNE growls]
What's going on?
What happened?
Is this Escaflowne?
The Dragon possesses the power
to seek the one who desires it.
[HITOMI]
Where you go, I go... Always.
[SORA] The Dragon
now has wings...
And it is flying
to you, Commander.
Very well...
You are free to do as
you please now, Sora.
You may leave this castle
and go wherever you desire.
Van is coming.
[FOLKEN laughs]
And bringing the
Wing Goddess with him.
[FOLKEN]
It is finally coming to an end.
Gaea's fate will be decided.
The Dragon Armor yearns
for me as I yearn for it.
And it seeks what I seek:
the total annihilation
of this world.
Free me, if you wish,
but I will remian.
to bear witness to your death,
Commander Folken.
[FOLKEN chuckles]
The prophecy of a divine being?
Yes, I will die...
I will destroy the world
and myself with it.
Hey, look! Is that a
White Dragon up there?
Yes... and it's a real one!
He flies among us.
It's the God of the Sky!
It's Escaflowne!
[BLACK DRAGON SOLDIER 2]
And look where he's going!
He's flying to Commander Folken!
Yes. He's here.
I can sense his presence.
[HITOMI]
Huh...
[BOTH gasp]
[FOLKEN] I've been
waiting for you, Van...
Last king of the Dragon Clan.
I will help you bear the
burden of your sorrow.
That is why I came, Folken.
Don't waste
your breath, brother.
[HITOMI]
Van!
[VAN]
Even if you do destroy Gaea...
Van.
[VAN] ...It won't matter,
your sorrow won't end.
You have no idea
what you're saying.
Don't you understand
anything, Van?
You are the source of my sorrow!
[HITOMI]
Stop this!
[FOLKEN] The only thing
I desire from life,
is to kill you
with my bare hands.
Now...
King of the Dragon Clan, get
back on your feet and fight me!
[VAN]
No! I won't fight anymore!
You have a choice:
Either fight, or die.
[gasps]
[HITOMI gasps]
Hitomi! Say something!
I'm okay, Van.
Really... I'm all right.
He didn't hurt me.
[HITOMI]
I feel sorry for him.
I was like that, before...
Numb to the pain and
suffering of other people.
Convinced that I would
always be alone.
[FOLKEN] That is why
you came to this world.
You were responding to my call.
But that's not me anymore!
I've changed since
I came here.
I'm not numb to Van's pain.
I can feel his suffering!
His sorrow is mine.
And you're the one
who created it!
Yes...
This whole cursed world
is filled with sorrow.
And its only hope of salvation
is its utter destruction.
I'm willing to destroy the
world to end its sorrow.
That is why I called you
and abandoned my own wings.
I pity you.
[JAJUKA]
Commander Folken.
There is something I've
wished for a long time
and now it will come to pass.
[yells]
[JAJUKA grunts]
[SORA inhales]
You have earned this
a thousand times over.
You have killed so many.
Now you, too, will...
[groans]
[FOLKEN grunts]
You wished for revenge.
[BOTH gasp]
[HITOMI]
Is he going to...?
[FOLKEN grunts]
Brother!
[FOLKEN] Stop!
Don't come any closer!
Brother...
[VAN]
Brother!
So long it's been since
I heard that word...
[HITOMI gasps]
You should go home now.
Leave here quickly.
With Commander Folken gone,
the castle will not remain
standing much longer.
Fly away from this
cursed place.
You have wings to carry you.
And what about you?
My place is here.
I will remain with
Commander Folken.
The castle's crumbling.
Hitomi.
White wings.
Dragon people are dancing.
Thank you, Wing Goddess.
Well, that's that.
The mighty Black Dragon
Empire has crumbled into dust.
Where shall we go now, I wonder?
There's always another war
to be fought somewhere...
Let's find it!
[CHILDREN, MERLE singing]
[HITOMI]
Look at that sunset...
It's so lovely here.
How long can I stay?
[VAN]
I don't know, exactly.
When the Mystic Moon
calls you back.
But until then...
I will be right here with you.
Good. I'm glad.
Whatever happens, we'll
always be together, won't we?
[VAN chuckles]
[SORA singing]
So beautiful...
Van, can you hear
that singing...?
Just listen...
[VAN gasps]