- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- ( patrons chattering )
- RYOKO, HUH?
WE HAVEN'T HEARD MUCH
ABOUT HER LATELY, HAVE WE?
- LIKE YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
I HEARD SHE SETTLED DOWN
ON PLANET EARTH.
- EARTH?
WHERE THE HELL IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY,
BUT THEY SAY IT'S OUT
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
- I HEARD THAT SHE WAS
LIVING WITH SOME FELLA.
- ( laughs )
RYOKO IS A WOMAN AFTER ALL.
HUH?
WHO-- WHO ARE YOU?
- HMM. SO I SEE WE'RE HAVING
A "MOST WANTED" RE-UNION.
- A BOUNTY HUNTER!
- Men: HUH?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING? HEY!
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
- THIS WAY.
- WHAT?
- OH!
- HUH?
- THERE'S NO NEED
FOR YOU TO WORRY.
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN YOU AT ALL.
- IT-- IT CAN'T BE.
YOU CAN'T BE.
- NOW TELL ME MORE.
TELL ME MORE ABOUT RYOKO.
- YO!
- ( grunts )
PHEW.
RYO-OHKI WILL BE HAPPY.
THAT'S A LOT OF CARROTS.
HUH?
AH-HA.
IS THAT YOU, RYO-OHKI?
CALM DOWN.
THESE CARROTS ARE ALL FOR YOU.
RYO-OHKI?
BUT YOU AREN'T-- HUH?
HUH? AAH!
- WHERE IS RYOKO!
( groans )
RYOKO!
ALL RIGHT,
NOW WHERE IS RYOKO?
- WELL...
- ( grunts )
NOW TELL ME THE TRUTH.
YOU'LL REGRET IT IF YOU
TRY TO HIDE THINGS FROM ME.
- ( chews )
( gulps )
SORRY, UM, EVERYBODY TOLD ME
TO STAY FOR SNACKS,
SO I WASN'T EATING
YOUR SHARE OR ANYTHING.
AT LEAST,
I HOPE I WASN'T.
- THIS ISN'T ABOUT SNACKS,
TWIT.
- SHE JUST GOT HERE.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I CANNOT FIND TENCHI.
- WHAT?
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR RYOKO.
- OW!
- WHAT I AM SAYING
IS THAT RYOKO MUST HAVE
TAKEN TENCHI WITH HER
TO SOME PRIVATE PLACE,
AND NONE OF YOU SEEM
TO CARE AT ALL.
RYOKO!
WHERE DID YOU GO?
YOU CANNOT HIDE FROM ME!
- SO THIS IS WHAT YOU
HAVE TO DEAL WITH, SASAMI?
- ( giggles )
- RYOKO, HURRY UP!
- YOU KNOW, SHE'S GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE THESE DAYS,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( meows )
( meows )
- WHAT'S WRONG RYO-OHKI?
- ( hisses )
- HUH?
- THERE'S SOMETHING UP THERE.
- OH NO, YOU THINK
IT COULD BE A RAT?
- A RAT CAN'T BE THAT BIG,
MIHOSHI.
- IS IT A CAT?
HUH?!
- WHOA!
- AAH!
- ( hisses )
- OH!
- WOW! HOW CUTE.
- HE LOOKS EXACTLY
LIKE RYO-OHKI.
- WELL, HOW DID HE
GET IN HERE?
- SO IS HE A FRIEND
OF RYO-OHKI?
- ( hisses )
- RYO-OHKI.
- ( both hiss )
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM,
YOU TWO?
- HEY, RYO-OHKI!
YOU SHOULDN'T BE SO HOSTILE.
- ( meows )
- NOW TRY TO GET ALONG
OR I WON'T GIVE YOU
ANYMORE CARROTS.
- CAN YOU BE FRIENDLY
TO THAT NEWCOMER?
- ( meows )
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S MY GIRL.
I GOT SOME FOR YOU TOO.
THERE.
YOU TWO EAT TOGETHER, OKAY?
- ( meows )
( chews )
- WELL, HE DOESN'T SEEM TO
LIKE CARROTS, NOW, DOES HE?
- HEY, THEY'RE
REALLY REALLY GOOD.
COME ON.
HERE, TRY SOME.
- ( sniffs )
( chews )
MM!
- YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT.
- HE ATE THEM OKAY.
- THEY ARE THE SAME
SPECIES, ALL RIGHT.
NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
- HERE. HAVE SOME MORE,
YOU LITTLE CUTIE.
( chuckles )
- ( both meow )
( chewing )
- THEY SURE ARE CRAZY ABOUT
CARROTS, AREN'T THEY?
- THEY SURE ARE.
- ( meows )
- YES, BUT WHO DOES
HE BELONG TO, I WONDER?
- ( both meow )
- ( chuckles )
HE'S SO SWEET, ISN'T HE?
- HE MUST HAVE BEEN
BROUGHT UP REALLY WELL.
- YOU MUST BE HAPPY,
RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- ( sighs )
THAT WAS A NICE BATH.
TAKING A BATH IN THE DAYTIME
FEELS SO GOOD.
IT'S-- IT'S KENOKI!
- KENOKI?
- DO YOU KNOW HIM, RYOKO?
HUH.
- KENOKI?
SO THAT'S HIS NAME, IS IT?
- NO WAY. SHE CAN'T BE
HERE ON THE EARTH.
- HMM.
- HUH?
- ( meows )
- AAH!
- KENOKI, COME BACK!
- WE'VE GOT TO FOLLOW HIM,
NOW.
- ( meowing )
- CAN SOMEBODY TELL ME WHAT
IN THE WORLD IS GOING ON?
- ( all panting )
- WHAT IS HAPPENING,
RYOKO?
HMM?
SO IT'S JUST AS I THOUGHT.
- LONG TIME NO SEE,
RYOKO.
- I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D TRAVEL
THIS FAR A DISTANCE AFTER ME.
- HMM. THAT'S WHAT
I DO FOR A LIVING.
I AM A BOUNTY HUNTER.
I TOLD YOU ONCE ALREADY
THAT I'D TAKE YOUR HEAD.
- NAGI!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE A BOUNTY HUNTER.
THIS IS MY JURISDICTION,
AND BOUNTY HUNTERS MUST
STAY OUT OF THIS AREA.
- ARE YOU KIYONE?
- HMM.
YOU'VE HEARD OF ME.
- THEY SAY YOU'RE THE BEST
AMONG THE YOUNGER GENERATION
OF THE GALAXY POLICE.
- All: OHH!
- BUT NOW YOU'RE ASSIGNED TO
A STATION IN THIS REMOTE REGION,
THE RUMOR HAS IT THAT YOU'RE
DOWN ON YOUR LUCK.
- ( growls )
THAT'S NOT MY FAULT!
IT'S BECAUSE OF
MY PARTNER HERE.
- HMM.
THAT'S A BIT LOW,
BLAMING OTHERS FOR
YOUR PROBLEMS.
- HEY, YOU.
YOU LISTEN TO ME NOW.
KIYONE IS NOT A LOSER,
ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S GETTING 200 MORE YEN
PER HOUR THAN ME,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW.
- ( grunting )
WILL YOU KEEP YOUR
MOUTH SHUT, PLEASE?
- RYOKO,
I'VE TAKEN YOUR MAN
AS A HOSTAGE.
- YOU MEAN TENCHI?
- IF YOU WANT YOUR MAN BACK,
COME TO VENUS.
WE'LL SETTLE THE MATTER THERE.
- HEY, YOU!
TENCHI IS NOT RYOKO'S MAN.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
PLEASE UNDERSTAND
THE SITUATION CORRECTLY.
- KENOKI!
- ( howls )
- HUH?
- ( growls )
- I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU,
RYOKO.
- HEY, COME BACK.
- ( laughs )
- ( meows )
- ( murmurs )
- YO!
- RYOKO!
- ( gasps )
- I'VE TOLD YOU THAT I WOULD
GET THE REWARD FOR YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU GO.
NOT YOU. NEVER.
( chuckles )
WE ARE HAVING SOME FUN,
HUH?
AREN'T WE?
- NOW, RYOKO!
I NEED SOME EXPLANATION HERE.
I CANNOT STAND IT.
TENCHI IS YOUR MAN?
THAT IS NOT THE TRUE
STORY AT ALL, IS IT?
- AYEKA, THAT'S NOT WHAT
WE SHOULD BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
- YEAH. WHO OR WHAT IS
THIS NAGI PERSON ANYWAY, HUH?
( sighs )
KIYONE?
- SHE'S A PROFESSIONAL
BOUNTY HUNTER.
SHE'S A LONE WOLF WHO GOES
AFTER WANTED CRIMINALS
FOR THE REWARD, AND
SHE'S THE VERY BEST
IN THE UNIVERSE AT WHAT
SHE DOES.
- AND SHE'S AFTER RYOKO!
OH NO.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- NAGI?
SHE AND I GO WAY BACK.
SORT OF LIKE
ARCH-RIVALS.
THE WANTED AND THE HUNTER.
WE HAVE FACED EACH OTHER
MANY TIMES IN THE PAST.
( shouts, grunts )
- AAH.
- ( grunts )
- ( laughs ) YOU CAN'T
GET AWAY FROM ME, RYOKO.
( laughs )
- ( shouts )
- OF ALL THOSE
HUNTED DOWN BY HER,
NOBODY HAS EVER SURVIVED.
EXCEPT FOR ME.
BUT THIS TIME,
I DON'T KNOW...
WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
- ( strains )
( grunts )
- HMM.
THIS GUY IS RYOKO'S?
- HUH?
- WE'RE ALMOST TO VENUS.
THERE SHE IS.
THIS IS JUST BETWEEN
ME AND HER, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU HAVE GOT TO STAY
OUT OF THIS, KIYONE.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
THIS IS A LEGITIMATE
CASE OF KIDNAPPING.
- I BEG YOU.
- WELL, RYOKO,
ALL RIGHT.
- I'M COMING, TENCHI.
- ( chuckles )
HERE YOU COME, RYOKO.
- NOW FIRE, RYO-OHKI!
WHAT'S WRONG, RYO-OHKI?
I SAID "FIRE."
- ( meows )
- KENOKI, FIRE!
- ( shouts )
- ( screams )
- OH, GREAT!
- ( stammering )
- COME ON, RYO-OHKI!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
SHOOT BACK!
- ( chuckles )
BEING IN LOVE WITH A GUY
HAS MADE YOU SOFT, HUH?
- RYO-OHKI!
- OKAY, KENOKI,
FINISH HER!
WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KENOKI?
- ( meows )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT STOPPED FIRING.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
- KENOKI IS NOT
OBEYING MY ORDERS.
RYO-OHKI IS IGNORING YOURS TOO?
- YEP.
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
SETTLE THE MATTER OURSELVES.
- FINE WITH ME.
WHERE SHALL WE DO IT?
- I, WASHU, SHALL PREPARE
A SPOT FOR YOU.
- HUH?
- YEE-HAW!
HOW'S THIS NICE AMBIANCE
FOR YOU?
- ( all gasp )
- YOU ARE ENJOYING THIS,
AREN'T YOU, WASHU?
- MM-HMM.
- HUH?
- HMM?
- SHE'S HERE.
- WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
- WHERE IS TENCHI?
- DON'T WORRY.
HE'S RIGHT HERE.
- ( grunting )
- TENCHI!
- IF YOU WIN,
I'LL GIVE HIM BACK TO YOU.
FAIR ENOUGH?
- FAIR ENOUGH.
- GOOD LUCK TO YOU,
RYOKO.
- RYOKO, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU DIE,
BUT DON'T LOSE, OKAY?
- ( both grunting )
- ( shouts )
- ( chuckles )
- ( shouts, grunts  )
- THE GAME IS OVER,
RYOKO.
- NO IT'S NOT.
- BYE-BYE, RYOKO.
- NOW TENCHI,
LET ME GET YOU OUT OF THERE.
- ( grunts )
- DO NOT MIND RYOKO.
I WILL GET YOU
OUT OF THIS MESS.
- AH! WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- ( giggles )
EXCUSE US, RYOKO,
BUT YOU KNOW
AS WELL AS I
TENCHI AND I WERE ALWAYS
MEANT TO BE TOGETHER.
YOU WILL WISH US
GOOD LUCK, WON'T YOU?
- AYEKA,
YOU'RE JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
- YOUR DEATH WILL
NOT BE IN VAIN.
PLEASE EXCUSE US NOW.
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- YAY!
- WE DID IT.
- ( meows )
- ( winces )
- ( shouts )
- ( sighs )
- HUH?
- HMM.
- IT'S JUST AS IF WE HAD
PLANNED IN ADVANCE,
ISN'T IT, RYOKO?
- OUR FRIENDSHIP
BROUGHT US THIS VICTORY.
- ( both laugh )
- THIS CAN'T BE TRUE.
- IT ISN'T.
- WELL, LET'S SEE NOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU WON, RYOKO.
KILL ME THEN.
- VERY WELL.
AS YOU WISH IT, NAGI.
OH--
- ( hisses )
- ( meows )
- HUH?
- ( hisses )
- ( meows )
( meows )
- ( sighs )
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO.
LEAVE BEFORE I
CHANGE MY MIND.
- YOU'LL REGRET THIS.
- I DOUBT IT.
I'VE NEVER EVER REGRETTED
ANYTHING I'VE DONE
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
- ( meows )
- LET'S GO, KENOKI.
- ( howls )
- NAGI WAS JUST AS STRONG
AS I HAD HEARD.
- YEAH.
IF AYEKA HADN'T INTERFERED
FOR HER OWN
SELFISH REASONS,
NAGI WOULD HAVE WON.
- ( meows )
- YOU KNOW, I THINK THAT
RYO-OHKI LIKES KENOKI.
- WHAT?  SERIOUSLY?
NO WAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT THAT.
- ( meows )
- NOW YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
GET OVER HIM, RYO-OHKI.
THERE ARE MUCH BETTER GUYS
JUST WAITING OUT THERE
IN THE UNIVERSE FOR YOU.
- HUH? YOU MEAN
TO TELL ME
RYO-OHKI IS A GIRL?
- GET A CLUE,
WILL YOU, MIHOSHI?
- UH-OH.
WHERE'S TENCHI?
- I ALMOST FORGOT
ABOUT HIM.
TENCHI!
- ( all gasp )
- ARE YOU GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT, TENCHI?
- YES.
THANK YOU, SASAMI.
- SASAMI GOT THERE
FIRST AGAIN.
- THAT SHOULD BE ME.
- ( both sigh )
- ( meows )
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- WELL THANK YOU ALL
FOR WAITING.
NOW WE'LL PRESENT
TENCHI'S SPECIAL EVENTS
WITH UTMOST CONFIDENCE
IN SUCCESS.
- THE DIMENSIONAL CONTROLLER
INVENTED BY WASHU
GOES TOTALLY OUT OF CONTROL!
BLASTED INTO RANDOM
TIME AND SPACE,
OUR DESTINY IS
BLOWING IN THE WIND.
- THE WHEEL OF FORTUNE
IS EVER IN MOTION.
IT'S A STUPENDOUSLY
FANTASTIC STORY.
- COMING NEXT IS
"JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
AND SPACE: PART ONE."
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
FANTASTIC.