- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- Kamidake: PRINCESS AYEKA,
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
- Azaka:
THE MARRIAGE MEETING
SEEMS TO HAVE EXHAUSTED YOU,
PRINCESS AYEKA.
MAY I SUGGEST YOU
HAVE SOME REST
BEFORE WE ARRIVE
AT PLANET JURAI?
- AS SOON I RETURN
TO TO PLANET JURAI,
I'LL HAVE TO DEPART FOR ANOTHER
MARRIAGE MEETING, WON'T I?
- Kamidake: YES, PRINCESS, BUT--
- I KNOW, YES, IT IS MY DUTY
AS THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
YES, I KNOW IT
TOO WELL.
- ( man howls )
- HEY, TENCHI. COME ON,
TENCHI, LET'S GO PLAY.
YOUR SILLY CHORES
ARE BORING.
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW GRANDPA'S VERY FUSSY
ABOUT KEEPING THE SHRINE CLEAN.
- ( hums )
- HUH?
MIHOSHI, WHAT IS THAT THING?
- A SPECIAL DEVICE
MADE EXCLUSIVELY
FOR THE GALAXY POLICE.
YOU TURN IT THIS WAY
AND THAT WAY.
THERE!  I CAN SEND OUT
A DISTRESS SIGNAL NOW.
- WE'RE IN THE BOONIES, KIDDO.
CAN YOU REALLY COUNT
ON A TOY LIKE THAT?
- ACCORDING TO
THE STATISTICS,
ONE CASE IN 200 YEARS
IS REPORTED TO RESULT
IN SUCCESSFUL RESCUE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- ( gong rings )
- ( whimpers )
( cries )
WELL, IT'S BETTER THAN
JUST SITTING AROUND
HERE DOING NOTHING!
- EH?
- WHAT IS IT AZAKA?
- PRINCESS AYEKA,
WE ARE PICKING UP
A DISTRESS SIGNAL.
- REALLY? FROM WHERE?
- JUST A MOMENT.
I'LL FIND OUT.
FROM THE THIRD PLANET
OF A NEARBY SOLAR SYSTEM.
- WELL, WE CAN'T JUST IGNORE IT,
I GUESS.
WE HAVE SOME TIME LEFT
BEFORE OUR SCHEDULED RENDEZVOUS
WITH SASAMI, DON'T WE?
- YES, YOUR HIGHNESS.
- HEAD FOR THAT PLANET.
LET'S GO.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HECK?
- UH-OH.
- HOORAY!  HERE I AM.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
YAHOO!
- HMM, THAT SPACESHIP
LOOKS AWFULLY FAMILIAR.
LET'S WAIT AND SEE.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
YAHOO!
( giggles )
OH.
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
- ARGH!
- MMM?
- HUH?
- Both: YOU?!
IT CAN'T BE!
- WHAT?
- SO YOU'RE STILL ALIVE,
MISS RYOKO.
THOSE GALAXY POLICE HAVE BECOME
SO INCOMPETENT THESE DAYS.
- AND I THOUGHT
THIS PLANET WAS REMOTE,
BUT HERE YOU ARE.
WHAT? HAS JURAI ROYAL FAMILY
FALLEN OR SOMETHING?
ARE YOU IN EXILE?
- ( growls )
( laughs )
YOU'RE SUCH A JOKER.
YOU KNOW JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
WILL LAST FOREVER.
WE'RE EVERLASTING.
- WHAT? JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
IS NEVER-LASTING?
- EVERLASTING!
- WELL, ISN'T THAT TOO BAD.
- OH, UH, EXCUSE ME.
YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING TO RESCUE ME.
YOU SEE,
I'M THE ONE
WHO SENT OUT
THE DISTRESS SIGNAL AND...
HELLO, EXCUSE ME.
- YOU MEAN, I CAME ALL THIS WAY
TO RESCUE SOMEONE
ONLY TO MEET A LOWLY DISGUSTING
CREATURE LIKE YOU?!
- YEAH, WELL, I NEVER
ASKED YOU TO COME,
YOUR ROYAL LOWNESS.
- WELL, YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WAS ME WHO ASKED YOU TO COME.
- HOW UNPLEASANT!
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
WE ARE LEAVING!
- Both: YES, MA'AM.
- YEAH, GREAT.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
SHE'S MY RIDE OUT OF HERE.
- GOOD RIDDANCE
TO BAD RUBBISH.
- J-- HEY!
- HMPH!
RESCUE,
WHAT A WASTE OF MY TIME.
- NO, WAIT!
DON'T GO!
( gasps ) OH PLEASE
DON'T LEAVE, PLEASE!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M IN DISTRESS.
I TOLD YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, LET GO NOW.
- PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME.
DON'T GO.  DON'T GO.
- ( both whine )
- ALL RIGHT!
NOW JUST LET ME GO!
- PLEASE HELP YOURSELF.
- ( sipping )
- SO YOU COME FROM A PLANET
CALLED JURAI, DID YOU SAY?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I WONDER, COULD YOU TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR PLANET?
TELL ME ABOUT JURAI,
ABOUT ITS MOUNTAINS,
VALLEYS,
ITS PEOPLE AND PLANTS.
- WELL, YES.
- YOU JUST CAN'T
BE SO RUDE TO HER.
SHE CAME HERE
TO RESCUE MIHOSHI.
- TENCHI'S RIGHT.
SHE ALMOST LEFT ME HERE
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
- NOW, LISTEN.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF WITCH SHE REALLY IS.
- COULD YOU PLEASE
WORK ON YOUR ATTITUDE?
- HOW DO YOU HAPPEN
TO KNOW EACH OTHER, ANYWAY?
A PRINCESS OF
JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
AND A MOST-WANTED CRIMINAL?
- IT WAS WHEN-- YES.
WHEN I WAS JUST
A YOUNG INNOCENT CHILD.
I WAS PLAYING IN A FLOWER FIELD
ON A PLANET.
SO MANY FLOWERS
AND SO MANY COLORS ALL IN BLOOM.
( sighs ) IT WAS SO PRETTY.
- HEY, YOU!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
- HUH?
- THIS PLANET IS JURAI
ROYAL FAMILY'S TERRITORY.
JUST WHO GAVE YOU THE PERMISSION
TO PLAY AROUND HERE?
- BUT I WAS JUST--
- YOU BETTER
GET OUT OF HERE AND QUICK.
- OKAY.
- NOPE.
- ( gasps)
- YOU CAN'T TAKE THOSE WITH YOU.
- BUT I--
- DON'T BUT ME.
I TOLD YOU THIS PLANET
IS ROYAL FAMILY TERRITORY.
AND EVERY SINGLE
THING THAT'S HERE
BELONGS TO ROYAL ME.
- YOU'RE MEAN.
- ( laughs )
- THAT WAS MY VERY FIRST
ENCOUNTER WITH AYEKA.
- WHAT A TERRIBLE STORY.
NOW I UNDERSTAND, RYOKO.
THAT WOUND IN YOUR YOUNG HEART
REMAINS FOREVER.
( gasps )
- YOU DO UNDERSTAND, MIHOSHI.
- OH, YES, NOW I KNOW
WHAT CAUSED YOU
TO STRAY IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SO YOU BECAME
A JUVENILE DELINQUENT
AND WENT DOWN
THE PATH OF EVIL.
OH, WHAT A PITY. I'M SO
SORRY FOR YOU, SO SORRY!
- I SEE. JURAI SOUNDS LIKE
A VERY BEAUTIFUL PLANET.
- IT IS.
AND I MUST KEEP AND CARRY ON THE
TRADITION OF JURAI AT ALL COSTS.
I'VE SWORN TO DO SO...
AT ALL COSTS,
EVEN IF--
- HMM.
WHO IS IT?
AH, IT'S YOU, TENCHI.
- YES, I BROUGHT
SOME TEA CAKE FOR YOU.
- VERY GOOD.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME, TENCHI.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE MISS AYEKA
AND SHOW HER AROUND.
- HUH?
- THE MOUNTAINS AND FIELDS
ON THIS PLANET
HAVE THEIR OWN CHARM,
THOUGH DIFFERENT FROM JURAI'S,
ESPECIALLY NOW.
THIS TIME OF YEAR,
THEY'RE QUITE SOMETHING TO SEE.
- BUT...
- IT'S ALL
WELL AND GOOD
TO LIVE FOR
THE DUTIES OF A PRINCESS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MEAN YOU CAN'T HAVE
A DAY OFF FROM TIME TO TIME.
WHATEVER LUCK
BROUGHT YOU TO THIS PLANET,
YOU SHOULD TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF IT
AND TRY TO RELAX.
FORGET ALL YOUR WORRIES
JUST FOR TODAY.
GOT IT, TENCHI?
- UH, YEAH.
- ( sighs )
LOVELY.
- YOU THINK SO?
- YES.
- WELL, I GUESS
THIS IS THE SEASON
WHEN THESE HILLS
LOOK THEIR BEST,
BUT THEY'RE JUST PLAIN HILLS.
- OH NO. THEY DEFINITELY
HAVE A BEAUTY,
A DIFFERENT KIND OF BEAUTY
FROM WHAT I SEE ON JURAI.
- HM-HMM.
YOU KNOW, IT'S INTERESTING.
WE DON'T SEEM TO
BE ABLE TO REALIZE
THE BEAUTY
OR HAPPINESS WE DO HAVE,
EVEN WHEN WE'RE RIGHT THERE
SMACK DAB IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
WELL, SHALL WE START BACK NOW?
- YES.
OH. ( gasps )
- ARE-- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OH?
- ( birds twitter )
- ( sighs )
- ( both gasp )
- OH, EXCUSE ME.
- EXCUSE ME.
- TENCHI? TENCHI?
- TENCHI? NO, I DON'T KNOW.
- TENCHI, WHERE ARE YOU?
TENCHI!
RATS!
COULD IT BE AYEKA?
- I HAVE NEVER FELT LIKE THIS
IN MY LIFE.
- WHAT? DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- OH, NO.
- WELL, THERE'S A NICE
LITTLE SPOT UP THERE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO CHECK IT OUT?
- YES.
- HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
ISN'T IT A WONDERFUL VIEW?
- ( cries )
- OH.
WHAT IS IT, AYEKA?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S NOTHING.
JUST THAT YOUR GRANDFATHER
WAS PROBABLY RIGHT.
THIS HAS TURNED OUT TO BE
THE MOST PERFECT DAY OFF FOR ME.
JUST PERFECT.
- Ryoko: THERE,
I FOUND YOU.
- HUH?
- AND JUST WHERE HAVE YOU TWO
BEEN HIDING ALL THIS TIME?
- WHAT? WE WENT
OUT FOR A WALK.
- AND YOU! HOW DARE YOU FLIRT
WITH TENCHI LIKE THIS, HUH.
- FLIRT? ARE YOU ADDRESSING ME?
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT IDEA?
- UH-HUH.  SO YOU'RE TELLING ME
YOU WEREN'T FLIRTING?
- WELL, OF COURSE NOT.
I WAS CERTAINLY NOT FLIRTING,
GUTTER BRAIN!
- OH, YOU LIE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
I'M NOT GOING TO
LET THAT ONE PASS.
- OKAY, OKAY.
ENOUGH YOU TWO.
- YES, RYOKO.
WE NEED TO START MAKING
ARRANGEMENTS TO GET BACK HOME.
- LORD TENCHI,
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
YOU MUST LISTEN
AND LISTEN CAREFULLY.
- THAT CREATURE CALLED RYOKO
IS BAD THROUGH-AND-THROUGH.
SHE ALWAYS HAS BEEN.
- YEAH, WELL, SHE'S
NOT MY FAVORITE ALIEN.
- IT ALL HAPPENED--
YES, IT ALL HAPPENED
WHEN I WAS VERY
YOUNG AND TENDER.
ON THAT DAY,
I WAS SO HAPPY
PLAYING IN A TERRITORY BELONGING
TO JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY,
MY FAMILY.
IT WAS THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL PLACE
WITH ALL SORTS
OF FLOWERS IN BLOOM.
- HEY, YOU!
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE HAVING FUN,
AREN'T YOU?
- HELLO, WHO ARE YOU?
- DID YOU MAKE
THAT THING YOURSELF?
- I DID.
- WELL, AREN'T WE SO TALENTED?
- ( whimpers )
- AND NOW IT'S ALL MINE.
SO LONG SUCKER!
- YOU'RE MEAN.
- THAT WAS MY FIRST ENCOUNTER
WITH RYOKO.
- RYOKO, THAT'S COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT FROM WHAT YOU TOLD US.
- ( sarcastic ) GEE,
I WONDER WHICH STORY'S TRUE?
- HEY, ARE YOU SUGGESTING
I TOLD YOU A LIE?
- I'M SURE YOUR STORY WAS
JUST MADE-UP MISH-MASH.
- HEY, YOU'RE FULL
OF MISH-MASH, PRINCESS.
- NOW, LISTEN, YOU!
YOU'VE BEEN CONVICTED OF FRAUD
AND YOU DARE CALL MY STORY
A MISH-MASH?!
- MISS AYEKA, PLEASE CALM DOWN.
I-- ARGH!
- OH, TENCHI!
YOU SEE HOW SHE IS?
YOU SEE HOW THAT HYSTERICAL
WOMAN IS SO MEAN TO ME?
- HEY, STOP IT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
LET GO OF HIM!
- HMM.
WHAT ARE YOU SO UPSET ABOUT?
YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T FLIRTING,
DIDN'T YOU?
- HMM.
- HEY, TENCHI,
LET'S SHOW HER.
LET'S SHOW HER
HOW MUCH WE'RE IN LOVE.
LET'S SHOW HER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- ( groaning )
- WILL YOU STOP IT?
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
ANYTHING, RIGHT?
- HEY, ARE YOU CRAZY?
- ( groaning )
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
FOR THE SAKE
OF UNIVERSAL PEACE,
I AM GOING TO FINISH YOU OFF
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- OKAY, GREAT.
LET'S JUST SEE
IF YOU REALLY CAN.
- HELLO.
UH, EXCUSE ME.
COULD YOU TWO FIGHT
AFTER YOU RESCUE ME?
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF,
UM, I--
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
OPEN THE HATCH!
WE'RE TAKING RYU-OH
UP TO ATTACK
- WAIT A MINUTE, PLEASE.
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF ME FIRST
BEFORE YOU FIGHT.
PLEASE, HELP ME!
( cries )
COME, RYO-OHKI.
- ( meowing )
- ( gasps )
- NOW, READY?
- HUH?
WHOA! WHY ARE YOU TAKING ME?!
- ( meowing )
- RYO-OHKI, THIS WILL
BE A FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
- ( meows )
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES
MUST RYOKO ESCAPE ALIVE!
- THE PROBLEM WON'T
BE SOLVED WITH VIOLENCE.
- PLEASE STOP!
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- ATTACK!
- FIRE!
- FIRE ANOTHER BARRAGE.
- OH, LET ME OUT!
- REST IN PEACE,
PRINCESS AYEKA.
- ( laughing )
YOU REST IN PEACE,
MISS RYOKO.
- I'M TOO YOUNG TO DIE!
- ( laughing )
- PLEASE STOP IT, MISS AYEKA.
STOP IT.
- ( laughing )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING DOWN THERE?
- ME?
- ( meowing )
( yowling )
- HMPH!
- ( laughing )
NOW YOU KNOW BETTER,
RYOKO.
- HA! WE HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED.
- ALL RIGHT,
ENOUGH OF THIS ALREADY.
- LORD TENCHI,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
- HMM.
WHERE ELSE WOULD HE BE?
TENCHI AND I
HAVE A SPECIAL BOND.
WE HAVE TAKEN A VOW
TO DIE TOGETHER.
- WHOA! WHAT VOW?
- YOU-- YOU MEAN...
OH NO!
LORD TENCHI, TAKING A VOW
WITH A LOWLY CREATURE LIKE HER,
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO BELIEVE IN.
- IT'S A LIE, AYEKA!
- NOW, TENCHI, LET'S
FIGHT THAT EVIL PRINCESS
WITH THE POWER OF OUR LOVE.
- ( crying )
- WOULD YOU STOP IT?
- WELL, IF THAT'S THE CASE...
WE DIE.
MISS RYOKO, LORD TENCHI,
THEN ALL THREE OF US
GO TO HELL TOGETHER.
MISS AYEKA, I THINK YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT ME.
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
- ( laughing )
- STOP IT, PLEASE, LADY AYEKA.
- Kamidake: WHOA! LADY AYEKA
HAS LOST HER TEMPER!
- ( all screaming )
- Ayeka: ( laughing )
- MM-MMM.
- WELL, NO ONE'S HURT
AND THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO STAY HERE
WITH US FOR AS LONG AS YOU LIKE.
- I APPRECIATE IT, SIR.
- WE TAKE YOUR OFFER
WITH THANKS.
- GREAT.
MORE FREELOADERS.
IT'S REALLY ANNOYING.
- WELL, IT'S ALL
YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH, WELL, MY RYO-OHKI
GOT DESTROYED TOO.
DO YOU REMEMBER, HUH?
- ( cries )
I TOLD YOU TO FIGHT
AFTER YOU RESCUED ME!
BY THE WAY,
WHERE'S MISS AYEKA?
- SHE'S STILL IN SHOCK
FROM SEEING RYU-OH,
HER SPACESHIP, BLOW UP.
- MISS AYEKA?
- OH, YES.
- I BROUGHT DINNER FOR YOU.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME, AYEKA?
MAYBE A LITTLE LATER, HUH?
- YES.
- WELL, ALL RIGHT THEN.
I'LL COME BACK LATER
WITH SOME NICE HOT SOUP.
IN THE MEAN TIME,
YOU HAVE A GOOD REST.
- WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
I GUESS I CAN TAKE
AN EXTENDED VACATION.
- ( theme music plays )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A FOOL ♪
♪ OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, YOU'LL NEVER BE
A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL ALWAYS WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG AND
I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE
TO THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE ♪
♪ HOW YOU WILL
MOURN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Tenchi:
"TENCHI MUYO."
THE NEXT AND THE FIFTH
IN LINE TO JOIN OUR FAMILY
IS SASAMI,
AYEKA'S LITTLE SISTER.
THIS BRAVE LITTLE GIRL
HAS TRAVELLED FAR TO EARTH
IN SEARCH OF HER
MISSING SISTER AYEKA.
AH? WHAT IS THIS
CAT-LIKE CREATURE?
WHAT? RYO-OHKI?
BUT I THOUGHT RYO-OHKI WAS
THE NAME OF RYOKO'S SPACESHIP.
"NO NEED FOR WORRIES"
IS COMING NEXT.
- Ryoko:
SHE'S UNDISPUTABLY CUTE.