- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ YOU'RE NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU ♪
♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER,
THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS WILL
OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU'LL LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION,
YOU DROWN YOUR DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ YOU'RE NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU ♪
- ♪ 'CAUSE RUNNING AWAY
WON'T MAKE AN ACTION. ♪
- Woman: SONIA!
- TENCHI!
- NO, AYEKA!
- HERE, TENCHI, TAKE THIS.
- WHAT IS IT, GRANDPA?
- SWORD TENCHI.
THE MAGICAL SWORD
THAT TRANSFORMS JURAI'S POWER
INTO A BLADE.
- SWORD TENCHI?
- TENCHI, YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DESTROY KAGATO.
- ( gasps )
- GO, TENCHI.
IT IS ALL UP TO YOU NOW.
- RYOKO, YOU'LL BE FINE.
- ( man yells )
- IS HE GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT?
IS HE GONNA MAKE IT?
- I DON'T KNOW YET.
- COME ON, GRANDPA.
- GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF.
WE HAVE TO VISIT
JURAI'S ROYAL PALACE NOW.
- BUT, WASHU, I CAN'T--
- LISTEN TO ME!
THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE DISCOURAGED.
I'M DYING
TO SEE KAGATO DEAD.
AND FOR THAT,
I'M COUNTING ON YOU, TENCHI.
- NO, I CAN'T.
NOT EVEN GRANDPA
WAS A MATCH FOR HIM.
AND, BESIDES, I DON'T POSSESS
THIS JURAI POWER
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- I SAY YOU CAN, TENCHI.
YOU DOUBT MY JUDGMENT?
- YOUR JUDGMENT?
- I COULD FEEL IT EVER SINCE
I FIRST SAW YOU.
I KNEW YOU HAD
GREAT POTENTIAL WITHIN YOU.
SINCE YOU WERE UNAWARE
OF YOUR CAPABILITY,
I WASN'T 100% SURE.
BUT NOW I CAN
SEE IT CLEARLY.
TENCHI,
YOU DO HAVE A FORCE
SURPASSING THAT
OF YOUR GRANDFATHER.
THE JURAI POWER.
( screams )
( gasps )
IT'S A WHOLE NEW GAME NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
TENCHI?
- ALL OF JURAI'S MILITARY
IS ATTACKING US.
- ALL SHIPS READY TO ATTACK.
YOUR TARGET IS THE OLD
ROYAL PALACE OF JURAI.
FIRE!
- HANG ON.  I'M TAKING US
TO THE BACK OF THE PALACE.
- ( all gasp )
- ( screaming )
- IT'S KEN-OHKI!
- YEAH!
- ( meowing )
- THANKS VERY MUCH, NAGI.
YOU JUST SAVED US.
- DON'T GET THE WRONG IDEA.
THE ONLY REASON
YOU'RE HERE IS BECAUSE
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE
TO TAKE RYOKO'S LIFE.
- OH, I SEE.
- HUH?
HMM.  YOU'VE GOT
A NICE PLACE HERE.
- WE DON'T HAVE MUCH
TO OFFER YOU,
BUT PLEASE MAKE YOURSELF
AT HOME, WON'T YOU, NAGI?
- COULD YOU EXCUSE US?  WE'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
WELL, REALLY,
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WE JUST HAVE TO SNEAK
INTO JURAI'S ROYAL PALACE
AND DO A LITTLE RESCUING
OF THE PRINCESS, THAT'S ALL.
- YEAH.  I SEE YOU'VE GOT
YOUR HANDS FULL, DON'T YOU?
- HERE.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME TEA?
- MMM.  GOOD.
LITTLE GIRL,
THIS TEA IS EXCELLENT.
NOW YOU ARE A PROFESSIONAL.
AM I RIGHT ABOUT THAT?
- ( laughs )
- ( machines beeping )
- LISTEN, TENCHI,
WHATEVER HAPPENS FROM NOW ON,
YOU STAND FIRM
AND FACE YOUR DESTINY
WITHOUT FEAR,
BUT WITH COURAGE.
- I WON'T LET YOU DOWN,
GRANDPA.
- ARE YOU GOING NOW, TENCHI?
- YEAH.
- YOU COULD DIE.
YOU KNOW THAT?
- POSSIBLY.
- TENCHI,
YOU SHOULD CHOOSE ME.
FORGET AYEKA, CAN'T YOU?
- HUH?
- YOU AND I COULD LEAVE
RIGHT NOW, TENCHI.
WE'D HAVE NO WORRIES.
JUST YOU AND I TOGETHER.
- RYOKO.
- SORT OF LIKE A HONEYMOON
IN DEEP SPACE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT WOULD BE FUN.
- IT SOUNDS FUN.
I'D LOVE TO GO ON A TRIP
WITH YOU.
- WOW.
I'M A SPACE PIRATE
AND A POWERFUL ONE!
I COULD JUST STEAL YOU AWAY
IF I WANTED TO.
OH!  DON'T GO, TENCHI!
( crying )
PLEASE.
DON'T, I BEG YOU.
I CAN'T BEAR THE THOUGHT
OF LOSING YOU.
DON'T GO.  DON'T GO.
- BUT I WON'T FORSAKE AYEKA.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
- TENCHI.
- AND YOU SEE, THIS IS
MY BATTLE AS WELL NOW.
- TENCHI!
I CAN GIVE YOU A LIFT.
LET ME HELP YOU.
I KNOW THE WAY THERE.
WHAT'S UP?
- SO YOU ARE GOING
WITH HIM, AREN'T YOU?
- I'M GIVING HIM A RIDE
ONE WAY, THAT'S ALL.
- IS THAT ALL?  WHAT ABOUT
OUR FIGHT, RYOKO, HUH?
- I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN.
WE CAN GET IT OVER WITH
RIGHT NOW IF YOU LIKE, NAGI.
( shouts )
( groaning )
- I THOUGHT SO.  WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
WITH A SERIOUS INJURY
LIKE THAT,
YOU MAY NOT EVEN MAKE IT
TO THE PALACE.
- SHUT UP.
DO YOU WANT TO FIGHT
WITH ME NOW OR NOT?
- I DON'T TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE WOUNDED.
- IF THAT'S YOUR CHOICE,
THEN I GUESS I'M GOING.
YOU JUST WAIT HERE.
I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
- GOOD LUCK.
- WE'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE MAIN FLEET.
YOU JUST CONCENTRATE
ON GETTING TO THE PALACE.
- I GOT IT.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW HOW
LONG WE CAN KEEP THEM BUSY,
BUT YOU KNOW THAT.
THE REST IS GOING
TO BE UP TO YOU.
- BE CAREFUL, TENCHI.
- DON'T YOU WORRY, SASAMI.
I'LL BRING AYEKA BACK
SAFELY
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE
JUST FINE, REALLY.
- I KNOW IT WILL.
- TENCHI, I KNOW YOUR GRANDPA
HAS GREAT FAITH IN YOU
AND SO DO I.
- DAD.
- YOU KNOW WE'LL TAKE
GOOD CARE OF GRANDPA.
SO YOU TAKE CARE.
- YEAH.  ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S ENOUGH GOODBYES.
LET'S GO.
- RIGHT.
WISH US LUCK.
- GOOD LUCK AND HAVE FUN,
OKAY, TENCHI?
- OKAY, I THINK YOU BETTER GO
BEFORE THINGS GET
A LITTLE TOO NASTY.
- I WAS JUST LEAVING.
- ( screeching )
- HMM.  YEAH, I KNOW.
- TENCHI.
- A MESSAGE
FROM THE FRONTLINE.
"THEY'VE JUST
SPOTTED RYO-OHKI
AROUND THE FOURTH
DEFENSIVE LINE."
- TRANSFER FLEET
TO THAT SITE IMMEDIATELY.
- WE'VE CHASED RYO-OHKI DOWN
TO THE SEVENTH SATELLITE AREA.
THEY WILL INTERCEPT RYO-OHKI
IN TWO MINUTES.
WHAT?  WHAT?!
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT LOOKS LIKE THERE ARE
TWO RYO-OHKIS.
- WHAT?  IMPOSSIBLE!
- NO, THE THE FIRST SHIP
WASN'T RYO-OHKI.
IT WAS ITS SHADOW.
- AH.  CLEVER.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY FELL
FOR OUR TRICK.
- WE ALL HAVE OUR PARTS TO PLAY.
- RIGHT.
- THANK GOODNESS THAT
NAGI DECIDED TO HELP US.
- MM-HMM.
- NOW, ENGINES FIRE!
- NOW LET'S GO, KEN-OHKI.
COME BACK ALIVE, RYOKO.
- ( screaming )
( grunts )
- HEY, RYOKO!
- ( screaming )
NO!
( panting )
- RYOKO.
- SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
WELL, LET'S GO.
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- RYOKO!
- OH, TENCHI, DON'T YOU
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING.
I SWEAR I WILL MAKE SURE YOU GET
TO JURAI'S ROYAL PALACE.
I SWEAR IT.
DON'T BE A CHICKEN, RYO-OHKI.
WE'RE NOT COWARDS.
LET'S SHOW 'EM WHAT WE CAN DO!
( grunting )
( screaming )
OH.  THAT'S IT.
SO WE'RE HERE.
- THEY'RE HERE.
- ( gasps )
- FROM THIS POINT,
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN, TENCHI.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
I WASN'T PLANNING
ON HELPING YOU RESCUE
THAT OTHER WOMAN.
AFTER ALL, I AM A PIRATE.
- I OWE YOU ONE.
THANK YOU.
- YOU AIN'T GOT ALL DAY,
YOU KNOW?  YOU'RE WASTING TIME!
- WE THANK YOU FOR THE ESCORT.
- NOT EVEN 1,000 KNIGHTS COULD
MATCH YOUR SPIRIT, RYOKO.
- GOOD-BYE.
- ( sobbing )
- TENCHI.
- WELL, RYO-OHKI,
IT SEEMS LIKE IT'S
JUST YOU AND ME AGAIN,
ALL ALONE.
- ( meows )
- IT'S BEEN FUN, THOUGH.
WE'VE HAD A BLAST SINCE WE FELL
ON THE EARTH, HAVEN'T WE?
I'M LONELY.
I SOUND SILLY, DON'T I?
SO WHERE SHALL WE GO NEXT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
RYO-OHKI?
- ( meowing )
( screeching )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ♪
♪ A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY,
YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I'M BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Kagato: COME IF YOU MAY, YOU
YOUNG CROWN PRINCE OF JURAI.
COME TO ME AND SHED
YOUR BLOOD OF DEFEAT.
- Tenchi: YOSHO AND KAGATO
DELIGHT IN THE DARKNESS
THAT DIVIDES THE UNIVERSE.
NOW THAT YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO OVERCOME THE LIGHT, KAGATO,
WHAT PLAN DO YOU HAVE IN MIND?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING, BUT
ONE THING I KNOW FOR SURE
IS THAT I WILL TAKE AYEKA BACK
FROM YOU WHATEVER THE COST.
COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR A SHOWDOWN."
- Washu: IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
A GREAT SHOWDOWN!