- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- ( car alarm blares )
- ( train whistles )
( train rattles )
- ( clock ticks )
- ( sighs )
AHH! OH MY GOD.
MIHOSHI, WAKE UP.
WE'RE GONNA
BE LATE FOR WORK.
- UH, YOU ARE UNDER ARREST.
- MIHOSHI,
YOU'VE GOT TO WAKE UP.
- ( sighs )
- GET YOUR
BUTT OUT OF BED!
( grumbles )
- ( light snores )
SO ANYWAY, AND THEN--
AND THEN I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO ARREST THIS--
THIS VICIOUS CRIMINAL.
- ENOUGH ABOUT YOUR DREAM.
FINISH YOUR BREAKFAST.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
IF YOU GET FIRED AGAIN?
- ALL RIGHT,
BUT ARE WE ALLOWED TO HAVE
PART-TIME JOBS ON THE SIDE?
- WE HAVE TO. EVERYTHING IS
SO EXPENSIVE HERE ON EARTH.
HOW ELSE CAN WE PAY THE RENT
ON THIS APARTMENT?
- ( slurps )
YUMMY!
WOW, KIYONE, YOUR MISO SOUP
IS JUST THE BEST.
- YEAH, YOU'RE TELLING ME.
- YO!
- BYE, I'M LEAVING.
- ( cartoons play )
- ( laughs )
- RYOKO, COULD YOU
SPARE THE TIME
TO HELP US CLEAR
THE TABLE, PLEASE?
- HMM? WERE YOU
SAYING SOMETHING?
- ( grumbles )
IF SHE DOESN'T WANT TO DO
ANYTHING AROUND THE HOUSE,
SHE SHOULD GO AND LIVE
ON HER OWN.
SHE SHOULD FOLLOW
MIHOSHI'S EXAMPLE.
- I WONDER WHAT MIHOSHI
AND KIYONE ARE UP TO.
- I WONDER AS WELL.
- POOR KIYONE
IS SO UNLUCKY.
THERE SHE WAS
ON HER WAY TO THE TOP,
AND SHE GOT MIHOSHI
FOR A PARTNER.
- BACK, BACK.
KEEP COMING.
- ( truck beeps )
- STOP.
- HEY, YOU'RE A NATURAL.
LOOKING GOOD.
- REALLY?
- OH, YEAH, KEEP UP
THE GOOD WORK.
- YES, SIR.
I WILL.
( thoughts )
GRADUATED SECOND IN MY CLASS
FROM THE GALAXY
POLICE ACADEMY.
AND NOW LOOK AT ME.  OH.
- ( loud crash )
- ( gasps )
- Mihoshi:
I THINK YOU SHOULD STOP NOW.
WAS THAT MY FAULT?
- ( sighs )
- UH, KIYONE, ( pants )
WHAT--
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
- OH.
- DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- ( chewing )
- Kiyone: ( quietly cries )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
HAVE YOU GOT A STOMACH ACHE
OR SOMETHING?
- NO, I DON'T.
- OH.
- I'M SORRY I CAUSED
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
LET'S HURRY AND
FINISH SHOPPING
OR WE'LL BE LATE
FOR OUR NEXT JOB, MIHOSHI.
- OKAY.
- UH, COULD YOU GET ME
A HOT PAD FROM OVER THERE?
- HMM?
- GET THAT BIG ONE.
- YOU SURE ARE SENSITIVE
TO THE COLD.
- CONSTRUCTION'S
A COLD BUSINESS.
- MHMM.
CAN I BUY SOME SNACKS?
- ( growl )
OH, OKAY, OKAY.
- WOW!
( giggles )
( humming )
- ( snacks clatter )
- HUH?
HEY! JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, MIHOSHI?!
- YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY.
- ( growls )
SO A BACON AND EGG SANDWICH
AND A SMALL COKE.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
FRIES WITH THAT, SIR?
- Customer:
YEAH, SURE, OKAY.
- THAT'S AN AFFIRMATIVE
ON THE FRIES, VERY GOOD, SIR.
- HELLO, I'M HERE
TO SERVE YOU.
WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
- Man: JUST A HAMBURGER
AND COFFEE.
- OKAY, THAT'S ONE HAMBURGER
AND ONE COFFEE.
WOULD YOU CARE FOR SOME
FRIES, APPLE PIE,
FRENCH TOAST, A SANDWICH,
OR MAYBE A VANILLA SHAKE
WITH THAT?
WHY A HOT CHOCOLATE
WOULD BE GOOD TOO.
HOW ABOUT
A PORK CHOP BURGER.
OUR PORK CHOP BURGER'S ARE--
- STOP ALREADY!
- BUT YOU TOLD ME TO GIVE THEM
SOME SUGGESTIONS, KIYONE.
- AND WHAT'S THE CUSTOMER
SUPPOSED TO DO WITH ALL THAT?
- THEY ALL TASTE
REALLY GOOD THOUGH.
- THAT IS NOT THE POINT!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT,
MR. CUSTOMER?
YOU LIKE PORK CHOP BURGERS,
DON'T YOU?
- ( groaning )
- UH, EXCUSE ME.
- ( growls )
UH, HOW MAY I HELP YOU?
- A TERIYAKI SANDWICH
AND A COKE, PLEASE?
AND A COKE, SIR.
WE'RE HAVING
A TERIYAKI SPECIAL TODAY.
IF YOU ORDER THIS
COMBO WITH FRIES,
IT WOULD BE A BETTER DEAL.
- MAKE IT A COMBO THEN.
- OH, RIGHT. THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, SIR.
- OH, YES.  WE'RE HAVING
A TERIYAKI SPECIAL.
AND IF YOU TAKE A COMBO,
IT'LL ALL BE FREE
WITH FRIES AND EVERYTHING.
ISN'T THAT THE GREATEST DEAL?
HOW COULD YOU PASS UP
A DEAL LIKE THAT?
- MIHOSHI.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
A COMBO WITH A LARGE BURGER
AND A COKE AND ONE ICE TEA.
- ( clattering )
- Mihoshi: WHOA!
- OH, I BEG YOU.
PLEASE DON'T LET IT BE
WHAT I THINK IT IS.
- OUCH, THAT HURT.
- OH BOY.
- NOT YOU AGAIN.
- WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU GUYS ANYWAY?
- I'M SO SORRY.
- ( beeping )
- MR. MANAGER,
WE'VE GOT AN EMERGENCY.
CAN WE PLEASE LEAVE EARLY?
- EARLY?! NOT AGAIN!
- COME ON, MIHOSHI,
LET'S GO.
- OKAY.
- HEY, COME BACK HERE.
- ( police siren blares )
- THAT EMERGENCY CALL CAME
FROM SOMEWHERE NEAR JUPITER.
LET'S GO.
WE'VE NO TIME TO LOSE.
- RIGHT.
COULD THIS BE AN ARMED ROBBERY
OR A SPACE MAFIA CASE?
THIS IS EXCITING.
- BEFORE YOU GET
TOO EXCITED,
CHANGE INTO YOUR UNIFORM.
( sighs )
CAN YOU HOLD THAT THING?
I'LL TRY TO OPEN UP
THIS VALVE HERE.
- UM, THIS THING HERE?
LIKE THIS?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( machine whirrs )
- YEAH, YOU FIXED IT.
- ( sighs )
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I WAS VERY WORRIED.
MY SHIP BROKE DOWN
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS GONNA DO.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
- TO BE A RESIDENT OFFICER
MUST BE QUITE
A DIFFICULT JOB, HUH?
- WE'RE JUST DOING
OUR DUTY, MA'AM.
- HOW ABOUT STAYING HERE
AND MARRYING MY GRANDSON?
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
YOUNG LADY?
- ( giggles )
I'M SO FLATTERED.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK,
KIYONE?
- ( nervous chuckle )
- YO!
YO!
- ( train whistles )
( train rattles )
- I AM SO BEAT.
- WE'RE VERY EXHAUSTED.
- ( cars honking )
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH, I HOPE IT'S NOT
ANOTHER SALESMAN.
- YES?
- OH WOW.
- SURPRISE!
- HI, EVERYONE.
- HI. WE JUST CAME BY TO
SEE HOW YOU GUYS ARE DOING.
- YEAH, WE MISS YOU GUYS.
SO HOW ARE YOU?
- ( meows )
- WE BROUGHT ALONG
A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR YOU TO EAT, HERE.
- Ryoko: YOU BROUGHT
THEM JUNK FOOD.
- WOW, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
- Ayeka: DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- HMM.
- I AM NOT TALKING
TO YOU ANYMORE.
- STRAIGHTEN UP THE ROOM,
WILL YOU?
- ALL RIGHT.
- PLEASE, COME
INSIDE, WON'T YOU?
- HURRAY! LET'S GO INSIDE!
- I AM SO GLAD YOU CAME OVER.
IT'S REALLY GREAT TO SEE YOU.
( giggles )
- SO THIS IS MIHOKIO'S PLACE,
IS IT?
- MIHOKIO?
- THAT'S SHORT FOR
MIHOSHI AND KIYONE.
- WELL, I DON'T
LIKE THE SOUND OF IT.
- YEAH, IT SOUNDS
LIKE THE NAME
OF A GOOFY COMEDY TEAM
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- HEY, GOOFBALL,
SHUT UP ALREADY.
- YOU SURE ARE LIKE CLOWNS.
- YEAH.  ( giggles )
- ( laughing )
- UM.
- ( sighs ) YOU KNOW,
IT REALLY WARMS MY HEART
TO SEE YOU BOTH
DOING SO WELL.
- UH-HUH, AND WE'RE SO HAPPY
AND FULL OF ENERGY.
- SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
OF COURSE YOU'RE ENERGETIC,
YOU SLEEP ALL THE TIME.
- WELL, I'M NOT SLEEPING NOW.
- ( meows )
- NO, YOU CERTAINLY AREN'T.
- ( laughing )
- TELL ME. HOW HAVE YOUR
JOBS BEEN COMING ALONG?
- WELL, BECAUSE
OF THIS RECESSION,
THINGS AREN'T EASY.
WE'RE ACTUALLY THINKING OF
GETTING ANOTHER PART-TIME JOB.
- ( muffled ) HM-HMM.
SURE SOUNDS TOUGH.
( slurps) AH.
- ( both gasp )
- HUH?
- LISTEN, RYOKO, JUST BECAUSE
THIS IS THE LAST ONE,
DOESN'T MEAN YOU
HAVE TO GET SO COMPETITIVE.
- THE SAME
COULD BE SAID OF YOU.
AREN'T WE BEHAVING
A WEE BIT GLUTINOUS
FOR THE PRINCESS
OF PLANET JURAI?
- ( giggles )
I WOULDN'T THINK OF IT.
OH, PLEASE BE MY GUEST, RYOKO,
HELP YOURSELF TO THE LAST PIECE.
I INSIST.
- HEY, TENCHI.
ALTHOUGH SHE'S ACTING
AS THOUGH SHE'S GENEROUS,
DID YOU KNOW AYEKA
HAS ALREADY HAD 10 CRACKERS?
DON'T THINK I DIDN'T NOTICE.
I COUNTED.
- HUH?
WELL, I GUESS IT
DOESN'T BOTHER YOU
TO BE THOUGHT OF
AS A COOKIE-COUNTER.
- NOT ONLY THOSE CRACKERS.
SHE'S ALSO BEEN MUNCHING
ON POTATO CHIPS,
AND CHOCOLATE PUFFS, AND STUFF
ALL BY HERSELF.
WHAT A PIG, HUH?
- LIES! LIES!
IT'S NOT TRUE!
- IT IS TOO.
YOU SAW HER STUFFING YOURSELF,
DIDN'T YOU?  HUH?  RIGHT?
- HEY, LET GO.
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU
DOING WITH TENCHI?!
LEAVE TENCHI ALONE.
YOU GO SIT OVER THERE
RIGHT NOW.
- COME ON, RYOKO.
- IT'S ONLY NATURAL
FOR LOVERS TO CUDDLE.
ISN'T IT, TENCHI?
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
OH NO! STOP IT.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING
THAT IN HERE.
- HEY, STOP THAT.
CUT IT OUT.
- ALL RIGHT,
THIS HAS TO BE SETTLED.
- YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT
ANYBODY BUT YOURSELF
AND I'VE HAD
QUITE ENOUGH OF IT.
I WON'T STAND IT ANYMORE.
- YOU'RE CAUSING US
TROUBLE NOW.
- PLEASE, WE BEG YOU,
BOTH OF YOU,
TAKE YOUR FIGHT OUTSIDE.
AAH!
HA!
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- ( all screaming )
- ( screeches )
- ( meowing )
- STOP IT!
- Ryoko: ( shouting )
- ( all screaming )
- ( chuckles )
- ( crying )
- ( chewing )
( slurps )
MM-MM.
YEAH, THIS IS GOOD TEA.
- ( sighs )
THAT WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
- YES, IT WAS.
- ( yawns )
AH. SOAKING IN A HOT TUB
IS THE BEST.
IT'S THE PERFECT WAY
TO RELAX.
- ( giggles ) YEAH.
YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ALWAYS RELAXED, MIHOSHI.
- YEAH, YOU THINK SO?
- ( laughs ) DEFINITELY.
- ( blows bubbles )
- ( humming )
( humming )
- ( through bubbles )
HEY, KIYONE.
- YES, WHAT?
- SAY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK WE
SHOULD DO ON OUR WAY HOME?
- WHAT? NOT AGAIN?
- WE JUST DID THAT
TWO DAYS AGO.
- COME ON.
- WE CAN'T.
YOU KNOW OUR BUDGET
IS REALLY TIGHT.
- PLEASE.  LET'S GO.
- ( growls )
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
- ( music plays )
- ♪ TAKE ME THERE ♪
♪ TAKE ME THERE
TO THE PLACE IN MY DREAMS ♪
- IN MY DREAMS!
- ♪ IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ TO PARADISE ♪
- ( laughs, claps )
WONDERFUL, KIYONE.
- OH, WELL, THANK YOU.
- PLEASE SING THIS ONE
WITH ME, KIYONE.
- OH NO.
- COME ON, LET'S
SING IT TOGETHER.
- OH, OKAY.  I GUESS.
- ( giggles )
- ( music plays )
- ♪ I WAS SO NAIVE ♪
♪ NOT TO KNOW THAT
LOOKS CAN DECEIVE ♪
♪ THE FIRST SIGN OF YOU
MAKES MY HEART JUMP ♪
♪ A GOOD LOOKING YOUNG MAN ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW HE LOOKED
TO MY EYES ♪
♪ BUT IT LASTED
ONLY A WHILE ♪
♪ IN THE MIDDLE
OF OUR KISS ♪
♪ I SAW HIS
HAIR PIECE COME OFF. ♪
- ♪ YOU SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN BETTER, MY FRIEND ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW GOOD
A RUG MAY BE ♪
♪ A CLOSER LOOK SHOULD
TELL YOU FOR SURE ♪
♪ IF IT'S FAKE OR NOT ♪
- ♪ BUT IT'S OKAY NOW ♪
♪ I DON'T MIND IT ANYMORE ♪
- Both:
♪ I LET YOU DECEIVE ME ♪
♪ CAUSE I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU. ♪
- Mihoshi: YAY!
YOU'RE REALLY GETTING
INTO THIS, KIYONE.
AREN'T YOU GLAD WE CAME?
- YEAH, I THINK THIS
IS A GREAT WAY
TO GET RID OF STRESS, MIHOSHI.
- AH, NOW, WHICH SONG
SHOULD WE SING NEXT?
- NO MORE.
OUR TIME'S ALMOST UP.
- OH, LET'S SING SOME MORE.
- I TOLD YOU. OUR BUDGET'S
REALLY TIGHT THIS MONTH.
- PLEASE, JUST
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- ABSOLUTELY NOT!
( singing )
- KIYONE'S THE ONE
WHO'S HOOKED UP WITH KARAOKE.
LOOK AT YOUR SCORE.
( laughing )
LET'S SING THIS ONE TOGETHER.
OKAY?
- NO!
- COME ON,
IT'LL BE FUN.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( beeping )
- OH MY GOD, WE'RE GETTING
A CALL, MIHOSHI!
- ROGER.
- WHOA.
HEY, YOU TWO, WHERE DO
YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
COME BACK!
AWW, THEY RAN AWAY
WITHOUT PAYING.
- ( police siren blares )
- I SHOULDN'T BE PREOCCUPIED
WITH KARAOKE AND FORGET MY DUTY.
WE HAVE TO GO TO SATURN,
FULL-SPEED!
- ( echoes ) OKAY.
I HOPE WE MAKE IT
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
I HAVE A FEELING
IT'S A BIG CASE THIS TIME.
- MIHOSHI, YOU BROUGHT
THE MICROPHONE?
- ( echoes ) WHAT?
OH NO, I GUESS I DID.
( laughing )
- Taxi Driver:
LISTEN TO ME, OFFICERS,
I WAS DOING THE SPEED LIMIT,
REALLY.
BUT THEN THIS GUY
CAME RIGHT AT ME!
- YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WASN'T
LOOKING WHERE YOU WERE GOING.
- ( blows raspberry )
- WOULD YOU PLEASE
CALM DOWN, BOTH OF YOU?
- NOW, ALL RIGHT,
WHO MADE THE FIRST TURN
AT THE RING OF SATURN?
- THIS GUY.
- UH-UH, IT WAS YOU.
- ( growling )
- YOU ARE SO FULL OF CRAP.
LIAR!
- STOP IT.
PLEASE, DON'T FIGHT.
- ( arguing )
- STOP!
- ( growls )
- LISTEN, I ASKED NICELY
AND NOW I'M TRYING TO
ASK YOU NICELY AGAIN.
- ( sighs )
- ( overlapping chatter )
- I SUPPOSE WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO GET ANOTHER JOB.
- ( car alarm blares )
- ( breathes deeply )
( exhales )
( sighs )
- ( alarm continues )
- ( train whistles )
- ( sighs )
- ( train rattles )
- WELL, MIHOSHI...
MIHOSHI?
- ( breathing )
- ( sighs )
AT LEAST
SOMEBODY'S CARE-FREE.
- ( in sleep ) LET'S SING
ONE MORE TOGETHER.
KIYONE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( theme music plays )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A FOOL ♪
♪ OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, YOU'LL NEVER BE
A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL ALWAYS WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG AND
I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE
TO THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE ♪
♪ HOW YOU WILL
MOURN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Tenchi: IT IS TIME MASAKI
SHRINE TO CELEBRATE HARVEST.
COME ON, SASAMI,
LET'S GO HAVE FUN.
- Sasami: HOORAY!
WE'RE GOING TO THE FAIR.
- Tenchi: EVERYONE'S SETTING
UP BOOTHS AT THE FAIR.
RYOKO HAS A BOOTH
FOR GOLD FISH SCOOPING,
AND AYEKA FOR TARGET-SHOOTING,
AND A FUN HOUSE
RUN BY WASHU.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
IT WON'T BE AN UNEVENTFUL DAY.
COMING UP NEXT,
"NO NEED FOR A FAIR,