- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- I HEREBY PASS SENTENCE
UPON THE DEFENDANT,
PROFESSOR WASHU.
THE DEFENDANT
SHALL BE IMPRISONED
IN AN ALPHA-L MODEL
RESTRICTION CAPSULE...
- ...AND EXILED.
- ( whimpers )
NOW WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
EXACTLY WHAT DID I DO
TO DESERVE THIS?
ALL I DID WAS INVENT
DIMENSION OSCILLATING BULLETS,
O-ZONE DESTROYING CANNONS,
AND A TIME-SPACE CONVERTING
TACHYON RAY.
- ISN'T THAT MORE THAN ENOUGH,
PROFESSOR?
- AAH!
MM.
- WAKE UP, WASHU.
GOOD MORNING, WASHU.
- UHH... HUH?
( groans )
THAT'S RIGHT.
I DIDN'T SLEEP AT ALL.
HMM.
IT'S WORKING.
META-DRIVE, PROPULSION,
EXTERIOR CODING.
FINALLY.
THE THIRD PHASE
IS NOW COMPLETE.
- WASHU, YOU ARE A GENIUS.
- THE GREATEST IN
THE UNIVERSE!
- ( laughs )
PIECE OF CAKE!
- IT WON'T BE LONG NOW.
( chuckles )
- YO!
- HEY, MISS. I GOT THIS RICE
FROM THE BLACK MARKET
JUST FOR YOU.
IT'S A SPECIAL BLEND.
IT'S THE VERY BEST KIND.
- OH, REALLY.
IS THIS FOR ME?
- BUT IN RETURN,
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT.
- OH, NO.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
NO, NO!
- HI!
IT'S TIME FOR THE
'HAPPY KIDS FUN TIME PLAY HOUR'.
HOW ARE ALL YOU
HAPPY KIDS TODAY?
- FINE! AND YOU?
- UHH...
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- WHAT?
- IT WAS JUST GETTING
TO THE JUICY PART.
UH... A CLIMACTIC MOMENT!
- OH, I'M SORRY.
- OKAY. SO ANYWAY,
MIHOSHI,
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I WAS GOING TO
INVITE MYSELF TO LUNCH?
- WELL, I'M SORRY. WE
FINISHED LUNCH AWHILE AGO.
- WHAT?!
YOU'VE ALREADY EATEN LUNCH?
- TENCHI, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WASHU DIDN'T SHOW UP
FOR BREAKFAST OR LUNCH.
I WONDER IF THERE'S
ANYTHING WRONG WITH HER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- YOU'RE RIGHT, SASAMI.
I THINK I'LL GO
CHECK ON HER.
- ( knocks on door )
- WASHU?
WASHU?
SHE ISN'T HERE.
OH, TENCHI, IT'S YOU.
WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, YOU MISSED
A COUPLE OF MEALS.
WE WERE WONDERING WHAT
WAS GOING ON, THAT'S ALL.
- ( chuckles )
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
- YOU DO WANT TO KNOW!
- COME ON,
LET US SHOW YOU.
- UH...
- OKAY THEN.
COME OVER HERE.
- UH, BUT...
- I COULD ACTUALLY
USE SOME HELP, SO...
( chuckles )
HERE IT IS.
WHAT IS THIS?
- THIS IS MY LATEST INVENTION,
TENCHI.
MECHA-WASHU.
- MECHA-WASHU?
WHAT'D YOU MAKE
THIS THING FOR?
- WELL, SINCE I'VE BEEN
SEALED OFF FOR A LONG 700 YEARS,
I'M WAY BEHIND SCHEDULE
WITH MY INVENTIONS.
I NEED AN ASSISTANT,
YOU SEE?
THIS MECHANICAL WASHU
IS JUST AS CAPABLE AS I AM,
WHICH MEANS NOW I CAN WORK
TWICE AS FAST!
- AND IS IT FINISHED YET,
WASHU?
- THE ONLY THING LEFT TO DO
IS TO INPUT MY MIND DATA.
- AND THEN WHAT HAPPENS?
- THEN IT WILL BE FINISHED,
OF COURSE.
- Both: HUH?
- WHOA, HEY.
HOW'D YOU GET IN HERE?
- MMM...
WELL, I USED THE DOOR?
- YOU CAME THROUGH
THE DOORWAY,
TENCHI AND I CAME HERE
THROUGH PSEUDO-SPACE.
- WOW, WASHU.
WHAT IS THIS THING?
- USING EXCESS ENERGY
FROM PSEUDO-SPACE,
THIS INVENTION DUPLICATES
THE RECORDED MIND DATA.
- OH, WOW.
IS THAT RIGHT?
- YOU UNDERSTAND NOW?
- HUH.
- YOU DON'T GET IT.
- UH...
- GET OUT OF MY WAY.
- AWW.
- OKAY, TENCHI.
HERE WE GO.
I WILL NOW BE
TRANSFERRING THE DATA.
COULD YOU TURN ON
THE SWITCH ON THE BOTTOM RIGHT
OF THAT CONSOLE?
- UH, IS THIS IT?
- NO, THE ONE BELOW THAT.
- THIS MUST BE IT.
- ( grunts )
AAH!
- UH...
- THIS, NO. THIS, NO. THIS?
NO!
- HEY, YOU!
DON'T PLAY AROUND WITH THAT.
STOP THAT!
- OH NO.
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
- AAH!
- ( both scream )
- ( groans )
OHH...
OH.
- ( giggles )
- LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE TO ME!
- I'M SORRY.
- All: HUH?
- GREAT!
NO DAMAGE AT ALL.
I'VE DONE IT!
I'M FINALLY FINISHED.
- YOU DID IT, WASHU.
- YOU'RE GREAT, WASHU.
- OKAY! MOVE, MECHA-WASHU.
- ALL RIGHT.
- OH YEAH! COME ON.
THAT'S MY GIRL.
SHE LOOKS GREAT.
COME TO ME NOW, YEAH.
- UHH...
- HUH?
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG,
WASHU?
- UH...
- Both: YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GETTING KIND OF HUNGRY.
- HEY, YOU ARE TOO?
- HEY, ARE YOU, TOO?
- ( sighs )
( grunts )
HUH, HUH?
( gasps )
WHAT IS THIS?
- A BLONDE HAIR.
- IS IT POSSIBLE THAT THE
GENETIC DATA FROM THIS HAIR
GOT IMPRINTED INTO
MECHANICAL WASHU?!
- WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( gasps )
HOW COULD YOUR MIND DATA
BE TRANSFERRED
INSTEAD OF MINE BECAUSE OF
JUST ONE PIECE OF HAIR?!
- WELL...
- HOW COULD YOUR GENETIC
INFORMATION
OVERRIDE MINE?!
- I'M SORRY AGAIN.
- THE ROBOT IS GONE!
- Both: HUH?
- IT HAS TO BE
SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE,
AND WE'VE GOT TO FIND IT.
- UH-HUH.
- WHA--?!
IT'S EMPTY.
- ( meows )
- COME ON. COME ON.
YOU WANT THIS,
DON'T YOU?
- OH, NO.
NOT SO FAST.
- WE INTERRUPT THIS REGULARLY
SCHEDULED PROGRAM
FOR A SPECIAL REPORT.
- OH NO.
- BANK ROBBERS BROKE INTO
THE BANANA BANK.
- ARE WE EVER GOING TO
BE ABLE TO SEE THIS SOAP OPERA?
- AND IT WAS JUST GETTING
TO THE GOOD PART.
- ( chewing )
- OH MY.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS.
- HUH?
- Both: HUH?
- UH, OKAY.
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- Both: HMM?
- HEY THERE, YOU PEOPLE.
DID I JUST COME THROUGH HERE?
OKAY, THANKS.
NOW HOW DID IT GET
OUT OF THAT ROOM?
- AYEKA, WHAT WAS THAT?
- WE'RE JUST SEEING THINGS,
RYOKO.
- HMM?
OH, DARN.
I DON'T HAVE A CAR
TO GET INTO THE CITY.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
- WHAT?
- FINALLY, I FOUND YOU.
NOW LET'S GO BACK TO
THE LAB THIS INSTANT, OKAY?
- PLEASE DON'T STOP ME.
I HAVE TO SAVE
THE HOSTAGES,
AND STOP THE BANK ROBBERS.
I HAVE TO GO.
- HUH?
- THAT BANK IS BEING
ROBBED RIGHT NOW,
AND AS A GALAXY POLICE OFFICER,
I HAVE TO--
- YOU'RE NOT A GALAXY
POLICE OFFICER!
- WELL, I THINK YOU'D BETTER
LEAVE IT TO THE LOCAL POLICE,
YOU KNOW.
- WE MUST GO CATCH
THOSE SUSPECTS.
- WILL YOU SHUT UP?!
- OKAY.
- AND YOU, WAIT RIGHT THERE!
- IF YOU TRY TO KEEP ME HERE
ANY LONGER,
IT WILL CONSTITUTE
AN OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
HUH?!
- ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS NECESSARY
TO DO JUSTICE.
- GO ON, WASHU.
- LET'S GO, WASHU.
- WHAT?! YOU TRAITOR!
- ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
MECHA-WASHU PUNCH!
- STOP IT!
- ( screams )
- WHAT?
- UH-OH.
COME ON. COME OUT.
- OH.
- AH...
- ( grunts )
- I GOT HER.
- ARE YOU OKAY, MIHOSHI?
- IT HURTS.
- WASHU, WHY DID YOU
MAKE THAT WEAPON?
- IT'S A DEFENSE MECHANISM,
JUST IN CASE.
AS A GENIUS, I ALWAYS HAVE TO
BE PREPARED FOR THE WORST.
- UH-HUH.
SHE IS A GENIUS.
- YEP.
A GENIUS CAN'T HELP IT.
- OH.
BUT SHE CREATES THE WORST.
- ( murmurs )
- YO!
- ( screaming )
- ( pants )
YOU'VE GOT NOWHERE
TO HIDE NOW.
MECHA-WASHU BEAM!
- WE CAN'T HEAR THE TV.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE NOISE,
WASHU?
- OH, I AM SO SORRY.
- WATCH OUT!
- OH! UH...
( groans )
- NOW I WOULD GO AND INVENT
A MACHINE LIKE THAT.
I'LL SAY SHE'S GOT
SOME POWER.
- WASHU, YOU ARE POWERFUL.
- YOU ARE GREAT, WASHU.
WHOO-HOO!
- ( laughing )
- WIPE THAT SMILE
OFF YOUR FACE!
- ( humming )
( slurps )
EVERYBODY SEEMS
TO BE HAVING FUN,
AS USUAL.
- ( meows )
- NOW I'M GONNA HAVE TO--
- USE THOSE SPECIAL TACTICS,
WASHU, RIGHT?
- WE ARE ALL BEHIND YOU,
WASHU.
- HUH?
- WE CALL THIS...
"OPERATION VOLLEYBALL!"
( grunts )
( chuckles )
PREPARE TO DIE.
NOBODY'S EVER SURVIVED
THIS ATOM DESTROYING BALL,
AND I MEAN NOBODY!
I'LL EXPLAIN.
WHEN SOMEONE SPIKES THIS BALL,
IT THOROUGHLY AND COMPLETELY
DISRUPTS THE ATOMS
OF THE TARGET,
SO IT'S ONE CLEVER WEAPON
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
OKAY.
AND SERVE!
HUH?
OH WELL.
I HAVEN'T PRACTICED
IN 700 YEARS
AND MY AIM NEEDS WORK.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"NEEDS WORK"? OH NO!
- AAH!
YAAH!
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
RYOKO?
- HERE IT COMES.
- HUH, HUH?
HERE.
- HMM?!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING,
AYEKA?
- OH, EXCUSE ME.
I'M SO SORRY.
- TENCHI,
IT'S COMING AT YOU.
- WHOA.
- THIS IS IT.
- ATTACK!
- MISSED ME.
- THERE GOES MY
VEGETABLE GARDEN.
( sighs )
- ( meowing )
( meows )
( crying meows )
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I DON'T WANT TO USE THIS,
BUT YOU GIVE ME NO CHOICE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S MECHA-WASHU'S
SELF-DESTRUCT DEVICE.
- YOU MEAN TO TELL ME YOU HAD
THAT CHOICE ALL ALONG, WASHU?
- HEY, SHE TOOK ME A LONG TIME
TO CREATE, YOU KNOW.
GOOD-BYE,
MY MECHANICAL WASHU.
I HAD WANTED TO TAKE OVER
THE UNIVERSE WITH YOU.
- ( all scream )
- AAH!
- MAY HER SPIRIT
REST IN PEACE.
- COME TO ME,
SPARE BODY.
AAH!
- ( groans )
OH NO!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S THE SPARE BODY
I WAS RESERVING.
- AH.
I THOUGHT THAT
I WAS GONE.
- ( all groan )
- KILLING AN OFFICER
IS A VERY GRAVE OFFENSE.
YOU MUST BE SEVERELY PUNISHED.
- ( all murmur )
- MECHA-WASHU!
BEAM!
- ( all scream )
- OH BOY.
NOW WHAT'S HAPPENING?
UH...
( crying )
- IT IS WAY PAST
OUR ASSIGNED PATROLLING TIME.
I WONDER WHAT MIHOSHI
IS UP TO NOW?
- YOU CAN'T TREAT ME LIKE THAT.
YOU CAN'T TREAT ME LIKE THAT.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- HMM?
- Both: HI, KIYONE.
- HUH?
- KIYONE, YOU HAVE TO
LISTEN TO ME.
- THESE GUYS ARE REALLY
GANGING UP ON ME, KIYONE.
AND THEY'RE REALLY
GETTING IN MY WAY.
- UH...
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( crying )
- KIYONE, BE CAREFUL!
- WHOA-HO!
- ( crying continues )
- WASHU, DO SOMETHING.
- THE SPARE BODY ISN'T
EQUIPPED TO SELF DESTRUCT.
- AAH!
- TENCHI, DOES THAT ROBOT
HAVE THE MIND OF MIHOSHI?
IS THAT IT?
- ( crying )
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GUESSED IT.
- ( chuckles )
- YOU KNOW YOU ARE
UNBELIEVABLE?!
TROUBLEMAKER IS
AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
- I KNOW. SORRY.
- AAH!
AND WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO NOW?!
- KIYONE, PLEASE.
HELP US.
- IF THE ROBOT AND MIHOSHI
TRULY THINK ALIKE,
TENCHI, THIS WILL WORK.
- HUH?
- MIHOSHI,
YOU'D BETTER HURRY.
IT'S ALMOST STARTING NOW.
- HMM? AH!
- ( crying )
- ( panting )
I DON'T WANT TO MISS ANYTHING.
- OH MY GOODNESS!
IT'S ALREADY TIME.
- ( pants )
- ( panting )
- OKAY...
- HMM.
- HUH?
- METAMORA FORCE!
AAH!
- YEAH, YEAH!
OH BOY!
- YES, GO, YEAH!
- SEE? I TOLD YOU
IT WAS GOING TO WORK, TENCHI.
- YEP, YOU TOLD ME
IT WAS GONNA WORK.
- NOW, TELL ME WHERE IS
THE SWITCH FOR ITS POWER?
- THE POWER SWITCH IS
BEHIND HER NECK.
- WOW.
- WOW. IT'S A GREAT SHOW.
YOU ARE SUCH A GOOD GIRL.
NOW HOLD STILL
FOR ME, OKAY?
- WOW! WOW.
WOW. WOW.
WOW...
WOW... WOW.
- ( sighs )
- KIYONE,
WHEN IT COMES TO KNOWING
HOW MIHOSHI'S MIND WORKS,
YOU'RE AN EXPERT!
- OH, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
I'M PROUD OF.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA. TRUST ME.
- HA!
- COME AND GET IT.
EVERYBODY, DINNER'S READY.
LET'S GO. COME ON.
- OH, GREAT.
IT'S DINNERTIME.
'CAUSE I WAS REALLY STARVING,
AND I AM SO
READY TO EAT!
UM, WASHU,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- YOU'RE SUCH AN AIRHEAD!
- WASHU, YOU ARE A GENIUS.
- WASHU, YOU ARE THE GREATEST
IN THE WORLD.
- I'VE FINALLY DONE IT.
I HAVE MADE SURE TO ONLY PUT
MY MIND DATA THIS TIME.
I'LL CALL HER
MECHA-WASHU TWO.
- All: OHH. HUH?
- HMM? WHAT?
AAH!
- ( meows )
- THIS MUST BE...
- RYO, RYO...
RYO-OHKI?!
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
NOW THIS IS FUNNY.
- ( crying )
( meows )
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- IT'S SNOWING!
COME OUT AND SEE IT QUICKLY,
OHKI.
- BRR! IT'S FREEZING TODAY.
OH, A DAY LIKE THIS IS PERFECT
FOR HAVING HOT SAKE.
- RYOKO IS GLUED
TO THE HEATER.
- ONE MORNING,
AS SNOW FALLS SILENTLY,
THE LONG FORGOTTEN MEMORIES
COME BACK TO US.
COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR MEMORIES."
YES, I REMEMBER.
IT WAS SNOWING LIKE THIS
ON THAT DAY.
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
MELANCHOLIC.