- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- ( meowing )
- ( drums playing )
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
TODAY WE ARE BRINGING YOU
THE CONCLUSION
OF "TENCHI MUYO"'S
SPECIAL EPISODES.
- BECAUSE THE DIMENSION TUNER
WENT OUT OF CONTROL
OUR HEROES HAVE BEEN TRAVELING
THROUGH DIFFERENT WORLDS.
HOW WILL THIS TIME
AND SPACE TRAVEL END?
- SO, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
LET US FIND OUT...
- Both:
WHERE THEY ARE GOING.
- ( drums play )
- ( man yodels )
- ( birds chirping )
- Tenchi:
ALL RIGHT, I'M OFF.
- Mihoshi: WAIT, HONEY.
- WHAT?
- YOUR TIE ISN'T STRAIGHT.
THERE, THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
( giggles )
- BYE.
- SEE YOU THIS EVENING, BYE.
OH, SASAMI, YOU BETTER HURRY UP.
YOU'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- COMING!
- THAT'S MY GOOD GIRL.
DO YOU HAVE
EVERYTHING YOU NEED?
- YEAH, I DO, MOM.
PLEASE DON'T FORGET
TO FEED RYO-OHKI, OKAY?
- OH NO, I WON'T FORGET
TO FEED HER.
- I'D BETTER GET GOING.
- WATCH OUT FOR TRAFFIC, SASAMI!
- I WILL!
- ( yawns )
HUH? OH, THE OLD MAID
OF THE HOUSE IS HERE ALREADY.
- ARE YOU CALLING ME
AN OLD MAID, SISTER-IN-LAW?
- UH, NO, I SAID
YOU'RE UP EARLY TODAY, HUH?
- YEAH RIGHT.
I KNOW I'M JUST THE OLD NAGGING
SISTER-IN-LAW, AREN'T I?
WELL, I GRIPE ABOUT LOTS OF
THINGS BECAUSE I AM RESPONSIBLE
FOR KEEPING THIS HOUSE
RUNNING, YOU KNOW.
( slurps )
EW, SALTY!
WHAT IS THE DEAL
WITH YOUR MISO SOUP ANYWAY?
- I'M SORRY.
- IF YOU WERE SOMEONE
I COULD COUNT ON,
I WOULDN'T HESITATE
TO GET MARRIED
AND LEAVE THIS HOUSE
IN YOUR CARE.
BUT LOOK AT YOU! YOU JUST
SIT AROUND AND SPACE OUT
ALL DAY.
HMM.
- ( moos )
- WHAT IS THIS WEIRD STUFF.
- WELL, IT'S CROQUETTE, SIS.
- YOU CALL THIS A CROQUETTE?
IT'S MORE LIKE A
LUMP OF CHARCOAL.
- SORRY AGAIN.
- MY GOODNESS. YOU KNOW,
IT'S REALLY QUITE UNBELIEVABLE
YOU JUST CANNOT GET ANYTHING
STRAIGHT, NOW CAN YOU?
( chokes, coughs )
COULD YOU MOVE ANY SLOWER?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SPEND ALL
DAY ON THAT, YOU KNOW?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY.
- WELL, LOOK HERE.
LOOKS TO ME AS THOUGH THESE
SCREENS ARE VERY DUSTY.
- OOH, RIGHT.
- AND THIS AREA IS
PARTICULARLY DIRTY.
- I'M COMING THERE RIGHT NOW.
- AND DON'T FORGET
OVER HERE EITHER.
- RIGHT AWAY, SIS.
- OH, WHAT HAVE WE HERE,
I WONDER.
COULD IT POSSIBLY BE
ANOTHER MESS?
- I'M COMING!
( yells, screams )
- ( both screaming )
- ( grunts ) THERE.
- SO TELL ME, SISTER-IN-LAW,
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU DID THE LAUNDRY ANYWAY?
- UH...
- HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU
THAT YOU SHOULD DO
LAUNDRY MORE OFTEN?
- ( yawning )
I'M SORRY.
- OH, NOT SO MUCH, MIHOSHI!
YOU MUSTN'T BE SO WASTEFUL.
YOU SHOULDN'T WASTE
DETERGENT LIKE THAT.
- ( yawning )
I'LL BE MORE CAREFUL.
COME ON, ARE YOU REALLY
SURE ABOUT THIS, SIS?
TODAY'S NOT OUR TRASH DAY.
YOU REMEMBER?
- HEY, WE'RE FINE
IF WE DON'T GET CAUGHT.
- ( meowing )
- EAT UP.
( laughs ) YOU HAVE A STRANGE
NAME FOR A CAT, RYO-OHKI.
"WHISKERS" IS MORE LIKE
A NORMAL CAT'S NAME,
DON'T YOU
THINK SO, RYO-OHKI?
HUH?
- ( meowing )
- HUH! MIHOSHI!
THE MEAT MARKET
HAS A 50%-OFF SALE.
- HUH?
- TODAY!
IT SAYS IT RIGHT HERE.
- ( trumpet playing "Charge" )
- HELLO, EXCUSE ME!
500g OF ROAST PORK--
UH, NO, BEEF.
300g OF DICED BEEF.
PLEASE, HELLO!
CAN SOMEBODY HELP ME PLEASE?
( sighing )
I'M EXHAUSTED.
HUH?
WELL, SINCE I'M ALREADY
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD...
- ( phone ringing )
- KIYONE, YOU HAVE
A CALL ON LINE ONE.
- THANK YOU.
HELLO, THIS IS KIYONE.
HOW MAY I HELP YOU TODAY?
( growls )
- Mihoshi: I HAVE TO SAY,
MY HUSBAND'S SISTER, SHE IS
SUCH A NIT-PICKER, KIYONE.
SHE'S ALWAYS FINDING FAULT
WITH EVERYTHING THAT I DO
AND SHE YELLS AT ME
ALL DAY LONG.
OKAY, LIKE TODAY
FOR EXAMPLE,
WHEN I SAID, "WHAT'S WRONG,"
SHE SAID STUFF LIKE,
"WHAT WAS THAT CROQUETTE
YOU SERVED THIS MORNING?"
I MEAN, LIKE,
COULD YOU LIVE WITH THAT?
- OKAY, LISTEN UP. IF ALL YOU
WANT TO DO IS COMPLAIN,
I'VE GOT LOTS OF WORK
TO DO, YOU KNOW?
- HUH? BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
WE GET TO SEE EACH OTHER
THAT OFTEN, IS IT?
- WE'VE BEEN GETTING TOGETHER
QUITE FREQUENTLY
SINCE OUR GRADUATION.
- REALLY?
- REALLY.
- BESIDES YOU ALWAYS TELL ME
THE SAME OLD STORY
EVERY TIME I SEE YOU.
- YOU KNOW, FRUSTRATION IS
NOT GOOD FOR YOU, KIYONE.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GET
MARRIED OR SOMETHING?
- NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- EXCUSE ME!
I'D LIKE TO HAVE ANOTHER
CHOCOLATE PARFAIT,
IF YOU PLEASE.
- ARE YOU LISTENING AT ALL?
- OF COURSE I AM.
WELL, SO MY SISTER-IN-LAW,
SHE CALLS ALL KINDS OF NAMES,
LIKE SLOW AND DUMB AND--
OH, I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
- I NEED A STRAWBERRY SUNDAE
HERE AND MAKE IT LARGE.
- ( door unlocks )
- HELLO, I'M HOME.
( sighs )
- ( bell ringing,
drums playing )
- ( hums )
- HI, MIHOSHI.
- OH, IT'S YOU, RYOKO.
HELLO.
- WE ARE OUT
OF SOY SAUCE AGAIN.
CAN YOU SPARE US SOME, PLEASE?
- OH SURE, JUST A MINUTE
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
HUH?
- SORRY TO BOTHER YOU LIKE THIS.
- EXCUSE ME, WAIT A MINUTE.
I DIDN'T INVITE YOU IN, DID I?
- OH, NOW YOU DON'T MIND ME.
- WELL, I KNOW YOU SAY NOT
TO MIND YOU, BUT, RYOKO--
- OH, I SEE YOUR HUSBAND
HASN'T HOME YET, HAS HE?
HUH? HMM? HMM?
- THAT'S RIGHT, RYOKO.
- AHHH.
THAT WAS A LONG DAY.
- HELLO THERE, TENCHI!
- ( moans )
- AHH, RYOKO, IT'S YOU!
- WELCOME HOME!
- ( yelps )
- NOW, IN ATAMI...
- HUH? WHAT ABOUT ATAMI?
- MY FRIEND RUNS
A BED AND BREAKFAST PLACE THERE.
DON'T YOU WANT TO GO
WITH ME THERE, HUH?
- HOW COME YOU ALWAYS
COME OVER HERE
AND TRY TO STEAL MY HUSBAND?
- ARE YOU HERE AGAIN, RYOKO?
WHAT ARE YOU, A CAT BURGLAR?
- HERE SHE IS, THE OLD BAG.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING
AN OLD BAG?!
RYOKO, YOU ARE A WIDOW.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY BEHAVING
LIKE ONE SOMETIME
AND ACT WITH A LITTLE MODESTY?
OH, IT IS VERY UNPLEASANT
TO SEE YOU FLIRTING
LIKE THAT.
- HMPH. IT'S VERY
UNPLEASANT TO SEE YOU
BEHAVING LIKE AN OLD BAG
WHO'S NEVER BEEN MARRIED.
- ( shrieks )
I CAN'T STAND YOU!
- AYEKA, RYOKO, STOP IT.
THE WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD
CAN HEAR YOU.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
- SEE, TENCHI?
ATAMI IS THE PLACE FOR US
TO GO AND GET MARRIED.
- HEY, RYOKO!
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
NOW I'M SURE EVERYONE WILL
GIVE US THEIR BLESSING.
- ( unison )
WE CERTAINLY WILL NOT!
- ( zapping sound )
- ( blues music playing )
- ( alarm ringing )
- ( gunshots )
- ( moans )
- OOOH!
- ( gunshots )
- ( whimpers )
- WHOO-HOO!
( laughs )
( tires screech )
- WE'VE DONE IT, TENCHI!
HA HA!
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
ROBBING A BANK, HUH?
- THIS ISN'T ME.
THIS ISN'T WHAT I DO.
WHY AM I DOING THIS?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
- HEY, WE'RE
HAVING FUN, AREN'T WE?
- I DON'T FIND THIS
AMUSING AT ALL!
- WELL, I DO!
HA HA HA HA HA!
- Both: YUP!
- ( drums playing )
- YUP!
- ( newsreel music playing )
- Reporter: RYOKO,
THE GANGSTER THAT HAS BEEN
TERRORIZING THE ENTIRE
UNITED STATES IS STILL AT LARGE,
DESPITE A NATIONWIDE MANHUNT
BY THE POLICE.
IT'S BEEN A MONTH
SINCE TENCHI MADURSKY,
THE GRANDSON OF REVEREND
MADURSKY AT SAINT MASAKI,
WAS KIDNAPPED BY RYOKO.
HIS SAFETY IS OF MAJOR
CONCERN TO THE POLICE,
BUT HE IS NOW A WANTED MAN,
SUSPECTED OF BEING RYOKO'S
CONFEDERATE IN THE SHOOTING
AT THE NATIONAL BANK.
F.B.I. OFFICERS MIHOSHI GRAMMY
AND KIYONE McKINBY
DECLARED RYOKO'S ARREST
IS IMMINENT.
TENCHI MADURSKY'S FIANCEE, JURAI
FINANCIAL GROUP MILLIONAIRESS
MISS AYEKA JURAI,
SEVERELY CRITICIZED THE
INCOMPETENCE OF THE F.B.I.
SHE ANNOUNCED THAT SHE WILL
OFFER A MILLION DOLLAR REWARD
FOR ANYONE WITH INFORMATION
LEADING TO THE ARREST
OF THE SUSPECT.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE CONSULTED WITH
US BEFORE YOU OFFERED A REWARD.
- YES, MISS AYEKA.
PEOPLE MIGHT GET THE IDEA
THAT WE'RE INCOMPETENT
OR SOMETHING.
- THERE IS NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THAT IS WHAT YOU ARE--
INCOMPETENT!
YOU CANNOT BE IN CHARGE OF THIS
INVESTIGATION ANY LONGER.
- NOW WAIT A MINUTE.
JUST WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THAT RIFLE?
- WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
I'M GOING TO TAKE CARE
OF THIS SITUATION MYSELF.
I'M GOING TO DEAL
WITH RYOKO IN MY OWN WAY.
- ALL RIGHT, I SEE!
- AYEKA, CAREFUL.
CALM DOWN.
- LET ME GO!
- ( whimpering )
- WHILE WE WASTE TIME HERE,
TENCHI'S WITH RYOKO
AND I WON'T ALLOW IT!
- ( all yell )
- DON'T SHOOT!
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
- ( screams )
- ( gunfire )
- HUH?
- THIS WAY, TENCHI.
- OH, OKAY.
UH, HEH HEH.
PLEASE COOPERATE.
THANK YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- ( laughs )
- ( whimpers )
- ( laughs ) TENCHI?
- OH UH...
( sighs )
- ( growls )
- LOOK, TENCHI, THE SETO BRIDGE
IS SOMETHING ELSE, ISN'T IT?
- D'OH!
LOOK HERE, RYOKO,
THAT BRIDGE HAPPENS
TO BE THE GOLDEN GATE.
- ( laughs ) WELL, IT REALLY
DOESN'T MATTER EITHER WAY.
HMMM.
WE CAN SURE SEE A SKY
FULL OF STARS, HUH?
THE STARS ARE BEAUTIFUL.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- WE'RE ALL ALONE UNDER
THE STARRY SKY, YOU AND ME.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW I GOT MYSELF
INTO THIS MESS.
- ( laughs )
- WHAT IS IT?
- NOTHING. IT'S JUST--
- IT'S JUST WHAT, RYOKO?
- ( boat whistle blares )
- HEY, TENCHI?
- HUH?
- WE'VE GONE THROUGH
A LOT OF STUFF
SINCE WE STARTED THIS
JOURNEY, HAVEN'T WE?
- WE SURE HAVE.
- ( sighs )
I JUST LOVE STARS.
- ( zapping sound )
- WHAT?
( moans )
- HUH?
- WASHU, IT'S YOU!
IT'S REALLY YOU!
- LONG TIME NO SEE, TENCHI.
- SO YOU'VE FINALLY
FIXED THAT MACHINE?
- IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
I HAD TO ELIMINATE NUMEROUS
DIFFERENT WORLDS
IN ORDER TO CATCH UP
WITH YOU TWO.
- ALL RIGHT!
SO NOW WE CAN RETURN TO OUR
ORIGINAL WORLD, RIGHT?
- WELL, THERE IS STILL
ONE PROBLEM.
- WHAT?
- YOU WERE THE FIRST ONE THAT
TAMPERED WITH MY MACHINE,
WEREN'T YOU, RYOKO?
- UH...
I DON'T REMEMBER.
- THIS WORLD SEEMS
TO BE REFLECTING
YOUR IDEA
OF A PERFECT WORLD.
- OH YEAH, RIGHT,
OF COURSE.
NO WONDER
IT'S SO MESSED UP.
- IT WILL BE IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME
TO ELIMINATE THIS WORLD
WITHOUT YOUR HELP, RYOKO.
YOU NEED TO RENOUNCE
THIS WORLD.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY FOR US TO
GET BACK TO OUR ORIGINAL WORLD.
- NO WAY.
- HUH?
- I WILL NEVER DENY
THIS WORLD.
- NEVER? BUT DON'T YOU
MISS OUR ORIGINAL WORLD?
COME ON, RYOKO!
- NOT AT ALL, NO, I DON'T.
- RYOKO, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SO SELFISH AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
WHY DON'T YOU WANT
TO GO BACK?
- BECAUSE I--
TENCHI, HAVEN'T WE HAD
SOME FUN TOGETHER?
- YOU DON'T GIVE ME ANY CHOICES.
HOW CAN I ANSWER THAT?
- I THOUGHT THIS WORLD WAS
BEGINNING TO GROW ON YOU,
TENCHI.
ISN'T IT, AT LEAST A LITTLE?
- THAT'S YOUR WISHFUL THINKING!
- YES, I HOPED!
I BELIEVED WE HAD
A DEEP BOND BETWEEN US.
I WISHED FOR THAT,
I ADMIT IT.
NOW TELL ME
I WAS WRONG, TENCHI.
DO YOU HATE THE IDEA
OF CONTINUING TO TRAVEL
WITH ME SO MUCH?
- WELL... I'M JUST...
- ( sobbing )
I'M STAYING IN THIS WORLD!
THIS IS THE WORLD I DESIRE.
THIS IS MY WORLD!
I'M NOT LEAVING IT!
- ♪ FEEL THE WIND ♪
♪ FEEL THE SUN
AND A NEW DAY ♪
♪ IN PARADISE
HAS ONLY BEGUN ♪
♪ ON THE SAND ♪
♪ BY THE SEA ♪
♪ IT'S A PEACEFUL OASIS ♪
♪ MADE FOR YOU AND FOR ME ♪
♪ TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ THIS PLACE WAS
ALWAYS WAITING ♪
♪ THERE'S BEAUTY
ALL AROUND US ♪
♪ THE AIR INTOXICATING ♪
♪ JUST LIKE THE LOVE
THAT FOUND US ♪
♪ LET'S FORGET
WHO WE'VE BEEN ♪
♪ AND GIVE IN TO THE DREAM ♪
♪ MAYBE LIFE IS A SONG ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW IT SEEMS ♪
♪ AND FOREVERMORE
WE'LL HEAR THE MUSIC PLAY ♪
♪ YES, FOREVERMORE I'LL TAKE YOU
IN MY ARMS THIS WAY. ♪
- ( boat whistle blares )
- GUH. RYOKO!
- YEAH.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- WE'RE GOING BACK TO
THE ORIGINAL WORLD, AREN'T WE?
- YOU'RE OKAY ABOUT THAT?
- YES.
- BUT YOU WERE SO ATTACHED
TO THIS WORLD, RYOKO.
- THIS JOURNEY ISN'T REAL
AND IT'S TIME I REALIZED THAT.
- RYOKO, I--
- SO, WASHU, I'M READY
ANY TIME YOU ARE.
LET'S JUST GET IT OVER WITH.
- HMM, LET'S GO THEN.
- ( beeping )
- RYOKO'S BRAINWAVES, CHECK.
- HUH?
- HMM.
- THE DIMENSION TUNER
IS NOW SET.
NOW HANG ON!
- ( zapping sound )
- RYOKO, I-- I'M--
- DON'T SAY ANYTHING
NOW, TENCHI,
OTHERWISE WE'LL NEVER
MAKE IT BACK.
- RYOKO--
- BUT SOMEDAY, TENCHI,
I WILL TAKE YOU
ON A REAL JOURNEY WITH ME.
I WILL, SOMEDAY.
- ( chirping )
- OH WOW, THAT WAS
REALLY EXHAUSTING.
- YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
WE'VE BEEN TO KYOTO
AND A NORTHERN FISHING VILLAGE
AND WE'VE BEEN TO--
- YOU DIDN'T LIKE IT?
I THOUGHT IT WAS KINDA FUN.
- ( giggles )
YEAH, IT WAS!
- YOU TWO ARE CAREFREE,
SO OF COURSE YOU HAD FUN.
- YOU KNOW,
ALL OF THIS WAS CAUSED
BY THAT RIDICULOUS
STUPID RYOKO.
HUH? RYOKO?!
WHERE IS SHE?
WHERE COULD SHE BE?
- SHE'S NOT AROUND, HUH?
- I'LL BET SHE'S FLIRTING
WITH TENCHI OR SOMETHING!
I CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT.
ARGHHH!
I CAN'T STAND IT!
- CALM DOWN, YOU OLD MAID.
CALM DOWN NOW.
- WHAT?!
WHAT DID YOU CALL ME?
- Tenchi: HEY, RYOKO!
- HUH?
HMM?
HMM.
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Tenchi: A JURAIAN BATTLESHIP
ARRIVES ON EARTH
WITHOUT WARNING.
THEY HAVE COME
TO ARREST AYEKA.
- Ayeka: THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
SOME MISUNDERSTANDING.
- Ryoko: OH WELL,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE THE
CONSEQUENCES OF YOUR BEHAVIOR.
- Tenchi: BUT THEN
THEY ARREST RYOKO TOO.
- Ryoko: WHAT?!
-
THAT WAS THE BEGINNING OF
THE BIG INCIDENT
THAT ROCKS THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED
ON PLANET JURAI?
COMING NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR REBELLION,"
THE SHOCKING START
OF OUR SPACE SERIES.
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
A NEW DEVELOPMENT.