- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- YO!
- RYO-OH'S TREE HAS
GROWN SO MUCH.
IT'S AMAZING.
- IT'S TRUE.
JURAI'S SHIPS ARE
VERY STRONG INDEED.
THEY CAN LIVE ON JUST
A LITTLE SOIL AND WATER
FOR THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
- WELL, I'M OFF
TO SCHOOL NOW, AYEKA. BYE.
- YOU HAVE A NICE DAY,
TENCHI.
- WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- ( chuckles )
- OKAY.
I GUESS WE SHOULD
DO SOME LAUNDRY.
- UH-HUH.
- HMM?
RYOKO?
WHERE DID SHE GO TO?
- HUH?
- ( groans )
I'LL BET SHE'S SKIPPING
HER HOUSE CHORES.
AGAIN.
SHE'S A REAL PARASITE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
SHE REALLY
DRIVES ME CRAZY.
- RYOKO, YOU SHOULD HELP OTHERS
AROUND THE HOUSE SOMETIMES.
- I SUPPOSE SO.
I AM SPONGING OFF YOU, AREN'T I?
I'M QUITE A MOOCH,
I GUESS.
- YEAH, WELL,
AYEKA MUST BE REALLY FURIOUS.
- LET HER BE FURIOUS.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT HER.
- OH, RYOKO.
- HEY, TENCHI?
- NOW WHAT IS IT?
- HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
SINCE AYEKA AND I CAME HERE,
TENCHI?
DO YOU REMEMBER?
- I GUESS IT'S BEEN
ABOUT THREE MONTHS.
- REALLY.
JUST THREE MONTHS, HUH?
- I BELIEVE THAT'S RIGHT.
- TENCHI...
WE ARE HAVING FUN.
AND EVERY DAY HERE
IS LIKE A DREAM.
I REALLY HOPE IT'S GOING
TO BE LIKE THIS FOREVER.
- HUH?
- TENCHI...
- ALL RIGHT, GREAT!
FANTASTIC!
I'M GETTING A PROMOTION.
I CAN GO BACK TO HEADQUARTERS.
OH, I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS DAY FOR SO LONG,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S GREAT NEWS,
KIYONE.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
FINALLY MY LUCK IS CHANGING.
I'M FULL-TIME GALAXY POLICE.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'RE SO FUNNY, KIYONE.
- OKAY.  JUST WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING, MIHOSHI?
- GETTING READY TO GO BACK TO
HEADQUARTERS WITH YOU,
OF COURSE.
- THEY'RE TAKING ME BACK
AND NOT YOU.
- HUH?
NO!
THEY CAN'T DO THIS TO ME.
WHAT AM I EVER GONNA
DO WITHOUT YOU?
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
DON'T WORRY, MIHOSHI.
IN THIS PLACE,
THERE WON'T BE ANYTHING
TOO BIG FOR YOU TO HANDLE.
MMM...
LET'S SEE.
OH, THOSE NEED TO BE
TURNED IN THIS WEEK.
OTHERWISE, YOU WON'T
GET PAID UNTIL NEXT MONTH.
AND ABOUT MY CHEESECAKE
IN THE FRIDGE,
YOU CAN GO AHEAD
AND EAT IT.
IT'S ALL YOURS,
MIHOSHI.
- ( crying )
DON'T LEAVE ME, KIYONE.
- WHOA, MIHOSHI,
GIVE THAT BACK.
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
- BUT I'VE ALREADY RECEIVED
AN OFFICIAL ANNOUNCEMENT
OF APPOINTMENT.
- NO, NO, NO.
- GIVE ME MY SUITCASE BACK,
YOU CRYBABY!
- ( strained)
NO, I CAN'T.
- CUT IT OUT!
- I WON'T!
- ( both grunt )
- UGH.
- SO YOU'RE GOING BACK TO THE
GALAXY POLICE HEADQUARTERS, HUH?
- YES. MY REQUEST FOR TRANSFER
WAS FINALLY APPROVED.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
- NOW, IT'S A PROMOTION,
ISN'T IT?
- EVERYONE, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR EVERYTHING, REALLY.
- I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU,
KIYONE.
- THANK YOU.
I'M GONNA START
MY LIFE ANEW
WITHOUT MIHOSHI, YOU KNOW?
I'M FEELING SO--
( giggles )
( cries )
- I KNOW HOW YOU MUST FEEL.
- OH, BUT WE ARE GONNA
MISS YOU, KIYONE.
WE REALLY ARE.
- ( crying )
I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT KIYONE!
- OH.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- ( crying continues )
- OHH?
OH, WHAT THE--?!
( stammers )
IT'S GONE!
MY HOUSE IS GONE!
UHH...
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI,
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
- ( meows )
- MEOW MEOW MEOW,
RYO-OHKI?
CALM DOWN.
CAN'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
- ( meows )
- OH, THIS IS HOPELESS.
- TENCHI.
- OH, GRANDPA.
- TENCHI,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS OVER AT THE SHRINE,
SO I DIDN'T SEE--
HUH?
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- WHAT IS THAT?
OH!
- AAH!
WHOA.
BUMPY RIDE.
- ( screams )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( meows )
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU GUYS?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( meows )
- WELL, THIS GENIUS
IS TOTALLY CAUGHT OFF GUARD,
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
NOW IT'S MY TURN.
NOW I MUST GET
BACK AT THEM.
- WASHU, WHAT HAPPENED?
TELL ME!
- HOLD ON A MINUTE.
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT.
- HUH? HEY...
WHERE IS AYEKA?
RYOKO ISN'T HERE EITHER.
- ( crying )
- AND SASAMI IS MISSING TOO.
I DON'T GET IT, WASHU.
WHY AREN'T THEY HERE?
- DIDN'T I SAY I'D
TELL YOU IN A MINUTE?
TO MAKE A LONG STORY SHORT...
WE FOUND OURSELVES
ON A SPACESHIP,
INCLUDING YOUR HOUSE
AND EVERYTHING.
THE SHIP BELONGED TO
PLANET JURAI'S MILITARY.
- JURAI'S MILITARY?
- SUCH RUDE BEHAVIOR.
DO YOU REALIZE I AM
THE CROWN PRINCESS OF JURAI?
I GUESS THE COUNCIL
MUST HAVE ORDERED YOU
TO BRING ME BACK TO
THE PLANET JURAI,
BUT I HAVE ALREADY TOLD THEM
THAT I WAS GOING TO STAY
HERE FOR AWHILE.
- YOUR HIGHNESS,
I'M AFRAID THAT...
BRINGING YOU BACK
TO THE PLANET JURAI
WAS NOT OUR INTENTION.
- EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WE'VE COME TO ARREST YOU,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
- TO ARREST ME?
- All: HUH?!
- HUH?
( laughs )
YOU'RE JOKING.
ARREST ME.
ON WHAT CHARGES?
- YOU ARE CHARGED
WITH HIGH TREASON.
- NO WAY.
- SO THAT'S WHY ONLY THE FOUR
OF US WERE SENT BACK.
- AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENED
TO OUR HOUSE.
- OUR HOUSE!
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT'S IT?
- NOT THAT I'M NOT GLAD
THEY GAVE IT BACK TO US,
BUT YOU KNOW.
- THEY COMPRESSED IT
DOWN TO A PORTABLE SIZE.
THOUGHTFUL, HUH?
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- BELIEVE IT.
CHECK OUT AZAKA
AND KAMIDAKE.
- UH...
( screams )
WHERE IS SASAMI?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO HER, WASHU?
WELL OF COURSE THEY CONSIDER HER
TO BE A PARTNER IN
THE REBELLION.
- I SEE.
SO THEY TOOK HER
INTO CUSTODY ALSO.
- AND RYOKO?
- AH, YES, RYOKO.
- WHAT?!
YOU CANNOT ARREST ME.
THERE MUST BE SOME
KIND OF MISUNDERSTANDING.
- HEY, AYEKA, MY DEAR.
- HMM?
- THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
A COUP OR SOMETHING,
AND YOUR FAMILY
WAS REPLACED.
HEY, IT HAPPENS.
WHAT CAN I TELL YOU?
- ( groans )
STAY OUT OF THIS!
- OH WELL.
SO JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
IS NOW OUT, HUH?
THEY SAY WHEN DYNASTIES FALL,
THE HEADS WILL ROLL.
- THEY DO NOT SAY THAT!
- I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET DEPRESSED NOW.
LIFE IN A CELL ISN'T
THAT BAD, PRINCESS.
( laughs )
- NO WAY!
SHE'S THE UNIVERSE'S
MOST WANTED SPACE PIRATE!
- HUH? RYOKO. YOU'RE RIGHT!
- ( laughs )
HUH?
- SO RYOKO WAS ALSO ARRESTED
BY JURAI'S MILITARY, I SEE.
- AND UP AGAINST
JURAI'S MILITARY FORCES,
EVEN RYOKO
COULDN'T GET AWAY.
- ( meows )
- HMM.
- YES, I KNOW.
- YO!
- HELLO? SOMEBODY, ANYBODY!
WHO DO YOU THINK I AM
IN HERE, ANYWAY?
TREATING THE CROWN PRINCESS OF
JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY LIKE THIS.
YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS,
YOU KNOW.
- RYO-OHKI.
CAN YOU HEAR ME,
RYO-OHKI?
- LET ME OUT OF HERE NOW,
I TELL YOU!
OR YOU SHALL BE
SEVERELY PUNISHED.
HEY, SOMEBODY!
- ( groans )
KEEP IT DOWN, WILL YOU?
I'M TRYING TO CONTACT
RYO-OHKI HERE.
I CAN'T CONCENTRATE AT ALL
WITH YOU SCREAMING LIKE THAT.
- THIS CELL IS WHERE
YOU BELONG.
WHAT ARE YOU
COMPLAINING FOR?
- CAN YOU EXPLAIN SOMETHING.
HOW DID THIS ALL HAPPEN,
AYEKA?
- I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA.
I'M SORRY.
- WELL, SINCE JURAI'S
MILITARY IS INVOLVED,
SOMETHING HAPPENED ON JURAI.
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
AN INCIDENT.
- I HOPE NOT.
- PROBABLY BECAUSE YOU'RE SO
UNPOPULAR WITH THE JURAIANS.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
LISTEN TO ME.
JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
IS OF GOOD LINEAGE,
AND THE PEOPLE JUST ADORE US
SO MUCH, I TELL YOU.
- ENOUGH ABOUT THAT.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO US NOW?
- WHEN YOU'RE CHARGED
WITH HIGH TREASON,
THE MOST COMMON SENTENCE
WOULD BE CAPITAL PUNISHMENT,
WOULDN'T IT?
- UH...
WELL, IF YOUR CASE
GOES TO TRIAL,
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH
THAT MERE 700 YEARS
OF IMPRISONMENT THIS TIME.
- ( both scowl )
- HUH?
- HEY! WHO IS IN CHARGE HERE?
- RYO-OHKI, COME IN, QUICKLY.
- BRING THE PERSON WHO IS
RESPONSIBLE AROUND HERE.
CAN'T YOU HEAR ME?!
- I TOLD YOU TO KEEP IT DOWN,
DIDN'T I?
- WE HAVE TAKEN
THE PRINCESSES AYEKA AND SASAMI
INTO CUSTODY.
AS WE PLANNED,
WE WILL JOIN THE FLEET
AT 34 HUNDRED HOURS EXACTLY.
- WELL DONE. LORD YOSHO WILL
BE VERY HAPPY TO HEAR THAT.
- ADMIRAL?
- WHAT IS IT?
- MAY I ASK ABOUT OUR PLAN?
WHY DID THE COUNCIL
DECIDE TO--?
- WE SOLDIERS SIMPLY
HAVE TO OBEY ORDERS,
NOT ASK QUESTIONS,
CAPTAIN.
YOU NEED NOT THINK ABOUT
ANYTHING ELSE, UNDERSTOOD?
- UH, UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
- CAPTAIN, AN UNIDENTIFIED
FLYING OBJECT IS APPROACHING US
FROM PLANET EARTH.
- REALLY?
- I THINK IT'S A PATROL SHIP
OF THE GALAXY POLICE.
- MUST BE THOSE POLICE
THAT WERE WITH THE PRINCESS.
- I'M A GALAXY POLICE OFFICER
ASSIGNED TO THIS
SOLAR SYSTEM AREA.
- AS I INFORMED YOU,
WE ARE FOLLOWING
PLANET JURAI'S DIRECT ORDERS.
THE GALAXY POLICE SHOULD NOT
INTERFERE, DETECTIVE.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
- THIS AREA IS
OUR JURISDICTION.
THE SPACE PIRATE RYOKO
IS A WANTED CRIMINAL.
WE REQUEST THAT YOU AT LEAST
HAND HER OVER TO US.
- INSIDE THIS BATTLESHIP
IS JURAI'S TERRITORY.
SINCE RYOKO WAS
ARRESTED ON BOARD,
WE WILL TAKE HER
TO THE PLANET JURAI
FOR TRIAL.
THAT IS OUR NORMAL PROCEDURE.
- BUT OUR SUPERIORS
WILL BE UPSET.
- THAT PATROL SHIP'S
STILL APPROACHING.
- HALT YOUR SHIP IMMEDIATELY,
OTHERWISE WE MUST ATTACK.
THIS IS NOT NEGOTIABLE.
IF YOU HAVE ANY COMPLAINTS,
TAKE THEM UP WITH
FLEET HEADQUARTERS.
- BUT LISTEN, PLEASE,
CAPTAIN.
- NO!
- ( gasps )
I CAN'T GO ANY FURTHER.
- COME ON NOW.
YOU HAVE TO GET CLOSER.
JUST A LITTLE BIT CLOSER.
- THE PATROL SHIP
HASN'T STOPPED YET, CAPTAIN.
- READY TO FIRE!
- ( gasps )
- EVERYONE PAY ATTENTION.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS MY LATEST INVENTION.
- All: HUH? WHAT?
- HERE IT IS.
- All: HUH?
- THIS DOOR FUNCTIONS
AS A PORTAL.
- HUH?
- WHAT?!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
WHY DIDN'T WE USE THIS
EARLIER, WASHU?
TELL ME, PLEASE.
- BECAUSE IT'S RANGE
IS ONLY 800 METERS.
IT DOESN'T WORK LIKE
IT WOULD IN A CARTOON!
- WELL, I GUESS WE'D
BETTER HURRY, HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- BE CAREFUL,
AND GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
- NOW WE'RE ALREADY
IN THEIR BATTLESHIP.
- SO THIS IS IT?
- I THINK WE'RE CLEAR NOW,
KIYONE.
- ROGER.
- ( panting )
WHICH WAY SHOULD WE GO?
- CAN YOU SENSE WHERE
RYOKO MIGHT BE?
- ( meows )
- THE PLACE WHERE
THEY'RE LOCKED UP
IS PROBABLY SHIELDED.
I'M AFRAID TELEPATHY
WON'T WORK HERE, TENCHI.
- WELL THEN, HOW ARE WE GONNA
FIND OUT THEIR LOCATION, HUH?
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING, GRANDPA?
- QUIT WASTING TIME,
EVERYONE,
AND HURRY UP.
- WHAT?
- WAIT.
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SURE IT'S THAT WAY?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S THAT WAY?
- I HAVE A HUNCH.
- OH.
- ( panting )
- CAPTAIN, INTRUDERS
INSIDE THE SHIP.
- INTRUDERS?
- HUH?
- ( grunts )
- ( shouting )
- AAH!
( grunting )
- ( shouting, grunting )
- ( grunting )
- Both: BRAVO.
- LET'S GO.
- ( grunts )
- HELLO.
- HUH?
TENCHI, HELLO!
( giggles )
- OH, TENCHI.
YOU'RE RISKING YOUR LIFE
TO SAVE ME.
HOW WONDERFUL YOU ARE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HE'S COME TO SAVE ME,
YOU IDIOT PRINCESS.
- ( chuckles )
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU BOTH,
BUT... HOW DO YOU
OPEN THIS THING?
- ( both grunting )
- WELL THAT'S CERTAINLY
NOT GONNA GET US ANYWHERE.
WE NEED MORE
DRASTIC MEASURES.
RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- THAT'S TOO DRASTIC,
WASHU!
- COME ON.
LET'S GET INSIDE NOW.
- ( meows )
- POWER UP ALL GUN PORTS.
WE CAN'T LET THEM ESCAPE!
- ( all scream )
- RYO-OHKI, LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE. TOP SPEED!
- ( meows )
- OH BOY. I REALLY HOPE
THEY MAKE IT, KIYONE.
- YEAH.
I WONDER WHAT'S HAPPENING
ON PLANET JURAI.
- THIS IS REALLY GREAT.
LOOK, THE EARTH IS JUST
A TINY SPECK NOW.
- OH MAN.
NO KIDDING.
HOW AM I GONNA GET
TO SCHOOL TOMORROW?
- HOW AM I GONNA
GET TO WORK?
- COME ON, YOU TWO.
JUST HAVE TO GO
WITH THE FLOW.
- I GUESS SO.
MMM.
IT'S A GOOD THING
I BROUGHT OUR HOUSE WITH ME.
- UH...
BUT I AM A ROYAL PRINCESS.
WHY MUST I HAVE
ALL THESE TROUBLES?
( sighs )
- AYEKA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- BYE-BYE, EARTH.
BYE-BYE.
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- MIHOSHI AND KIYONE RETURN
TO GALAXY POLICE HEADQUARTERS
ONLY TO FIND OUT THAT
THE ENEMY HAS ALREADY
INFILTRATED THE STATION.
NOW WE'RE THE MOST WANTED
CRIMINALS IN THE UNIVERSE.
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO US NEXT?
- I'M A WANTED CRIMINAL NOW?
- COME ON, BUDDIES.
WE'LL HAVE FUN TOGETHER.
WE CRIMINALS ARE LIKE
BROTHERS, YOU KNOW?
- ( groans )
WHAT'S GONE WRONG WITH MY LIFE?
- COMING NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR ESCAPE."
WE SEEM TO HAVE BECOME A BUNCH
OF BONNIE AND CLYDE'S NOW.
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
FAST-PACED.