- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- SO THERE'S REALLY
NOTHING LEFT, SASAMI?
HMM. AW.
HMM...
WHAT IS THIS?
- SORRY. NO MORE
SNACKS FOR AWHILE.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF FOOD.
- I SEE.
WE'LL HAVE TO
ASK KIYONE TO STOP
AND DO SOME GROCERY SHOPPING,
I GUESS.
- AAH!
- WHOA!
- OOH!
- AAH!
- OHH.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- OH MY, I WONDER
WHAT'S GOING ON, KIYONE.
- ( stammers )
HOW CAN YOU BE SO UNAWARE?
ENGINE POWER'S NOW
GOING DOWN TO 50, 40.
- WELL, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOT NOW!
- HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
IT SOUNDS LIKE THE ENGINE'S
ABOUT TO STOP, YOU GUYS.
- I KNOW THAT.
I'M WORKING ON IT RIGHT NOW.
- KIYONE, I TOLD YOU
YOU SHOULD LEARN TO RELAX.
- AND YOU SHOULD
LEARN TO PANIC!
- ( stammers )
( gasping )
( grunts )
( sighs )
IT'S BROKEN.
- YO!
- RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO ME
TO FIX THIS.
- All: YEP.
- ME FIX THIS?
- All: MM-HMM.
- LET ME MAKE THIS
CLEAR FOR YOU.
I'M A SCIENTIST,
NOT A MECHANIC.
NOW I HAVE SOME
RESEARCH TO DO,
SO IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
- WAIT, WASHU.
I MEAN, PROFESSOR WASHU,
THE GREATEST SCIENTIST
IN THE UNIVERSE.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
- YES.
YOU'RE A GENIUS,
AND I AGREE WITH KIYONE,
WASHU.
THE GREATEST GENIUS
IN THE UNIVERSE
SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DO THIS.
- SINCE YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
FIXING ENGINE TROUBLE
SHOULD BE A PIECE OF CAKE.
- All: WE THOUGHT SO.
YOU'RE A GENIUS,
WASHU.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL
FOR A GENIUS.
( laughs )
- YES, WASHU.
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
- THE GREATEST
IN THE UNIVERSE.
- Both: GENIUS WASHU,
GENIUS WASHU!
- THANK GOD SHE'S
SO EASY TO PLEASE.
- NO KIDDING.
- ( meows )
- HEY, BE QUIET,
WILL YOU?
- ( meows )
- HA, HERE THEY ARE.
I GOT THEM.
- ( crashing )
- WHAT?!
HELLO?
ANYBODY IN THERE?
- ( chuckles )
- ( screams )
- OKAY. I'M GONNA USE
AN S-32 PLUG HERE.
HMM.
NOW I NEED SOME ADHESIVE.
WHERE IS THAT ADHESIVE?
WHERE ARE YOU, ADHESIVE?
- IS THIS WHAT YOU NEED?
- OH, THANK YOU, MIHOSHI.
I'LL JUST STABILIZE THIS,
AND THEN I--
HUH?!
( screams )
- MAYBE THIS IS WHAT
SHE SHOULD HAVE USED?
- ( coughs )
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
WASHU?
- YOU GET OUT OF HERE.
- JUST WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
- UH, WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
HUH?
- HMM?
- ( sniffs, meows )
- All: WHA--?
- ( meows )
- HAVE YOU BEEN
STEALING OUR FOOD?
- ( meows )
- IDIOT.
WHY ARE YOU
CARRYING THAT AROUND?
I TOLD YOU TO
EAT THEM IN PRIVATE.
- ( meows )
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
- HMM?
- SO YOU'RE BEHIND
ALL OF THIS, AREN'T YOU?
- SO WHAT IF I AM?
IT'S ONLY A LITTLE FOOD.
DON'T BE SO UPTIGHT.
- YOU DON'T EVEN
FEEL GUILTY.
- DON'T FROWN TOO MUCH, OR THOSE
WRINKLES WILL NEVER DISAPPEAR.
- HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT!
- LET'S CALM DOWN,
BOTH OF YOU.
WHAT'S GONE IS GONE.
WE NEED TO GO TO
THE GROCERY STORE.
- BUT HOW? THE SHIP
IS STALLED, GRANDPA.
- YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, I'LL GO.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
- HUH?
IT SEEMS ONLY PROPER.
- I'LL NEED SOME MONEY.
- HUH?
- I'LL GO.
MONEY, PLEASE.
- I SUPPOSE YOU DO
NEED SOME MONEY.
HERE.
- RIGHT.
- WHAT?!
- NOW...
LET'S GO, TENCHI.
- NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
TENCHI CAN'T GO!
WE NEED ALL THE HANDS WE CAN
GET TO FIX THE ENGINE TROUBLE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF
THINGS TO DO.
RIGHT, TENCHI?
- UH, YEAH.
- RIGHT.
- ( clears throat )
- HMM?
- I COULD COME ALONG.
- I'M OUT OF HERE.
SEE YOU.
- UH...
- TENCHI?
DO YOU THINK RYOKO IS GOING
TO BE OKAY ALL BY HERSELF?
- I THINK SHE'S
GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
- HMM.
WELL...
SHE BROUGHT IT ON HERSELF.
SHE HAS TO FACE THE MUSIC.
- ( beeping )
- THERE.
IT'S ALL DONE.
NOW THAT THIS IS COMPLETE,
ALL I HAVE TO DO NEXT IS...
- I'LL HIT THAT SWITCH.
- ( Washu screams )
- ( all sigh )
- LOOKS LIKE
A FEW EXTRA DAYS
TILL THE REPAIRS
ARE FINISHED.
- UH-HUH.
HEY, TENCHI?
RYOKO SHOULD BE BACK
ANYTIME NOW, RIGHT?
- UM...
YEAH, ANYTIME NOW.
- SURE, SHE WILL.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT SPENDING OUR
MONEY ON SOMETHING ELSE.
- LET'S TRY TO TRUST HER.
COME ON.
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH,
AYEKA.
- ANOTHER SAKE, PLEASE.
- WHAT?  ANOTHER ONE?
YOU SHOULDN'T DRINK SO MUCH,
YOU KNOW.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M FINE,
AND I'VE GOT
A LOT OF MONEY.
- WELL, IF YOU INSIST.
- ( meowing )
- HMM?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( meows )
- DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THOSE GUYS.
- HERE WE GO.
- AHH.
THANKS SO MUCH.
HEY, EVEN IF WE'RE
A LITTLE LATE,
IT'LL BE FINE.
NOW WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN ME?
HERE, HAVE SOME.
- ( meows, gulps )
MMM!
( meows )
- RYO-OHKI, THAT'S IT.
NOW YOU'RE GETTING
INTO THE SPIRIT.
ALL RIGHT THEN!
LET'S HIT IT.
- ( meows )
- YEAH!  YEAH!
OH YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH!
PARTY DOWN!
- ( meowing )
- WHOO-HOO!
- SHE COMES BACK,
SHE COMES BACK NOT.
SHE COMES BACK,
COMES BACK NOT.
- YOU ARE AWARE OF THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE THE CAUSE OF
THIS DELAY, ARE YOU NOT?
- SHE COMES BACK...
- LISTEN.
I DON'T WANT YOU IN THAT
ENGINE ROOM ANYMORE.
- ( stomach growls )
- KIYONE?
- MIHOSHI.
TELL ME YOU WERE
LISTENING TO ME!
- OH.
- HUH?
- WHAT NOW?
- WOW!
HERE, LOOK, KIYONE.
THIS FLOWER TELLS ME
RYOKO IS COMING BACK.
IT WON'T BE LONG.
LET'S TRY TO HANG IN THERE,
OKAY, KIYONE?
- MIHOSHI?
- I'M STARVING.
- MIHOSHI!
AAH!
MIHOSHI,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- RYOKO,
PLEASE COME BACK TO US SOON.
WE'RE STARVING.
- ( grunts )
- ( fanfare plays )
- ALL RIGHT!
HEY, SOMEBODY.
BRING ME SOME BIG BUCKETS.
- LARGE BUCKETS
COMING RIGHT UP.
- CONGRATULATIONS
TO THE LADY ON 327.
YOU JUST HIT THE JACKPOT!
WIN MORE COINS THAN
YOU CAN CARRY, EVERYBODY!
HERE'S OUR SPECIAL
LIMITED TIME OFFER.
DOUBLE ODDS!
DOUBLE ODDS ON
ALL SLOT MACHINES!
- ( giggles )
- ( meows )
- YO!
- HELLO, EVERYONE.
IT'S TIME FOR MORE
DELICIOUS DELECTABLE DELICACIES.
TODAY'S SHOW WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO COOK
THIS DISH.
IT LOOKS SO GOOD
AND SO MOUTHWATERING,
DOESN'T IT?
- ( all groan )
- I'M SO HUNGRY.
- YEAH.
- RYOKO,
WHERE CAN YOU BE?
- WOW!
I'M GONNA DIG IN.
MMM!
( gasps )
( sighs )
THIS PLACE DESERVES
THREE STARS.
I'LL TRY A FIVE STAR NEXT.
HMM.
BUT BEFORE I DO THAT,
I'D LIKE TO ORDER
FIVE JUMBO STEAKS,
AND HURRY!
- ( muffled meows )
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T GO ON LIKE THIS.
- WASHU, HANG IN THERE.
- YOU CAN DO IT, WASHU.
- Both: COME ON, WASHU.
YOU CAN DO IT, WASHU.
COME ON, WASHU.
- HEY, YOU GUYS TRY
FIXING IT, WHY DON'T YOU?
I'M TOO HUNGRY FOR THIS.
- WOW.
THIS LOOKS GREAT.
- ( muffled meows )
( meows )
- TAKE IT EASY.
LOOK HERE.
- ( meows )
- NOW YOU'RE HAPPY.
OKAY, BRING THEM IN!
- ( dings )
- ( clears throat )
( groans )
- AHH.
OHH.
WHAT A FEAST.
MY PRAYERS ARE ANSWERED.
( sighs )
THAT WAS JUST GREAT.
- ( meows )
- ( screams )
I WANT FOOD!
GIVE ME SOME FOOD!
- HEY, DAD!
GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF.
( grunts )
YOU'RE FLIPPING OUT,
DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WITH
THAT ORANGE PEEL, ANYWAY?
- IT'S BETTER THAN
DYING OF STARVATION
ON THIS STUPID SPACESHIP
IN THE MIDDLE OF SPACE.
- WOW. THIS RICE AND CURRY
IS DELICIOUS.
- HUH?
- ( chewing )
THIS IS GOOD.
HERE I SEE SOME HAMBURGER STEAK
AND HERE I SEE
SOME PASTA TOO.
FRIED SHRIMP, STEW, TEMPURA.
SO MUCH TO EAT!
( giggles )
- MIHOSHI...
- LOOK, KIYONE,
WE HAVE SO MUCH FOOD.
- AAH!
MIHOSHI,
STOP HALLUCINATING.
NOW, YOU ARE A GALAXY
POLICE DETECTIVE.
WILL YOU GET A GRIP, HUH?
- HUH?
- ( both sniff )
- Both: HUH?
( sniffs )
- Both: OH?
UHH?
( sniffs )
- HMM?
- ( all murmur )
- NOW ONE BITE FOR EACH,
ALL RIGHT?
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR WAITING.
- A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
AT A LUXURY HOTEL.
IT'S GREAT.
EATING FANCY FOOD.
- ( meows )
- HMM?
- ( meowing )
- WHAT IS IT?
- ( meows )
- OH, I FORGOT!
WELL, THEY CAN WAIT.
- ( meows )
- ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH ALREADY.
TIME TO GO BACK.
HERE. THAT SHOULD
BE ENOUGH, I THINK.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
MA'AM.
- HMM?
UHH...
( gasps )
( whimpers )
- ( crowd cheering )
- AROUND THE STRETCH THEY COME.
IS IN THE LEAD
FOLLOWED CLOSELY BY...
- COME ON! LET'S GO!
RUN, LET'S GO!
- GO!
- ALL RIGHT. GO! GO!
COME ON.
- AND COMING UP
FAR FROM THE OUTSIDE,
CROSSING THE FINISH LINE
IS...
- ( cheering )
- ONE MINUTE AND 29 SECONDS.
- OH NO.
I LOST.
I REALLY CANNOT
BELIEVE THIS.
( sighs )
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
- ( meows )
- OH, I KNOW.
OH, YES.
I WONDER HOW
THOSE GUYS ARE DOING ALSO.
TENCHI.
( gasps )
BANK OF JURAI, HUH?
UH...
AHH.
- RYOKO...
- WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
TRUSTED RYOKO.
- WHAT NOW, TENCHI?
- HEY NOW,
DON'T YOU WORRY.
SHE'LL BE HERE SOON.
JUST TRUST ME.
- BUT TENCHI...
- IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, SASAMI,
BACK HOME ON EARTH
WE HAVE A FABLE.
IT IS A TALE
OF TWO FRIENDS,
AND THE STORY'S MORAL
IS THAT IF YOU TRUST SOMEONE,
YEAH, IF YOU TRUST SOMEONE,
YOUR FAITH WILL
BE REWARDED.
- YEAH, BUT RYOKO IS
A SPACE PIRATE AND ALL.
- UH...
- ( repeated )
UH-HUH. UH-HUH.
- ( chuckles )
THIS SHOULD BE MORE THAN
ENOUGH MONEY, I THINK.
( giggles )
- Both: HUH?!
- ( siren blares )
- OKAY.
HERE THEY ARE.
RYO-OHKI!
- ( meows )
- ( crowd gasps )
- SHE'S ON THE ROOF.
- OH!
- HMM.
- LOOK OUT.
- ( gasps )
- ( shudders )
IT'S THE SPACE PIRATE.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- THE REPAIRS ARE
FINISHED FINALLY.
( sighs )
- WASHU?
- CAN WE GO NOW?
CAN WE GO TO A PLANET WHERE WE
CAN GET SOMETHING TO EAT NOW,
PLEASE?
- BUT RYOKO ISN'T
HERE YET.
- LET'S JUST FORGET ABOUT
THAT TRAITOR, ALL RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
LOOK, AYEKA.
- Both: HUH?
- HI, GUYS. I'M BACK.
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK YOU FOR
WAITING FOR ME SO PATIENTLY.
- ( meows )
- ( all gasp )
- TENCHI, YOU MISSED ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
AYEKA,
GET ME SOME TEA.
- WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
AND WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG,
RYOKO?
- HERE.
- AHH.
MMM.
- I'M SORRY.
EVERYTHING TOOK A LITTLE
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
- SEE?
MY FLOWER TOLD ME
THE TRUTH.
I WAS RIGHT, KIYONE.
- YEAH, YOU MUST HAVE
GOTTEN SIDETRACKED.
- ( chuckles )
PLEASE DON'T CONCERN YOURSELF
WITH THE MINOR DETAILS.
- YOU WERE SO RIGHT,
TENCHI.
OUR TRUST WAS
TRULY REWARDED.
- YEP.  THAT'S RIGHT.
- COME ON.
LET'S FIX SOMETHING TO EAT.
- YEAH.
LET'S HAVE A FEAT.
- YAY!
- ALL RIGHT!
- All: WHOA!
- WHAT'S GOING ON THIS TIME?
- ( all scream )
- All: HUH?
- IT'S ALL MONEY!
- UH...
WITH THIS MUCH MONEY,
WE CAN GO TO ANY
RESTAURANTS WE WANT.
I GUARANTEE YOU.
- RYOKO!
YOU DIDN'T, DID YOU?
- THE BANK I ROBBED
WAS THE BANK OF JURAI,
SO THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- THE BANK OF JURAI?!
THE MONEY IN
THE BANK OF JURAI
IS MY PEOPLE'S MONEY.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND
ANYTHING, RYOKO?
- ( all scream )
- ( sighs )
- WE'RE EVEN INVOLVED
IN A BANK ROBBERY.
- TENCHI?
OUR TRUST WAS NOT REWARDED.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( stomach growls )
- I'M SO HUNGRY.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- ( stomach growls )
- All: WE ARE SO STARVING.
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- WE WANDER INTO
THE SARGASSO SEA IN SPACE
AND ENCOUNTER A GHOST SHIP.
SASAMI DISAPPEARS
WHEN A MYSTERIOUS GIRL
INVITES HER TO THE SHIP.
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- WE MUST RESCUE SASAMI!
- YOU MEAN, GO INTO
THAT GHOST SHIP?
- OF COURSE.
WHERE ELSE?
- WELL, GOOD LUCK.
- YOU'RE COMING WITH US,
MIHOSHI.
- OH, NO.
- A FRIENDSHIP IS FORMED
BETWEEN SASAMI
AND THE GHOST GIRL.
COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR A GHOST,"
A STORY OF THE SECRET TIME
YOUNG GIRLS CHERISH FOREVER.
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY SWEET.