- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- ( alarm sounds, speaks )
- ( groaning )
( yawning )
- MIHOSHI, MY PARTNER...
IT'S ALREADY BEEN A MONTH
SINCE SHE DIED.
- ( rings )
- YOU WERE ALWAYS
SUCH A BURDEN TO ME.
BUT NOW,
I'LL NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
AND THAT KNOWLEDGE...
MAKES ME SO HAPPY!
MAY YOUR SOUL REST IN PEACE,
MIHOSHI.
WHAT?!  MIHOSHI'S ALIVE?
- NOW ALL I SAID IS
IT'S POSSIBLE SHE'S STILL ALIVE.
- BUT I THOUGHT MIHOSHI
HAD DIED IN THE LINE OF DUTY,
WHILE PURSUING
THE WANTED CRIMINAL, RYOKO.
- WELL, THAT POST
IN THE SOLAR SYSTEM
HAS BEEN VACANT
FOR QUITE SOME TIME,
SO THEY HAVEN'T REALLY
FOLLOWED UP
THE CASE YET, YOU SEE.
- ( groans )
- BUT DETECTIVE KIYONE,
HERE'S THE THING:
SINCE YOU WERE DETECTIVE
FIRST CLASS MIHOSHI'S PARTNER,
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO UNDERTAKE
A SEARCH FOR HER IMMEDIATELY.
THAT'S AN ORDER.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
AND HERE, I THOUGHT MY NIGHTMARE
WAS OVER, ONCE AND FOR ALL.
( sobbing )
OH, GOD.
PLEASE PLEASE DON'T LET
MIHOSHI BE ALIVE.
- YO!
- MM, IT FEELS SO NICE.
JUST ANOTHER QUIET DAY.
( yawns )
FOR SOME REASON
THIS PEACEFUL ATMOSPHERE
MAKES ME SLEEPY.
- THANKS FOR WAITING. AND IT'S
JUST THE WAY YOU WANTED IT.
- ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE READY FOR THIS.
- ( giggles )
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON NOW?
- WE'VE GOT A NEW BATH NOW.
RIGHT?
- WHAT DO MEAN? THERE ALREADY
WAS A BATHROOM THERE.
- WELL, WE ASKED WASHU TO
REMODEL THE INTERIOR
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
- OH, WELL THEN,
IS WASHU GOOD AT
CONSTRUCTION AS WELL?
- BUT YOU GUYS SHOULD
HAVE ASKED IF IT'S OKAY
TO CHANGE THE BATHROOM.
- HUH?  AAH!
- AAH!
- OOH, THIS LOOKS PRETTY COOL.
- ( others cheer )
- WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THIS?
- I CONNECTED THE INSIDE
OF THE BATHROOM
TO A DIFFERENT DIMENSION.
LIKE WHEN I CREATED
MY RESEARCH LAB
IN THE STORAGE UNIT.
SAME TECHNIQUE.
- ENOUGH WITH CREATING DIFFERENT
DIMENSIONS ALL OVER THE HOUSE.
- TENCHI, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SO NARROW-MINDED.
THE BATH WILL SERVE AS A WAY
OF BRINGING OUR WHOLE
GROUP CLOSER TOGETHER.
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
I THINK WE SHOULD REALLY GET
CLOSE TO EACH OTHER RIGHT NOW.
- BUT THIS ONE
IS THE LADIES' BATH.
- YOU TWO SHOULD GO
TO THE MEN'S BATH.
HEE.
- ( guys stammering )
- IT'S RIGHT THIS WAY.
THERE!
- MEN'S BATH?
BUT THERE'S ONLY ONE
BATHROOM HERE, RIGHT?
- HUH?
- UGH.
- WELL THEN,
WE SHOULD GO IN THERE.
( giggles )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?!
- HEY, ALL I'M SAYING IS
CLOSENESS IN THE FAMILY
IS A GOOD THING,
AND-- AND SO IS A GOOD BATH.
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU THINKING?!
- ( both grunting )
- LET GO OF MY SHIRT.
- I'M NOT LETTING GO.
- COME ON, WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON?
- THOSE GIRLS ARE INSIDE THERE.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
I'M PEEPING.
- UH-HUH, I KNEW IT.
YOU JUST WANNA PEEP, DON'T YOU?
- LET ME GO!
I'M COMING IN!
HUH?
- WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S JUST THE SAME OLD BATHROOM.
- NOW THIS IS REALLY STRANGE.
- OH, HI, I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU THIS.
WHEN THE DOOR IS OPENED
BY A MAN,
IT DOESN'T LEAD
TO ANOTHER DIMENSION.
- I WOULDN'T MIND
BATHING WITH YOU.
SO DON'T YOU WANNA GO
INSIDE WITH ME?
WELL?  WHAT DO YOU SAY,
TENCHI?
- GET BACK IN HERE!
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- OUCH!
- ( girls arguing indistinctly )
- ( piano music playing )
- THE HOUSE MUST BE
JUST AHEAD OF ME.
THAT'S WHAT
THE COORDINATES SAY.
THAT MUST BE IT.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH DAD.
EW.
- YOU THERE, EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- UH, HELLO. ( chuckles )
I WANNA ASK YOU SOMETHING.
- WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
HMM?
- HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
THIS WOMAN BEFORE?
- HUH?
SURE, I KNOW HER.
- WHAT?!
DO YOU KNOW WHERE SHE IS NOW?!
TELL ME!  TELL ME!
- OKAY, SHE'S RIGHT OVER THERE.
- HUH?
- ( moaning, groaning )
- ( gasps )
THAT'S IT--
MY ALL TOO BRIEF
PEACEFUL MOMENTS
ARE ALL OVER NOW.
- ( squeaking )
- HEY, COME HERE!
WE'RE TRYING TO DRY YOU OFF!
- OH, YES,
THAT WAS A NICE BATH.
- YES, THAT CERTAINLY WAS.
- LET'S SAY WE TAKE
ANOTHER ONE LATER.
- EXCELLENT IDEA.
- Mihoshi: WOW, KIYONE,
I MISSED YOU!
- All: HUH?
- IT'S BEEN SO MANY DAYS,
BUT I KNEW YOU'D COME FOR ME.
HOW MANY DAYS
HAS IT BEEN ANYWAY?
DID YOU KNOW I COULDN'T
SLEEP AT NIGHT,
BECAUSE I MISSED YOU SO MUCH?
- SO, YOU SLEEP
DURING THE DAYTIME?
- WELL WELL,
YOU MUST BE TIRED.
YOU'VE COME ALL THIS WAY
TO FIND YOUR PARTNER MIHOSHI.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
TERRIBLY WORRIED ABOUT HER.
- OH, TO SEE MIHOSHI ALIVE
AND WELL MAKES ME SO VERY MAD.
I-- I  MEAN, SO VERY GLAD.
( nervous chuckle )
- WE HAVE A SPECIAL CHEMISTRY
TOGETHER, SHE AND I.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?  WE WERE
SO CONFIDENT TOGETHER, REALLY!
- GOOD FRIENDSHIPS
BETWEEN TWO WOMEN
ARE A BEAUTIFUL THING
INDEED.
- ( fake laughter )
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN TAKING
VERY GOOD CARE OF MIHOSHI HERE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
EVERYONE HERE IS SO NICE.
OH, LET ME INTRODUCE THEM
TO YOU!
- ( gasps )
- THIS IS TENCHI MASAKI.
- WE'VE MET, KINDA.
- AND THIS IS HIS FATHER,
NOBUYUKI.
- HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
- OH...
- AND THAT'S THE GRANDFATHER,
KATSUHITO.
- IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- KIYONE, KIYONE!
THIS IS THE SPACE PIRATE,
RYOKO.
- HI, HOW YOU DOIN'?
- ( gasps )
NOW WHAT IN THE UNIVERSE IS THIS
MOST WANTED CRIMINAL DOING HERE?
- OH, WELL, IT JUST KINDA
SEEMS NATURAL. ( chuckles )
- KINDA NATURAL?
- MOVE ON WITH
THE INTRODUCTIONS, WILL YOU?
- I THINK I WILL.
NEXT TO RYOKO
IS AYEKA
FROM THE PLANET JURAI.
- HELLO.
HOW DO YOU DO?
- ( gasps loudly )
YOU MEAN THE PRINCESS AYEKA
WHO'S BEEN MISSING?
- AND NEXT TO HER
IS SASAMI.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- PRINCESS SASAMI?
HOW DID THE TWO OF THEM
END UP HERE?
- AND THIS IS THE GENIUS
SCIENTIST WASHU, OF COURSE.
- AAH... OW!
- ( thuds )
- YOU MEAN TO TELL ME SHE'S
THAT LEGENDARY MAD SCIENTIST?
- MM-HMM!
- DOES SHE HAVE TO MAKE SUCH
A BIG DEAL OUT OF EVERYTHING?
- I HAVE TO SAY, I THINK
HER REACTION IS QUITE NORMAL.
- WHAT?  WHAT IS THIS ALL?
HOW DID ALL THESE PEOPLE
COME TO MEET ONE ANOTHER?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- ALL I CAN SAY IS, WELL,
JUST THINGS JUST SEEM TO
DEVELOP THIS WAY.
- ( all gasp )
- ( grunts )
- SPACE PIRATE RYOKO, I HEREBY
PLACE YOU UNDER ARREST.
- I SEE, YOU'RE NOT KIDDING,
ARE YOU?
- YO!
YO!
- BOY, THIS IS REALLY YUMMY.
- THE RATIO BETWEEN THE POTATOES
AND THE GROUND MEAT
IS JUST PERFECT.
THIS COULD STAND UP UNDER
ANY SCIENTIFIC ANALYSIS.
- AND SASAMI COOKED ALL THIS
FINE FOOD, IS THAT RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT, YOU REALLY ARE
A GREAT COOK, SASAMI.
- ( giggles )
- HARD TO BELIEVE SASAMI
IS RELATED TO AYEKA.
- THAT IS NONE OF YOUR CONCERN.
- HERE, KIYONE.
HAVE SOME MORE
IF YOU'RE STILL HUNGRY.
- OH, WOW.
THANKS, I AM.
- YOU ARE HUNGRY.
YOU EAT LIKE A HORSE, KIYONE.
YOU KNOW THAT?
- ( chuckles )
- THE ONE WHO EATS
LIKE A HORSE IS YOU.
- YEAH, I GUESS I AM
THAT KIND OF WAY.
( giggles )
- ( all laughing )
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE SCENE
I WAS JUST IN?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE
EATING LUNCH WITH THESE PEOPLE?
- WELL, FOR ONE THING,
IT'S LUNCHTIME.
WE CAN'T HELP THAT.
- MIHOSHI!
- BOY, SHE REALLY IS SERIOUS.
- NOW DON'T MAKE IT DIFFICULT!
- HOLD ON A MINUTE.
I'M RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF EATING HERE.
- COME ON, MIHOSHI.
- WAIT.
OKAY OKAY, SO RYOKO
IS A VICIOUS PIRATE.
ONE OF THE WORST CRIMINALS EVER,
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
IN HER BEHALF, I HAVE TO
SAY THAT SHE DID GIVE ME
THE BIGGER RICE CAKE...
- ( groaning )
- ...THE OTHER DAY, REALLY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- MIHOSHI, YOU'VE GOT TO THINK
BEFORE YOU TALK.
- ( sighs )
- AND JUST WHAT SIDE ARE
YOU ON, ANYWAY?
- KIYONE, MAY I SAY, YOU ARE
TRULY THE PARAGON OF DETECTIVES.
I WOULD LIKE TO ASSIST YOU
IN ARRESTING THIS MOST
VICIOUS PIRATE
AND WANTED CRIMINAL.
- WHY, YOU LITTLE TRAITOR!
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
RYOKO?
I NEVER WAS ON YOUR SIDE
TO BEGIN WITH.
YOU KNOW THAT, SILLY.
- AYEKA, YOU THINK
YOU'RE GONNA BE RID OF ME
ONCE I'M ARRESTED,
IS THAT IT, HUH?
- HUH?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, REALLY.
I AM JUST TRYING
TO COOPERATE WITH THE POLICE.
- YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET YOUR WAY.
MIHOSHI, SOME TEA.
- UH-HUH.
- WOULD YOU LOOK AT YOU?
YOU CALL YOURSELF A DETECTIVE?
- SORRY, I'M JUST POLITE.
- WAIT RIGHT HERE.
( munches loudly )
I'LL BE DONE WITH HER
IN A MINUTE.
- THAT'S IT, GIRLS,
STEP OUTSIDE.
- ( growls )
- AAH!
( grunts )
- ( laughs )
- ( moaning )
- THAT'S SOMETHING.
- ( yells )
- AAH...
- MIHOSHI, WHY DON'T YOU
USE THAT?
- ALL RIGHT.
I AM A SPACE DETECTIVE.
FIGHTING TO THE DEATH
IS WHAT I DO.
IT'S WHAT I AM.
WHOA!
WH-- WH-- WHOA!
OH, BOY!  OH, BOY!
( screaming )
- OH, BOY.
- WELL, THAT'S MIHOSHI FOR YOU.
- ( screaming )
- I GOTTA TELL YOU SOMETHING,
YOUR PARTNER
REALLY CRACKS ME UP.
- I'M NOT THAT EASY.
( straining grunt )
- PRETTY GOOD.
- HMM.
- BUT NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
( shouts )
THIS FIGHT IS MINE!  HA!
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
A MAGICAL FORCE FIELD?
- ( cackles )
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
HOLD RYOKO TIGHT...
AND DO NOT LET HER GET AWAY.
- Both:
YES, MA'AM.
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE...
- WE HAVE TO OBEY
PRINCESS AYEKA'S ORDERS.
- WE'RE SORRY ABOUT THIS.
- ( grunts )
DAMN!
- ( laughs )
I THINK I GOT YOU NOW.
- FINALLY THE NOTORIOUS
CRIMINAL GOES TO JAIL, HUH?
TOUGH BREAK, RYOKO.
- RYOKO, I GUESS I'LL VISIT YOU
IN JAIL, I PROMISE.
- AND I'LL WRITE TO YOU.
- HEY, I'M STILL HERE.
STOP TALKING LIKE TH--
( grunts )
- YOU TAKE IT FROM HERE.
- OKAY.
YOU ARE CHARGED
UNDER GALAXY POLICE LAW
ITEM 2546,
AMENDMENT NINE-SEVEN-THREE.
THE SUSPECT HAS
THE RIGHT TO REMAIN SILENT
REGARDING ISSUES
TO YOUR DISADVANTAGE.
YOU ALSO HAVE THE RIGHT
TO AN ATTORNEY.
- ( distant screeching )
- HUH?
- ( screeching )
- All: HUH?
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- WHAT?
- ( all screaming )
- EVERYTHING WAS GOING
SO SMOOTHLY...
UNTIL THEY MADE
MIHOSHI MY PARTNER,
AND SINCE THEN,
IT'S BEEN A NIGHTMARE.
- I KNOW.  WELL...
HERE, HAVE SOME SAKE.
MM.
- ( exhales )
( groans )
- OH!
- THEN WE WERE DEMOTED
AND ASSIGNED TO A REMOTE SITE,
LOSING ALL THE CHANCE
OF PROMOTION TO THE HIGHER RANKS
AT HEADQUARTERS.
( exhales deeply )
ALL OF THAT
WAS MIHOSHI'S FAULT!
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF HER!
( burbling )
- ( giggles softly )
UM, KIYONE?
- AS PER YOUR REQUEST,
I CONTACTED
THE PLANET JURAI AND TOLD THEM
THAT YOU WERE ON VACATION.
DID I SAY THE RIGHT THING,
PRINCESS?
- YES, THANK YOU, KIYONE.
I THINK WE NEED A BREAK
IN SOME REMOTE PLACE LIKE THIS.
DON'T YOU THINK, SASAMI?
- MM-HMM.
- WELL THEN, WE'LL PREPARE
FOR TAKEOFF.
- EVERYBODY, THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING.
I WILL NEVER FORGET YOU ALL.
NEVER.
- OH, THAT'S SO SWEET,
AND I WILL ALWAYS REMEMBER YOU,
MIHOSHI.
- HMM?
- SO LONG, MIHOSHI.
- I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO VISIT YOU OR ANYTHING,
BUT TAKE CARE.
- ( softly sobbing )
- HERE.
- HUH?
- SOME RICE BALLS.
HAVE SOME WHEN YOU'RE HUNGRY
ON THE WAY BACK HOME.
HERE, TAKE THEM WITH YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
EVERYBODY, BYE NOW.
- GOODBYE.
- BYE-BYE!
- All: BYE!
- BYE, MIHOSHI!
- KEEP IN TOUCH.
- I'LL REMEMBER YOU!
BYE!
- GOOD-BYE.
- SO, ARE YOU READY
TO GO HOME?
- YES.
- ( rapid beeping )
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE RECEIVING
AN ULTRA-SPACE COMMUNICATION.
AH, SECTION CHIEF.
AS I REPORTED,
I'VE LOCATED DETECTIVE MIHOSHI,
AND WE ARE HEADING BACK
IMMEDIATELY.
- OH, YOU DON'T NEED TO DO THAT.
- WHAT?
- YOU HAVE JUST RECEIVED
AN APPOINTMENT
FROM THE CHIEF OF
THE GALAXY POLICE.
LISTEN.
- Both: HUH?
- "AS OF TODAY, MIHOSHI
AND KIYONE ARE ASSIGNED TO EARTH
AS OFFICERS IN CHARGE
OF THE SOLAR SYSTEM AREA."
THAT'S ALL.
- AAH!
NO, THIS CAN'T BE TRUE!
- THE PERSONNEL SECTION CHIEF
WAS VERY HAPPY WE FOUND
QUALIFIED OFFICERS.
KEEP UP YOUR GOOD WORK.
- WOW.  THIS IS GREAT!
I AM SO HAPPY.
NOW WE CAN STAY ON EARTH.
AREN'T YOU HAPPY, KIYONE?
WE GET TO
WORK CLOSELY TOGETHER.
HA HA!
WE'RE STATIONED ON EARTH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS IS GONNA BE THE BEST EVER.
THE BEST!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT
ON EARTH.
- IT'S OVER.
- ( Mihoshi continues )
- THIS IS IT.
MY CAREER IS DOWN THE TOILET.
OH...
( sighs )
- ON EARTH, ON EARTH!
OH, YES YES YES!
- ( music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Tenchi: IN OUR NEXT EPISODE,
KIYONE AND MIHOSHI
SETTLE DOWN AS ROOMMATES
IN A TINY STUDIO APARTMENT
IN AN OLD BUILDING
FACING WEST.
- WE'LL BE FRIED
IN THIS AFTERNOON'S SUN.
- Tenchi: EVEN THOUGH
THE RENT THEY SHARE
IS AS LOW AS IT COULD BE,
THEY NOW HAVE TO WORK
DAY AND NIGHT
ON PART-TIME JOBS TO KEEP UP
WITH THE HIGH COST OF
LIVING ON EARTH.
AND WHENEVER THEY RECEIVE
A DUTY CALL,
FLY OUT TO SPACE
IN THE AGAMI.
HANG ON, RESIDENT OFFICERS
OF THE SOLAR SYSTEM,
COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR RESIDENT OFFICERS."
- Kiyone:
IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY PATHETIC.