- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WE NOW PRESENT FOR YOU
A SPECIAL TENCHI MUYO EVENT.
- THE DIMENSIONAL
CAUSE-AND-EFFECT CONTROLLER--
A GREAT INVENTION
BY PROFESSOR WASHU--
IS A DEVICE THAT CONTROLS
THE SEQUENCE OF TIME AND SPACE.
IT CAN CHANGE THE WORLD
IN ANY WAY THAT YOU WANT.
BUT WHEN THIS DEVICE
IS DRIVEN OUT OF CONTROL,
WELL...
- TENCHI AND COMPANY
HAVE BEEN THROWN
INTO AND BEYOND
THEIR TIME AND SPACE
TO WANDER ABOUT
CHAOTIC WORLDS.
- WE'RE CERTAIN
YOU'RE WONDERING
JUST WHAT KIND OF WORLD
AWAITS US THIS TIME.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO PAY ADMISSION
UNTIL YOU FINISH
WATCHING THIS SHOW.
- YO!
- ( ship's horn blows )
- ( motor whirrs )
- HOW MANY YEARS HAVE PASSED
SINCE I GAVE UP EVERYTHING
AS A POLICE DETECTIVE
AND LEFT ON THIS
ENDLESS JOURNEY?
I'D BE LYING IF I SAID
I HAD NO REGRETS.
BUT I HAD NO OTHER CHOICE
IN ORDER TO ESCAPE
FROM THAT NIGHTMARE,
THE DAYS AFTER ALL HOPES
FOR A PROMOTION
AND MY CAREER
HAD BEEN COMPLETE.
I WANDERED FAR
AND FINALLY ARRIVED
AT THIS PORT TOWN
AT THE END OF THE WORLD.
BUT SOMEHOW, I FEEL
THIS STRANGE TOWN HAS
IN SOME WAY
FILLED MY WOUNDS.
- HELLO, THERE.
WHAT'LL YOU HAVE, HUH?
- UH, NORTH COUNTRY NOODLES.
- ALL RIGHT, ONE
NORTH COUNTRY NOODLES IT IS.
- ARE YOU TRAVELLING ALONE?
- WELL, SORT OF.
- OH HOW NICE
TO BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
BUT WHY IN THIS LITTLE TOWN?
BECAUSE THERE IS REALLY NOTHING
TO SEE AROUND HERE, YOU KNOW?
- WELL--
- MAYBE YOU HAVE SOME SECRET
STORY TO TELL US, HUH?
- AYEKA, NOW, YOU
SHOULDN'T BE PRYING.
- OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- I WOULDN'T BE
SURPRISED IF YOU DID.
I WOULD NEVER HAVE
COME TO THIS TOWN
IF I HADN'T HAD A STORY MYSELF.
- AH, WELL,
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
- HA, HERE YOU ARE AGAIN.
AYEKA, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
LOITERING HERE LIKE THIS.
WE HAVE OUR OWN DINER TO OPEN,
YOU KNOW.
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
- YEAH, IT'S HARD ON YOU,
ISN'T IT, SASAMI?
- ( giggles )
- HERE YOU ARE,
NORTH COUNTRY NOODLES.
- WOW.
( blows lightly )
( slurps )
DELICIOUS.
- SO TELL ME, ARE YOU PLANNING
ON STAYING IN TOWN FOR A WHILE?
- I GUESS.  IT LOOKS LIKE
A NICE PLACE TO LIVE.
- YEAH, IT'S A VERY NICE TOWN.
- I WONDER,
DO YOU THINK I COULD GET SOME
KIND OF JOB AROUND HERE?
- OH, I SEE.
SO YOU ARE LOOKING FOR A JOB.
- YOU SHOULD COME
WORK AT OUR PLACE.
- HUH?
- OH YES, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
YOU KNOW WE RUN A TAVERN
NOT FAR FROM HERE.
IT'S A SMALL PLACE FOR LOCAL
FISHERMEN TO EAT AND DRINK IN.
BUT WE CERTAINLY
COULD USE THE HELP.
- THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
- YEAH, COME ON. COME
WORK WITH US.
- WELL, IF IT'S NOT AN
IMPOSITION, I'D BE GLAD TO.
- YAY!
- WELL THEN, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO COME WITH US NOW?
- ( drunken laughing )
- THERE YOU GO.
GO ON.
DRINK IT UP, YOUNG FELLA.
YOU GO ON AHEAD NOW.
- GO, BABY, GO.
- OKAY.
( gulping )
AAH.
- HA HA, NICELY DONE.
- ( cheering )
- HEY, MORE SAKE.
- RIGHT.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
HERE YOU ARE.
- Ryoko: OH GOODIE,
MORE SAKE.
- I'D LIKE SOME GRILLED FISH
TOO, KIYONE.
- PLEASE? THANKS.
- OKAY.
ONE ORDER, GRILLED FISH.
- Both: RIGHT.
- HOW ARE YOU DOING?
GETTING SETTLED ALL RIGHT?
- THANK YOU.  YES.
- I HEARD YOU USED TO
BE A POLICE DETECTIVE.
- OH, WERE YOU REALLY?
- YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT, OLD MAN?
( gulping )
AAH.
- IT'S A LONG TIME AGO,
A LONG TIME.
- WELL, I SURE AM GLAD TO
HAVE A SWEETHEART LIKE YOU
WITH US NOW, KIYONE.
- THANKS.
- YES, BUT I'M THE SWEETHEART
OF TENCHI.
- HEY! WAIT A MINUTE!
WHO DID YOU SAY WAS
TENCHI'S SWEETHEART?
- ME, HERE.
THAT'S ME.
- WHAT YOU ARE IS RUDE,
AND IMPERTINENT,
AND A DRUNKARD.
- HUH?!
HOW DARE YOU SAY SUCH
A THING TO YOUR CUSTOMER.
- WHAT KIND OF A CUSTOMER
ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
PAY UP YOUR TAB FIRST
AND THEN SAY WHAT YOU LIKE.
- TENCHI,
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK AYEKA'S
ENVIOUS OF US.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
- ( growling )
- ( laughing )
- STOP IT, SIS, STOP IT.
- I'LL SHOW YOU!
- ( laughing )
- TAKE THAT!
TAKE THAT!
- OH, HEY!
GIVE ME THAT PAN.
- OOH, I CAN'T STAND IT.
- ( Kiyone's thoughts ):
A FUN PLACE WITH FUN PEOPLE.
- ( arguing continues )
- ( Kiyone's thoughts ):
FOR SO MANY YEARS,
MY HEART HAS BEEN FROZEN.
- GOOD MORNING.
- THESE PEOPLE IN THIS TOWN
ARE SO KIND
- I'M LEAVING FOR SCHOOL.
- THAT I CAN FEEL MY HEART
STARTING TO THAW...
- GOOD MORNING.
- SLOWLY BUT SURELY,
CUDDLED IN THE WARMTH
OF THEIR HEARTS.
- MISS KIYONE.
- HI, SASAMI.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ARE YOU BACK
FROM SCHOOL ALREADY?
- YEAH.
YOU'VE BEEN WATCHING THE OCEAN
AGAIN, MISS KIYONE?
- YES.
- YOU LIKE THE OCEAN?
- I'VE GROWN TO LIKE IT.
AND SINCE I CAME HERE--
IT'S TIME TO GO
OPEN THE TAVERN.
- RIGHT.
( giggles )
- I'LL WORK HARD.
- LET'S GO.  COME ON.
- ( giggles )
- ( laughing )
- Nobuyuki: HEY, OKAY!
- Ryoko: COME ON, FOLKS.
BRING US MORE SAKE.
MORE, MORE.
MORE!
- AND MORE AND MORE.
HOW DARE YOU!
YOU HAVEN'T PAID A CENT.
- ( Kiyone's thoughts ):
A PEACEFUL LIFE
IN A SMALL TOWN--
I DON'T HAVE TO LOOK BACK
TO THE PAST ANYMORE.
YES, THE NIGHTMARE IS OVER
NEVER TO RETURN.
- OH, WELCOME TO--
( gasps )
- KIYONE.
- ( gasps )
- OH, I LOOKED
EVERYWHERE, KIYONE.
- MI-- MI-- MIHOSHI?
- SOMEONE TOLD ME
THAT THEY SAW YOU HERE.
- OH, WHEN I HEARD THAT,
I RUSHED HERE AS
FAST AS I COULD.
- ( gasping )
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME, YOU KNOW.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING EVER SINCE
YOU DISAPPEARED, KIYONE.
( crying )
I MISSED YOU, KIYONE.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH.
- All: OH.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID YOU DISAPPEAR
ALL OF A SUDDEN, KIYONE?
OH, I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
OH, I HAVE NEWS FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, I WAS APPOINTED
TO THE TOP POSITION
AT THE OKAYAMA POLICE.
- ( gasps )
- LET'S GO HOME NOW
AND WE'LL FIGHT CRIME TOGETHER
JUST LIKE BACK IN
THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
COME ON, KIYONE.
- JUST A MINUTE, PLEASE.
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
BUT I'D LIKE YOU TO KNOW
THAT MISS KIYONE
IS WORKING FOR US
AT THIS PLACE NOW.
- HUH?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
MISS KIYONE'S LIKE A MEMBER
OF OUR FAMILY NOW.
- OH, REALLY?
IS THAT RIGHT?
- AH, YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- WELL, I GUESS I'LL JUST
WORK HERE TOO THEN,
TOGETHER WITH HER.
THAT'S RIGHT, BECAUSE
WE TWO ARE PARTNERS FOREVER.
( echoes ) WE TWO ARE
PARTNERS FOREVER.
- WE TWO ARE PARTNERS FOREVER.
- ( screams )
- OH NO, WAIT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, KIYONE?
KIYONE!
- WHEW.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN EVEN HARDER JOB
THAN I EXPECTED.
- ( train whistles )
- ( Kiyone's thoughts ): MY
PEACEFUL LIFE IN THE PORT TOWN,
IT TURNED OUT TO BE
A MOMENTARY DREAM.
WHEN WILL I BE RELEASED
FROM THIS NIGHTMARE?
( sighs ) THIS NIGHTMARE
NAMED MIHOSHI.
- CANCEL.
THERE WE GO.
- ( train whistles )
- ( sighs )
- GOOD MORNING,
STUDENT COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN.
- OH, GOOD MORNING.
- ( scoffs )
- HOW UNUSUAL FOR YOU,
MISS RYOKO,
NOT TO BE LATE
FOR SCHOOL TODAY.
- OH MAN, WHAT I LOUSY WAY
OF STARTING A DAY.
I KNEW WHEN I WOKE UP,
IT WAS GONNA BE A BAD ONE.
- ( both growl )
- GIRLS, GOOD MORNING.
- Both: OH, HI.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, TENCHI.
HMM?
HMPH.
- HUH?
- ( school bell rings )
- YO!
YO!
-  ( bell rings )
- OH NO.
( pants )
( panting )
UH, I'M LATE.
LATE!
AH!
OH NO.
LATE!
- WELL, NOW.
- ( clattering )
- HUH?
- OWW, THAT HURTS.
- YOU'RE LATE AGAIN, MIHOSHI.
- I'M SORRY, MISS KIYONE.
- REALLY, MIHOSHI, WHAT KIND
OF TEACHER DO YOU EXPECT TO BE
WHEN YOU'RE LATE FOR SCHOOL
EVERY DAY?
I'M SO EXASPERATED,
I CAN'T EVEN TALK ABOUT IT.
- OH, PLEASE,
DON'T BE THAT WAY.
DON'T ABANDON ME,
MISS KIYONE, PLEASE.
- I WOULD HAVE ABANDONED YOU
A LONG TIME AGO
IF I COULD HAVE.
- ( bell rings )
- PLEASE, PLEASE.
- OH NO.
OF COURSE MY CLASS
IS STARTING.
- OOPS, MINE TOO.
( yawns )
WELL, NEXT IS
UJI SHUI'S STORY VOLUME FOUR.
IN THIS STORY ABOUT THE DEMON
AT RASHOMON,
THE DEMON AND A WARRIOR
CREATE A TRIANGLE RELATIONSHIP
WITH A PRINCESS.
AND THEN THE MOST UN-HONORABLE
THINGS START TO HAPPEN.
( thoughts ): I SHOULDN'T
BE DOZING OFF LIKE THIS.
NO, NOT ME, THE RESPECTABLE
CHAIRMAMN OF THE STUDENT BODY
WHO SHOULD BE THE ROLE MODEL FOR
EVERY STUDENT IN THIS SCHOOL.
BUT THEN THIS CLASS MAKES ME
SO DEMONICALLY SLEEPY.
- ( snickering )
- HUH?
HOW COULD SHE BE AWAKE?
SHE MUST BE EATING
OR SOMETHING.
- THIS IS MY FAVORITE CLASS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, RYOKO?!
- HUH, WELL, I'M HAVING
MY EARLY LUNCH.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
AND SINCE WHEN DOES
A HIGH SCHOOL GIRL'S
EARLY LUNCH INCLUDE SAKE, HUH?
- WELL, SINCE TODAY, I GUESS.
( laughs )
- ( grumbles )
I JUST CANNOT BELIEVE YOU!
- ( mutters sleepily )
- IT'S SO DISRESPECTFUL!
- WHAT?
- YOU ARE RUDE!
- HEY, YOU TWO GIRLS, THERE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE QUIET
OR I'M GONNA GET ANGRY, I GUESS.
- YES, GO ON. SAY SOMETHING
TO HER, MISS MIHOSHI.
- ( pants ) MISS RYOKO!
- YOU WANT SOME TOO? HERE.
- OH, GREAT, THANKS.
- MISS MIHOSHI!
- ( gasps ) MISS RYOKO,
YOU MAY NOT DRINK SAKE IN CLASS,
YOU KNOW?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SEE, IF YOU WANT TO DRINK SAKE,
WAIT TILL YOU GO HOME
AND HAVE SOME WITH YOUR DINNER.
- THAT'S NOT RIGHT!
- HEY, NOW, NO NEED TO BE
SO UPTIGHT, MISS.
JUST HAVE A SIP AS A TOKEN
OF OUR FRIENDSHIP.
- UH, OKAY.
THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU, RYOKO.
- JUST WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU TWO?!
- TENCHI, CATCH IT.
- UGH.
- ( yowling )
- NOW WHERE IS IT?
HMM.
OH HERE IT IS.
BUT HOW COME THERE ARE
TWO OF THEM?
OH!
- ( meows )
- HMM, IS THIS A CAT
OR WHAT?
OH, YOU'RE HURT.
AREN'T YOU, LITTLE GUY?
- ( meows pitifully )
- JUST A SECOND NOW.
WELL, HOW'S THAT?
- ( happy meow )
- OH, AHA!
SO HERE YOU ARE, RYO-OHKI.
- ( meowing )
- ( giggles )
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE FOR YOU.
- ( meows )
- WHAT'S WITH
THIS HANDKERCHIEF?
OH, I SEE NOW.
DID YOU TAKE CARE OF HER WOUND?
- SORT OF.
- THANK YOU.
I'M SASAMI.
- SASAMI, I SEE.
MY NAME IS TENCHI.
HER WOUND IS NOTHING SERIOUS.
SO THERE'S REALLY NO NEED
FOR WORRY, SASAMI.
- YOU WERE LUCKY, RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- GOT TO GO.
BYE-BYE, SASAMI.
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
- SORRY, SASAMI.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I GOT KIND OF LOST.
- HEY, BE CAREFUL, RYO-OHKI.
WE'RE NOT IN
THE MAGIC KINGDOM NOW.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HEARD TALKING
OR THERE MIGHT BE TROUBLE.
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
NOW, LET'S GO HOME
TO THE MAGIC KINGDOM.
- WELL, I'D LIKE TO STAY HERE
FOR A WHILE.
- WHAT? WHY'S THAT?
- WHY? I WONDER.
- ( bell rings )
- ( chattering )
- BYE-BYE.
- SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- SEE YA'.
- WHERE'S MY BOOK?
- WE HAVE A TEST TOMORROW.
- I LEFT IT AT THE MALT SHOP.
- GEE, I WONDER WHERE
TENCHI IS RYO-OHKI.
- HEY, SASAMI,
WE'D BETTER LEAVE SOON.
- NOW WHERE...
( gasps )
HUH?
- HEY, ARE YOU
LISTENING, SASAMI?
- HA! THERE!
- TENCHI.
- OH, HI, AYEKA. HOW'S IT GOING?
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO WALK HOME WITH ME?
- SURE I WOULD.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
- HUH?
- TENCHI HAS PROMISED TO
WALK HOME WITH ME TODAY.
- HUH?
- HMM?
- UH.
- WE PROMISED TO WATCH
THE NIGHT LIGHTS
OF THE GRAND BRIDGE OF SETTO
AND SPEND THE NIGHT TOGETHER
TILL MORNING.
REMEMBER, TENCHI?
- WELL, NO.
I REALLY DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
- YOU REALLY ARE
A JUVENILE DELINQUENT, YOU KNOW!
GO AWAY, YOU PESKY PERSON.
SHOO, SHOO.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU GO AWAY.
LEAVE US ALONE, OKAY.
TENCHI IS MINE.
- I WILL NOT ALLOW IT.
- OH! STOP IT, GIRLS!
- ( growling )
- THERE THEY GO AGAIN.
- CUT IT OUT, BOTH OF YOU.
STOP IT RIGHT NOW, PLEASE.
IT'S REALLY DISGRACEFUL.
- WELL, I BELIEVE IN
OBLITERATING THE SOURCE
OF THE DISGRACE
HERE AND NOW, MISS KIYONE.
- SHE DOESN'T REALIZE SHE'S
A DISGRACE TOO, YOU KNOW.
- MISS RYOKO, I CAN'T
SURRENDER TENCHI TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU ARE
THE DISGRACE OF OUR SCHOOL.
IT IS MY DUTY AS THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE STUDENT BODY
TO SAVE TENCHI FROM YOUR
JUVENILE DELIQUENCY.
- OH BOY.
- ( grunts )
IT'S MY DUTY
TO SAVE MY TENCHI FROM YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, STOP.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- NOW, CALM DOWN, AYEKA
WITH A DARK PATH.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( groans )
- OH NO, TENCHI'S
IN REAL TROUBLE.
HE SEEMS TO BE INVOLVED
IN A FIGHT BETWEEN THE GIRLS.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO, RYO-OHKI?
- SASAMI, TRANSFORM INTO
PRETTY SAMMY NOW.
- OKAY, THEN.
( vocalizing )
SAMMY DAVIS BROILER CHICKEN!
THE MAGICAL GIRL,
PRETTY SAMMY.
- I DON'T KNOW, THEY WERE
JUST STANDING OVER THERE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY--
- ( chattering )
- OH MY, WE HAVE
A GREAT BIG AUDIENCE,
DON'T WE?
- ALL THE MORE DISGRACEFUL.
- LEAVE IT ALL TO ME, NOW.
- Both: HUH?
- FIGHTING IS NO GOOD AT ALL.
BE FRIENDS AND CHEERFUL,
ALL OF YOU.
THAT'S THE FIRST STEP
TO PEACE.
I ALWAYS SMILE
I'M PRETTY SAMMY.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- AND WHY ARE YOU
DRESSED LIKE THAT?
ARE YOU CRAZY OR SOMETHING?
- NOT AS CRAZY AS YOU ARE,
GIRLY-GIRL.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- WAIT A SECOND AND I'LL MAKE
YOU FRIENDS IN NO TIME.
- ( both growl )
- PRETTY ARCHERY SETUP!
( vocalizing )
BE FRIENDS, YOU TWO!
- ( both growl )
- ( screaming )
- MISS RYOKO? MISS AYEKA?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- UH, WHAT IS THIS
FEELING I HAVE?
MY HEART IS POUNDING.
- AYEKA, I'M SO SORRY,
SO SORRY
I WAS MEAN TO YOU.
- HMM, OH NO.
I'M SORRY.
- AYEKA, I CONFESS
THAT I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
RATHER FOND OF YOU.
- ( gasps )
IS THAT TRUE, RYOKO?
- BUT YOU SEEMED TO CARE ABOUT
NO ONE BUT TENCHI.
I GOT SO JEALOUS
THAT I HAD TO THROW MYSELF
BETWEEN YOU TWO.
I CAN'T LIVE WITH MYSELF.
CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
- MISS RYOKO.
- AYEKA.
- ( all gasping )
- OH, YOU'RE WONDERFUL.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME GO,
NEVER EVER.
- HMM, YOU'RE A SWEETHEART.
- UH, HOLD ONTO YOUR SANITY,
BOTH OF YOU.
- THIS IS WAY TOO MUCH FOR ME.
- WHAT IS GOING ON HERE? HUH?
- Ryoko: SO THIS IS WHAT
THEY CALL HAPINESS?
- HOLD ME TIGHT.
- UM, I'M NOT SURE
THIS IS EVOLVING
INTO AN APPROPRIATE
RELATIONSHIP, GIRLS.
- OH, THIS HAS TO BE THE MOST
DISGRACEFUL MOMENT
IN THE HISTORY OF THIS SCHOOL.
- I'M SO HAPPY FOR THEM
BEING SUCH GOOD FRIENDS AND ALL.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- I REALLY LOVE YOU, AYEKA.
- I'M SO HAPPY.
- THE TIME HAS COME
TO CONCLUDE THIS EPISODE,
BUT THEIR WILD JOURNEY
WILL CONTINUE ON.
- HOW FAR DO THESE
DIFFERENT WORLDS GO?
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO
OUR HERO AND HEROINES?
- IN OUR NEXT EPISODE,
TENCHI GENESIS JOURNEY THROUGH
TIME AND SPACE PART THREE
WILL SEE THE RAGING CLIMAX.
- Both: PLEASE STAY TUNED
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS,
OH RESPECTABLE VIEWERS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A FOOL ♪
♪ OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, YOU'LL NEVER BE
A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL ALWAYS WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG AND
I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE
TO THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE ♪
♪ HOW YOU WILL
MOURN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- ( silent )
- Tenchi: OUR EVENT
REACHES A CLIMAX,
WITH RYOKO AS A GANGSTER
AND AYEKA AS A MILLIONAIRE'S
DAUGHTER.
- Ayeka: OH, I FIND THE
CASTING MOST APPROPRIATE.
- Tenchi: MIHOSHI'S A HOUSEWIFE
AND AYEKA'S AN OLD MAID.
- Ayeka: WHO DID YOU SAY
IS AN OLD MAID?!
- Tenchi: WHAT FATE AWAITS US
AT THE END OF THIS ADVENTURE?
- Ryoko: A GRAND FINALE THAT
WILL MOVE YOU TO TEARS.
- Tenchi: COMING NEXT IS
"JOURNEY THROUGH TIME AND
SPACE PART THREE."
- Ayeka: IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
SENSATIONAL.