- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ YOU'RE NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER,
THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS WILL
OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU'LL LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION,
YOU DROWN YOUR DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ YOU'RE NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- MY NAME IS YOSHO,
THE MAN WHO ONCE DESERTED
JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
- I AM AZAKA,
A KNIGHT OF JURAI.
- AND I AM KAMIDAKE.
- AND FROM NOW ON, WE PLEDGE
OUR ALLEGIANCE TO YOU.
- YO!
- THIS PLANET IS THE PLACE
WHERE THE JURAI IMPERIAL
VILLA USED TO BE.
- HMM.
AND IT'S A PERFECT SPOT
TO HIDE FOR A WHILE
FROM THOSE WHO ARE
AFTER US, AYEKA.
- ( screaming )
- THESE ARE THE RUINS
OF DREAMS PAST.
- SOMEHOW,
THAT FACE LOOKS FAMILIAR.
- HE HAS GENTLE EYES.
AHA!  HIS EYES LOOK
JUST LIKE YOURS, TENCHI.
- HUH?  YOU THINK SO?
- THAT'S THE LEGENDARY
WARRIOR YOSHO.
- HUH?
- THAT'S THE STATUE OF YOSHO.
- WHAT?!  SO THAT'S YOU
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG, FATHER?
- YOU SURE WERE
HANDSOME.  WOW!
- HUH?
SO THAT'S GRANDPA.
- LOOK, IT LOOKS LIKE THERE USED
TO BE ANOTHER STATUE OVER THERE.
- Sasami: YEAH, EVERYBODY LOOK.
I WONDER WHO IT WAS.
- HUH?  I DON'T REALLY
KNOW, SASAMI.
- THAT USED TO BE
A STATUE OF A MAN
WITH THE MOST AMAZING
POTENTIAL.
HE WAS OF NOBLE BIRTH.
HIS FAMILY TREE BEING THAT
OF JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
HE WAS
EXTRAORDINARILY GIFTED
BOTH IN SWORDSMANSHIP
AND ACADEMICS.
HE WAS A WONDERFUL MAN.
AND IT WOULD HAVE BEEN HE
WHO WAS PRAISED
AS THE LEGENDARY WARRIOR.
IF ONLY HE HAD
NOT ALLOWED HIMSELF
TO BE CHANGED SO MUCH
BY THE JURAI POWER,
THE INCREDIBLE POWER
THAT BELONGS
TO JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY,
THE DOMINATOR OF ALL GALAXIES.
THE SECRET BEHIND THE FAMILY'S
ABSOLUTE STRENGTH LIES
IN THIS JURAI POWER.
THE MYSTERIOUS POWER
GIVEN BY THE GOD,
THE MIGHTIEST POWER
IN THE UNIVERSE
THAT DENIES ANY ELUCIDATION
BY HUMAN INTELLIGENCE.
THAT IS THE JURAI POWER.
THE MAN BECAME FASCINATED
AND OBSESSED WITH THE POWER.
HE BECAME
A PRISONER OF IT.
THE POWER BEING FAR TOO IMMENSE
FOR HIM TO RESIST.
AND THERE WAS NOTHING
THAT COULD STOP HIS AMBITION.
- ( shouting )
AND THEN I BATTLED
WITH HIM
AND WON.
AFTER THAT, HE VANISHED
INTO THE DARKNESS OF SPACE.
HIS NAME ERASED
FROM JURAI'S HISTORY.
IT WAS THEN I DECIDED
TO LEAVE JURAI
NEVER TO RETURN.
- SO THAT'S THE IDENTITY
OF OUR ENEMY.
- EVEN THOUGH
THERE IS NO PROOF.
KAGATO.
- OF COURSE I HAD NO IDEA.
I NEVER KNEW ANYTHING
HAPPENED LIKE THAT ON JURAI.
- WELL, I DON'T THINK AYEKA
KNEW EITHER, SASAMI.
SHE'S KIND OF SHAKEN.
- HERE'S YOUR DINNER,
EVERYONE.
THANKS FOR WAITING!
- WHAT?!  MORE CARROTS?!
- AFRAID SO.
IT'S THE ONLY FOOD LEFT.
- ( sighs )
- I BOUGHT TOO MANY CARROTS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
LIFE IS LIKE THAT.
- I KNOW RYO-OHKI LOVES THEM,
BUT I'M GONNA
TURN ORANGE SOON.
- OH!  THAT REMINDS ME.
WHERE IS RYO-OHKI?
- HMM?
- YEAH.  WHERE IS SHE?
WOULDN'T WANT HER
TO MISS MORE YUMMY CARROTS.
- I GOTTA SAY I KIND OF LIKE
HAVING DINNER UNDER THE STARS
LIKE THIS, DON'T YOU GUYS?
- YEAH, I AGREE.
- HEY, DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
GO GET TENCHI AND AYEKA?
- MIHOSHI, I THINK WE SHOULD
JUST LEAVE THEM ALONE FOR NOW.
- YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
- HEY, COME ON, PAY ATTENTION!
THE FIRE'S GOING OUT!
- OH, NO!
I REALLY WISH
THEY'D COOK FASTER.
HUH?
- ( screaming )
- TENCHI.
- OH.  HELLO, AYEKA.
- YOU SEEM VERY LOST
IN THOUGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
YOUR ROYAL BLOOD, AREN'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST SO STRANGE.
ONLY A WHILE AGO I WAS JUST
AN ORDINARY EARTHLING, YOU KNOW?
JUST AN ORDINARY
HIGH SCHOOL BOY
AND NOTHING MORE.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I DON'T KNOW.
- TENCHI,
I KNOW IT'S DIFFICULT,
BUT I'VE ENJOYED IT ALL.
- HUH?
- FROM THE TIME
WE LEFT THE EARTH
CHASED BY
THE JURAI FORCES.
IN FACT, EVER SINCE
I ARRIVED ON THE EARTH
AND STARTED TO LIVE
WITH YOU AND YOUR FAMILY,
I HAVE BEEN SO VERY HAPPY,
ENJOYING EVERY MINUTE OF LIFE.
- BUT--
- BUT I HAVE ALWAYS
UNDERSTOOD MY DUTY
AS THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE PLANET JURAI.
AND OF COURSE I KNEW
THAT MY HAPPY HOLIDAY
WOULD HAVE TO COME
TO AN END ONE DAY.
AND, YES, I ALWAYS KNEW
I WOULD EVENTUALLY
HAVE TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOU, TENCHI.
- AYEKA, I ALWAYS THOUGHT--
- PLEASE LISTEN, TENCHI.
EVEN THOUGH
I AM THE FIRST PRINCESS,
I AM MERELY A MEMBER OF ONE
OF MANY BRANCH FAMILIES.
NOW THAT
IT HAS BEEN REVEALED
YOU ARE
THE DIRECT DESCENDANT
OF JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY,
IT IS YOU, TENCHI,
WHO SHOULD
SUCCEED THE THRONE.
- BUT, AYEKA, I--
- IF YOU DO SO, TENCHI,
I CAN BE NEAR YOU.
TENCHI, I CAN BE
CLOSE TO YOU ALWAYS.
AND THE WISH
I'VE ALWAYS HAD,
THE WISH I'D THOUGHT
WAS IMPOSSIBLE
MIGHT COME TRUE.
I CAN'T HELP
THINKING THAT, TENCHI.
FORGIVE ME FOR POURING
OUT MY HEART.
( sighs )
- I KNEW YOU WOULD COME,
YOSHO.
YES, I WAS CERTAIN
YOU WOULD COME
HERE, YOSHO.
- AND SO IT WAS YOU
ALL ALONG, KAGATO.
- I'VE WAITED.
I'VE WAITED SO LONG
FOR THIS MOMENT
TO MEET YOU AGAIN.
OF COURSE I WASN'T DEAD,
BUT YOU KNEW THAT.
ALL THIS TIME,
I WAS IN THE DARKNESS
OF THE UNIVERSE,
REFINING AND STRENGTHENING
MY JURAI POWER
TO THE MOST EXTREME LIMIT.
I'VE BEEN THINKING OF YOU
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
I MUST SAY, IT'S VERY NICE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I SEE YOU'VE AGED,
EH, YOSHO?
- I THINK I LOOK PRETTY GOOD
FOR MY AGE.
- JUST LOOK AT ME.
THE INFINITE POWER OF YOUTH
IS COMPLETELY MINE
TO COMMAND.
- IS THAT ONE OF THE POWERS
YOU ACQUIRED
IN THE DARKNESS
OF THE UNIVERSE?
- INDEED, IT IS.
THERE IS NOTHING
JURAI'S POWER CANNOT DO.
- SO YOU'VE HAD
A UNIVERSAL FACELIFT.
IS THAT IT, KAGATO?
- ARE YOU READY?
THAT'S GOOD.
I CAN FEEL YOUR
FIGHTING SPIRIT NOW.
- KAGATO, I HAVE TO MAKE
YOU DIE ONCE AGAIN, YOU KNOW?
- AS THE HEIR TO THE THRONE
OF PLANET JURAI,
WILL YOUR POWER WIN,
OR WILL MY POWER TRIUMPH
AMPLIFIED BY THE DARKNESS
OF THE UNIVERSE?
WE SHALL SEE.
TAKE THIS!  HA!
YOU'RE STILL QUITE GOOD.
YOU'RE EXACTLY
LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
BUT I'M NOT EXACTLY
WELL, WELL.
THAT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE, YOSHO.
WORTHY OF
A LEGENDARY WARRIOR.
- HUH?
- I DID WARN YOU
I AM NOT THE SAME
AS THE OLD DAYS.
- I CAN SEE THAT.
- IN THE DARKNESS
OF THE UNIVERSE
FIGHTING A FEAR
AND DESPERATION
WORSE THAN DEATH ITSELF,
I WOULD DREAM
OF THIS MOMENT OVER AND OVER,
DREAM OF THE MOMENT
I KILLED YOU, YOSHO.
( screaming )
- KAGATO.
KAGATO.
AT THE TIME I SLAYED YOU,
I KILLED MYSELF AS WELL.
AND NOW AGAIN.
WHY MUST I FACE YOU
IN BATTLE ONCE AGAIN?
FORGIVE ME, KAGATO.
- HUH?
INTERESTING.
YOU WANT US TO KILL EACH OTHER
AT THE SAME TIME, DON'T YOU?
- ( shouting )
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT WAS THAT?!
- IT'S A TREMENDOUS ENERGY,
VERY CLOSE.
- THE JURAI POWER?
- PROBABLY.  YES.
- ( gags )
- ( gasps )
- GRANDPA.
- HURRY, KAMIDAKE.
- RIGHT!
- WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE TO DIE TODAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
AND VISIT HELL THIS TIME?
YOU CAN GO
AND TAKE MY PLACE!  HUH?
- YOU THERE, WHO ARE YOU?
- JURAI'S EMPEROR AND KING.
YOU'RE NOT.
- YES, THE MIGHTIEST AND LAST
OF ALL THE JURAI KINGS.
I AM THE GOD.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT!
- YOU'RE FUN TO PLAY WITH,
BUT I'M VERY BUSY JUST NOW.
GET LOST!
- ( screams )
- RYOKO!
RYOKO.  HUH?  GRANDPA!
- YOU WATCH OUT, TENCHI.
THIS GUY'S
NO ONE TO MESS WITH.
- PRINCESS AYEKA.
- HUH? ( gasps )
- I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME
TO WITNESS THE LEGENDARY
WARRIOR'S DESTRUCTION.
- NOT SO FAST.
- HMM?
- YOU WILL HAVE TO
DESTROY US FIRST, KAGATO.
- BE GONE, YOU FOOLS!
- AZAKA!  KAMIDAKE!
- YOU WILL HAVE
TO FIGHT ME NOW!
- SILLY BOY.
I SEE.
- YOU MUST STAY BACK,
TENCHI.
- WE'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
- WELL, MY BOY,
WHY DON'T YOU AND I
CHOOSE ANOTHER TIME
AND PLACE TO MEET?
- NO!
( screaming )
- HUH?  OH!
- NO.  AYEKA!
- TENCHI!
- AYEKA!
- TENCHI, HELP ME!
- OH, NO!
- ( screeches )
- COME BACK, AYEKA!
- I WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
AT THE JURAI PALACE,
AND I WISH YOU LUCK
GETTING THERE IN ONE PIECE.
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY!
- ( laughing )
- TREACHEROUS COWARD!
- PLEASE, GRANDPA.
GRANDPA, HANG ON.
- PLEASE, GRANDPA,
YOU MUST LIVE.
- QUICKLY.
WE HAVE TO HELP HIM!
- GOTCHA.
- HERE, TENCHI, TAKE THIS.
- WHAT IS IT, GRANDPA?
- SWORD TENCHI.
THE MAGICAL SWORD THAT
TRANSFORMS JURAI'S POWER
INTO A BLADE.
- SWORD TENCHI?
- TENCHI, YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DESTROY KAGATO.
GO, TENCHI.
IT IS ALL UP TO YOU NOW.
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY ♪
♪ FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ♪
♪ A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY,
YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I'M BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Ryoko:
TENCHI, YOU SHOULD CHOOSE ME.
FORGET AYEKA.
- Tenchi: WHAT?
- Ryoko: DON'T GO, TENCHI.
PLEASE! ( sniffling )
I BEG YOU.
- Tenchi: RYOKO.
- Ryoko:
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE.
I JUST CAN'T BEAR
THE THOUGHT
OF LOSING YOU.
- Tenchi: COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR RYOKO."
- Kiyone: IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
TRUE LOVE.