- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- Ryoko:
( grunts )
- HMM.
- Ryoko:
( noisily eats food )
- ( sips )
- ( chews )
- SLOW POKE, COME ON.
EAT UP, WILL YOU?
- WELL, I'M NOT LIKE YOU, RYOKO.
I REALLY CAN'T BRING MYSELF
TO EAT LIKE A BARBARIAN.
FIRST I START WITH MY APPETIZERS
AND THEN MOVE ON TO MY SOUP.
- HEY, IT'S JUST PICKLES
AND MISO SOUP.
- EXCUSE ME.
OH, MR. MANAGER.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU SERVED US OUR MAIN DISH.
YOU KNOW OUR ORDER,
THE EXTRA LARGE BEEF BALLS.
- ( huffs )
- SORRY, I'VE GOT
PART-TIME HELP TODAY.
YOUR ORDER SHOULD BE
COMING RIGHT UP, MA'AM.
HEY, AMARUBE, YURA,
THAT'S A LONG ENOUGH BREAK!
COME ON, YOU TWO,
GET BACK TO WORK.
AMARUBE, YURA,
YOU ARE FIRED!
NOW GET OUT!
- ( scoffs )
SCREAM YOUR HEAD OFF.
WE WERE LEAVING ANYWAY,
YOU BIG MOUTH.
I'M TOO GOOD TO BE WORKING
IN A BEEF BALL JOINT ANYWAY.
SPACE IS CALLING TO ME.
IT'S TELLING ME
I CAN BE SOMETHING,
BECOME SOMETHING GREAT.
- HEY, AMARUBE, IT'S OPEN.
- OKAY.
( thoughts ):
THIS IS IT,
THE LEGEND OF AMARUBE AND YURA,
THE DELINQUENT DUO OF SPACE,
BEGINS TODAY.
( laughs )
- YO!
- Manager:
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- HEY, AYEKA,
WE'RE GONNA GO ON AND
HEAD BACK TO YAGAMI NOW.
OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( slowly chewing )
- ( gasping )
- ( engine rumbles )
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HECK?
- ( screams )
- OH NO.
THAT'S YAGAMI!
- HEY, STOP!
( panting )
- WE'RE YOU GOING?
DON'T GO ANYWHERE WITHOUT US!
- PLEASE, WAIT FOR ME.
I WANT TO GET ON YOU TOO,
YAGAMI.
- ( panting )
( screaming )
- OH WELL, YAGAMI'S GONE.
- YAGAMI'S BEEN HIJACKED.
HOW CAN YOU BE
SO CASUAL ABOUT IT?
- WHAT? HIJACKED?
- ( screaming )
- COME BACK, YAGAMI.
DON'T LEAVE WITHOUT US.
- WHY? WHY? WHY?
- WELL, I'M GLAD YOU
TOOK YOUR TIME EATING
BECAUSE YAGAMI'S GONE NOW.
WHOEVER STOLE MY SHIP
SURE HAD A LOT OF NERVE.
THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
- HEY, YAGAMI'S MY SHIP.
- COME ON, GIRLS,
LET'S FOCUS.
- FIRST, I'M GONNA FIND 'EM
AND THEN I'M GONNA
BEAT 'EM UP REAL GOOD.
COME ON, RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- LET'S GO.
- RIGHT.
- OKAY.
- ( meows )
- ( gasps )
RYO-OHKI IS LEAVING US.
- HEY, TENCHI, WAIT FOR US.
- PLEASE, CALL
A SPACE CAB, SASAMI.
WE SHOULD FOLLOW THEM.
- BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
- HUH?
- ( coughs )
- HERE'S YOUR CHECK.
- YEEHAW!
WE ARE CRUISING.
- ALL RIGHT! GO FASTER!
- WE MUST NOT LET THEM GET AWAY,
RYOKO.
- COUNT ON ME.
- I DO.
GRANDPA AND DAD ARE
STILL ON YAGAMI, YOU KNOW.
- ( stomach rumbles )
( sighs )
GEE, WHERE ARE THEY?
I WONDER, DO YOU THINK THEY
FORGOT ABOUT OUR BEEF BOWLS?
- EASY NOW.
DON'T ACT SO DESPERATE.
A SAMURAI SHOULD BETRAY
ABSOLUTELY NO WEAKNESS
WHEN STARVING.
- BUT, DAD, COME ON.
- CHECKMATE.
- HUH?
HUH?!
- ( beeping )
( whirring )
( beeping )
- ( meows )
( meowing )
- ( honking )
- ( screaming )
- ( grunts )
- ( meows )
- ( screams )
- ( all groaning )
- HEY, IDIOT.
YOU RAN A RED LIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU LOOK
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, YOU JERK?
- GREAT.
NOW WE'VE LOST THEM.
- NOW WHAT?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
TO DAD AND GRANDPA?
- WHAT ABOUT YAGAMI?
WHAT ABOUT MY SHIP?
- I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT IT NOW.
- HEY, I KNOW.
WHY DON'T WE REPORT
THIS INCIDENT
TO THE GALAXY POLICE.
WHAT'D YOU THINK, HUH?
- MIHOSHI, AND JUST
WHO DO YOU THINK WE ARE?
HUH? CAN YOU TELL ME?
HUH? HUH?
- WE ARE THE MOST
WANTED CRIMINALS
IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE,
AREN'T WE?
- TO US!
( gulping )
- AH, SO WE DID IT, AMARUBE.
- A PIECE OF CAKE. FOR THE
BEST GANGSTER IN THE UNIVERSE,
STEALING THIS SHIP
WAS TOO EASY.
HMM.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALWAYS
BEEN A DREAM OF MINE.
TO TRAVEL IN A SHIP
LIKE THIS.
- WELL, YOU'VE GOT YOUR WISH.
AND THUS, OUR LEGEND BEGINS.
- BUT HOW?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
TO BECOME A LEGEND?
TELL ME THE PLAN.
- HUH, WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE SELL THIS SHIP
AND GET US SOME DOUGH?
- GREAT!
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT?
I WANT A NICE PURSE,
AND SOME NEW SHOES,
AND A PIECE OF CHEESECAKE
FROM SIRIUS.
- AND I'M GONNA BUY
MYSELF A SPACE SHIP.
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
KEEP THIS ONE?
- HUH?
OH.
- ( laughing )
- ( beeping )
- ATTENTION ALL PATROL SHIPS,
ATTENTION ALL PATROL SHIPS...
WE HAVE JUST SPOTTED YAGAMI
IN SPACE ZONE 6-0-2.
PROCEED TO THE SCENE
IMMEDIATELY.
THIS IS GALAXY POLICE.
YAGAMI, STOP YOUR
ENGINE RIGHT NOW.
WE WILL ATTACK
IF YOU DON'T COOPERATE.
- UH, I DON'T GET IT.
HOW DID THOSE GUYS KNOW
THIS WAS A HIJACKED SHIP?
- WHAT'S OUR PLAN FOR THIS?
- HEH! WE'LL JUST
OUTRUN THEM.
- THEY'RE TRYING TO GET AWAY.
ENGAGE AND PURSUE!
- YOU SEE,
THEY'RE NO MATCH FOR ME.
- THEY MUST BE DREAMING
IF THEY THINK THEY CAN CATCH
THE GREATEST GANGSTER
IN THE UNIVERSE.
- "YAGAMI." THAT NAME SOUNDS
FAMILIAR, SOMEHOW.
HUH?
- ( beeping )
- HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
- WHAT?
- LOOK!
- HUH? AAH!
OH MAN! WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- IT'S JUST A REGULAR HIJACKING.
I MEAN, AREN'T THEY KIND OF
OVERDOING IT?
- YO!
YO!
- EARLIER TODAY, PRINCESS AYEKA
AND HER GROUP
WERE SPOTTED
IN SPACE ZONE 6-0-2
ABOARD THE SPACE SHIP YAGAMI.
THE GALAXY POLICE
ARE IN HOT PURSUIT.
AND ARE HEADING TOWARD
SPACE ZONE 5-28.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?
- ON BOARD YAGAMI
ARE PRINCESS AYEKA,
HER SISTER PRINCESS SASAMI,
THE SPACE PIRATE RYOKO,
AND TWO FORMER GALAXY
POLICE OFFICERS.
THE PRESENCE OF THREE
UNIDENTIFIED CIVILIANS
HAS YET TO BE CONFIRMED.
- ( whimpering )
- HEY, THEY WERE CUSTOMERS
AT THE BEEF BOWL PLACE, YURA.
- THEN DON'T YOU SEE?
THIS SHIP BELONGS TO THEM.
- SO WE'RE BEING MISTAKEN
FOR THE MOST WANTED
CRIMINALS IN THE UNIVERSE.
- OH NO!
- OH, THIS IS TOO PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE.
NOW WE KNOW WHERE YAGAMI IS.
- JUST WHAT'S THERE
TO BE CHEERFUL ABOUT?
- THE GALAXY POLICE
ARE AFTER US, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, I'LL WORRY
ABOUT THEM, OKAY?
RYO-OHKI, PROCEED IMMEDIATELY
TO SPACE ZONE 5-2-8.
- ( meows )
- GRANDPA, DAD,
I HOPE YOU'RE SAFE.
- CHESS IS A BATTLE
FOUGHT PEACEFULLY.
IT CULTIVATES THE MIND,
THE SPIRIT, AND THE SOUL.
AND WE MUST ALWAYS
CULTIVATE THE SOUL.
- CHECKMATE.
- EH?
- ( sirens wail )
- ( cries )
AMARUBE, DO SOMETHING.
YOU WANT TO BE THE GREATEST
GANGSTER IN THE UNIVERSE, RIGHT?
YOU WANT TO BE A LEGEND, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
DOESN'T THIS SHIP HAVE
A TURBO BOOSTER OR SOMETHING?
- ( fireworks crackle )
- NO!
WHAT DID I DO?!
- SIR, THEY FIRED AT US,
CAPTAIN.
- RETURN FIRE.
THESE ARE MOST WANTED CRIMINALS.
SHOW NO MERCY.
- THIS REPORT JUST IN.
APPARENTLY, MOMENTS AGO,
YAGAMI AND THE GALAXY POLICE
BEGAN EXCHANGING FIRE.
- NOW, THEY'RE MAKING THINGS
EVEN MORE COMPLICATED.
- NO KIDDING, RYOKO.
BUT WE DON'T WANT
TO GET CAUGHT EITHER.
- WE SHOULD BE
ROOTING FOR THEM.
COME ON, GET AWAY
FROM THE POLICE.
- UGH! I HAVE MIXED FEELINGS
ABOUT THIS.
ARE WE ROOTING
FOR THE HIJACKERS?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'VE GOT THE POLICE
ALL ANGRY.
- WELL, I REALLY
DIDN'T MEAN TO.
- ( cries )
- Captain: YOU HAVE NOWHERE
TO HIDE, PRINCESS AYEKA.
- THIS IS A SLIGHT
MISUNDERSTANDING.
- YEAH, WE'RE JUST A COUPLE
OF INNOCENT GANGSTERS.
- ( cries )
I'M SO SCARED.
- PLEASE HELP ME, MOMMY.
- HOW PATHETIC.
- AND THOSE ARE THE GUYS WHO
STOLE YAGAMI FROM US?
- BUT I FEEL SO
SORRY FOR THEM
BEING MISTAKEN FOR
THE MOST WANTED CRIMINALS.
- WILL YOU PLEASE--
- Amarube: OH NO!
WE'RE GONNA BE KILLED.
AND I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
- WHEN ARE WE GONNA CATCH UP
WITH THEM, RYOKO?
- IT'S NOT THAT EASY, TENCHI.
THEY ARE TRAVELLING
AT TOP-SPEED TOO, YOU KNOW?
- CHECKMATE.
- HMM?
NOW JUST WAIT.
- WELL, NOW THERE'S
NO WAITING IN BATTLE,
BUT I'LL DO THIS INSTEAD.
- WHAT?!
- LOOKS LIKE WE DON'T
HAVE ANY OTHER CHOICE.
- WE DON'T.
- OPERATION SPEED UP RYO-OHKI.
IF WE USE THIS TACTIC
ON RYO-OHKI...
HMM.
- ( yowling )
- HMM?
- BUT THAT IS A CHILI PEPPER
FROM THE BEEF BOWL PLACE.
- FEEDING SOME CHILI PEPPER
TO RYO-OHKI?
THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT BY
OPERATION SPEED UP?
- WELL, YEAH. UNFORTUNATELY,
BY USING THIS TACTIC,
RYO-OHKI WILL BE ANGRY WITH ME
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
- ( yowls )
- ( sirens wail )
- THERE IT IS.
- HUH?
THAT STAR IS...
- YAGAMI IS HEADED STRAIGHT
TOWARD THAT SUPER NOVA.
- GOOD.
THEN THEY CAN'T
GO ANYWHERE ELSE.
- I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
STOP, PLEASE.
LET'S JUST GO HOME.
RIGHT NOW!
- ( gargles )
- EEK.
AAH! A-- OH!
- WE'LL BE ENTERING
THE SUPER NOVA'S
GRAVITATIONAL FIELD
IN TWO MINUTES.
ONCE WE FLY INTO
THE SPHERE OF GRAVITATION,
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO ESCAPE.
- HURRY UP, RYOKO.
- TENCHI, YOU'VE
GOT TO TRUST ME.
- ( meows )
- 60 MORE SECONDS BEFORE WE
REACH THE GRAVISPHERE.
- ( growls )
ALL RIGHT, HOLD THE FLEET.
- ( Ryo-Ohki whirrs )
( meows )
- ( grunting )
- HUH?
- WELL, THEY'RE TOTALLY
OUT OF IT.
- HM-HMM.
- GRANDPA, DAD!
- ( pants )
- OH WELCOME BACK, TENCHI.
- WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG THERE,
MY SON, HUH?
- HUH?
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO NOW?
- DON'T WORRY.
ACCORDING TO MY CALCULATIONS,
WE USE THE GRAVITY TO ESCAPE
IF WE GO IN IT
AT A 34 DEGREE ANGLE
AND THEN GO FULL-BLAST
8.1 SECONDS LATER.
- USE THE GRAVITY?
ARE YOU INSANE?
- WELL, WE DON'T
HAVE TIME TO ARGUE.
- ACCELERATING?!
THEY'RE CRAZY!
- GO NOW.
- NO, IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
- ( laughs )
YES, WE'VE DONE IT!
- HMM, SO AM I GENIUS
OR WHAT?
Tenchi: AND SO THE
HIJACKING-OF-YAGAMI INCIDENT
FINALLY ENDED.
- ( both scream )
- HMM, YUM.
- WHEW, I'M EXHAUSTED.
- OH BOY, WHAT AN
ORDEAL THAT WAS.
- ( chewing )
- THIS BEEF BOWL
IS REALLY GOOD.
ISN'T IT, DAD?
- YES.
THE ONIONS ESPECIALLY,
VERY TASTY.
- ( laughs )
GOOD BEEF BOWLS, HUH?
BEEF BOWLS?
BEEF BOWLS!
( screams )
- YES, WHAT ABOUT
BEEF BOWLS, TENCHI? WHAT?
- UH, WE'RE FORGETTING
ABOUT AYEKA AND SASAMI.
- ( squeals )
OOH.
( giggles )
- ( sighs )
- THAT'S THREE HOURS
DISHWASHING.
THAT MEANS YOU HAVE
ANOTHER 89 HOURS TO GO.
- OH NO!
- OH NO.
- HERE YOU GO.
- OH.
HELP US, TENCHI!
PLEASE COME AND RESCUE US,
TENCHI.
( whimpers )
- ( theme music plays )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A FOOL ♪
♪ OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, YOU'LL NEVER BE
A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL ALWAYS WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG AND
I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE
TO THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE ♪
♪ HOW YOU WILL
MOURN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Washu:
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THERE'LL BE A SWIMSUIT CONTEST
IN OUR NEXT EPISODE.
- Ayeka: MISS RYOKO, IT'S SEEMS
TO BE A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
FOR US TO PROVE WHICH
ONE OF US IS SUPERIOR,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- Ryoko:
UH-HUH, IT SURE DOES.
THIS CONTEST WILL DECIDE
WHO THE REAL WINNER IS.
NOW I CAN SHOW OFF
THIS PERFECT BODY OF MINE.
- Ayeka:
( scoffs )
- Both:
( laugh )
- Washu: COMING UP NEXT
IS "NO NEED FOR SWIMSUITS."
OH BOY, WELL, THEY CAN DO
WHATEVER THEY WANT.
- Ayeka:
IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY BEAUTIFUL.