- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL NOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- ( crowd chattering )
- LOOK IT, LOOK IT!
- YEAH!
- IT'S GREAT. YEAH.
- WE'RE GONNA COME OVER
HERE FOR A MINUTE, OKAY?
- CAN WE GO OVER THERE?
- OKAY.
- MEET YOU BACK HERE
IN HALF AN HOUR.
- SO GOOD!
- ( giggling )
- ( chanting )
- ( meows )
- HERE I AM.
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
- WOW!
YOU LOOK CUTE.
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
YEAH, REALLY.
RIGHT?
- ( meows )
- IT'S A TRADITIONAL
FESTIVAL COSTUME
WE HAVE ON JURAI.
( giggles )
- WELL, SHALL WE GO NOW,
SASAMI?
- I DON'T KNOW,
TENCHI.
EVERYONE ELSE IS
WORKING THERE AS STALL KEEPERS
EXCEPT ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- SASAMI, YOU WORK HARD
EVERY DAY.
YOU DESERVE A DAY OFF.
BESIDES,
AYEKA AND THE OTHERS
ARE EXCITED ABOUT
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
LET'S GO.
YOU'RE GOING TO YOUR
FIRST FAIR ON EARTH!
- MMM.
YES!
RIGHT!
- YO!
- ( chuckles )
- ( meows )
( meows )
- TENCHI, COME ON,
YOU SLOWPOKE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( pants )
WOW!
HEY, TENCHI.
WHAT'S THAT?
- OH, THAT'S THE GOLDFISH
SCOOPER.
YOU WANT TO TRY IT?
- ( squeals )
MM-HMM!
AHH...
GOTCHA!
AW. OHH.
- HERE.
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
- AHH.
( giggles )
AHH.
- HEY!
- UH?
IT'S YOU, RYOKO.
HI, RYOKO.
SO YOU'RE WORKING AS
AS GOLDFISH SCOOPER TOO?
- SORT OF.
- AND HOW'S IT GOING,
RYOKO?
- NOT GOOD.
NOT GOOD AT ALL.
- BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY GOLDFISH HERE.
- WELL, HOW CAN YOU EXPECT
TO GET ANY CUSTOMERS
WITHOUT ANY GOLDFISH?
- OH, I'VE GOT FISH,
ALL RIGHT.
- HUH?
- I DON'T SEE ANY.
WHERE ARE THEY?
( stammers )
- YOU JUST CHECK IT OUT
YOURSELF.
- WHERE? WHERE?
HUH?
- ( roars )
- ( screams )
- AAH!
- I AM THE BIG FISH.
- ( shudders )
- SEE?
I GOT YOUR FISH.
- ( sighs )
THAT GAVE ME A HEART ATTACK.
- I'M CLOSED.
- BINGO!
YOU HIT THE BULLSEYE.
- ( bell rings )
- COME ONE, COME ALL.
IT'S THE BEST PLACE
TO LET OUT YOUR STRESS,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
GREAT. NICE SHOT.
( laughs )
WELL, WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT I COULD MAKE A BUSINESS
OUT OF SOMETHING
AS FUN AS THIS?
- ( sizzling )
- WOW.
IT LOOKS DELICIOUS,
KIYONE.
- AND THIS IS A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY
FOR US TO MAKE UP OUR
FINANCIAL DEFICIT, TENCHI.
- RIGHT.
- I'M KIND OF HUNGRY,
TENCHI.
- SO AM I.
CAN WE HAVE TWO
FRIED NOODLES, PLEASE?
- RIGHT AWAY.
GOT THE SHREDDED CABBAGE,
MIHOSHI, HUH?
- I GOT AS MUCH
AS YOU WANT.
- UH...
- ALL RIGHT.
FORGET THE CABBAGE
AND HAND ME THE CARROTS,
PLEASE.
- OKAY.
WOW.
NOW THIS IS STRANGE.
THIS ONE'S EMPTY.
AND THIS.
OHH.
- ( chewing )
- ( meows )
- I KNEW IT.
- YOU AGAIN, RYO-OHKI?
- AN UNBALANCED DIET
IS NOT GOOD FOR YOU.
- ( meows )
- HMM.
THIS PLACE LOOKS
GOOD ENOUGH.
AH-HA!
GATHER ROUND,
GATHER ROUND.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
SEE WHAT I'VE GOT HERE.
- YEAH, WHAT?
OH, WOW.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
- TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS FROG RIGHT HERE.
THIS FROG IS NOT JUST
ANY FROG.
NO. NO ORDINARY FROG, THIS.
THIS FROG IS DIFFERENT
FROM ANY OTHER FROG.
IT'S A VERY SPECIAL FROG,
I TELL YOU.
- WOW. IT'S DIFFERENT?
HOW IS IT DIFFERENT
FROM OTHER FROGS?
- I'M SO GLAD YOU ASKED,
MISS.
NOW LISTEN,
THIS FROG MAY LOOK LIKE
AN UGLY COMMON FROG,
BUT IT'S AN INHABITANT
OF ALPHA-CENTAUR AND SHULOCK
AT THE BOTTOM OF
MOUNT ZUKUBA.
THIS IS THE FAMOUS FROG
KNOWN AS...
SHULOCK TOAD!
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS IT.
- THE SHULOCK TOAD?!
OH, WOW! OH, WOW!
- AND NOW I PUT THIS TOAD
IN THIS BOX OF 3D MIRRORS,
AND GUESS WHAT HAPPENS?
- ( crowd murmurs )
- THE TOAD STARTS TO SWEAT
AT THE HORRIBLE SIGHT OF ITSELF
REFLECTED IN THE MIRRORS.
- OH, WOW.
- I CAN'T SEE.
- I COLLECT ALL THE DROPS
OF ITS PERSPIRATION
IN A CERAMIC PAN
AND COOK IT SLOWLY,
STIRRING THE LIQUID
FOR EXACTLY 42 DAYS.
AND IT COOKS DOWN
TO THIS RIGHT HERE,
THE SPACE TOAD OIL!
- OOH!
- ANYTHING FROM
BRUISES AND SPRAINS
TO CRYING BABIES
AND ARTERIAL-SCLEROSIS.
A DROP OF THIS
MIRACLE OIL
CAN CURE THEM ALL!
- YOU KNOW, I'M SUFFERING
FROM STIFF SHOULDERS AND STUFF.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT
THIS THING HERE
CAN EVEN CURE THAT?
- OF COURSE, PRETTY MISSY.
IT'LL WORK SO WELL,
YOUR SHOULDERS WILL FEEL
LIGHT AS A FEATHER.
YOU NEED THE PROOF?
GO AHEAD AND TRY IT.
- THANKS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
DRINK IT UP.
- WOW. IT'S A MIRACLE!
THEY FEEL JUST GREAT.
SO LIGHT.
- WHOA!
- REALLY.
THEY'RE SO LIGHT, SEE?
- I'M OFFERING THIS
TOAD OIL
AT A SPECIAL
DISCOUNT PRICE OF
3,000 YEN.
IT COSTS TWICE AS MUCH
AROUND THE PLANET JURAI AREA.
- OHH, REALLY?
WHAT A DEAL.
YOU'RE GOOD LOOKING
AND CONSCIENTIOUS
IN YOUR BUSINESS.
- AND YOU HAVE
A WEIRD WAY OF TALKING.
- HUH?
- ENOUGH MONKEY BUSINESS.
- HEY NOW.
WHAT MONKEY BUSINESS
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE NO MONKEYS.
- Both: RIGHT.
DO WE LOOK LIKE WE'RE
DOING MONKEY BUSINESS?
- ( murmurs )
OY. OBVIOUSLY.
- ( laughs )
OH, THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
IT JUST FEELS GREAT.
- HEY, WILL YOU
LET ME PLAY TOO?
- ( laughs )
OH, JUST A SECOND.
I'LL FINISH IN A MINUTE.
( laughs )
OH, I MAY GET
ADDICTED TO THIS.
- YO!
- COME TO THE HAUNTED MANSION,
FOLKS.
IT'S THE BEST OF ITS KIND.
THE TRICKS WE HAVE HERE,
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
SUPER TECHNOLOGY CREATED
BY THE BEST SCIENTIFIC GENIUS
IN THE UNIVERSE--!
- HELLO, WASHU.
HERE WE ARE.
- AHH.
AT LAST.
- HAUNTED MANSION, HUH?
- RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT POPPING IN
AND CHECKING IT OUT?
YOU'LL BE IMPRESSED,
YOUNG MAN.
- ( chuckles )
I'M SURE OF THAT.
WELL, I ACCEPT
YOUR INVITATION, WASHU.
- ALL RIGHT.
PARTY OF TWO COMING IN.
- SO JUST WHAT DO YOU
HAVE IN STORE FOR US?
- JUST LIKE IT SAYS:
"THE EIGHT WORST HELLS."
- OHH.
- SCARY.
- SO YOU MAKE SURE
YOU ENJOY YOURSELVES.
- IT'S KIND OF SMALL.
- ( laughs )
WELL, IT'S NOT SURPRISING.
YOU KNOW, WASHU TENDS TO
EXAGGERATE THINGS.
SO WE GO INSIDE THROUGH
THIS DOOR, I GUESS.
- I'M EXCITED.
- WHOA!
- WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
( screams )
WHAT IS THIS?
WHERE ARE WE?
- ( meows )
- WOW, IT'S A SEA
OF MAGMA.
- ( growls )
- WHOA!
- ( meows )
- WHAT'S THAT?  COULD IT BE
THE HELL POOL OF BLOOD MAYBE?
- THAT'S WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
- ( grunts )
PHEW.
THIS IS NOT FUNNY.
- TENCHI!
( murmurs )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
AAH!
- ( meows )
- OH, IT CAN'T BE.
- THE... HILL OF NEEDLES.
- IT LOOKS MORE LIKE
THE HIMALAYA OF NEEDLES.
WHOA!
- WHOA!
- ( grunts )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
SASAMI?
- YEAH. I'M OKAY.
- ( grunts )
WHAT WAS THAT--!
- ( Sasami screams )
- AAH!
- TENCHI, I'M SCARED!
- ( grunts )
- GO. GO!
HUH?
AAH!
- HEY.
GATHER AROUND, YOU PEOPLE.
- ( grunts )
- ( meows )
- ( whimpering )
- WOW.
YOU'VE MANAGED TO
COME OUT IN ONE PIECE.
- YEAH, WELL, WE CLEARED
ALL EIGHT STAGES ANYWAY.
- WELL, HOW WAS IT?
- BAD. AND SCARY.
TOO SCARY.
- STEP RIGHT UP AND
RELIEVE YOUR STRESS.
IT'S THE BEST THING FOR YOU.
COME ON, COME ON,
AND STEP RIGHT UP.
STEP RIGHT UP FOLKS,
AND TAKE A SHOT.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, STEP RIGHT UP HERE.
- EXCUSE ME, RYOKO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CAN'T YOU SEE?
IT'S A SHOOTING GALLERY.
- AND YOU HAD TO SET IT UP
RIGHT NEXT TO MINE?!
IT'S SABOTAGE!
- MAYBE.
NOW ASK ME IF I CARE.
- ( groans )
- HMM.
- IT'S GOING TO TAKE
MORE THAN WORDS
TO MAKE YOU CARE.
- HEY. OUCH OUCH OUCH
OUCH OUCH OUCH OUCH.
EXCUSE ME.
I NEED THESE FOR A MOMENT.
- HEY THERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( scoffs )
- HMM.
- ( crowd murmurs )
- ( groans )
- HMM?
- ( grunts )
- OHH!
( gulps )
( groans )
AAH!
- ( gasps )
HOW DARE YOU.
( grunts )
- HERE YOU GO.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
- WOW!
( giggles )
- ( chuckles )
- YOU'RE SELLING
COTTON CANDY NOW?
- YEAH. WE RAN OUT
OF THE INGREDIENTS
FOR THE FRIED NOODLES.
- I'M SORRY.
IT WAS RYO-OHKI'S FAULT,
WASN'T IT?
- IT'S OKAY.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
COTTON CANDY?
- WOW! WOULD I?!
- HERE. FOR YOU.
- AH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
( chews )
DELICIOUS!
- I GUESS IT'S A HIT,
HUH, SASAMI?
- MM-HMM.
- NOW, MIHOSHI, I KNOW WE
CAN KEEP SELLING LIKE THIS.
SO WORK HARD
AND KEEP 'EM COMING.
- COUNT ON ME.
WITH THIS ULTRA-HIGH SPEED
COTTON CANDY MAKER,
ESPECIALLY MADE BY WASHU,
I CAN HANDLE ANY
LARGE QUANTITY OF ORDERS.
- HUH?! SO IT WAS WASHU
WHO MADE THAT THING?
- YEAH, TENCHI.
THAT'S RIGHT.
- HEY, MIHOSHI, WATCH OUT.
BE CAREFUL.
- I AM. HUH?!
( screams )
- STOP THE MACHINE NOW!
- I CAN'T STOP IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
- WHAT?!
- OH NO!
- ( all scream )
- ( chuckles )
WELL IT SEEMS
WE ARE CONNECTED.
CONNECTED TO EACH OTHER
THROUGH THESE FAIRS, AREN'T WE?
- HMM. YEAH.
IT WAS AT A FAIR ON A PLANET
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD OF JURAI.
- YES. THAT WAS
MY VERY FIRST TIME
TO BE OUT AMONG COMMON PEOPLE
TO EXPERIENCE A FAIR.
- WOW.
- HEY, MISSY!
YOU THERE!
- HUH?
YOU MEAN ME?
- YES, YOU.
WELL NOW, AREN'T YOU
THE LUCKY ONE?
I JUST GOT A SHIPMENT
OF GREAT PRODUCTS.
HERE. I'LL SELL IT
TO YOU, MISSY,
AT A SPECIAL
DISCOUNT PRICE.
HERE.
- BUT I DON'T WANT IT.
- HEY NOW, DON'T BE SHY.
TAKE IT.
AND YOU'LL HAVE TO
PAY FOR IT, OF COURSE.
- OH!
HEY, WAIT!
GIVE ME BACK MY WALLET.
- OH, NO. NO REFUNDS
OR EXCHANGES.
YOU ARE SUCH A LIAR,
AYEKA.
- WHAT? A LIAR?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
ALL OF IT.
LISTEN.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED.
YES, IT WAS
A COLD, COLD NIGHT,
CHILLING ME TO THE BONES.
I HAD WORKED SO HARD
TO MAKE ALL THAT POTTERY
WITH MY OWN HANDS,
BUT NO ONE CAME TO BUY.
NO ONE AT ALL.
- CAN I HELP YOU?
OHH...
- YOU THERE!
TELL ME,
WHO GAVE YOU PERMISSION
TO DO BUSINESS HERE?
- HUH?
- YOU SEE,
THIS IS THE FAIR
TO PRAISE JURAI'S
ROYAL FAMILY.
SO I CAN'T ALLOW YOU
TO DO BUSINESS HERE.
CAN YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
- I GUESS.
- HA. LOOK AT THIS
SHODDY BOOTH.
- OH!
AWW.
OH, WHY ARE YOU SO MEAN?
- HOW DARE YOU MAKE UP
A STORY LIKE THAT.
YOUR MEMORY MUST BE
COMPLETELY ROTTEN.
- I'M TELLING YOU
JUST THE FACTS, YOU KNOW.
- WHERE ARE THE FACTS
IN YOUR STORY?
- IT'S ALL FACT.
EVERYTHING I SAID,
PRINCESS.
IT'S YOU WHO'S TELLING LIES.
YOU CAN'T GET BY
WITH ALL YOUR STORIES.
FACTS ARE FACTS,
AND PEOPLE CAN TELL, YOU KNOW?
MMM.
- REALLY.
YOU ARE SO HOPELESS!
IT IS NO USE TRYING
TO TALK TO YOU!
- SO WHO CARES?
I WANT TO MAKE YOU PAY
FOR WHAT YOU DID
TO ME BACK THEN.
- ( groans )
- ( crowd shouts )
- OH?
- HUH?
HUH?
- ( crowd screams )
- WHA--?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( both scream )
- ( giggles )
- SORRY, SASAMI.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A FUN EVENING AT THE FAIR,
BUT IT WAS
A REAL MESS.
YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED.
- MM-MM.
NO, I'M NOT.
I SURE AM NOT.
( chews )
DELICIOUS!
WOW!
SEE?
( chuckles )
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- MECHA-WASHU IS A ROBOT
INVENTED BY WASHU.
IT'S AN ALTER-EGO OF WASHU,
BUT THINGS GET MIXED UP
AND THIS POWERFUL ROBOT
ASSUMES MIHOSHI'S PERSONALITY
INSTEAD.
- AHEM!
- WHAT ARE YOU ON YOUR
HIGH HORSE ABOUT?
- WASHU'S BRAIN COMBINED
WITH MIHOSHI'S PERSONALITY?
IT MAY AS WELL BE THE MOST
POWERFUL IN THE UNIVERSE.
COMING UP NEXT IS
"NO NEED FOR A GENIUS."
THE BATTLE BETWEEN WASHU
AND MECHA-WASHU
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY
SPLENDID.