- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- YO!
- ( women chattering )
- ( meowing )
( yelps )
- ( laughter )
- THIS BATH HAS SO MUCH ROOM.
IT'S REALLY NICE, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH.
- ( giggles )
WELL, YOU KNOW YOU CAN COME OVER
AND USE IT ANYTIME YOU LIKE.
- AND SINCE WHEN IS THIS
YOUR PLACE, PRINCESS?
- UGH...
- WOW, THAT WOULD BE NICE.
WOULDN'T IT, KIYONE?
- HMM?
- WE'VE ONLY BEEN ABLE TO TAKE
A BATH ONCE EVERY THREE DAYS
SINCE THE PUBLIC BATHS
RAISED THEIR PRICES, RIGHT?
- ( groans ) I THOUGHT I TOLD
YOU TO KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT?!
- IN THAT CASE, YOU CAN COME
HERE EVERY DAY, IF YOU'D LIKE.
- LIKE I SAID, PRINCESS.
THIS ISN'T EVEN YOUR PLACE.
- REMEMBER, THIS IS NOT
YOUR PLACE EITHER.
- HEY, LET ME IN,
LET ME IN!
I WANNA TAKE A BATH
WITH YOU GIRLS!  HEY!
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GIVE IT UP, DAD?
( sighs )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( unintelligible speech )
LET'S GET UP HERE.
- ( gasps )
HUH?!
- AH, WELL,
IT'S YOU, TENCHI.
HEY, I'LL WASH YOUR BACK
AND YOU WASH MINE, DEAL?
- WOW!  I WANNA WASH
HIS BACK TOO.  ( gasps )
- ( girls scream )
- ( inhales deeply )
HUH?
THE KITCHEN?
- WASHU, WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
I THOUGHT THE BATH WAS IN A
DIFFERENT DIMENSION COMPLETELY.
HEY, WASHU!
- All: HUH?
- HUH?
- All: WHAT?
- WHAT THE HECK IS THIS THING?
- ( chuckles )
( cackles )
- YO!
- SO, THE BATHROOM WAS
IN FLUX, HUH?
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
OF THE DIMENSION TUNER.
I WAS JUST EXPERIMENTING
ON THAT.
- DIMENSION TUNER?
- OVER THERE, YOU SEE?
IT'S A CENTRAL PART
OF MY MACHINE.
- All: OHH...
- BUT, WHAT DOES
THIS MACHINE DO?
IT LOOKS SO HUGE.
- CONTROLS DIMENSION AND CAUSE
AND EFFECT. ( chuckles )
IT'S JUST MY BEST INVENTION
IN THE PAST 700 YEARS!
- RIGHT.  EXPLAIN IT AGAIN.
- IT DETERMINES VARIABLE FACTORS
IN TIME AND SPACE
BASED ON A CERTAIN CRITERIA.
- RIGHT...
NOW, WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- WITH THIS MACHINE
YOU CAN CREATE A CERTAIN NEXUS
FROM THE INFINITE POSSIBILITIES
THAT EXIST IN TIME AND SPACE!
UNDERSTAND NOW?
- All: NOT AT ALL, NO.
- AAH!  AARGH!
WHY IS IT SO DIFFICULT
TO UNDERSTAND?!
- ( mockingly ) WHY CAN'T YOU
EXPLAIN IT MORE CLEARLY?!
- LISTEN, PEOPLE, ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS WHAT IT DOES...
IT CHANGES THE WORLD
TO SUIT YOUR NEEDS!
IS THAT CLEAR ENOUGH FOR YOU?!
- All: WHAT?
- NO WAY.
- REALLY?
- WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE, WASHU, HUH?
- BUT I HAVE BEEN.
- SAY, I HAVE AN IDEA, WASHU.
DO YOU THINK I COULD
BORROW THIS MACHINE FOR AWHILE?
DO YOU?
- NOW, JUST A MINUTE.
- ( grunts )
- COULD YOU PLEASE LEND IT
TO ME, WASHU?
- HOLD ON!
I ASKED YOU FIRST, YOU--
- I HAVE TO USE IT FIRST!
- YOU ARE TOO SLOW.
- I TOLD YOU, I GET
TO USE IT FIRST.
- ( clearing throat )
- KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF!
- YOU WANNA USE THIS MACHINE
TO GET TENCHI, DON'T YOU?
- I AM NOT THAT SNEAKY!
GET OFF MY BACK!
NOW WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU COME IN HERE AND YOU--
- HEY, CUT IT OUT!
( clears throat )
FIRST OF ALL,
THIS INVENTION ISN'T FINISHED.
YOU CAN'T USE IT YET.
( huffs )
- Both: UH...
- I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S NOT FINISHED.
- AND I JUST WANNA SEE IT WORK.
- NO!
- CAN WE USE THIS
MACHINE, PLEASE?
- I JUST WANNA TRY IT.
I'M JUST CURIOUS, YOU KNOW?
- I SAID NO!
- I'D REALLY LIKE TO KNOW
HOW I ENDED UP IN THE KITCHEN.
- ( excited chatter )
- WOW, WHAT A MACHINE!
- TENCHI, I THINK
WE BETTER GET GOING.
- I THANK YOU FOR
HAVING US OVER.
- HEY, GIRLS, IT'S AWFULLY
LATE ALREADY, YOU KNOW, HUH?
WHY DON'T YOU STAY
OVER HERE TONIGHT?
- I DON'T WANNA BE A BURDEN.
- REALLY?  WE'D LOVE TO.
- HUH? ( growls )
- WE WERE HESITANT TO GO BACK
TO OUR APARTMENT,
BECAUSE WE HADN'T PAID
THE RENT FOR AWHILE, YOU KNOW?
- YOU ALWAYS SAY
ONE WORD TOO MANY!
( chuckles softly )
I GUESS WE'LL BE TAKING
YOUR OFFER.
- ( snoring )
- ( chuckles )
WASHU IS NOT HERE, HUH?
( chuckles )
YES, ALL RIGHT.
NOW I KNOW I SHOULDN'T LET
THIS USEFUL MACHINE
JUST SIT HERE, SHOULD I?
LET'S SEE, THE WAY TO
TURN THIS ON HAS TO BE... HMM.
IS THIS IT?
- ( whirring )
- OH, YES,
I THINK THAT'S IT.
THIS WORLD'S FOR YOU AND ME.
- FOR YOU AND WHOM, PRAY TELL?
- FOR TENCHI AND I, OF COURSE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
HUH?
OKAY, WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YOU'RE SO AWFULLY SNEAKY,
RYOKO.
- HA HA, I GUESS WE'RE
ALL JUST TRYING
TO CREATE OUR OWN IDEAL WORLD,
AREN'T WE?
- UHH...
OH, NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I WAS DOING.
I'LL TELL YOU
I WAS JUST TRYING TO STOP
RYOKO'S TREACHERY, THAT'S ALL.
- WHAT YOU WERE DOING,
WAS YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT
GETTING TENCHI
WITH THIS MACHINE.
- GO AHEAD, BE SELF-RIGHTEOUS.
- WOW.
( chuckles )
WHAT KIND OF WORLD
DO YOU WANT, RYO-OHKI?
- Both: HUH?  AAH!
- ( meowing )
- DON'T!
- SASAMI!
GET OUT OF MY WAY.
I CHOOSE--
- NOT SO FAST, AYEKA.
- ( both groan )
- LET ME GO!
- ( giggles )
THIS WAY KIYONE AND I
CAN ALWAYS BE PARTNERS.
NOW WOULDN'T THAT BE GREAT?
- ( shouts )
FORGET IT.
NO WAY.  I WANT A WORLD
TOTALLY DEVOID OF MIHOSHI!
AAH!
- A WORLD JUST FOR
TENCHI AND ME.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
- ( overlapping arguing )
- WAIT, I'M NOT KIDDING.
- ( rumbling )
- AAH!
- HUH?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- MM?
- ( all scream )
- ( gasping )
- HUH?
- WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THAT?
- OH, BOY...
HUH?  OH, NO!
MY INVENTION!
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY MACHINE?!
THE CONTROL PANEL'S
REALLY MESSED UP. HUH?
I CAN'T STOP IT NOW.
THE MACHINE IS TOTALLY
OUT OF MY CONTROL.
- ( all scream )
- LISTEN UP,
EVERYONE HERE WILL BE
TRAVELING THROUGH ENTANGLED
TIME AND SPACE VERY SOON.
IT'S POSSIBLE WE COULD ALL DRIFT
THROUGH MANY WORLDS FOREVER.
I'LL TRY TO FIX THIS DIMENSION--
- WASHU!
- WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO US NOW?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
- WASHU!
- THIS IS REALLY STRANGE.
- HUH?
- ( all scream )
- YO!
YO!
- ( all screaming )
- EVERYONE HERE
WILL BE TRAVELING
THROUGH ENTANGLED
TIME AND SPACE VERY SOON.
WE COULD ALL DRIFT THROUGH
MANY POSSIBLE WORLDS FOREVER.
- HUH?
- LADY AYEKA.
- LORD TENCHI.
YOU ARE HERE.
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
- JUST A MOMENT AGO.
I SUDDENLY FELT AN URGE
TO SEE YOU, LADY AYEKA.
- OH, TENCHI.
I AM FLATTERED.
- OH, AYEKA,
I MISSED YOU SO.
- TENCHI...
- ( thunder roars )
- A DEMON AT RASHOMON?
- YES, AYEKA. THE PURPOSE OF MY
JOURNEY WAS TO SEE THE EMPEROR.
HE ORDERED THAT I
SUBDUE THE DEMON
THAT HAS BEEN TERRORIZING
THE CAPITAL.
- THAT'S DANGEROUS.
- I HAVE TO
FOR OUR NATION.
PLEASE TRY TO UNDERSTAND,
AYEKA.
- OH, BE CAREFUL, TENCHI.
- THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX...
- MIHOSHI, KIYONE,
I REALLY APPRECIATE
THAT YOU CAME.
- MY PLEASURE.
- OH, DON'T MENTION IT, REALLY.
- MY FIANCE, LORD TENCHI,
IS ASSIGNED TO GO ON
AN EXPEDITION AGAINST
THE DEMON AT RASHOMON.
I AM SURE YOU'VE HEARD OF THIS.
- OH, CERTAINLY.
- YOU KNOW, IT HAPPENS
TO BE THE TALK OF THE TOWN.
- AHEM.
- UH?
- YOU KNOW OUR WEDDING
IS COMING UP,
AND I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT I WOULD DO
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS TO HIM.
( voice breaking )
I JUST DO NOT KNOW.
- OH, YOU MUST BE WORRIED.
- YOU MUST BE WORRIED.
YOU'LL BE AN OLD MAID
IF YOU MISS THIS OPPORTUNITY,
RIGHT?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- I WAS SAYING--
- OH OH!
UH, HOW MAY WE BE OF SERVICE?
- WELL, I WAS HOPING THAT
YOU TWO COULD HELP TENCHI
WITH HIS QUEST.
- Both: WHAT?!
- THE DEMON AT RASHOMON
IS KNOWN TO BE
THE MOST WICKED VILLAIN,
ISN'T SHE?
- SHE'S COMMITTED
NUMEROUS CRIMES,
AND ANYONE WHO EVER TRIED
TO CAPTURE HER
HAS NEVER COME BACK ALIVE.
- YOU TWO ARE THE MOST COMPETENT
POLICEMEN I KNOW.
PLEASE.
- UH...
- UH, WE ARE PUBLIC OFFICIALS
AND WE HAVE OTHER DUTIES
WE MUST FULFILL.
BUH-BYE.
- BYE!
- OH, WHAT A PITY.
I WAS GOING TO
MAKE YOU EXECUTIVES
AT THE POLICE DEPARTMENT,
IF YOU SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED
MY ASSIGNMENT.
- Both: HUH?
- OW!
- LADY AYEKA,
DO YOU REALLY MEAN THAT, HUH?
- OH, NO, I'M SCARED!
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
WE'LL DO IT
AND WILL NOT LET YOU DOWN.
- HUH?  REALLY?
HOW NICE.
- THE PUBLIC SAFETY
OF THE CAPITAL IS OUR BUSINESS
AS POLICE OFFICERS!
REST ASSURED
YOU WON'T BE DISAPPOINTED.
- OH, KIYONE...
- LADY AYEKA.
- ( crying )
I DON'T WANNA FIGHT THE DEMON!
- ( sighs )
HEY, RYOKO!
RYOKO, I KNOW YOU'RE UP THERE.
COME OUT.
- HMM?
- ( meows )
- AHH, TENCHI!
( chuckles )
- WHOA!
- I'M GLAD YOU CAME, TENCHI.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
ANYWHERE ELSE TODAY, DO YOU?
- UH...
- HMM?
- I'VE GOT BAD NEWS FOR YOU.
I WAS ORDERED TO SUBDUE,
CONQUER AND KILL THE DEMON
AT RASHOMON.
- OH, THAT'S GONNA BE TOUGH.
WELL, LET ME HELP YOU, TENCHI.
- WHAT ARE TALKING ABOUT?
YOU ARE THE DEMON.
- OH, SO I AM.
- ( Mihoshi crying )
- QUIT WASTING TIME.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
- I DON'T WANT TO!
THIS ISN'T A GOOD IDEA.
- OUR PROMOTIONS ARE AT STAKE.
WE'LL STAY AT THE
LOWEST RANK FOREVER
IF WE WASTE THIS
CHANCE, MIHOSHI.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
- I'LL BE EATEN BY THE MONSTER!
- STOP WHINING
AND GET OVER HERE!
- AAH!
- IT'S YOUR FAULT.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE COMMITTED
ONE CRIME AFTER ANOTHER.
- OH, WELL,
LET'S NOT WORRY ABOUT IT.
WHAT WILL BE WILL BE.
- RYOKO, TRY TO UNDERSTAND
MY POSITION, WILL YOU?
- THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
BECAUSE NOBODY KNOWS HOW
INTIMATE WE ARE WITH EACH OTHER,
DO THEY, TENCHI?
- DON'T TALK LIKE THAT.
TALK LIKE THAT CAN BE
VERY MISLEADING.
- WELL, YOU KNOW WE'VE ALREADY
COME TO THE POINT OF NO RETURN.
- WHAT?
- BUT I SUPPOSE YOU AND I...
- AAH!
- ...CAN JUST RUN AWAY.
WE COULD JUST
RUN AWAY RIGHT NOW, COULDN'T WE?
- HEY! ( groans )
- DON'T YOU THINK IT'S
A BRILLIANT IDEA?
LET'S JUST DO IT.
- CUT IT OUT.
STAY AWAY FROM ME. I DON'T
WANT ANYBODY TO SEE US TOGETHER.
- WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
- ( Mihoshi whimpers )
- CLIMB UP HERE.
LET'S GO, OKAY?
TENCHI, WE ARE HERE
AS YOUR BACKUP.
- NOW THAT WE'RE HERE,
YOU'LL DEFINITELY HAVE THE
UPPER HAND, TENCHI.
- HUH?
- ( both scream )
- TENCHI, YOU ARE--
- THE DEMON'S
SECRET BOYFRIEND, HUH?
- OH, NO, NOW REALLY,
THIS IS NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
- WELL, THERE.
SO NOW YOU KNOW.
- AAH!
- JUST DON'T LEAK
THIS INFORMATION
TO THE PRESS, THOUGH.
- ( Tenchi screams )
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR
UNDERSTANDING, KIYONE.
- WELL, WE DIDN'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
- DON'T LET AYEKA KNOW
ABOUT ANY OF THIS, PLEASE.
- OF COURSE NOT.
IF AYEKA FOUND OUT
ABOUT ANY OF THIS,
I'D BE IN BIG TROUBLE TOO,
YOU KNOW, TENCHI.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- I PASSED THE MESSAGE ON
TO MIHOSHI TOO,
SO THERE SHOULDN'T BE
ANY MIX-UPS.
- Mihoshi: IT WAS QUITE A SHOCK
TO ME, YOU KNOW?
- Both: HUH?!
- WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT TENCHI AND THAT DEMON
WERE AN ITEM, HUH?
IT'S SO SCANDALOUS,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I MEAN, THEY REALLY DID
SEEM VERY CLOSE.
- YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
CAN'T TELL--
- DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE, TENCHI?
- UH, SURE.
UH, AYEKA, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
AND SO I CAME TO
CHECK ON YOU, TENCHI.
SO, WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO
SAY FOR YOURSELF?
- ( nervous laughter )
YOU DON'T MEAN TO TELL ME YOU
REALLY BELIEVE ALL THAT STUFF?
- ( nervous chuckle )
YOU KNOW SHE'S NUTS.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I'M SO CERTAIN.
- KIYONE, IF I FIND OUT
THAT YOU ARE LYING,
I WILL MAKE SURE
YOU GET DEMOTED.
- WHAT?  OH, NO.
DEMOTED?
- UH-HUH.
- TENCHI, COME ON.
IT'S TIME TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( Tenchi and Kiyone scream )
- RYOKO, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- WHAT, LIKE WE DIDN'T
PLAN THIS?
- ( yelps )
- WE DECIDED TO RUN AWAY
TOGETHER, YOU AND I, DIDN'T WE?
I COULDN'T WAIT ANY LONGER, SO I
WENT AHEAD AND PACKED MY STUFF.
- ALL RIGHT, TENCHI...
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME WHO
IS THIS WOMAN.
- WOMAN?  UM...
- WAIT A MINUTE.
WHO ARE YOU?
- WHO AM I?
I AM TENCHI'S OFFICIAL FIANCE,
THAT'S ALL.
- WELL, I GUESS THAT MAKES ME
HIS OFFICIAL MISTRESS THEN.
- HMM?
- AAH, NOT TRUE!
- UH, ARE YOU WHAT PEOPLE
CALL THE DEMON OF RASHOMON?
- THERE YOU GO.
SO, YOU ALREADY KNEW ABOUT US.
DON'T WE MAKE
A FANTASTIC COUPLE?
- ( groans )
- ( grunts )
- JUST WHAT DOES THIS WOMAN
HAVE THAT I DON'T?
CAN YOU TELL ME THAT, TENCHI?
HUH?  CAN YOU?
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING TO MY MAN?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOUR MAN?
HE'S NOT YOUR MAN!
- AND GET OFF YOUR HIGH HORSE!
- HEY, NOW!  WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?
- YOU'RE THE GIRL
WHO GOT DUMPED BY TENCHI.
- ( groans )
- YOU JUST DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO STOP!
- HMM...
- EVERYTHING IS
TOTALLY MESSED UP.
- THE ONLY THING LEFT FOR ME
TO DO IS TO ELIMINATE
THE MULTIPLE WORLDS ONE BY ONE.
- ( shouts )  AAH!
YOU HOLD STILL
AND I'LL FINISH YOU MYSELF.
- WHOA!  WATCH OUT!
- HA, I'LL HOLD STILL.
- ( growls )
- ( chuckles )
- PREPARE TO DIE!
THAT WON'T HURT ME.
- HERE!
- AAH!
- ( Tenchi screams )
- HERE.
- ( screams )
- HERE'S THE DEMON.
COME ON, RIGHT HERE.
- YOU ARE A DEMON,
AREN'T YOU?!
- LADY AYEKA,
YOU MUST CALM DOWN.
- YOU MUST BE DEMOTED.
- WHEWIE!  THERE, NOW.
THIS DIMENSION IS ENCLOSED.
LET'S ELIMINATE THE FIRST ONE.
CANCEL.
- KIYONE, GET A HOLD
OF YOURSELF.
- TENCHI, LET'S RUN AWAY
TOGETHER.
- I TOLD YOU, LORD TENCHI
IS MY FIANCE.
- ( girls growl )
- HUH?
- ( all screaming )
- THUS BEGIN THE SPECIAL
EPISODES OF "TENCHI MUYO."
- TENCHI AND THE WHOLE GANG
HAVE TRAVELED THROUGH
TIME AND SPACE.
WHAT KIND OF WORLD
DO YOU THINK AWAITS THEM NEXT?
WILL THEY EVER BE ABLE TO COME
BACK TO THEIR ORIGINAL WORLD?
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO THEM?
- WATCH "TENCHI: GENESIS,
JOURNEY THROUGH TIME AND SPACE,
PART TWO" AND FIND OUT.
- Both: WE LOOK FORWARD
TO SEEING YOU THERE.
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Tenchi:
IN THE HIGH SCHOOL WORLD,
RYOKO IS A JUVENILE DELINQUENT
AND AYEKA IS CLASS PRESIDENT,
WHEN A MYSTERIOUS GIRL APPEARS.
- TRANSFORM INTO
PRETTY SAMMY NOW.
OKAY, RYO-OHKI,
DUKE 'EM, DUKE 'EM.
GO ALONG THE RACE.
SAMMY DAVIS, JR. BOILED CHICKEN!
- WHAT IS THE TRUE IDENTITY
OF PRETTY SAMMY?
COMING NEXT IS "JOURNEY THROUGH
TIME AND SPACE, PART TWO."