- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- WOW.
THIS IS REALLY DELICIOUS.
MM-MM.
( chewing )
( gasps )
- HERE, MISS AYEKA.
BE CAREFUL BECAUSE
IT'S REALLY VERY HOT.
- OH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
TENCHI.
( grunts )
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
IS YOUR HAND ALL RIGHT,
MISS AYEKA?
- HEY.
ARE WE GONNA EAT
OR ARE WE GONNA FLIRT?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- REALLY, RYOKO.
YOU ARE JUST IMAGINING THINGS.
- YEAH, WELL,
I HOPE SO.
- YES.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
I'M SURE.
MMM!
DELICIOUS.
- YO!
- DAMMIT.
THAT AYEKA HAS GOTTEN
TOO CLOSE TO MY TENCHI LATELY.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH HER
EVERY MINUTE.
- ( meows )
- HMM.
- WELL NOW.
I SEE IT'S FINALLY BORN.
- WHA--?!
OHH.
WHOA.
OH-- WHOA!
( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- HUH?
( chuckles )
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
SEEN YOU AROUND HERE BEFORE.
HAVE YOU COME TO PAY
RESPECT TO THE SHRINE?
- I'M SASAMI.
I'VE COME TO FIND
MY OLDER SISTER.
- SO YOU'RE CALLED SASAMI,
HUH?
THAT'S SURE A CUTE NAME.
- ( giggles )
HMM!
- WHOA!
HUH?  UH...
HELLO?  EXCUSE ME?
SASAMI?  HELLO?
HUH.
- HMM?
WHAT'S WRONG, TENCHI?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE JUST SEEN A GHOST.
DID YOU MEET A LEPRECHAUN
IN THE WOODS?
- I THINK I DID,
ACTUALLY.
- HMM?
TENCHI,
THE GIRL YOU SAW,
SHE MAY NOT BE A PHANTOM
OR A MAGICAL LEPRECHAUN.
- YOU CAN TELL JUST BY
HEARING MY STORY, GRANDPA?
- HMM.
WELL, IT'S FAIRLY EASY
FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME
WHO HAS EXPERIENCE WITH
THIS SORT OF THING.
- WOW!
I'M IMPRESSED!
- HMM.
NOW I SEE HER
IN MY MIND'S EYE.
OH, SHE HAS HER HAIR
TIED ON BOTH SIDES.
- WOW, GRANDPA.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I SAW!
- AND SHE HAS SOME
FRECKLES ON HER CHEEKS.
- MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
YEAH, RIGHT, FRECKLES!
- TENCHI!
SHE'LL SHOW UP HERE
VERY SOON.
- WHAT?! REALLY?!
- SO...
YOU ENJOY COOKING,
HEY, SASAMI?
- OH YEAH.
I COOK ALL THE TIME.
- OOH!
- JUST LIKE I SAID.
- OH, HI.
- SO, YOU KNOW EACH OTHER,
HUH?
GETTING PRETTY QUICK WITH
THE GIRLS THERE, TENCHI.
- HOW COME SASAMI IS HERE?
- BECAUSE SASAMI IS THE
LITTLE SISTER OF AYEKA,
AND SHE'S COME TO
TAKE AYEKA HOME.
- OHH!
AYEKA'S YOUR SISTER.
- ( giggles )
- SASAMI?
- AYEKA!
( laughs )
- SASAMI, HOW DID YOU
GET HERE BY YOURSELF?
SO, THIS IS THE END
OF MY HOLIDAY.
- All: CHEERS!
- ( glasses clink )
- OH, YOU CAN'T IMAGINE
HOW HAPPY I AM.
NOW I CAN FINALLY GO HOME.
- I'M GLAD FOR YOU,
MIHOSHI.
- NOW DIG RIGHT IN.
HAVE SOME DRINKS AND EAT
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
YOU AND AYEKA ARE OUR
GUESTS OF HONOR TONIGHT.
- THANK YOU ALL
SO VERY MUCH.
- ( laughs )
- MISS AYEKA.
- HMM?
( sighs )
- HEY, RYOKO,
IS THAT ALL YOU CAN EAT?
- I DON'T HAVE MUCH
OF AN APPETITE TONIGHT.
- YOU MUST HAVE EATEN
TOO MANY SWEET POTATOES, RYOKO.
- BUT I REALLY CRAVE
SOME PICKLES AND ICE CREAM.
- PICKLES AND...
( gasps )
RYOKO, MY GOODNESS,
CAN IT MEAN THAT
YOU ARE PREGNANT?!
- ( all gasp )
- I THOUGHT YOU'D BEEN PUTTING
ON SOME WEIGHT LATELY.
- THEN THAT MUST BE IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT CAUSES PREGNANCY,
DON'T YOU?
- WELL, YES.
- WOW. I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE THE BABY.
- MM!
( groans )
( gags )
- ( baby cries )
- THE BABY IS BORN.
THE BABY I MADE
WITH TENCHI.
- ( all gasp, scream )
- WELL DONE, TENCHI!
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU WERE
RATHER SLOW TO MATURE,
BUT NOW I'M SO HAPPY
TO SEE YOU'VE GROWN
INTO A HEALTHY MAN!
I'M PROUD OF YOU,
TENCHI.
- CONGRATULATIONS,
- I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
- ( both laugh )
- IT'S A MISTAKE,
I TELL YOU!
RYOKO, YOU BETTER
TELL THE TRUTH RIGHT NOW,
I'M NOT KIDDING!
- OOH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE SO EMBARRASSED,
TENCHI, DADDY.
- SO, I GUESS I'M A GREAT
GRANDFATHER NOW, AREN'T I?
- OOH!
MY FIRST GRANDCHILD.
- ( groans )
MISS RYOKO!
YOU DO NOT REALLY EXPECT US
TO BELIEVE THAT EGG
IS YOURS, NOW DO YOU!
- WELL I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU CAN BE SO
VERY CRUEL TO ME.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
IT'S SO CRUEL TO SAY
SUCH A THING.
POOR RYOKO.
- OH, AYEKA'S JUST
TRYING TO PICK A FIGHT
SO SHE CAN RUIN THAT
SPECIAL HAPPY FEELING
WE ALL SHARE.
- AND YOU ARE ANNOYING
LORD TENCHI.
- YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW MEN ARE.
HE'S REALLY VERY HAPPY INSIDE.
- ( groans )
- OH, NO I'M NOT!
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I WILL NEVER BE CONVINCED
IT'S YOURS UNLESS I SEE PROOF.
- IF YOU MUST KNOW,
TENCHI AND I MADE LOVE,
AND THIS EGG HERE WAS BORN.
WHAT OTHER PROOF
DO YOU NEED?
- MADE LOVE?
( stammers )
WE'LL SEE WHAT KIND OF
EGG IT IS WHEN WE BREAK IT!
- NO, YOU WON'T.
STOP IT, STOP IT,
STOP IT, STOP IT.
HEY, STOP IT!
- OH, PLEASE, AYEKA.
- AAH!
( gasps )
- ( all gasp )
- OH NO.
THE EGG IS--
THE EGG IS SMASHED.
- OH.
- ( stutters )
MY FIRST GRANDCHILD.
- ( all gasp )
- ( meows )
- WOW.
- YO!
- ( giggles )
MY DEAR,
OUR FIRST GRANDCHILD IS BORN.
WELL, SHE'S NOT
THE TYPICAL KIND
YOU NORMALLY WOULD EXPECT,
BUT SHE'S HEALTHY
AND SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE TENCHI.
- I FAIL TO SEE
THE RESEMBLANCE!
- HERE.
- ( meows )
- A PERFECT MATCH.
- SASAMI...
- OH, WOW.  IT'S TRUE.
- TENCHI, YOU MAKE SURE
YOU RAISE HER WELL.
- DAD.
- ( meows )
- ARE YOU HUNGRY?
WOULD YOU LIKE THIS?
- ( sniffs )
( chews, meows )
( meows )
- ( laughs )
SHE NEEDS A NAME,
DOESN'T SHE?
I KNOW!
WHAT ABOUT TENKO,
THE CHILD OF TENCHI
AND RYOKO?
- ( spits )
IT'S NOT MY CHILD!
( crying )
- OH, SORRY.
RIGHT.  WELL THEN,
WHAT SHOULD WE NAME HER?
- RYO-OHKI.
- HUH?
OH, GOOD MORNING, RYOKO.
I'VE GIVEN HER THE NAME
RYO-OHKI.
- RYO-OHKI?
OH, NOW IF I REMEMBER
CORRECTLY,
I THINK THAT'S THE NAME
OF YOUR SPACESHIP, RYOKO.
- ( meows )
- AH, I'M IMPRESSED
YOU REMEMBER THAT.
- ( gasps )
THAT MEANS THAT...
THAT MEANS THAT YOU MUST REALLY
LIKE THE NAME OF RYO-OHKI.
( giggles )
- ( meows )
- ( crying )
- WOW.
SO THIS IS YOUR SPACESHIP,
SASAMI?
- WELL, I GUESS
IT'S TIME TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
I'LL MISS YOU.
I'LL BE GLAD TO
ESCORT YOU PART-WAY,
IF YOU WANT?
- ( scoffs )
WITHOUT A SHIP?
- HMM.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
RYO-OHKI.  WHA--?
- ( meows )
- BAHH!
- ( chews, meows )
- HEY NOW.
KNOCK IT OFF.
I'LL LET YOU EAT
ALL YOU WANT LATER.
- AH.
SO IT'S JUST
AS I SUSPECTED.
SHE IS A CHILD OF RYO-OHKI,
ISN'T SHE?
SHE IS THE NEW RYO-OHKI.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
MISS AYEKA?
- HM.
I'LL SHOW YOU!
- ( meows )
- ( grunts )
- WHOA!
- ( meows )
- All: WOW!
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW,
RYO-OHKI IS A SPACESHIP.
- WELL, LET'S GO AHEAD
AND MOVE 'EM OUT.
- NOT WITH YOU,
I ASSURE YOU.
- OH, PLEASE?
IT WOULD BE SUCH A HELP.
YOU KNOW, I'M TOLD IT'S NOT
AS SAFE AS IT USED TO
BE AROUND HERE.
- YIPPEE!
RYO-OHKI'S COMING
PART-WAY WITH US.
- SASAMI, MIHOSHI,
WE ARE LEAVING.
- WAIT FOR ME,
AYEKA.
- PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND.
OH, RYOKO,
I'M COUNTING ON YOU
TO BEAT UP THE SPACE PIRATE
IF YOU SEE HER, OKAY?
- CAN YOU BELIEVE
SHE HAS COMPLETELY FORGOTTEN
THAT I AM THE SPACE PIRATE?
- VERY EASILY.
- ( meows )
- BYE.
NOW YOU BEHAVE YOURSELVES.
- GOSH.
I CAN NO LONGER SEE
TENCHI'S HOUSE FROM HERE.
- ( sighs )
UH...
I COULD HAVE...
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING,
AYEKA?
- OH...
NO, NOTHING.
- I BET YOU WERE THINKING
ABOUT TENCHI, WEREN'T YOU?
- WELL, I--
- YOU'RE BLUSHING.
AYEKA, I KNEW IT.
♪ YOU WERE IN LOVE
WITH TENCHI. ♪
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
SILLY?
- WHAT?!
YOU, MISS AYEKA?
- UH, MIHOSHI, YOU TOO?
- I GUESS THAT'S WHY
YOU HAVE THINGS LIKE THIS
IN YOUR LUGGAGE.
- WOW.
- IT'S JUST A SOUVENIR
PICTURE.
- COME NOW,
DON'T BE SHY ABOUT IT.
- WHY NOT COME
RIGHT OUT AND SAY IT?
- YOU SHOULD!
YOU SHOULD. GO ON, SAY IT!
- OH, YOU'RE IMPOSSIBLE.
OH, DON'T STARE
AT ME LIKE THAT, PLEASE.
IF YOU ONLY KNEW.
I JUST-- OH...
- HELLO?
- OH, NO, LORD TENCHI.
- EXCUSE ME?
- HUH? UHH...
- SORRY, DID I DO
SOMETHING WRONG?
- OH, LORD TENCHI.
- LISTEN, AYEKA,
I BET YOU HAVE
TONS OF SUITORS BACK HOME.
AM I RIGHT?
SO, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LEAVE TENCHI TO ME THEN?
HUH?
- LISTEN, LORD TENCHI...
I AM AYEKA, THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND I HAVE
MANY OBLIGATIONS, TENCHI.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- SO YOU SEE, I JUST CAN'T
STAY ON THE EARTH FOREVER.
- I KNOW.
- I ENJOYED EVERY MINUTE
I SPENT ON THE EARTH, TENCHI.
I CLOSE MY EYES
AND I CAN REMEMBER ALL THE
WONDERFUL THINGS,
LIKE THE BEAUTIFUL AUTUMN LEAVES
I WATCHED WITH YOU,
THE DELICIOUS TASTE OF
THE SWEET POTATO YOU GAVE ME.
- MISS AYEKA.
- OKAY, OKAY.  THAT'S ABOUT
ENOUGH OF THAT, YOU TWO.
- I WILL NEVER EVER
FORGET YOU, LORD TENCHI.
- NOR WILL I.
- LORD TENCHI, I--
THE FEELING
I HAVE FOR YOU...
- HUH?
- HMM?
- NO.
IT'S NOTHING, TENCHI.
- LET HER GO, TENCHI.
COME ON.
- MISS AYEKA,
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
AND HAVE A SAFE
JOURNEY HOME.
- I--
I THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FAREWELL, LORD TENCHI.
BE GOOD.
FOREVER AND EVER.
( crying )
I DID THE RIGHT THING.
- BLEHH!
- WE ARE NOW PREPARING
FOR FINAL ACCELERATION.
- PREPARATION COMPLETED.
WE AWAIT YOUR ORDERS,
PRINCESS AYEKA.
- FULL SPEED TO
PLANET JURAI.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HUH?
- OH, WHAT'S THAT
CARROT FOR, SASAMI?
- THAT'S THE CARROT
RYO-OHKI WAS EATING
A FEW MINUTES GO.
- ( meows )
- NOW LET'S GO BACK TO OUR
LITTLE LOVE NEST, TENCHI.
AHH?
- ( meows )
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( meows )
- ( both grunt )
- ( alarm blares )
- ( both gasp )
- RED ALERT!
RED ALERT!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI IS HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR OUR SHIP.
- LOOK OUT, AYEKA!
- WHAT?!
- ( meows )
- UH...
- WHAT?
- ( meows )
- WHY DOES IT HAVE TO
BE LIKE THIS?
( sighs )
- ( meows )
- WOW, DELICIOUS.
- I'M JUST GLAD
I'M STILL ALIVE.
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GROUNDED HERE ON EARTH
FOR AWHILE.
IF ONLY SASAMI HAD NOT
FOUND THAT CARROT UP THERE.
- HERE, MISS AYEKA.
BUT BE CAREFUL BECAUSE WELL,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- AH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- HEY HEY HEY HEY!
LISTEN, PRINCESS,
WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- NOTHING.  NOTHING AT ALL
AS YOU CAN SEE THAT, CAN'T YOU?
- NOTHING, HUH?!
- AND ANYWAY,
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- HERE, TENCHI.
IT'S GOOD.
- AHH!
MM!
- I'LL HAVE THE NEXT ONE.
- OKAY.
THERE.
- ( chews )
- Both: SASAMI!
( both scoff )
- ( music playing )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A BOOT
OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN
AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY
YOU'LL NEVER BE A GODDESS ♪
♪ LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ WHO WILL ALWAYS
WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG
AND I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY? ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE ♪
♪ TILL THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE,
HOW YOU WILL MOAN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- AN ANCIENT MONSTER
IS SEALED IN THE MASAKI SHRINE.
LEGEND HAS IT THAT
IT BRINGS HORRENDOUS DISASTERS
TO THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
HEY, RYOKO,
ARE YOU LISTENING OR WHAT?
- OOPS, SORRY.
I'VE BROKEN THE SEAL.
- WHAT?!
- HEY, WHAT KIND OF CREATURE
IS THIS MONSTER ANYWAY?
( gasps )
OH, NO. NOT THIS ONE!
- THE BIGGEST TROUBLE
THE UNIVERSE HAS EVER SEEN
IS RESURRECTED
IN OUR NEXT EPISODE,
"NO NEED FOR MONSTERS!"
- IT'S INDISPUTABLY SCARY.