- ♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN,
POOR YOU ♪
- ( man rapping )
- ♪ THE DAY YOU SEE HER,
A LOVELY STRANGER ♪
♪ YOU ONLY PRAY THAT SOON
YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU'LL KNOW HER NAME ♪
- ♪ YOU FINALLY TOUCH HER ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE IN DANGER ♪
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
YOU FEEL THE PAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOUR EMOTIONS
WILL OVERTAKE YOU ♪
♪ YOU LOOK FOR HEAVEN
IN HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ HER BIG BROWN EYES ♪
- ♪ BUT SHE'S NO ANGEL
AND SHE'LL FORSAKE YOU ♪
♪ IT SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY GREAT SURPRISE ♪
- ♪ OOH OOH OOH ♪
- ♪ PASSION ISN'T
REALLY HAPPINESS ♪
♪ THERE IS TROUBLE
IN HER SWEET CARESS ♪
♪ LOST IN CONFUSION ♪
♪ YOU'LL DROWN IN DELUSION ♪
♪ IF YOU DON'T RUN ♪
♪ GET READY,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA HURT YOU,
TILL YOUR HEART IS DYING ♪
♪ CAN'T ESCAPE IT,
AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING ♪
♪ AIN'T NO EXCEPTION,
LOVE WILL LEAVE YOU CRYING TOO ♪
♪ TILL YOU'RE A BROKEN MAN ♪
♪ POOR YOU. ♪
- ( man rapping )
- SONIA...
- Ayeka: THERE IS A LEGEND
OF AN IMPERIAL SON
THAT HAS BEEN TOLD
ON THE PLANET JURAI.
HE WAS THE BEST SWORDSMAN
EVER SEEN
AND GIFTED WITH AN
UNMATCHED MASTERY
OF JURIA'S POWER.
HE WAS COMPASSIONATE
AND AFFECTIONATE.
EVERYBODY ADORED HIM.
BUT HE SIMPLY VANISHED
WITHOUT A TRACE
BEFORE ASCENDING
TO THE THRONE.
HIS WHEREABOUTS
WERE TOTALLY UNKNOWN.
HIS NAME WAS YOSHO.
THAT IS THE LEGEND
OF THE CROWN-PRINCE
THAT HAS BEEN HANDED DOWN
FOR GENERATIONS
ON THE PLANET JURAI.
- YO!
- AH.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THERE'S
NOTHING QUITE LIKE
SOME QUALITY TIME
WITH FAMILY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS THE BEST.
- IF WE'RE ALL FAMILY,
TENCHI AND I
ARE HUSBAND AND WIFE, HUH?
- NO, OF COURSE NOT!
- ( chuckles )
- HEY, THIS IS NOT A SITCOM.
WE HAVE MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
TO THINK ABOUT, DON'T WE?
- CALM DOWN, TENCHI.
- BUT GRANDPA--
- LOOK THERE.
TENCHI, THAT SUPERNOVA
IS JUST GORGEOUS,
ISN'T IT?
- OH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- HOW CAN YOU BE SO COMPOSED
WHEN THERE'S NOTHING
BUT ENDLESS SPACE
RIGHT OUTSIDE OUR WINDOWS.
- Nobuyuki: YOU SHOULD BE
THANKFUL TO WASHU.
WE ONLY HAVE OUR HOUSE
BECAUSE SHE FIXED IT.
- Washu:
THE HOUSE HAD BEEN COMPRESSED.
ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS RESTORE IT,
LIKE ADDING WATER
TO DEHYDRATED FOOD.
- Sasami: IT'S LUCKY THE HOUSE
WAS JUST THE PERFECT SIZE
FOR YAGAMI'S CARGO BAY.
- Ayeka: THANKS TO WASHU,
WE HAVE ENOUGH BEDDING
FOR EVERYONE.
- HI THERE, KIYONE,
I BROUGHT YOU SOME TEA.
- THANK YOU, SASAMI.
- SOMEHOW, THAT VIEW JUST
DOESN'T HELP ME RELAX,
NOT AT ALL.
- HOW ARE YOU GUYS FEELING?
ANY BETTER?
- MY ENERGY CIRCUIT IS NOT YET
COMPLETELY RECHARGED.
- I TRANSFORMED YOU BACK
TO NORMAL SIZE.
WOULD IT HURT YOU SO MUCH
TO SHOW ME A LITTLE GRATITUDE?
- WE WOULD ALL HAVE
BEEN BETTER OFF
IF THEY HAD REMAINED
IN THEIR COMPACT SIZE.
I THINK THEY TAKE UP
TOO MUCH SPACE.
- I WOULD NOT LIKE THAT.
- BEING CONDENSED ONCE
WAS ENOUGH.
- ( beeping )
- GAAH!
ATTENTION, EVERYBODY,
REPORT TO THE BRIDGE AT ONCE.
HMM, HEY, EVERYONE,
CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME?
I NEED EVERYONE
UP ON THE BRIDGE!
HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?!
HMM, I WONDER
WHAT'S GOING ON, SASAMI.
- YEAH.
- ( music plays )
- Kiyone: MIHOSHI, ANSWER ME!
HEY, ANYBODY HOME?!
- Ryoko: ( singing )
♪ MAYBE THEY'RE RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT ♪
♪ TO GIVE YOUR
WINNING CHARMS A TRY ♪
♪ MOST PEOPLE
THINK I'M A LOON ♪
♪ BECAUSE I'M SUCH A BEAUTY ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ BUT, HONEY, TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I JUST MIGHT ♪
♪ BECAUSE YOU'RE SUCH A CUTIE,
OH-OH ♪
♪ DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT
CATCHING YOUR TRAIN ♪
♪ I GOT A HOTEL ROOM
AND I WANT TO EXPLAIN ♪
- HA HA.
- ♪ TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT ♪
♪ I AM GOING TO HAVE YOU ♪
- RYOKO, GREAT!
( laughs )
- ♪ COME ON, BABY,
LET'S GET IT ON ♪
- ♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
IT'S CHRISTMAS TIME ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ BE MY PRESENT ♪
♪ ALL NIGHT LONG ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY,
DON'T BE A SQUARE ♪
♪ THE LIQUOR STORE
IS OPEN NOW ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY,
OPEN LIKE MY HEART. ♪
- Kiyone: HELLO?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CAN'T YOU HEAR ME? HELLO?
WHAT ON EARTH COULD
THEY BE DOING?
- ( clapping )
- ( music plays )
- ♪ OH, I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ YOU'VE NEVER KNOWN ♪
♪ SOMEONE LIKE ME ♪
♪ SO WITTY AND
SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ OH, I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ JUST TRY TO FIND
A HOLD WITH ME ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE LOOKING FOR ♪
♪ A NEEDLE IN
A HAYSTACK ♪
- HMPH.
- ( snickers )
- ♪ NO, I CAN'T EVEN SAY ♪
♪ THE HALF OF
WHAT I WANT TO SAY ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T ♪
♪ EVEN SAY HALF
BECAUSE I AM SO MODEST ♪
♪ SO NOW I SAY TO YOU ♪
♪ YOU 700-YEAR-OLD
MUMMY WOMAN ♪
♪ I ENVY YOUR ♪
♪ INCREDIBLE BLUNTNESS. ♪
- HMPH.
- COULDN'T YOU HEAR ME CALLING?
- WHAT? OUT OF FUEL?
- UGH, RIGHT.
YAGAMI'S RUNNING OUT OF FUEL.
- SO DOES ANYONE KNOW
A GAS STATION AROUND HERE?
LET'S GO AND GET SOME MORE.
- I WOULDN'T BE
CALLING A MEETING
IF WE COULD AFFORD THAT.
- AH, A FINANCIAL CRISIS.
- NOBODY BROUGHT
ANY MONEY WITH THEM, HUH?
- NOW, WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
I THOUGHT WE HAD SOME
PETTY CASH WITH US.
- YEAH, WE SPENT IT ON THAT,
DIDN'T WE?
- All: HUH?
- OH, YOU MEAN WE HAVE
A CRITICALLY IMPORTANT MISSION
TO UNCOVER A CONSPIRACY
ON PLANET JURAI
AND WE SPENT OUR MONEY
ON A KARAOKE MACHINE?!
- YEAH, I WANT TO KNOW WHO
BOUGHT THAT STUPID THING ANYWAY?
- Washu:
IT WAS YOU, RYOKO.
- HOW'D YOU KNOW?
- RYOKO, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- BUT YOU WERE GETTING INTO
SINGING WITH THAT MACHINE
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE, WEREN'T YOU?
- THE BOTTOM LINE
IS THAT WE HAVE TO
EARN SOME MONEY AS WE GO.
OTHERWISE, WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT
TO PLANET JURAI.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME
I HAVE TO GET A JOB
WHILE I'M ON THIS TRIP?
- Newscaster: PRINCESS AYEKA AND
HER GROUP ARE STILL AT LARGE.
POLICE SAY THE SUSPECTS
MAY HAVE STOPPED AT
THE PLANET CONCORD
AND ARE DOING THEIR BEST
TO SEARCH FOR THE CRIMINALS
IN THE SURROUNDING AREA.
POLICE ARE
ALSO INVESTIGATING
ANY POSSIBLE REASONS
FOR THIS DETOUR.
- LET'S GO KEN-OHKI.
( thoughts ):
RYOKO, THIS TIME YOU'RE MINE.
I WILL NEVER LET ANYBODY ELSE
CATCH YOU.
- FROM HEADQUARTERS
TO ALL PATROL SHIPS,
FROM HEADQUARTERS
PRINCESS AND AYEKA
ARE STILL AT LARGE.
PLEASE REMAIN ON FULL ALERT.
- Kamidake: COME ON IN.
STOP BY AND HAVE A DRINK.
- WE'RE OFFERING
SPECIAL PRICES
DURING OUR GRAND OPENING.
- LOW PRICES FOR
A GREAT TIME
WITH DRINKS AND
KARAOKE-SING-ALONG.
HEY, MISTER!
- PLEASE COME ON IN.
DON'T BE SHY.
- YEAH, COME ON, IT'S GREAT.
- GO ON IN.
YOU'LL HAVE A GREAT TIME.
- IT'S A FUN PLACE.
- DON'T BE AFRAID.
- SIT THIS CUSTOMER, PLEASE.
- WELCOME TO OUR PUB.
HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
PLEASE FOLLOW ME
RIGHT THIS WAY, SIR.
- AH, UH, WAIT--
WAIT A MINUTE.
I WASN'T GONNA-- OH!
- THE HOSTESS WILL BE
RIGHT WITH YOU.
- UH, HEY, LISTEN--
- HOW ARE YOU THIS EVENING?
I'M THE OWNER OF THIS PUB.
MY NAME IS AYEKA.
- YEAH, RIGHT, UH--
- WE HAVE A LOT OF
VERY PRETTY GIRLS AT THIS PUB.
WANT KIND OF GIRL
WOULD YOU LIKE?
- UH, LISTEN. I WAS JUST
PASSING BY. I REALLY DON'T--
- OH, REALLY?
YOU LIKE A QUIET
AND OBEDIENT TYPE.
WELL, ALL RIGHT THEN.
- HUH?
- ONE MOMENT PLEASE, RYOKO.
WILL YOU ATTEND TABLE FIVE?
- UH-HUH.
- YOU KNOW I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
- DON'T WORRY.
LEAVE IT TO ME.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH? WELL, UM--
- WE HAVE ANOTHER CUSTOMER.
- HUH?
- COME ON, DRINK UP.
OH YEAH!
( gulping )
HEY, WE NEED SOME MORE DRINKS
AROUND HERE.
PEOPLE, LET'S GO.
- UH.
- AND HERE ARE THE DRINKS
YOU ORDERED, MISTER.
- ( groans )
- NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
- ( gulping )
- AND HERE'S THE SCOTCH AND
WATER YOU ORDERED, MISTER.
- UH, THANK YOU
SO VERY MUCH.
- HEY, WE'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED.
COME ON.
- WOW.
YOU SURE CAN DRINK LIKE
A FISH, CAN'T YOU?
- UGH!
PEOPLE THOUGHT I WAS GONNA BE
AN EXECUTIVE AT GALAXY POLICE,
BUT NOW...
LOOK AT
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO ME!
- ( both sigh )
- YO!
YO!
- STEP RIGHT UP
AND STEP RIGHT IN.
- WE HAVE ALL THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRLS.
- AND THAT'S THE TRUTH.
IT'S A PARADISE.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
- Both: HUH?
- ( laughs )
( gulping )
- OH THIS IS GREAT, HUH?
ARE WE HAVING FUN YET?
- Both: HI, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
- NAGI!
- UH!
- ( whimpers )
- WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
- I WILL HAVE
THE SPECIAL OF THE HOUSE.
- OH, OKAY.
- OH.
- HERE WE GO.
- HMM, PRETTY GOOD.
- WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- TELL ME SOMETHING.
HAVE YOU SEEN
THIS WOMAN BEFORE?
- LET'S SEE, OUR PLACE
JUST OPENED HERE,
SO I...
- SO YOU HAVEN'T?
WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE DRINK.
- AND THIS IS YOUR CHECK, MA'AM.
- HMM? 11,000?
IS THIS SOME KIND OF A JOKE?
- LIKE I SAID,
THIS IS THE BILL.
- I JUST HAD ONE DRINK.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
- ( whimpers )
- ( glasses breaking )
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
COME AGAIN.
- YES, PLEASE COME AGAIN.
SHE SEEMS TO BE VERY UPSET.
- YES, I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED?
- FORGET IT, JERK!
- Both: HUH?
- I'M NEVER COMING BACK!
DO YOU HEAR ME? NEVER!
- WHAT?
- OH MY.
- OH.
- AND 20, AND 40,
AND 60, AND 80,
THAT MAKES 100.
AND 20, AND 40, AND 60, AND 80--
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
BEING THE CROWN PRINCESS
AS I AM,
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE INVOLVED
IN THIS RIP-OFF BAR?
- LAST I HEARD,
YOU WERE A FUGITIVE IN HIDING.
GOT ME, PRINCESS?
- PRINCESS AYEKA, I'M SO SORRY.
- UNDER DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES,
YOU WOULD BE ABLE
TO TRAVEL LIKE ROYALTY.
- UH, I REMEMBER MY FIRST TRIP.
YES, I REMEMBER MY FIRST TRIP
TO A NEIGHBORING GALAXY.
WE VISITED FAMOUS PLACES
IN THE UNIVERSE
FULL OF NATURAL BEAUTY
AND HISTORICAL INTEREST.
IT REALLY WAS
A FABULOUS TRIP.
OF COURSE, WE STAYED
AT A FANCY HOTEL
IN THE ROYAL SUITE.
HMM, HOW STRANGE.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
A SWEET MEMORY,
BUT THERE SEEMED TO
BE SOMETHING UNPLEASANT.
( gasps )
NOW, I KNOW.
- ( snoring )
- HEY THERE, YOU,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ON MY BED?!
- Present-day Ayeka:
NEVERTHELESS,
THE BLUE OCEAN WAS
STILL BEAUTIFUL.
( sighs )
IT'S SO CALM AND PEACEFUL.
- ( sirens wail )
- HUH?
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- ( screams )
( screaming )
- YOU LIAR.
YOU'RE JUST MAKING UP
THAT STORY.
- OH I SEE.
YOU'RE AWAKE ARE YOU?
- WHAT REALLY HAPPENED WAS
I WAS WORKING AT
A SEASIDE HOTEL.
- ( machine whirrs )
- I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU SHOULD FEEL HONORED
TO BE ABLE TO CLEAN
THE ROOM OF A CROWN PRINCESS
OF JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
YES, INDEED, IT'S QUITE
A PRIVILEGE. - ( panting )
- ( laughing )
- ( pants ) WORK!
- Present-day Ryoko:
BUT WHEN I WAS OUT ON THE OCEAN,
I FELT SO HAPPY.
IT'S SO QUIET.
- ( laughter )
( continues laughing )
- ( screams )
- YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
THE BIGGEST LIAR OF ALL TIME.
- WELL, IT TAKES ONE
TO KNOW ONE, GIRL.
- WHO DO YOU THINK IS
TELLING THE TRUTH?
- BOTH STORIES SOUND SO REAL.
- WELL, BOTH OF THEM
MUST BE TELLING THE TRUTH.
- Both: HUH?
- SHE'S A LIAR!
- SHE'S A LIAR.
- WELL, I THINK
I'M GOING TO BED.
- Sasami: ME TOO.
( yawns )
- WE SHOULD GET SOME SLEEP TOO.
- Tenchi: YEAH, 'CAUSE WE'VE GOT
TO GET UP EARLY TOMORROW.
- Washu:
AND WE'RE OFF TO BED TOO.
- Both: ( grumbles )
- OH, YEAH, DID ANYONE REMEMBER
TO TURN OFF THE GAS?
- YES, I DID.
I REMEMBERED TO DO IT.
SO NO ONE HAS TO WORRY, WASHU.
- OH GOOD.  THANK YOU.
- ( gas leaking )
- All: EH?
- ( siren blares )
- HEADQUARTERS
TO ALL PATROL SHIPS,
HEADQUARTERS
THERE HAS JUST BEEN
A MYSTERIOUS EXPLOSION
IN ZONE 9-0-7.
PROCEED TO THE SCENE
IMMEDIATELY.
- REPEAT.
WE HAVE JUST DISCOVERED
THAT THE EXPLOSION IN ZONE 9-0-7
WAS CAUSED BY PRINCESS AYEKA
AND HER GROUP.
ALL PATROL SHIPS,
ENGAGE IN PURSUIT.
- ( groaning )
- A WHOLE BUNCH OF THEM
ARE COMING AFTER US.
- AND IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT,
MIHOSHI.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
- HURRY, THEY'RE
RIGHT BEHIND US.
- OH NO.
A BATTLESHIP OF JURAI.
- A BATTLESHIP IN FRONT AND
THE GALAXY POLICE IN BACK, HUH?
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- Ken-Ohki: ( howls )
- IT'S KEN-OHKI.
- OH, GREAT!
SO WE'VE GOT NAGI
ON OUR TAIL NOW TOO!
- ( meows )
- YOU CANNOT ESCAPE FROM ME,
RYOKO.
I WILL DEFEAT YOU.
- HUH-- OH!
- ( screams )
- RYOKO IS MY PREY!
I WON'T LET ANYBODY INTERFERE.
- Ken-Ohki: ( cries )
- GO WHILE NAGI IS DISTRACTED.
- RIGHT, I KNOW.
- Nagi: UGH! STOP!
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?!
- YOU TAKE CARE OF THEM FOR US,
OKAY?
- WHAT?!
HEY, HOLD ON A MINUTE!
YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS, RYOKO.
YOU WILL PAY!
- Newscaster: PRINCESS AYEKA
IS THOUGHT TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR BOMBING ON
PLANET CONCORD.
THE TERRORIST GROUP EXCHANGED
FIRE WITH THE GALAXY POLICE--
- GREAT, I GET IT. SO NOW WE'RE
TERRORISTS. THAT'S PERFECT.
- THE POLICE ARE STILL LOOKING
FOR THE SUSPECTS.
EMPEROR YOSHO DELIVERED A SPEECH
REGARDING THIS INCIDENT,
CONDEMNING IT AS A REBELLION
AGAINST THE SPACE PEACE.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THIS YOSHO CHARACTER.
CAN HE REALLY BE THAT
LEGENDARY HERO, OR WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT'S STRANGE
THAT HE HASN'T APPEARED
IN FRONT OF THE MEDIA YET.
LOOK, WE HAVE TO REVEAL
HIS TRUE IDENTITY
OR OTHERWISE, WE'LL BE WANTED
CRIMINALS FOREVER, TENCHI.
- WELL, COME ON.
YOU THINK POSITIVE, KIYONE.
SOMETHING WILL WORK OUT
ONCE WE GET TO PLANET JURAI.
I KNOW IT.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHETHER OR NOT
WE'LL EVER MAKE IT
TO THE PLANET JURAI.
- OH.
- ( music plays )
♪ SIT BACK AND LISTEN
TO THIS SONG THAT I'M SINGING ♪
♪ PHOTON, PROTON ♪
♪ SYNCHROTRON ARE INTERESTING ♪
♪ SCIENCE IS BETTER
THAN LOVE CAN EVER BE ♪
♪ FALLING IN LOVE
IS BASED ON CHAOTIC THEORY ♪
♪ EMOTIONS ARE EXHAUSTING ♪
♪ QUANTUM MECHANICS NEVER
EVER MAKE YOU FROWN ♪
♪ WITH SCIENTIFIC METHOD,
♪ IMAGINARY WALLS ♪
♪ WILL COME TUMBLING DOWN!
YEAH! ♪
LISTEN, THROUGH HIS EXPERIMENTS,
HEISENBERG CONCLUDED
THAT THE ACCURATE MEASUREMENTS
OF ONE OF TWO RELATED
OBSERVABLE QUANTITIES,
SUCH AS POSITION AND MOMENTUM,
PRODUCES UNCERTAINTIES
IN THE MEASUREMENT OF THE OTHER.
HE FIGURED THAT THE PRODUCT
OF THE UNCERTAINTY OF POSITION
AND THE UNCERTAINTIES
OF MOMENTUM
EQUAL TO OR GREATER THAN
"H" OVER TWO PI,
WHERE H EQUALS
PLANKS CONSTANT.
IT MEANS THAT OBSERVATIONS
IN QUANTUM MECHANICS
ALWAYS LEADS TO UNCERTAINTY--
YOU UNDERSTAND THIS, DON'T YOU?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- ( sighs )
- I THINK IT'S HOPELESS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ♪ WHEN YOU GO FISHING ♪
♪ YOU CATCH A FOOL ♪
♪ OR SOME OTHER TRASH ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PLAY AT CARDS ♪
♪ YOU LOSE ALL YOUR CASH ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO PATHETIC ♪
♪ YOU NEVER WIN ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER WILL ♪
♪ NOT THE KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ WHO'D MAKE ANY GUY
FEEL A THRILL ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, YOU'LL NEVER BE
A GODDESS LIKE ME ♪
♪ STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ THIS IS HOW
IT'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ YES, I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL ALWAYS WIN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M STRONG AND
I AM BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ WHAT MORE CAN I SAY ♪
♪ I'LL GET THE GUY ♪
♪ HE'LL HOLD ME CLOSE
TO THE VERY END OF TIME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOSE ♪
♪ HOW YOU WILL
MOURN AND CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE GUY
WILL BE MINE. ♪
- Tenchi:
WE'RE HEADING FOR PLANET JURAI
ABOARD KIYONE'S SPACE SHIP,
YAGAMI.
YAGAMI BREAKS DOWN
AND WE'RE STALLED
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
RYOKO'S GONE ON RYO-OHKI
FOR GROCERIES,
BUT WILL SHE RETURN BEFORE
WE STARVE TO DEATH.
- Sasami:
I'M SO HUNGRY.
- Ayeka:
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN BETTER.
RYOKO MUST HAVE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT US,
HAVING SOME FUN FOR HERSELF.
Mihoshi:
WE MUST TRUST HER, EVERYONE.
IF WE BELIEVE,
SHE WILL COME BACK.
Ayeka: GET REAL.
IT'S NOT A FAIRY TALE.
Tenchi:
NEXT, "NO NEED FOR HUNGER."
Ayeka:
IT'S UNQUESTIONABLY DISGRACEFUL.