(energetic, lighthearted music)
- [Narrator] Shuurei's group,
who had quietly entered
the blockade of cap ital
of Sa Province, Korin City,
found a letter from
Sakujun Sa already waiting
for them at their hideout.
It was an invitation to
the selection ceremony
for the new head of the Sa Clan.
Meanwhile, Kokujun
was determined to stop
his grandfather, Chuushou, and
his elder brother, Sakujun.
However, his desperate
pleas were in vain,
and he was thrown into
the Sa Clan's dungeon.
- Huh?
(gasps)
Is that you father?
(dog barking)
- So, you're going
after all, princess?
- Well, it is by
special invitation.
Besides, I have to
get my flower bud pin
back from that man.
That means I have to
go wherever he is.
- My lady, I don't like this.
- Neither do I, Shuurei,
it sounds too dangerous.
- Thank you both for
worrying about me,
but the thing is...
- Please don't forget, don't
forget that I do love you.
- Please don't
forget, don't forget
that I love you, Shuurei.
- This is something I must do.
I have to meet him face to face.
- Ah, my lady.
(wind blows)
- Huh?
- Hm!
(ominous music playing)
- I've come to collect you.
- Huh?
- When did he arrive?
- You realize you're
awfully early.
- So I guess this man
must be Mr. Sakujun.
He's very good
looking, isn't he?
- His looks are all
that's good about him.
You shouldn't follow
him, even if he says
he'll give you candy.
- Mr. Seirain, I'm not so much
of a child I'd fall for that.
- If I were able to
sell a portrait of him,
I could make a
very decent profit.
(laughing suspiciously)
- Would you cut it out,
Sho? Now is not the time
to be calculating. Do
you know what kind of
situation we're in?
(giggles)
- Huh, my lady?
- I'll go with you. Thank
you for your invitation.
- Good. I'm very
happy to hear that.
I suppose this means I
haven't grown tired of you
just yet, doesn't it?
(gasps)
That's rather dangerous
little whirlwind.
- Oh I'm sorry. There
was a fly over there that
was bothering me.
- I see your speech and
your skills have degraded.
I feel sorry for
you wasting your
time on meaningless hardship.
- At least I'm lucky enough
not to become like a certain
foolish lord I know who's
brains have rotted away from
too much fooling around.
(suspenseful music)
- Wow, you're pretty
scary Mr. Seirain,
but on the other
hand, Mr. Sakujun
isn't even shaking at all.
Both of them are
really incredible.
If I want to be that good,
I've got to try harder.
- At what?
- What are you doing? I
thought we were leaving.
Since he's been kind
enough to come for me,
I guess I'll be on my way.
- I'm sure I'll see you
later little whirlwind.
(angrily growls)
(melancholy music)
- You're going to have
to give back my flower
bud at some point you know.
- Hm.
(melancholy music continues)
- Ugh, just great.
Now that the diamonds
been taken out
of the rough, there's
nothing left behind but us
big rough men!
But that was impressive Seirain.
You held it in well. I think
you need a hug after that.
- Not a chance.
(laughter)
(dog barking)
- Okay, this is the residence
of an important man in Kinka.
(grunt)
(laughing)
Now, to take care of Mr.
Ensei's request of us.
I'm going to talk to
the big man in Kinka
on our way to Korin.
(quiet footsteps)
- Here's your tea.
- Thank you very much Korin.
- Here you are.
- Good evening!
Excuse me for intruding
so late at night.
I am the deputy leader of the
Bald Eagle of Sa Province.
Yoshu is my name and
I am at your service.
- Uh, official you...
- Yes, it seems our visitor
here to see me about something.
- Please sir, don't stand up.
Seeing as you have some trouble
walking, please,
stay in your seat.
- Now how do you know that I
have trouble walking young man?
- It's just that you
have the same look as
a wild deer with an injured leg.
(laughing)
- Yes, I heard about
you from Ensei Row.
He had goo things
to say about you.
It's a pleasure to meet
the famous deputy head
of the Bald Eagles of
Sa Province Mr. Yoshu.
- Huh, oh no! I'm only
the deputy leader.
I'm just in training.
I'm not famous.
Oh! But my big brother.
I mean Bashorein is
definitely famous.
He's our famous leader, yeah!
- Here you go.
- Huh? Oh, thank you very
much for the tea miss.
(slurping)
(deep swallow)
Wow, that was really nice.
At last, I'm beginning
to feel relaxed again.
Excuse me, would you be the
most important person here?
- Yes, for the time
being at least.
I've been appointed to fill
the highest ranked official
post in the city of Kinka.
- Whoa! That's amazing
for someone so young!
- I'm very honored
to receive such
a fine compliment from you,
but now, if you don't mind
me asking, where is you
leader and lady Shunki Sa?
- They've gone on ahead
of me and they're on their
way to Korin.
- But it was my
understanding that Korin
has been blockaded. It's
not going to be easy
for them to enter the city.
- Normally, that would've
been a problem but this
totally awesome guy
gave us a wooden token.
When he did, Ms. Shunki
said it'd be all right
and they'd be able
to enter no prob.
- Hm?
- The wooden token was
blue with a picture
of dragons and a
lotus flower on it.
You know, there sure
are some amazing young
men in the big city.
- Hm, just out of curiosity,
what was it about this
person that struck you
as particularly amazing.
- His outfit!
The feather, the color
coordination, even the shape!
They were all totally
unique and incredibly cool!
- Um, did that person
happen to carry
a flute with them by any chance?
- Yeah! He did! And he
made really wonderful
music with it!
(sad sign)
- Is it that guy
from the Ran Clan?
- Hm.
(Mysterious flute music)
- I live in the country
so I never knew that
refine city folk
could be so amazing!
- Is that so?
Well I wouldn't say
it has anything to do
with whether or not
he's from a big city.
In the case of that person,
it's his personality
and disposition that
makes him unique, even
in a very big capital.
- Huh?
(agreeing under breath)
- Uh
(wolves howling)
(somber music)
(indistinct chattering)
- You may pass.
- We made it to
Korin, Ms.Shunki.
We're in the capital
of Sa Province.
It's all thanks to that
awesome guys wooden token.
(suspicious music)
I'll see what I can get from
these horses hoof prints.
A few of them suddenly
picked up the pace.
Okay, looks like
they went this way.
(grunt)
I assume that it was Ensei
who caused the horses
to gallop so fast
through the city.
If we follow these
tracks, we should find
them in no time.
Hang in there just a
little longer Ms. Shunki.
We'll be there
before you know it.
(suspicious music fades)
- The stars...
So, Shunki is making her move.
Shunki, you should
know by now that
men are utterly foolish.
It's always the
women who have to
rescue them in the end.
On top of that, that
one in particular is so
useless and unreliable.
(soft melody)
- Shunki, I borrowed one of
great uncle Enjun's books.
Whou-, would you like
to read it together?
- Invite her for a
walk or something.
What a fool.
Hm, but for all his
little faults, that boy
had the same eyes as Enjun.
He's the man who
Shunki has chosen.
Perhaps in time we'll
discover that he's inherited
more from Enjun than
merely his eyes.
(soft brooding music)
- What. What should I do?
I was too late.
I couldn't stop any of them,
not grandfather Chuushou
or brother Sakujun.
It's all over.
The Sa Clan is finished.
Great uncle Enjun, what
would you have done?
You could've done
something, I know it.
Every since I was a child,
I have always admired you.
But there was just one thing
that I could never understand.
Why did you kill
all the airs in the
main branch of the Sa Family?
Why?
(crickets)
- Thank you very much for
getting in touch with me, Yoshu.
You have been extremely
helpful on this.
- No, no, it's nothing.
It's a chivalrous
thief's duty to finish
a job they've been asked to do.
Now that's done,
it's off to Korin!
(grunt)
- Wait a moment, where do
you intend to go in Korin?
- I'm gonna go to where Bos is.
- But Korin is under
blockade, remember?
You won't be able to enter.
Having said that,
I'm also planning to
travel to Korin very soon.
If it's all right
with you, could you be
my body guard on the way there?
That way, we can both make
our way into Korin together.
- Huh! Really? Would
that really be okay?
Oh wow! The outside
world is filled with
so many kind people!
(grunt)
- But this job I'm
asking you to do
is not without danger.
Is that okay?
- How dangerous are
we talking about?
Is it as dangerous as
being chases by five
giant, hungry man eating bears?
(crashing sound)
Or are you saying that
the risk in the big
city is even worse
than I've imagined!
Like maybe 10
bears or something!
- Mh, uh, no, I don't
believe that our jounrey
to Korin will be
quite that dangerous.
(grunt out of relief)
- Well that certainly
is a relief to hear.
- (sad sigh)
(lighthearted music)
(crickets and
flowing water sounds)
- Stop worrying,
it'll be all right.
Princess has a really good
head on her shoulders.
- You're right.
- Once everything is
over, than you can beat
him up as much as you like.
- It won't be enough.
- Huh?
- In that guys case,
just beating him
up won't be anywhere
near enough.
- Hey don't do anything
too distasteful, okay?
- Hm
(sword unsheathed)
(grunt)
(angrily grunting)
(yells)
- Cut it out, Seiran!
Hold on a sec!
- What do you think
you're doing you idiot!
Who starts swinging a sword
when there's young girl around?
- Huh?
- Wow. Guess the worlds
not such a bad place
when it comes to coincidences.
Just as we lose one
diamond, another one
flies right into our arms.
(happy piano must)
This here is lady Shunki Sa.
- Hm.
(graceful violin music)
- You said this
building's detached from
the main Sa Clan
residence, right?
- Yes
- Why is the layout
here so complicated?
It seems too easy to get lost.
- It's in case of emergencies.
- Huh?
- As it's laid out now,
it's not an easy place
to occupy and it's
difficult to discern where
people might be.
That sort of thing.
It is a place where the
history of rebellions and
betrayals from long
ago have after all.
- Rebellions and betrayals.
You mean like what
your grandfather is doing?
- Yes
(gasps)
- What? You're right.
He's the one who
wanted you here.
He ordered me to bring
you to the residence.
That way, no one
could interrupt us.
And I would then be
free to ravish you.
(confused gasp)
- Apparently, our
wedding ceremony will be
formally held after that.
At the same time as
the selection ceremony
for the leadership of the clan.
- So wait just a second,
are you saying you brought
me all the way here
with the intention of
violating me at some point?
- Well, in the end that
was the general idea.
- Ha, in that case you're
just wasting your time.
Even if that were to happen,
I would not become your wife.
- That doesn't particularly
bother me much.
I'm not necessarily
interested in the structure of
having a marriage or a wife.
(gasps)
(fearful gasp)
- As long as you bring
color to the daily monotony
and boredom I must
endure in my life.
I have no more to ask.
- Until you eventually become
tired of me, is that right?
- That's right. Until
I become tired of you.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You must take me for some
sort of fool or something.
I would've preferred it if you
had grown tired of me by now.
That way, all I'd need to
do is get you to hand over
my flower bud and then leave.
(violin music continues)
- I suppose that's true.
However, since you are
special to me, this might
drag on for a little while.
- Look, the reason I came
here was not so i could
relieve you of your boredom.
I only came so I could get
my flower bud back from you.
I though you said it didn't
matter to you whether or
not I became the governor.
- I did say that, but
I wasn't aware that you
were required to have the
flower hair pin in order
to take the position
of governor.
- Normally not.
But in my case, it's
necessary to have it.
(echoing voice)
- We look forward to the
day when the buds you've
both been given
bloom for all to see.
- I understand if
that's the case.
- Hm?
(gasps)
- Then I'll give it back to you.
Now let's see.
You can have it back on the
day of the selection ceremony.
- What did you say?
- Well if I gave it back
to you right now you'd have
no reason to stay here
and would probably
flee in the blink of an eye.
(grunt)
- No I won't run away!
Not until the clan
selection ceremony.
- Well then there's
no problem, is there?
You can trust me
to keep my promise.
- All right, very well.
- Come then, your
room is over here.
(mysterious music)
- May I ask you something?
Mr. Kokujun, he's returned
to his residence, right?
- Yes.
- What is he doing now?
(laughing)
- What is it?
- Oh nothing,
you're quite right.
He is definitely here,
but his status is an issue
within the Sa Clan.
That means it doesn't
really concern you, does it?
- Can't I be worried about him
as one individual to another?
- All right, then
he's perfectly well.
- Wait a minute, how do you
expect me to believe you!
You say that in such
a patronizing manner.
- Then why don't you try
searching for him yourself.
You're free to do anything
you like while you're here.
I don't mind what you
do or where you search.
And that includes not just
the separate residence but
the main building as well.
- In other words, you're
saying Mr. Kokujun is
hidden away in a place that
I'll never be able to find
by searching for him alone, huh?
(suspicious laughter)
- Um, but the compound for
he Sa Clan's residence.
That's very impressive.
To think she's able to
draw this accurately.
- Even though she's
live there for
most of her life,
it's still amazing how
much detail she's included.
- Lord KMyk would
get totally lost in
this place that's for sure.
- Mhm.
- I wonder if they've
returned to Kio by now?
(soft guitar music)
(wolf howling)
(dog barking)
(fire crackling)
(sigh)
- If only we'd been able
to meet her in Kinka.
Oh, Shuei...
(gasps)
- This will be your room
while you're our guest.
If there's anything
you'd like, I'll have it
prepared for you immediately.
But once night falls,
I'd like you to play
the arrow and make some
tea for me like old times.
Also.
(gasps)
I'd like you to wear
your hair like this.
I've told you many times, this
is the style that I prefer.
(sigh)
- So, is there anything
else you'd like to ask me?
- Am I allowed to send letter?
- I am afraid to
say that wouldn't be
part of my jurisdiction.
Even if you could, it would
be under the condition that
the letters would be checked.
- You would go that far?
- I know that my grandfather
would go that far.
- I understand.
- If there's nothing else
for the moment, why don't
we go to my room.
- Huh?
- It's just next door to yours.
You'll play the arrow
for me won't you?
I have one there.
(concerned sigh)
(calm mellow music)
- Oh before you start
playing, could you brew
some tea for me?
There are several different
kinds of tea leaves over there.
(sighs)
and of course I have some
garden tea as well so you
could make some of
that if you like.
(sighs)
(sound of flowing liquid)
(content sigh)
- Mm, it's delicious.
- Thank you for saying so.
- But, I would much
rather gano tea
specially made by you.
(sighs)
(music continues)
- There are walls and passages
in such strange places.
It's quite a complicated
compound, isn't it?
Anyone would get lost in here.
Not just Lord Koyu.
- The whole residence
is equipped with
dead ends and traps.
Jeez, what a place.
- But this map could
prove extremely helpful.
Shall we make a copy and
deliver it to our lady ship?
- Sounds like a good idea.
Shorin, as the second
generation leader of the
Bald Eagles of Sa Province.
I have another
assignment for you.
There's a young lady in
the Sa Clan's residence
that I need you find.
I want you to deliver a message.
- Now what! Look Ensei, I
know you've been watching
out for us but now you're
just being demanding!
- A chivalrous thief
doesn't ask for
anything in return.
Besides, it's Lord Shoka's
daughter that you need to find.
- Why didn't you say
that in the first place?
Mr. Shoka did favors
for my father so if
it's his daughter then
it's obvious I'll be
glad to search for her.
- That's what I'm talking about.
As for locating her,
just listen to for the
sound of an arub being
played and you'll
find her in no time.
You've got the skill that
would make wild children
call you a wild child.
(laughing under breath)
- Was that a compliment?
- Don't know.
But remember you got to
be quite and discrete.
You don't want anyone
else but her to see you.
- So this is a stealth job then.
Certainly a job fit for a
chivalrous thief like me.
I like it.
Just copy the map and wake
me up once it's ready.
I'm taking a nap to
store up some stamina
for this little venture.
(snoring)
- Amazing. He's
all ready asleep.
- Like I said,
he's a wild child.
- But even though he's
a wild child, will he
be able to track down
the sound of an arub
in such a big residence?
Do you think he'll be
able to find Shurei?
- Don't worry.
These animal instincts
of his can be trusted.
After all, this is the same
guy who was able to find
us by following the horses
hoof prints from the
gate checkpoint.
- I guess you're right.
He is quite something.
It's not as if there's
only one horse in the
whole Korin, right?
- But even so, when I
look at him and at you, it
still amazes me how different
you can be at the same age.
- The same age?
Wait what?
You can't be serious.
- Yes, I am.
- I can't believe it, wow.
I guess I'll have
to work even harder.
(solum music)
- This is a very well drawn map.
Well, let's start making a
copy for princess to use.
- When it comes down to
it, this young lady was
a lot more help to
us than Kokujun was.
- Hey, that's just
the way it works.
When the going get
tough, girl's tend to be
much braver and
stronger than guys.
(music continues)
(all speaking together)
- Yes, they are strong.
(snoring)
(suspenseful
orchestration music)
(laughing)
- It that right?
Now I see, so that's how
it was great uncle Enjun.
That the reason you killed
all the airs at the main
branch of the clan was
because it was already far
too late for you
to do otherwise.
There was no longer any
other way you could help
set things right again.
To that extent, this family,
the entire Sa Clan was
rotten to the very core.
So there was nothing
left for you to do
but start all over from scratch.
And now, all I can do
is to bring everything
to an end by my hand
just like him.
Just like great
uncle Enjun once did.
(music continues)
father.
(dreamy music)
- Honestly, Eru this, Eru that.
I'm surprised that man
never gets tired of it!
I can't afford to
waste time here.
I have to look for Mr.
Kokujun and lady Heki.
But hey, why is this
residence so huge!