(melodic music in
foreign language)
- [Narrator] Seiran and
Sakujun Sa are casting dice
with their lives at stake.
They will determine
which of the two
will be the first to drink
the poison in the wine cups.
In the meantime,
with the revelation
of various crimes
committed by the Sa clan,
everyone connected
to the family,
without exception,
has been arrested.
In the midst of the chaos,
Kokujun became the heir apparent
to the position of clan head.
This means that he must
now bear the heavy burden
of guilt and responsibility
for his clan's sins.
(ominous music)
(dice clanking in glass)
- [Sakujun Sa] Two, three.
Here.
- Nine years ago, the
person who arranged
for the murder of
Shunki's parents,
the late advisor, Sa's
son and daughter-in-law.
It was you, wasn't it?
- There's no way that advisor
Sa's brother, Chuushou,
could have managed to
pull it off on his own,
let alone gotten the
idea in the first place.
- Oh, really?
- I wouldn't be
the least surprised
if some unproductive
youngster from the Sa clan
got fed up with advisor Sa
constantly interfering
with his depraved amusement
and gave a few
suggestions to Chuushou
as a small form of
personal revenge.
(slurps cup)
(sighs)
- That is a rather intriguing
story you're telling.
- [Seiran] Oh, it gets better.
Don't you want to
hear the reason
why your father
was brought down?
- [Sakujun Sa] It seems that
hardship can make people grow.
The former prince has
become quite skilled
in little tricks and traps.
Perhaps we should have a toast
in honor of your
pathetically sincere effort.
- Do as you wish.
(glass clanks)
- Then, in honor of
the former prince,
who has become
cool-tongued, spiteful,
and pessimistic in his old age,
I raise my glass, a toast.
(soft ominous music)
- I had the merchant's
guild do some investigating,
and I found out that the
Sa clan's main branch
ordered several kinds
of incense all at once.
- Yes, so?
- [Seiran] They were
highly addictive
and would gradually
affect the person's
mind in a certain way.
- (chuckles) You're
very knowledgeable.
I assume that, in your research,
you discovered
exactly who it was
that ordered those
special drugs.
- Yeah, it was your
mother and grandmother.
- [Sakujun] Well,
those two would
certainly do
something like that.
- Oh, yes, and I'm sure
it had nothing to do
with a certain
unproductive slacker,
who knows all sorts
of strange things,
quietly telling them about it,
just to cope with this boredom.
- Perhaps.
I'm sure there are probably kind
and honest people out there
who would actually answer
if you asked them
about such things.
- This wine is strong.
My throat is burning.
- It's finally over, isn't it?
- Yeah, job well done, you two.
As I said to lady Shuurei,
you've done outstandingly
as the new governors.
- Thank you very much, Mr. Sai.
- It's not over yet.
We're still not finished here.
I have to take the flower
bud pin back from that man.
- Yeah.
- Then why don't I go and finish
the last part of
our mission, okay?
(group grunts confusedly)
- Do you think Shuurei
will be all right
going on her own like that?
- This is Princess's problem.
That means it's only proper
for her to get it back herself.
- Right.
This is one of those things
that we can't really
interfere with.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(panting frantically)
- [Sakujun] Would you
tell me something?
Why are you, or rather,
why are the people of this
world so open-hearted?
- Open-hearted?
What do you mean?
- I only need one person
in the entire world,
and that would be more than
enough for me, but most people,
for example, you, are
different, aren't you?
You may love your princess,
but there are other people
whom you hold dear as well.
- Yeah, that's right.
(soft ominous music)
In the past, the only
person who was truly
important to me was
my little brother,
but now, things
are very different.
- But I only have one person
who's important to me.
That means I'm trying
to give all of myself
to her and her alone,
so I would appreciate
it if people like you,
who have others to care
about, would stop interfering.
(dice clinging)
- When it comes
to me, Sakujun Sa,
I can actually be
extremely selfish,
if I do say so myself.
(slurps) I take anything
and everything I desire.
I don't pick and choose.
Why bother when I
can grasp it all?
- If you become too greedy,
you won't be able to get
the things you truly desire.
- As usual, you
don't understand.
Someone like you
could never comprehend
how much I love all of them,
and how fortunate I am
to have them in my life.
- You're right, I don't
think I do understand,
and frankly, I don't
think I care to, either.
(dice clanking)
Say, how would you
react if I told you
that your princess served me
Ganlu tea while she was here?
- Knowing her, I
could only guess
that you used some cheap
tactic to make her do it.
My lady's Ganlu tea
was exceptionally
delicious, wasn't it?
- Now, I'd like you to
make some Ganlu tea for me.
- No way.
- Yes, it was very delicious.
(crickets chirping)
(panting frantically)
If you don't brew
any Ganlu tea for me,
then I'm afraid
I'm going to die.
- I don't understand.
Why did he want to
drink that tea so badly?
(dice clanking)
- I'll tell you one thing.
I was told by my lady
that I'm her second favorite
person in the world.
(dice clanking)
- Why tell me
something like that?
I wouldn't say that's
particularly worth
bragging about.
(dice clanking)
- It is when her
favorite person is a man
who no one can hope to match.
Is it all right if I ask you
who your number one
favorite person is?
- It's father, of course.
He would know he's
a hopeless father.
He's always been my number one.
- That's why second place
is good enough for me,
and don't try to pretend
you don't understand
exactly what I mean by that.
- My goodness, you always have
had a terrible personality.
- I wouldn't mind
being told that
by anyone else, but not you.
(dice clanking)
- [Sakujun] I envy you.
- Huh?
- I said I envy you.
I would love to be told
by her that I'm, say,
even her third favorite
person in the world.
- His face is turning pale.
There's no more time left.
I have one more question.
- You certainly are
inquisitive, aren't you?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you wanted to
get acquainted with me.
If that were the case,
then you really should have
said something at the beginning.
I would've been able to
entertain you somewhat better.
- You've already
returned the flower bud
hairpin to my lady, right?
- Yes, I returned it.
(sword clanks)
- Now that I know for
sure, I'm satisfied.
If you don't mind, I
am going to have you
let me win this little bet.
- You are joking, right?
(loud whooshing)
(grunts loudly)
(loud thudding)
(glass breaking)
You certainly are as merciless
as always, my prince.
(yells angrily)
(swords clanking)
(both grunting)
- And which of us is
cold-blooded enough
to put poison in all the cups?
- Very impressive.
(swords clanking)
(grunts loudly)
I made sure to prepare a
tasteless, odorless poison,
but it seems you've
come prepared to ensure
you wouldn't lose to
that sort of thing.
Frankly, I find that
little cowardly of you.
- Do you think I'd risk my
life with you as my opponent?
Besides, you're only
able to stand up
to this fast-acting poison
because you're using
a neutralizing antidote as well.
- I did no such thing,
it's just that I've experimented
with so many poisons
over the years to kill time,
my body's built up a
resistance to them.
- You're a monster!
(grunts loudly)
(ominous music)
(grunting in anguish)
- Are you all right?
(sword clanks)
(grunts painfully)
I must admit, I'm impressed.
You must have quite a
strong stomach for alcohol.
To tell you the truth,
I couldn't resist making
a few small improvements
to the wine we drank.
It's so strong that even
the heaviest of drinkers
will fall over after
drinking just a single cup.
For you to non-nonchalantly
drink so many cups of it
and only become dizzy now,
after physically
exerting yourself?
Just what kind of
body do you have?
(grunting painfully)
Well, sorry to run
off, but I'm afraid
there's some place I have to be,
so I'll take this
chance to excuse myself.
Why don't you stay here?
You look like you could
use a little rest.
(grunts loudly)
(loud thudding)
(chuckles) If anyone were
to win a bet against me,
that someone would never be you.
(ominous music)
(light kokyu music)
- Shunki.
- Don't worry about a
thing, Lord Kokujun.
I'm still right
here by your side.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be with you.
Always.
(crickets chirping)
- There's no moon.
That's right, tonight's
supposed to be the new moon.
(erhu music)
(grunts in surprise)
(sighs)
(panting frantically)
This will probably
be the last time.
As governor, it's my
duty to arrest him
and pass judgment on his crimes,
that's why this will
be the very last time
I can really meet him as myself,
as just plain Shuurei Hong.
(erhu music)
- It seems I can hardly
move my fingers anymore.
Oh, come to me quickly,
my lovely princess.
You never betray
my expectations, so
please, come quickly.
(distantly rustling)
(panting)
- What do you
think you're doing,
hanging around in such an
out-of-the-way place like this?
(gasps)
(far-Eastern music)
(gasps surprisingly)
What happened?
(gasps)
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
- Just as I promised, the
thing most important to you.
- This is no time for that.
- In the end, in
the end, it was you.
You only gave me hot water.
- You've been drinking
wine, and a lot of it.
If that wine mixes weirdly
with Ganlu tea in your stomach,
you can end up
making yourself sick.
Just have the hot water today
and get some decent rest, okay?
- If you don't brew
any Ganlu tea for me,
then I'm afraid
I'm going to die.
- Ugh, that is something
a child would say.
You know, you do have to try
to treat your body properly.
I'll just give you hot water.
- What you didn't know was
that in that hot water,
I had already added
a slow-acting poison
that I'm not resistant to
that would eventually kill me.
- I don't get it.
There was nothing wrong
with you yesterday.
- I also chopped up a
neutralizing antidote
and added it to the Ganlu tea.
- You were all energetic
and running around.
How could this have happened?
- When I said I would die if
you didn't make Ganlu tea,
I was telling the truth.
- Hey, this is probably just due
to a scratched throat
or something, right?
- I was thinking of telling
you the truth, you know?
That you were the
one who killed me.
If I did that, then you'd
never be able to forget me.
I felt like I could become
a special person
to you that way.
- You need medicine.
You don't have any
on you, do you?
- But it's funny, for the
first time in my life,
I began to think
about what I could do
for the sake of someone
other than myself.
Once I started to
think that way,
I realized that no matter
how I looked at it,
I was the greatest
obstacle in your way,
but I was weak enough to make
one final gamble for my life,
but you overcame it easily.
(chuckles)
- What, why are you
laughing like that?
(strained coughing)
Where's your medicine?
- I always keep
making you angry.
Just once, I would have
liked to see you smile.
(sighs)
- Come on, where is it?
- My eyes.
I guess that means
the last part of me
to go will be my hearing.
Please play the erhu for me.
- Quit joking around.
Nevermind, I'll go
and get Eigetsu.
(grunts feebly)
What is it?
- I must have told
you over and over
that it's much better like this.
(soft somber music)
You never called me by my
real name, not even once.
- (whimpers softly) Let me go.
I'll get Eigetsu
to come right away.
- To you, what place do
I hold in your heart?
- I'm begging you,
please let me go.
- It's not really your fault,
but while I still
have the chance,
I'm giving you the
life of Sakujun Sa.
- It this my fault?
- They say beauty and a
happy life don't go together.
Deadly illness always
strikes the ideal man.
I was planning on passing away
without saying this to you,
but now, at the very
final moment, I love you.
The way you play the erhu,
the way you always made tea
for me, everything about you.
(whimpers)
- No, I'm not gonna let you
avoid the subject like that.
I'm not going to
allow you to say
something like
that and then die,
and I'm not going to
call you by your name.
What should I call you, anyway?
You were always
Young Master to me.
Besides, you never
once called me
by my real name either, did you?
Wait for me.
- You were the one
person who could ever
win a bet against me.
In all truth, you really
were a special person to me.
When I decided this path,
I fully expected to
die with no regrets.
They always say that every
meeting ends in parting,
but still, I wanted
you to say my name.
I wanted to hear you
play the erhu again.
I wanted to spend more
time together with you.
I wanted to make you
say you loved me.
(somber piano music)
Where is the moon?
(crickets chirping softly)
- Tonight is the
night of the new moon.
- What's the matter,
your majesty?
Is there something out there?
- No, I just had
this strange feeling.
It's funny, every since
Shuurei and Seiran
came into my life, I've
found what's important to me.
It's given me
courage to the extent
that I'm not frightened
of the darkness anymore.
- Indeed.
- Of course, I also
love you very much,
Shuuei, and Kouyuu as well.
- Thank you for saying
so, your majesty.
I have to ask, though, where
do I rank compared with Shuuei?
- How am I supposed
to answer that?
You can't compare
between the two.
Long ago, I thought
it would be enough
just to have my elder
brother with me,
but now, I can't help but feel
that would be a total waste.
- Sounds like you're being
rather greedy, your majesty.
- Didn't you know?
A real king is
supposed to be greedy.
- But, despite your
greediness, you've done a very
admirable job of restraining
yourself and doing your best.
It's very impressive.
- Stop, if you keep
saying such nice things,
I might end up crying to
you like a spoiled child.
Right now, I feel
like I must have
a pretty pathetic
expression on my face.
- Well, that's true.
You certainly do.
But, that's fine.
I actually kind of like it.
Don't worry, it's all right.
We're all here by your
side supporting you.
- You know, if I could only
see Shuurei and no one else,
I feel like, until I met her,
the world would be boring,
and once we did meet,
I'd make up for it by
living like a blazing fire,
burning furiously
until it goes out,
and I die alone, and yet,
I don't think I'd
have a single regret.
But, you know, Shuuei,
even if that were the case,
I can't help but
think I'm luckier
to have many different
people dear to me.
(doors bang)
(all gasp)
- Seiran.
- Hold on, what's the matter?
- My lady.
(both gasp)
- I'll go find her.
(grunts softly)
(panting frantically)
- Shuurei.
(grunts)
- We were worried.
- Come with me, quickly.
(soft piano music)
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
You've never once called me
by my real name,
either, did you?
- Goodbye, Shuurei.
(somber piano music)
(melodic music in
foreign language)
- What's the matter, Seiran?
You're so unsteady on your feet.
Come on, you've gotta
get your act together.
Okay, now to put an end to
this conflict once and for all.
Come on, everyone.
It's time to go and
rescue Yushuun Tei.