(whirring)
(light music)
- [Narrator] Morning had
not yet fully broken.
Having received word that Korin,
the capital of Sa Province
was under complete blockade,
Shuurei's party was forced
to depart early from Kinka.
They will try their hardest
to enter the sealed-off
city of Korin.
- Official Yu?
- [Yu] Yes, what is it?
- I was wondering,
would you mind apologizing
to Korin for me?
We're leaving without
saying anything.
When she finds out she's
the only one left behind--
- I wouldn't worry, I'm sure
she understands perfectly.
She already knows how
dangerous this journey will be,
and that she would only
be a burden to you.
- [Sei] He's right.
- [Yu] Well, please take care.
- Yes, we'll be off now.
- You look after things here.
- Hmm.
(hooves clopping)
- [Man] Governor Hong!
- Huh?
- Hm?
- It's my father.
- Ensei, stop,
stop the carriage.
(horse neighs)
- What did you say?
Of all the escorts
you could have chosen,
you're only taking my son?
- Yes, that's right.
Mr. Si knows the route
to Korin very well.
And since we're hoping not
to get into any battles
on our way there,
it would be best not
to take any soldiers
or armed guards along with us.
- I'm very honored by
you choosing my son,
but to put it bluntly
he will be of no help
as your bodyguard.
He's stingy with money,
and when he's most needed,
he may very well
leave the battlefield
rather than act as your
shield as he should do.
- Good for you,
father, and thank you.
You know your son very well.
Those are the qualities that
every merchant should have.
- It wasn't a compliment!
(Shuurei laughs)
- Well, the sun has risen.
Let's hurry up and get going.
- Normally it takes at least
five days to reach Korin,
but given the current situation,
we must try to arrive
as soon as possible.
- You're right, every day
we're delayed on the road,
the conditions in Korin are
likely to become even worse
thanks to the blockade
they're under.
- Like people always
say, time is money.
- You really are always working
at the abacus aren't you?
- Not only is it true,
but I'll take that
as a compliment
(Shuurei laughs).
(gentle music)
- [Narrator] Shuurei
and her companions
have departed for Korin City.
What they don't know is
that right about now,
Ryuuki's party is headed for
Kinka at about the same time.
- At last we finally made it.
- Right.
- Here, here, just
where exactly is here?
- We're in Sa Province
- I know that much!
- Being directionally
challenged could prove
to be fatal on a
journey like this.
If you get lost from the group,
we'll likely never
see you again.
- [Narrator] Ryuuki and his
party had departed from Kiyou
and even cut back on sleep,
so they could gain more ground
along a wild animal trail.
They will arrive in
Kinka before long.
- [Ryuuki] I wonder if
that's where Shuurei is.
- Well, we'll be
arriving in the morning.
- I apologize to you.
I made you travel
treacherous mountian paths
that people don't normally use,
and had you sacrifice
sleep to get further,
all for my personal desires.
By all rights, as king I
shouldn't be leaving Kiyou,
for any reason.
- But you didn't come here on
just personal feelings alone.
Did you?
As King you wanted to survey
Sa Province with your own eyes.
Am I right?
- Yeah, but as far as this
situation goes as king,
you definitely can't
get involved at all.
It's good you understand
that much at least.
- Of course, I don't
intend to help them.
If they can't overcome these
challenges on their own,
then it would have
been meaningless
to send them to Sa
Province to begin with.
All I'm able to do
is watch over them.
Huh?
(snoring)
- Still, given the
pace we've been going,
neither we nor our
horses will be able
to make it much
further this evening.
I suggest that we rest
here until morning.
- Good idea.
(gentle music)
- [Korin] Here you are.
- Ah, thank you
very much, Korin.
- I can't help but wonder
if Lady Shuurei is okay.
- Korin.
- It's all right, I understand.
I would have only been a burden
if I had gone with
them on their journey.
But still, I wish I
could've at least,
said to them have a
safe trip or something.
- Don't worry, I have great
faith in Governor Hong.
I'm sure that she'll
arrive in Korin safely,
and attend her
appointment ceremony
with no cause for concern.
And the same goes
for Governor To.
- I'm not worried about him.
I'm only worried about
Lady Shuurei, that's all.
- [Yu's Voiceover] I'm certain
Governor Hong will be safe,
but the others are
a different matter.
As far as the Sa
Clan is concerned,
they're merely nuisances.
I wonder, will they all be able
to reach Korin successfully?
(fire crackling)
- It's them.
- All right boys,
we're not to kill the
daughter of the Hong Clan.
We have to capture her alive.
- And the rest?
- We kill them all
and leave their bodies
for the wolves to eat.
- You're the ones who
are gonna be eaten.
(yelling)
(fire crackling)
- Mm-mm, delicious!
Was it you who made
this savory rice
and bean ball, Governor Hong?
- Yes.
- It's stuffed with
lots of barbecued pork,
so it's really very scrumptious.
- Mm, I'm sure this
could sell quite well.
- Honestly, Mr. Shosi, you
truly are always thinking
about business and
money aren't you?
- So much so that
I have the urge
to run back to Kinka
and sell these.
- But if you do that,
it'll only get you
into another quarrel with
your father, won't it?
- That argument you two had
this morning was kind of fun.
- Especially compared to
the Sa Clan's family fights.
- Welcome back.
- Just as we
expected, those guys
from the Sa Clan's private
army were wondering around
and waiting for nightfall
to come and attack us.
- Thanks for helping.
- I'm worried about
Mr. Kou Kijin.
He's facing Tu ShoSa
all on his own,
and I wonder if he'll
succeed in putting a stop
to that man's plans, as well.
- Princess, how about
I tell you something
I bet you don't even know?
- What is it?
- When things started getting
messy within the Sa Clan
following old man Injun's death,
the first thing that boy did
was set off for the
Sa Clan residence.
- Huh?
- If that weren't gutsy enough
Kou Kijin made his opinion known
that the full authority
of the clan should go
to old Lady AeKei of all people.
- Mr. Kou Kijin said that?
- Unfortunately, no one
would listen to his opinion,
but he still felt the
need to do something
to set things right,
so he came to me
while I was trapped in
that dungeon back in SeiDe
- I think Mr. Kou Kijin
is a man who fights
for what's most precious to him.
- In any case no one
other than a member
of the Sa Clan will be
able to solve the problems
that are within the Sa Clan.
- Hmm.
- He has tasks only he can do,
and in the same way
you too my lady,
have tasks only you can do.
But I'm sure the time
will come when your path
and his will meet again,
and when that moment comes,
I know you'll make every
effort to help him.
- Yeah you're right, Seiran.
(wolf howling)
Once we reach Korin,
it means I'll have to meet
up with that man again.
(fire crackling)
- Hm, My Lady it's late.
- Could I have some
water please Seiran?
(cork pops)
Hmm.
I remember that when
I was a little girl,
mother always used
to tell me stories
whenever I was unable
to get to sleep.
- [Seiran] Yes, I remember.
- Out of all the
stories she told,
my favorite was always
"The Rose Princess".
(crickets chirping)
(snoring)
(grunts)
- Dammit.
Not only is he
directionally challenged,
he tosses and turns
in his sleep as well.
Huh?
Your Majesty?
- Huh?
I was watching the stars.
- You won't be able to
take much more of this
if you don't get some sleep.
We'll drive the
horses to their limit
as soon as the sky
starts to lighten.
- When I was little I
was afraid of the dark
so I would often look up
at the stars by myself.
But when Shuurei
was in the palace
I found myself looking
forward to night coming,
every night Shuurei
would play her erhu
and tell me wonderful stories.
- What kind of stories?
- Like "The Rose Princess".
Please continue where you left
off with yesterday's story.
- You'll just fall asleep in
the middle again, won't you?
How many times must I
tell you the same tale?
- As many as you can.
- Hmm.
Once upon a time,
there was a very
beautiful princess named
The Rose Princess.
Besides her beauty, she
possessed the amazing ability
to heal any injury or illness.
However there was
a greedy master
who wanted that
power all to himself,
so he captured
The Rose Princess.
Before long, the story had
spread across the country.
The story of this princess who
could control the mysterious
and whose eternal beauty
shined bright enough
to dim even the moonlight.
(gentle music)
Men came in great numbers,
all wanting to propose
marriage to her,
so her master
decided to take her
where no one could find her.
He gave her whatever
her heart desired.
Except freedom.
Just as I thought!
- I'm not asleep you know.
- What, you're
pretending to be asleep?
Huh?
- Go ahead, please continue.
- Time passed and then
one day a man was able
to make his way in
to meet the princess.
- The man jumped over the many
fences that encircled her,
to get to where
she was being held.
A single look, and he
fell in love with her.
Even though he had
come to kill her,
because she was disturbing
the country's peace
with the stories about her.
Taking the princess,
the man fled as far
away as he could.
As she spent time with the
man The Rose Princess found
that she had lost her
special abilities,
but the man didn't mind at all.
- What happened to the
Rose Princess then mommy?
Did she get to live
happily ever after?
- She sure did.
The princess gave birth to
a beautiful little girl,
but that little girl was
always falling ill with fevers.
But in her heart the
princess became aware
that she would be able
to have a single wish
in exchange for
giving up her life.
The Rose Princess
did not hesitate,
she said to the man
and her little girl,
"I will turn back
into an ordinary rose,
'but my heart will belong to
you through all eternity".
- It was from then
on that the rose
as we know it grew thorns
so it could never
be captured again.
- So the rose's thorns are proof
of the Rose Princess'
love, right?
Nice story.
- I don't wanna
become that master
who only knew how to
confine her with walls.
On the other hand,
I'm not in a position
to throw everything away
and flee with the
Rose Princess either.
- Hmm.
- But if I could be
the man who loved her,
if I could be the
man who was loved
by the princess in return.
- It's kind of strange.
I don't have any mysterious
power like the Rose Princess,
and I'm not beautiful like her,
but maybe I do have thorns.
- You have thorns so that
no one can capture you.
Is that it?
(snoring lightly)
(birds cawing)
- What did you say?
They've left for Korin?
- Apparently they set
off yesterday morning.
That's what I was told by the
castles' government official
when I asked to
have them contacted.
- It appears we barley
just missed each other.
- It looks like those rumors
we heard from the merchants
while we were on route
were the real thing.
Korin is under a blockade.
- Oh damn it.
If only we'd anticipated the
actions of Shuurei's group
and gone to Korin instead.
- The fact that they
headed for Korin
as soon as they
heard of the blockade
shows some quick reaction
on their part I'd say.
- Not to mention the
new Co-Governors seem
to be working hard of
their own volition,
both Shuurei and Eigetsu
- I found out more as well.
They were able to get rid
of the murderous blades
that were taking
control of the city,
and they liberated
the mayor of Kinka
who had been placed
in confinement.
- Oh?
- Sure Seiran and
Ensei are with them,
but even so I'd say
that's pretty impressive.
(sighs)
- Yeah, an impressive near miss.
- [Both] Huh?
- Hmm, it's not fair I
can't even get a glimpse
of Shuurei from
afar at this point.
- There's also that
monstrous Sakujun.
Apparently, he's planning
to take the position
of head of the Sa Clan,
and make Shuurei his wife.
According to the rumors, he's
supposed to be in Korin too.
- Well in that case,
shall we head to Korin?
- Huh?
- The woman you love who gives
you a thousand years worth
of thoughts in a single day
is just a short
distance away from you.
Although as a king it's
a pretty pathetic move,
as a man, sometimes, it's all
right to do foolish things
in the name of true love.
- Hmm, thank you Shuurei.
- Of course that's
more trouble for those
who serve a certain stupid King.
(laughs)
- Stop calling me stupid,
I'm king you know?
- Come to think of it
advisor Sho is also
in Sa Province now, isn't he?
- There is absolutely no need
to be worrying about
that old badger!
(suspenseful music)
- [Servant] Lady Aeki,
Advisor Sho has arrived.
He says he would like to
request an audience with you.
- So he's finally
decided to show up.
Far too late.
Let him in.
- Yes
- I have never liked that man,
and unless I miss my guess,
I imagine he's still
walking down the path
of the sly beast monster.
(door creaks)
- [Shou] Whoa!
(horses neigh)
- So that's Korin.
- Ugh.
- How did it look?
- Soldiers of the Sa
Clan are over there
awaiting our arrival.
Oh, Sho Sai.
- Yes, what is it?
- You take over the carriage.
Seiran and I will
sneak over there
and take out those guys
so we can open a path.
Of course, I don't
know we'll be able
to beat the whole lot of them.
- And?
- As soon as I give the signal,
go full speed ahead
down the road, okay?
- I've always held
the basic principal
of only using 80% of my power
while conserving the rest,
but I'll make an exception.
- We're counting on you.
Come on, Seiran, let's go.
- Please both of
you, be careful.
- Look, let me make this
clear to you one more time,
unlike you, I'm
a civil official.
- That may be so, but putting
your swordsmanship aside,
you are trained in
horsemanship correct?
By Lo Raching?
- Ugh.
- As you can see, the road
suddenly gets wider from here,
then we reach the
end of the cliff.
It's all forest
from this point on.
- If they are going to attack,
it will definitely be over here.
- Yes, you're right.
- If we get past it,
then we will reach Korin.
- Okay.
(dramatic music)
- They're awfully late.
- We thought so too,
so we went out of our
way to come to you.
Hmm.
(suspenseful music)
(men grunting)
(yelling)
- There certainly
are a lot of them.
- Yeah.
- Hm.
- Seiran, behind you.
(yelling)
- Huh?
- No Way!
Cool!
- Don't stand there, attack!
(bodies thud)
- That's pretty impressive.
- I can't believe you
came all the way here.
- Yes, I know it's
stupid and I'm sorry,
but at least now we can
swing these swords together.
- Now's the time.
(whistling)
- It's the signal.
- Right, let's go.
Hyah!
(horse whinnies)
- Wait, that's, damn it!
- Nice try.
- Shuurei?
- Don't let your guard down.
- Yeah, got it.
(panting)
- Miss Shuurei, be careful.
It's dangerous to
stick your head out.
- Oh right, good point.
- Shuurei.
(men laughing)
- Hmm.
- So, well, uh, the
reason I came was.
- Hey, we won't say a
word to Princess about it.
- Thank you Ensei.
As for the rest,
I'll leave it to you.
- Hmm.
(upbeat music)
- Well, shall we get going?
- Yeah.
- Let's return home.
- Yeah, we should.
- So the nights
will be long again.
- If you like, I could
tell you a bedtime story.
Once upon a time there was a--
- Cut that out!
You, just what's going
on inside your head?
- You know I can't help
but feel you need to try
to have a bit more fun.
- Have a bit more fun at what?
What are you implying
that I should enjoy?
- Am I unable to
even touch the rose?
(gentle music)
- Governor Hong and her
party should be arriving
in the city anytime now.
- There's Korin.
(soft music)
- [Shuurei] We've come
all the way here to Korin,
the capital of Sa Province.
It may be completely blockaded,
thanks to the orders
of the Sa Clan.
But we're not gonna just
turn around and leave.
All right, Seiran, Ensei,
let's enter Korin carefully.