(techno music)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
- [Narrator] Seiran,
Ensei, Eigetsu and Kourin,
who was acting as a
stand-in for Shuurei,
have all been
captured by Sojun Sa.
His grandfather, Chusho Sa,
is seeking leadership
of the Sa Clan.
Currently, they are
being held captive
in the town of Sairi,
the checkpoint on the
border of Sa Province.
(knocking at door)
(calm music)
- Mr. Kokujun.
- Wait, do you know this man?
- He's the younger
brother of Mr. Sojun,
the third son of the Sa family.
- Ms. Kourin, it's
been quite a while.
- Huh?
This isn't good.
He knows.
(birds chirping)
- [Narrator] Shuurei
was the only one
who escaped danger in Sakyou.
Using Kourin's
name as a disguise,
she is traveling with a merchant
by the name of Senya Rin.
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
It's already been
six days since we entered
Sairi in Sa Province.
I wonder if
everyone's all right.
- No matter what, get to Kinka.
Got that?
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
That's all well and good,
but when is this
prodigal young master
of mine planning to
depart for Kinka anyway?
- [Sakujun] Oh. Mm.
- Huh?
Good morning, young master.
Did you sleep we--
(enchanting music)
- Good morning to you, Kourin.
- Ah!
Young Master!
Could you put on some clothes?
You're awake unusually
early today, aren't you?
- It's too hot.
No one can sleep like this.
- At times like this,
you've got to sleep
out of sheer will.
- Sheer will you say?
Those words are not in my
vocabulary, I'm afraid.
- You really don't
have any drive, do you?
Anyway,
I've prepared some
ice and fruit for you
and I've brought you
your fan as well.
- No.
I'd rather have
you play your erhu.
If you can, please
play something that
would make me feel
a little cooler at least.
- I'm surprised you're
not tired of it by now.
After having me
play every night.
- That will never happen.
No one's music has
ever pleased me
as much as yours has, Kourin.
- Yes, yes.
But, more importantly,
what day are you planning
on leaving for Kinka?
- [Sa Hmm.
It should be anytime now.
- Anytime?
- Huh.
Now, play on.
- Huh?
(sighs)
(calm music)
- [Sou] You look rather
troubled, your Majesty.
- Huh?
Advisor Sou, isn't there
anyone in the Sa Clan
as talented as advisor Sa?
- Why are you asking
me something like that
all of a sudden?
- Well, I've been thinking
about things ever since
advisor Sho said he
would go to Sa Province.
- [Sou] Oh yes, he
went to return the ring
to the Sa Clan's
leader, didn't he?
- Wait.
You knew that advisor
Sho had the ring?
- Hm.
And as for the Sa Clan,
around 14 years ago,
advisor Enjun Sa returned
home to take care
of some business.
When he returned
from Sa Province,
he was quite disturbed.
He said something
about the possibility
of a monster existing
within the Sa Clan.
- A monster?
- That was the only time
he ever spoke openly
of the subject.
But nine years ago
during the Civil War,
When Enjun's only son and
daughter-in-law were killed,
I couldn't help but
remember those words of his.
- [Shi] Hm.
- Sure Enjun was
here in Shi Province,
but how did the one
responsible for killing his son
and his son's wife manage
to slip passed Eiki?
- That would be advisor
Sa's lady I presume.
- Yes, Eiki is the
daughter of the Hyou Clan,
a family that possesses
unusual abilities.
They say she has the
power to see the future.
Pulling off something
like killing
the son and his wife
with Eiki so close by
is a feat that no
one in the Sa Clan
could possibly accomplish.
- So, they assumed
there was a monster
amongst the Sa Clan?
- We don't know if
there is one or not.
However, if there is that
person must be regarded
as extremely dangerous.
- A monster?
Huh.
(calm music)
- You really are extremely
good, aren't you?
Where did you learn how to play?
- From my mother.
She always excelled
at playing the erhu.
By the way, I know you
did put on some clothes
like I asked you and
thank you, for doing that,
but you've done
nothing more than just
drape some flimsy
robe around you.
- Likewise, you don't wear
the cute outfit I
set out for you.
- That's ridiculous.
Young master, I'm
not a princess.
What need is there for me
to wear an outfit like that?
- Because it would
be food for the eyes.
- Just admit it,
it's all a way to
tease and spite me.
- What a strange thing to say.
It's easy to see how
much potential you have
to be truly beautiful.
- Wha?
- [Sa] Although the word cute
might suit you better right now.
(exclaims)
(chuckles)
(footsteps thumping)
(gate creaks)
- You're not merely here
to feed us today, I assume.
- [Visitor] It's
been seven days.
You should know that Ms. Kourin
appears to be
feeling a lot better.
- Kokujun, you sure about this?
- Hm.
You were probably
waiting for Ms. Kourin
to regain her
strength, weren't you?
Knowing you, you could've
escaped anytime you wanted.
- Well, yeah.
But if I can get
away without having
to waste any energy
then so much the better.
Hey, Seiran, before
we get outta here,
we'd better go and
find that sword
his Majesty entrusted you with.
After all, it wouldn't
be amusing if it ended up
getting sold, would it?
- Don't worry about it.
That sword is actually
quite a fussy thing.
It won't be sold easily.
And besides, this sword
doesn't look too bad either.
- Well, in that case,
shall we make a run for it?
- Wait just a minute.
Don't you intend to
save the governors too?
- Did Eigetsu ever ask for
us to come and save him?
- Well, no.
He only asked me to tell
you Ms. Kourin's condition.
Nothing else.
- Then they should be fine.
- But they've both
been captured.
- If they've already
been captured,
then they're not in any danger
of being captured again.
That's why they're
fine where they are.
- Don't you think there's
something wrong with that logic?
I thought that as long as I
let you out of the dungeon--
- That everything would
turn out okay, huh?
- Hmm?
- You assumed that I'd
save Eigetsu, Kourin,
and even Shunki, right?
- Huh?
- Life's not that easy, kid.
You think you're doing something
but in fact you're
doing nothing.
All you do is sit
around and hope.
Hope that someone
stronger than you
will take care of things
so you don't have to.
I gotta say, Kokujun,
Shunki is a lot braver
and stronger than you are
from where I'm standing.
- [Kokujun] Shunki.
- Instead of just
worrying about Shunki,
why don't you do something
about it yourself?
- [Kokujun] What do you mean?
- Even though they're younger,
Eigetsu and Kourin have
prepared themselves
much better than you.
The reason those
two are still alive,
despite everything
they've been through,
is because they're not
afraid to go to the brink.
They're willing to
walk a tight rope
and use their wits to the limit.
Sometimes, you just
gotta take risks.
Before hoping for someone
to come to the rescue,
try making a
difference yourself.
Look, Kokujun,
I do admire your bravery.
Not only in bringing us food
and water for seven days,
but in even as going as
far as to unlock the door
for us to escape.
I realize that's a big thing,
especially considering you're
the third son of the Sa Clan.
If you're elder brother
Sojun finds out about this,
you could be in danger.
That's why I think you did well.
Nobody's telling you that
you have to risk your life,
but there is a difference
between the impossible,
and giving up right
from the out set
on things that
might be possible.
(chuckles)
See ya later.
- Huh?
Hm.
(crickets chirping)
- You really can be officious.
Not only do you tell
him to take action,
you give the poor man a lecture
and still manage to get in
a little push at the end.
- If something good comes
out of giving the guy a push,
then that's all
the better, right?
- Do you really believe he'll
be able to make a difference?
- [Guard] There they are.
It's them.
- Hm.
- [Guard] Don't
let them get away.
(guards yelling)
- Let's clean things
up here quickly
and join up with
princess and the others.
- Just try not to injure
any of the officials.
- Right.
(men grunting)
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
Please, be safe everyone.
- Damn that man!
(both gasping)
- Ensei Ro, that bastard.
He really did escape in the end.
(groans)
Now I'm not sure if you two
really are the governors.
If you were, then why would
Ensei leave you guys behind
and make a run for it?
- That's because,
that's because we are
the real ones, right?
- What?
- Just think about it,
if we are the real governors,
then you people can't kill us.
That's why.
- Get real you brat.
(grunts)
- Ah.
- The only one we
can't kill is the girl,
because she's from
the Hong clan.
Make no mistake,
we're only keeping you
alive for the hell of it.
That's all.
And I can kill you
whenever I want.
Like now, for instance.
(exclaims)
- [Kourin] Stop it!
- [Sojun] Huh?
(thoughtful music)
- If you doubt us then
go ahead and kill him.
However, expect consequences.
- What do you mean?
- If you kill governor To,
I promise you I will kill
myself shortly afterwards.
If I should die
then the Hong clan
will take action immediately.
If both of us lose our
lives on your land,
whose fault is it
going to be seen as?
- Now wait.
- And when you see
their revenge against
the Sa Clan,
you'll regret it so
much that not even death
will free you from
your conscience.
(grunts)
If you're prepared for that,
then go ahead and kill him.
(grunts)
- And besides,
didn't you know that master
Ensei was going to escape?
I remember that man
who was with you before
said that he would.
- That man who was with me?
Escapes?
- Oh, he will.
Don't you ever doubt that.
- [Sojun] Meisho.
(growls)
Damn it all.
(glass shatters)
So, that's it then.
I'm supposed to take
these two to Kinka
after Ensei escapes?
Damn, what a waste of my time.
All I wanna do is find that guy
and smash his head
into little pieces.
- In that case,
why don't you leave it to me
to take the two co-governors
to Kinka, big brother?
- Kokujun?
You?
Every since you fell
under Shunki's influence,
you've been spouting stupidity.
- [Kokujun] Please, Sojun,
I want the chance
to restore my honor
as the third son of the Sa Clan.
(foreboding music)
- And that idiot Sakujun
hasn't come out of Kinka yet.
Well, I guess even you can
babysit a couple of kids.
(Kourin scoffs)
All right, fine Kokujun.
Try to get them to Kinka
as soon as you can manage.
(door thuds)
- Mr. Kokujun?
I wanna thank you very
much for releasing
Mr. Ensei and Mr. Seiran.
- Huh?
- What is it with you?
You're too small
to be so reckless!
- You know, I am a lot tougher
than I appear, Ms. Kourin.
I feel just fine.
- No matter how tough you are,
being stabbed by a spear
will still kill you.
- [Ensei] The reason
those two are still alive,
despite everything
they've been through
is because they're not
afraid to go to the brink.
They're willing to
walk a tight rope
and use their wits to the limit.
Sometimes you just
gotta take risks.
(Kourin sobs)
- Well then, Mr. Kokujun,
we'll be together for
the next little while
so, I hope we get along well.
In any case, we can
finally relax a little.
- Are you sure the two of
you are okay with this?
I am still Sojun's
younger brother, you know?
- That's true.
But even though you knew
Kourin was a fake governor,
you didn't tell anyone about it.
- I have to warn you,
I'm not very strong.
I might even end up
betraying you later.
- Oh, I understand that.
You still have to deal with
your own circumstances.
Whatever ends up happening,
we'll all still do whatever
it is that we have to do.
- Hm.
And we'll probably end
up taking about a month
to go from Sairi to Kinka.
You should get ready
for the journey ahead.
- [Both] Yes sir.
(calm music)
- Its been seven days
since we entered Sairi.
Just when are we
gonna leave, anyway?
(click)
Huh?
- Uh huh.
Just as I thought,
you look much nicer
with your hair down.
In fact,
I wish you'd leave it down
because I like it that way.
- Please give back my hair pin.
I have no intention of leaving
my hair down in this heat.
(growls)
Honestly, young Master.
- If you don't mind, would
you do my hair as well?
- But I thought you just
tie it back, don't you?
- Yes, but it's quite
difficult to manage.
(sighs)
- All right, I'll do it for you.
You might've inherited
the merchant business
from your family,
but that business
will end with you
if you keep on like this.
- You're very blunt.
Why is that?
- Every merchant knows
the most important aspect
of a successful business
is to do things promptly.
But no, not you, young Master.
- Hm.
Very well.
In that case,
we'll depart today.
- Huh?
- We will depart today.
Around noon.
I should do things
promptly, didn't you say?
- Well, yes.
But still.
- Besides, it looks
like things can become
quite unpleasant around here.
- Oh, really?
- It seems there's been an
escape from the border prison.
(gasps)
- They say the escapee's
are an incredibly strong
pair of men.
- That certainly does
sound unpleasant.
- It's rather
frightening, isn't it?
- Yes, very much so.
- If that were not enough,
Sa Province has been on edge
over the two newly
appointed governors.
First the rampaging bandits
and now this escape.
- [Shuurei] Hm.
- [Sakujun] Still, don't worry.
It's all right.
I'll see you safely to
Kinka so you can rest easy.
After all, I took you the
first moment I saw you.
I would never let
anything happen to you.
- Would it be all right for
me to go out for a moment,
young Master?
- Hm?
(murmuring)
- [Merchant] Ah, welcome.
- I'd like some
ganlu tea, please.
I'll take all you
have in the shop.
- Huh?
All of it?
- Yes.
As for payment for the tea,
it should be sought for
my prodigal young Master,
Mr. Senya Rin before noon today.
- [Merchant] Oh, yes.
One moment please.
- At last, I can
finally move forward.
Seiran, Ensei, Eigetsu,
Kourin will meet in Kinka.
For sure.
(calm music)
- [Narrator] 20 days
and a bit later,
Shuurei found herself
staying in a small town.
- [Man] This time they
appeared in the town of Rosen,
it's that mysterious
bounty hunting duo.
- Word is that those two are
capturing Murderous
Blades members
and earning quite the bounty.
- Not to mention one of
them sure is handsome,
don't you think?
(giggles)
- [Woman] The other one doesn't
even look human, does he?
- [Woman] I hear he's part
man part bear monster.
(nervous laughing)
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
They're really something.
Earning travel money as they go
through turning in bounties?
And the fact that
Eigetsu and Kourin
aren't with them must
mean those two are safe.
If they weren't,
Seiran and Ensei
would've rescued them.
I'm so glad.
That's one last thing I
have to be worried about.
- This sketch of
me is really harsh.
I happen to be a
very good looking guy
when I shave my beard, you know?
Anyway, Princess is doing
a fantastic job as usual.
She's been leaving
us clear signs
of her whereabouts.
- I'm afraid we're
all out of ganlu tea.
- [Merchant] A young
lady bought it all.
I remember she was very
skilled with the erhu.
- [Ensei] All we need
to do is go to any
tea merchants in town
and ask if they have
ganlu tea and we get
news about her location.
We don't bring any undo
attention to ourselves
in the process.
Plus, it's much safer
and remains more vividly
in the shopkeeper's
minds than just leaving
a note or message behind,
where anyone can
find out about it.
Talk about a brilliant idea.
- Brilliant ideas are a
given for her ladyship.
- Still, it's really
quite impressive
for our princess of frugality.
To squander so much money
like that just for our sake's.
(laughs)
Guess we really
must be loved, huh?
- Hm.
Huh?
It's the Murderous Blades.
- Hm.
(tense music)
Sa Province is my territory,
as well as you should.
You're the Murderous Blades.
Are you stupid?
You have some nerve
coming out like you did
while I was away.
Trust me, you're
gonna regret this.
(upbeat music)
(sword clanks)
(men grunting)
(yelling)
- Kori.
- Hmm?
(exclaims)
Young Master!
- What do you mean by "gah"?
I've never before
received such a response
from anyone.
Least of all when
speaking to a young lady
such as yourself.
(chuckles nervously)
You just really
surprised me, that's all.
- I came out here to
keep an eye on you
so that you don't purchase
any more tea, but--
- Oh, I'm sorry.
If that's the case then
I'm afraid you got here
a little late.
- Huh.
So it appears.
You keep buying all the
ganlu tea everywhere we go.
What are you planning to do?
Do you intend to
open a tea house?
- That's not it.
Later on I'm going to
make lots of this tea
for the people who
are important to me.
- [Sa] Hm.
So you have people
important to you then?
- That's right.
They're precious.
- Well, I feel somewhat jealous.
- Hm?
- So, Rosa.
- Huh?
- I was just noticing
that they passed us.
Those two mysterious
bounty hunters.
- Oh.
You're right.
- It looks like the
Murderous Blades bandits
and this bounty hunting
duo are both heading
in the exact same
direction we are.
It's almost as if they
were chasing after us.
- You, you think so?
- It must be nice to be
as carefree as those men.
But as for us,
let's take our time
and go at a casual
pace, shall we?
It'll be at least another 10
days before we reach Kinka.
- [Sa] What you do isn't
called taking your time,
it's called laziness.
- Huh.
You have a way with words.
- Huh?
- Look, until now,
no woman has come to
understand me so thoroughly
in such a short time.
I think that means
there's nothing left
but for the two of us to marry.
- Uh.
Ah, you know, young Master--
- I wish you'd stop calling
me young Master, Kourin.
- [Shuurei] Huh?
- Rather then the young
master of the Rin family,
I want you to see me.
- Huh?
- [Man] Rather than the
king, I want you to see me.
- [Shuurei] This man...
- Senya, yes?
More than anything,
hmm, I wish to hear
you say my name
with that cute voice of yours.
(calm music)
- Uh.
Actually, I think I prefer
calling you young Master.
And also, I wish you wouldn't
joke about us getting married.
- I think the two of us would
make an excellent couple.
- Please, think about the
difference in our ages.
- Really?
Our ages you say?
Come to think of it,
your age and mine are
not very different at all
from those of the couples
in the upcoming marriage.
Between the governor and
the son of the Sa Clan.
- Is that so?
The new governor and
the son of the...
Hmm?
Say what?
That would be me, right?
But what's this
about a marriage?
- By the way,
there was a quite an
interesting rumor in town.
- [Shi] Oh yeah?
- Princess' marriage to the
second son of the Sa Clan.
- Huh?
- Judging by your
response, you're surprised.
Like a bolt out of the blue.
But, that's a pretty high road.
Trying to make her
theirs through marriage.
The eldest is our
good friend Sojun.
Then Kokujun is the third son,
so the second is Sakujun.
He's supposed to
be 29 years old.
That means he's just a
little older than us,
and there's a 12 year difference
between him and princess.
- Anyway you look at it,
that marriage proposal
would never be accepted.
And even if, by some
remote chance it was,
this Sakujun man would only
be assassinated immediately
by Lord Reishin's men.
He'd be a goner before
he had a chance to blink.
- The terrifying thing is that
that's actually
pretty believable.
Those two will make
good governors.
I have no doubt of that.
I look forward to the day
I get to work with them.
- [Shi] Yeah.
- Not to mention
you'll be around too.
(wind howls)
- [Meishou] So sorry, gentlemen.
- [Both] Huh?
- [Meishou] But I'm afraid
you'll have to give up
on that day ever coming.
- No way.
Meishou.
(growls)
- So the leader of
the Murderous Blades
is finally making a
personal appearance.
- It's been about
14 years, hasn't it,
little whirlwind and
little rascal king?
(calm music)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
- [Shuurei] A noble lady of the
direct line of the Hong clan
is to marry into the Sa clan?
That is definitely me,
they're talking about, right?
How did this whole
thing come about?
Sakujun Sa?
What kind of person is he?