(electronic sounds)
(opening tune plays)
- [Narrator] During
the palace celebration
Shuurei boldly presented
the plan to make
South Province a center
of academic research.
The news of her success had
reached Eigetsu and the others.
- [Ensei] Way to go Princess!
She's taken a great first step
towards making our
big plan a reality.
- I almost can't
believe they'd consider
such a large scale and
outrageous proposal.
- Utter nonsense.
This plan was yours
and Governor Hong's wasn't it?
- That's true but...
- It will be a
long journey ahead.
But I too will be holding out
to the best of my abilities.
[Laughter]
- [Someone] All
right, let's do it.
- [Eigetsu] Yeah.
- [Narrator] However, the
person who received the biggest
shock from the plan was...
- Ah, it's finally over.
It's been nothing but
New Year's greetings for seven
days now over and over again
from dawn till dusk. I'm
absolutely exhausted.
- Your majesty,
we were thinking.
Perhaps we should
all take a break
and pay a visit to Lord
Shouka's residence tonight.
- Ah. Unfortunately, I'm
afraid I'll have to pass.
- Huh?
- [Ryuuren] I must look over
the New Year's greeting letters
and write replies to
those that require them.
- I'm surprised, I assumed
he would come and see Shouka
the moment he got
the opportunity.
- Well that's his
royal spirit for you.
- Yes but all the same I was
secretly hoping for him to say
and do things somewhat
differently. You
think so too right?
- [Kouyuu] So she's not here?
- [Shouka] Afraid not, right
now she and Lord Yushun
are running around
doing errands I gather.
- Is that so?
- Well, it's not as if Shuurei's
reason for coming home is
just to visit, right?
- You're right, I suppose not.
We're both terribly sorry
for our thoughtlessness.
- We'll be sure to send her
a letter first next time.
- As a matter of fact,
Shuurei really wanted
to see the two of you. She
was saying that she'd like
to invite both of
you for dinner once
everything has settled
down and so on.
- Really? She's matured so much.
- She'd be glad to
hear you say so.
She said she didn't
want you to think
she'd just come
home to have fun.
- [ Shouka] And even
if you didn't think so,
she said you wouldn't
acknowledge her
unless she worked hard
enough for two people.
- Shuurei really
is an admirable,
hardworking young
lady isn't she?
Could you please give this
to her when she gets home?
- [Shouka] Oh. Thank you
very much for the gift.
- Goodbye.
- We'll drop by again.
- Great, I'll be expecting you.
- Oh. Speaking of which, has
His Majesty been in touch
with you since
Shuurei came home?
- [Shouka] No, not even once.
- Is that so?
- Huh? Something wrong?
- Not really, it's just that
His Majesty hasn't stopped
working lately. Even
though Shuurei's returned,
he hasn't even attempted
to meet with her yet.
- Lord Kouyuu, General Ran.
- Yes, what is it?
- Tell me, do you remember what
His Majesty's real name is?
- Uh, of course,
it's King Rikishi.
(calm music)
- [Voiceover] Since I've
back I've only seen Eiuki
face-to-face once,
at the celebration.
(gasps)
- Why don't we stop there
and call it a day,
Governor Hong?
- No, I want to
continue checking into
Royal Council Research
Institutions a bit more.
But you shouldn't leave Miss
Rin Sai alone any longer.
I don't want to keep
you from your Honeymoon.
- Don't worry, she has her
own business to take care of.
For starters, tonight she's
hosting a reception for
merchants from all
over the county.
- A reception? May I ask
where its being held?
- I think it's a place
called Kogaro or something.
(gasps)
- Why didn't you say so?
Let's go!
(crowd chatters)
- Please wait here for a moment.
- You might not believe
it, but before I became
a government official I
worked here from time to time.
Keeping accounts,
doing maid service
and lots of other little things.
- You worked here?
- That's right.
And the experience has
helped me a lot in life.
(dreamy music playing)
- Shuurei!
(screams)
- My darling.
Welcome back my dear Shuurei.
You've become such
an impressive woman.
- Ah, thank you miss Kochou.
(men talk)
- [Shuurei] Excuse us please.
My name is Shuurei Hong,
I'm the Governor of Sa Province.
And this gentlemen is Yuhsun
Tei, Lieutenant Governor.
- [Kochou] It's a
pleasure to have you here.
Please allow all of us
here at Kogaro to give you
a warm reception and
a pleasant evening.
(crowd murmurs then cheers)
- Ah, Governor Hong?
(cheerful music)
- [Kochou] I hope you
had a good time tonight.
- [Rin] Yes, I did.
- Oh, Miss Kochou, thank you
so very much for everything.
- Don't mention it. I'd do
anything for you Shuurei,
after all you're
our pride and joy.
Not to mention our
dream come true.
- [Kochou] Speaking of
which, I was quite surprised
to learn that the leader
of the Merchants Guild
for Sa province is a
beautiful woman like you.
- Yes, but now my term of
office is finally finished
- What? It's over?
- It's something that
cannot be helped.
But I have done everything
I could in the meantime.
When my brother and I
were little, the Sai Clan
was in the grip of
poverty and destitution.
As the Sa Clan became
stronger, so the Sai Clan
became weaker in proportion.
That's the reason why
Shou and I decided
to become merchants.
Within the meritocracy
of the Merchants Guild
we would not have to
bow to Sa Clan pressure.
And we would have the
opportunity to build
on our strengths,
also some of the doors
usually closed to women
were open in the Guild.
- It sounds a lot like the path
that my dear Shuurei
has been walking too.
- [Kochou] Not really, what
I've done doesn't compare
to what she's
accomplished. The sincerity
of the heartfelt feelings
you and Governor To have
has saved Sa
province from itself.
You've been able to
accomplish things
I could only dream of doing.
- From now on, Miss
Rin, will you be
concentrating on
raising a family?
- No, I'll devote myself
to being an inventor
- Huh? An inventor?
- I entered the Merchants
Guild in the first place
because I was praised
for my inventions.
I'm thinking that in
the future I would like
to invent things
that will benefit
the lives of people
who can't move freely.
After all if my dear
husband can maintain
the balance between his work
and his love for his wife
then I should be
able to do it too.
(clears throat)
- [Shuurei Voiceover] A
balance between work and love?
I'm home!
- [Shouka] Welcome back,
you're here in perfect time.
- I had just finished brewing
some tea when you got in.
- [Shuurei Voiceover] But
the tea father brews is...
So bitter!
Huh?
- Nothing. I'm glad that
the flavor hasn't changed.
- Well, I'm happy to hear that.
- Hey, by the way,
where's Sieran?
- He's gone out
- I see.
- Speaking of which, Lord
Kouyuu and General Ran
stopped by today.
They brought along
a lot of groceries for dinner.
- Father? Now that
I think about it
I haven't properly
said I'm home yet.
Not to those who
took care of me.
And not even to you,
father. I was only able
to get this far because
of everyone supporting me
along the way, yet I...
- It's quite all right.
- Maybe I can
invite everyone here
and cook dinner for
them like I used to.
But first,
I'm home father!
(chuckles)
- Welcome home.
(mysterious music)
- Its been a while big brother.
I'm glad to see that
you're doing well.
- I didn't think I
could bring myself
to see you face-to-face.
I intended to protect
her with my life but I failed.
- I don't understand, Shuurei's
come back safe and sound.
- [Seiran] But on
her own strength. I
wanted to protect her
but before I knew it
I was being protected.
I feel angry and ashamed
of my own worthlessness.
- Even still, I
envy you brother.
Because I don't
even get the chance
to feel that frustration.
(pensive music)
(birds tweeting)
- Seiran! Good morning.
- Good morning, my lady.
- Here, come and join me.
- My lady.
- Hello mother, I'm home.
Seiran?
- Yes?
- You know, this is still
our home town in the end.
It's the place we come back to.
So we mustn't forget
it, no matter where
our lives might lead us.
I used to think to myself
since I was going to become
a Governor of Sa province
I should try not to think
of my hometown that often.
But this is still
the place where
all of my dreams first started.
I know I said so
before but thank you
for supporting my
dream up until now.
And I hope you'll
keep on doing so!
All right! I'm going to
prepare a feast tonight,
the first time in a while.
Seiran, I'll need you to help.
(traditional music)
(sound of chopping)
(glass squeaking)
- Master?
(chuckles)
- You know, seeing you two
working around the house
like this again is really
making me quite misty eyed.
It's like it's so nice that
two have finally come home.
(traditional music)
- Master? I know it's kind of
late for me to be saying this,
but all the same, I'm home.
Right now I feel
emotional as well,
so much happiness in having
a place to come home to.
It reminds me that I'm not
alone in the world. But still...
- It says she'll be
preparing a big dinner
with the ingredients
we bought yesterday.
- But why is the
dinner party being held
at the Palace Archives
instead of at their residence?
(mysterious music)
(magical music)
- Honestly, why are
we having dinner
at the Archives and not at home?
Sometimes I really have to
wonder what father's thinking.
- Perhaps it's so we can
have Senior Secretary Kou,
Assistant Secretary Kei
and some other people
drop by for a bit.
- Yeah, I suppose you're right.
- [Seiran] My lady.
- What is it?
(gasps)
No wonder I was
beginning to feel cold.
- That's right.
- It's so beautiful.
- [Hakumei] Wow,
this looks delicious.
- [Shuurei] Hakumei?
- So you have a talent
for home cooking as well?
- Yes, please have as
much as you'd like.
- Thank you.
- Oh my.
This looks like a sumptuous
feast, doesn't it?
- Welcome everyone.
- Oh the meal looks delicious.
- Did you make all of
this yourself, Shuu?
- Uh-huh!
- Wow, you're amazing.
- Lord Kouyuu, General
Ran, I'm so sorry
I was out yesterday
and I missed you.
- Not at all, I'm the
one who feels sorry
for intruding the way we did.
- Kouyuu's been feeling
incredibly remorseful
for what happened last night.
- Really? But I was very happy.
When I heard that you
two came by to visit me
I got all nostalgic
for the old days,
and it also gave me a great
sense of encouragement.
(nervously laughs)
- Oh my, this bean cake.
- Advisor Shou and Advisor
Sou, when did you get here?
- Mind if a couple of
old men join the party?
- Not at all,
please. Now everyone,
let's eat before it gets cold.
- Yeah! Let's dig in.
(chatter)
- Everyone,
I wanted to say this sooner but,
I, Shuurei Hong am glad to be
home safe from Sa province.
(giggles)
(men chuckle)
- Welcome back home Shuu, you
really have come a long way.
- It feels like almost
a hundred years ago
that you were still an
initiate in training.
- It sure brings back memories.
To think the whole thing
started from a sweet
bean bun like this.
- Yes, it was thanks to
your strong recommendation
and quick thinking that Shuurei
first entered the Palace.
(serene music)
- [Shuurei] Now everyone,
please enjoy the food
before it gets cold. Hey Seiran,
you come over here too,
don't be a wallflower.
- Ugh. Everyone's
having such a good time.
- Why don't you enjoy
yourself too elder brother?
Now if you'll excuse
me I'm going to sample
a bit of Shuurei's cooking.
(grunts angrily)
- Big brother, you
going in there too?
- Well, I am the one who
manages the Archives after all.
- [Reishin] And just like
that you all desert me.
- [Shouka] No
one's stopping you,
why don't you go
in and join them?
- I guess I'll just
continue watching
over her from the shadows.
- Like I've always
been telling you,
you should just properly
introduce yourself as her uncle.
- I'm so lonely.
- There's someone even
lonelier than you.
He's a man who was
possessed by loneliness
from which he can never escape.
The more he behaves
like a true king,
the lonelier and more
isolated he becomes.
- [Reishin] But that's what it
means to be the King, right?
- Yes it is,
but still,
he has a dream that he was
never expected to have.
(laughter)
- [Reishin] You're saying
that dream is Shuurei?
- From now on as he
gains a reputation
as kingdom ruler there will
be fewer and fewer people
who see him just as Ryuuki.
- And your point is?
- That in the end, Shuurei
is and will always be
the only person who will still
call him by his real name.
You were lucky enough to
have Shuurei and Lord Kouyuu
as well as Senior
Secretary Kourin.
If Seiran had walked the
road to becoming King,
he wouldn't be
standing over there--
- Hey, what are you doing
over here by yourself
- He wouldn't have Ensei
- Come on Seiran,
- or anyone else
- let's get some food in him
- Right now Seiran is able to
grab everything he cherishes
and hold on to it as much
as his heart desires.
However, from now on, King
Ryuuki will never be able
to obtain anything for himself
for the rest of his life.
He's aware of that, and that's
why he can't bring himself
to let go of the one
dream he has left.
- This is troublesome,
why did Shuurei
and His Majesty ever have to
meet each other, I wonder.
- But still, Reishin. When it
comes to two people meeting,
fate is a mysterious
yet fascinating thing.
(dog barking in distance)
(men laughing)
- All right young man,
- Hey, what are you doing
to me?
- time for a little mid-winter
swim
- I don't like this,
put me down.
(water splashes)
- Shuurei?
- What?
- Yes? Oh, father.
- There's somewhere I'd like you
to deliver a few bean buns to.
(ominous music playing)
- I don't get it,
there's no one here.
(ominous music continues)
(wind whooshes)
- Why are you?
- I could ask you the same.
- I come here every
night, since...
I guess it's been ever since
you returned from Sa province.
- Um, you know, I was
able to accomplish
a little bit while
I was over there.
Oh, but you already know, of
course, cause you're the king.
I think I might've even
matured a little bit.
I'm back home,
Ryuuki.
(slaps face)
What, what's the matter?
- Shuurei
Shuurei,
Shuurei.
You really did it. You kept
your promise after all.
- [ Ryuuki Voiceover]
I want you to see me
not as a king but as who I am.
- [Shuurei] To tell the truth,
I thought about you a lot,
in fact, I was afraid that the
longer I was away from you,
the more I'd see you as a good
king before anything else.
- [Ryuuki] It's all right,
it's not important now.
I confess, I couldn't
help but feel lonely
without you here with me.
I love you.
I love you Shuurei.
You
and only you,
forever.
(romantic music)
But, why?
- Don't you why me! Now,
sit down, right now.
- Right.
- I've had a lot of time
to think about life and romance
while I was in Sa province.
- Okay.
- And while I was thinking
I realized I still have a
lot of gaps in my defenses,
because of that I've
decided to make my heart
totally steadfast
against men from now on.
- What? Well, I
wouldn't mind if you
made an exception in my case.
- And, there's one more
thing I've decided.
If I learn that someone
has feelings for me,
I'll think about it carefully,
then give them my answer
as soon as possible.
And that's--
- You don't have to say it now.
I'm not in any hurry.
I'll be waiting for you, always.
No matter how far into
the future it may be,
or however far away you are,
I know that day will come.
My dream,
is here.
It has been ever
since the first time
we met each other
under these trees.
(end credits play)
You know... I'm
not going to change
Yeah I already knew
I want to keep
moving further ahead
So... things might never
change from how they are now
I know
Even so?
Even So
Even so ...I'll wait forever