(cool music)
(smooth music)
(flute music)
- [Narrator] One
month has passed since
Shuurei entered the
imperial palace.
In accordance with
his promise to her,
Ryuuki has attended
court section
every morning without fail.
And in the afternoon,
he's made a routine
of attending everyone
of Kouyuu's lessons
together with Shuurei.
- Well then I think we've
done enough for today.
- Right.
- Thank you very
much for teaching us.
So, tell me what
issue were discuss
in this morning's court session.
- Today we mainly discuss the
general lack of tax revenue.
- The lack of tax revenue?
- [Kouyuu] It's only
been eight years since
the chaos during this
struggle for the throne.
The country is not
fully stabilize yet.
So we can't expect
to collect much tax.
- On the other hand,
without enough money
we cannot run the country.
A suggestion was put forward
to slightly increase taxes.
- But you can't do
that! How can you
burden the people of this
country even further?
Instead of that you
should be thinking
about how to make
the people wealthy.
If you do that then
even if the tax rate
remains unchanged, your tax
revenue will still increase.
- Hmmm...
- That's very true! If
the state of the economy
improves the tax
revenue improves too!
Is really quite impressive
to have the foresight
to plan ahead for 10 or
20 years in the future.
It would be great
if you could take
the national exam
someday, Shuurei.
- Hmm mmm.
Yes, I would be.
(deep music )
(violin music)
- [Ryuuki] Brother? Why?
Don't go brother!
Oh! It's you Seiran.
- Please, forgive my intrusion.
You seem distress by your
nightmare your majesty
so I enter without permission.
- Ah, I see.
- Oh, you, you reached
out on your sleep
so I instinctively.
- Hmm.
How would you like to sleep
with me tonight Seiran?
- I, ahh, bahm.
I mean everybody has their
different tastes and so, ah...
- I was just joking.
(intriguing music)
- What's wrong?
- [Ryuuki] You're a fine man.
Perhaps a little too fine,
it's just, well I can't help
to fell that Shuurei
relays more on you
that she does on me. Of course,
You have been living with
her fro a very long time
so I can understand it.
But as Shuurei's
husband, I must admit,
it sometimes upsets me a little.
Alright. I've made a decision.
Starting right now I
will breach the gap
between my wife and I.
You won't need to
stand guard tonight.
- Your Majesty,
please wait a moment.
You'll catch a cold
dressed like that
the nights are still chilly,
won't you wear something warmer?
- I like Shuurei very much
but I like you too Seiran.
(dropping water)
- [Shuurei] Shusui, what
was that you just said?
- You and the king always seem
to get along so
well consort hand,
so, why is it that
you continue to sleep
separately at night? Everyone
finds that a little strange.
- Well, perhaps but that--- Ahh.
- Consort hand, are you alright?
Did you hurt yourself?
- I'll get the medicine
box right away!
- I don't know what
the confusion is about
the king prefers
men, wouldn't be
completely natural for him
not to come to my room?
- Oh my lady, is that
what you really believe?
- Think about it.
Whenever Seiran
and I are together
the king is always
staring at Seiran.
That mean he must have
feeling for Seiran.
- I think your being
oblivious ma'am. Right?
- Yes. There, is
all taken care of!
- Thank you Kourin.
- It's obvious that the
king cherish you very much,
consort hand. I'm
sure we really wishes
to take his time and nourish
the love between you.
- But still we hope to see a
royal heir before too long.
- Don't worry. We're
already planning
all the necessary preparation
for when the time comes.
- Preparations?
Preparations for what?
I do appreciate
you thoughtfulness
but you know this
kind of thing...
Well, you have to let
nature take its course.
- So that's how it is then.
Oh my! How beautiful.
Consort hand,
you really are
good at everything.
- Do you really think so?
I'm only good a
needlework because
I had to repair all
clothe day after day,
of course I'll be good about it!
- I'm afraid that my
needlework is quite terrible.
- Then if that's the case,
would you like me to teach you?
- Oh consort hand,
would you really?
- Oh, what's this? Is
there someone you'll
like to give a needlework to?
- That person that
always sends you letters?
You want to give
it to him, right?
- Yes, I do.
- He must be someone
very important to you.
I'm a little envious of that.
- But you shouldn't
be, consort hand,
you stated the king is
your important person.
- Well, hmm, I guest so.
Shusui, why don't you join
us for needlework lessons?
- I'm afraid I'm not
too fond of needlework.
- So even you have something
you're not so good at.
- I was adopted in a sense
back when I was a child.
So I learned the manners
and etiquette of a lady
but I'm afraid of
this sort things.
- I see but even so
if he brought you
to work in the royal residency
he must have thought
very highly of you.
- Yes, he's a very
important person.
At least to me he is.
- So who is this person?
- Um um.
Come along child
is getting late.
You can learn how to
do embroidery tomorrow
for now we should
excuse ourselves.
- Yes, well then I wish a good
night and pleasant dreams.
- Thank you, good
night to you too.
- I will be taking
my leave as well,
please have a good
night my lady.
- I will thank you
for all you hard work.
- Consort hand, this is serious!
- Kourin, where
are your manners?
- [Kourin] The king is
coming! He is on his way here!
- What? The king here?
What are you doing
here so late at night?
- I am here to breach the gap.
- Ahh...
Those flowers. Are they
supposed to be for me?
- Hmm mm.
- What? Don't tell me you picked
them with your bare hands,
They're all scratched!
And on top of that,
they're freezing cold!
That's probably because
you've been wandering
around with next to nothing on!
Hurry up and come inside!
(flute music)
- Those are pink roses.
- Oh, Seiran picked up those
earlier for me this afternoon.
Here, let me see your hands.
- Seiran...
Oh right.
- Goodness it must
be very painful,
didn't it hurt to pick
roses with your bare hands?
- Not really.
- These hands? They're all
calluses and thick skin.
Tell me, of you practice
swordsmanship Your Majesty?
- It's part of my
royal training,
So I learned a little.
- Oh, I see. It's just
they look like Seiran's.
- Shuurei...
- What is it?
- From now on call
me by my real name.
I just want you to
call me by my name.
- What's this all of the sudden.
- I'm the only person
you don't call by name.
It's not fair!
- It's not an issue
of being fair or not.
Ryuuki, like that?
- Hmm.
- Right, I understand.
But I only use it
when we are alone, okay?
- Ahh.
- Sorry.
- Why is it that
roses have thorns?
- Well is because the
rose princess fell in love
with a human man of course.
- What do you mean by that?
- Oh, don't you know it?
It's an old fairy tale.
- I don't know it,
no one's ever told me
those kind of stories before.
- Once upon a time,
there was a very
beautiful princess called
"the rose princess",
she had the amazing power
to heal all injuries
and cure any illnesses,
so many people
ask for her hand in marriage.
You're so hopeless.
Now then, where should I sleep?
This guy only likes
men in that kind of way
so is not like he's gonna
try anything weird with me.
At least I think, but
still just in case.
(yawns)
Good night.
(dropping water)
- consort hand! Good morn---
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
(intriguing music)
- What the? Your, Your
Majesty, please wake up!
Left go off me, please!
- I told you call
me by my real name.
- [Shuurei] No way, wake up!
Wake up right now I said!
Wake up!!!
(smooth music)
- [gossiping girl] I heard
the king and consort hand
finally share the same bed!
- [gossiping woman] Really?
- Yes. Apparently
one the mates saw it
with her own eyes.
- Well then if
that's the case...
- [Crowd] It's time
for celebration!
(calm music)
- So have you heard Kouyuu?
All those rumors about
the king and Shuurei?
- I'm not interested!
- What's wrong, you're
certainly in a bad mood.
- You knew, didn't
you? You knew from
the very beginning
that the king was
only pretending to be stupid!
Why didn't you say anything?
- You didn't need
me to tell you,
You still noticed it.
- Well, yeah. I would
be impossible to
learn as much as he
has in so a sort time!
There's no way anyone
could just take
only one month to grasp
what I spent years studying.
- They say a capable falcon
hides its talents, don't they?
Still, no matter how
talented a person is
if he doesn't use those talents
he's not different
from a useless buffoon.
As king he must do his best to
fulfill his responsibilities
but he makes no
attent to do that
he still the same spoiled,
stupid king as always.
- If you are telling
me all of this
then I assume you think there's
still hope for the
king for shape up.
- I supposed there
is, ever since
Shuurei came to the
palace's consort
things have become a little
bit more interesting.
- Maybe but if she
finds out the king
is only pretending to be stupid,
how do you thing she likely to
react to his little dissection.
- I imagined she would
be incredible angry.
- Hmm mm.
Serves him right.
- Give me a break.
What are you doing
walking in here
again so casually?
- I came to hear the
rest of yesterday's
rose princess story.
- Then I supposed you're
planing to sleep here again?
- Hmm mm.
- Alright, alright. I guess I'm
just gonna have to accept it.
We can't erase a rumor
that's already spread.
One night or two isn't going
a difference a this point.
- Were did you get those from?
- Oh, father gave them to me.
He said that his younger
brother sent them to him.
They're made of pure silver,
beautiful aren't they?
What's the matter?
- It's nothing.
- Oh, that's right!
(nice music)
This is for you.
- For me, why? Thank you.
Did you make this
yourself Shuurei?
- Well is not as if that
pattern appears on its own!
So, yes.
- You know what, this
is the first time
I've ever been given
anything like this.
- I don't do
embroidery very often,
so be sure to
treasure that, okay?
- Note even for Seiran?
Doesn't HE has
something like this?
- Hmm... I guess
not. I've mended his
clothes before but I never
done any embroidery for him.
- I see.
(dropping water)
- So last night
Shuurei gave you a gift
that she made by herself?
- Yeah.
- She certainly is
quite talented with
her hands, isn't she?
If you don't mind some advising
might I suggest
that you give her
a gift in return, Your Majesty
- That would certainly
make Shuurei very happy.
Women loves gits.
- A gift for Shuurei?
(festive music)
- [Gossiping Man] At any
rate the king certainly looks
like the ruler of the
country now, doesn't he?
- [Gossiping Old Man]
Marriage does change a man!
- [Gossiping Man] He's also
started actively participating
in court discussion as of late.
- [Gossiping Old Man] This
is really all thanks to
consort hand's good influence.
- [Gossiping Man] Look
He retains a dignified
presence even before the
provincial governors.
- Your Majesty allow me
to pour some wine for you.
(crowd talking)
- Now some wine for
consort hand as well?
- Thank you.
- Ah this one is empty already
you there bring some
more wine over here.
- Yes, right away My Lord.
- There you are, please enjoy.
- Oh, yes, of course. Thank
you very much My Lord.
YOUR MAJESTY!
- Consort hand doesn't
drink very much
so instead please allow me
to drink this on her behalf.
- Oh, impressive. I'm (mumbles).
- Honestly, what's
wrong with you!
Did that little big of wine
really get you this drunk?
- Yeah. That's
probably what it is.
- I'm taking you to
my room. It's closer.
- [Seyran] Your Majesty.
- Seyran?
- You've been...
Been poison.
- Poison? Then the
wine you drank...
- That's right, you were the
one that was intended for...
- If you knew it was poison,
then why did you drink it?
You should just have
thrown all that wine away!
- Rejecting any
way pour by other
in a banquet is considered
a incredible rude gesture.
If the king or the
consort would have done
such a thing, it
would have given rise
to unnecessary
speculation and rumor.
- But even so, wait a moment
I'll go get the doctor.
- Don't get it him involved.
It only make matters worst.
- But you...
- I'm all right. The
poison wasn't strong.
I doubt it was
intended to kill you,
anyway I should be fine
after a good night sleep.
Seyran, you may leave
for the evening.
- Yes.
- What about me?
- Please, stay here with me.
(dropping water)
I hate the darkness,
being alone in the
darkness. I hate it.
- Why is that?
- Long ago, I was
often locked away,
in the dark.
- By who?
- By my mother and brothers.
- But why?
- Because I was
an unwanted child.
The time of my birth was
inauspicious apparently.
I was the youngest
of six brothers
so my father's love for
me faded in comparison.
My mother was always
angry with me.
All I remember is
the fear I felt
when I was locked
in that storeroom,
for days on in,
my brothers didn't
treat me well either.
I was the youngest but
I was often overlooked,
if I was lucky, I was
kicked and beaten,
the perfect object to
vent their frustration on.
- [Shuurei] How could they!
- But even with
all that I was fine
as long as my big brother
Seien was there for me.
- Your big brother Seien?
- Yes, he was my
second eldest brother.
He taught me everything he could
from literature from math, when
my other brothers beat me,
he was the one that
treated my wounds,
- But wasn't your second
eldest brother...?
- Yes, he was. When
I was six years old
he was exiled from the palace.
(crying)
I couldn't stop crying.
Luckily, it was around
that time I met Shouka.
- [Shuurei] My father?
- [Ryuuki] When I
went to the archives
I was not longer alone.
But even so, I still
hate the night.
Being alone in the
dark makes me remember
things that I would
rather forget.
It brings back all
those terrible memories.
I don't wanna be
alone with them.
Shuurei would you
play the erhu for me?
(erhu music)
Your ehru's music sounds
like something divine.
It's so gentle and
warm in my heart.
(dropping water)
(flute music)
- Ah, Ryuuki! How
are you feeling?
- Don't worry, I'm fine now.
- Oh, thank goodness.
What's this on my hair?
- Actually, I had
originally planned
to give it to you yesterday.
- What? But, but this is...
One of this will fetch enough
money to build two
or three warehouses.
- Oh, really?
- Honestly, well anyway,
thank you very much.
Does it suit me?
- You look beautiful.
- What, what are you saying?
- So, from now on, is it
alright if I sometimes
come to listen to
you play the erhu?
- You can't sleep
alone, can you?
Well, I supposed
I can't be help.
(firmly steps)
- Lord Kouyuu Li,
Lord Shuuei Ran...
The king has sent me
to offer his greetings
and give these to you both.
- You mean the king is
offering these two flowers?
- Yes.
- Well, well. This
really is something.
I never expected
it to come to this.
But I didn't think you
usually use fresh flowers,
they are so common and vague.
- Indeed, I said the same
thing to the king, My Lord,
but he said it was urgent
and bid me to pick them
myself and delivery
to you right away.
- So he said is urgent.
Ah, I see. In that case,
I'll make my decision now.
How about you? What are
you going to decide?
- Please report to
the king that we have
both accepted the
flowers he offered.
- [Delivery Man] Yes My Lord.
- Honestly, I didn't
expect you to accept
the offer so willingly.
- To accept the
flower from the king
is to bow absolute loyalty
to him and his rule.
So it goes, but I
wasn't expecting him
to give us both irises.
So I figured, why not?
- Ah yes, the iris.
It carries a certain
meaning, it says
I put my faith in you, right?
- Plus they're purple, the
color of the royal family.
Is very cleaver of
him to use a flower
that conveys a double
meaning. Don't you think?
- Yeah.
- (beautiful music)
- Wait a minute, now
that I think about it,
how we could've known there
was poison in that wine
before he went
ahead and drank it?
Is it possible?
Could it be this guy
has exceptional
observation skills?
No, it's more than that.
During Lord Kouyuu's lessons
he isn't faced by anything,
not even the hardest questions
and during court
sessions he always
seem to rise insightful
opinion when he speaks.
It's so obvious, why did
I not notice earlier?
Ryuuki isn't a stupid king,
he's just pretending
to be one. But why?
HEY!, that's it. Is
because he finds it
amusing to watch me try so hard.
(furious sound)
Wake up Ryuuki.
- [Ryuuki] What are you doing?
- [Shuurei] I'm doing this.
- [Ryuuki] Ahhhhh.
(peaceful music)
- [Shuurei] That, that,
that damn Ryuuki, he's being
deceiving all this time. I
gonna return home right now!
What that? Don't I still
want the 500 gold coins?
Of course I do...