- [Narrator] From the very
day after the inquiry,
people's views and
opinions of Shuurei
had completely changed.
There was no longer a
single person in the palace
that doubted her ability.
With the swearing in ceremony
only a few days away.
Shuurei was intent on
preparing the evening meal,
as usual.
- So I don't suppose you
mind me staying here again,
huh Princess?
- You intend on staying here
even if I say no don't you?
(laughs) - You got that right.
To think someone this small has
become jogen this year, huh?
Quit amazing if I
do say so myself.
- Oh I'm sorry, I forgot
to introduce myself.
I'm Eigetsu To, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
- Wow what a polite
introduction.
Please to meet you
too, I'm Ensei Ro.
- What? You're Ensei Ro?
You were selected as the
governor of Sa Province,
even though you've never taken
the national exams right?
- Nevermind the national
exams, it gets better.
He hasn't even passed
the qualifying exam
to become the regional official.
- Really? He didn't
even do that?
(laughs)
- What is it Ensei?
- Just that I passed the
qualifying exam for Sa Province.
- Congratulations,
that's so great!
- Yeah, eh I tell you though
I don't think I've ever
studied so hard my entire life.
Hey why don't you ask
me where I ranked?
- Oh you must have
done well then,
so what rank?
- Second from the bottom.
(scream)
- My lady, Eigetsu,
please allow me
to dispose of this
idiot somewhere.
- Hey!
Passing is what counts! Passing.
Top or bottom, you're still
an official if you pass.
- Just try telling an official
who passed with top marks
that the former
governor of Sa Province
was only second from the bottom.
They probably despair for the
world and join a monastery.
- Well, wow, this
is the first time
I've ever seen
Mr.Seiran like this.
- I guess it is,
he only seems to
act that way in front of Ensei.
They get along really well.
- Well anyway,
I'm afraid I gotta
go out for a bit.
Oh, by the way Princess.
- What is it?
- This time I
brought someone along
with me from Sa Province.
I don't suppose you'd mind
seeing her once you're free?
- [Shuurei] Huh? Who is it?
- Your old handmaid, Ms. Kourin
- Hmm
- Kourin! Well that
brings back memories,
I'd love to see her!
- Well it seems she
has various errands
to take care of in Kyo city.
So I'll bring her once
things have calmed down.
- Sure!
(laughs) - Oh and don't forget
to set aside some food for me.
- All right, see you later.
- This ring is
really badly made,
so this is what the
old man commissioned
in such a rush, and
hid under his wig huh?
- Then it really was
a fake all along.
- Well we had already
figured as much.
- So it seems the original
ring Senior Secretary Sai
was said to have lost
in the first place
is yet to be found?
- Yes, but we have people
searching for it right now.
- The question is
whether that one is
actually the real thing.
- By the way, you've got
quit a collection here
- There items we confiscated
from Secretary Sai,
he was planning to
use them as bribes.
- What's this?
- It's a portrait of Senior
Secretary Sai's daughter,
he was offering her to call
you as a potential bride.
- Wow, you passed on
a great opportunity.
- Oh, shut up!
(gasp)
- What is it?
- Look? Found it.
(gasps all around)
- I had it brought from Senior
Secretary Sai's residence.
- So what do you think?
- It's extremely
well made, but fake.
- Hmm
- Geez to have it stolen so
openly by his own daughter,
and then have her portrait
painted without even
noticing she had it on.
Wow that' pretty laughable
as far as families go.
- But if that's the case,
it still leaves us
with the question
of where the real one might be.
- I'll have my people
continue searching.
- [Ensei] This was
a really close call,
if it had gotten back
to the main house
of the Sa Clan, anyone would
have believed it was real.
- What's the current
situation in Sa Province?
- Ever since Lord
Enjun passed away,
the Sa Clan has
been in disarray.
Everyone has been
fighting over leadership
of the family.
- Hmm
- As part of that struggle,
they've all been
frantically searching
for ring of the
Sa Clan's leader.
And now it's been almost a
year since Lord Enjun died.
- If a full year passes without
the official ring of a
clan leader's being found,
the family is then permitted
to install a provisional leader
and have a new
ring made for him.
- That's right. At this point,
there'd be nothing
more troublesome
than to have some dubious
character end up as clan leader.
It's the regular people
who would end up
caught in the fall out.
In Sa Province, the authority
of the Sa family is absolute.
Only a proper governor
with the full support
and backing of the king
would have the power
to counter them.
- Yes, we already know.
But first we wish to have
the consent of those present.
Is anyone against
our recommendation
regarding the governorship
of Sa Province?
(dog howl)
- You've always been skilled
in so many things, Kurou.
I guess it was because you
have an insolently smug Reishin
and and awkward me
as elder brothers.
As a result you
ended up being able
to do almost
anything on your own.
There's a name they have
for that sort of thing.
Right! They call it
"the capable poor".
- Just what is there
about me that's poor?
- It is only a saying,
but unlike Reishin,
you're very serious. So people
tend to rely on you a lot,
and you often end up with
the short end of the stick.
Of course I'm the one
responsible for that.
Since I abandoned
the responsibilities
of the eldest son,
it was inevitable that all
of father's expectations
would fall upon you in the end.
After all it wasn't like Reishin
was the type of
child who would pay
the slightest
attention to father.
My actions must have caused
you a lot of loneliness.
Didn't they?
- Not particularly,
the way I see it,
I was fortunate enough to
be spared the companionship
of an idiot elder
brother like you.
(laughs)
- When you put it like
that, you may be right.
- Now don't me
wrong, I do hate you.
But still, even now I
can't help but regret.
Regret not being able to
stop what happened here
in this residence when
elder sister Shoukun died.
- Hmm you shouldn't feel guilty,
you were in Kou
Province at the time.
- It's still my fault,
the servants I assigned
to you were supposed
to take care of you,
but they were nothing
more than vultures.
They set their sights
on the valuables
and eldest sister's keepsakes.
And even robbed you
while you were still in
shock over her death.
- It was my own fault for
having been in such a daze.
- That's the point.
That's exactly why brother Rei
and I were supposed
to watch over you.
Since everything had
already happened,
the only thing I
was able to do was
hunt down every
last one of them.
And show them all
what a living hell
worse than death would be like.
- It's not like I
lost everything Kurou,
the most important and
precious things in my life
are in places where no one
can ever hope to steal them.
- I'm sorry brother.
- You came to visit my house
so you could say that to me,
didn't you?
That's a very kind
gesture, I'm touched.
- And just what is
that supposed to mean?
- Huh? Well, that is say-
- Don't you dare
take me for a fool,
it would be the death of me
to have you feel sorry for me.
- Uh I'm sorry.
- You must know I came here
for Kouyuu and Shuurei's sake.
- Oh
- Someday, in the future
Kouyuu is to take Shuurei
as his wife and take over
the Kou Clan as it's heir.
- Well I certainly
won't oppose it.
But I have a feeling that
the issue won't be coming up
for a while yet.
- Huh? Then you
intend to let her go?
- There's no doubt that
child will say yes.
(gentle music)
- Being king is a difficult job.
Hmm
oh Shuurei.
(sigh)
- I guess today's the last
day I'll ever wear this,
my uniform.
Hmm.
(murmuring)
- Now then, I wonder where
we're all going to be assigned.
I'll definitely be in
central administration.
- If possible, I'd
prefer regional post,
and how about you Shuurei?
- It doesn't really
matter where.
After all what we have
to do is still the same.
- That's quit right.
- Oh Official Ro! I
mean Senior Secretary-
- It's all right, they're both
the same thing in the end.
What Initiate Kou just
talked about is the truth.
When it comes down to
it, it does not matter
what position or location
you're assigned to.
It doesn't change what you must
do for the sake of this country.
There's an important
question to answer.
For what reason do
officials exist.
If you do that you'll soon
realize for yourself
what you have to do.
Now then, today you take your
first steps as new officials.
[All Together] Yes.
- Hakumei Heki, you
are to be assigned
to the department
of civil affairs.
- Yes, sir.
- That's the same
department as Lord Kouyuu,
whom he respects so
much; how wonderful!
- The department is challenging,
but we believe Senior
Secretary Ro's report.
It says you'll be readily
able to meet that challenge.
We're counting on you.
- I most humbly accept this.
- Lastly, we ask
that Initiate Tou
and Initiate Kou come forward.
(everyone gasps)
- What? Both of us together?
(crowd muttering)
(footsteps)
- Initiate Eigetsu Tou,
who passed this year
with top rank of Jougen
and Initiate Shuurei Kou
who passed this year with
rank of Tanka, you are hereby
both assigned as
co-governors of Sa Province.
(crowd mutters)
- But Your Majesty, you're
entrusting these two
complete novices with the
position next to the rank
only to a leader of
one of the ministries!
With all due respect, what
on earth are you thinking!?
- Not to mention, two
people at the same time!
- Each of them can do
the job of half a person,
so both of them together
should be just about right.
- [Official] Just about right!?
- Well then, will you go forth
as governor of Sa Province?
Are there any others who
believe they are most
fit for the position?
There was also much
dispute before the previous
governor of Sa
Province was chosen.
You know what
happened in the end?
An unknown young man who
hadn't even passed the
national exams was sent,
despite having neither
rank nor experience, he
carried out his duties
as governor of Sa
Province admirably.
- But that's because he
had an extremely capable
man as his assistant.
Official Tei was the one
who helped him.
- Certainly, that was a
major factor. That is why
we will be assigning
assistants this time as well.
As there are two new
leaders, we will assign two
officials to
properly assist them.
One is Lieutenant Governor
Tei, who will remain in his
current post in Sa Province.
The other is former
Governor Ensei Ro. Step forward.
- Yes.
- Huh?
- Ah?
- As a successful former
governor of Sa Province,
no doubt you will be
able to provide excellent
guidance for these two.
Accompany them both and
go forth to Sa Province.
- I humbly accept this
appointment, Your Majesty.
- And given the unusual
situation in Sa Province,
a military officer is to
be exclusively assigned
to them. Now, Seiran Shi.
- Huh?
- Yes sir?
- As of now, you are to be
assigned as their officer.
The authority of this
position shall be higher
than that of a
provincial general.
Together, with Ensei Ro,
proceed to Sa Province and
assist the two new governors.
Kanshou. Bakuya. The twin swords
once wielded by our highly
esteemed elder brother.
Kanshou and Bakuya were both
formed from the same ore.
And even though he was given
both, Elder Brother Seien
was generous enough
to give Bakuya to me
as a gift. At that time,
I was too young and
small to wield it or
even carry it properly.
All the same, Bakuya
has always been my most
precious treasure. And
now, it is my honor to
present you with Kanshou,
the twin sword that
elder brother Seien
wielded. You are most worthy
of this distinction, Seiran.
(coronary music)
- I most humbly
accept this gift and
your charge to me.
(crowd muttering)
- Finally, Initiate
Tou and Initiate Kou,
we must ask for
your official reply.
As you well know, Sa Province
is a dangerous region.
While we intend to everything
we can to protect you,
our influence can
only grant so much.
We cannot guarantee your safety.
With this in mind, will you
still go forth as governors?
- [In Unison] Of
course we'll go!
We humbly accept this
post, Your Majesty.
- Hm, in that case, we
entrust you with the charm
and seal of the governor.
You can understand that
we cannot make
duplicates of these.
Thus, from now on, you should
each carry one of the two.
In other words, both of you
together are the governor.
- It's unprecedented!
The birth of co-governors
in our country!
- There is still one more
gift Initiate Tou and
Initiate Kou. I wish to
give you each a flower,
from me to you.
- A flower is proof
of absolute trust!
- Until now, Kouyuu and
I have been the only ones
to receive flowers
from the king.
(music)
- These are buds.
- That's right.
They represent infinite
possibility and hope.
We look forward to seeing you
how the two of you are able
to make them bloom
in the future.
Once those buds
have fully opened,
we'll present you a
flower in full bloom.
- This indicates
their potential,
and that those two are expected
to support the king and
the nation in the future.
- It means that those who
seek to harm either of them
are enemies of the king.
- Sa Province, I wonder what
it's going to be like there.
- Shuurei.
- Ryuuki, what are
you doing here?
- I told you before
that I wanted
to talk to you after your
assignment was decided.
Don't you remember?
Shuurei?
I had a very hard time
making this decision.
They say you should send
your dear child on a voyage.
But the truth is I didn't want
to have you go to Sa Province.
I don't think you could
ever really understand,
the way I felt when I
wrote down your name
on the scroll of parchment.
The truth is I wanted
you to stay here,
by my side.
- That's very flattering of you,
but you're more than
capable of doing things now,
without having me
around to help you out.
Don't you think that's right?
And it's not only because
Lord Kouyuu and General Raien
are here with you.
You know what it kind
of hurts to admit it,
but right now, you don't
really need me anymore.
- You're wrong!
I've told you so many times,
I've always said
you're very dear to me.
By that I mean I don't
want you below me,
I want you to stand by my side.
- I can't do that.
- Don't worry, I know.
I know not to hope for
that much right now.
But I do want you
to remember this,
I don't intent to
marry anyone but you.
- I'm afraid that's impossible.
- But why?
- Because I can't
become a consort.
The goal that I'm striving
for is completely different.
- Shuurei, be honest,
do you care about me?
- I do, but I imagine that
it's probably quite different
from what you must
feel about me.
- That's good enough,
I'll say it one more time.
I will not take anyone
but you to be my consort.
I was alone for an entire year,
it's simply a matter
of doing that again.
But still, I am
very lonely Shuurei.
I only have one wish,
I know it can't be helped
in official situations.
But beyond that, I don't want
to distance yourself from me.
I don't want to kneel before
me, I want you to see me,
not as a king, but as who I am.
If you don't I'll be
so sad and lonely,
I won't be able to sleep.
You don't want me to
lose sleep do you?
I know you probably
can't return my feelings
and I'm not asking
you to but please,
don't ever use my
being king as an excuse
to run away from me.
You're the one who found me
and made me king
in the first place.
So running away at this
point would be unfair.
- Maybe but you were always
doing silly things back then.
- For some things, I
was always serious.
Please, never forget Shuurei,
the only thing I want is you.
- I have no doubt that
the woman whom you love
will be very happy.
But I'm begging you please
find someone else to
give that happiness to.
I didn't take the national
exams and work so hard
just so I can become your wife.
I came to serve and support you
as king from
beneath your throne.
- You're so stubborn, but
you know that's all right.
That's because I'm stubborn too.
If you should happen to fall
in love with someone other
than me while you're out there.
You have to promise that
you'll contact me
before you get married.
- Why do you want me to do that?
- Isn't it obvious? It's
so I can come running,
challenge him to a fight,
make you realize just
who the better man
really is and break
off your engagement.
(laughs) - All right I
promise I'll contact you
if I get engaged.
And I also promise that
I won't kneel to you,
I won't look at you through
your position as king.
I'll look at you as a man.
I'm sure you're going to
become a great king Ryuuki.
And knowing you,
you're probably going
to become a great man too.
- You won't be able to
forget me now will you.
- You um, well I um
- Please don't forget, don't
forget that I love you Shuurei.
(crowd murmuring)
- Wonderful aren't they?
- Yeah and in an
instant, just like that,
she's merged the idea
of women officials
into this court of men.
- Yes and so very naturally too.
- [Masked Man] It's not unlikely
that she could very well
go through life changing many
other things in this way.
- [Another Official]
Changing the world quietly.
Little by little.
- One day those buds
presented by His Majesty.
- Will bloom beautifully
without fail.
- We give our heartfelt
blessings to all of you.
Ensei Ro, together with
the help of Yuushun Tei,
may you guide these two
well on the road ahead.
- Yes, sir.
- And you Seiran Shi,
may you keep them
from even the slightest harm.
- I swear upon this royal sword
that I will not fail them.
- And you Eigetsu Tou, as
someone pure and not bound
to any previous ties, we'll
be counting on you greatly.
- I'll do everything
within my abilities.
- And finally Shuurei Kou.
- Yes.
- Now as a woman, freely and
fully do all that you wish.
- As long as this body is able.
- [King] We look
forward to the day
when the buds you've been
given, bloom for all to see.
Today from this moment on,
you shall become the
pillars of this nation.
- [Shuurei] We're getting
ready to leave for Sa Province
and there's just so much to do.
But with both Seiran and
me gone from this house,
will father be all
right on his own?
Will he even be able
to survive without us?