(electronic music)
("Hajimari No Kaze")
(dramatic, quiet
percussion music)
(crowd chatter)
- [Narrator] Shourin, the
leader of the bald eagles
of Sa province, seemed to
be flying as he made his way
to the Sa Clan's main residence,
carrying a message from
Ensei Ro to Shuurei.
(erhu music)
Meanwhile, in accordance
with Sakujun's request,
Shuurei was playing the
erhu for him after lunch.
- Huh?
- [Narrator] Shuurei is here
to search for two things,
one is the hairpin
decorated with a flower bud,
the other is the location
where Kokujun Sa and Lady Eiki
are being held.
(erhu music)
- Well, then, I'm going
to take a nap now.
Please be sure to come
here again tonight.
I truly do not get tired of you.
(door closes)
- I have to find where Mr.
Kokujun and Lady Eiki are
right away!
Jeez, what's up with this place?
It's like a maze or something.
I wonder which way I should go.
Hm, okay.
Hm.
- [Shourin] Miss Shuurei!
- Huh?
- [Shourin] You must be
Miss Shuurei Hyou, right?
- Who are you?
- [Shourin] Your erhu playing
earlier was wonderful,
just like Ensei said, I
knew right away it was you.
- Huh!
- So this is the first time
that we meet, Miss Shuurei.
- But who are you?
- Oh, me?
My name is Shourin,
I'm the leader
of the chivalrous thieves,
the famous bald
eagles of Sa Province.
- The bald eagles
of Sa Province?
Never heard of them.
- You and I are
sort of connected.
You see, my father received
lots of favors from Mr. Shouka
a long time ago.
- From father?
- I always hoped someday I
could repay that kindness.
That's why I came
here to help you.
I brought along a letter
for you from Ensei Ro.
- Huh.
It's true, this is definitely
Ensei's handwriting.
- [Shourin] It's
in your hands now.
- Huh, what?
- Now that I think of it,
earlier I could hear
the sound of an erhu
from one of the outer buildings.
Was it Master Sakujun playing?
It was so wonderful.
- This is... hm.
(ancient music)
- Oh, do you now like me
enough to take a nap together
with me?
- I have a request,
I need a housemaid's outfit.
- Hm, if you wish.
- Thank you for this,
I'll be borrowing it
for a little while.
- While I have you here, I'd
like you to tie my hair up,
my lovely housemaid.
- Hm.
Fine, I'm done!
- I truly hope you find
what you're looking for.
- Hm.
(laughs)
- This is the perfect
outfit to gather information
about what's going
on in the household.
Besides, I'm used
to maid's work.
I'm definitely going to
find those two, I promise.
- Lord Chuushou's a really
scary man, don't you think?
- Now that you mention it,
have you heard the rumor
about Lady Eiki being banished
by Lord Chuushou?
- [Maid] What, really?
Well, that figures, no wonder
I haven't seen her lately.
- So Lady Eiki
must be an obstacle
that Chuushou saw in his plans.
At least I'm used
to cleaning toilets.
- Is it true?
Is Master Soujun really dead?
Which means the next
in line for clan head
is the prodigal
son, Master Sakujun.
- At least he's a better choice
than that undependable boy,
Kokujun.
- [Passerby] Which reminds
me, there are rumors
he's been placed
under house arrest.
- House arrest?
If that's the case, then
he must be somewhere
on the clan premises after all.
(slow music)
- Hm.
A hidden room?
He's not here.
Huh?
(trapdoor creaks)
A secret passage?
Hm, this isn't it either.
Just how many of these
things are there?
This residence is
way too suspicious,
with all its hidden rooms.
And nobody's saying
a thing about
what I really want to know,
like where Mr. Kokujun is.
I wonder where you
might be, Mr. Kokujun.
- End everything,
bring it all to an end.
Just like Great Uncle
Enjun did, everything.
(bird chirps)
(grunts)
- It's no use.
- [Man] What are you
doing over there?
- Sorry, I've just come
to collect the garbage,
excuse me, sir (laughs).
That was way too close.
- So, tell me, have you found
what you were looking for,
my lovely housemaid?
How about a break?
Shall we have tea together?
- I've got work to do!
(laughs)
Perhaps there might
even be a hidden room
in a place like this.
- Oh my, you're
working hard, I see!
- Oh, um, uh, thanks, you too.
- We're all working hard.
We've been so busy, yet we're
totally understaffed as well.
- Yeah, I suppose
you're right about that.
- I mean, we've got both
the selection ceremony
for the clan head, and a
wedding ceremony coming up.
Guess it can't be helped, huh?
(laughs)
But to think, after
all this time,
Master Sakujun is
getting married!
They say his new wife is
a member of the Hyou clan.
She took the national exams
even though she's a girl.
I bet you anything she's
got a big frown on her face
all the time,
don't you think so?
- Yeah, she probably does,
a girl taking the exams.
By the way, I wonder if
Lady Eiki will be attending
the wedding ceremony,
what do you think?
- Lady Eiki?
I don't know.
- I would love to
meet her and find out
what she's really like.
- You're new here, aren't you?
Trust me, you'd be very wise
not to talk about Lady Eiki
too much.
- Huh, why's that?
- Everyone close to Lady
Eiki's been expelled.
In any case, if you attract
the attention of Lord Chuushou,
you're finished!
Rumor has it that both Lady
Eiki and Master Kokujun
are locked up somewhere
because they angered him.
- If Chuushou Sa imprisons
anyone who gets in his way,
that would mean, with
all these hidden rooms,
the most likely place
for it would have to be
in Chuushou's room, but
it's not going to be easy
to get inside his chambers.
- Yeah, that's suspicious.
- How the heck did
you get in here?
- Nevermind that, I
searched around the grounds
quite extensively,
but in that room,
the sound echoes back to my
feet in a really weird way.
- Wait, you went in there?
When?
- A couple of times at night.
The floor has the same
kind of hollow sound
as when I make a trap
hole to catch animals
and I check to make sure it's
all ready by tapping the top
with my foot.
- So, there's a basement?
- [Shourin] Yup, from the
way my footsteps echo,
I can tell it's
deep and spacious,
but I also can sense
something alive
down there.
- You're saying there's
a person down there?
- Hm, I can't say for
sure that it's human,
but there's a good possibility.
- A basement beneath
a private room.
It would be the perfect place
to keep someone locked up.
Shourin, could you tell Ensei
and the others about this?
- All right, you got it.
- I understand now why
Ensei sent him here.
I'll be counting
on you, Shourin.
- So, there's a cellar
beneath Chuushou's room, huh?
No, that's not
suspicious at all.
- And that's likely where
Lady Eiki is, right?
- No, if anyone's in
there, it'll be Kokujun.
Old Lady Eiki is one tough
woman, so she'll be all right.
I can't imagine she'd allow
herself to be locked up
below old man, Chuushou's room
without a damn good fight.
- But what about him?
Is Mr. Kokujun all right?
- If Shourin said that he
sensed a living presence
down there, then
he's probably alive.
Besides, now that's
Soujun's ended up dead,
Chuushou would have to keep
him around as a back-up
in case something were to
happen to that Saku jerk.
- He's a back-up?
- Shourin, go back and
tell Princess we're certain
that Kokujun must be the one
in prison in the basement.
- Mm-hmm, got it.
(ancient music)
(bird chirps)
- [Shourin] Shuurei?
- Shourin!
- I got a message
for you from Ensei.
He figured out the person
trapped in the basement
is probably Mr. Kokujun.
- I see, but how
do I get in there?
- There didn't seem to be
any mechanisms on the floor.
- So the entrance to the
basement isn't in his room,
it must be somewhere
else in the complex.
- It'll be the middle
of the night soon,
I'll go and search
the grounds again
and see if I can find it.
- Thank you, Shourin, be careful
not to let them discover you.
(erhu music)
Say, isn't this residence
just a little too suspicious?
- What makes you say that now?
- This is not funny.
Why does a house need
so many hidden rooms?
It's like some parade of shame.
- Oh, it sounds like you've
been making some progress.
Don't you enjoy the
challenge in finding
all the hidden rooms?
- So, you admit to
the shame openly then?
- Like I said, why
are you asking now?
But of course,
there's only one thing
that I'm not ashamed about.
- Huh, only one thing?
How can you say something
like that so bluntly?
- Hm.
What, what are you doing?
- Between the two of us,
there's nothing going on
that we should be ashamed of.
Or could it be you want
to change all that?
- Enough already,
let that at least be one thing
you don't feel guilty about!
- It's such a pity, you
keep putting this off.
- Hm.
- Oh yes, by the way,
about my grandfather,
he says he'll be meeting
with you tomorrow.
- You mean Chuushou Sa?
Why does he want to see me?
- Well, for one thing,
our wedding ceremony
will be held very shortly.
- What, our wedding?
- Your wedding dress has
already been prepared,
so you'll have nothing to worry
your pretty little head about.
- Nevermind that, why are
you going ahead with this?
I thought you told me
you weren't interested in
the structure of weddings and
marriage and all that stuff.
- You're right, I'm not, it's
my grandfather who insists
on these sorts of things.
If you don't want to
go through with this,
tell him yourself.
- Yes, I'll do that, I'll
tell him right upfront.
I believe in telling someone
what they need to be told,
and now's no exception.
Ugh, all this yelling
is making me thirsty.
- Say, I don't suppose
you feel like brewing
some Gangnam tea for
me today, do you?
- No, I don't.
- Today's tea is going
to be Silver Needle.
Honestly, you have such
expensive tea leaves now,
as if there's nothing
special about it.
It makes me want to
go and sell them.
For crying out loud,
everything in this
house is so wasteful.
- Then marrying you
might be just the thing.
I'm sure it's something that
will be greatly enjoyable.
- Good job on your patrolling.
So, how are things
in the big city?
- Hm, nothing out
of the ordinary.
- Is that right?
Let's just hope for our
sakes that it isn't the calm
before the storm.
Here.
How is it?
Is it tasty?
- Terrible.
- You're so mean, I put all
my heart into making it.
So you're saying it could
never compare to the tea
that Princess
brews for you then?
- A grasshopper shouldn't
try to be anything
other than a grasshopper.
- Don't worry about
Princess, she's all right.
- Hm?
- Once those two are
sworn in as governors,
we'll have her make
Amut tea for us.
- Only for me.
- That's not fair.
(peaceful music)
- Oh!
It's you.
- Hm.
- And here I
thought she was just
another newly hired housemaid.
- Grandfather, I've
brought our guest.
Here you are, go on in.
- Hm.
(intense music)
This man is Advisor Sa's
younger brother, Chuushou Sa.
- Is it, young lady?
Is a member of the Hyou clan
that you look down on me?
I admit that among the
seven colored clans,
your bloodline is second only
to the Ran clan in eminence,
does that make you
too good to bow to me?
- Ah, you're mistaken, it's
nothing to do with my clan.
The reason I refuse to
bow before you has to do
with your use of the Murderous
Blades as your private army.
You allowed them to
ravage across Sa Province,
and used any and all means
to attack assigned Governors
whom you considered a nuisance.
You also show no concern
towards to casualties suffered
by the citizens.
You've convinced yourself that
the Sa Province belongs to you,
and that you are therefore
justified in your actions.
Given that, as the
King's official,
I will not bow to
anyone so conceited.
- After the selection
ceremony for the new head
of the Sa clan, we will wed
you and my grandson, Sakujun.
You shall remain quiet
and wait until then.
- Ah!
My only value to this
man is as the daughter
of the direct line
of the Hyou clan.
He doesn't see me as a Governor,
or even as a person worthy of
discussing issues as an equal.
I decline the engagement between
Lord Sakujun Sa and myself.
- If you know what's best for
you, you'd be wise not to say
such foolish things.
My only grandson is to become
the next head of the Sa clan.
That should be worthy enough,
even for the Hyou family.
- Your only grandson?
What about Mr. Kokujun?
- [Chuushou] I don't
know such a person.
- You don't know him?
He's your grandson, and
he's not the only one,
you also had a grandson
named Soujun, didn't you?
- You say very amusing things.
- This man, he just
erased Soujun's existence
like it's the
natural thing to do.
- It's about my elder
brother, Soujun's remains,
would it be all right if
I could see to his
burial by myself?
- Now I'm positive, Mr.
Kokujun's got to be locked up
beneath us.
Hm, this man has no feelings
of affection towards
his own blood relatives,
his own grandsons.
He's definitely capable of it.
- There's no way that
I can be prevailed upon
to marry your grandson.
You will leave your post
as the Governor here
and become Sakujun's wife.
You will find you will
have a much easier life,
surrounded by luxury.
- I have absolutely no intention
of complying with your request.
- Are you saying
that you refuse?
- Yes, I am.
- Even if it means Koren
will burn on the day
of the Governor's
swearing in ceremony?
- Huh?
- Or who knows?
Perhaps violent mobs might
start fights in every district
and town at the same time,
forcing all the mayors
and officials to run back
to where they came from.
When that happens, what
are you going to do?
You're just a little girl
who recently passed the
national exams.
- I see you're incapable of
doing anything other than
causing destruction, and
yet you have the power
and the resources to protect
Sa Province and its people.
You're pathetic and sickening.
- You talk big, but if you
think you've made an ally
in the merchant's guild,
you're in for a big surprise.
They're merchants
to the very core,
so they'll change
their loyalties easily.
They'll follow anyone
if there's enough profit
in it for them.
Surely you knew that.
Didn't Shou Sai tell you?
- Huh?
- Unfortunately for you,
I've been in communication
with Shou Sai since before you
came into contact with him.
He's given me all
kinds of information.
I've also asked him
to make a new ring
for the head of the Sa clan.
Although it seems that he's
been delayed considerably
due to a large increase
in work from elsewhere.
- You have my solemn
word as leader
that the merchant's
guild of Kinka
will devote 80% of its
strength to the new Governors.
In other words, it
could very well be
that the remaining
20% is allocated to
helping the Sa clan.
- Now you understand.
Just keep quiet and wait
for the wedding ceremony.
- I said I refuse.
- In that case,
perhaps I should add
Yuushun Tei's life
to the balance.
- And what is that
supposed to mean?
- It would be such a simple
thing to burn that tower down.
- Huh.
- In his case, there's
no need to worry,
the two of us already
decided together
that we would transfer
all authority as Governors
to you with the
best possible stake,
so I ask you to put
your trust in Yuushun.
- Okay, Yensei, if
I doubt you now,
it'll put everything
I've done to shame.
You've supported Sa Province
and its people for 10 years,
who can I trust if
I can't trust you?
I declare my refusal.
- What did you say?
- I declare my refusal,
that's what I said.
- So you don't care if
everything goes up in flames
because of your selfishness.
- Since I do not actually
believe everything will be
going up in flames, I
will repeat, I refuse.
- Then you shall remain
in this residence
until the deadline for you
to arrive at your assignment
has passed.
When that happens, you will
be immediately be relieved
of your position as Governor,
and the precious Governor's
seal that was given to you
will lose its
validity and power.
- That's all right.
You may as well know the truth.
Before I came here,
I made sure to write an
official Governor, Eigetsu To,
it stated that all authority
would be transferred to him
in case of an emergency.
I left the Governor's
seal with him as well.
Even if the deadline
for arriving
at my assignment has
passed, nothing will change,
other than the fact that there
will be one less Governor.
- What, but didn't you
come here as Governor
to witness and celebrate
the selection of the new
head of the Sa clan?
- No, I did not, I came
here as a private individual
to search for two things
while in your residence.
- Hm.
- Rest assured, a Governor
will attend the ceremony.
Governor To will arrive here
on the day of the selection
in full formality,
accompanied by Ensei Ro,
the lieutenant Governor.
- You'll pay for
mocking me, girl.
When you see every region
of Sa Province burn.
When you see it in flames
on the day of the ceremony,
you will regret every
obstinate word you've said.
- Hm.
(breathes heavily)
They say that a man's
word is his bond.
But a woman's word
is her bond as well.
- That witch.
(intense music)
("Saikou no Kataomoi")
- [Narrator] The long
awaited day of the Sa clan
selection ceremony has finally
come, so why is that man
so relaxed?
Hm, you want me to make
Gonglu tea for you?
Hm, well you don't expect
much, have hot water instead!