(digital tone)
(peaceful music in
foreign language)
(chimes)
- [Narrator] Shkrei, having
passed the national exams,
is on her way to attend
the initiation ceremony
for those eligible to
become court officials.
It's the beginning
step for Saiunkoku's
first ever female official.
- It certainly is
a fine day today.
- [Shkrei] You're right!
Well, Father, Seiran,
I'll be on my way now.
- All right, be sure
to do your best.
- Okay.
(traditional Japanese music)
- [Shkei] Are you prepared for
the ceremony, Your Majesty?
- Yes, has everyone
been assembled?
- Yes, mostly.
Though I'm afraid there is one
person who hasn't shown up.
(laughs)
(traditional Japanese music)
- What a beautiful day.
- Quite.
- [Reishin] Ah, what a
lovely day it is, KMyk.
The sky has the exact
same color as that day.
The day you passed the exam in
first place at the age of 16.
You spent the rest
of the day running
from high-ranking
officials wanting you
to become their son-in-law.
Hm.
What're you looking at, KMyk?
- [KMyk] I was just
wondering, sir,
about you acting as
Shkrei's sponsor.
Are you still intending to
keep that a secret from her?
- Hm, I have to tell her
that I'm her uncle first.
- In other words, not
for quite a while.
- The best things in life should
always be saved for later.
- Hm.
- [Announcer] Lord Reishin
Hong, Senior Secretary
of the Department
of Civil Affairs,
and Lord KMyk Li,
Assistant Secretary
of the Department of Civil
Affairs have arrived.
(footsteps)
- [Kijin] There's
more of a commotion
today than there
was when KMyk Li
and Shkei Ran passed the exams.
- That was only to be expected.
After all, look at who the
top three ended up being.
- [Official] Eigetsu Tou.
He passed the exams and took
first place at the age of 13.
It smashed Lord KMyk's
record with ease.
- [Official] Second
place went to Rykren Ran,
the younger brother of
General Ran, isn't that right?
- [Official] Yes, but
skipping the initiation
ceremony is unheard of.
- [Official] This
is an odd year.
As soon as the national
civil service examination
system was open to women, one
came in and took third place.
- [Official] You
know, that girl looks
an awful lot like the princess
who entered the royal harem.
- [Official] Yes, now
that you mention it.
- Really?
I thought she looked
more like that young boy
who was working for
the department of
finance last summer.
Perhaps they're
siblings or relatives.
- Sounds like things will
get hectic around here.
- [Kijin] I'm sure
she's prepared for it.
She has to handle
things on her own.
All we can do is
wait for her to claw
her way up to where we sit.
Don't you agree, Reishin?
- Yes, you're quite
right about that.
- [Announcer] The
king of Saiunkoku,
His Majesty Rykki
Shi, has arrived.
- Things are finally
getting underway.
- Why don't we sit back and
observe these youngsters
as they work together
to create a new era?
- [Announcer] When we
call your name, stand up.
This year, passing in first
place, Jougen Eigetsu Tou.
- Yes.
- And second place,
Bougen Rykren Ran.
(clears throat)
Third place Tanka Shkrei Hong.
- Yes.
(crowd murmurs)
- The aforementioned top
three are hereby acknowledged
for their outstanding
achievements.
- Hm.
(exclaims)
- [Shkrei] Miss KochM!
- Huh?
- Big news, today was the
initiation ceremony and huh?
- I'm sorry to have to
tell you this, Shkrei,
but it would be best if you
stopped coming here for a while.
(exclaims)
(sad music)
- Oh, right, I almost
forgot, we're out of salt.
Maybe I have a bag
of salt please?
- Sure thing.
Oh...
- Huh?
It must be getting late,
I'd better hurry on home.
Lord KMyk and General Ran
will be arriving soon.
Huh, ah!
Hello there, ma'am, is your
back feeling any better?
- Ah, yes, yes, thank you.
(fast footsteps)
- Huh?
(gasps)
Ah, hm.
- Excuse me, My Lord.
- [Angry Lord] This is absurd!
You're saying you lost the ring?
The ring signifies
leadership of the Sa clan!
We only just found it.
How could you let this
happen, you idiots?
I already reported
that it had been found.
If they realize I don't have it,
that reward money and chance
for promotion will be lost.
KochM, I'm sorry, but I won't
be staying here tonight.
- What a shame,
that's really too bad.
(bird calls)
(clatters)
- Hm?
(groans)
Let me guess, you got lost
on your way here again?
- Just shut up.
Besides, that's not important.
I'm more interested
in the recent rumors
about you going to
that brothel again.
- You shouldn't be
so jealous, KMyk.
I'm just a normal, healthy,
adult male after all.
- Forget the brothel!
What you need is
a doctor who will
fix that stupid head of yours.
- C'mon, at least I'm
doing my work sufficiently.
For example, I
received a report that
that ring has been found.
- What, really?
- Yes, but apparently it got
lost again soon afterwards.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Is this some kind of joke?
(chuckles)
- Forget it, why
don't we head on over
to Shkrei's house and enjoy
some of her home cooking?
Today's a day to celebrate.
(contemplative music)
- [Shkrei] I don't
get it, it's not like
I've changed at all.
(grunts)
- Ah, I'm so sorry.
- Eigetsu? (gasps)
Don't tell me you got
into another fight.
- I don't know.
It sure does look that way.
- (sighs) What a relief.
At least I didn't run into
your other personality.
- [Seiran] Lady Shkrei!
I've been looking
all over for you.
- Hello Seiran.
- Mr. Seiran.
- Oh, I didn't realize you
were with Eigetsu, My Lady.
- [Eigetsu] Yes.
- Still, I thought I
made it clear to you
that you shouldn't be
going out on your own.
It's too risky and dangerous.
The initiates have just
received their salaries,
meaning each of you has
a large sum of money.
That makes you prime
targets for thugs.
Hm, Eigetsu, you're all beat up.
Don't tell me you've already
been attacked by them.
- No, I haven't and
they couldn't have
gotten anything if they tried.
I sent all the 80 silver
coins back to my hometown.
- [Seiran] You sent all of it?
- Uh-huh.
- Then why did you end
up getting into a fight?
- Well, from what
I can remember,
I was in the estate of
some kind of nobleman.
He was forcing me to
drink wine with him.
And he kept asking me if I'd
like to marry his daughter.
- [Shkrei] You got into a
fight at a nobleman's house?
- No, I made a run
for it right after
he forced me to drink the wine
so I doubt I fought
anyone or made a scene.
- I think it'd probably
be in your best interests
to turn down all banquet
invitations from now on.
- You did pass the exam with
the title of Jougen after all.
Those who place in the top
tier enjoy many privileges
so naturally many people
who would like to become
a relative or an
in-law to a promising
future official will
approach you like that.
- Good point.
It makes a lot more sense when
you put it like
that, Mr. Seiran.
- You did write a
letter to the people
in your hometown to tell them
you passed the exam, right?
- No.
The Department of
Protocols said they would
send a messenger by
horse to notify everybody
so I just gave the money to
the messenger to deliver.
- (groans) Later I'll
give you some paper
and I want you to write a
letter by the end of the day.
- Huh, but why?
- No buts!
You have to tell
everyone back home
that you passed the exam.
It's really important.
Think about all the
people who are waiting
for word about your results.
They'll be much happier to
hear it from you directly.
- Thanks a lot Shkrei.
- [Shkrei] Besides,
you should write
in order to ensure the
safety of your money as well.
- What?
Ensure its safety?
It's not safe?
- Of course it's not safe.
Sending all 80
silver coins at once?
That's way too much.
Even if you go through the
Department of Protocol,
in the hands of the
wrong messenger,
it's only possible
that half of that money
will make it to its destination.
The money should've been
sent in lots of separate,
small amounts that
wouldn't be worth stealing.
- Really?
Wow, you're amazing, Shkrei.
You sure know how to
deal with money issues.
(gasps)
- [Seiran] It's true.
When it comes to money,
I don't think anyone
is as clever as Lady Shkrei.
- Hey, stop it, you two.
(laughs)
- [Father] By the
way, when will Shkrei
and the others in her
group receive notice
of their placements, Lord KMyk?
- From what I've heard,
I believe you should
be receiving some sort of
written notice about that soon.
- Oh, yes, of course, I see.
- So this year's national
exam was rather controversial.
- For starters, how about
your younger brother
skipping the
initiation ceremony?
- I have to admit
that one is beyond
even the limits of
my comprehension.
True, I did expect
him to run away
but I didn't expect it
would happen so quickly.
- A case of like older
brother, like younger brother.
Good lord, neither one of you
can take anything seriously.
- I have to say that he's quite
an amazing person in many
ways, both inside and out.
- That's one way of saying it.
To put it bluntly, if
he had passed the exam
in the first place,
I would've lost
all hope for fairness and
justice in this world.
While everybody else was
studying desperately,
he was always sleeping.
On the odd occasions
when he was awake,
he was tooting away
on that flute of his
and to top it all off,
after stuffing his face
full of a meal I made, he says,
"If you end up missing
out on finding a husband
"and raising a family,
I would be happy
"to hire you as
my personal chef."
And he said it with
a straight face.
I seriously wanted to
kick his brains out.
I only restrained
myself because he's
General Ran's younger brother.
- It's very generous of
you to restrain yourself.
- (gasps) Sorry, I didn't
mean to talk like that.
- Don't worry about it, Shkrei.
After all, you were
only telling the truth.
- So I bet you two
are looking forward
to your new job tomorrow.
- Yes.
Let's both do our best, Eigetsu.
- Yep, you bet.
I'm looking forward
to finding out where
we'll be assigned.
- Me too, I wonder where
the two of us will end up.
Although to be
completely honest,
I really hope I'm not assigned
anywhere near the
central palace.
What should I do?
Secretary Kou will
find out for sure.
But then again, he
probably already knows.
- [Eigetsu] Shkrei,
hang in there, okay?
Whatever happens, I'll be
right there by your side.
- Thanks for
reminding me, Eigetsu.
(jazzy music)
(foot steps)
- Secretary Kou.
(gasps)
(jazzy music)
(sighs)
- Senior Secretary,
about last summer.
- [Kijin] What are
you talking about?
- [Shkrei] You don't remember?
I was using the name Shu Hong.
- You must be mistaken.
The Shu Hong I know is a
fairly capable young man.
You would do well to
learn from his example.
- Ah!
Yes.
- By the way, are you
sure it's all right
for you two to be
casually idling
out here at this time of day?
- [Initiates] Huh?
- There you are.
What are you two
doing over here?
You're gonna be late.
- [Initiates] Late?
(gasp)
- [Shkrei] Ah, you
gotta be kidding me.
The meeting time stated
in the letter was wrong?
Gimme a break.
- [Eigetsu] We can't afford
to be late on the first day.
- [Rykki] I can only
imagine it's a prank pulled
by someone jealous of you.
- [Shkrei] We sure
seem to be hated a lot.
- It'll be faster if
we cut through here.
- Geez, I had high
hopes for my future
and then all of this happens.
- That's why I'm here.
For the time being,
most of my duties
as king have been handed over
to a more than capable man.
(groans)
- Huh?
- Starting today,
we, I mean, I will be
your personal guard.
- [Initiates] Huh?
(pants)
- Somehow.
- We were able to
make it in time.
- Hey you two, although it's
a little late to say so,
congratulations on
passing the exams.
- [Eigetsu] Aw, they've wilted.
- I put them in my
pocket right after
I picked them, so, forget it.
- [Shkrei] Oh.
Adonis amurensis.
Congratulatory
flowers, thank you.
Well, we should be going.
(traditional Japanese music)
(crowd murmurs)
- [Fellow Initiate] So they
actually came because they
don't know what's good for them.
- [Fellow Initiate] Huh,
a woman taking the exams?
- [Fellow Initiate]
I bet they worried
they'd lose face
if no women passed
so they cut her some
slack and passed her.
- [Fellow Initiate] I was
really thrilled to have passed.
When I heard a woman
did it as well,
it wasn't so special anymore.
- [Fellow Initiate] And
taking the Jougen title at 13?
What trick did he
use to manage that?
- [Fellow Initiate] We've
got a woman and a kid.
This year's a total joke.
- [Initiates] Huh?
- Ah, hmph.
- [Announcer] Senior
Secretary Si and Official Ro
of the Department of
Protocol have arrived.
- I must congratulate you all on
passing the national
examinations.
This year, as per His
Majesty, the top 20 examinees
will be temporarily
assigned to the royal court.
Although it is only
for a short time,
I trust you will all make
the most of the opportunity
and learn as much as you can.
In two months, we will
review your performance
and your formal
placements will be decided
based on your abilities.
Until that time, Official Ro
of the Department of Protocol
will be your instructor.
I'm sure he'll
provide you with all
the guidance you'll need.
(dramatic music)
Just a reminder, they
have yet to be appointed
an official title and rank.
Try not to be too harsh on them.
- Yes, of course, I understand.
- Hmm.
- [Ro] You have managed
to place in the top 20
and are the first new officials
of the present king's reign.
As such, you're
in a good position
to be considered for important
government roles in the future.
Over the next two months,
you will be assigned
various practical jobs
in and around the palace.
After one and a half
months, while you're
still working on
your assignments,
you are to put your
thoughts together
and submit a formal report.
You do not have to submit
this report to me personally.
The content and format
is entirely up to you.
Hm.
Initiate Hong, Initiate Tou,
what is the meaning of this?
Your uniforms are
absolutely filthy.
- Sir, this is--
- Do not talk back, Initiate.
Your appearance is a disgrace.
Were you under the
impression this place
is some chicken coop?
- [Initiates] We're
very sorry, Official Ro.
- It seems you're
lacking self-awareness.
Very well, I'll see
to it that you're
assigned appropriate work.
I will now issue your
designated assignment areas.
For further details
of your duties,
please inquire within
the departments where
you're assigned.
- [Shkrei] (groans) Bring it on!
If they think this is
gonna discourage me,
they're in for a shock.
I've cleaned lots of
toilets in my old jobs.
(sighs) But it really
stinks all the same.
I guess the stuff that
comes outta great officials
is no different
from the rest of us.
Well, at least with
this, the toilets
now look a little nicer.
- [Official] Oh,
it really stinks.
- [Official] It smells
like there's a pig in here.
- This may be only
a toilet but it's
still horrible having
one of those roam around
the holy royal court.
- Hmph, speaking of which, have
you heard about that report?
(frustrated groan)
- Yes, it seems like
quite a large amount.
- [Shkrei] I am not going
to let this get me down.
- I feel terrible
having an honored Jougen
such as yourself do stuff
like polish my shoes.
- Don't worry, this is
part of my job, after all.
- But I guess with
the meager lifestyle
of someone from way
out in Koku province,
you'd be used to
this sort of work.
- Of course, you're
absolutely right.
Although I must admit,
I've never polished
such fine shoes before.
All right, I'm done!
Ugh!
- Oops, oh, clumsy me.
I lost my balance for a second.
(groans)
- Huh?
- We don't have a
lot of time to waste
so I'll need you to
take care of both of us
at the same time.
- Oh yes, with pleasure, sir.
(gasp)
(chuckle)
- By the way, Official
Waha, what about
that rumor going around?
- [Waha] Yes, I heard there was
a ridiculous amount of money.
(comedic music)
(splashes)
(gasps)
(laughs)
(groans)
- Oh, sorry about that.
- That's all right, sir.
- I leave organizing
these documents up to you.
(gasp)
(determined exhale)
(pants)
- Shu is still cleaning
the palace toilets?
Poor thing, it's been
half a month already.
And despite being a
top-ranking Jougen,
Initiate Tou is still out
there polishing shoes.
- [Kijin] Their
instructor is Official Ro.
It can't be helped.
Those capable of clawing their
way to the top will do so.
Don't concern yourself with it.
That aside, Ykri,
take these documents.
Toilet cleaning
and shoe polishing
duties are in the morning.
I believe they
spend the afternoon
organizing documents
in the archives.
Add these to their pile of work
before either Shkrei
or Recruit Tou arrive.
(gasps)
- How could you?
I'm disappointed in
you, Senior Secretary.
People are already making
things more difficult
for them by giving them
additional work out of spite.
- [Kijin] So?
What of it?
In the meantime, why
don't you come up
with your objections while
you read over these documents?
- Hm?
(gasps)
Then, these are...
- [Kijin] Go.
I've heard enough
of your complaints.
- Yes sir.
- [Shkrei] They say
part of learning
is three years on a rock.
I just have to keep
believing that one day
all of this is gonna pay off.
All right, at last
I'm finished here.
Huh?
Oh hello, you're Hakumei
Heki, aren't you?
(bell chimes)
- Hmph.
- Hey, what's wrong, do
you have a stomachache?
- It's not that.
Aren't you even
annoyed by all this?
I mean, come on, you've
been doing nothing
but cleaning these toilets
for half a month now.
- Well...
- [Hakumei] Hm, guess it's true.
Maybe women really
are better suited
for this kind of work.
You're a woman, so why did
you take the national exams?
- [Shkrei] Well, I--
- It's because of
you taking the exam
that I only ranked fourth.
Me, the one hailed by
everyone as a child prodigy.
It's a total embarrassment
to have placed below
someone who is now in
charge of cleaning toilets.
(exhales)
- Hmph.
- [Shkrei] Pardon me, I have
to work in the archives next.
I should probably get going.
- Hm?
Hmph.
(string music)
(curious vocalization)
- Huh?
Mm.
- It must be boring
cleaning the toilets.
That's why I've
agreed to specially
allow you to assist
with my work.
You ought to be grateful
for my generosity.
Make sure everything's done
by tomorrow morning, hm?
- Yes sir.
I'll be sure to have it done.
(sighs)
- You're a woman, so why did
you take the national exams?
(troubled sigh)
- Oh well, I guess I should
try and get some of this
done before Eigetsu gets here.
- Hello, Shkrei.
- Huh?
- Ah, Lord KMyk.
- I was looking for Lord ShMka
but it seems he's not
here at the moment.
Have you finished cleaning
the toilets already?
- Yes.
- Is this part of your work?
- No, it's not.
Mm, yes, it is.
Eigetsu and I agreed
to take on this work.
- I see.
Mm.
Fight your way up.
(gasps)
From here on in, you're
on your own, Shkrei.
Don't expect any more
help from Shkei or myself.
But even so, you
gotta claw your way up
until you reach your goal.
Passing as Tanka as
your age had nothing
to do with my assistance
or Lord ShMka's.
It happened because
you had a strong desire
within your heart.
Otherwise, you never
could've become Tanka
at the age of 17.
There is a place you
wanna get to, isn't there?
(harp music)
- Yes, there is.
- Mm, from now on,
it's that dream
of yours that's gonna support
you and keep you going.
Keep fighting your
way to the top
as if your life depended on it.
We'll be waiting.
(gasps)
- Thank you Lord KMyk.
Thank you for reminding me.
(gasps)
Lord KMyk!
- Ah?
What is it?
It's almost time for lunch
so I'm on my way out.
- Well, you see the
exit, isn't over there.
- (grunts) This mountain of
books is so disorienting!
Why do they insist on having
so many books in here?
Just because it's the archives.
(traditional Japanese music)
- Ah!
Hm.
(snores)
- [KMyk] From now on,
it's that dreams of yours
that's gonna support
you and keep you going.
Keep fighting your
way to the top
as if your life depended on it.
- The one thing that
will always support me
is that dream of mine.
(traditional Japanese music)
(peaceful music in
foreign language)
- [Shkrei] Whether
it's toilet cleaning
or shoe polishing, I'll
do whatever I have to.
There's no way I'm gonna give
into harassment like this.
Huh?
Lord KMyk, are you all right?
You look a little
under the weather.