(singing in foreign language)
- [Narrator] On the
day of the new moon,
in the dark of night,
the selection ceremony
for the new head
of the Sa clan was concluded.
Once Kokujun had been
named head of the family,
the principal members of
the clan were arrested.
In the meantime,
Sakujun lost his final
gamble with Shuurei
and despite her best efforts,
his life was fading away.
(gentle flute music)
(crickets chirping)
- I didn't find anyone nearby.
Look Shuurei, I understand
that you must be worried
about Mr. Sakujun, but
there are other things
that we have to do right now.
Shuurei!
- (sighs)
- You and I are the governors
of Sa province, right?
- Eigetsu.
Let's go.
We'll go and save Mr. Yuushun
and put a stop to
this once and for all.
(chariot wheels rattling)
(melancholy music)
- Shuurei, look!
- (gasps)
Mr Yuushun!
(people yelling and crying)
(fire roaring)
(Shuurei and Eigetsu panting)
- Right on time,
just as I'd expect.
- Ensei, we're going in to
save lieutenant governor Tei.
- We'll have to be careful.
Sa clan soldiers probably
have the prison surrounded.
- Mr. Shou Sai, we'll
need the help of soldiers
from the merchants' guild.
What are you waiting
for, Ensei, hurry up!
- Princess, Eigetsu, now
just hold on for a minute.
- We can't wait!
- If we don't get in
there and save him,
lieutenant governor Tei will--
- [Yuu] It won't be
necessary to save anyone.
- Official Yuu!
What do you mean, it won't
be necessary to save anyone?
He's in danger!
- Yuushun Tei is already
safe and out of prison.
As a matter of fact,
he's on his way
to Korin castle right now.
- Then Lieutenant
Governor Tei is all right?
But where is he now?
- Right here.
He's standing right in
front of you, princess.
- Then you mean...
(dramatic music)
(flame whooshes)
- Yosei Sho.
You were the one who
killed Enjun, weren't you?
- That's right.
Would it be easier for you
to hit me in this form?
- I would rather hit
you as an old man.
That way there's a
better chance you'll die.
- You've always been a
very scary woman, Eiki.
(hand slapping)
- I always knew. (sighs)
I knew that Enjun would
eventually be killed by you.
I knew it from the start.
That's why I've always
hated you with all my heart!
You were the only one that my
husband would ever focus on!
(whimpers) He was so
busy chasing after you
that he only stopped to look
back at me occasionally.
But in the end I didn't mind.
It was enough for me just
to love him and be his wife.
- Eiki.
- However, that doesn't
mean my heart is kind enough
to forgive you for your
miserable existence.
You were always interfering
in my relationship
with Enjun, even
to the very end!
But there was something he once
said to me a long time ago.
- [Enjun] I feel like
the manner of my death
has already been decided.
- Enjun. (gasps)
- When the time comes,
I want you to promise
not to cry for me because I
know I'll pass away satisfied.
- (whimpers)
(melancholy music)
- Did Enjun, did he
at least die happy?
- He lived as he wanted
until his last moment.
- [Eiki] Is that so?
Did he say anything
about me before he died?
That's why he was
always the worst lover.
- Even so, I know
Enjun loved you
more than anything
else in the world.
- I knew that
already, I don't need
someone like you to tell me!
He was simply that kind of man
and that's the reason
I loved him so much!
I have no regrets.
- Live a long and
peaceful life, Eiki.
When I get home, I'll send you
some wrinkle-removing cream.
People in the Capitol
say it's very effective.
(fan whirring)
Ugh!
- Get out of my house,
don't you ever let me
see your face again!
- There's something
I forgot to tell you.
Just so you know, Kokujun
didn't kill anyone.
But then, you knew
that didn't you?
(crickets chirping)
- [Tei] It'll be daybreak soon.
- I still can't believe it.
Official Yuu was actually
Lieutenant Governor Tei
all this time?
- Huh?
Well, as they say,
to fool your enemies,
start by fooling your
friends! (laughs)
- [Tei] I'm truly sorry
for deceiving you.
- [Eigetsu] But how exactly
were you able to escape
from that prison tower?
- To be honest, I
don't even know myself.
You see, I had entrusted the
task to master Naan, but--
- Master Naan?
- He's Ensei's
mentor, you could say.
All I remember was that I was
suddenly struck from behind.
(fist thumping)
- You mean he punched you out?
- My master's always
been enthusiastic.
- I was knocked unconscious
and when I came to,
I found myself
abandoned in Kinka.
- He left you there?
- Hey, my teacher's
a generous guy.
- That's not what
the problem is.
- I was surprised too.
I woke up feeling really cold.
That was how I realized
I was in Kinka. (laughs)
(Eigetsu and Shuurei
chuckling nervously)
- Lieutenant governor
Tei, were you the one
who dispatched the
provincial guards?
- [Tei] Yes, I
imagined that by now
the people who accepted
Chuushuo Sa's orders
and attempted to set
fire to the city of Korin
had been found and arrested.
Of course, I had
the two bald eagles
of Sa province helping as well.
- Huh?
- With the head of
the Sa clan decided,
the two provincial governors
safely inside Korin castle,
and the town no longer in
danger of going up in flames,
we can welcome this
morning in peace.
All is right with
the world, indeed.
- [Men] Heave ho!
(building creaking)
- Heave, that's right!
(building crashing)
(gentle flute music)
- Chuushuo's trap has
crumbled and fallen at last.
The long darkness has
finally come to an end.
- A new day is about to begin.
(gentle guitar music)
(footsteps tapping)
- I suppose my punishment
has been decided.
Governor Hong and
governor To, I promise
in order to atone for
the countless wrongdoings
committed by my clan, I shall
humbly accept any punishment.
(water trickling)
Is it okay for me to be
walking around free like this?
- We've decided not to
charge you with any crime.
- But considering everything
the Sa clan has done
up until now, it wouldn't
be out of the question
for you to have me beheaded!
- Executing you would
accomplish nothing.
It wouldn't change
the past at all.
- Rebuilding the Sa clan
is what you should be
focusing on now, Mr. Kokujun.
- Lord Kokujun.
- [Shuurei] I know
you'll do your best.
Hand-in-hand with Shunki.
(uplifting music)
(birds chirping)
- [Shunki] Grandmother?
- I realize you must
all be busy dealing
with everything the
Sa clan has done.
Please forgive me for asking
you to come all this way.
It won't take long.
- What is it you
wanted to tell us?
- It's time I finally
tell you the truth.
The whole truth of
what really happened.
- What do you mean?
- It's important to those
who will lead the Sa clan
and those who will
guide Sa province.
Kokujun.
- Yes?
- [Eiki] Chuushou Sa and
your father are both dead.
- I know.
- You should also know
you didn't kill them.
I can already tell
from looking at you.
You haven't killed anyone.
It had all been planned
by someone else.
By Sakujun.
- (gasps)
- During that time, in the
cellar under the shrine,
incense was burning.
It was Sakujun's incense.
It took away the mental clarity
of whoever breathed it in.
- [Kokujun] So,
that sweet smell--
- [Eiki] That's
right, and then--
(sword clattering)
(sword scraping)
(footsteps receding)
(Kokujun grunting)
- [Visitor] Kokujun.
(Kokujun panting)
(bars rattling)
(door creaking)
(gentle guitar music)
- [Eiki] But contrary
to Sakujun's plans,
that monster Chuushou
fell to his only son,
the one he had always
considered an idiot.
Your father protected you
right through to the end,
even as he took the final
blow from Chuushou's sword.
- Father, he did
that for my sake?
- You haven't killed
anyone, Kokujun.
And yet you tried to bear
all the responsibility.
It seems you really
are just like Enjun.
- Huh?
- He was said to have
killed all the men
from the main branch
in order to become
the head of the Sa clan.
Everyone believed the rumor
and he never denied it.
But that story was a lie.
My husband never killed a
single person in his life!
- Wait a second, you're
saying old man Enjun
never killed anyone?
- If that's true, then
who killed the heirs
from the main branch
of the family?
- [Eiki] It was a man of the
main branch who had always
respected and admired Enjun.
- Huh?
- [Eiki] That man was
willing to commit murder
and wipe out all the heirs
in order to hand the clan
over to my husband.
Without saying a word
in his own defense,
Enjun stepped forward
and took all the blame
upon his shoulders.
- Great uncle did that?
- I don't understand why
Advisor Sa would be willing
to take all of the blame
without clearing his name.
- I think that I
finally understand!
I've been thinking
about it for a while,
about why Advisor Sa
would start a rebellion.
- Huh?
- I always thought he started
it because he wanted power!
- That's right.
That's how most people saw it.
But the truth was very
different, wasn't it?
Advisor Sa wasn't
doing it to seek power
or further his own ambition,
nor was he actually trying
to bring Ryuuki down
from the throne!
He really cared
about the Sa clan.
And it's not only that,
he cared about Sa province
and its people more than
anyone else, didn't he?
That's why he wanted
to rebuild it,
even if it meant sacrificing
the rest of his life.
I'm sure he must have thought
about what to do
for a long time.
- So that's why Advisor
Sa, as head of the Sa clan,
felt he had to take
action and rebel
against the King to
get things moving.
- If the head of a clan
instigates a rebellion,
the King would have a reason
to investigate that clan
and then sentence them.
- Guess he saw the
festering rottenness
in the heart of the clan and
was trying to drive it out.
- Then the only reason
Advisor Sa started a rebellion
was to take everything
apart and then rebuild it
from the ground up.
- And now finally, his
hopes have all come true.
The sickness that's infected
Sa province has been cured,
the rottenness driven out,
and the land has been revived.
- It feels like the
beginning of a new era.
- Grandfather.
- Enjun was always a
foolish man, believe me.
But in the end,
this was something
that no one else could do.
Of course, only my
husband could manage it.
- [Kourin As Voiceover]
I'm so sorry, Lord Enjun.
I thought I understood
what you were planning,
but I didn't really
understand at all, did I?
- After hearing this, I don't
think I'll ever come close
to being like great uncle Enjun.
- Lord Kokujun!
- It's too great
a goal for anyone,
let alone someone like me.
But I'll swear it
all over again.
I'll spend my life working hard
to take even one step closer
to being like him.
- Yes, and I'll be sure to
be by your side helping you.
- Oh, come to think of it.
Shunki, Kokujun.
- Yes?
- You had better see
a fortune-teller soon
to choose an auspicious
date for your wedding night.
(everyone giggling and laughing)
(slow somber music)
- (crying)
- My lady, are you awake yet?
- Yes.
- You should start getting ready
for the governor's
swearing-in ceremony.
- [Shuurei] Thanks, I'll
start preparing right away.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Yuushun.
I feel bad about having
you help me dress!
- Not at all.
It's fine by me.
Besides, unless I miss my guess,
it's better for Kourin
to help governor To
get dressed and prepared,
wouldn't you say?
- (laughs) Absolutely.
- I can't believe this.
Why on earth am I
stuck helping you
get ready for the ceremony?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- (chuckles)
- Mr. Yuushun?
- It's nothing.
I was just thinking
about that little girl
and how happy I am to see
her all grown up like this.
- Wait a minute, have
we met somewhere before?
- In a manner of speaking.
It's more like I was
forcibly dragged along
by a couple of friends to
secretly watch over you.
(slow sentimental music)
- (chuckles)
- Huh?
- [Eigetsu] Shuurei!
- Oh, looks like you're all
dressed up and ready to go!
- And it looks like
you're all ready, too!
- Lady Shuurei, you're
incredibly beautiful!
- [Shuurei] Come on,
you're exaggerating!
- But in comparison, this
little idiot can't even tie up
his own sash without someone
there to hold his hand!
Really, you need to
pull yourself together!
- Well, shall we be on
our way, governor Hong?
- Please wait, not just yet.
Before we go--
- Hey, what the--
- I, Shuurei Hong, hope to
follow in both your footsteps
and fulfill the royal mandate
with which we have
been presented.
To that end, I will work with
utmost diligence every day.
I ask that you offer
me your guidance
and kind encouragement
in the days to come.
- Likewise, I, Eigetsu To,
despite my lack of experience,
intend to put forth
my best effort.
Please do me the kindness
of offering your guidance.
- Ah, you're making me blush.
Look, enough of this!
You can stand up now.
- He's right, you know.
After today's ceremony,
you can't do anything
like this again in public.
You must always be
aware of the differences
in rank, Governor.
- Jeez, you kids.
- Now, it's time to go.
- Right.
(intense music)
(Shuurei and Eigetsu gasping)
- We're not exactly being
welcomed with open arms.
- Oh, we just have very
stern-faced officials
in our province.
Underneath that, they're
all happy to welcome
two adorable young
governors like you.
It'll be a change from
the previous unsteady
and unlovable governor.
- Is that so?
- Well, excuse me,
if I wasn't lovable.
- Governor Hong and Governor To.
From the bottom of our
hearts, we hereby declare
our sincere joy upon your
acceptance of this position.
From this moment on, all the
officials within the government
of Sa province offer to support,
guide, and serve you both.
- [Shuurei] I, Shuurei Hong.
- And I, Eigetsu To.
- Will from now on,
- devote our entire efforts
- to the governing
- of Sa province.
- Of Sa province.
(officials cheering
and applauding)
- What?
- What's going on?
- Like I said, despite
their stern looks,
they're all extremely happy
to welcome the two of you.
- Oh, yeah.
- Aah, finally, everyone's
here together again.
Let's do our best from now on!
(crickets chirping)
- So, you made it home at last.
Then it's all over?
- It's over.
- I see.
It's finally finished.
- [Shou] The governors have
arrived at their assignment
and the new head of the
Sa clan has been decided.
- Is he similar to Enjun at all?
- He's still a long way
from matching Enjun.
But yes, he's like him.
He's in the habit of being too
kind for his own good though.
- Now that
everything's in order,
Enjun's soul can
finally rest in peace.
- Shou, I'm sure you realize
I'll be dying before you
in the not-too-distant future.
- You shouldn't talk about
such an unlucky subject.
- Enjun and I lived
and went on living
for more than long
enough, no regrets.
Even when we're gone, it's
not as though the time
we've spent together
will ever go away.
(sword clanging)
Rest when you're
tired, old friend.
If you grow weary of
living, be certain
that Enjun and I
will come to get you.
- It's a promise.
- We just received a
report from Sa province.
The swearing-in ceremony has
finished without incident.
- The word is that
they are both well
and doing a good job so far.
- Is that right?
The future of Sa province
looks bright, perhaps.
- Knowing those two, I
think we can count on it.
They certainly won't
give up without a fight.
- And they have Ensei
Ro and Yuushun Tei
as their assistants.
If that weren't enough, they
also have Seiran on board.
- You're right.
By the way, I wonder who
will be Sa province's
representative at the
New Year's celebrations.
- Since there are two
governors for Sa province,
I should think that
only one of the two
will come to the Capitol
for the celebrations.
- Is that right?
(gentle contemplative music)
(singing in foreign language)
- [Shuurei As Voiceover]
All right, Eigetsu.
Let's rebuild Sa province
and pull it out of its slump!
As the new governors, we'll
spend every free minute
on the job, and that means
working without stopping.
We don't have time to think
about unnecessary things!