(intimate music in
foreign language)
(intimate music in foreign
language concludes)
- [Narrator] The sky was
clear and blue, however, the
weather is something that
changes all the time.
Rain may start to fall in
the moment you notice clouds
gathering and every now and
again a typhoon will come
sweeping in.
- You look puzzled Consort
Hong is something the matter?
- Shuzwai, I don't suppose
you've seen the ink stone case
I keep here.
- No.
- Excuse me, please. I
brought your tea, my lady.
- Kodene, perhaps you know.
Have you seen Consort Hong's
ink stone case anywhere?
- No, ma'am.
- It seems like a few
of my things have been
disappearing lately. I can't
find my embroidery needle
or my incense pouch, either.
- (gasp) I'm sure there around.
- Well, anyway, I'll
keep looking for
them a little longer.
- Voiceover: 'Hmm. This
is really strange.'
- Suai, have you determined
the composition of the poison
on those items I
gave you yesterday?
- According to the report I
received from Koiu and Dr. Toau,
the poison they are using is
getting stronger: an embroidery
needle, an incense pouch,
and now a ink stone case.
Anything they can get
their hands on, I guess.
- It's more than that. It's
almost like their asking us
to notice all these
poisoning attempts.
- It only seems obvious
to you, Your Majesty.
- It's just that this kind
of thing used to be an almost
a daily affair in the
palace in the past.
- (gasps with surprise)
You're lucky to have such a
heightened awareness of
the dangers around you.
It's what's kept you
safe, thus far, right?
- (silently acknowledges)
- Now then. What do you
intend to do about Suai--
- No need to worry.
I've been secretly giving her
a specially prepared anecdote
every night.
And what about the
source of this poison?
- It's coming from
the same place.
Nevertheless, it
is very strange.
Of all of Suai's things
the culprit chooses items
that are easily traced back.
- Let's not jump to
conclusions, just yet, please
investigate other
suspects, as well.
(a figure approaches)
- I understand.
- I'm counting on you.
- No problem. After
all I did accept
(footsteps nearing)
that lovely purple
Irish from you, didn't I?
(treats thumping floor)
- (surprised) Oh, hello, Suai.
- Oh, I made some
fried Sesame Dumplings,
but...
Compared to dumplings
flowers aren't the thing, right?
So, Sorry to interrupt you.
- What was that all about?
(upbeat orchestral music)
- I would wager
she's uncomfortable,
because she still thinks
you're interested in men,
Your Majesty.
- I'm afraid that if
I tell Suai the truth,
she'll run away from me.
- Looks to me like she
ran away from you, anyway.
- What's with those two?
Are they close enough to be
giving flowers to each other?
- Voiceover: 'That
is quite the outfit!'
- Oh, good afternoon.
- What are those round
objects you have there?
- There Sesame Dumplings.
Would you like one?
(sampling a Sesame Dumpling)
- (pleased) Um.
- How is it?
- An exquisite combination
of grainy sesame seeds,
the softness of sticky
rice, and the sweetness
of the red bean paste.
A triple tier, triple cheer
surprise for the palette.
- You know, a simple thank you
would still be nice to hear.
(appreciative flute music)
- Do you mind if
I ask a question?
Are you playing the flute
as a way of saying, thanks?
- If that is what you think or
feel when you listen to this
music, then that must
be it's true meaning.
- Oh (laughing) pardon me.
What is you name?
- My name is--
- - [General Rahn] Ruidan!
- General Rahn?
- Long time no see, silly
brother number four.
- Silly brother what?
- That's what I call my
pathetic older brother.
- Surai, this is my younger
brother, Riu-Rin Rahn
- Younger brother?
- Enlighten me. What are
you doing here in Kio City?
- A wanderer has no objective.
(Surai exclaims in disbelief)
- Oh, good Lord!
How on earth did you get
in here in the first place?
- What? You mean he bypassed
all the palace security?
- He's always had the ability
to sneak into anyplace he wants.
It's frustrating, I
can tell you that.
- What the?
He's gone!
- Damn it!
- I hear that Surai Rahn and
Koiu Lee have both accepted
flowers.
- You must be very proud of
yourself, Zhou, everything seems
to be progressing
as you anticipated.
- Yes. For the time being.
(startling flute music)
what's that?
- I just heard the sound
of the flute over there.
- We can't afford to
let him wonder around
unsupervised like this.
Come on, let's hurry.
- How the heck did I
get roped into joining
this little search
party of there's?
- Oh look? It seems
that I've won, again.
(groans of losers)
(nagging flute music)
- You bastard!
Let's have just one more round.
- Wait! There he is.
- Please excuse us, my lords.
- What is it?
- Oh hi, silly
brother number four.
- Just what have you been doing
with the three
elders of the court?
- I was concerned
that their old age
was keeping them
from having fun,
so I taught them
how to play cards.
(elders protesting)
- How did this
come about anyway?
- I was complaining about the
awful noise he was making,
and he said he would only
stop if we won a game of cards
against him.
- [General Rahn] Right!
We are sorry for my
younger brother's behavior,
please forgive us.
- Come on, we're going.
- Not so fast!
- One more game.
- Let's go.
- We can't handle
the losing note.
- We will excuse ourself now.
(elders yelling in protest)
- You shouldn't spoil
a game like that,
silly brother number four.
- To get a sigh
like that from you,
this younger brother of yours
must really be something.
- I'd ask him to go
away, but there's no way
he'll just up and
leave obediently.
- Well, since he's
here for now anyway,
why don't we show him
around the palace?
- This is a painting of the
eight-color enlightened ones.
- I can tell by looking at it.
- It's impossible to hold a
conversation with this guy.
- Why the peculiar
younger brother, huh?
I hear he's just
been mostly wandering
from place-to-place playing
cards like he was just now.
- Wow! Intrepid, isn't he?
- But that guy is Riu Rin Rahn.
Only a true genius of the
Rahn family is allowed
to carry that name.
I'm the fourth child and have
three elder brothers above me,
but the only one deemed worthy
to carry the name of Riu Rin
was him, the youngest son.
- Even over his
four elder brothers?
- My younger brother is
odd, but the Rahn Clan
expects great things.
Still, he's always wandering
and even if you can catch him
you can hardly talk to him.
- Interesting.
If he's really that
difficult to control,
I imagine he wouldn't
easily be manipulated.
- Be that as it may,
the Rahn clan considers my
younger brother indispensable.
- What do you
think you're doing?
- I've made up my mind, I'm
going to stay here tonight.
This is where I want to sleep.
- I'm not sure I want to
know the answer to this,
but where were you
staying last night?
- I was counting the
stars as I fell asleep.
- So you camped out, huh?
- Riu Rin, no matter what
your reasons this is no place
for you to sleep.
Why don't you stay with
your elder brother--
- There's no way I'm
going to spend the night
with a tasteless,
unrefined man like him.
- And then how about my place?
- And make Lord Showka
have to deal with this guy?
- Then that case, Koiu,
your place will do.
- What!
- That's a wonderful
idea. Please Lord Koiu?
- Oh, all right, if I must.
- There's nothing,
but books here.
There isn't a shred
of taste in this room.
- Shut up!
- Oh, Your Majesty?
- Advisor Sau.
- Would you happen
to be on your way
to Counsel Tong's
chambers, again, tonight?
- I am.
- It pleases me greatly to
see the two of you growing
so close to each other,
but give this some thought:
I have a granddaughter.
She's just as pretty
as Consort Hong and
has an equally
lovely personality.
- I'm satisfied with
Suai, thank you.
There is no need for any others.
- My. Consort Hong
certainly has you smitten.
- What do you mean by that?
- It means you've fallen
head over heels in love.
Well, fare enough. If you
happened to change your mind
on this subject, don't
hesitate to let me know.
- Suai, I'm coming in.
- Sure go ahead.
(door booms open)
(door bangs closed)
- [Suai] Liaukee?
- Ah, yes, what is it?
- I'm going to read for
a little while longer,
so go on to bed without me.
- You're more determined
to study than I am
and I'm the king.
- I'm no genius,
so I have to do this, but
they always say that a genius
can't better a
hard-working man. Right?
- That's very true.
If you were a man,
I'm sure you'd make
a wonderful official.
- When I was a child,
it was my dream to take
the National Civil Service exam
and become a court official,
but thanks to me
entering the royal harem,
I have all these
opportunities to study
and reflect on the
affairs of the country.
I feel like I'm allowed
to be a little closer
to that old dream. Anyway...
Don't mind me, Liaukee,
you go on to bed.
- Lord Koiu, are you all right?
- I didn't get a wink
of sleep last night
and it's all thanks to that guy!
What the hell is
with this idiot?
I don't get what's going
on inside his head.
First he lay down in the
courtyard so he can look
at the moon while
he fell asleep,
then out of nowhere he started
playing that damned flute
and on top of that, first
thing in the morning
he wanted to weed
the lawn, and I--
Heaven help him!
- I see, well, helping
him out with weeding
was very considerate of you.
- It's not as if he
could do much else.
Really, you must do something
about your frighteningly
horrible sense of direction.
You even got lost
near your own house.
- Mind you own business!
- Do something, silly
brother number four!
- Look, I'd love
to stay and chat,
but I have to take care
of palace security.
- Oh, no. Don't
you try and escape!
- Riu Rin, you strike me as
someone who's above it all.
- [Koiu] I knew there was
something about this guy--
(giggles)
- [Silly Brother Number
Four] Let go of me!
but if you cause trouble
for someone who took you in,
the proper response
is to apologize.
- [Koiu] Stop trying
to weasel out of this,
Silly Brother Number Four!
Come on.
Now, the next step is
to say "I'm sorry".
- I am sorry, sir.
- Oh, it's fine.
- I'm sorry, too, for
acting so self-important.
Now, I'd hate to bother
Lord Koiu any further
seeing that he's been so
kind and patient already,
so why don't we go to my
chambers and have some tea,
and then tonight, I insist
that you come and spend
the night at my house.
- Please.
- Thank you, Kodene.
- Silverware, huh?
I see you're not without your
own difficulties here, Suai.
- What do you mean?
- Didn't you know?
Silverware will change color
if it come into
contact with poison.
- [Surai] What?
- Are you all right child?
- Yes, I'm sorry.
- I don't know what to say,
I had no idea that silverware
was used for that purpose.
Luakee saved me that time
at the banquet, but I need
to be more aware of
what's going on around me
and start looking
out for myself.
- I was wondering about
that woman, Shuzwe,
do you know about
her background?
- Just that she's
my lady and waiting.
- She appears to have
had considerable training
to move like that.
- You're right. Shuzwe
has a very elegant manner,
don't you think?
- You can be so
dim-witty, sometimes.
- Dim-witty?
- Suai and--
who's that?
- Hey, Suai, how would you
like to travel with me?
This life here in the palace
doesn't suit you at all.
(Suai giggles in embarrassment)
- [Luakee] Who are you?
Who dare to seduce
our royal consort?
- Your Majesty?
I'd like you to
meet, Riu-Rin Rahn.
He's General Rahn's
younger brother.
- From the Rahn Clan?
- Suai is not a
bird to be caged.
She's a bird that
should fly free.
Right? How 'bout we have
Chicken Eat Chicken Hot Pot
for dinner tonight?
Yesterday's dumplings
were delicious!
Tonight, I'll return the favor
and make something for you.
- Anyway, Liaukee, I'm
going home for the night.
Okay?
Bye.
- I never intended to cage her.
- Your Majesty?
- Sairon?
- What are you doing
out here, Your Majesty?
- I was just talking with
Suai's younger brother.
- You mean the young
man from the Rahn Clan
whose been visiting
the palace recently?
- The same.
Apparently, he'll be staying
at Suai's house, tonight.
- I heard he's very
unusual kind of person.
- But he and Suai seem
to get along well.
Sairon, I have a
request to make of you.
Could you also go home
with Suai tonight?
- If you're worried I can
certainly send some guards over.
I'd like to stay
here and investigate
something a little further.
- If you're talking
about that, I asked Suai
to look into it as well.
Don't do anything reckless.
- Right.
- [Merchant] Here you go.
- Didn't you say we were
having Chicken Hot Pot?
- Yes, I did.
- Since when do you need soy
beans for Chicken Hot Pot?
- This tiny round thing,
for some reason I was
suddenly drawn to it
- You broke them.
- [Merchant] This
is a problem, sir.
- I apologize. Please
take these in payment
for the broken eggs.
- What's this?
This much?
Wait a minute, sir, at
least take these in return!
- Well, it's a little closer
to chicken, I suppose,
but still...
- Please.
I see.
- Excuse me, what's the matter?
- Nothing.
I just wanted to buy some eggs
for my sick husband to eat,
but I don't have enough money.
- In that case, I'll
exchange these eggs
for those green
onions you got there.
- Would you really?
Thank you very much!
- I guess this means we're
getting a little closer
to Hot Pot, but--
we're getting further
away from chicken.
Hey, Riu-Rin, why
don't you and I--
- If it's okay with you, I'd
like to make an exchange.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Just what kind of theory
are you basing these
trades on, anyway?
- There is no theory to it.
- And the Chicken
Eat Chicken Hot Pot?
- No more than an illusion.
- I don't think I can
stand much more of this.
He's driving me totally nuts!
(child crying)
- Don't cry, what's wrong?
- The wind blew away the
straw that I was getting used
to make a raincoat.
What am I gonna do?
(gasping in relief)
Thank you!
(Suai laughing)
- Tonight, we can pick
vegetables from our garden
and make Veggie-Veggie
Hot Pot, instead.
- You're not angry with me?
- It reminds me of
an old folk tale.
A man began with a piece
of straw and traded up
until he was rich,
but you ended up doing
the complete opposite, Riu-Rin.
You know, all the same,
I still had a lot of fun!
- Suai, do you know if those
guards outside our front gates
were sent here on
the king's orders?
- I think so.
It's probably because
I'm staying here tonight.
- Riu-Rin, another helping?
- Please relax.
Make yourself at home.
- There was a piece of
vegetable on your face.
- Well, Riu-Rin, that's a first.
- What is it?
- That must be the first
time I've seen you smile.
- No need to make a fuss,
it's nothing to be
surprised about.
- I guess not.
- Why don't we have some more
before the food get cold?
Let's eat!
Riu-Rin, you're spilling it.
- Well, take care
of yourself, okay?
- Right.
- [Suai] General Rahn?
- The thought that
my younger brother
may have caused you
trouble was worrying me.
- No, not at all.
He wasn't the least
bit of trouble.
- Thank you, General, but there
was no need to be concerned.
- Excuse me, Suai, but
I should get going.
- Good luck and stay safe, okay?
- Yeah, but one more
reminder before I go.
I hope you remember that
you're my kindred sp irit.
(Suai gasps)
- You are my kindred spirit,
and that'll be for life.
- Thank you, Riu-Rin.
- Now I'll take my leave.
(startling flute music)
- Next time we meet
will probably be at
the National Exams.
- The Exams?
- That's right.
- He'll be taking the National
Civil Service Examination.
He had to make a promise
to the Rahn Family
that he will place in
the top three rankings.
- [Suai] Why is that?
- That's the condition
under which he's allowed
to wander around like this.
- I see.
The National Exams.
- Suai?
I really must thank you.
You are the first
person I've ever met
who didn't turn and run away
from my younger brother.
- That can't be true.
- He has always been very
eccentric and that a fact,
has isolated him from others.
- That's because he's a genius.
I'm sure he sees things
in a very different way
than the rest of us do,
but if you think about it,
that can also mean that
he's unable to see the world
in the same way as other people.
It must be terribly
lonely, enduring that kind
of mental isolation.
- But for the first time he
has a real friend to turn to.
- A kindred spirit.
For life.
(regal flute music)
- Liaukee?
- What is it?
- I've never been able to
do anything, unless I put
a lot of effort into it.
Like this Erhu.
I had to practice constantly,
before I was able to play it.
It's hard to have to put in
so much effort all the time,
but it must be hard
to be a genius, too.
- Yes. I'm going to
make an effort, too.
- Tada! Please accept these,
these all my gifts to you.
I'm making an effort and trying
my best to earn your love.
How am I doing, Suai?
It's hard work, but
I'm happy to do it.
For you, I would do
whatever it takes.
Suai? Suai--
- There is nothing I hate more
than someone who wastes money!
(Liaukee screaming)
(intimate music in
foreign language)
foreign language fades)
- [Suai] Liaukee has
turned into a true king.
It won't be long now
before my work here
finally comes to an end (yawns).
This feeling of relief
is making me sleepy.
What?
Where am I?
Could I have been kid-knapped?