(bright music)
(light Japanese into music)
- [Narrator] Several
days have passed since
the liberation of the
mayor of Kinka, Shin Sai,
from his confinement.
And the banishment of
the murderous Blades
from the city.
A government official said
to have arrived from Koren
has appeared before Shuurei,
Eigetsu, and the others
as they were busy
processing matters
relating to the incident.
- So you're Mr. Jun
Yu from Koren City?
- [Jun Yu] Yes.
(laughs)
- Then you've decided
to come after all.
Is everything all
right over there now?
- I think for the time being.
What's important is
that we work together
to immediately bring
the situation back
to normal in Kinka.
- Uh, right, yeah, of course.
You're absolutely right.
- Hey, maybe you should
properly introduce him to us
rather than just
telling us his name.
- Don't worry, we can
save that stuff for later.
We've got a mountain
load of work to do.
- Save that stuff for later?
(soft music)
(sighs)
- Excuse me, Official Yu?
About this document.
- Hm.
Ah yes, of course.
Since it's necessary
that this be checked
and verified against
the taxation records
from last year, I will
take care of this for you.
More importantly, I'd
like to have your approval
on this document.
- [Eigetsu] Hm?
Uh, right.
- Could you stamp this
document with your seal
as well, please?
- Sure.
- [Ensei] After that,
there's this, and this.
Oh and these, too.
- Oh dear, you've gotten
quite a lot of work again.
- Yeah.
But you know, if we can
bring happiness and peace
to the people of Kinka by
doing our job like this,
I don't really mind.
- Right.
But just imagine what
things could've been like
if we didn't have
those two here to help
us out with all of this.
- Even though we were
appointed as co-governors
we still are total
novices to government.
The fact is, as we are now,
we don't know left
from right, do we?
- Right now, our
entire job description
is just putting our
signatures and seal
on the documents
that they verified.
Official Yu's assistance
has been really helpful.
He's very precise and quick
when it comes to
this sort of thing.
Oh?
- Come on, don't just
sit around talking.
I need a stamp on
this too, please.
(sighs)
- For crying out loud!
Why is there so
much work to do?!
(splatters)
Ah!
Official Yu, I am so, so sorry!
(laughs)
- No, it's perfectly all right.
None of it got on the
documents, so it's fine.
- This is so embarrassing,
I'm utterly ashamed of myself.
- Yeah, me too.
- Oh, it's to be
expected at this stage.
- Oh yeah, that's right.
Actually, you two are
doing a whole lot better
than I did during my time.
- If you don't mind me saying,
that's not something
to brag about.
Or are you trying to
make excuses for the way
you irresponsibly put
your seal on documents
when you hadn't even
read through them?
Or how you used to act
recklessly whenever you had
a spare moment or two.
- Agh!
That couldn't be helped.
Back then, the assassins from
the Sa Clan were persistent.
And besides, that
was 10 years ago.
You certainly have
a good memory.
- [Jun Yu] Yes, I
remember it very well.
Even in 100 years, I could
never forget your kind act
of pushing me into a
manure pool with a warning.
- [Ensei] But that was to save
you from a poisonous arrow!
And besides, thanks
to that incident,
all those people who used
to think you were too cool
and calm to approach,
they warmed up to you
and started coming
to you more often.
- Look, please
refrain from making
pointless excuses for yourself.
We have more important
things to do.
The taxation information
for last year
is on the bookshelf
on the north side.
Second from the right,
fifth shelf from the top.
- Yes, sir.
Wow, Official, you and Mr.
Ensei really get along well.
- Yes, they do, but
have you noticed
that Ensei is the
one running around?
I don't think I've
seen Official Yu
get up from his
seat a single time.
- [Ensei] Is that so?
- It makes perfect sense.
Ensei's the type
of man you'd assume
has muscles in his
head instead of brains.
He's got to be moving
continually, or
he gets restless.
- Yeah, exactly.
That's right.
Hey!
Wait just a minute, why would
you go say a thing like that?
(laughs)
(soft music)
- Huh?
- [Seiran] I understand
you buried Soujun's son
in that courtyard
all by yourself.
- Yes, as a member
of the Sa Clan,
it was the very least
I could do for him.
- That's very impressive of you.
- No, you're wrong!
You guys are the ones
who are impressive!
You were able to chase
the murderous Blades
out of Kinka, and
liberate it from the hands
of the Sa Clan.
- [Seiran] Maybe, but
we weren't able to do
any of that by ourselves.
- Even so, you're
all incredible.
Especially Miss
Shuurei, I think.
(soft music)
- [Seiran] I should be
getting back to work soon.
(light music)
- In comparison,
all I can do, huh?
(light music)
- [Eiki] Listen to
me well, Shunki.
Read the stars, and
gage the right moment.
And when that moment comes--
- Oh, Miss Shunki!
Wow, so you've come all the
way down here, have you?
I guess your legs have
become a lot stronger
since you arrived, Miss Shunki.
Ah?
You've cut your hand on
a thorn or something.
I'll mix up some medicine
for it when we get home.
I feel kinda bad, your
hands were like a princess'
when you first came
to stay with us.
Huh?
I only wish I had some
kind of medicinal herbs
that could bring your voice
back to you, Miss Shunki.
(light music)
- Huh?
Boss, Miss Shunki,
you're right on time.
I just finished preparing lunch.
- You were able to
pick quite a lot!
Huh?
Those mushrooms are poisonous.
- [Shorin] Yoshun, you idiot!
What are you trying to do?
Embarrass the poor girl?
If something like that happens,
you tell her later in secret.
- Ah, you're right!
I'm stupid, I wasn't thinking.
I'm sorry, Miss Shunki,
please forgive me.
- Listen Yoshun, Miss
Shunki was entrusted to us
by Ensei Ro, and we have
to do everything we can
to protect her, right?
But there's no way we'll
accomplish this important task
with half-hearted devotion!
- Got it!
- If we can fulfill
this mission,
we'll mature into a
second generation of
chivalrous thieves!
The Bald Eagles of Sa
Province will fly again!
- You said it, boss man.
(wind blows)
- [Eiki] And when
that moment comes,
you shall do what you
need to do, Shunki.
- This is delicious.
Kourin, your skills improved.
- Nonsense.
I still hardly compare
to you, Lady Shuurei.
- [Ensei] Hey!
Could I have two sweet bean
paste ones as well, please?
Why should only Princess
get more than one?
- It's a difference
of affection.
- Never in my life have
I been shown so clearly
the difference in the
amount of affection
someone has for me.
- Don't sulk, Ensei.
It's not just you.
Official Yu and Eigetsu
only got one each as well.
- Yes, but look at mine.
Mine's the smallest!
- Nice try, but they're
all the same size.
Fine then, I'll give
you half of one of mine.
- All right!
(sighs)
- Huh?
A chestnut?
(light music)
I see.
A difference in
affection, indeed.
- I'll go make some more tea.
- By the way, I
meant to ask, Ensei,
would you mind filling us in
on exactly what's going
on in Koren right now?
- Such as?
- [Shuurei] I, mean you made
such an effort to get us into
Sa Province quickly, but
you haven't said a word
about moving on since
we arrived here.
- [Eigetsu] It's true
that we can reach Korin
in five days travel,
even at a relaxed pace.
But we only have 20
days before our deadline
to arrive and take our post.
- If we miss that date,
then our post as
co-governors will be stripped
from us regardless
of the circumstances.
- Yes, I realize that, but
bear with me a little longer.
I would prefer to wait
until we get the latest news
on Korin by way of Sho Sai
and that sister of his.
- I see.
But Ensei, will Lieutenant
Governor Tei be all right?
(chews)
- Yuushun, huh?
Yeah, I think
he'll be just fine.
- That's your answer?
Aren't you worried about him?
- Yes, that's right.
Until now, as acting governor,
he held the highest
decision-making authority
in the Province, so
he was still safe.
But the moment we take
our posts and he transfers
his authority over to us,
his life could be in danger
from the Sa Clan!
(laughs)
- I think if Yuushun
heard you say that,
he'd be so happy,
he'd burst into tears.
- Yes, he sure would.
- In his case, there's
no need to worry.
- Are you absolutely sure?
- I'm positive.
Not even Sakujun Sa
himself would be able
to do anything about
Yuushun at the moment.
(dramatic music)
The two of us already decided
together that we would
transfer all authority
as governors to you
in the best possible state.
So I ask you to put
your trust in Yuushun.
- You know, it looks
like the two of us
are truly blessed,
aren't we, Shuurei?
- It's true.
Sending you to Sa Province
was a wise decision
by His Majesty.
This will be an ideal
first assignment for you.
- [Both] Huh?
- Given that your predecessor
is the unusual Ensei Ro,
the unique circumstances
regarding your age and gender
will not even be an issue to
the people of this Province.
- You've got some
nerve to say that
while I'm sitting right here.
Of course, you are quite right.
This place has always been
a Province mostly abandoned
by the central government.
- Deep down, everyone was
anxious and ill at ease.
But then, people
received the good news
that truly legitimate
governors would be arriving;
governors to whom His
Majesty had bestowed flowers.
The citizens of Sa
Province were overjoyed
upon hearing that.
- Why were the people so happy
about us receiving a flower?
- [Jun Yu] The flower is proof
of His Majesty's absolute trust.
Those with flowers
bestowed upon them
are rarely assigned to
work in other districts.
By dispatching such governors,
His Majesty is
telling the people
that he is clearly committed
to paying close attention
to this Province.
Not only does bestowing
the flower upon you
protect you personally,
it also spares Sa Province
from much of its
laments and fears.
It's a brilliant move.
- [Ensei] There's one more
reason why it was good for you
to come to Sa
Province, Princess.
- What's that?
- Well, the headquarters
of the Merchant's Guild
in Sa Province is run by
Sho Sai's older sister.
Her ability to run
things puts men to shame;
multiple times, as
a matter of fact.
- For that reason, there
will likely be less prejudice
towards a female governor here
than in the other Provinces.
I believe this would be
the most appropriate place
for the first female
government official.
- [Shuurei Voiceover]
I can't believe
how much Ryuuki thought
this assignment through.
(knocks)
- [Messenger] Excuse me.
- [Shuurai] Huh?
- Lord Sho Sai has
asked to speak with you.
- Oh, so he's arrived already?
Please, show him in.
Well, how was everything?
- As of four days
ago, by the order
of Lieutenant Governor Tai,
an official announcement
has been issued ordering
the complete blockade
of all Korin traffic.
- What?!
A complete blockade?!
- [Ensei] Well that's
certainly a pretty in-your-face
move from the Sa Clan.
- The official story is
that the two new governors
are already in the city.
They say the blockade
is for safety.
It's supposed to
protect them from any
possible danger until
the assignment ceremony.
- [Shuurei] Ugh,
that's ridiculous!
- [Sho Sai] As well,
rumors are spreading
throughout the city alleging
that the new governors
are under the protection
of the Sa Clan.
People have interpreted
this as a sign
you are under Sa Clan control,
and your popularity
is declining.
- Great, as if things
weren't already hard enough,
we have the Sa Clan spreading
preposterous rumors.
- What should we do now?
(laughs)
- Okay then, why don't we
leave tomorrow morning?
- Huh?
- We'll start out first thing,
so get to bed early
tonight, got it?
(laughs)
(light music)
(knocks)
- Yes?
What is it, Ensei?
I'm busy packing right now,
so I don't have very
much time to be chatting.
You did want to leave
really early, right?
- Hm.
Say, Princess, I was wondering,
have you talked
with Seiran lately?
- [Shuurei] Uh no, we've both
been busy with work, I guess.
- Sorry to butt in,
but would you mind
having a heart to heart
talk with him soon?
- Huh?
(dramatic music)
- Ensei certainly doesn't
seem like the sort of guy
who notices details, but
he's really perceptive
where it counts.
- [Seiran] My lady.
So this is where you are.
- Oh, yeah.
(soft music)
Seiran, let's have
some tea together.
(soft music)
- You sure about this?
There's not much
time left for sleep.
- [Shuurei] If I
went to bed now,
I don't think I'd be
able to wake up in time.
(sips)
- [Seiran] May I ask, why are
you making bean paste buns
at this time of night?
- Well, I suppose I--
- Is there something
bothering you?
(sighs happily)
Well, it's just that you're
my second favorite person
in the world, Seiran.
(spits out tea)
Are you all right?
- What's gotten into
you all of a sudden?
- I'm just as surprised
at myself for saying that.
It's not really like me to
say things unintentionally.
But you know, it kinda came
out naturally, didn't it?
Like saying peach buns are my
second favorite in the world.
(laughs nervously)
- [Seiran Voiceover] Her
second most favorite person
in the world?
Am I supposed to be happy
about that or miserable?
My lady, please stop giggling,
and give me an explanation.
(sighs)
- [Sa Kokujun] I don't
know what I should do.
- [Ensei] About what?
- Ever since I was a child,
I've always been watching
and seeing what crimes
my Clan commits.
I saw how much
they did to torment
the poor citizens
of Sa Province.
And now, even my older
brother Sakujun is doing it.
- So?
(sighs)
I'm sure that deep
down in your heart,
you already know what to do
without having to ask me.
Believe in yourself.
Do what you feel you have to
do, and nevermind the rest.
- [Kokujun] Mr. Ensei.
Thank you very much.
(crickets chirp)
- Now, I gotta wonder
what's happening over there.
(light music)
- [Shuurei] It's been a
while since we've sat down
and talked like this, hasn't it?
- Well, yes, I suppose so.
- [Shuurei] Seiran, is there
something you'd like to ask me?
- Uh, like what, my lady?
- I seem to have caused you
a lot of worry and upset
because of that incident with
that stupid young master.
Ask me whatever you want
so we can clear the air
before we leave.
- [Seiran Voiceover] It's
supposed to be my job
to support you.
I'm pathetic.
(light music)
My lady.
- There's the old Seiran.
Yes?
- Is it all right if I ask
you who your number one
favorite person is?
- It's father, of course!
Even though he's
a hopeless father,
he's always been my number one.
Mother's in a different
category altogether.
- So, my lady, do you
like Sakujun Sa at all?
(spits tea)
- [Shuurei] Whoa, as far
as Seiran's concerned,
that's pretty straightforward.
- I don't really have any
choice but to answer that
I don't really know.
- You don't?
- [Shuurei] Seiran, I'm
sure you understand.
When it comes to
this kind of thing,
I'm totally unfamiliar with it.
But I remember the way that
Mother got along really
well with Father.
You remember, right?
- [Seiran] Yes.
- As a child, there was always
something to laugh about.
I remember just how lively
and fun it always was
in our house.
- That's true, but only
because Madame would insist
on making medicinal soup
and cause an explosion.
(coughs)
- [Hyou Shoukun]
Wait just one moment.
Your medicine will
be ready very soon.
(explodes)
(screams)
Oh dear, I'm sorry
that I scared you.
Shh, shh, it's all right.
- What on earth are you doing?
What if she had been hurt?
What would you do then?
- My goodness, you can talk.
- If I remember correctly,
those were the very
first words you ever said
after you came to live with us.
- That's because
there was a real risk
of you burning yourself.
- Yes, but after I would drink
Mother's special medicinal soup,
I'd become as healthy as
any other child for a while.
Then she'd teach me
how to play the erhu.
We went persimmon picking, she'd
teach me all about manners,
we even made bean
paste buns together.
I think we did as much as
we could in a short period
so that we wouldn't
run out of time
before I came down with a
fever again, or even worse.
But in the end, it wasn't
me that time ran out on.
It was Mother.
(dramatic music)
The reason I hadn't pursued
things like love or romance
might be because of Mother.
Her death made me really scared.
I guess it may have made me
afraid to let my guard down
and fall in love with someone.
I have no confidence in myself.
Maybe that's why I haven't
been making any effort
to find a person who's
especially important to me.
And although I
always looked away,
that man was
extremely aggressive.
He was very strange, but he
had such a beautiful face.
My heart would sometimes
start pounding despite itself.
(laughs)
- That's certainly a very
objective analysis of yourself.
- Hey!
Why are you laughing?
You probably don't understand
because you're a very
handsome man, too.
But it can be quite
important to a normal person
whether your looks
are good or bad.
- That's a very nice
thing for you to say.
I'm flattered.
- For all the trouble
that young master was,
he was good at exposing
that weak point of mine.
Or maybe I'm just
generally weak.
Weak against that special
kind of pressure, anyway.
Sorry, I guess my answer's not
making a lot of sense, is it?
- No, it's all right.
If anything, I should
be thanking you
for thinking so much
about my feelings.
- Do you really mean that?
(yawns)
That's not good.
Now I feel like I'm about
to fall fast asleep.
(light music)
- I'll be sure to wake
you up in the morning.
Please, get as much
sleep as you can.
- But what about you, Seiran?
- I have more stamina,
so don't worry about me.
- In that case, I
think I might go to bed
for a little while.
- Okay.
- [Shuurei] I still have to
take that flower bud back, but,
(yawns)
that flower belongs to me,
so I'll do everything
I can on my own.
You really shouldn't
spoil me so much, Seiran.
(sighs)
- [Seiran] Hey.
- Oh, so you noticed
I was here, huh?
I was just curious as
to what was going on
since it looked like
you were going to worry
yourself to death.
As I thought, all you had
to do was talk with her,
and your problems were solved.
I knew things would get better.
It's always darkest
before the dawn.
(chews)
It's been a while since I've had
any of Princess' steamed buns.
You know, I don't think
Princess has any idea
just how much you
really depend on her.
You're the type of guy who
needs at least three adults
on hand to make certain you
don't forget how to breathe.
Without three babysitters,
you're completely lost.
But Princess, Mr. Shouka, and
myself make up those three.
- Well, I'd happily trade
that last one in
for a grasshopper.
It's not like I've
got any use for you.
- A grasshopper, huh?
Well at least I work all
year round, unlike them,
I'll have you know.
The problem with being
your friend though,
is figuring out
how to spoil you.
Oh, by the way, looks
like the Senior Secretary
of the Department
of Civil Affairs
won't be taking action.
He must truly cherish Princess.
- In which case,
that means Sakujun--
- If he sees the
head of the Han Clan
isn't acting, he
won't see a point
in pursuing the position of
head of the Sa Clan anymore.
So I guess in the
end, Soujun was killed
for no good reason.
- At least he was
properly buried
by his younger
brother's own two hands.
- [Ensei] Koku says he's
gonna make his move today.
But his opponents are
Chuushou and Saku.
- He's well-aware of that,
yet he's still
acting on his own.
I see surprising potential
in that young man.
- Yes, well, hopefully
that will be true.
- I'm taking a nap, so wake
me up when it's time to go.
- Hey, what about me?!
- Let's see, you have
more than enough stamina,
and you've done
nothing but desk work.
You can stay awake.
- But that's not my fault!
Somehow I don't think
you're being fair at all.
(birds chirp)
- Goodbye, Elder Brother.
I'm off now.
- [Eigetsu] You're
going aren't you?
- Hm?
- So you really have
made a decision?
- Yes, I have.
Do you mind if I ask a favor?
- [Eigetsu] What is it?
- Please take care of Shunki.
I know I could just
go ask Mr. Ensei
and have nothing to worry
about on that end, but...
- I understand, and
yes, I promise you.
- And just in case
I should die--
- [Eigetsu] I won't listen
to the rest of that!
I'm also not going to accept
any messages for Miss Shunki.
You should not be speaking
of death and dying so easily.
- You've always given me nothing
but strong encouragement.
I'll do my best, and I
won't die that easily.
I will go and stop Grandfather
and my big brother Sakujun.
I swear it.
(dramatic music)
(soft Japanese outro music)
- [Shuurei] We're finally
going to depart for Koren
in order to arrive in
time for our assignment
as governors of Sa Province,
and to settle all the
problems facing us.
Now, is everybody ready?
Then let's get going!