(electronic whirring)
(singing in foreign language)
(tense music)
- [Narrator] Sa Province is
one of the eight provinces
that make up Saiunkoku.
In its capital city of Korin,
in the chambers of a
particular residence
an old man is
gloating to himself.
The man is no other
than Chuushou Sa
the younger brother of
the late advisor Enjun Sa.
- At last the time has come.
It's been one year since you
died, my dear elder brother.
You can't imagine how
much fighting there's been
in the struggle for
the clan leadership.
However, that will
all be at an end soon.
As long as the new
governors are held in check,
the one who controls
their seal and charm
will be the one to become
the new clan leader.
(evil laugh)
First will be the
elimination of Ensei Ro.
- We're from the border
office of Sireen, do not move.
(growls)
(whimpering)
- You're charged with running
through the border
station twice.
Both last summer
and this spring.
You can't talk
your way out of it.
(nervous grimace)
- And there are further charges.
This past month
you've been assaulting
neighboring cities and
towns, committing robbery
of money and
valuables, even murder!
You shall confess to
everything you've done
little rascal king of
the murderous blades.
- Look I have no knowledge
of anything other
than running through
the border station.
I guess there's no way out
of this, I'll go with them.
- I'm afraid you're
not the only one
who will be coming with us.
Aren't you the little whirlwind
of the murderous blades?
- Don't, don't resist
Seiran, just let it go.
- Next we get the
two new co-governors.
I don't care if the
boy gets killed.
The main problem will
be the other one.
The Hong clan wouldn't
take her death lightly.
So we'll have to lure
her into our arms.
Sakujun should be most
suitable for that.
The time has come.
As soon as we get rid
of elder brother's his bloodline
will come to a fitting end.
Even if I die, my bloodline
will still continue.
You died first,
and you have lost.
I promise that I will surpass
you Enjun Sa. (laughs)
(dramatic music)
(gasps)
- [Seiran] You hit a government
official and used his seal
while he was down?
- Hey, I told him I
was in a hurry to go
and make a direct
appeal to the king.
But he kept searching
for faults in me
and refused to let me through.
- Ensei, you stupid idiot.
If anything bad happens to
her ladyship I'll kill you.
- Geez will you have
a little faith in her.
In case you'd forgotten,
princess remained hidden
and didn't come out.
If she had come out
or remained with us,
both governors would have
easily fallen into the clutches
of the Sa clan.
She saw what was going
on and understood
what the best course
of action was.
These are the good results
of princess's appraisal
of the situation as governor.
No matter how you look
at it, it's her job
to make the decisions.
- I'm not in the
same position as you.
My job is to protect
the governors.
Why did you drag
me along here too?
- If you were your usual self
it wouldn't be a problem, but--
- [Seiran] What?
- [Ensei] The murderous
blades are involved.
(gasps)
- After all this time,
who'd ever thought we'd hear
that name again here and now.
I'm about the only
one who can stop you
if you lose control
and go on a rampage
because of those idiots.
Letting you escape with princess
while you're in that state
would only make me worry.
- You're being annoying
as always Ensei.
- Don't worry, knowing
princess we'll be able
to meet up with her
and Kinka in no time.
(scoffs)
(happy village chatter)
- Hey princess, there are so
many delicious things here.
Can I go buy some?
(gentle music)
- It's a very lively
town isn't it?
Wow there's a used
book store over there.
- My lady, are you
sure you're not tired?
Shall I buy you some
ice or something?
- Lady Shuurei, when
I'm feeling better
I'll see to your needs
again, I promise.
(hinges squeaking)
- Ah they've come, that was a
lot quicker than I expected.
- Hmm?
(flame crackling)
- [Soujun] I didn't
believe it at first,
but it is the real you Ensei Ro.
- Hey, long time no see Souji.
- Address me as lord Soujun.
Since they were with
you I must assume
that the kid and the young
girl are the new governors
of Sa Province.
- Why don't you ask
them instead of me?
- Not that it matters whether
they're imposters or not.
The charm and seal
are what's important.
As long as I have
those, I have the power
to name anybody I
wish as governor.
But wouldn't you know,
those very things
are nowhere to be found.
Tell me, where did you
hide the charm and seal?
- Who knows?
- (grunts) Well,
threatening you won't work.
- Whoa, what happened?
In the short time
since I last saw you,
you've actually become
pretty reasonable.
(metal clanking)
- Shut up, as long as
I have you in custody
it doesn't matter what sort
of new governors come in.
And I don't care if
you don't tell me
where the charm and
seal are hidden.
You can try shipping
them in, or whatever.
But ultimately they'll
come to Korin city,
and that's our territory.
As long as we get rid
of you and Yuushun Tei
we can take all the time
we need to look for them.
- You really have gained
a lot of wisdom Souji.
So who's the poor guy
who had to teach you?
(sword clanking)
- Ya, damn you, if I
ever get the opportunity
I want to kill you
with my own two hands.
- That's impossible, at
least not with your skills.
(scoff) Well then I'll
just starve you to death.
- What, but that's
the worst way to die!
- While I'm at it here's
a little something
you might want to know.
Kinka is already under control.
The control of the
murderous blades.
(gasps)
- You heard me, the
murderous blades.
That legendary band of
vicious thieves is working
for our family now.
- I thought that group was
wiped out a long time ago.
- It turns out there
was a survivor.
The second in command at that.
His name is Meishou.
(growls)
- Well if you think you can
escape go ahead and try.
(door slams)
- So that's Soujun Sa?
- Yeah, and it looks
like someone formidable
has been giving him some ideas.
- It certainly looks that way.
- Souji learned and
used the word starve
for the first time after all.
Meishou he says, that's
obviously how they all knew
my old nickname of the
Little Rascal King.
Seiran.
- [Seiran] What?
- You're going to
hunt down the ghosts
of the past, aren't you?
- Yes, if there's anyone
who might threaten to reveal
the past to her ladyship,
then I'll send them
to the very depths of hell.
- First things first,
we'll meet up with princess
in the town of Kinka
as originally planned.
If the murderous blades really
have taken control there
I need to weed them out
quickly as an assistant
to the governors.
- What about Eigetsu and Kourin?
- Do you mind if we stay
here a little longer
to make a decision about that?
- Huh?
- When everything is
over let's all drink
ganlu tea together.
Delicious tea that
princess has made herself.
(moans)
- Are you feeling all right?
- Where's Lady Shuurei?
- She got away, but Mr.
Seiran and Mr. Ensei are here
in the dungeon.
- This is my fault, you
should have left me behind
and made your escape.
- Miss Kourin,
it's not like that.
Why do you think Mr. Ensei only
hid Shuurei and no one else?
- I don't know.
- If we are going to be
caught, then we'd be better
off being caught as a foursome.
By now everybody knows
that the new governors
are a 13 year old boy
and a 17 year old girl.
And their assistants are the
previous governor Mr. Ensei
and his special
officer Mr. Seiran.
The Sa clan was looking
for this foursome.
- So I'm supposed to be a
stand-in for Lady Shuurei?
- Mhm, Shuurei is a
lady of the direct line
of the Hong clan.
Normally you'd think of a lady
who's well bred and sheltered.
I know that Shuurei would
probably be mad at me
if she heard me say this,
but you fit that sort
of image much better
than she does.
- Huh?
- Thanks to that
mistaken identity
they're taking good care of you.
We even save on accommodations.
We also prevent anyone
from pursuing Shuurei,
so all kinds of good things
have come out of this.
- You know, when
you put it that way
I'm beginning to feel
the same way too.
- So let's do our best to
keep fooling them, okay?
- You're right, no
matter what happens
from here on in, I'll do my
best for Lady Shuurei's sake.
- Hmm.
- (gasps) Why are you smiling?
- Oh, I was just thinking
that you're much prettier
with that sort of determined
expression on your face.
- How rude you are!
(laughs nervously)
(soft music)
(windchimes chiming)
(birds chirping)
- Your majesty, I have
a small favor to ask.
- Denied.
- I don't particularly
need you to hear me out.
I'll just go anyway.
- What's that,
where are you going?
- To Sa Province, I was
planning to deliver this.
- The Sa clan leader's ring?
So you're the one who had it!
You really are a
scheming, evil old man.
- Well I suppose
I'll be off then.
- Just who do you intend
to hand that ring to?
- There's no need to
worry, Your Majesty.
I don't intend to do anything
like blame you officials
with bright futures
ahead of them.
Besides, I'm not the one
who will choose, this will.
I can at least assure
you of that much.
- Huh?
- My but I'm looking
forward to it.
I haven't seen Shuurei
in such a long time.
Perhaps while I'm there
I'll see if I can have
some of her homemade
sweet buns again. (laughs)
(growls)
(village chatter)
- This is all the money I have.
I'll have to watch my spending.
- You are to make your
way to Kinka, got that?
- That's right, I
have to make my way
to Kinka no matter what.
(dull thudding)
(pottery shattering)
- Hey!
- I'm sorry!
- You little idiot,
look what you've done!
That wine cost me
20 silver coins.
- 20 silver coins, it
can't have cost that much.
- You heard me girl,
that's what it cost.
Damn, this is all you've got?
- Give that back!
I'll cover the expense, but
there's no way you can convince
me the wine was that expensive.
- What did you say?
- [Merchant] I agree with
her, I also don't believe it
to be that valuable.
- Oh yeah, what's it to
you, and just who are you?
- Who am I, well as you can
see I'm a merchant dear sir.
And a member of the
merchant's guild.
- The merchant's guild?
- That's right, the
merchant's guild can help me.
- Huh?
- So you two are
the new governors?
But you're just
a couple of kids.
- True, for starters
we'll test them
and make sure they're
the real thing.
In the seven scriptures, what
were the nine fundamentals
for ruling a country as
told to King Yuu by Keishi?
- The elements, businesses,
objects, arrangements,
royal perfection, virtues,
examination of doubts,
verifications, and happiness.
- Name the book,
section, and page number
in the seven scriptures
where I'd find that.
- It's in the book of History,
the section on the great plan
from the third line on
page 42, to the 12th line
on page 43.
- I see, very good,
now for you girl.
I want you to write down the
work that marked the beginning
of the brilliant career
of poet Mei Senshei.
- You can't be serious,
you want her to write all
of that long piece?
- Is there a problem with that?
- Well no, it's just she's not
feeling very well right now.
- Please give that to me.
(harp music)
(gasps)
- That will be enough, I
think it's safe to consider
them both the genuine article,
don't you lord Soujun?
- Oh, yes.
- The charm and the governor's
seal are all that remain now.
- Why not force these two
to give us the location?
- No, that's pointless,
they probably don't know.
It's likely that
they've been given
as little information
as possible.
Like, go to Kinka, or
something like that.
(gasps)
- As I thought, I never
expected the two of you
to be carrying such a
treasure in the first place.
That's why we've
taken the initiative
and already gained
control of Kinka.
As you know Kinka is the
merchant capital of Sa Province.
All material goods
entering Korin,
no matter how small,
go through there.
No doubt your plan
was to hide them in
with some other goods and
slip them in that way.
- That's Meisha for you,
that's why he's the new leader
of the murderous blades.
- Don't look so concerned,
even without the charm and seal
the two of you can still
be of great use to us.
Especially the girl.
(nervous gasping)
Lord Soujun, where is
your younger brother?
- You mean Sakujun,
he's still in Kinka.
He says he's scared
because the bandits
have apparently been
attacking the highway.
- In that case it would
probably be faster
to take these two
to him directly.
Young lady, please don't worry,
your future elder brother
will see to it that
you reach Kinka safely.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Only the happiest of meanings,
my lady, the Sa main house
wishes for you to
become Sakujun's wife.
(shocked gasps)
- I will go on ahead
and return to Kinka
to get everything prepared.
As for you, lord Sojun,
you are to stay here
for the time being
until Ensei Ro escapes.
- Escapes?
- Oh he will, don't
you ever doubt that.
- What, you're going to
Kinka on your own, but--
- Yes, I know it's
probably very dangerous.
But that's why I was
thinking of going
through the merchant's guild
and having you introduce me
to a caravan for Kinka.
- Ah, I see.
- After all, the merchant's
guild can always be trusted.
- Not to mention,
there's little fear
of being attacked by bandits.
- Of course, because
then the guild
would be sure to retaliate.
- Exactly, it is only
natural to try and destroy
bands of thieves, and
we would also lay claim
to any valuables they
have hidden away.
- So unless they're an
exceptionally foolish
band of thieves, there's
no way they'd dare
attack a caravan belonging
to the merchant's guild.
- That's exactly right.
(indistinct chattering)
- [Trader] Young lady, you
have very discerning taste.
- Huh?
- That erhu is a
truly exceptional item
from Koku Province.
- Would you mind if I
tried it out for a bit?
- Of course, please do.
(gentle music)
(crowd applauding)
- That was amazing!
You're truly an accomplished
player young lady.
Out of respect for
your skill I have
to give you a special
discount, five silver pieces.
How about it?
- Sorry, I'm afraid I don't
have that much money on me.
However.
- However?
- I'll buy it for
one silver coin.
- Young lady, that's
way too cruel.
(chuckles)
- Huh?
(laughing)
(sweet music)
I beg your pardon
for interrupting.
You would like to have
that erhu, wouldn't you?
I'll make you an offer.
If you plan five tunes
that I request I'll pay
the five silver for you.
- And the titles of those tunes?
- They're Toshoki,
Ooten, Saiogu-shu,
Bewakei, and Soyokei.
- Those are all
difficult pieces to play.
- You can't play them?
- Nice try, I'll
accept your challenge.
(sweet music)
- That was truly wonderful.
- Why thank you.
- And I'm not only talking
about your performance.
You bargained the merchant down,
bought the erhu for
two silver coins,
and pocketed the
remaining three.
- You promised me
five silver pieces,
so I'm not giving
any back Mr. um?
- My name is Senya Rin, but
please, you can call me Senya.
- This is the Sakyo branch
of the merchant's guild.
- Now then, shall we go inside?
- Huh, you have
business here as well?
- I do, I finished
my work here in Sakyo
and I'm about to
return to Sa Province.
I thought I would have
the guild take care
of the preparations for that.
- So that means this
person is also a merchant,
and a member of the guild.
- Aren't you coming in?
- Oh, sorry, just a moment.
(indistinct chattering)
- Ah, Mr. Rin, you're most
welcome to our humble office.
Someone will show you the
way shortly. (hands clapping)
- If we do not meet
again, then do me a favor
and think of that erhu as
me, take good care of it.
- Uh, sure.
- Now then young lady,
what is your business here?
If you don't mind me asking.
- Right, I was hoping
I could join a caravan
on its way to Kinka.
- Hmm I beg your pardon,
but do you have a pass
you could show me?
- Oh yes, here it is.
- What, but this is,
my sincerest apologies.
I'll show you the
way immediately.
- Uh.
(gentle music)
- You'll be seeing the
Sakyo regional director
of the Shi provincial branch
of the merchant's guild.
- Huh, why such an
important person?
I received this pass from senior
secretary Ko before I left.
It has the Ko family emblem
of Mandarin ducks and flowers.
I was told it should let
me through most checkpoints
without being searched.
- Please, do come in and
make yourself at home.
I am Koku, regional director
of the Sakyo branch office.
I've heard your companions
were taken into custody.
- Huh?
- Please don't look surprised.
There's nothing that
happens in this city
that we aren't aware
of, now what favor is it
that you wish of the guild?
- I want to be added to a
caravan bound for Kinka.
Really that's all.
- Are you planning to leave
your companions behind?
- Right now the only
thing I'm able to do
for my friends is get to Kinka.
- I understand, say
no more my lady.
If that is what you wish,
then the merchant's guild
will see it done without fail.
- Huh?
- You look rather
confused about things.
The explanation
lies in your token.
- I don't understand,
I thought this was just
a standard travel pass?
- That's where you're mistaken.
The emblem on that travel token
has had a little
extra work done on it.
(doors clattering)
(gentle music)
- Oh this is--
- [Koku] It's called
luminous seven-colored paint.
It's a very special
commodity that only merchants
under the direct control
of the Hong clan know
how to manufacture successfully.
- The Hong clan?
- If a person carrying
a token bearing a
Ko family crest made with
this paint should come to us,
we were to help that
person regardless
of what we were
doing at the time.
That was a direct request from
the leader of the Hong clan,
as well as the
proxy clan leader.
(gasps)
- And in return for
our help, the Hong clan
will surrender the
manufacturing process to the
merchant's guild
as well the rights
to any derivative
works or products.
Despite refusing to budge during
many years of negotiations,
they've agreed to give
up those rights in return
for your guaranteed protection.
- Uncle Kuro.
- Now what would you like to do?
- Thank you, my wishes
are still unchanged.
Please find me a place in
a caravan headed for Kinka.
I don't care if
it's menial work.
- Very well my lady.
(people chattering)
- Huh?
(gentle music)
- Hmm?
- What are you doing here?
- I heard from the guild
that there's a girl
who wants to join
the group to Kinka.
So I replied that
I would be willing
to take her on as
my personal maid.
- Personal maid,
not menial work?
- They say through companionship
and travel we find
compassion in life.
I do trust that
we'll get along well.
- I understand,
your personal maid.
- Yes, but that reminds me,
I haven't even
asked your name yet.
- Huh, oh yeah, right,
my name is Kourin.
- I see, I'm pleased
to meet you, Kourin.
- [Kourin] In order to
get to Kinka I've become
the personal maid to a young
master of the Rin family.
But somehow this young
master reminds me of someone.
He's handsome, somewhat
removed from the norm,
and making advances towards me?