(logo trills)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
(bright music)
(woman panting)
- [Shuurei] Hey, Ryuushin, wait!
(both panting)
- (laughs) You can run faster
than that, Miss Shuurei.
Come on, catch me if you can.
- Don't give me any
of your lip, Ryuushin.
Today you've gone too far.
I won't forgive you for this.
It's one thing to
forget your homework,
but doodling on
the temple walls?
- [Narrator] Despite
the bitter winter cold,
Shuurei had reason to be heated.
This happened after she
took the aptitude test
but she was still waiting for
the results to be released.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
Stop that!
Ryuushin!
- I bet you can't reach me
all the way over
here, Miss Shuurei.
- (grunts) All right,
you asked for it.
- Huh?
Oh, no, no wait, on
second thought this
is too hard for you.
No, don't, stop it!
- You just wait right
there, Ryuushin.
- I said it's too hard.
(Ryuushin grunts)
(Shuurei screams)
Miss Shuurei, no!
(light music)
- You've caught a cold,
jumping into a river in
the middle of winter.
I'm just glad your heart
didn't stop beating.
You're very, very lucky.
- I wonder how long it's
been since I had a cold.
- Well the least I can
do is take care of you.
I'll make you a warm
drink and an ice pack.
So just lie back and
get a little rest, okay?
Hmm?
(light music)
- Sorry, I'm being childish.
Huh?
- [Seiran] I'll stay with
you a little while longer,
so please, just get some sleep.
- Your hand is cold, but right
now that feels really good.
- Huh?
(light music)
- [Young Shuurei]
Seiran! (giggles)
- My lady, I thought I
told you to rest quietly.
You have a bad fever
so stop rolling around
and pull the covers
over yourself.
- What's this I hear?
Speaking to such a young
child as if she's an adult.
You certainly are an
interesting fellow, Seiran.
- [Seiran] Madame, what
about her medicine?
- Don't worry I
have it right here.
My, Shuurei really has
taken quite a shine to you,
hasn't she?
- Madame.
What are you doing?
Please, stop.
- I told you to
stop looking sullen.
I won't have that in my house.
It's a waste to have a cute
face looking like that.
Come on, cheer up.
(icepick tapping)
(Seiran chuckles)
- What's this I hear
about Shuurei being sick?
- Master Shouka.
I thought you were planning
to spend the whole
night at the archives.
What's that?
- Huh?
How did I end up
carrying these things?
But we have to keep
her warm with blankets.
And we need some
nourishing food,
and, right, and icepack.
Wait, what?
That doesn't make any sense.
Why keep warm yet cool her down?
- [Seiran] Please,
calm down, master.
- Ah, yes, of
course, you're right.
I really must calm down.
You know it's been
a very long time
since anybody got
sick in this house,
so I was very surprised.
Hmm.
(light music)
(icepick tapping)
(upbeat music)
Oh, Seiran, I'll
take care of it.
(upbeat music)
- [Seiran] Please, master,
let me take care of this.
- [Shuurei] What's going on?
- Ah, are you feeling
all right, Shuurei?
- [Shuurei] Yeah.
- Wait just moment, I know
the very thing to perk you up.
I'll go and make you some
of my special ginger tea.
- Huh?
- Father, it's okay, really,
you don't have to do that.
- It's not a problem,
you just rest.
One small sip
and your cold will be
blown away in an instant.
- [Shuurei] If you do that.
- [Seiran] It's the kitchen
that'll be blown away.
- Seiran, you have
to go stop father.
If this house falls apart
any more than it already has
we're gonna have
nowhere to live.
- [Seiran] Yes, please
just get some rest, milady.
(Shuurei groans)
(dishes clatter)
Master!
- I remember this sort of
thing happening before,
now that I think about it.
(coughs)
- [Seiran] Madame, what
did you have her drink?
- [Shoukun] Well she's
always complaining,
"It's bitter, it's bitter,"
so I tried to make it sweet.
- [Seiran] Oh,
this is too sweet.
- That's strange, I
asked Shouka to try some
but he just smiled and
said it was sweet enough.
Now that reminds me,
Shouka said he'd make some
ginger tea for Shuurei.
(Seiran grunts)
(water bubbles)
(fire crackles)
- [Shouka] Let's see.
Where on Earth
would the ginger be?
- [Seiran] In all these years
he hasn't changed a bit.
- Excuse us.
- Huh?
- I hope you don't mind
us barging in like this.
No one came when we called
so we decided to just
come on in.
We couldn't help but
be a little worried.
Lord Shouka dashed
home immediately
once he heard Shuurei was sick.
We brought medicine
and vegetables for her.
- Well, now who do we have here?
Hello, General Ran,
and you too, Kouyuu.
I take it you've come to
pay poor Shuurei a visit?
(Ran groans)
(laughs) I was just making
some ginger tea for, Shuurei,
but I can't find
the ginger anywhere.
- I guess that's a
problem, you know?
Can't ginger it up
without any ginger, right?
(Seiran and Kouyuu scoff)
(Shuuei stammers)
Okay, that was pretty
bad, forget it.
- [Seiran] Master, don't worry,
we'll take care of
everything from here.
So please, go back and
sit with her ladyship.
- Really?
And here I was all fired
up to do some things.
Very well then, I'll
leave you to it.
- [Seiran] Don't worry
about a thing, sir.
- [Shuuei] Now then, Seiran,
you're gonna have to
walk me through this,
I've never held a
kitchen knife before.
- Maybe not a kitchen knife,
but you've certainly held
swords before, right?
They're both blades so
the basics are similar.
At the very least you
should be more helpful
than the master.
And if that's not
really your thing,
I can have you take care of
cleaning this place up instead.
- In case you've forgotten,
I happen to be a much higher
ranker officer than you are.
- [Seiran] How are you
at cooking, Lord Kouyuu?
- If it's fairly simple stuff
I should be able to
manage pretty well.
How 'bout yourself, Seiran?
- Well I've mastered
the innermost secrets
of replacing roof tiles,
repairing the outer walls,
getting rid of pests, and
bargaining for vegetables.
Given those facts I'd say
that's a rather foolish question
to ask, don't you agree?
- All right then!
(frantic violin music)
- [Reishin] Ooh,
she's sound asleep.
Her face is all flushed red.
She looks so pitiful.
- [Kijin] (coughs) I still
don't quite understand
why we have to act like thieves
and clamber over
the wall in secret
just to visit your niece.
- As I told you, I still haven't
been able to prepare myself
to tell her who I really am.
- [Kijin] Well, I'm going
to the front entrance
to visit properly.
If you wish to hang around here
and cling to the wall like
the dead shell of a cicada,
then go ahead.
- (scoffs) How pompous.
And bringing orchids no less.
- [Kijin] It is customary
to bring flowers
to someone who's not
feeling well, is it not?
- What are you doing, skulking
around outside like this?
Hello, Reishin.
Oh, Senior Secretary
Kou as well.
(Reishin grunts)
- [Reishin] Oh, big brother!
- You're so hopeless,
little brother,
but thank you so
much for coming by
to check on everything.
Please, come on in.
- Really?
Are you sure?
- Of course, I'm
not about to leave
two senior secretaries
out here to catch cold.
Besides, I can't
exactly ignore my dear,
younger brother as he sits
out here in the snow, can I?
But there is one thing, Reishin.
- Yes, what is it?
- Why not try the door
instead of a window?
- [Reishin] Oh, sorry.
I was so happy that I must've
gotten a little carried away.
(Kijin whooshes)
- [Kijin] I've brought flowers,
as well as some herbal medicine
that boosts resistance.
- Why thank you, Secretary Kou.
- Hey!
How dare you make your
entrance ahead of me?
I'm coming too, big brother.
(objects clatter)
They say that eating lots of
fruit is good for illness,
and I brought pretty
much every medicine
that we had available.
- But you brought way too much.
Honestly, it's the
same as always,
you run from one
extreme to the other.
And why did you bring
medicine to improve virility
and fight constipation?
- Huh?
I will have the herbalist
beheaded immediately.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Nevermind.
I do appreciate the
sentiment, Reishin.
(Reishin laughs)
- [Reishin] It's been
awhile since I last saw her
from this close.
- [Kijin] You followed her
around all during the summer.
You even went so far as to
have her call you uncle.
- I really am her uncle though,
so there's nothing
wrong with that.
In comparison, you're
her former boss,
almost a stranger.
Since dear Shuurei
is yet to be married,
I hereby forbid you to
come any closer to her!
- [Kijin] Remember that she
is not even acknowledged
your very existence yet?
(Shouka laughs)
- Pardon me, master,
but we're finished with
the meal preparations.
- Well thank you.
Well, then--
(Kouyuu gasps)
- Lord Reishin, you're here!
- [Reishin] And what, pray
tell, is wrong with me,
as a devoted uncle,
visiting my sick niece?
And now that I am here
I can see clearly.
It seems you've been
jumping the gun on things
without my knowledge,
haven't you, Kouyuu?
I'll deal with you later.
- [Kijin] (chuckles) I
wouldn't be surprised
if he throws you
out of the house.
(Kouyuu yelps)
(heavy banging)
- Who's that?
(light music)
- [Man] I'm deeply sorry
our foolish son has caused
you so much trouble.
- Oh, don't worry,
it's all right.
There's nothing to
be concerned about.
- Yes, but.
- [Shouka] Is there
something else?
- Actually, I was
wondering about Ryuushin.
Did he happen to
drop by here today?
- Huh?
No, he's not been
here at all today.
When did you see him last?
- [Man] Shortly after noon.
He said he was going
to the mountain
and hasn't been back since.
(grunts) I'll keep
searching for him.
- Wait one moment.
- Huh?
- Perhaps we can help.
Ryuushin said he was going
to the mountain when he left?
- Yes, sir, that's right.
- If he's talking about
a mountain close to here
perhaps he went to Mount Ryu
where madame's grave is.
- If it's Mount Ryu we
can get there by horse.
We'll go back to the
palace right away
and get some horses saddled up.
- Right, in the meantime,
I'll head back to the
main Hong residence.
I can get some protective
gear and torches ready.
- Do whatever you wish to.
But remember if you get
lost in the mountains
it won't matter how
extensive your knowledge is.
Against the snow and ice it
will essentially be meaningless.
- Yes, sir.
(hand whacks)
- [Shouka] Reishin,
at a time like this
the proper thing to say is,
"Be careful and
come home safely."
Got it?
- Yes, big brother.
- [Kouyuu] I can't believe
he did something like that
to the ever so
shrewd Lord Reishin.
Look at him.
He actually seems a bit happy.
- Seiran, I'd like you
to help the Kouyuu.
Could you go with him
to my brother's house
and help carry the torches
and protective gear?
- Yes.
- We could go back to the
palace for horses, General Ran,
but I'm afraid time
is of the essence,
so we'll borrow horses from
the main Hong residence.
- [Shuuei] Very
well, understood.
- [Kijin] My home is
closer to Mount Ryu.
If you do happen
to find that child
you should take him there.
- [Seiran] All right,
then the rest of us will
head to the Hong house.
(light music)
- That's a shame.
Kouyuu and the others
went to all the trouble
of preparing this meal
but now it's gone cold.
If necessary I'll go as well,
that way there'll be no
chance of anything happening
to Kouyuu and you can rest easy.
No need to worry about him.
- I would never
ask you to go out.
I'd rather have people
from the Hong family
sent out to conduct
a search instead.
- [Shouka] Mm, bell pepper pork.
It's a bit on the watery side
but very well made
for a first timer.
- I don't want you
do anything anymore.
In the end the goal
doesn't really matter.
There's only one thing
I truly want out of life
and that's for you and Shuurei
to live happily and peacefully.
- I'd say you've already
achieved that goal,
thanks to your keeping me
assigned to the archives
I've been able to read
the books that I like
as often as I like and
live happily and quietly
for the past 10 years.
I'm sincerely grateful.
- But that's only 10 years!
And those years haven't
been quiet or peaceful.
You've still been trapped by
all the political intrigue.
When I'd learned that you'd
gone to find the exiled prince,
I took the initiative
and sent assassins to
eliminate the previous king.
- (laughs) But your
efforts were thwarted
by Advisor Sho, right?
- Yes, the were.
Just what is he, some
sneaky raccoon spirit?
So much for his faithful promise
to have you live peacefully.
He's nothing but a liar!
He cheerfully used
you to the very end
and put all the
heaviest burdens on you.
- Everything that happened
was by my own will.
These bloody hands of mine
are nobody else's fault.
Thank you for always worrying
so much about me though.
I'm a very lucky man
to have two such adorable
younger brothers.
(chuckles) And yes,
regardless of what Kurou
might have you think,
he also worries about us.
At any rate, there's
something else,
I want you to properly
introduce yourself to Shuurei.
- But, big brother, I can't.
After what I did, Shuurei
must think I'm a bad person.
No doubt she believes I'm a
cruel villain of an uncle,
having thrown you out,
cut all ties with you,
and taking over as
head of the family.
"You're the worst
possible uncle.
"I despise people like you."
To think of her
saying that to me.
(light music)
- Reishin, what do you think?
Isn't our daughter cute?
Your niece carries my
blood and Shouka's,
and by extension,
your blood as well.
But Shuurei doesn't know
yet the depths of spite,
your utter self-conceit, or
your extreme selfishness.
Perhaps you'd like
to keep it that way.
You can make a start on it
by practicing your smile.
If you smile nicely then
Shuurei will smile back at you,
so you should start
practicing right away.
(light music)
(Shuurei cooing)
You know, Reishin,
it would be very nice
if one day everyone in this
family could find happiness.
(light music)
- This isn't looking very good.
- Ryuushin may be reckless
but he always has a
reason for his actions.
Let me think a minute.
His reason for coming to a
snowy mountain this season
would be--
- Medicinal herbs.
- In that case we should
concentrate our search
on places where medicinal
herbs are known to grow.
- All right, let's get going.
- [Reishin] You
know, the truth is,
I seriously did
practice smiling.
- [Shouka] You certainly didn't
improve very much, did you?
- Why are only Shouka
and the Senior Secretary
of Civil Affairs here?
Well, nevermind that, I
have another purpose here.
(light music)
She's hot.
That's right, Shuurei
gave this to me.
(light music)
That was a gift from me.
It's all right, I can
still wait for her.
(Shuurei moans)
- Water.
- Oh, she's thirsty.
Water, water.
This is awful,
I really hope that she
doesn't get sick too often.
To think that a sick
woman, once full of energy,
can become so unguarded
and defenseless like this.
It's torture.
(light music)
Not good.
The medicine.
Given the reason,
this is forgivable.
(cup rattles)
(light music)
(Shuurei screams)
- Shuurei, what's the matter?
(both gasp)
(Shuurei moaning)
- Well, you see.
(both growl)
- Ryuushin!
- Ryuushin.
- Where are you?
- Seiran, Shuuei, over here!
(calming music)
(Seiran sighs)
- [Ryuuki] Look, I told him,
I didn't do anything wrong.
- I bet I can guess
what happened.
You gave her the master's
special ginger tea
with no ginger, right?
- Nevermind that now, tell
me how's Ryuushin doing?
- At the moment
he's being treated
at Senior Secretary
Kou's residence.
His hands and feet are
slightly frostbitten
but there's no need to worry,
he's going to be fine.
- Geez, that boy is so reckless.
- Well you seem a lot perkier.
I suppose your fever
must've gone down somewhat.
Although that's a
little bit of a shame.
You looked very
lovely and attractive
when your cheeks were
all flushed like peaches.
- (giggles) Yeah.
- Oh boy, I don't believe you.
Why don't you go stick
your head in a snow bank
until spring?
- [Seiran] My lady?
- I'm leaving.
I've gotta go check on Ryuushin.
- That's not a good idea.
- But I'm really
worried about him.
(door slams)
- Huh?
- [Shuurei] Ryuushin!
- [Kijin] He insisted
on coming to see you
and wouldn't listen to reason.
- Miss Shuurei, I'm so sorry.
- Aw, Ryuushin.
- Miss Shuurei, you said
you'd be taking a break
from teaching at the temple.
I thought you only meant
for a little while.
But then I heard
from the head monk
that you might not be
coming back at all.
I was so worried.
I've been doing my homework,
but if I handed it in then
that would be the end of it.
I didn't ever mean to cause
you trouble, Miss Shuurei, but.
- Oh, Ryuushin, I'm sorry to
have put you through all that.
- [Ryuushin] I don't
want you to go.
Please don't do it!
Please don't get married!
- Married!
- Promise, in another
five years I'll become
just as good a man as
Seiran is right now.
- Now wait just a
minute there, young man.
Give me another five
years and I'll--
(fan whooshes)
- [All] Huh?
- What the?
- A fan?
Where'd the heck that come from?
(door creaks)
- Oh my, your majesty,
I'm very sorry about that.
The silly thing must've
slipped from my hand.
(Reishin grunts)
Come on, Ryuushin,
your father's bound to be
very worried about you,
so we better get
you home quickly.
Thank you very much
for gathering herbs
to help Shuurei get better.
- Yes, sir.
- [Kijin] Take care
of your health.
Once you're fully recovered
I'll send some camellias to you.
- Thank you very much, sir.
- [Kijin] I'll you
see to your home.
(door slams)
Reishin, I'm afraid you're
not doing anyone any favors
by acting like an
ornament out here.
- Uncle, I'm Reishin,
you're uncle.
I've been constantly watching
over you from the shadows
all these years.
- [Kijin] We're going.
- [Shuuei] Well then,
we'll be on our way too.
- [Kouyuu] Take care
of yourself, Shuurei.
- [Seiran] Hey, you two,
the kitchen still needs
cleaning, you know?
- Huh?
(Seiran chuckles)
- We can't ask that of
General Ran and Lord Kouyuu.
- Honestly, it's quite
all right, Shuurei.
- Don't worry,
just get some rest.
- I'll help out too.
I'm sure I can be useful.
- Thank you very
much, your majesty.
I have no doubt that
scrubbing pots and pans
will be of valuable
use to you someday.
- [Shouka] In that
case, I'll help out too.
- [Seiran] No, no,
please retire and rest
for the evening, master.
(door slams)
(melancholy music)
- [Shuurei] If only some
beautiful and kind person
could come into your life
and become your consort.
We keep drawing closer because
of your strong desire for me,
but I--
- [Shoukun] I think you
must be the biggest fool
I've ever met.
Do you honestly think
I'll ever come to call you
"Husband of mine?"
Falling in love with the
one you're supposed to kill?
In all my years I've
never heard of such a
laughable assassin.
Hey, Shouka, I love you.
I really do.
Shuurei and Seiran are
the cutest things ever.
I'm truly fortunate
to be your wife.
Thank you.
- It seems what
they say is true,
there's no medicine
for lovesickness.
(woman singing in
foreign language)
- [Shuurei] This
is the last time
I'll be working at Kougaro,
the number one brothel of
the entertainment district.
All I need to be focused on now
is the main national exam.
Huh?
Miss Kochou?
Who's that boy?