(upbeat music)
(singing in Japanese)
- [Narrator] Before they could
understand what was going on,
Shuurei and Eigetsu found
themselves being chased
by member of the Seikin Gang.
They escaped into Kogaro,
the number one brothel
of the red light district.
There, Ryuuki Shi,
the king of Saiunkoku,
was reunited with
his beloved Shuurei.
It was quite the
heart-warming scene.
(gentle music)
- Well?
Aren't you going to tell
me what you're doing here?
- Actually I came
to see your friend.
- [Shuurei] What?
To see Eigetsu?
- From what I understand,
Shuuei took him
under his protection yesterday
and brought him here to rest.
- Lord Ran was in my room,
but he was called out
in the middle of the night.
It turns out it
was because the boy
was being harassed by gangsters.
- Then Miss Kochou, you mean
the customer who left you early
was actually General Ran?
- Huh?
- (chuckles)
- He's got quite the nerve
treating someone like me
that way, don't you think?
- Ah, yeah.
- Excuse me sir, but
did I have anything
taken from me back then?
- Hmm, that's odd.
You're like a completely
different person
from the boy I met yesterday.
- Huh?
- Well, see, what
actually happened
- It's that Seikin gang
again, that poor kid.
What's wrong boys, the
loser of the drinking
game pays for all the
drinks, and 10 gold coins
that was the deal.
- You've got to be
kidding, there's no way
a little fret like you
could drink so much,
you must have cheated.
- You were the ones who
insisted on the drinking match,
How could I possibly
have cheated?
Being treated to free
booze was certainly nice
but you could have
at least picked a
better quality wine for me.
(laughs)
- What! Why you
little jerk, I'm gonna
strip you clean
and sell you off.
(Fight noises)
- What the...
- 1,2,3
- [Ryuuki Shi] Wow, not bad.
- He barely had 10
gold coins on him.
- Wait, that's...
I lost track of you for
a little while after that
but when I found you later,
you were half asleep.
You insisted on going to
the number one brothel
in Keio, so I brought
you here, you didn't
appear to have anything
stolen from you however.
- Oh but...
- [Ryuuki Shi] What
was it you lost?
- Er, well, to tell you
the truth, it was my
admittance token.
(Gasp)
- It seems I was
targeted because of it.
They said they had
already collected many so,
it's possible that
other people may have...
- The gang is collecting
them!? Is this true?
- [Eigetsu] Yes! Those
guys we encountered
said so.
- Hm
(Door opens)
- Madam Kocho
- Mm, yes what is it?
- A member of the Seikin
gang just walked in
and surrendered himself.
- [Madam Kocho] What?
- In fact it's someone we
know, it's that kid who
always comes here
to see Miss Shuurei.
- What!? Saunta?
Saunta, you idiot...
- What kind of relationship
do those two have?
- They've been friends ever
since they were children,
he has been hitting on
Lady Shuurei as long as
I can remember, it's been
tough keeping him away.
I even had to throw him in
the river during winter once.
After that, I'm
surprised to hear
he's still hanging around.
- I thought it'd be
cool, I wanted to have
something special about
me that would impress
the girl I like and
earn her respect.
Not to mention, to
prove to my love rival
that I could do
just as well as him.
- What does he mean by that?
- What are you going
on about Saunta?
For one thing, I don't
have the faintest idea
of who this girl you like is!
But I can tell you that
your logic is way off!
If someone tried to
impress me with "Hey, look
at me, I think I'm head
of a pack of thugs"
(laughs)
"awesome aren't I"
If I heard that, heck,
I'd drop him so hard
he'd bruise.
Now do you think you've
outdone that love
rival of yours by
joining a gang? Hm?
I didn't think so.
- [Saunta] I'm sorry.
- But what about my
token? Do you know
if it's at the Seikin
gang stronghold?
- [Saunta] I think
so. But they're
planning to come here
and make this place
their new base of operations.
- [Lord Ron] When?
- Tonight
- So they'll be coming
here, bringing all of those
tokens with them.
How convenient for us.
- [Madam Kocho] Just
a minute Lord Ron
as you well know, the
Seikin gang is our quarry.
- The circumstances have
changed somewhat, if possible
id like for us to
handle the matter.
- No!
If we're not the ones to
deal with these people
it will undermine our
standing in the city.
- Miss Kocho
- Then in the case, how
about on the condition
that we'll back off
as soon as we find
what we're looking for.
- Hm, I suppose that's fine.
We were only going to
give them a few more
days of free reign anyway.
- [Lord Ron] Shuurei
- Uh yes?
- Kocho is one of the
underground crime bosses
of Keio, she's the
leader responsible for
the Red Light District.
They say she's the the
heroine controlling the
gang alliances from
behind the scenes.
- So this is Kokaro huh?
- [Thug] Boss
- (grunt)
- Don't you think it's
a little too quiet
in there?
- [Boss] They're probably
jut scared of us,
enough waiting
around, let's go boys!
(Cheers)
- [Madam Kocho] Alright,
that's far enough
so you've dared to show
your faces here did you?
We give you a little
freedom and you act like you
own the world.
We'll show you what you
get for messing around
in our territory.
And we won't go easy on you.
Tonight this place has
been surrounded by all
the bosses of Keio's underworld.
- What was that you
just said? What the...
- [Madam Kocho]
You'll regret that you
ever dared set foot
in here. Now...
Let them have it!
(Cheer)
- Miss Kocho was one of the
underwolrd bosses all this time
- Glad now that I didn't
take her up on her offer
- You idiot, you don't
seriously think she'd spend time
with you, do you?
- Hey! Keep in down you
three, for Pete's sake.
- [Eigetsu] Sir, I've been
thinking I should go out
there too, the item is
very important to me,
if I lose it then coming to Keio
will have been a waste of time.
- [Ryuuki Shi] The
more important issue
is, can you fight?
- No, I can't, in fact
I'm actually kind of weak.
- [Ryuuki Shi] I'm
pretty weak too.
That means for the most part
the best I can do is search
thugs that are already down.
- Thank you so much.
- [Ryuuki Shi] Shuurei,
you come along too.
- Er, okay.
- [Ryuuki Shi] You and Eigetsu
stay where I can see you.
- And what about me?
- [Ryuuki Shi] I
don't care about you.
- (sad noise)
- That wasn't part of
the plan at all, damn!
Well as long as I have
these I won't have to worry
about money.
- Its not here
- I'll use you as a hostage
and get myself out of here.
- Shuurei!
- Shurrei!
- So you're the litte
snitch that ratted us out!
- I am so sorry boss.
Wait no that's not
right, let go of Shuurei!
(harp noise)
- Why hello there Eigetsu,
is it my turn yet?
- Eyogetsu, please I
beg you, save Shuurei.
- That's not any of
my concern, but still.
- [Shuurei] Eigetsu!
- Stand still!
(smash)
- Are you alright?
- Yes
- How dare you, you bastard!
( screams)
You!
- Eigetsu! Look out!
- I'm not Eigetsu.
- Huh?
- [Eyogetsu] My name...
(lightning)
Is Eyogetsu!
- Eyo..Eyogetsu?
- [Saunta] So he's the guy
Shuurei saw last night.
Is that wine?
- [Shuurei] It's
not that he simply
gets nasty when he's drunk,
he becomes a completely
different person.
- Huh? Here they are! This is it
help me pick them up Shuurei.
- Okay
Admittance tokens!
For the final exam!
How dare you do this
to people, Seikin Gang.
- Hey!
- Huh?
- [Saunta] Shuurei!
- (screams)
- What? Shuurei!
- Ryuuki!
- Be more aware of your
surroundings next time.
I did help you, but only because
Eigetsu asked me, don't
expect it a second time.
Oh and one more thing,
Eigetsu's token isn't here
(stumbles)
The alcohol is wearing off
- Mm, this young mans
skills really are
something.
- [Boss] Quite impressive
I have to admit,
of course my organization
will be taking him in.
- Are you kidding? I was the
first to set my eyes on him.
- [Ryuuki] I hate to
break it to you gentlemen
but we had an
interest in him first.
- Huh?
- And who might you be?
What's your name?
- [Ryuuki] Ryuuki,
my name is Ryuuki Shi.
(Laughter)
- [Boss] You have the
same name as the king huh?
I guess that means we'll
have to obey you then, right?
But anyway, the bottom
line remains the same,
we saw him first.
- [Ryuuki] Not quite, from
the moment Eigetsu accepted
this token, we had already
set our own eyes on him.
- A kid like this
is a final examinee?
But that means he
would have damned those
Seikin bastards!
- A commendable sentiment
but I hope next time
you'll take action
a little sooner.
- Your delay almost put
is in a very undesirable
position.
To think, they take
examinees admittance
tokens which they value
more than their lives
and use them for
blackmail purposes.
We trust that you will
give them the punishment
they deserve.
- One moment, are you
allowing us to repay our debt
to you by handling this
matter from here on?
- That seems only proper.
- Hm, we do not bow
before you simply
because of the seat
you occupy you majesty.
- To me personally then?
- Indeed. We bow
before you because you
are the one who righted
the mistake we made,
you were able to intervene
before matters became
irrevocable. And we bow
to offer our sincere
apologies for failing to uphold
our end of the agreement.
(Shocked whispers)
- (sigh)
- After today's incident,
the gang alliance
owes us a favor.
But more importantly, for
time being it would seem
that they've acknowledged
us as worthy allies
to have.
This is certainly an
unexpected surprise.
- Pardon me, but is
that my exam token?
- No it isn't, Shuurei,
have you found it yet?
- I'm afraid not, when
the other Eigetsu came out
he insisted that it wasn't
here with the others.
But he fell asleep
before he could tell me
where it really was.
- Hm
- Eigetsu?
- I'll drink some wine.
- [Shuurei] But I thought
you couldn't have alcohol?
- I'll get Eyogetsu to
come out, and then you can
ask him where he put it!
- I'm not gonna let you do that
- I have no choice, they
won't give me another token!
I have to find it,
no matter what!
- I know and I
understand how you feel
but...
- [Saunta's Father] Erm,
excuse me, please pardon
my intrusion
- [Shuurei] It is
Saunta's Father.
- Oh Miss Shuurei,
it's been a while,
it's so good to see you again.
As always I must thank
you for being so good
to my foolish wayward son.
Well then, to my business,
is there a Mr. Eigetsu To
in the building?
- Er, I'm Eigetsu To.
- [Saunta's Father]
Yes yes it was you!
Thank you so much for
the order to placed at my
store last night.
It was truly an honor to
have such a fine upstanding
young man visit
our store, to think
we were visited by
the youngest person in
history to pass the
provincial exam,
I was happy to be of service.
- My admittance token! Did you
get, er, did I give you this?
- Have you already forgotten?
- [Eigetsu] I went a
little overboard today,
it could lead to
trouble, please deliver
this along with the wine
otherwise the nitwit
is likely to end up
losing it in the chaos.
Send them to the number
one brothel in Keio.
Late tomorrow evening should do.
- [Sauntas Father]
Those were your words,
were they not?
By the way, here's
the bottle of wine
you ordered. You certainly have
discriminating taste,
even the king himself
rarely enjoys wine
of such quality
if I do say so myself.
It's a premium item
of course, one bottle
alone costs 10 gold
and 30 silver coins.
- No wonder you had
so little money!
- Now then, since my third
son seems to be intent
on sleeping like a baby,
I'll leave him to it.
When he wakes up,
please be so kind as
to tell the boy to
walk home by himself.
I hope you'll
patronize our humble
store again in the future.
- [Ryuuki] Eigetsu, from Saka
village in Koko province,
sweet Kyodo temple
serving as your sponsor
at age 12 you taught
the Koko provincial
exam.
This year, you'll be
taking the final exam
at only 13.
We're glad to token was
returned to you, do well and
pass the exam, then please
come and serve me.
- Then you're.. yes sir.
- That goes for you too.
I'll be waiting for you.
- [Madam Kocho] So today
is your last day isn't
it Shuurei?
- [Shuurei] Yes, thank you
for everything you've done.
- Like I said before,
I have a gift for you
a complete makeup set, with
instructions on how to apply it.
- It's very beautiful Miss
Kocho but I don't wear makeup.
- We had a promise didn't we?
Got that? As I said a promise
otherwise I'll be
forced to tell Mr Hong
and say you it all that
you've been working
in the Red Light District.
- Now that you mention it,
I was wondering, do you
know Sadon and my father?
- Yes I do. I first
met your father
a little while after
you began working here
one day he visited
me all on his own.
- Wait, so you mean that
father knew I was working here?
- He was very polite, he
bowed his head deeply and
said to me "Please take
good care of my daughter."
- What? He..he said that?
- He said "My daughter has
only recently lost her mother,
from here on in she will
encounter many things that I,
as a man, cannot
understand, that is why I am
asking you to take
good care of her."
Then not long after that I got
a visit from Sadon as well.
He said exactly the same
things Mr Hong had said and
then left.
I couldn't help
but laugh about it.
- [Shuurei] Sadon was here too?
So that's how he
knew about Kogotto.
- Alright it's done.
Take a look
- (gasp)
- Remember this well,
makeup is the war paint
of a woman.
Whenever you find yourself
heading into battle,
make sure you wear it.
That way you'll be certain
that you'll never cry,
if you cry your makeup
will run and no matter
how little you apply,
your face will end up
looking disgraceful.
That's why no matter
how difficult things get
you'll keep yourself
from crying.
You are headed into
battle aren't you?
Give it all you've
got, your courage
and determination make me
very proud to have known
you Shuurei.
- Thank you Miss Kocho.
- Come on, don't you
start crying, and remember
no matter what others
say you must never lose
pride in being a woman,
even if you find yourself
on the same stage as men,
don't try to become one, instead
be a woman and do all those
other things that men can't.
And if anyone gives
you a hard time,
be sure to tell me!
If he dares to come to
the Red Light District,
I'll give him a beating he
won't forget before I throw him
out.
- Coming from you I know
that's not supposed to be
a joke.
- Of course it isn't,
I'm being quite serious,
I'm not the only one either,
the same goes for Mr Hong
and Sadon.
You're surrounded by people
who care about you and
want you to succeed.
Go forth Shuurei, one day,
you will become a wonderful
woman.
(Soft Japanese music)
- Here I go, I'm going to
fight with everything I've got
- [Ryuuki Shi] Am I
making a big mistake?
I was so determined to open
the exams to women that
I didn't really think
about what it could mean
for me personally,
Shuurei said she wants to
become an imperial court
official and I know
she'd fulfill her
duty without question.
Yet I can't help but feel
that it's different from what
I want.
We'd be closer but somehow
I sense there'd be more
distance between us.
- Your majesty, in the end
the circumstances don't
matter at all, no matter
what you might think
it doesn't change how
difficult it is to try and
attract someones
affections towards you,
so what if Shuurei does
become a royal court official?
What difference does
that make? As far as
you're concerned, you
still have to take the same
actions and stay the
same course, don't you?
- You're right, you're
absolutely right.
- [Other Examinee] A woman
is taking a national exam?
- [Examinee] There's
a kid here too.
- Everyone's gawking at
us like we're a couple
of rare animals aren't they?
- Has another rare animal
arrived or something?
Wait a minute, don't
tell me that's...
Fioren!
(Flute)
It's been a long time hasn't it?
Oh this is Fioren,
general Ron's brother.
He's also taking the
final exam with us.
Fioren, I'd like you
to meet Eigetsu To
he's a.. we're friends, right?
- Yes
- [Fioren] Any friend of
Shuurei's is a friend of mine.
(gasp)
Eigetsu To, from now on
you're my kindred spirit too.
Look around us! Even the
weather is giving its approval
to our meeting,
the snow is blessing our
friendship and our bright
future ahead. So let's go!
Let's march on together,
into the final exam,
and into battle.
(Flute)
(Giggle)
- We definitely
have to pass okay?
- That's right! Definitely
- So let's get going!
By the way, I meant to tell you,
you look really pretty
with your makeup on.
- No way, I know I'm
lousy at applying it.
So there's really no need
to flatter me, Eigetsu.
- [Narrator] The results
of this years national
civil service examination
shocked everyone.
Standing above all other
examinees and impressively
taking first place position,
Eigetsu To, age 13,
was awarded the title of
Jogan, he thus became the
youngest person in history
to pass the national exams.
Second place, and the title
of Bogan, were awarded
to Fioren Ron, 18 years old,
and an incredibly gifted
eccentric.
And third place, along
with the title of Tanka
was awarded to Shuurei Hong,
age 17, thus the winter
of the third year of the
Jochi era, saw the birth
of Sian Koko's first female
imperial court official.
(Soft Japanese outro music)
- [Shuurei] A dream I never
thought would come true
has been realized, I've
taken my first step in
becoming a court official,
I wonder what my first
assignment will be.
What? Clean the toilets?