(singing in foreign language)
- [Shi Ryuuki] This
is an emergency.
Half the town's functions
have come to a halt
because of the Hong
Clan ceasing all work.
- Even for the Hong Clan,
there are some things
that are simply not acceptable.
- What exactly caused
all this Your Majesty?
- We believe the original
cause is quite obvious.
As you know, Senior Secretary
Hong of the Department
of Civil Affairs was arrested.
- That was because
Secretary Hong is suspected
of interfering with Initiate
Shurei Hong's national exam.
- [Shi Ryuuki] The Hong
Clan is a proud family
and equal to the Ran
Clan in nobility.
If you arrest the leader of
their family, especially without
evidence, that would naturally
enrage any prideful clan.
Not to mention
Secretary Hong himself.
(chattering)
- Secretary Hong is the
leader of the Hong Family?
- The leader of one of
the seven elite families
within Central Administration?
- Hmm.
- It's surprising how
many Senior Officials
were unaware of
this information.
- It was about fourteen
or fifteen years ago.
That was when he
took over the Clan.
- It can't be.
He's the leader?
(rattling)
(ominous music)
- Hey, where's Shurei?
- Seiran is with her,
don't worry about it.
(ominous music)
(water splashes)
- My Lady, before we go out.
Here.
(gasps)
Miss Kocho asked me to
bring it from the residence
when I was there last night.
She also said she
had to go elsewhere
this morning and apologized
for not being able
to see you off.
(gentle music)
- Hmm.
Miss Kocho gave this
to me a while back
during the final exam.
(gentle music)
(paper rustles)
- [Miss Kocho] Makeup is
the warpaint of a woman.
Whenever you find
yourself headed
into battle, make
sure you wear it.
That way you'll be certain
that you'll never cry.
- Hmm.
- [Miss Kocho] If you
cry, your makeup will run.
And no matter how
little you apply
your face will end up
looking disgraceful.
That's why no matter
how difficult things get
you'll keep yourself
from crying.
- Though Miss Kocho
was thoughtful enough
to give me this.
I couldn't bring myself to
wear makeup in the Palace.
Because the world of
politics is so male-dominated
I thought is wasn't necessary.
- My Lady.
- But I see I was wrong.
It doesn't matter whether
or not I wear makeup.
It's not gonna change
who I really am.
And besides, it's
impossible for me
to become the same as a man.
(chuckles)
I never had any intention of
trying to become one anyway.
Thank you Miss Kocho.
(mysterious music)
I'm gonna wear makeup today.
Seiran, I know you told me
I could always come to you
if I wanted to cry,
but I'm not gonna cry.
- Very well My Lady.
In that case since you
deprived me of that pleasure,
I'll just have to support you
so that you'll never
feel the need to cry.
- Oh Seiran, how is it
that you always seem
to know exactly what kind of
words I want to hear, huh?
(chuckles)
- [Seiran] Hey, you
better get ready.
We should get going shortly.
- The accusation is that
Senior Secretary Hong
altered illegally the
results of the exam taken
by Initiate Hong
who he sponsored.
Secretary Sai of the
Department of Protocol.
We understand you were
completely against women
taking the national exams
right from the beginning.
- Is that a crime?
Most people were against it.
If you're going to make
failed accusations.
Official Ryo would be
far more suspicious.
Well he's been treating
Initiate Hong very harshly.
I'm sure he's also got some
grudge against Secretary Hong.
Official Ryo never
had any objections
against female Officials
and not only does
he not bear a grudge
against Secretary Hong,
he's a favorite of
the Senior Secretary.
(whimpers)
- [Shi Ryuuki] Moreover,
you knew beyond a doubt
that your subordinates
were treating some
of the Initiates unfairly
and yet you still did
nothing to stop them?
- But I've heard this sort
of thing always happens.
- Yes, it does always happen.
Because Official Ryo
pays special attention
to outstanding Initiates.
(gasps)
- You showed absolutely
no mercy towards me back
when I was an Initiate.
I'd even say you
completely humbled me.
- I somehow doubt
your pride is fragile
enough for you to be humbled.
Now Secretary Hong, how long
do you plan on spending here?
- Official Ryo, why don't
you stay and have some tea?
- No, please hurry and
make your way to Court.
I only came because you said
you'd go if I went with you.
Do you know how bad things are?
Both inside and
outside the Palace?
- Can't say I
particularly care much.
For starters, it's a good lesson
for that young whelp
sitting on our throne.
He needs to learn more
about the hardships of life
and about not getting his way.
- Well I imagine you
would be the last person
he'd ever want to hear
that kind of talk from.
- Please have a seat.
After all I so
rarely get the chance
to spend time talking
with you in this manner.
And have some tea.
I swear it hasn't been poisoned.
(sighs)
(footsteps)
- As a matter of
fact I did seriously
contemplate eliminating
you a number of times.
After you ordered me to work
in the royal stables of course.
- [Official Ryo]
I'm not surprised.
I remember sensing
danger to my life then.
- I'm glad I didn't
go through with it.
Your true intentions
became apparent afterwards.
Eigetsu Tou is very
young and has no backing.
Shurei is not only
young but also female.
It was clear from the
start that they'd both
be looked down on by
Officials and that certain
people in the Court
would try to crush them.
Your strict guidance
and stern treatment
builds confidence in one's
self, as well as resistance
to the corrupting
influence of the Court.
Then by demonstrating
just how capable
the Initiates really are,
you make certain they're
no longer looked down upon.
Giving Initiates menial
jobs like cleaning toilets
and polishing shoes
are ideal for observing
what Officials are truly like.
(chuckles)
The highest Senior
Court Officials
base their decisions on how
capable the Initiates are.
They decide that based on how
much work you've
been giving them.
- [Official Ryo] You're
giving me too much credit.
- Not at all. All you
need to do is talk to
Kijin or myself and
we'd promote you
to any position you'd like.
- I don't want any other
position than this.
Many years ago the
previous King himself
bowed his head to me.
He said then that someone
like me was necessary
for the Court to exist.
And now once more,
his son was willing to
extend the same favor and trust
and said he would
leave everything to me.
This year I'm filled with very
high hopes for the future.
The young recruits all
understand the spirit
of helping each other
and their country.
From here on with their support
and assistance in
the Royal Court,
I have no doubt the
current King's rule
will be truly secure
and productive.
He's been quite fortunate
right from the very beginning.
(sips)
- In my opinion he's
very fortunate because
he has someone like
you around to help out.
I have to admit I
practically flipped
when I learned that
you were the one
secretly bringing
them stuff like
sweets, meat buns,
and tea every day.
Very sneaky of you.
It appears that practice
hasn't changed, even now.
- [Official Ryo]
I seem to remember
you being in quite the
snit about it saying
"What's with this
pathetic sweet pea bun?"
- Yes, but I still ate it.
You know, you
never say anything.
From my point of view,
your life is one
where you always get
the short end of the stick.
- Would you kindly
mind your own business?
- I hear his Majesty
intends to reward you
for your many years of service.
- Huh?
- From now on, I hope that you
will always attend
Court by my side.
Won't you?
- I'm quite satisfied
with my current situation.
Thank you.
- If you don't go with me,
then I won't go either.
Knowing you, if that
resulted in all work
outside the castle
walls coming to a halt,
it would bother your
conscience like hell
and you would feel responsible.
- Uh, are you trying
to blackmail me?
- Are you that dead
set against it?
Certainly your skills in loyalty
would be wasted on his Majesty.
Ah, I know!
Why don't you be a steward
for my household then?
Perfect, that's great!
- Hmm, very well.
I'll attend Court with you.
- Oh I see.
Oh well.
That's too bad.
So in that case, let's
be off as I promised.
(grunting)
(shouting)
- This is just like Ryuuki said.
It doesn't look like they're
gonna make it easy
for me does it?
- Are you all right?
- You bet! They're
solely mistaken
if they think these
guys are gonna stop me.
(footsteps)
- [Crowd] Come back here!
- Now then, onto a
different subject.
Senior Secretary Ko.
- Since a few years ago,
the Department of
Protocol has continually
requested annual
increases to their budget.
However I could not imagine why.
So after conducting
a complete audit.
We have found that
rather then unnecessary
or unwise expenditures,
an excessive number of odd
items are being purchased.
In addition every
year as a service
to those who pass
the national exams,
couriers are sent to
notify their home towns
of the good news.
- [Official] Is there
a problem with that?
- Yes, this year for instance,
Eigetsu Tou sent
his entire stipend
of 80 silver coins
by the Department of
Protocol's courier.
But not a single coin
arrived at his home town.
- What does he mean by that?
- A number of similar
incidences have been reported
over the past several
years as well.
(audience chattering)
So this year after the
Department of Protocol
sent out it's couriers,
we had them secretly followed.
Now whose residence do
you think they went to
with that money still
in their breast pockets?
- Oh, That's a lie!
- But I haven't even
mentioned any names yet.
- Well then.
I'll have my own say on
matters as well, Secretary Ko.
What is the meaning
of that mask you wear?
And how can we accept that a man
who can't even show his own face
somehow rose to the top ranks?
- Huh?
- Hmm.
- You could in fact be some
unknown man wearing that mask.
Pretending to be the
real Secretary Ko.
If you truly don't
have anything to hide
then take that mask
off immediately
and show your face to us.
(sighs)
This development is something
you'd expect more from some
second rate fiction novel.
But, very well, if you
insist then I'll take it off.
- No!
Please don't do it!
I beg you.
I mustn't betray
my wife anymore!
- Please Senior Secretary don't!
Don't disturb my peaceful
life any further.
- Huh, what's this?
Is Secretary Ko's
face that ugly?
- Lord Reishin says his face
is one that would cause crows
to fall from the
sky unconscious.
- I know it may be
unconvincing coming from me
but looks don't
actually make the man.
- (wheezing laugh)
If he's insisting
to that extent,
then why not take that mask off?
However, everyone else
must turn their backs
and you're only to
show Secretary Sai.
- Can I look too?
- You mustn't!
- Hmm?
(whimpers)
- Those of you who don't know
what Secretary Ko's face
looks like, don't get curious.
If you look you'll be
distracted from work
for three years at best.
If you're unlucky
you'll lose your senses.
- Who does this old
fox think he is?
Now then.
(whimpering)
(crowd jeering)
- My Lady let's stop and take
care of these guys already.
- No if we fight here,
we'll cause trouble
for everyone else.
- That's Miss Shurei!
(panting)
- [Crowd] Keep running!
- This will only take a moment.
- Oh you gonna fight!
(screaming)
(crashing)
(tense music)
- Let's hurry My Lady.
- Right.
(tense music)
- This way!
(panting)
- Aah!
(malicious laughter)
(crowd jeers)
- Oh no!
- Don't worry Miss Shurei!
- Ayushin.
(rattling)
- Whoa, what's with them?
- You have a lot
of nerve treating
our Miss Shurei like this.
We're not gonna let
you get away with it.
(crowd jeers)
- I'm very sorry about how
we acted towards you lately
but Officials are
really important people.
So if you hung around
poor villagers like us
we thought you'd be made fun of
and end up shamed because of us.
We didn't want that for you.
(jolly music)
- Hmm.
- You'd better get going.
You're in a hurry aren't you?
- We'll take care
of things here.
Go on!
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
(footsteps)
- (laughs)
You're not going anywhere.
(yelling)
(crashing)
- Thank you Ayushin.
Thank you everyone.
(jolly music)
- Halt!
- Huh?
- This isn't a place
that people like you
are permitted to enter.
Turn around and leave.
- But I'm an official Initiate.
I have a right to enter!
- Don't know you.
- I have to be at
the Court by noon!
You have got to let me in.
Stand aside right now.
- My Lady, I think our best bet
is to fight our way through.
Huh?
(doors rattling)
(gasps)
- Hello, Initiate Heki.
(jolly music)
- [Miss Shurei] Hakumei!
- I figured something
like this would happen
so I came out here to meet you.
Your family is noble but poor.
Mine is of a higher status
so lots of Officials
are soft on me.
I'll escort you in.
Hurry!
- Uh, thanks very much.
Let's go, Seiran.
- Yes.
(jolly music)
(prestigious music)
- If you please, Secretary Ko.
(gasps)
(whimpers)
- Are you quite satisfied
now, Senior Secretary Sai?
(whimpers)
- It's just as expected.
There's no way he'd be able
to keep his senses after
seeing Hoju's utter beauty.
I can't help but pity him,
even though it's Secretary Sai.
(sighs)
- You're the person
who attempted
to entrap Initiate Hong and
Reishin Hong are you not?
- Uh huh.
- You have also
embezzled public funds,
spent money recklessly on bribes
to pave your way to promotions
and even tried to
blame your wrongdoings
on Official Ryo, haven't you?
- Uh, uh huh.
- We have our testimony now.
- Hoju, you tricked him into it.
- It's all the truth.
We also have testimony
from the idiots involved
in that mud ball incident.
This is no trick.
- Well yes, that may be so.
But it still feels
like you tricked him.
- No!
Personally, I think this
should have been done
from the very beginning.
(laughs)
Honestly, I never imagined he
would be this much of a fool.
(whimpers)
(claps)
- Oh, Senior Secretary Hong!
- Now, it seems
you've been doing
some exceptionally
amusing things lately.
- No, no, no, it wasn't
my doing I swear.
- Even if there's a one in a
million chance that's true,
I believe it was your doing.
So the truth of the matter
is of little importance.
- That's insane.
- From now on it's
in your best interest
to avoid anywhere with
connections to the Hong Clan.
I've already sent
out several notices.
If they find you
you're as good as dead.
You'll be weighed down
and tossed in the
nearest river to drown.
- And of course, there isn't
a single place in this country
that doesn't have ties
with the Hong Clan.
- Like me, my Clan is
extremely difficult
to control when angered
and is exceptionally vindictive
towards those who insult us.
Rest assured we won't
forget your name
or face, even after
a hundred years.
(gasps)
- What a scary option.
- Oh, I'll never do this
sort of thing again.
- Too bad.
I make it my practice
to crush those I despise until
they can no longer stand.
A few years ago you made
fun of my adopted son
by calling him an
abandoned child.
Since that moment
I've had no intention
of ever forgiving you.
Oh, one more thing.
(officials gasp)
- So that's where he was
hiding it all this time?
- There's a saying
about hiding one's head
but not ones bottom.
- But he couldn't even
manage to hide his head.
- The ring that symbolizes
the Sa Clan's leader
or rather a fake of it.
- Oh that's...
- I don't know why you
would have this sort
of thing nor do I really care,
but I can tell you it's
pointless to take this
to the Sa family and try
getting help from them.
I've already taken
care of matters.
- Oh, you're not serious?
- Did you expect me
to leave a single escape
route open to you?
How foolish.
(whimpers)
- This isn't my fault.
It's all because of women.
- Hmm?
- Oh, this is all because of
women coming into the picture.
- She's late.
- She'll be here.
(jolly music)
- You surpassed even me when
you passed the national exams.
It's time you show those
brainless Officials
who can only make fun of women
and children what
you're capable of.
- Hakumei!
- Huh!
(clash)
- Not again.
- Initiate Heki.
How are you at fighting?
- We of the Heki family excel
in the arts and literature.
We don't know the first
thing about fighting.
- He's useless.
(guards jeer)
- Can I fight while
protecting them both?
(guards jeer)
(laughs)
(scream)
(gasps)
- Hey there!
- Ensei!
- Yeah, it's been a while,
Princess, Seiran, hmm.
(officials muttering)
- The ones who compiled
the papers documenting your
misdeeds are none other
than Initiate Hong
and Initiate To.
- But these detailed figures...
- Having been falsely accused
of inappropriate conduct,
Initiate Hong
stayed up all night
to finish this in hopes
of vindicating herself.
They were quite aware
of whose conduct
was inappropriate,
Senior Secretary Sai!
- Huh!
Don't you all think
it's very strange
how the national exams were
all of a sudden open to women?
Not to mention a 17 year
old girl passing is Tanka.
- The national exams
aren't that easy.
- The King forced the issue
of women taking the exams.
Don't you find that odd?
- Your Majesty, I
do agree with him.
Please, we must demand the
full truth of the matter.
- If she didn't pass
using her own ability
we cannot accept it.
After all, that was
the primary reason
why the previous King
introduced the exam system.
- [Officials] That's right.
Your Majesty?
- You're right.
Ability is the main principle.
The previous King knew this.
That's why he created
a system even the King
could not interfere with.
[Officials] Ah!
- All of you have gone
through the national exams.
You should already know
this better than anyone.
You all have first-hand
experience of the
system's fairness.
You know how impartial
the exams are
and how effectively they
prevent any impropriety.
The national exams aren't easy.
- But, if that's truly the case,
why doesn't Initiate
Hong show herself?
Huh.
I have doubts that
it was Initiate Hong
who actually wrote these papers.
How are we supposed
to know for sure?
(muttering)
It's almost noon.
The time of the
Inquiry's about to start.
Could it be she knew
she'd embarrass herself
and decided to run away instead?
(muttering)
But still, even if she's unable
to become an Official,
as a Lady of the Hong Clan,
no doubt she'll have plenty
of good marriage proposals.
(laughs)
(doors rattle)
(gasps)
- [Officials] I
don't believe this.
- Shurei Hong reporting
for duty My Lords.
(muttering)
(growling)
- Initiate Hong, some in
this Royal Court suspect
there was impropriety involved
in you passing the
national exams.
Your response?
- I will prove myself.
I cannot afford to
quit being an Official
since as of yet I have
not accomplished anything.
- It is now noon.
We will hold the Inquiry
here in this Court.
With a public oral examination
there can be no means
for impropriety.
- As you wish, Sir.
Please?
(gentle music)
- Hmm.
- Very well.
Let the inquiry begin.
(doors rattling)
(jolly music)
Now, one final question.
Why did you as a woman
want to become an Official?
I'm afraid that if the
crux of the question
is why as a woman
do you do this,
then I have no answer
for you or this Court.
I came to do what I can do
as myself and simply that.
I would have taken
the national exams
whether I were a man or a woman.
I want to be an Official.
I want to protect as much
as I can with my own hands.
Those were my reasons.
That's why I took
the national exams.
(gentle music)
(singing in foreign language)
- [Shurei] At last,
the special observation
of the new Officials
is almost over.
I wonder, where will we
all be assigned after this?
On second thought, it
doesn't really matter.
It's still just an
issue of doing my best.
No matter where I am.