(techno instrumental)
(singing in foreign language)
(tense music)
- [Narrator] As she
confronted Tsushou Sa,
Shuurei flatly refused any
engagement with Sakujun.
However, her flower bud
hair pin still remained
in the hands of Sakujun
and she had no idea
as to the whereabouts
of Eiki Hyou.
Luckily, she did have a good
idea where Kokujun Sa might be.
(tense music)
(footsteps pattering)
- Hey boss, that's you isn't it?
- How did you guess?
- I kind of sensed it.
So what did you find out?
- It was just like
you suspected, there's
an unusual shrine
at the edge of the
residence courtyard.
- I thought as much.
- How'd you know, Miss Shuurei?
- In rich residences it's
customary to have a shrine
for the eight colored
enlightened ones.
Since having one of those
shrines is so common,
a lot of people
just ignore them.
- [Shourin] Oh, I get
it, I understand now.
- [Shuurei] That's
where the entrance
to the basement must be.
- The only thing is there are
a lot of guards in front of it
what do we do?
- They're holding the
selection ceremony tonight.
The guards will be busy with
the gate in main building.
If security's ever going to
be light, today's the day.
- Huh, but, uh...
Sorry, but tonight really
isn't a good time for me.
- Huh?
- I already accepted another
assignment for tonight.
So if you'll excuse me.
- Hey wait a second Shourin?
Oh great, well if
that's the case,
then I'm just going to
have to go there by myself.
(gentle music)
(drink pouring)
- Huh?
You need to be at the
selection ceremony soon.
Why are you sitting
here drinking
and not even getting ready?
- It's because I
don't feel like going.
- You really have no motivation
to do anything, do you?
- It's just that this
is the very last day
that I'll be able to
spend together with you.
To me, that's more important.
- Oh, honestly.
- Hey, would you do
my hair up for me?
- Look, I'm not your
personal maid, okay?
Why not ask somebody
else to do that for you?
- I only want you to do it.
- Huh?
- Could you do my hair and
make me some tea as well?
- All right, since
it's the last time.
You seem sort of quiet today,
have you had too much to drink?
Are you not feeling well?
- (laughs) No, that's not it.
I have a very strong stomach
when it comes to alcohol.
- Now that you mention it,
I don't believe I've ever
seen you drunk before.
- That's very true.
- All right, I'm done.
If you're not going to
the selection ceremony,
then you should try to
get some more sleep.
Here, I'll pour a little
hot water for you.
- I'd really prefer Ganlu tea.
- Not happening.
- Why not?
- Because.
Wait a sec, the shelves
look a little different.
There's a lot more empty space.
Ah, Ganlu tea is the only
kind of tea leaf you have.
- It's only fair since you
rejected an engagement with me
so bluntly.
I don't think it's asking
too much to let me savor
a little sweet thought from you,
especially now since
you're leaving.
- He's got to be kidding.
He wants to drink
Ganlu tea that badly?
Here, have some hot water.
- (sighs) Are you
worried about me?
- Well, yes, you're acting
even more strangely than normal
so I am a bit concerned.
- (chuckles) You're very kind.
Then I'll drink it.
There, I've had some.
Now I'd like you to make
some Ganlu tea for me.
- No way.
- Huh?
- You've been drinking
wine, and a lot of it.
If that wine mixes weirdly
with Ganlu tea in your stomach,
you could end up
making yourself sick.
Just have the hot water today
and get some decent rest, okay?
- I don't care, I don't
mind if I get sick.
This is going to be
the very last day
I can have you make tea for me.
- (sighs) Now come on.
- If you don't brew
any Ganlu tea for me,
then I'm afraid
I'm going to die.
- (chuckles) That's
something a child would say.
Hmm, geez, guess
it can't be helped.
Say, do you remember
the promise you made?
- Of course, I'll return
your flower bud to you.
You seem awfully
busy at the moment,
so come back here after you
finished everything else.
- You know, I wouldn't mind
having it back right now.
In fact, I insist you
return it this minute.
- Don't spoil my dreams now.
Dreams, do I have one, hmm.
- Hey, what's the matter?
- No, it's nothing.
- Okay then.
(tea pouring)
(people chattering)
(crickets chirping)
(horse neighing)
- I still wonder,
will it be all right?
- Why not?
It was an official invitation
that the Sa clan gave us.
We can just hold our heads
high and go in the front gate.
- Okay.
- Anything could happen
during the selection ceremony.
You take care of
matters on that end.
- Got it.
As for you, make sure
that Shunki's safe.
The people from the Sa clan
will know what she looks like,
so you'll have to be careful.
- I know.
(crickets chirping)
Fortunately it's a
new moon tonight,
it's the perfect
night for sneaking in.
- Well then, shall we
join the celebration?
- [Man In Wagon] Yeah.
(horse neighing and trotting)
(gentle music)
- Huh?
Kanshou.
(item clatters)
- [Ryuuki] Bakuya?
- Ryuuki, you're a man so
that should keep Bakuya
a little quieter
when you use it.
That Bakuya and this
Kanshou are yin and yang,
the same sorts
put into two parts
by the members of the Hyou clan.
It's said that if they're
forcibly separated
from each other, they
put up resistance.
But they say the Bakuya
possesses a woman's nature
within itself and for that
reason it will go quiet
if it's wielded by a man.
(laughs) Of course, it may
still be difficult for you.
(tense music)
- If Bakuya's female,
then Kanshou must be male.
It's a reflection
on your great skill
that you're able to keep
Kanshou under control, brother.
The origin of the
twin swords is--
- Exorcism.
(crickets chirping)
If the swords that were
forged for the purpose
of obliterated demons
are now howling...
Lady Shunki, from here on
I fear I will be heading
in a different direction
than you are going.
This sword's gentle
towards women.
It will definitely protect
you, please take it.
I'll be fine, even without
this sword with me.
- [Guard] You,
identify yourself.
- Hmm?
- Come out of there.
- What's going on?
- Over here.
- Is that them?
- (grunts) What
is it Lady Shunki?
(tense music)
- Huh?
What are you doing?
I don't understand.
Huh?
(guards chattering)
- Hey, who is that?
- Wait, wait a second,
this girl is...
- Uh, uh...
(guards grunting)
Hmm.
(footsteps tapping)
Why, of course.
I completely forgot that
she was a blood relative
of the clan that created
you in the first place.
(laughs) Whether
it's her or my lady,
the embarrassing
fact still remains
that the women are
by far the stronger.
(crickets chirping)
Now.
(footsteps patting)
I will do what I have to do.
(tense music)
- Listen to me Shunki,
you must promise me
that you will only use that
power for the sake of one person
and one person alone.
Keep your power locked away
and use it for the sake
of that one special person
whom you'll meet one day.
Muster all your
effort and go forth
to save that fool whom you love.
Just as I once did in the past.
- Oh.
There it is.
Guards!
In that case...
(crickets chirping)
(footsteps patting)
(water trickling)
- But I have evidence.
You have to let me
through immediately.
- We can't do that, we've
been specifically ordered
by Lord Tsushou not
to let anyone through.
- There's someone in
there, isn't there?
- No, there is no
one inside here.
- If there's nobody in there,
then what's the problem?
Let me through.
- Oh, no, no way, the
divine punishment.
- Are you nuts or something?
Divine punishment
comes from the Gods,
not the eight colored
enlightened ones.
- What are you saying?
- Ah, she's being a
pain, just take her.
- Ha!
(tense music)
- Huh?
- What?
- Lady Shuurei Hong, please
keep your ears covered
with your hands until
I say it's all right.
- Ah, why are they moving?
I can't stop.
- You, rank in file
guards, lose consciousness
and remain asleep until
I command otherwise.
(guards grunting)
- Ah, what, what the
heck just happened here?
- Don't worry,
it's all right now.
- (gasps)
It is a great honor and pleasure
to finally meet you
at last, Lady Shuurei.
My name is Shunki Sa.
- Lady Shunki?
But I've been told that
you are unable to speak.
- No, it's not that
I couldn't speak,
I simply made the choice not to.
- Huh?
- It's the words that
come out of my mouth.
They contain the
power to force people
to do whatever I might say.
As you can imagine, it's
extremely dangerous,
and that's why in order to
hide this power from people
I kept my voice sealed away.
- Who would've guessed it
was something like that?
(footsteps echoing)
Huh?
- Huh?
- Well, I have no
idea what that is,
but I'm pretty
sure it isn't good.
(footsteps approaching)
Come on.
(tense music)
- Ah, ah, oh.
(breathing heavily)
- That man, it's
great uncle Tsushou.
- (sighs) I can't believe
someone like him could ever...
(breathing heavily)
I am not going to die
here, I've come this far.
Just a little further
and everything will
be within my grasp.
(breathing heavily)
(tense music)
- Lord Tsushou.
I've come to deliver the
item you were promised.
Here's the ring that
marks the bearer
as the head of the Sa clan.
- Huh?
- (gasps)
- Ah, ah, huh?
(breathing heavily)
What's the meaning of this?
- Normally, it is the
pride of a merchant
to meet any request from his
customer, no matter how big.
However, this is one
request I cannot meet.
As a member of a family that
has confronted generations
of Sa clan tyranny and a clan
of proud government officials
determined to uphold the law
without yielding to others,
as a member of the Sai clan,
this is my response
to your request.
- (grunts)
- All the mayors and
officials of Sa province
have already entered
Korin, bringing with them
the evidence to condemn
Sa clan once and for all.
- What?
- In particular, officials
Ensei Ro and Yushun Tei
have already begun
to make their move.
They have put a stop to
the anticipated riots
you instigated in Korin
before they even began.
The official military
officers of Sa province
have joined those of
the merchant's guild.
They will descend on the
gathered clan members
to formally arrest and
detain every one of them.
- (laughs)
So I suppose you're intending
to tie them up in ropes.
Go ahead and try binding
corpses and dragging them away.
- What did you say?
- Hmm?
- Oh.
- Hmm, hmm.
It's getting close to the time
of the selection ceremony.
All those fools who are obsessed
about how pure the
family line was
or how we'd be tainted by
blood from outside the clan,
they were all a nuisance.
I was planning to use the
ceremony to clean house.
Just like him, just like
my older brother Enjun did.
- You're not serious?
- (gasps)
- (laughs)
(footsteps pattering)
- Quick, we have to hurry,
we must notify Governor To
and Lieutenant Governor
Ro immediately.
- Wait a moment. (gasps)
- (breathing heavily)
(gasps and grunts)
- Lord Tsushou Sa once details
of your crimes are made clear
I'll decide what
will become of you.
If you have any pride as
a member of the Sa clan,
please wait right here.
I will finish what
I have to do first
before I have you arrested.
(gentle music)
I'll get a doctor,
you mustn't move.
- We can arrange for a doctor
but it may already be too late.
- Yes, I know that, but still.
- Thank you very
much, Lady Shuurei.
- Huh?
- Hmm?
- You've shown concern
for great uncle Tsushou,
even to what may be
his very last moment.
I want to thank you for your
kindness and compassion,
Governor Hong.
- Lady Shunki, Governor Hong.
- Hmm?
- I have to admit, you've
made a magnificent start
at being governor
of this province.
- (chuckles)
Mr. Shou Sai, will you please
attend the selection ceremony?
I'll be going along
with Lady Shunki.
- Very well.
Here, please take this.
Governor To had me
hold onto it for you.
With this seal
returned to your hands,
you'll be a governor of
Sa province once again
both in name and in
deed as you should be.
- Thank you very much
for bringing the seal
back to me, Mr. Sai,
and I owe you an apology
for suspecting you.
I'm sorry.
- It was only right,
you wouldn't be doing
your job properly
if you believed everyone
and anyone so easily.
You should be especially
cautious of greedy men like me.
Well then, good luck to you.
(footsteps pattering)
- We'll be sure to
catch up with you later.
Well, I guess that means you
and I should get going too.
Are you ready?
- This is what I came here to
do from the very beginning.
(footsteps pattering)
- Huh?
- What is it, Lady Shuurei?
(gentle music)
- I'm not sure.
(Tsushou gasping)
- Elder brother, Enjun,
if only I'd been blessed
with a little more luck
and talent like you.
- [Stranger] You fool.
- Huh?
- You think it was
only luck and talent?
Did you think Enjun climbed
that high on that alone?
- What?
Who the heck are you?
And how do you know anything
about my older brother, Enjun,
or me?
(grunts) Well, at this point
in time, I don't really care
who you might be.
- If Enjun had had as much
luck and talent as you thought,
then he would never have
had to struggle so hard
in his life.
Over thorns, on red hot
iron, or through frozen snow,
he was the type of man who
would willingly walk barefoot
through it.
I've never known any other
man as foolish as he.
If there was anything he
possessed in abundance,
it would be the true
kindness of his heart
and his unwavering perseverance.
Even if he were
covered in wounds,
he would never utter
a single complaint.
He wouldn't even
glance down at them,
but would proceed down the path
that he himself believed in.
- (grunts) Elder brother.
- The hour's grown too late.
Enjun no longer has time
left to spare for you.
That's why I've
come at his request,
to see your final
moments in this world.
- Oh. (grunts)
- On that dark day, you
saw everything, didn't you?
Are you really
unable to remember
what Eiki said to him then?
(Tsushou breathing heavily)
(gasping)
- This isn't your fault,
don't you understand?
None of this is your fault.
Why is it necessary
for you alone
to carry everything on
your shoulders, Enjun?
- (gasps)
- You were mistaken
from the very beginning.
There's no way that someone
like you, who never tried
to understand anything,
could ever surpass Enjun.
Even though that idiot
tried with all his heart
to protect everything.
- But, I... But I...
(whooshing sound)
Huh, Enjun, brother.
(Tsushou falling to ground)
(crickets chirping)
(air whooshing)
- There's no use in crying
over spilled milk, is there?
It's all too late now,
all because you insisted
in doing the unnecessary but
right thing to the very end,
Enjun.
(gentle upbeat music)
- [Narrator] The start
of the selection ceremony
for the head of the Sa
clan was drawing close.
As every person on
all sides run headlong
toward their respective goals,
Shuurei and Shunki began to
follow the dark path before them
in search of Kokujun Sa.
(footsteps echoing)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
- We're in the courtyard
shrine of the Sa clan
where the eight colored
enlightened ones
are supposed to be worshiped.
Is Mr. Kokujun locked
up inside here?
I have a really bad
feeling about this.
But all right, I'm going in.