(electronic chords)
(soothing Japanese singing)
(tense music)
- [Voiceover] Sakujun
Sa, the man who had been
controlling the
murderer's blades
from behind the scenes
has disappeared.
Shortly afterwards,
Shuurei encountered
the mayor of Kinka, Shinsai.
However, almost immediately...
(harp music)
- [Seiran] Sakujun Sa.
I will not forgive that man.
(tense music)
- So, Sojun has died.
You may take your leave.
Sakujun, to think he has
started to make his move.
I thought he was no more
than a vain hedonist.
I mustn't underestimate him.
(dark music)
(gasping)
- Is that you, Chushou?
- Elder brother.
(gasping)
The eldest on of the main house.
I thought the two of
you got along well.
(gasping)
- Every last heir of
the main house is dead.
As of now I will be the
head of the Sa clan.
- It's quite
possible that Sakujun
might take after
my elder brother.
The brother who never let
anyone see his other side,
and who, once the
opportunity presented itself,
made a blood bath out of all
the men of the main house.
(horse neighing)
(rain falling)
- Until Koren then.
(soft music)
- My lady.
(sighing)
(birds chirping)
- Such beautiful weather.
- [Kourin] Lady Shuurei?
- Oh, sorry, the tea's ready?
Thank you very much.
Kourin, by the way, I'm
really glad your safe.
- That's supposed to be my line.
You were unconscious
for so long.
I'll have you know
that I was so worried
I couldn't even sleep.
- I was only sleeping
because I was exhausted.
Isn't that right, Eigetsu?
- That's right.
You probably didn't rest
much during your long voyage.
So this was just a result of it.
(dinging)
- You get out already,
I can take care of
everything here on my own.
So scram you quack doctor.
(groaning)
- In that case, please
take this medicine
with your tea, Shuurei.
- Thank you.
(growling)
What's wrong?
You're being very cold to him.
- But lady Shuurei, he
was just terrible to me.
He collapsed after Lord Ryuuren
made him drink some wine.
So I was trying to
take care of him,
and then suddenly...
- [Eigen] Move it,
out of my way girl.
- And saying that
he pushed me away.
- Well that's because-
- I don't like those
kinds of people,
and that's that.
(soft harp music)
(laughing)
Lady Shuurei, this is
no laughing matter.
- But I haven't seen you so
lively in quite some time.
It's nice, Kourin.
I guess we have Eigetsu
to thank for that.
Hey, Kourin, please smile again.
The truth is I really
like seeing you smile.
- Lady Shuurei?
- And thank you so much
for all your efforts
in becoming my replacement.
You did it even though
you were in great danger.
(knocking)
- Princess, do
you have a moment?
If you don't mind,
there's someone here
who would like to
speak with you.
- Speak with me?
What is it?
(chuckling)
- Nothing.
I'm just glad to see you're
feeling better today.
- I'm so sorry I worried you.
I'm all right now.
- Good to hear.
Koku, come on it.
- Koku?
- I'm pleased to meet
you, I'm Kokujun Sa.
- You're Kokujun?
That person's younger brother.
They don't look at all alike.
- [Ensei] Princess?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just that even
though you're brothers
you seem like completely
different people.
- That's true I guess.
The oldest, Sojun was
always very hot tempered.
And in the other extreme,
the second son Sakujun
is so beautiful you'd never
guess we were related.
And as I'm sure you can see,
as a third son I'm no
better than a commoner.
- No, I disagree.
If it weren't for your
bravery and support
I probably never would
have been able to see
Eigetsu and Kourin alive again.
Thank you for protecting the
people who mean so much to me.
I'm in your debt.
- I...
I have a small favor
I'd like to ask of you.
- Yes, what is it?
- It's about my elder
brother, Sojun's remains.
Would be all right if I could
see to his burial by myself?
(suspenseful music)
- It's been a while since
your last visit home,
hasn't it, Enjoun?
- The chrysanthemum residence.
- The chrysanthemum emblem out
front has been scratched out.
And the Sa clan crest,
the profusion of peacocks,
has been carved in its place.
- It's Sakujun's doing.
- To think that he's the one
who would dare to erase
the chrysanthemum,
the flower specially bestowed
upon you by the previous king.
- He's finally making
his move, the monster,
who at the age of 15
manipulated the murderous blades
however he pleased.
- Let's see, where
should I be taking this?
To the new Ko
governors, perhaps?
Or maybe to where
Yuushun Tei is waiting?
Or perhaps I should
give it to Eiki?
- [Shosai] I must
say, I'm glad to see
that you're feeling better.
- Wait a minute, you're-
- Let me introduce
myself, I'm Shou Sai.
Head of the merchant's guild
special district of Kinka.
- Sai, than you must be
the son of the mayor.
And you're the leader
of the special district
at such a young age?
- May I point out
that I'm nowhere near
as young as you two.
I'm a little hurt that
you're so surprised.
- I'm sorry, it's
just that I assumed
the other man I met was the
special district leader.
- Nope, this guy
really is the head
of the merchant's
guild of Kinka.
Not only that, but he
has an older twin sister
who's leader of the
provincial branch.
In other words, together,
these two siblings control all
the commerce in Sa province.
- I've heard the
merchant's guild
places great importance
on merit and practicality.
Becoming the leader
at such a young age
shows you must be an
incredibly capable businessman.
- Governor Hong,
the time has come
to fulfill my promise to you.
You have my solemn
word as leader
that the merchants guild
of Kinka will devote 80%
of its strength to
the new governors.
- 80%?
Well, that's a merchant for you.
- It has been a constant
principle of mine
to always keep some
strength in reserve.
In case of emergency.
- Well I certainly don't
dislike that way of thinking.
- Princess is always looking
for ways to save costs.
- Well, then I'm sure
we'll get along just fine.
I'll get in touch
with my elder sister.
We will also provide
you with an ample loan.
Of course, we'll be
claiming due compensation.
- Is that compensation
something we'll be able to pay?
- Our price is that you
help the merchant's guild
better carry out business
in this province.
You can best do that by
bringing order to the land,
driving out the
Sa clan's tyranny
that has become so entrenched,
and governing the
land in a manner
fair to business ventures.
How does that sound,
governor Hong?
- You're extremely
generous to accept payment
long after the fact.
- However, we won't be
giving you any breaks
when we collect.
- I could discuss
this with Eigetsu,
but I'm sure he'd have
the same thoughts as I do.
Ensei?
It appears we're going
to be in serious debt
before we even take office.
Will you help?
- A debt with Shou on your case?
You're gonna have to work
extra hard to pay that one off.
- I look forward to it.
- Then it seems we have a deal.
We'll work out the terms
before leaving for Koren,
if that's acceptable for you.
Governor To is currently
working with my father
getting the disturbances
in town under control.
So we'll begin with just you.
- [Shuurei] Yes.
(soft music)
(sighing)
(string music)
- [Shuurei] Would you
hurry up and go home?
- [Eigetsu] Yes, please
go home Mr. Ryuuren.
- Thank you so much
for bringing the
governor's seal and charm.
Now you can finally
return to your journey.
- Mr. Ryuuren?
Please visit us again
once things have settled
down a little bit.
- But kindred spirit
number one and number two.
- Please, just go home.
We don't want to get
you dragged into this
any further than you
already have been.
(sighing)
(flute playing)
- I was staying so I could get
dragged into things further.
There are only two
people in the world,
kindred spirit number
one and number two,
who have the power to take
advantage of Ryuuren Ran.
(flute playing)
- It was the right
thing to do, right?
(knocking)
Come in.
- Please excuse me.
I brought some tea for you.
- Thank you.
Say, Kourin, mind if
I ask you something?
- Yes?
- I ask only in
an innocent sense.
It's about advisor Enjoun Sa.
What was he to you?
What's that?
- A remembrance of him.
Lord Enjoun was
everything to me.
If it weren't for his sake,
I would have no regrets
even throwing away my own life.
- Is that love though?
- I don't really know.
It's just,
I wanted to exist for his sake.
I had no hesitation dirtying
my hands in sin for him.
So maybe the word love
wouldn't really be suitable
to explain the
things that I felt.
I believed that I
was the one person
who cared the most
about Lord Enjoun,
more than anyone
else in the world.
But I was mistaken.
I can't even begin to
compare with his wife.
- Advisor Sa's wife
that much be Lady
Eiki, I assume.
- Yes.
When I compared my
feelings with hers
they seemed to tiny.
When she first welcomed me to
Sa Provence when I returned,
Lady Eiki told me something
I'd always remember.
- Choosing Enjoun to
adore at such a young age
shows you to a great
judgment in character.
The man I chose is the best
man in all the country,
so I can understand all
too well how you must feel.
However, it must have been hard.
While he may have
been the best man
he was always the worst lover
when it came to the
women in his life.
- Those were the very first
words that Lady Eiki said to me.
- She's a very strong
woman, isn't she?
- Yes.
I think it was that moment
that I realized deep
down in my heart
that to Lord Enjoun, she was
the most important person.
Even though they
lived far apart,
their commitment to each
other never wavered.
- They loved each other
even though they were apart.
I see, there are many different
forms of love, aren't there?
(soft bell music)
- So I take it this
is your true nature
showing itself at last.
What do you want, Lord Sakujun?
- You've been locked
up in this dungeon
for over half a year.
Tell me, how could you not get
bored in there, Yuushun Tei?
- Are you joking?
I would love to be bored
if that were possible.
Unfortunately, there's just
simply too much work to be done.
If you have no business
here, then please leave.
- You're no fun.
- I'm just very busy right now.
(klinking)
Lord Sakujun, what is that?
- What do you think it is?
Hey, Yuushun, isn't it strange?
It's so mysterious because
this simple hairpin
decorated a certain
woman's hair,
it now has exceptional meaning.
I have never felt
this way before now.
- Love, is it?
- Yes, my first
real infatuation.
Spring has come
late into my life.
I'm already in the 29th year
since my birth into this world.
- I don't care to have you
warding off your boredom
by making advances
toward my dear superior.
I suggest that you think
things over quickly
and return that flower
you have in your hand.
- I truly believe that
I must have been blessed
to meet that noble woman and
hear her beautiful Erhu music.
I could very well go
through my entire life
and never again be
able to find a person
who captures my
attention so thoroughly.
Should ever grow
weary of that music
I feel that I would lose
all reason to go on living,
and simply fade away.
They say the prettier that
flower, the higher the branch.
But I will get that
flower, rest assured.
I'll have her no
matter what it takes.
By the way, grandfather
wishes to make use
of your authority as
acting provincial governor.
He wishes to have you seal
off Koren immediately.
- Would you be so kind
as to tell me why?
The new co-governors have yet
to enter Koren city properly.
- Exactly.
- [Yuushun] And if I refuse?
- I'm guessing some bad
things could happen in Koren.
It's all right, Yuushun Tei,
your superiors should still
be able to enter the capital
even after it's been
blockaded, isn't that right?
Until next time.
- [Yuushun] Everything
that needs to be done
has already been set in motion.
There's no reason
for fear and doubt.
It's all just a
matter of time now.
Lord Sakujun.
- To think that my
oldest brother Sojun
would rest in a place
like this all on his own.
It's true that I
was afraid of you.
But I never hated
you, big brother.
The Sa clan is making
a grave mistake.
As a member of the family,
I intend to do as much as I
can to set things right again.
I must stop my big
brother Sakujun.
- [Ryuuki] Second son of
the Sa clan and Shuurei?
- [Kouyuu] That's right.
Lord Reishin send
out a personal letter
to confirm matters regarding
that man's proposal.
There should be no
mistake about it.
- Sakujun Sa?
He's the grandson of advisor
Sa's younger brother Chushou,
if I'm not mistaken.
Rumor has it that he's a
completely hedonistic playboy
who spends all of his
time messing around.
- Impressive, Ran clan.
You're pretty well informed
when it comes to good gossip
on the seven clans of Color.
- Well, Lord Reishin has
already taken action, right?
Is this Sakujun even
still alive after that?
- Yeah.
- Wow, then he must be either
clever, stubborn, or both.
- One thing's for sure,
he's not just some
simple hedonist.
Don't underestimate him.
There may be more disturbances,
much like there
were when advisor Sa
took over the main
branch of the clan.
- All right, as soon as we
get all of this work completed
we need to head to Koren
as quickly as possible.
Huh?
It's Ganlu tea,
don't you remember?
I promised to make
lots of it for you
back at the inn in Sakyou.
- My lady.
- Yes?
- Am I a special
person to you, my lady?
And what about that man?
The man who said he loves you.
Please tell me.
What is he to you?
- That man was like Ryuuki.
- They're not alike.
- You're wrong, they're
very similar in some ways.
They're both adults who
act like they're children.
Yet they're complete opposites.
That's why...
- That's why?
- I guess that it's just that
he leaves a long
lasting impression, huh?
- You haven't once called
him by his real name,
have you my lady?
Is it that you don't
want to acknowledge it?
The fact that he's actually
a member of the Sa clan?
- No, it's not
anything like that.
- It's very unusual for
you to lie to me, my lady.
- Seiran.
- That man is too dangerous.
There's nothing in him
but eternal darkness.
Please, don't get
dragged into that.
And don't let yourself
be deceived by him.
He may say things like he
loves you more than anyone,
but those words are lies.
You haven't tied your hair back.
Did that man say
something to you?
- Aha, just as I thought.
You look much nicer
with your hair down.
- One day you will fall in love.
I know that,
it's something I've been
aware of for a long time now.
- Seiran.
- But if he's the
one you fall for,
you should know that I would
be a much better choice.
Understand, my lady, I
want you to be happy.
I remain by your side
for that purpose alone.
That's why I won't forgive him.
(soft music)
(tense drumming)
You bastard.
You have the guts to
pick a fight with me.
I'll admit you have
some courage to do so
after knowing that
I am prince Seiran.
Sakujun Sa.
(soft music)
- [Sakujun] And as for you,
come to the provincial
capital of Koren.
I'll be waiting for you.
(soft Japanese singing)
- [Shuurei] We need
to hurry to Koren.
We also have to find and free
lieutenant governor Yuushun
Tei, who's being held captive.
Who are you?
What?
You're Junyu, from Koren?