(logo beeping)
(keyboard music)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
(upbeat pop music)
- [Narrator] The
imperial archives,
a building that sits
in a quiet corner
of the Saiee Koku
Palace grounds.
It has absolutely
no connection to the
central government
administration,
and few officials know the
job here since it involves
nothing more than taking
care of dusty books.
- [Shurei] Father!
- Oh, hello Shurei.
- Why don't you join
us for tea father?
This is Mr. Shuei Ran.
You know each other, right?
- Oh why of course we do.
Welcome your maj, I mean Shuei.
- (coughs) Good day
to you too Shoka.
- [Shurei] Now, let us start
preparing the tea, Mr. Shuei.
- [Shoka] Right, I'll
join you as soon as
I finish the work I'm doing.
(gentle flute music)
- [General Han] Hey Seiran.
- General Ran?
- Come here a moment.
(shoes clicking)
- [Shuei] Who's this?
- I'd like you to meet Koyu Li.
He's with the Department
of Civil Affairs,
and he's also an
old friend of mine.
- Who are you calling
your old friend?
An unfortunate acquaintance
is more like it.
- Are you the assistant
secretary of the department,
the youngest ever to pass
the national examinations
at 16 and with top marks, too?
- Way to go Koyu, your
reputation precedes you.
- But don't you usually have
official department business
to do in the mornings?
What are you doing
here in the archives?
(wood snapping)
(Koyu growling)
- (laughs) Actually, we're
both here on official duties
just like you are Seiran.
- You are?
So you mean?
- That's right.
Like you, Koyu and I have
been personally assigned
to serve the king, but I'm
afraid that we haven't had
much to do this whole month.
- You serve as Shurei Hong's
family retainer, do you not?
- Uh, yes.
- Since neither of us have
anything better to do,
we thought we'd come
and watch Consort Hong
and see how your lady
deals with the king.
- [Shurei] Here you are.
Please, enjoy.
(gentle string music)
- It's delicious.
So then, this is how it's
really supposed to taste?
- Oh no, don't tell me
you've been putting up
with that awful daddy tea
all this time. (laughs)
- Daddy tea?
- That's my name for
the awful, bitter tea
that my father always makes.
- I see, but I rather
like Shoka's daddy tea.
- He really is a nice person.
Do you come to the
archives often?
- Yes.
- Even though you're
in the military?
- (coughs) So, you were
serving as the royal consort?
- Oh, you knew about that.
- Yes, I found out from Shusui
when I was at the
royal residence.
- Oh, now I see, but
why were you near
the private imperial quarters?
- Well, that is to say, I--
- Could it be that you had
a message from His Majesty?
- No, uh, that.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Hmm?
(wood chair clacking)
- Please Shoka, come sit
down and have some tea.
Shurei, you're a princess of
the Hong family, aren't you?
Then how did you come to be
so skilled at making sweets?
Also, there's your
(Shurei sighing)
- My hands?
- They so chapped and rough,
not at all like the
hands of a princess.
- Actually, they've
become a lot softer
and nicer since I
entered the royal palace.
My family is very poor.
As a result, I've had
to work hard every day,
and that's why my hands
aren't as fair or smooth
or elegant as the hands
of a normal princess.
But you know, I don't mind.
It's also that the three
of us, my father, Seiran,
and myself can
still live together,
so it's really all right.
- Who's Seiran?
- You may have
met him somewhere.
After all, he was
assigned to His Majesty
in the Left Urian Army.
(gasps) Look at you, dropping
crumbs all over the place.
You're like a child!
- I'm not a child,
I'm 19 years old.
- Oh, is that so?
Then you're the same
age as the king, right?
(playful music)
How many of those did you eat?
- Five or six maybe.
(hand slapping)
- That's too many!
I'll wrap them up for you so
you can take them with you
and have them later.
- (laughs) Shurei really does
sound like a nagging mother,
doesn't she?
- She can.
- Father!
- (laughs) Sorry,
I'm sorry Shurei.
- But it's really
nice like this.
(playful music)
(shoes clicking)
(water gurgling)
- Hmm, wait, that's.
(gentle strings music)
(door creaking)
It seems the rumors were true
about him preferring men.
- My lady, what are you
doing out here so late?
- Oh it's you Seiran, you
frightened me half to death.
- Could it be that you're
unhappy that His Majesty
doesn't come to spend
his nights with you?
- What, don't be ridiculous!
I was just.
- Yes, go on.
- I was just wondering, maybe
that man is really lonely.
That's what I think.
The very first time I met him,
I asked what his name was,
and can you guess what
he answered me with?
He said it was Shuei Ran.
- Isn't that interesting?
- Honestly, running
around the palace
without a government
uniform wearing loose,
luxurious clothes.
He's practically advertising
the fact that he's the king.
- [Shuei] My lady,
what are those books?
- Oh, these books here?
I'm gonna do a little studying.
After all, I came to the
palace with the main purpose
of being a kind of
tutor to the king.
That means I need
to be prepared.
I thought he would be a
stupid and hopeless lord,
but I realized he's
not like that at all.
He is kind of childish for his
age, but on the other hand,
he's not short-tempered
or arrogant.
What's more, he listens
closely to what I have to say.
If he can listen to
what people have to say,
then I think my
words can reach him.
He's nowhere near as
bad as I imagined.
(sighs) Actually, if you ask me,
I think he could become
an excellent king.
- Yes, I think he can, too.
- [Shurei] And that's
why I need to study.
(shoes clicking)
- [Shurei] Advisor Sho.
- [Advisor Sho] Well, if
it isn't Shurei, greetings.
- I have a favor to ask
of you, Advisor Sho.
- [Advisor Sho] What is it?
- Well I wish to do
some more studying,
but simply reading
books is not enough.
My hope was that you could
introduce me to a teacher.
- Oh, I understand you.
Please, leave it to me.
(gentle upbeat music)
- First, let's begin with
the fundamental structure
of the court.
Now Shurei, I heard that
you came to the palace
at Advisor Sho's request.
- I did.
- Then I assume you already
have a basic understanding
of the government.
Can you name the four
ministries and six departments?
- The four ministries are the
Ministry of State Affairs,
the Chancellery,
the Secretariat,
and the Enlightened One's Cave.
The six departments under
the Ministry of State Affairs
are the Departments of
Civil Affairs, Finance,
Protocol, Military,
Justice, and Public Works.
- Wow, you do know quite a lot.
- Actually, to
tell you the truth,
I always wanted to take
the national exams,
so I studied for them
under my father's guidance,
but after I learned that
women can't take the exams,
I decided to pass that
dream on to the children
and taught at the local temple.
- So you were a teacher
before you came to the palace?
- Yes.
- Well then,
if that's the case, then
I imagine there isn't much
left for you to learn.
- Far from it.
In fact, quite the opposite.
I don't believe there
can ever be such a thing
as a limit to learning
and knowledge.
Wouldn't you agree?
(General Ran grunts)
(gentle upbeat music)
(Shurei laughing)
By the way general,
I was wondering.
You're a military
officer, right,
so why are you
giving me lessons?
- Oh, that, that's because.
Ah, he's here at last.
(shoes thumping)
- Huh?
(Koyu breathing heavily)
Lord Koyu?
- Lost your way again.
I was beginning to think that
if you didn't show up soon,
I'd have to step in and
take your place as teacher.
- Just shut up.
- Although you could
say this man is a genius
in many respects, he has
no sense of direction
and tends to get
lost within 30 steps.
- [Shurei] No
sense of direction?
- Stop babbling and shut up!
- Your student has been
waiting patiently for you.
(Koyu grunting)
- [Shurei] Thank
you for helping me.
(books slamming)
- So you were being
serious when you said
you wanted to study for
the sake of this country?
Man, if you compare this
with that stupid king.
- Ah, the stupid king?
- The palace seems large,
but in reality, it's small.
- [General Ran] If it's small,
then why do you get lost?
- Shut up!
What I'm trying to
say is that the king
still doesn't
understand anything yet,
but here is a woman
who's keen to learn
because she's worried
about the country.
- [General Ran] Look,
don't get all worked up
just because the stupid
king doesn't give you
any work to do.
- Excuse me.
- What is it Shurei?
- The stupid king, I
shouldn't say that.
I mean His Majesty, has he
never left the palace grounds?
- [General Ran] I'm not certain,
but it's highly unlikely.
- You on the other hand
are always slipping out
to a certain district
in town to have fun
with the women there.
- Why don't you come with me?
- No thank you!
- [Shurei] A frog in the well
knows not about the ocean.
- [Both] Huh?
- No matter how stupid
the king might be,
if he sees the world outside,
it might arouse his
interest in governing, hmm.
- [Both] Hmm.
(people chatting)
- [Shuei] So your home
is near here Shurei?
- Yes, that's right.
(people chatting)
- Wow, this certainly is a
lively area of town, isn't it?
- There are all kinds of
shops in this district.
Naturally, there
are food stores,
but there are also antiques,
furniture, clothing, books.
You can find anything here.
Ah, mister, I'll
have two please.
- [Man] Here you go.
- Why don't you
try one of these?
- Huh?
(shoes clicking)
(people chatting)
This is good!
- Yeah.
- This is the first
time I've ever eaten
while I was walking.
As experiences go, it's not bad.
(Shurei laughing)
(children laughing)
- Wait for me!
- Come on!
- [Child] Hey wait up guys!
- Hello there, Ms. Shurei.
- Ryushin!
- We haven't seen you lately.
Where've you been?
- Well I've been a bit busy.
- [Girl] Um, Ms.
Shurei, where's Seiran?
- [Boy] And who's the
guy in the fancy dress?
- (gasps) Oh my
goodness, he's right.
- Fancy dress?
You think so?
(playful music)
- Guess it doesn't matter
of you're not Seiran.
Let's play together anyway.
(children giggling)
- Hey, wait.
- Ms. Shurei!
Kinren's in big trouble!
- What?
(gentle flute music)
- A lousy comb like
this costs that much?
Don't screw with me kid!
- But, but that's, that piece
is made from genuine boxwood,
and it's very reasonably priced.
- Huh, that's a lie.
You're just saying
whatever you like.
- You know, a person can
say whatever they like.
- Huh?
- Of course, anyone who
claims that they can't see
the fine craftsmanship in
this piece must be blind.
- Hey, what was that?
- If you continue on
arguing like this,
it's only going to reveal
just how tasteless you are.
Are you okay with that?
- Huh?
(people chatting)
(shoes clicking)
(people laughing)
- Thank you for
saving me, Ms. Shurei.
- Not at all, it was nothing.
More importantly, how
is your mother doing?
- Well, she's been sick in bed
with a cold since this morning.
- So that's why you're taking
care of the shop, right?
Wait a second, I have
the perfect idea.
- Huh?
(frame beeps)
- [Kinren] Thank you Ms. Shurei.
- No problem, just leave
the shop to the two of us
and go look after
your mother, okay?
- Yes ma'am. (laughs)
- Right, let's make some money.
Welcome to our store.
How about buying a hair pin?
Come on, you have
to call out, too.
- Me, you mean
you're asking me to?
- Of course, I don't see
anyone else here, go on.
- Uh, welcome to our store.
- Say it louder.
- Welcome to our store!
(Shurei laughing)
- My, what a good-looking man.
- Welcome, take a look.
How about this hair pin for you?
Do you like it?
- My, that is a very
lovely hair pin.
- I can give you a special
discount on this one.
Perhaps you'd like
to try it on and see?
Why don't you go put
this in her hair Shuei?
(playful flute music)
(woman sighing)
- [Shuei] Like that?
- Wow, it's beautiful!
It really suits you very well.
- (grunts) I think
it suits you, too.
- Oh my, does it really?
- Yes.
(woman giggling)
Well in that case,
I will take one.
- Oh, thank you
very much. (laughs)
(playful music)
(people chatting)
- This is great having
such a good-looking guy
put it in for me.
- Me, too, I wanna be next.
- Oh, please choose one for me.
- Okay now, no pushing
please, no pushing.
Everyone wait your turn.
(women giggling)
(playful music)
- So the king's a shopkeeper.
Punishment for using
my name perhaps.
Hmm, wait a minute,
that's Seiran.
- He is a true bodyguard.
He watches over the
king without being
too close or too far.
- [General Ran] I
can't wait for the day
you finally meet
the king in person.
- [Kuyo] Me neither.
I intend to give him a
piece of my mind when I do.
- We made quite a
lot today, didn't we?
This should take care
of the cost of medicine
for Kinren's mom for a
while, so that's a relief.
Oh, are you tired?
- Not at all.
To be honest, I really
enjoyed myself today.
- I'm so glad to hear that.
I think it's a wonderful
thing helping other people.
- Helping other people.
- [Shurei] This is my home.
(gentle flute music)
- Your family
really is very poor.
- That's not very nice of you.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right, it
is the truth I guess.
(gentle flute music)
- So Shurei, you used to
teach those children, right?
- Yes, that's right, I did.
- You're so energetic,
and you're good at
selling things, too.
(raven cawing)
Are those cherry trees?
- Yes, they are,
but our cherry trees
don't blossom any more.
They haven't for
eight years now.
- Eight years?
- That was when there was the
big struggle for the throne.
After the king collapsed,
the court administration
was thrown into disarray
by the fighting.
Those of us who lived
outside the castle walls
were hit badly in the aftermath.
Many aristocrats
locked their doors,
and the front gates were
littered with the bodies
of people who starved to death.
Father and Seiran did what
they could to help people
get by in those hard
times, but in the end,
there was very little
that we could do for them.
Probably the best help we
could provide was our garden.
We had many fruit trees,
and our pond was large,
so we were able to
share our fruit and fish
with the townspeople.
As a result, there isn't
a single fish in the pond,
and it'll be years before
the trees bear fruit again.
Think about it, not
even the flowers bloom
because we ate everything.
(melancholy music)
Many people died
right before my eyes.
- (sobs) My dear Shurei, would
you please play your Aeru
for the sake of
this child's spirit?
Please play it so he
may rest in peace.
- Day after day,
I played the Aeru
more times than I could count.
It was as if we were
all living only to die.
Why did we have to live only
to experience such hardship?
Father and Seiran got thinner
with each passing day.
I was so scared.
Every night, I had
nightmares of them dying
and leaving me behind all alone.
Those were truly the most
terrible days of all.
- I'm sorry Shurei.
- That's the reason I
entered the imperial palace.
I've had enough of being
unable to do anything
but cry over my
own helplessness.
That's why if it happens again
and there's anything at all
I can do, I want to do it.
What I'm hoping for
isn't really that much.
It's not like I have a
foolish wish or request
such as please build a country
where everyone can live
in perfect happiness.
Being happy or unhappy
is up to the individual,
so the king shouldn't have to
take responsibility for that.
A person's life is one's own.
There are many
options available,
so we should all
choose our own path.
- People choosing
their own paths.
- But there are still times
when a person isn't able
to choose and
doesn't have options.
If it's due to a
natural disaster,
then you have to deal with it,
but problems caused by man
should be preventable, right?
- That's why you
went to the palace?
- You see, there are
some thing people can do
to make life better,
yet there are other
things you can't do
no matter how hard you try,
and that's why
the king's job is,
to take care of such matters,
but who will do that
if the king slacks off?
(gentle music)
I don't know why he
doesn't take care
of his governmental duties,
but since he's already
taken the throne,
they can't really be avoided,
so he'll just have
to do his best.
In exchange, I
intend to do my best
and work together with you.
If you say you've
never studied politics
because you were the youngest
prince and not the heir,
then I'll just study with you.
If you're feeling insecure,
I'll stand by your side.
If you want to
complain, I'll listen,
and if you wanna cry,
then you can just
go ahead and cry.
I'm not an official, so
there's no need to act brave.
I didn't come here
to bear your child
or merely to place
blame and scold you.
The reason I came is
to give you my support.
I'm here to stand by
your side and support you
as you stand up to be king.
Well, that's what I
want to say to the king
when I meet him, but
I haven't been able
to do that yet.
Hey, since you know
the king personally,
would you mind telling him
everything I just said,
and tell him that if
he's interested and
would like to come,
I'll be waiting in the imperial
archives tomorrow afternoon.
(chair clattering)
(clothing rustling)
- All right, I'll pass it on.
- The tea's gotten
cold, hasn't it?
I'll go and make some more.
(water bubbling)
- [Seiran] My lady.
(gentle flute music)
- Hello Seiran.
(gentle music)
(Shurei sobbing)
- You really gave it your best.
Even though eight
years have passed,
just remembering those
days must still be
very painful for you, my lady.
(gentle music)
(Shurei sobbing)
- I'm sorry, I'll
be fine, I'm sure.
- Don't worry, I'm
certain that the king
will come to the
archives tomorrow.
(birds chirping)
(shoes clicking)
- Huh?
- We are known as Ryuki Shi.
We received your message
from a man who knows us well.
- Yes?
(chair clattering)
And what is your reply?
- Let us start
governing this country.
- (gasps) Oh thank you!
(Shurei laughing and gasping)
(gentle strings music)
Can I ask you one question?
- What's that?
- It is true that you
prefer relationships
with men as opposed
to women, right?
- Well, I suppose I do.
- (sighs) That's what I
thought, thank goodness.
Of course, there will be
an issue with successors,
but we can always
worry about that later.
For now, let's study the basics
of governmental administration.
- Huh?
(drum pounding)
- First, let me introduce
you to your new teacher.
- It's an honor to finally
meet you, Your Majesty.
My name is Koyu Li.
Please do your
best, Your Majesty.
- Shuei Ran, what
are you doing here?
- It has always been my
duty to guard Your Majesty.
Besides, I heard that
someone in the archives
has been using my name,
so I've come to see for myself.
(Seiran gasping and laughing)
(books slamming)
- From now on, I'll be
giving you intensive lessons,
so be prepared.
- I'm looking forward to it.
- [Advisor Sho] So the
king has finally taken
an interest in things.
- It seems that bringing
Shurei and her knowledge
of the people into the
palace was a wise decision.
Considering it came from
you, it was a splendid idea.
- You know, you didn't
have to add that first bit.
Now the question is whether
His Majesty will give
Koyu Li and Shuei Ran the
flowers of trust, or not.
(pleasant flute music)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
(gentle guitar music)
(dramatic pop music)
(woman singing in
foreign language)
- I think Ryuki's the
type who can do anything
he puts his mind to.
I've changed my mind
a bit about him.
Don't get ahead of
yourself, I said a bit.
So what are you
doing in my room?
Didn't I tell you not to
get ahead of yourself?