(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
(eerie music)
- [Narrator]
Shurei's group is now
only a short
distance from Korin,
the capital of Sa Province,
where the swearing in ceremony
for the provincial
governess will take place.
Also in that city,
that mysterious man
known as Sakujun Sa
has been awaiting
Shurei's arrival.
(people chattering)
However, with the capital
under a complete blockade,
Shurei and her companions
are stuck on the wrong
side of the town walls.
(people chattering)
(suspenseful music)
- So the whole place is
under total lockdown.
- Yeah.
- But the swearing in
ceremony for the governors
is supposed to be held there.
- And the day after that is
their deadline to arrive.
If they're late for it,
then they're deemed to
abandon their assignment.
Both Princess and Eigetsu
would be dismissed
from their positions
as co-governors.
- Regardless of blockades,
or whatever else they try,
we're gonna enter Korin.
- There are 19 days until
the swearing in ceremony.
That means 20 days
before the deadline.
- Before we get that far,
we'd better make sure
we recover Shurei's
flower bud, right?
- People here are
anticipating a governor
with a flower bud of trust.
To a province that's
been abandoned
by the central
government for so long,
that symbol is crucial.
That's why you must get it
back before the ceremony.
- In any case, the Sa
Clan is an opponent
we'll be able to avoid.
- We'll have to
samba with the Sa.
(gong chimes)
- Well, gee, that food sure
smells delicious, right?
- Yeah, you bet.
- Hey, that was really funny,
don't you think, huh, huh?
- Regardless of what
might come afterward,
our first priority is clear.
We must get past
that blocked gate.
- But before that, let's have
a little something to eat.
(eerie music)
- [Narrator] Meanwhile,
there is another person
who is on his way to Korin City.
The youngest son of the
Sa clan, Kokujun Sa.
With a mere handful of courage,
he's trying to create a path
towards a brighter future
for someone he loves.
(gentle music)
(boys snoring)
- Miss Shunki, what's wrong?
Need to use the bathroom?
Huh?
Ah!
Here you go, Miss Shunki.
- [Chouka] The man known
as Hokuto has always been
a treasured and
irreplaceable friend to me.
- Lord Chouka, please
allow me to pour the tea.
- It's all right,
Shusui, please.
Have a seat and relax.
Despite our close friendship,
Hokuto only wrote a
letter to me once.
It said, "Don't bother to visit,
"I'll come to see you someday."
I waited a long time for
that day to come, but...
- In the end, he
passed away quietly,
while his children
were watching over him.
- If you had known that
man many years ago,
the last thing you'd ever expect
would be a quiet death for him.
As members of the
Wolves of the Wind,
we entrusted our
lives to each other.
It was all a part of walking
the path of darkness together.
I'm glad that in the end,
he was able to leave
this world peacefully.
- I understand he
left two sons behind.
Were you the one who looked
after them, Lord Chouka?
- To be honest, Hokuto had
done such a magnificent job
of raising them that there
wasn't much I needed to do
when it came down to it.
They're sons of the Bald
Eagle of Sa Province.
One day, they'll soar
majestically in the sky.
- Yes, definitely.
(both sipping)
- Shusui, what's wrong?
Is the tea too bitter for you?
- No, actually it's very tasty.
- It's a really good
thing that our father
taught us how to read
and write and stuff.
- Yeah, thanks to
him helping us,
we're able to talk with
Miss Shunki like this.
- [Both] Huh?
- Starting this moment--
- I'm heading down the mountain.
- Youshun.
- Yes, big brother.
- You idiot, call
me boss, remember?
Now you know what it is
you're supposed to do, right?
- Yes, of course.
I've gotta get packing.
- Right, we hereby declare
our official revival
as the next generation
Bald Eagles of Sa Province.
- Wow, you sound
totally awesome, boss.
I'll pack some freshly
picked autumn fruit.
That'll sure keep us going.
- Okay, let's continue
what our father began.
The second generation of the
chivalrous thieves begins here.
- Yeah, and I'll write
everything down in my leaf diary
so that we'll never
end up forgetting it.
- Yeah!
(tender music)
What is it, Miss Shunki?
(gentle music)
No way, a journey is
all about the company.
Now you'd better
use the bathroom
before we leave, Miss Shunki.
Don't worry, there's no
need to be embarrassed.
(Eigetsu munching)
- This is delicious,
thanks Shurei.
- Yeah, it has a good
flavor, doesn't it?
- Hey Seiran, isn't your piece
a little bigger than mine?
- It is utterly
depressing to think
that you're the former governor.
But, putting that aside
from the time being,
what should we do?
If only Lord Ryuuren
Ran were still here,
things would be much
simpler for us right now.
- [Ensei] Because of the Ran
Clan crest, the twin dragons?
- [Shou] Right!
With that, all it would take
is saying have a
look at this token,
and we'd all pass through the
gate without being inspected.
But--
- He's not here,
so it's not an option.
- Yes, that's right.
- So what will you do?
How do you propose
we enter Korin?
- Well, why don't we
just walk right up
to the front gate and pass
on through, simple as that.
- [Shou] I'm sure I already
informed you earlier
that even the gate
guards have been replaced
with members of the Sa
Clan's private army.
- Yes, but that's
illegal, right?
Seiran can use his
authority to arrest them,
and once we push
them off to the side,
there won't be
anything to stop us
from walking through that gate.
So, do you have any
problems with that?
- I understand.
No problem.
- As for the situation
with my flower bud,
I'm sure that guy
will find a way
to approach us when
we enter Korin.
- [Eigetsu] Well, then I guess
all that's left to
do now is sleep.
- That's right, Eigetsu.
Good food, and a good night's
sleep are always necessary.
All right then, I'll
get to bed first.
Remember to put out the
fire before you go to sleep.
- Goodnight.
- Hey Shou, our bosses are
incredible, don't you think?
They're the best.
- Indeed, it seems
they'll become governors
who won't settle for taking a
back seat to the previous one.
- Hmm.
(intense music)
- At this rate, we'll
reach the goal of Kinka
before we even know it.
- Of course we will, we're the
Bald Eagles of Sa Province.
Mountains like this are a
piece of cake, right boss?
- [Shourin] You got it!
(both panting)
Miss Shunki, hold on to
me as tight as you can!
- [Both] Let's go!
(both grunting)
(air whooshing)
(people grumbling)
- It really is completely
blocked, isn't it?
- Yes, but we've gotta get
through, no matter what.
(horse whinnies)
(people grumbling)
- What's that?
- Well, shall we do it?
- Yep.
(intense music)
- Checkpoint breakers!
(men grunting)
- Okay then, let's get
this stamped already.
- Hey Ensei, you seem awfully
used to this kind of thing.
- You're pretty
experienced, huh?
(Ensei chuckles)
- Experienced in breaking
through checkpoints?
You're the governor's
aide, for crying out loud.
- Oh, hey Shou, can you
ride a horse by any chance?
- [Shou] Yes, I can manage.
- I don't suppose we could go
over to your sister's house?
Actually, there's
nowhere else we can go,
so we may as well
head over there.
(horse snorts)
(hooves clopping)
(all grunting)
- Wait a minute, why
are we on horses now?
(gentle music)
(horses whinnying)
(Shurei sighs)
- It must have been
tough for you, my lady.
Not only did you have no saddle,
but we were going a little fast.
- You call that a little?
My butt's hurting like crazy.
(gentle music)
What is this place?
- It's Mr. Sai's sister's house.
The residence of Lady Rin Sai.
- Mr. Shou Sai's older sister?
The garden and house
aren't exactly flashy,
but they definitely have a
very fashionable air to them.
I can see that she's a
person of excellent taste.
- Well, come on in.
I'm sure my sister has
already planned ahead
and left a letter or two for us.
(hooves clopping)
(gentle music)
- To the two honorable
new governors.
- Just like you said,
a letter for us.
But how'd she know
we'd be coming here?
- One of the skills necessary
for becoming a merchant
is the ability to correctly
predict the future.
Like assistant Ro said earlier,
this is the only place
where we could go.
- Hey, it's no fluke that
your sister happens to be
provincial leader of
the Merchant's Guild.
- What about the other letter?
- Right.
(gentle music)
(Shurei gasps)
- What is it, Shurei?
- This is an invitation
from the Sa Clan.
(all gasp)
Wait a minute, why don't we
look at the other letter first?
- Sure.
It says the Sa Clan
has been causing
numerous disruptions
within Sa Province.
- Since the Sa Clan
has a tight grip
on even the Merchant's Guild,
the guild will only be able
to provide us with
minimal assistance.
- So, what do you
intend to do now?
Please don't forget that
depending on your strategy,
the future actions and support
of the Merchant's
Guild may be affected.
- Whoa, you really
are merciless.
- Since you and Officer Shi
enjoy being soft on them,
it's necessary for me
to balance things out.
- All right, Eigetsu.
I think this is a situation
where we should use
the governor seal.
- Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
The Merchant's Guild
has agreed to provide us
with at least minimal
assistance, right?
- Yes, if at all possible.
- Please send the following
reply to Miss Rin Sai,
leader of the Sa Province
branch of the Merchant's Guild.
We hereby request immediate
military assistance
from all soldiers affiliated
with the Merchant's
Guild of Sa Province.
Soldiers are to take action
and control all civil conflicts
that have arisen,
as well as protect
all mayors and senior officials
who will be present at
the swearing in ceremony
of the new governors.
The above request for
assistance is made
in the names of the new
governors of Sa Province,
Eigetsu To, and Shurei Hong.
However, there
shall be no reward.
We do not intend to buy your
conscience with money or goods.
- This is a request,
not a direct order.
You shall make your own judgment
on whether or not you accept.
- [Shurei] We ask
that you provide us
with a reply as
soon as possible.
- From the governor of
Sa Province, Eigetsu To.
- And the governor of Sa
Province, Shurei Hong.
- I'm afraid it's
missing something.
- What do you mean?
- Lieutenant Governor of
Sa Province, Ensei Ro, and?
- Military officer of
his majesty, Seiran Shi.
(both sigh)
- You have no intention
of buying her conscience
with money, or goods.
Well, that's splendid.
I'll deliver the letter to my
sister as soon as possible.
- No matter how you look at it,
the Sa Provincial Army on
our side won't be enough.
Luckily for us, the
soldiers and mercenaries
of the Merchant's
Guild are talented,
and have good leadership.
- But you know, most people
would normally be too afraid
to request assistance
from the Merchant's Guild
without offering
any compensation.
Luckily, our princess
isn't most people.
- I humbly request
you deliver this.
- Very well, I
accept your request.
Now are you going to
keep us in suspense,
or are you going to
open the other letter?
(plucky music)
- This is bad.
It feels like a
cursed invitation.
- It does kinda give
me a bad feeling,
but we have no choice.
We still have to open it.
- Ah!
- Way to go, women are brave!
- Let me see, "We hereby
make this announcement
"that all members of
the clan will assemble
"to officially select
the clan's leader,
"followed by the Sa Clan
appointment ceremony.
"As such, we humbly
request the attendance
"of the two new governors
"to partake in this
glorious occasion,
"as well as to
formally acknowledge
"the new head of the clan.
"We look forward to
seeing you there."
- In other words, a trap.
- [Shou] Yeah, in a nutshell
they're saying, now come to me.
- In any event, the timing
for this trap of theirs
couldn't possibly be worse.
(Shurei sighs)
- Isn't this another
one of those situations
where we just have
to tackle it head on?
- They have got to be joking.
It's on the day before
our swearing in ceremony?
- [Shou] Then will
you turn him down?
- No, of course
we're going to go!
I have to get back that flower
bud that was taken from me,
and there's Mr. Kokujun as well.
- [Ensei] They must know that.
You could call it a
flowered invitation,
with the bud as bait.
- He sent you this
letter knowing very well
that you wouldn't be
able to turn it down.
- That's why I'm so mad!
(dog howls)
(water trickling)
- Mr. Shou Sai, were you able
to find what I asked for?
- You should know by
now that there's nothing
the Merchant's Guild cannot get.
Here's the item, as promised.
(eerie music)
- Yes indeed, thank you
for procuring it for me.
- It's amazing how you're
so knowledgeable in poisons.
I admit I was stunned
that you'd know so much
about those things
that spread secretly
through the underground
of common life.
- My knowledge is not
something that concerns you.
It's not as if I learned
about these things
because I wanted to.
- You intend to take it
upon yourself to use that?
- You're very nosy, at least
as far as merchants go.
- [Shou] Look, I'm just
saying you're overdoing it
for a military officer.
- It's a little
different for me.
I am the person to
whom his majesty
bestowed the sword Kanshou.
That means I am obligated
to protect the governors
from any and all dangers.
Besides, Ensei can't do this.
He's a man who's always
walking in the sun.
The tentacles of
darkness will never
be able to wrap
themselves around him.
He will never be
bothered by dark nights.
That's why Sakujun Sa is not
an appropriate opponent for him.
- [Shou] And you're different?
- That's right, in fact I'm
the exact opposite of Ensei.
I know how to handle those
kinds of dark-hearted men
better than anyone else can.
I know how to deal
with an opponent
who I can't kill,
or leave alive.
I know, because I
was once like that.
I was the troublesome
second prince
who could neither be
killed, nor be left alive.
- You're the real
king, aren't you?
(wind whistling)
You see, you speak in
the manner of someone
who walks the path
of a conqueror.
Are you trying to say
that light and darkness
have nothing to do
with hope or despair,
but instead are merely
part of the tactics you use
for the purpose of
achieving your goals?
I believe I might
have said too much.
Forgive my curiosity,
I shall continue to
deliver the requested
information potions to you
as soon as I receive them.
- Thank you very much, Mr. Sai.
(eerie music)
Darkness or the light,
I'll take advantage
of anything I can use.
- Seiran, Seiran!
- [Seiran] In order to protect
what I ought to be protecting.
- Grandfather,
stop this already.
It's not too late to
undo your mistakes.
We've committed so many crimes.
We have to stop,
we have to atone
for the sins of the Sa Clan.
Of course, I will bear that
responsibility as well.
- You are a disgrace
who has no pride
in being part of this clan.
- You've forgotten
about honesty,
righteousness, and reason.
Your desires have blinded you
to how soiled you've become.
That's the disgrace.
You can show your true
pride in the Sa Clan
by putting a stop to this
before you fall even
deeper into the darkness.
We must return to
the correct path.
- Pride in the Sa Clan, you say?
How dare you talk
like you know it all!
(ominous music)
- Grandfather!
- Don't take that tone
of voice with me, boy.
Meeting with you on a
whim was a total mistake.
I should have thrown
you in the same place
as that foolish man
right from the start.
- What?
- Yes, the same place
I put your father.
- Father?
But I thought you said
Father was recuperating
from an illness
in a far off place
where he could get better!
Are you saying that was a lie?
- That's what makes
you foolish and naive.
But that man is currently
sitting in his prison,
not even aware of
who he is any longer.
- But that's, how can
you be so heartless,
Grandfather Chuushou?
- I'll let you out for
the selection ceremony.
Take him away.
- [Kokujun] Grandfather!
- For far too many years,
you've admired my
elder brother, Enjun.
Know this, even if you do
have intentions of leading,
I will inherit that position
from my brother first.
- What?
What are you planning
to do, Grandfather?
No, Grandfather!
- [Man] Come on!
(somber music)
- [Shou] Eiki, if you wish it,
I could free you from
this prison right now.
- Shou, the great arrogance
snob adviser, Shou.
Why would an old man like you
come here looking like that?
You're a sly fox in
a young man's skin.
I would never accept
any help of yours.
I have one question.
Tell me, where is the ring
belonging to the
head of the Sa Clan?
The one you stole a
year and a half ago?
- I stole?
It won't be long before
the ring returns here.
- Is that right?
Well then, I have nothing
further to say to you.
You may leave, get
out of my sight.
- Eiki.
- It would be a simple
matter for me to leave here,
take over, and smack those
fools into utter submission,
but then what would happen
after I leave this
world for good?
Old people like me
should stick to giving
whatever knowledge is requested,
and providing
guidance to the young.
That's why I'm still
sitting here waiting.
Right now, I am in the
middle of surmounting
one of the most significant
challenges of my life.
- What are the odds?
- That's why men are useless.
They waste all their
time and energy
worrying about such things, ha.
(shrill flute music)
(crickets chirping)
- Maybe we were going too fast.
- Let's rest a bit.
Are you all right, Miss Shunki?
(shrill flute music)
- Shunki?
Huh.
You, boys and girl over there.
You young children
who are few in years,
where are you going?
(all sigh)
- Well, Kinka, and after
that, we're headed to Korin.
- Wow, he's cool.
- [Man] If that's the case,
you shall accept my charity.
(crickets chirping)
You don't need to thank me.
I wish you happiness
on your journey.
Now as a farewell gift,
I will play a tune
that just came to
me this moment.
(shrill flute music)
- So as long as
we have this token
that super cool guy gave us,
we'll be able to enter Korin
without having to
go through Kinka.
- Great.
- But what about
what Ensei told us?
He said that before
we get to Korin,
we had to talk with an
important man in Kinka.
- Why don't I run
to Kinka on my own?
- Great idea, then I'll go
ahead to Korin with Miss Shunki.
- [Both] Let's go!
(Shourin panting)
- Listen, Shunki.
This is a promise between
you and your grandmother.
Use your power only for
the sake of the person
most important to you.
Until then, I shall
seal your voice.
(somber music)
- [Shurei] I'm coming,
you just wait for me.
(singing in foreign language)
We've entered Korin at last.
I'm going straight to the place
where that guy from
the Sa Clan is.
I'll find Lady Eiki and
the others, and wait,
what are you doing here?
Huh, you've come to get me?