(techno sound)
("Hajimari no Kaze"
Japanese theme song plays)
(stringed instrument music)
- [Narrator] Shurei Hong,
who has been assigned
to the post of co-governor
of Sa Province,
is currently en route to
the place of her assignment.
But at the moment, she
is faced with a serious,
but familiar problem that
could have a profound
effect on her future
and her dreams.
- He said I'm marrying
a son of the Sa clan?
(Instrumental music)
- What's the matter, Korin?
Your music sounds distracted.
- You can tell?
- I feel like having
some fruit now.
- Okay, I'll bring some.
(Instrumental music)
- Are you worrying
about the governor's
marriage into the Sa clan?
- I was just thinking,
I'd heard she's around my age.
But it's political, right?
- Those happen quite often.
- That's true, but this
entire marriage business
seems far too rushed and
forceful for my taste.
Not only have they
not asked her,
they haven't even sought
her family's consent.
- That's because she's
the most cherished lady
of the Hong clan.
If approached directly,
the Hong clan would not
choose to deal with the Sa clan.
- [Shurei] She's
a cherished lady?
- [Sakujun] They think only
members of the royal family
of the Ran clan would
be a worthy match.
Given their extreme
pride, the Hong clan
wouldn't even consider
a Sa proposal.
Getting acceptance
after the fact
is the only way the Sa
clan would have a chance.
- The Hong family name
really does have value.
- [Sakujun] And of course,
even the Hong clan isn't likely
to demand her return after
she's done that with someone.
According to rumors, that
noble woman is very beautiful,
proud, and lady-like.
She's said to be, very
much, the high-born lady,
so if something like
that were to happen,
they would surely give in.
No one would take
her in marriage,
even if she did return.
- Wow, a high-born lady, huh?
True, in a way.
Korin is pretending
to be me right now,
and she's much more well-bred
and lady-like than I am.
- But I prefer you, much
more than some haughty
and high-born lady
of the Hong clan.
- Uh, thank you very
much, Young Master.
- May I ask you?
- [Shurei] Yes?
- What are your defending
yourself against so strongly?
- Um...
- [Sakujun] You always seem
very timid when it comes
to falling in love.
If I try to get closer
to you, you pretend
you don't notice, and
hide your heart away
behind strong armor.
That's why you insist
on continuing to call me
Young Master, isn't it?
Were you rejected by
some cruel man, perhaps?
- No, it's--
it's just...
- [Man] Please don't forget.
Don't forget that
I love you, Shurei.
- I'm just not prepared for it.
- Why do you say that?
- Right now, I have
too much going on
to devote my heart to love.
- [Sakujun] Are you
afraid of falling in love?
- To be honest, I am, a little.
- We are very similar
then, I am also afraid.
- You're what?
But Young Master, you go
around making advances
towards every beautiful
young woman you ever see.
- I can do it, because
it's just a game, but if
I should find that
someone special,
I will no longer be
able to hesitate.
Korin, will you play your
ehru for me again, please?
- Sure.
- [Man] The Little
Whirlwind, it's been such
a long time since we last met.
Back then, I really
liked how you could kill
so coldly and calmly with
that pretty face of yours.
Do you have any
idea how proud I was
to have you all to myself?
- Seems you haven't
changed a bit
over the years, old Meishou.
Now, quit being such
an idiot, and scram.
You're nothing but an
eyesore, one I might kill.
- Oh, how low the
son of a wealthy
merchant family has fallen.
Now, you're a common thug.
- Even though I was only a kid,
I never forgot the face of
the guy who came to our home,
claiming to be a famous painter.
It was your face, bastard!
(dramatic music)
(footsteps)
- [Meishou] Our old leader's
one and only mistake in life
was deciding, on a
whim, not to kill you,
when we broke in to your house.
And all because one
child was spared,
the Murderous Blades
were wiped out.
- You know my one
and only mistake?
It was that I didn't chase
you to the ends of the Earth,
and the depths of
Hell, and kill you
after you escaped.
Go ahead and state
your business here,
I wouldn't mind
getting that over with,
and finishing things
off, right now, you know.
- Oh, I just came to
see your faces today.
Listen, unlike
our previous boss,
I use what I have up here.
Why don't you come to
Kinka, and see for yourself?
You'll understand
what I mean then.
- Be sure to have a grave and
casket ready for yourself.
Unlike a certain
someone, I'm a nice guy,
but I'm not so kind and helpful
as to prepare those for you.
- I'll see that
they're prepared.
However, they'll be for you.
Because unlike a
certain someone,
I'm considerate.
- [Seiran] Geez. What a
rotten guy to run into.
Let's go.
I'll even treat you
to a cup of Ganlu tea.
- I'll let you treat me
to anything but Ganlu tea.
- Hey, why is the--
Oh, of course. I get it.
Ganlu tea is something
you'd rather have
Princess make for you.
- I would just prefer to
save the best for last.
That's all it is.
- Yeah, well, I don't
leave things for later.
I like to go right after it.
- I have no doubt.
(stringed instrument music)
- Korin, I have a question.
- Yes.
- We'll be reaching Kinka soon.
Once we get there, I was
wondering if you would
tell me your real name?
Don't look so surprised.
The name, Korin,
doesn't suit you.
It's too cute.
- Oh, well, jeeze.
I'm so sorry for, apparently,
not being cute enough.
- A more dignified name
would suit you better.
(light stringed music)
- Young Master!
- [Sakujun] Korin.
Good night and
sleep well, Korin.
- When I get to Kinka, I'll
be able to see everyone.
I just have to endure
this a little longer.
(wheels turning on ground)
- [Kokujun] We'll be in
Kinka soon, won't we?
I asked you to help me
with my studies en route,
but I seem to be struggling.
I'm so sorry.
If that wasn't bad enough,
I'm a lot older than you.
- Are you hoping to
become an official
some day, Mr. Kokojun?
- It's sort of been
a dream of mine
that I might pass the
national examinations one day,
and become like
great uncle Enjun.
I figured that if I
could have the boy
who passed his Jougen at age
13 assist me with my studies,
it might help me out a bit.
And give me an edge.
I'm sorry for asking such
a strange favor of you.
- Not at all, but, uh--
Great-uncle Enjun, you say?
Are you talking
about Advisor Sa,
who passed away recently?
- Yes, that's right.
Great-uncle was an
incredible person.
He's what you would
call a genius.
Great-uncle was the
pride of the Sa clan,
and I've always admired him.
- But you've already
studied quite a lot,
haven't you?
You seem to have a
good understanding
of all the important
fundamentals.
- Only because I've
been doing it for years.
But, I'm nothing in comparison
with your knowledge.
- [Eigetsu] You do have a point.
You're not a genius after all.
- Eigetsu, how could you!
- No, it's fine. He's
only telling the truth.
- But, the thing is,
I'm not a genius either.
- Nonsense, if anyone
is a genius, you are.
(carriage rattles)
- [Eigetsu] I studied
with all of my heart.
I didn't have any time or money,
so last winter's exam
was gonna be my first
and final attempt at passing it.
I sometimes had trouble
absorbing what I was studying.
So I took my time.
I memorized material
by transcribing it,
over and over, until
I was satisfied.
I didn't wanna waste
money on paper,
so in the wintertime,
I'd write in the temple
gardens with a stick.
During other seasons,
I'd write on the path
between rice fields
until I could write
everything from memory.
But I still lacked confidence.
I had to put in
that much work just
in order to pass.
So then, am I really a genius?
- I'm sorry.
I really am pathetic, aren't I?
And I'm almost 18 years old.
- [Eigetsu] Please
don't apologize.
I'm not saying you're
to blame or anything.
It may have sounded
impertinent before but,
I just wanted you
to realize that
even if you're not a genius,
there are ways to
make up for it.
- [Sojun] What?!
Kill the two kids?
- [Meishou] Yes. It's an order
from the person who hired us.
- Weren't we gonna make
that girl from the Hong clan
in to Sakujun's
wife or something?
- Apparently, that girl
is actually a fake.
- A fake?!
You're tryna tell me
that some ordinary girl
made a total fool out of me?!
I won't forgive them!
I'm gonna kill those brats
with my own two hands!
- Do whatever you
wish with them.
But I'm afraid it appears
you're going to have to
wait a bit before that.
First, we're going to
put them both to good use
before killing them.
- Good use?
- Nevermind that for now.
Something interesting has
come in to our possession.
- Huh?
- Turn that flat rock over
and take a close look.
- What! It's the
governor's seal!
- The other one's a
part of the charm.
I'm having my men search for
the rest of the pieces now.
The seal fragment was
found inside a steam bun.
The charm piece was stuck
to a gold chamber pot
as decoration.
- [Sojun] A chamber pot?
- I doubt they ever expected
us to break open every
single steam bun
that came to Kinka.
- Then as long as
we have these...
- [Meishou] We have no
need for the governors.
All we need to do now is sit
and wait for their arrival.
- Yeah.
But, in that case,
where did the real girl
from the Hong clan get to?
- Don't worry about her,
she'll come here on her own.
To recover the seal and charm,
if nothing else.
Now, all that remains
is the preparation
of a room for her wedding
night with Lord Sakujun.
- But where is that
idiot Sakujun anyway?
- [Meishou] He says
he's too afraid to stay
with the Murderous Blades.
So we've already arranged
for a separate residence
for him.
- Dammit, you'd never imagine
he was my younger brother,
he's such a coward!
But never mind.
You know something, Meishou?
Why don't you work for me,
instead of grandfather?
- Oh? Are you planning to
push Lord Chusho aside?
- [Sojun] How about it?
- I'll consider it,
and the prospects
it holds for the future.
- Go on, take a look.
We've reached the city of Kinka.
- So this is it.
We're finally here.
(crowd murmurs)
- [Sakujun] What's the matter?
- Isn't this supposed to
be the center for commerce
in Sa province?
- Yes, that's right.
- [Shurei] Something's
wrong here...
Why does this town
feel so lifeless?
- [Sakujun] What
will you do now?
We've reached Kinka as promised.
Would you like to come with
me to where I'll be staying?
- [Shurei] No, I have a
number of places I need to go.
When I'm finished
with my business,
I'll come to say my goodbyes.
What inn will you be staying at?
- Actually, I won't be
staying at any of the inns -
my family has a residence here.
Just ask anyone where the
Chrysanthemum Residence is,
and they'll direct you.
- Yes, very well.
- Korin.
- Yes, what is it?
- Oh nothing.
It's just that I'd
feel much better
if you wouldn't be
so cold toward me.
- Young Master! You haven't
even apologized to me.
- I won't apologize,
because frankly I don't believe
I've done anything wrong.
- I wonder why--
why does seeing this
man remind me of Ryuuki.
Is it an accidental resemblance?
No... They're not at all alike.
You said the Chrysanthemum
Residence, right?
I should be able to
come by within the day.
- I'll be waiting for you.
- Till then.
- I'll be waiting for you...
- They've got seriously ill
bred thugs on patrol here.
They're obviously not
protecting the town.
They're just making the
entire atmosphere worse.
On top of that, they're
out in such numbers.
It feels like we're
all being watched.
Ah, thank goodness.
I finally arrived.
They're not the Kinka
Merchant's Guild for nothing.
This place is huge!
Hm? On the other hand, it's
very quiet around here.
Something's not right.
I should gather some
information first.
Ah! Oh dear, I'm so sorry.
- Pardon me young lady,
might you be a
visitor to the town?
- Huh?
- Is this your
first time in Kinka?
Are you here looking for
work in the Merchant's Guild?
- Ah, well, I, um--
He's wearing some
pretty unusual items,
that the average person
would have trouble getting.
Are you associated with
the Merchant's Guild?
- My my, you're very
perceptive indeed.
Likewise, I noticed that you
carry a special token with you.
It bears the luminous
seven color paint.
- Who are you, and
how do you know that?
- The situation is grim.
The Murderous Blades have
taken complete control
of the Merchant's
capitol of Kinka.
- So is this man the Kinka
Special District Leader
of the Merchant's Guild?
- By the way, just so you know,
the Guild hall we
were at has been
a den of thieves for some time.
- What do you mean?
(men yelling)
- [Man] A few months ago,
the Murderous Blades suddenly
came to town en masse.
They were most ingenious.
Even though they forced
their way in to town,
they made a point not to
go looting and burning.
Meishou,
the man who called
himself their leader,
made a formal declaration
to the people:
if they would accept him openly,
then his men would do no harm.
- And the mayor of
Kinka was willing
to agree to those conditions?
- He made a decision to put
the peoples lives first.
- The Murderous Blades
have not been reckless
in their command.
However, they made certain
everyone was clear about
who was in control.
On top of that, they've
been increasingly putting
psychological pressure
on the townspeople.
- They've locked up the mayor
and have assigned their
men to patrol the town.
They've also hinted they
may have the backing of
the Sa clan.
- The Sa?
- Merchant's were drawn
in by the prospect of
being associated
with the Sa clan,
and one after another
began to support them.
On the surface, the
Merchant's Guild does as well.
- It's only natural;
we're merchants.
We never stop calculating and
weighing profits and losses.
Depending on the circumstances,
we'll become anyone's ally.
- This is it! The
moment of reckoning.
It's my first job as governor.
I have to get the Merchant's
Guild on our side,
no matter what.
If I can't do that,
we'll have no chance when
facing the Murderous Blades,
or the Sa clan!
Please state your
conditions for assisting me.
What will I need to do
in order to get you to
mobilize the mercenaries
of the Merchant's Guild?
- In that case,
please show us the cards
you have in your hand.
After taking in to
consideration both your cards,
and our conditions,
if we determine that
you have an 80% chance
of success, than you will
have the support of the guild.
However, you should first
know that according to
our sources, the Murderous
Blades have already managed to
obtain the seal and
charm of the governor.
As such,
those two things will be of
no use in these negotiations.
- What you're saying
is not possible.
They're fakes!
- What makes you say
they must be fakes?
- Truthfully?
- [Man] The governors seal
and charm should arrive in
Kinka at about the
same time as you do.
Even without more information,
you'll know them the
instant you see them.
I will leave them
somewhere very safe,
where there's no
chance that anyone will
be able to steal them.
- [Shurei] That's what his
majesty, the King said.
I think we can believe his word.
- So where exactly are
the seal and charm then?
- Well, uh...
I don't know yet.
- What?
- [Shurei] I'll find
them without fail.
- I don't know.
If it were solely up to us,
we would never
use such a foolish
and irresponsible
method ourselves.
- But how do you
intend to find them?
- So, this must be
the town of Kinka.
- Uh, show us your
pass token, sir.
- My pass token? Oh
right, of course.
Let's see, where did I put it?
- Hey! You're holding
up the line! Hurry up!
- This is a new
experience for me.
I've never been told to hurry
up before in my entire life.
(crowd gasps)
Now that you mention it,
it could be fun to have
to hurry up for once!
Ah-ha! So that's where it was.
- [Guard] Come on. Honestly,
causing so much trouble.
The twin dragons!?
My lord! Then you're a
member of the Ran clan?
- Now to play a melody to
celebrate my arrival in Kinka.
(off tune flute plays)
- Argh! That awful flute music!
- Only one man plays like this!
He must be Lord Ryuren Ran!
Ugh!
- I will find the
governor's seal and charm
before the end of the day.
Furthermore, Lt. Governor
Ensei Ro is coming.
He's traveling with Seiran Si,
the officer assigned
to the governors.
He wields a precious sword
given by his majesty himself,
and he has a higher
rank than even
the general of Sa province.
They're both on their way,
along with the other
governor, Eigetsu To.
All of them will be
arriving in Kinka shortly.
- Well now, that's
all very interesting,
but are those all the
cards you currently have
up your sleeve?
- [Shurei] No.
I can't lose, no matter what.
If I lose here, we
don't stand a chance.
I'll do whatever it
takes to win this fight!
The last card I have...
Is my own life!
If it should come to that,
I'm willing to offer my own
life as a bargaining chip.
- Your meaning?
- Losing my life here
in Sa province would be
a grave insult to
the entire Hong clan.
The Sa clan can
not kill a lady of
the direct line
of the Hong clan.
The backlash would
be too severe,
they can't afford that.
And that's why my life...
Is valuable.
- There is no guaranteeing
your final card.
We won't really know how
the Hong clan will react
until that time actually comes.
- But sir!
- We will give you
our conditions now.
Get rid of the leader
of the Murderous Blades,
as well as taking care of
all his senior officers.
If you promise you can do that,
then I in turn will promise
to send our elite troops
to join you and assist you.
I can see the value in that
strong spirit of yours.
- Thank you, sir.
- Governor Hong.
- Yes?
- Can you promise that
you will not betray
the hopes of the
people of Sa province?
- Yes.
- At last! We finally
reached Kinka!
- I know.
(all in wagon yell)
Mr. Kokujun?
- [Man's Voice]
We've been waiting!
- Welcome to humble
Kinka city, Governor To.
And of course, welcome to the
young lady imposter as well.
- Shall we arrange a room for
you at the inn for the night?
- No, thank you. It's
all been taken care of.
I'll be staying at the
residence of the son
of the Rin family.
Huh? Um, is something wrong?
- A few days ago the entire
Rin family was slaughtered
by the Murderous Blades.
As far as we can tell,
there were no survivors.
- But how can that--
how can that be?
Then, who is that man?
Who in the world--
could he be?
(Japanese ending theme)
- [Shurei] I finally
reached Kinka,
where I promised to meet
up with Reiran, Ensei,
Korin, and Eigetsu.
But what's worrying me most
is Senya Rin's identity.
Could it be that I was
traveling with someone
very dangerous?