(intro music)
- You never called
me by my real name
not even once.
I love you, the way you
play with your hair,
the way you always
make tea for me.
Everything about you.
(gasps)
(cries)
(barking)
- [Narrator] The days
pass by, and soon
Autumn was about to end.
However, for Shurei and Eigetsu,
the brand new Governors
of Sa Province,
their duties and
responsibilities
had only just begun.
- Hmm
Its just as we thought, there
isn't much to work with.
I can finally understand why
Sa Province was abandoned
by the central government
for such a long time.
How's the crop situation?
- Not too good, most
of the land is barren.
- On top of that, because
the Sa Clans strangle hold
lasted so long,
relations with other
provinces are non-existent.
- And since this
province is isolated,
peddlers and traders
don't come here.
- Well, what about
the mountains?
Maybe there's some iron
ore, or even gold or silver.
- [Shurei] There all kinds
of places that haven't
checked out for
things like that yet.
But if we're basing our
infrastructure off an industry,
we need to pick something
like agriculture.
Something that'll
produce goods every year
and will still be around
100 years from now.
- 100 years from now?
Really?
- Yep, that's right.
That's why we've gotta
think hard about it.
(Windows opening)
- [Eigetsu] Wow, the morning
sky is really beautiful
isn't it?
- No, now that I think about it,
they still haven't
found the Sturioran.
- You're right.
I guess its not surprising,
we did drive them away
pretty harshly last time.
- We've watched the
daybreak countless
times together, but
it must be really
lonely for him.
Watching it all by himself.
- [Ensei] Oh?
(gasps)
- [Ensei] You've seen the
sun come up a lot lately?
- So are you planning
to make a habit of
staying up to watch the
sun rise from now on?
- Uh, no it's not like we
pulled another all nighter
or anything.
- I thought you said you were
gonna go home last night.
That was the only reason
why Seiran, Yuushun and I
agreed to do some extra work.
- [Ensei] You should be
sleeping at the Governors
residence right now.
What are the two
of you doing here
surrounded by books and
getting bags under your eyes?
- Uh, come on your
imagining things Ensei.
- Oh I am, am I?
Well, what do you think?
- Oh uh, Seiran
- All right you two come here,
its been a long time
since I had to teach
anyone a lesson.
- Yes
(tap)
- Don't get me wrong.
I'm very happy you're
both so enthusiastic
about your work.
But if you ruin your health by
pushing yourself too hard,
that won't do anyone any good.
- [Yuushun] Taking regular
breaks and maintaining
your health while
performing your duties
is also an important
part of the Governors
responsibility to the province.
- Yes
- We're sorry.
- Even if they get
a lecture like this.
- I bet you anything,
they'll still keep
forcing themselves
for quite a while.
- Yeah
- As long as she has trouble
forgetting about him.
- (grumbles)
- [Shurei] The
palace celebration?
- When the new year arrives
representatives from
the seven colored clans,
as well as officials
from each province
go to Kiyou City
in order to extend
their greetings to the king.
- (thinks) to the king, to Ryuki
- [Ensei] More than that,
- Hm
- It's a once a year
opportunity for important
people from across the
country to gather together.
That means, there's
a considerable amount
of diplomatic exchange
going on behind the scenes.
- [Shurei] Diplomatic exchange?
- The discussions between
officials are important.
- You wouldn't be
exaggerating to say
they have a direct
influence on everything
that's decided for
the rest of the year,
from personnel, to budgets.
- And it's not as easy
as just turning up,
saying a few casual
hello's to people,
then coming home again.
- [Ensei] So which
one of you will go?
- Huh
- Since there's still
quite a lot of work
that needs to be done here.
Either Governor
Hong or Governor To
should stay behind
while the other makes
the official visit.
- I think you should be
the one to go Shurei.
I'm sure Mr.Shoka will
be happy to see you.
- Huh
- Besides, that's
not the only reason.
You've got a lot more
weapons in your arsenal
when it comes to
diplomatic maneuvers.
- I
- I hope I'm not
insulting you by
pointing that out.
- Oh very well, yes I'll go.
- [Yuushun] You
won't be going alone.
I'll be accompanying
you along with Mr.Seiran
The Merchants Guild
representative, Ms.Sai Rin Si
and Lord Kokujun,
will be offering his
greetings as clan head.
- Hm
(barking)
- I'm glad I'll be
able to see father
but, to see Ryuki
when I feel this way.
- [Ensei] Princess?
- What's wrong?
- Oh don't worry, it's nothing.
- Hey that's obviously not true.
- I just feel a little uneasy.
You won't be going to
the palace celebration
will you Ensei?
It just made me
realize how much I've
been depending on you without
being aware of it.
- That makes me very
happy to hear that.
(chuckles)
- But come on, will you be
that lonely separated from me?
- [Shurei] Mhmm
- Huh
- (Giggles)
But don't worry,
this time I'll do
my best to get by without you.
Good night Ensei.
- [Ensei] Wait a minute.
- Huh
- Princess, why don't I make you
some delicious tea, right now?
(tea pours)
- [Ensei] Here ya go.
- [Shurei] Thank you.
- For crying out loud
this is supposed to be
your private residence
but, it looks more
like a library.
- [Shurei] I feel
more at ease this way.
- Ensei, do I really
look so depressed
that you felt like
you had to make
some tea to cheer me up?
- No, it's all just me
worrying about you Princess.
- I heard they've
recently finished cleaning
away the debris from the
building that collapsed.
- [Ensei] Oh, right.
You mean the trap
where the whole place
falls down when
you apply a certain
amount of weight to it?
That was pretty smart of Chusho
to come up with
an idea like that.
- [Shurei] They founds
lot of gun powder and
jars of oil
underneath the floor.
I guess he wanted
to make sure but,
luckily they
finished the clean-up
without incident.
- So in the end, the only
thing they couldn't find
was Saku himself.
(gasps)
- That's right.
It's just like him to
cause trouble for me.
Even up to his
very final moments.
I know that man was involved in
so many dreadful deeds.
And yet, he never
treated me cruelly,
not even once.
He never forced me to
do or feel anything.
'Play the erhu for me,
brew some tea for me.
Please do up my hair.'
Those were the only things
he ever asked of me.
I, just couldn't bring
myself to hate him.
- It's fine for you
to feel that way,
of course you would.
You were the first
and only person in
Saku's whole life that he
cared not to be hated by.
Because of that
he only showed his
prettiest colors to
you, and you alone.
There's no way you could
hate him after that,
and there's not really
any need for you to.
- But you know, I wasn't
really fair to him either.
I couldn't help but be
charmed by that man as well.
And it kept me from
telling him properly
until the very end.
- Telling him what?
- I should have told him,
I can't be with you.
(laughing)
- Stop it, it's no
laughing matter.
(laughing)
- Oh sorry, it's
just, a guy like him
would never go along
with a line like that.
- Ah you're right.
Even if I did say that,
he'd probably play
it off as a joke.
But
I still should have
said it over and over.
Until the words finally
reached his heart.
- Hm
- Uh
- I thought you
might be out here.
- [Seiran] Yeah
- Honestly I'm fine, okay?
Don't worry about me.
(water trickling)
(Dog Barking)
- [Ensei] I'm afraid
I wasn't able to
do anything for
her either Seiran.
On the contrary, you
and I are the ones
being worried about as usual.
- [Seiran] You're pathetic.
- Yeah but, so are you.
- It's all because you and I are
too deeply involved
with this whole thing,
and neither of us can
help her like this.
- Somebody died right
before her eyes.
There's no way anyone
as kind as Princess
wouldn't be upset.
Damn, Saku.
Even when he's dead,
he's still causing
trouble to the bitter end.
(sigh)
- [Seiran] Right now,
only Master Shoka or completely
neutral third party
can make a difference.
- Uh!
What a klutz I am.
(drips)
Oh no
I can't cry.
(sobs)
(flute plays)
You know, when you're
visiting someone's house
it's generally considered
polite to announce
yourself first, Rykren.
- If you had some more
elegance and surprise
to the myriad aspects of life
then you'll find it more
satisfying and fulfilling.
- It's already
way past midnight.
Next time, please at
least try to get here
before the sun sets, okay?
- Sure, but
I want some rice
porridge with mushrooms
for dinner then.
- All right I got it, now
get inside quick.
The nights have been
getting a lot colder lately.
(thud)
(window creeks)
- Hey, what happened to
those feathers you wore?
- Well in the midst
of my travels,
I re-encountered
two young men who
were enamored of my feathers.
In the end I traded
them for some things.
- [Shurei] It couldn't be.
(shivers)
- Uh
- By the way, I'm
sorry I chased you off
the last time.
I said some pretty harsh things.
- What the?
- No one can know
what goes on in
other people's hearts.
And no one can really predict
where following the
heart will lead you.
Ever since Sakujun
Sa's rampage stopped,
casualties have been
reduced to the minimum.
You were the only one
who succeeded in that.
In fact only you could do it.
- Yah and what about it?
I still
I'm stil the one who killed him.
- [Rykren] That's true.
While he chose death for
his own satisfaction,
you were the one who drove
him to make that choice.
(gasps)
He merely existed
until he met you.
Then he developed
an interest in life.
That's what made the
choice important.
In the end, you
were the only one
who could save Sakujun Sa,
and the only one
that could kill him.
That means, you're
the only person in
this whole world
who's allowed to cry
for his sake.
The funeral right
are finished and
judgements all laid down.
That means the only thing
that remains for you to do,
is to cry for him.
- If I'm allowed to
cry then, I'll cry.
You'd better be
ready for clothes
you're wearing to be
soaked and ruined.
If not, just tell me
how much the whole
outfit is gonna cost to replace.
I should be able to
hold my tears back
if I hear the price.
- If you like, I
can play you the
tragic song of the century.
- Oh Rykren, I'm gonna
cry even without the song.
(sobs)
They say tears from eyes
and rain from Heaven,
those will always be part of
the natural way of things.
(sobs)
And justice and blue
sky eventually beats
through the clouds,
Tears will also dry away.
(high flute playing)
(pours)
- [Shurei] I was wondering.
Did you come all this
way just to cheer me up?
- I had heard from
Kokujun that you were very
cheerful and excited.
But you can never truly
fool a kindred spirit.
- Huh, you met Mr. Kokujun?
- [Rykren] Of course I have.
Since I'm staying at his
place, I see him everyday.
- What?
You're staying with him?
But how did that happen?
(flute playing)
- [Rykren] While I was
walking in the city
and he called out to me.
- [Kokujun] Please
excuse my rudeness but,
I was wondering, would
you be willing to help
me select a new wardrobe?
I'm supposed to be going
to the palace celebration
in the new year but I
have no idea what to wear.
I don't know anything about
fashion trends in Kiyou.
If its all right with you
Sir, please come to my home
as my guest, and offer me
some advice about my wardrobe.
- No matter how you look
at it he picked the wrong
guy for the job.
- As we're the same
age, I couldn't help
but sympathize.
And when he insisted, I couldn't
very well turn him down.
- Huh
What's that?
You're the same age as him?
- That's right.
On top of that, he
and his new bride
appreciated my flute playing and
applauded all of my tunes.
- If he can be that
diplomatic, maybe he will
make it big.
- You have a strange way of
opening paths for people.
Look at all that's happened.
Me coming here, Kokujun becoming
the head of the Sa Clan.
Ensei taking the Basic
Provential Exams.
And even the Provential
government becoming
as stable as it is today.
All these things are
because of your actions
aren't they?
- And you have a
strange way of knowing
a lot about
everything don't you?
- I suppose that's what
I means to have the name
Rykren Ran.
(grunts)
- And with that, I'll
have to excuse myself.
Being in a women's
bedroom at midnight
might lead to a
rather bad reputation.
(laughs)
(flute playing)
- All right, I've
gotta give it my best.
- Let's see if
agriculture and forestry
won't work, and the city
can't be turned into
a commercial center.
I wonder what we can make into
Sa Provinces main industry.
What is it, something
on your mind?
- Oh nothing, it's
just that, well
I was thinking that you
look a lot more refreshed
and relaxed, that's all.
- Maybe because I
cried my eyes out.
- Huh
- I'm sorry that I made
you worry about me.
But I'm feeling much better now.
As long as I'm alive,
I'll keep putting one
foot in front of the other
and do the best that I can.
- Yeah you're right.
As long as we're around,
we'll do our best.
- Having said that,
when it comes to setting
up new industries to base
our infrastructure on,
there's a limit to
what you and I can come
up with on our own.
- That's very true.
We should probably
ask for the opinions
of specialists in
various fields.
- For example?
- [Eigetsu] Well
like applied arts,
fine arts.
- [Shurei] Pharmacy, medicine.
We'd have to gather
specialists in those
fields together and then,
(gasps)
- [Both] Aha!
- Eigetsu.
- Yes that's it, there
is that possibility.
- Right!
- In any case, lets start
working on that idea.
(upbeat music)
- Huh
(dreamy sound)
- [Ensei] Are you two
planning on watching
the sun rise again?
- Oh uh, Ensei
We were just thinking of
going home in a few minutes,
really.
- [Ensei] So what's
that you go there?
- Please give it back, it
isn't even finished yet.
- Aye, perfect timing.
Catch Yuushun.
- [Yuushun] Hm, what is it?
- Hm, Ensei, please gather
all of the provential
officials here for a meeting.
Also, please invite
Mrs.Sei Rin Si as well.
As for the two of
you, if you can,
please collect all
the documents relating
to this matter as
quickly as possible.
- [Yuuhsun] Now I
would as you both to
explain your proposal
to those gathered.
- The two of us have
been considering how best
to raise the entirety
of Sa Province from
its current depression.
- Not only must we
continue the work that
Lieutenant Governor Ryou,
Lieutenant Governor Tei began.
But it is also our
responsibility to take
the province to the next level.
- To the next level huh?
Huh
- And that's what this
plan is all about.
- We'd like too create
a research institution.
To make Sa Province a center
for academic research.
- We believe this will lead
the province to prosperity,
as well as guarantee a strong
future 100 years from now.
(crowd mumbles)
- It's and interesting idea.
- Of course the plan still
has quite a few holes.
But it's definitely
worth discussing further.
- I would agree.
- [Sai Rin] Indeed, it is
quite a promising plan.
- [Yuushun] Ms. Sai Rin Si.
- Of course it's also
incredibly far reaching.
And would require considerable
funds, significant land,
and many talented people
to complete it properly.
- We invited you with
the intention of asking
the Merchants Guild for
cooperation in areas
such as, financial assistance.
- Personally, I would
like to help you.
But I can not officially
support a plan that
may be aborted
while in progress.
As Chief Representative
of the Merchants Guild,
I'm afraid I am unable to
give my assent so readily.
- Sister please.
- However I can't
help but be touched by
the spirit the two
Governors have shown by
thinking of Sa Provinces'
future for 100 years from now.
It votes well for the project.
We'll consider the
proposal further
with all intentions
of making it work.
- Well then we will
reveal the find points
of the plan thoroughly and
- [Yuushun] Let us reconvene
in one months time.
- Huh
- One month?
- This is an
important matter when
it comes to Sa
Provinces' future.
I hope that everyone
will do their best.
- In other words, it should
be ready by the new year.
Right Yuushun?
- For the new year?
You mean the celebration?
- Right.
If we finish in one month
we can present the
matter officially during
the palace celebration.
- Hm
- All right I understand.
I'll do everything that I
can while in Kiyou City.
(Cheers)
- Well done
well done
(calming music)
- [Ensei] So you're
admiring the sun set today
instead of the sun rise huh?
- [Shurei] Ensei.
- You're really
amazing Princess.
- You came up with an
incredible plan like that
out of the blue.
- I have to keep moving forward.
I realize now, the
reason I could never
take that mans hand
is because I want to
keep fortune ahead
one step at a time.
You know I'm very greedy.
I can't give up the things
that are important to me,
and the things that
I've cultivated.
When it comes down to
it, I can't trade away
all the feelings and
hoped I hold in my heart
in exchange for living my
life only for his sake.
I'm just not willing
to make that sacrifice.
If I were able to throw it
all away just like that,
I would never have
taken the national exams
in the first place.
I wanted to become a government
official for so long.
But all I had were
these vague idea like,
I'll become an official
and work diligently
to prevent the country
from collapsing.
Now its different.
I want to become a
government official who earns
the acknowledgement of
the people I respect.
And I want to become
an official who will be
capable of helping those I love.
And that means, I'll
have to keep moving
much further up.
- Huh
That's a pretty astounding
confession Princess.
It's not fair catching
me off balance like that.
- Hm
- You know, you shouldn't
be in such a hurry
to become and adult.
- But I intend to.
After everything
that's happened,
I realize that I
can't remain a child.
I've decided that I won't
make the same mistake again.
So I'll give everything
lots and lots of thought
so it doesn't happen.
I can do it.
I swear, I'm going
to do it Ensei.
(crow caws)
- Well then, we'll be
going back to Kinku now.
- Right, take care.
- Oh, headed home?
- What's got you in
such a satisfied mood?
- I was just thinking
about how fortunate I am
to have such a great boss.
- Thinking ahead one
hundred years down the road.
Pretty impressive.
It's not a simple thing
for most people to imagine.
It's the sort of
thinking a Prime Minister
might use as he
oversees a country.
Lieutenant Governor, you
and I and everyone else
may be assisting in
the first steps of two
soon to be legendary officials.
Who will have their
names etched in history.
- I know, it's giving
me chills down my spine.
- Still, the real battle
will be at the palace.
(peaceful music)
- Hey Shurei
- What is it?
- I'm glad that we're
in this together.
I'm proud to serve with you
as a government official
of Sa Province.
- I feel the same.
- I brought a midnight
snack for you two.
Please, I hope you
enjoy it, Lady Shurei.
- Thank you Karin.
Oh you've made
meatball soup for us.
This is really delicious.
Not only is the soup good but,
the texture of the meatball
soaks it up perfectly,
its fantastic.
Right?
- Yes I agree.
Actually this is one
of my favorite dishes.
- What do I care,
I only made it for
Lady Shurei.
- [Eigetsu] Maybe but, it truly
is delicious all the same.
(end song)
We're on our way to Kiyo
To attend the New Year's
Palace celebration
Eigetsu, Ensei,
Please look after Sa
Provence while I'm gone
I'll be seeing you soon Father
Lord Koyu, General Ran, and...