(logo swooshing)
(singing in foreign language)
(acoustic music)
- [Man] On this day invoice
from the Imperial court
have come to visit Shuurei Hong.
They have come to inform
her of the results
of her Aptitude Test and
based on that let her know
whether or not she'd be
permitted to take the last test
of the national exams.
(epic music)
(Shuurei sighs)
Shuurei Hong,
Aptitude Test pass.
Now it is up to Shuurei
to study for her first
and last attempt at
taking the final.
It's a big step towards
realizing her childhood dream
of becoming a court official.
(acoustic music)
(indistinct chatters)
(footsteps approaching)
(horn blowing)
- I finally made it
(indistinct chatters)
This is the end of the road.
(footprints scatters)
(epic music)
- It's just over a
month until the final,
there's been a sharp increase
in visitors as a result,
how's town security?
- As in past years, the
gangs will see to it
that the streets are safe.
However, there are some
new rumors going around.
I'll look into it and provide
you with a full report,
once I've gathered
more information.
- Things are likely to get busy.
I'm counting on you both.
- Live it to us your majesty.
(acoustic music)
- Hey, you wanna get some food?
- I'd love to, but unfortunately
I've got somewhere to go.
- Huh?
- Actually, I'm headed to
the Red Light District.
- Red Light District?
- Don't look at me like
that, this is also part
of my duties you know.
- Oh, is it really?
(indistinct chatters)
(epic music)
- Shuurei, hey, come on.
You're going somewhere
again, aren't you?
I hear you've been making
farewell visits all around town.
You know, you're at
that ripe age now.
Why not quit wandering around
and settle down already?
You're getting a bit
old to be unmarried.
It's gonna get more and
more difficult to find
a good partner that'll
take you without a dowry.
But I, well I'm from
a pretty rich family,
so I wouldn't ask for a dowry.
(Shuurei sighs)
- It's none of your
business, how late I marry
or how few men
are gonna take me.
You're just a childhood friend,
so it's not any
concern of yours.
- The point I'm tryna make is.
- Look at any rate,
I don't have the time
to deal with you today.
Why don't you just hurry
up and go home Santa?
- Don't call me Santa,
please call me Keichou.
- You never seem to grow up,
so I'd say Santa is
more than appropriate.
(Keichou sighs)
- My my, if it isn't Master
Rosyang son come to visit.
- Oh, Ms Kochou.
- What is it this
time young man?
Are you trying to
hit on her again?
Oh you never learn, dear boy
just wait until night time
then I promise
I'll play with you.
I'll even set some time
aside especially chest free.
- No, that's fine, I'd
never have enough money
to pay for your services
anyway, Ms Kochou.
Later.
(Kochou giggling)
- Honestly, talk about gutless.
- I'm surprised to see you
up and about so early, ma'am.
- My client left my
bed in the middle
of the night yesterday.
- Someone left early from the
room of the number one lady
of the Red Light District.
- There are some truly
foolish men out there,
but there is a
bright side to it.
It means I can spend
more of what little time
you have left you with you.
- Huh?
- Soon you will be leaving us,
by my reckoning you'll only
be working for us
for seven more days.
- Yes.
- When I look at you, I still
remember that little girl,
who came to my door
all on her own.
You bowed your head and ask
politely if you could work here,
you'd obviously been
brought up very well,
even beyond bearing the
Hong name and being part
of that noble family.
You had such a grim
look on your face.
You'd more than prepared
yourself to come
and work in a Red
Light District,
whatever that entailed.
- Madam, I have to prepare
dinner in the evening,
so I'll need to be home
by sunset every night.
- Hmm?
(soft music)
(Kochou giggling)
- Ms Kochou please.
I asked you to forget
about that already.
- Quite a long time
has passed since then.
The days go by so quickly.
Oh, by the way, would
you do me a favor?
Make certain you come and
see me on your last day
of work here, I have
something I wanna give you.
- Please, you mustn't.
- Now now child
there's no need to be
so cold and polite about
it, you're the only person
I've come across who's ever
been able or will ever be able
to make me promise an honest
date and keep it do Shuurei.
Got that?
As I said, a promise.
Otherwise they'll be forced
to tell Mr Hong and say on
that you've been working
in the Red Light District.
- No, no please,
anything but that,
I'll come you have my word.
(Kochou giggles)
- By the way, I
forgot to mention it,
we had a rather unusual
guest arrive yesterday
- An unusual guest you say?
(soft gentle music)
- A child?
- I'm guessing is around
12 or 13 years old at most.
- Wow!
Well that certainly does
qualify as an unusual guest.
- [Eigetsu] Hey,
what is this place?
- It seems like he's awake.
- So you don't even
remember how you got here.
- Oh, right I'm Eigetsu To.
- Hi, Eigetsu.
- Let's see, I just
arrived in Kiyo yesterday
and got tangled up
with some gangsters.
I remember everything
up until the point
of them dragging me
into a restaurant.
But um...
How did I end up in this place?
- It's quite simple, really.
One of our regulars carried
you here and asked us
to put you up for
a little while.
He was willing to pay us
very handsomely for it,
so we agreed.
- What?
I can't possibly
impose like that.
How much did he pay?
I can pay for everything so
please give him back his money.
Huh, why is this so light?
- What, this is nowhere near
what I'm supposed to have.
- You don't even have
enough for a month
at the cheapest lodging in town.
- I was sure I had a lot
more in my bag yesterday.
What should I do?
- Why not accept the man's
generosity and stay here
for the time being.
- I, but.
- If not, how about at my place?
Well, it's a bit rundown,
but there's lots of space
and last year we had a bear
like man stay without any notice
so, we're used to having
unexpected visitors.
- I'm truly sorry for
imposing on you like this.
Are you sure it's really
all right for me to stay?
- If you're worried, why don't
you help me with something?
- What?
- To tell the truth,
I could use some help
finishing the accounting.
- Oh sure, I'm pretty good
at that sort of thing.
- In that case, I'll leave
it all to you, Eigetsu.
- Yes ma'am.
- Wow, you're really
something else Eigetsu,
who could have guessed you'd
be so fast and accurate
with your calculations,
you are amazing.
- Thank you.
But you're too kind.
- My lady.
- Hello Seiran, what is it?
- I thought we might go to a
restaurant for dinner tonight,
so I came to meet you.
- But isn't that extravagant?
- I know it's a little
bit on the late side,
but you can consider
it a special dinner
to celebrate passing
the Aptitude Test.
- For me?
Thank you so much Seiran.
(epic music)
- My, my my, must have been
quite a journey all the way
from Koku province.
- Well, sort of.
- Pretty impressive
considering he's only 13
but just to warn you, the
final exam is coming up
and lots of people are
here from out of town.
It's kind of a dangerous
time to be in the Capital
if you're not familiar with it.
I don't know what brings you
here, but I suggest you finish
it up quickly and return home.
- I guess you're right.
- By the way, have
you heard those rumors
about this year's final?
They say a lot of kids
are showing up to take it.
Rumor has it,
there's even a girl.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
She's only 16 or 17 and
supposedly she's guaranteed
to win top position, so I'm
gonna put 30% of my fortune
on her getting the
number one ranking.
- Didn't you lose your entire
fortune doing the same thing
a few years back?
- Jeez, you keep
bringing that up.
That was the time those two
long shot teens took first
and second spot.
Nobody expected that to happen.
- Oh yeah, I remember, but as
I recall, they were both kids
from really high class
families weren't they?
- Must be nice.
Have your parents pay for
everything while you focus
on studying and your future
will be safe and secure.
- But all that aside, I
don't think I've ever heard
of women being allowed to
take the national exams.
I mean, a highly respected
teacher once tried
and didn't get anywhere,
so there's no way
some ordinary woman can
make it to the final exam.
- You got that right, besides
what business is a woman
have taken the exams
in the first place.
(men laughing loudly)
(men grunting)
- What's just happened?
- [Kou] I wonder,
very mysterious.
- [Seiran] Serves
them right. Anyway,
- We should really
start eating before all
this food gets cold.
Eigetsu you be sure to
drink all your soup,
you look like you need
to warm yourself up.
- Yes, sir.
(Eigetsu sipping soup)
- One thing's for sure.
No one in this entire
world, can hope to gain
what's truly important to
them, unless they're willing
to work hard for it.
Take General Ran and
Lord Kyou, for example.
In the beginning they were
constantly ridiculed because
they were so young, but in
the end they shut everyone up
and prove themselves
thanks to the type
of strength we call effort.
This is just my opinion, but
perhaps all you really need
is effort.
- Thank you father.
(acoustic music)
Here, have some wine father.
- Thank you.
- Would you like to try a sip
of this as well and Eigetsu?
- No, thank you.
- Really?
Are you positive?
- Yeah, I'm really weak
when it comes to alcohol.
To tell you the truth, I try
to avoid even snowing if I can.
- Hey, that reminds me.
Do you think it's possible
that the money you're missing,
could've been stolen by those
gangsters you mentioned?
Maybe they forced you to
drink some strong wine
and you passed out or something.
- No, I, I don't think
that's very likely,
but, I guess it'd be
possible that there'd be one
or two very skilled people in
the Capital who could do it.
Maybe, but.
- If that's the case, it would
have to be the Seikin Gang.
- Seiran, you know
something about this?
- A little, from what I've
heard, it's a gang of thugs
and hooligans who arrived
in town just recently.
They wear a blue cloth
somewhere on their bodies
to mark themselves
as gang members.
- That is not good.
Do you mean to tell me
that the crime bosses
have been turning a
blind eye to them?
- Up until now, but
lately the Seikin Gang
has been getting more
flagrant and open
in their criminal activities.
- In that case, maybe it will
spur the bosses into making
them move soon.
- Wow, by the sound of
it, it seems pretty clear
that this gangs leaders
from outside the Capital.
- [Seiran} I agree,
otherwise their actions
would be suicidal.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, of course I'm sorry.
You don't know too much
about the city, do you?
- Not really.
- Kiyo City may be the capital,
but there's a very clear
distinction between
who governs the State
and who governs Downtown.
- A clear distinction.
- Yes.
Kiyou the underground
crime boss is responsible
for managing the
Downtown hooligans
at this time of year when
there's an increase in visitors
from other provinces
for the final,
it's their job to protect the
piece of the downtown core.
The bosses take pride
in ensuring everything
is kept under control,
specifically their control.
- Usually that's
the case but then
what are the bosses waiting for?
They've let it go too far,
Eigetsu even had
his money stolen.
- Let's not jump to
conclusions just yet.
Actually, the money wasn't
mine, it was gathered
from the people in my hometown.
I feel really bad
about losing it, but.
- That makes matters even worse.
- But it's not the
end of the world.
I'm fine as long as
I still have this.
(Eigetsu crying)
- What's wrong?
- It's gone.
- W www what's gone?
- I'm really sorry
I have to go back.
- Ww wait What?
Where are you going?
I mean just hold on a minute
Eigetsu
- I'll follow.
(acoustic music)
(Shuurei panting)
- Oh, where'd he go?
There he is.
They're wearing blue cloth,
they must be the Seikin Gang.
- Hey, you're the one we're
looking for, aren't you?
The little brat, who
not only embarrassed
my boys last night, but ended
up robbing them blind too.
- Oh my goodness, I did that?
I'm so sorry, please forgive me.
- Eigetsu did what?
I can't believe it, these
guys have gotta be mistaken.
- You making fun of us, kid?
- Do you know if I dropped
something yesterday?
A token around this big?
Did you happen to see it?
- A token?
Yeah, we got it, we've been
making a little collection.
- A collection?
- Hey, Eigetsu
- Who the heck is she?
- Now's not the time
to be having a chat,
hurry up and run.
- Nice try kids.
Damn, go after them and
get that money back.
(men shouting)
(both panting)
- Miss Shuurei We shouldn't
run, wait a minute.
- I'm not waiting, it's no
use trying to talk sense
into that sort, discretion
is the better part of valor.
- But
- Eigetsu, was it true
what they said back there?
About you taking their money?
Do you remember
anything about it?
- No, but maybe yes.
- Which is it?
- where'd those two brats go?
- Oh no.
- There they are damn.
- I'm the one the thereafter
so please try and get
away by yourself Miss Shuurei.
- Hey wait, that's no good.
You don't know your
way around this town.
I can't just abandon
you like that.
- But Miss Shuurei.
- At last, found you.
(Shuurei screaming)
(man grunting)
- Hurry, let's go Eigetsu.
- Wow!
- Seiran told me that if
you kick a man in the groin,
he drops like a rock.
- Yes, I did good job Shuurei.
- Seiran did you just see that?
- Thanks to you, I couldn't
make much of an entrance.
- Hey, find them?
- They can have gotten far,
they should still
be in the area.
- Search everywhere.
- Right.
(footsteps fading)
- We can't go home at this
rate, they would probably follow
us to the residence.
Eigitsu where were you
going when you ran out?
A place called Kogaro in
the Red Light District.
When I met Shuurei,
(Eigitsu mumbles)
(shuurei laughs)
- Lady Shuurei have been
looking for you everywhere.
- Really?
- Yes my lady.
Ms Kochou sent me to find you.
It's not safe out here,
please return to Kogaro
along with the young men
and if it's not too much
of a problem, Mr Seiran as well.
We'll have our
underlings take care
of those annoying
Seikin Gang members.
- What?
Take care, how?
- It's a good idea,
given the Kogaro status,
those hooligans won't be
able to enter the premises.
- What?
Seiran how the heck
did you know Kogaro
- We'll talk about
it later, hurry.
- Right?
(indistinct chatters)
- Give me a break, what
on earth were you thinking
when you left that
boy at some brothel?
- I was thinking that it was
the safest place for him.
- But the Red Light
District is dangerous.
- That's just your
prejudice talking,
it's actually very safe.
Keep in mind that the
underground is in control here.
Of course, considering
you never come here,
it's not surprising you'd have
no clue about such things.
- You come here way
too much, by the way,
what's with all these women?
- [Woman] You haven't been here
for a while, we missed you.
- [Woman] Hey, hello there Mr
Ran, Maya here early today.
(indistinct chatters)
- This place is incredible.
Is this district
your Harem Shuei?
- Well, I guess
you could say so,
although its purpose is
rather different from yours,
it's a place for men to enjoy
themselves and have fun.
If you wanna think
of it in other terms,
think of it as
every man's heroine.
The brothel we're going
to now, has many women
who are both beautiful
and accomplished.
They're easily the equals
of any of the ladies
in your residence.
You've got something
to look forward to.
- Ah, Kochou.
- Oh Lord Ran, as always,
your timing is perfect
and who might these
two young men be?
- They're my companions.
They've come to see the
boy I left with you.
- Your companions?
Interesting.
- She's certainly is beautiful.
I've seldom seen so much
beauty, she's equal to Shusui.
- Dear me, I'm
afraid that last part
is absolutely
unacceptable young master.
If you mean to
compliment a woman,
then you must never dream
of comparing her to another.
- Oh, is that so
(dog barking)
- I don't believe,
you let them get away.
This is no time to
be fooling around.
We are here to make a name
for ourselves in the Capital,
and become the boss
to the downtown core,
so why in the hell aren't you
able to catch one single boy?
- You're right boss,
but we got it covered,
in fact, we have
word of him going
into a place called Kogaro
along with some girl who
was carrying an Abacus.
- Kogaro.
Hey Keichou.
- Yes.
- What is Kogaro?
Some kind of bravo?
- Yes, actually it's the top
brothel in the whole district.
The famous courtesan Kochou
has clients paying 1000
gold coins for her.
- The right to make up for
the trouble I'd been through
I think I'll make
this Kochou my girl.
- Boys, I got a
great idea why don't
we make Kogaro our
new base of operation?
(men chanting)
- Girl carrying an Abacus?
Could it be..
- Hmm I've definitely
made the right choice
in going after those, steal
that thing from someone
threatening you'll pay
any price to get it back,
his businesses is gold,
this is a great one.
Located boys start
getting things packed up.
(men shouting)
- Huh.
(dogs barking)
(footsteps approaching)
- [Man] Shuurei.
- Oh jeez, what are doing here?
So you decided to sneak
out with General Ran
and Lord Kyou and go have
some fun in a brothel, did ya?
- No you're wrong Shuurei.
I don't need to come to
this kinda place for that,
I can do as much as
I like in the palace.
(giggling)
Well, I mean. I.....I
(singing in foreign language)
- Before I knew it,
I was back at Kogaro.
What's Shi Ryuuki doing here
and why is Eigetsu being
hunted by gangsters?
Hey Santa what's that you say?
The Seikin Gang is
gonna attack Kogaro.