- How do you like this building?
Pretty fuckin' sweet
place, isn't it?
- [Sawa] Yeah.
- [Man] You're really a lucky
little girl, you know that?
Those ugly dogs in my fan club
don't even know
about this place.
I'm gonna do things to you that
they never even dreamed of.
- Disgusting, vulgar,
arrogant punk.
Touching sweet young
girls like that in public.
Just because you think
you're some big TV star,
you think you can do
anything you want.
Who do you think you
are bringing young girls
up to your apartment
to do who knows what?
Shame on you!
- Shut up!
So, how does it
feel being kicked
by an arrogant celebrity punk?
You old bitch!
Your stinking perfume makes
me utterly sick to my stomach!
You're the disgusting one,
you shriveled up cunt!
(gun firing)
Uh!
Oh!
Ah!
- Oh, where are my glasses?
I'm going to sue you for this.
My son is an excellent lawyer.
He eats punks like
you for lunch.
Let's see what kind of a
career you have in jail.
He'll put you away for life!
Oh, where are those glasses?
(gentle music)
(siren blaring)
(sultry music)
(camera clicking)
- Yeah, looks like we got
fragments from two bullets.
One in the chest,
one in the head.
Blood's been forced
through the skin.
Hmm, guy never
knew what hit him.
- Hey, Boss.
- Yeah?
- Take a look.
We're looking for a special gun.
The weapon that did this was
designed with exploding shells.
- Let me know what the lab
finds on those fragments.
The coroner's boy should
be here any minute.
- Didn't they tell you?
They're all in the hospital
with food poisoning.
- Yeah, right, those assholes.
Betcha you they
still get overtime.
So, what's her story anyway?
- Well, apparently
the whole ordeal
must have sent her into shock.
My guess is the old broad
had a massive heart attack.
- Maybe, but we'd better get
an autopsy to cover our ass.
So, who the hell is this clown?
Some kind of movie star?
- He calls himself a comedian.
Some people seem
to like him though.
He's on the tube
seven days a week.
Ironically enough, the
guy told a whole lot
of dead body jokes.
Go figure.
- Someone didn't
find him amusing.
What a fuckin' tearjerker.
- He was such a nice guy.
He was the nicest guy
in all of show business.
Why would anyone want to
kill someone like him?
All of the little
girls just loved him.
We made such a great team.
It can't end like this.
What am I gonna do?
- Thank you, Mr. Ogata.
We've also received recent
reports that his outraged fans
have been arriving on the
scene in surprising numbers.
Such support is truly an
indication of mass popularity
and admiration on a grand scale.
According to inside
sources, however,
this case may also
involve organized crime.
I'm Miss Nagachima
for channel six.
- Nicely done.
- [Miss Nagachima]
Evening Edition.
- I can't stop thinking
about that old lady.
- People die everyday.
Come here, Sawa.
- I'm not in the mood.
(birds chirping)
- [Kanie] You ought to
be more punctual, Oburi.
- Who are we doing?
Which one, Kanie?
- All of them.
- [Oburi] Huh?
- We've called someone else in.
You concentrate on
the one in the front
and our associate will
take care of the other two.
- So, what did these
guys do anyway?
- The three of them are
child molesters, Oburi.
Let's just say they're going
to pay for their lifestyle.
- [Oburi Voiceover] So,
there's another one,
another one besides me.
- Yeah, how about
again this weekend?
Give me a call later.
I am, of course,
talking about our usual
recreational activities,
if you catch my drift.
My wife sure isn't getting
any younger, you know.
Hmm.
(explosion booming)
(screaming)
(gun firing)
(alarm bell ringing)
- Come on!
That surprise you?
- That was you back there?
- That's right.
(somber piano music)
(children yelling)
(keyboard clacking)
- You'll get your usual
fee, same as always.
Kanie will take
care of you later.
- You stink, Mr. Akai.
- Oburi, you don't
have a clue, do you?
Let me tell you
something about my job.
I spend all goddamned
day around dead bodies.
The corpses stink so
bad my eyes water.
The rotten stench hangs
over me like a cloud.
And you wonder why I
stink so fuckin' bad.
(keyboard clacking)
- So, Mr. Akai, have
you had a chance
to think about our discussion?
- Sure, kid.
Far be it from me
to hold you back.
- Oh really?
Your generosity never
ceases to amaze me.
- However, there is a matter
of three more little jobs.
- Had a feeling that was coming.
- Hey, you understand,
don't you, kid?
It's just business that's all.
Just taking care of business.
Right, Kanie, just
taking care of business.
- Mr. Kanie, I'll do my best
to be more punctual this time.
- Hmm?
(door clicking shut)
(jazz music)
- [Girl] Show me what you got!
- [Boy] Oh, well,
give me that ball!
- No way!
- It's my turn!
- [Girl] Uh-uh, watch it.
- Oh man!
- Oh shut up!
I'd like to see you do better!
- [Boy] All right, I'm
gonna go get that ball.
- [Girl] Hey,
wait, it's my turn!
- [Boy] Slow coach!
(children yelling)
- [Girl] Watch this shot!
It's gonna be the
prize shot of them all!
- [Boy] Ha-ha, you missed!
- Huh?
- Hey, mister, give
us our ball back!
- [Boy] Yeah, give
- You got my jacket wet, kid.
- What that old piece of crap?
Go home and wash it
yourself, you old fart?
(laughing)
- [Boy] Yeah, you old fart!
- [Both] Whoa!
(gun firing)
(screaming)
(jazz music)
- He's very good, isn't he?
- That's why I need
you so much, Sawa.
(horn blaring)
- Here's your change, sir.
Thanks a lot, have a nice day.
- [Sawa] Psst, hey!
- Hmm?
- [Sawa] Nice apron.
- Where'd you come from?
- [Sawa] Mm, this
is pretty good.
This must be a new flavor.
You want some?
- [Oburi] You asked Kanie
where I worked, didn't you?
- [Sawa] Mm-hm.
- So, what for?
- I don't know.
- Doesn't matter.
What's your name?
- Sawa.
As in the sand you can't hold
and the feather
blown by the wind.
Remember that, okay.
- Sawa?
Is that your real name?
- Of course.
- Well, my name is--
- Oburi.
You're Oburi, right?
- You seem to know more
about me than I do you.
- Are you mad at me?
- No, not really.
- Well, I asked Kanie where
you worked, that's all.
So, is Oburi your real name too?
- [Oburi] Yup, that's it.
- It's very unusual.
- [Oburi] Everyone says that.
- Do you have a family?
- Afraid not.
How about you?
- [Sawa] No.
Me neither.
Kind of alike, aren't we, Oburi?
- Kinda.
Sawa, can I ask you something?
- I'll tell you anything you
want to know about me, Oburi.
Huh?
(cat purring)
- So, what's Akai's
relationship to you, Sawa?
- Akai's my,
well, he's kinda
like a guardian.
- Same as me, huh?
Strange coincidence.
- [Sawa] Hmm.
- Don't you think?
(dramatic music)
(earring clanking)
Those earrings must
be special to you.
- Huh, what do you mean?
- You were wearing them
the first time I saw you.
Remember?
It was at the mall.
They look really
beautiful on you.
And mysterious.
- They were made from
the blood of my parents.
In memory of my
mother and father.
They're lucky.
Okay, let's go!
- Huh?
- Come on.
I wanna see where
you live, Oburi.
(bird squawking)
- Ah, shit!
Ah!
(giggling)
Hmm.
- [Sawa] Wait a
minute, isn't that?
- [Kanie] Yeah, you know him?
- [Sawa] Not really, but
he's a movie star, right?
- Mm.
- Some of the kids at college
are fans of his.
I didn't know he had
a twin brother though.
- [Kanie] They'll be
here in a few minutes.
- Kanie, this is
the third celebrity.
- Sawa, kill the right one.
- If I kill the wrong
one, I'm really sorry.
- They're going to have
three bodyguards with them.
So, be very careful.
- [Sawa] So, where
do I find him?
- Our collaboration
is working well
and it works because the
world knows both of us
as only one person.
The Academy is gonna have
to create a new category
for action hero just for us.
Too bad we can't grab
two Oscars for it.
I say next stop is
the director's chair
and squeeze the producer for
300-mil on our next action pic.
We'll keep half the money
and get another Oscar.
Well, any Oscar we don't win,
we can buy the rest!
(laughing)
- Uh!
Ah!
- Huh?
- Ah!
- Who the hell are you?
(grunting)
- It's a girl!
- Ah!
(groaning)
(energetic jazz music)
(gun firing)
- Hey!
- Ah!
(gun firing)
Uh!
- Die!
Ah!
(gun firing)
- Ah!
(groaning)
- You piece of shit, you!
I'm gonna kill you!
Ah!
Come here!
- Ah!
(gun firing)
- Impressive, my
cute little assassin.
Too bad you're gonna die ugly.
Don't move an inch!
(gun firing)
- [Sawa] Ah!
- What the fuck is that?
- Ah!
(explosion booming)
Ah!
(glass shattering)
- Huh!
Huh!
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
(groaning)
(gun firing)
- [Sawa] That's mine!
That's mine!
Give it back!
- Sawa.
You want mummy and daddy back.
Kill him.
Sawa, do you know
what this man does?
He kidnaps sweet,
young, innocent girls.
Just like you, Sawa.
He rapes them.
And he chops them up
into little pieces.
He deserves to die, Sawa.
Kill him, kill him.
(gun firing)
(jazz music)
- Find who killed my
mother and father.
You promised.
- Hey, of course I will, Sawa.
(dramatic music)
- Just die already!
(gun firing)
(screaming)
(horns blaring)
(explosion booming)
(screaming)
(siren blaring)
- If we're lucky maybe
the killer got stupid
and left some evidence behind.
Man, we're gonna have
to search every inch
of this fucking mess.
- How do they expect us to
find anything in this war zone?
This is gonna take all day.
- That's why we make
the big bucks, ain't it?
Huh!
- Whoa.
Jesus, if you fell from here,
there wouldn't be anything
left for the coroner's office.
- Oh, you lucky little girl.
What the hell did
you do, grow wings?
- Huh?
- Hey, Akai, getting a little
tired of waiting out here!
- Yeah, we're done.
Hey, how come there's no
media monkeys hanging around?
- That's cause they all went
down to the precinct house.
- What, did they
finally find out
about the chief's
Lolita complex?
- Huh, you mean no one told ya?
They got a witness downtown.
Talking to him right now.
- Really?
This guy given us
anything useful?
- Not yet.
We keep working on him but I'm
afraid he's still in shock.
He did say it's a woman though.
- [Akai] A woman?
- Yeah, he said the
killer was a woman.
A young woman.
- Huh!
- I'm going back to look for it.
- Someone spotted you
at the scene, dammit!
- Why didn't you find it?
You were supposed
to find my earring.
- You destroyed half
of the building,
what the fuck did you expect?
You're lucky I found
the goddamned gun.
Fuck the earring.
- Those earrings are
really important to me
and you know that.
They're my family!
They're all I've got left.
- Get over it, you've
got another one.
Besides, we have a
slightly larger problem
to deal with now, thanks
to you, you little fool.
You killed the
goddamned client, Sawa.
- Well, Mr. Kanie gave
me the wrong information.
It's not my fault.
- I don't give a rat's ass.
- Then do it
yourself from now on!
- Hey!
Don't be gone too long, Sawa!
(door slamming)
(rain pounding)
- [Oburi] Sawa!
- What's up?
- What happened to you?
Are you okay?
- Does it look like I'm okay?
Feels like I fell
out of a building.
I even have a bald
spot and everything.
I'm exhausted.
- Do you wanna come in?
I can make some
coffee or something.
- I like tea, really
strong green tea.
- Ah tea, well,
I don't have any.
- I brought some.
- Ah!
- This tastes good.
- [Oburi] Sawa.
- What is it?
- In 10 years, what do you think
we'll be doing with our lives?
- Well, I don't know.
Why?
(telephone ringing)
- Just one target.
It's an easy job.
Meet me at the train station
just inside the front entrance.
You got that, Oburi?
And try to be
punctual this time.
- Sawa.
- Whether it's 10
years or even five,
tomorrow might not even
come for you and I, Oburi.
All we can ever do is live
our lives to the fullest.
There aren't any guarantees
for people like us.
We have to make it happen.
- [Oburi] Did Akai send you?
- He did.
You've become my next contract.
- Is that the only reason
you came here, Sawa?
- Do I have another reason?
Do I, Oburi?
- Akai and Kanie
killed your parents.
Did you know that, Sawa?
- I've known that for
a long time, Oburi.
(gun clicking)
You'll come back here
to get me, promise?
- Hmm.
- This guy's a prosecutor
with the DA's office.
He's been taking bribes
from a major corporation
while ignoring
illegal activities.
He'll be sitting in
the last train car
in about three minutes, so
take care of him there, Oburi.
- Sure doesn't look like a
government suit type to me.
- Be careful.
- I'll just try my best
to get there on time.
(energetic jazz music)
(explosion booming)
(gun firing)
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
(gun firing)
- Ahh!
- Ah!
Ah!
Who the hell are you?
- No one special.
I'm just an ordinary citizen.
Die.
Ah!
(dramatic music)
You punk!
I'm gonna blow you into pieces!
- The one in pieces is you, pig!
(gun firing)
(man screaming)
(explosion booming)
(screaming)
(humming)
(groaning)
- Sorry, Akai, I hate
to inconvenience you.
- Oburi, looks like you
got something on your mind.
- [Oburi] Oh, fuck you!
I should kill you now,
you son of a bitch!
- Just relax, kid.
- Relax!
Who the fuck was that
fat pig on the train?
- Just a cop.
Just some stupid, fucking
cop from the SWAT team.
I thought Kanie told
you that, I swear.
- Well, that cop had a piece.
He tried to take me out!
- Sorry, kid.
Maybe he didn't want to die.
- Shut the fuck up, Akai.
I'm sick of your bullshit.
You can kiss my ass
good-bye, I'm out.
And if you even try to come
after me, I'll kill you.
- Wait a minute.
Aren't you forgetting about
our little deal, Oburi?
- Do it your damned self.
- What about Sawa?
- She's coming with me.
- I see.
(grunting and groaning)
(gun firing)
(groaning)
Fuck!
Jesus, you're more
trouble than you're worth.
- What's all the noise?
- You!
I thought you were
dead, you little punk!
(gun firing)
- Get away!
I said get away from him!
- Sawa.
- [Sawa] Oburi, hang on!
I'll get you out of here.
Oburi!
- Sawa.
What are you doing here?
- Can you stand?
- [Oburi] I think so.
My arm, I can't feel it.
- We've got to get
you to a doctor.
Don't even move!
(gun firing)
- Sawa.
- Oburi, don't worry,
I'm not gonna kill ya.
Sawa, you should thank me.
- If you're just going
to kill him anyway,
you didn't have to
go through all this.
- Just killing him isn't
enough for me, Sawa.
- You hate him
that much, do you?
- It's deeper than that.
It's my, how shall I say, hobby.
- Hobby?
- You'll never understand
how much watching
other people's pain gets me off.
Hearing their
screams and knowing
that I have the power of a God.
- Gross hobby.
- You had me going for
a little while there.
I almost believed
you'd betray me.
- So, I'll be on my
own from now on, right?
- Don't worry, we've
already found a replacement.
- Where are you
going to kill him?
- In the place where you tasted
blood for the first time.
Awwh, man, I can't wait
for tomorrow's autopsy.
- [Sawa] I've got to go.
- Stay with me, Sawa.
- [Sawa] I have
an exam tomorrow.
- [Akai] Why don't you give
up that stupid college shit?
- No way.
I look better with pencils
than I do with guns.
Don't you think?
- [Man] Death caused
by massive blood loss.
He's been shot five
or six times at least.
- [Akai] Why the hell do you
guys have to drag me out here
and see this shit
before my breakfast?
He's not going anywhere.
- [Man] We did most
of the grunt work
before you got here, boss.
- Hmm, thanks for nothing.
Huh!
- [Man] Something wrong, sir?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Did you know him?
- [Sawa] Huh.
No, no.
- Wait a minute.
You know something?
We've been here.
I know it's a parking lot now,
but do you remember
about four years ago
when we investigated
that family homicide?
- Four years ago?
- [Man] Yeah, you remember,
that double murder.
Real messy investigation.
Only survivor was
the little girl.
I heard she got
adopted or something.
What a sexy little thing.
I'll bet she's hotter
than a pistol by now.
You got to remember her?
- Oburi.
(water pattering)
I got to tell you, Oburi,
I really didn't think you
had the balls to kill Kanie.
But we both know that in
your present condition,
you won't be able
to take me down.
Isn't that right?
I should have done
this a long time ago.
(gun clicking)
Awwh, come on kid, we both know
you don't have the strength
to pull that trigger.
How's the shoulder, Oburi?
(gun firing)
Sawa?
What's going on here, Sawa?
(gun firing)
(groaning)
My hand!
You bitch, you bitch!
Goddamned you!
- [Sawa] I killed Kanie.
Oburi is fine.
- You ungrateful whore,
you and Oburi set me up.
But why?
- You bastard!
I've waited a long
time for this.
This is for my
parents and for me.
- Sawa!
(gun firing)
(soft music)
- [Boy] Where have you been?
- [Girl] None of your business.
- [Boy] What do you mean
none of my business?
- [Girl] Exactly that,
it's none of your business.
(soft music)
- Be patient my friends.
Very soon, Oburi
will come home to us.
(cat purring)
Right?
(soft music)