[ZOEY] You nervous...?
Don't be afraid.
Our clients? No one
to be scared of.
A lot of them are
total pervs, though.
Masochists, too. Some of
'em'll really freak you out.
You two are not helping!
[rings]
[MADAME] Hey, new girl.
You've got a client.
See you later.
Best of luck!
Just try to relax.
It's room three‐oh‐four.
Here's the key.
[door clatters]
You must be Tilarna.
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[MOZELEEMAY]
Do you speak Earth tongue?
A little.
Come here.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Stop.
Don't take off your socks.
Those can stay on.
[TILARNA gasps]
I heard that you're
the new girl.
[TILARNA]
Yes.
Don't worry. I'm not
going to hurt you.
[doorbell rings]
What the...?
Dammit.
Police! You're under arrest.
There's gotta be some mistake,
officer, please.
I'm only here because‐‐
[KEI] Let me guess you just
happened to find yourself
in the room of a
high‐dollar brothel?
Come on, man. You sure as hell
don't look like the pizza guy.
[MOZELEEMAY] You must've
just gotten the wrong room!
You've got to hear me out.
[KEI]
Sure, we'll do that.
When we get you
down to the station,
you can tell us
anything you want.
It's closing time, Miss.
Get your things,
we're going home.
I didn't even lay a finger on
that girl. You can ask her!
Take him, boys.
[MALE COP A]
Come on, let's go.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Get your hands off me!
Come on!
What's your problem? Ow!
My problem is, you're late!
I had that creep's
greasy hands on my hair!
Moron! Dummy! Rakebye!
[KEI] We got what we needed
on the club, so who cares?
[TILARNA]
I care, stupid!
If you'd been
five seconds later,
I would have killed
that pervert!
[KEI] You better not say that
crap in court, got it?
Oh, hey, his stuff's still here.
Probably some info
hiding out in there.
Coal Mozeleemay.
That sounds familiar.
I've seen the name somewhere.
Some detective you are.
[KEI] Hm? Mayoral candidate.
A politician?
[TILARNA] I've seen him
on the news a few times.
Ha! Whaddaya know?
[REPORTERS chattering]
So Mister Mozeleemay.
Is it true that you were
discovered in a brothel?
Our sources say that some of
the girls on staff were minors.
Are you going to withdraw
from the mayoral election now?
I'll have the date for my
official press conference
on my blog soon.
My entire career, I've fought
for Semanians on issues
of poverty and discrimination!
My supporters are baffled by
these crude and baseless
allegations against me.
It's clearly a set up, and a
blatant abuse of power!
That is all!
[REPORTERS chattering]
Marla. I'm so sorry that you‐‐
[MARLA] It's okay, honey.
I know that you're innocent.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Yes.
[MARLA] I know it was a
mistake that you somehow
ended up there. One of your
opponents must have set you up.
Evil people are doing
whatever they can
to sabotage your campaign.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Forgive me.
[MARLA] We're going to
fight this together.
[MOZELEEMAY gasps]
Please don't touch me.
My supporters are baffled
by these crude and baseless
allegations against me.
It's clearly a set up,
and a blatant abuse of power!
That is all!
Liar!
Yeah, can you believe the crap
that's coming outta
that guy's mouth?
I doubt even your sword
could cut through bullshit
as thick as that.
I was there. I know what
he was trying to do.
Has he no shame?
[KEI] Just shows that
they're already spinning
their defense strategy.
It'll be hilarious when we
get you up on the stand.
What was it?
"I want your socks on,"
or something like that?
[KEI laughs]
Shut up, it isn't funny!
Not funny to me at all!
All powerful people
are just like him.
Don't waste your time getting
mad, or that'll drive you crazy.
[TILARNA]
You should be as mad as I am!
Oh I should?
[TILARNA] I never want
to see his face again!
I'll wait for you in the car.
[ZOEY]
Hey, Tilarna.
‐‐[camera snaps]
‐‐[TILARNA] Mm?
It's Zoey. You remember me?
[TILARNA gasps]
Yeah. Of course.
You just seem a
little different.
This is my normal look!
You got arrested
that night, too, right?
Did they let you go?
[TILARNA] Um, yes. I uh...
I had someone post bail for me.
[ZOEY]
Hmm. Hm‐hm‐hm...
Well, whatever. Look what
they gave me to wear.
A tracking device?
[ZOEY] Yeah. If you agree to it,
they discount your bail.
Hey, listen! Are you
free right now?
Yeah, I guess so.
[ZOEY grunts]
[TILARNA] I didn't know this
is what you had in mind!
[ZOEY]
Thank you, it's a huge help.
I got kicked out, so I
was pretty desperate.
A lot of the moving companies
around here can't be trusted.
Watch out, your TV
is gonna fall!
I told you it would!
[TILARNA] I'm sorry I just
kind of disappeared.
I had something come up.
No! Why would I be mad at you?
Uh, hey, I gotta go.
[ZOEY chuckles]
[grunts]
[ZOEY]
Who were you talking to?
On the phone? That was my mom.
Oh? Here. Your payment.
Is that all?
Huh? Oh, you want
this one, too?
No. So, did you find a place?
Sure did. Let's go.
[ZOEY gasps]
You can see the ocean!
[TILARNA]
Save your review for later!
Help me move this stuff!
Aw, that can wait.
Check out this view!
[TILARNA]
You're the one who's moving!
Don't you want to get
your new place set up?
Oh, come on, Tilarna,
lighten up!
[TILARNA yelps]
[camera clicks]
I've been meaning to
ask you, what is that?
It's a camera. Why?
I was just curious. Did you
take these with that, then?
[ZOEY] Yep, I'm a
photographer by trade.
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[speaks Farbani]
Even if you're just
being polite.
[TILARNA] I'm not. I don't quite
understand the technology, but,
the people you show
in this town.
It's like they seem so alive.
Like they're all living
inside this little frame.
[ZOEY] Huh? Jeez, Tilarna!
Stop, you're making me blush!
[TILARNA]
Is photography your real job?
No way! Man, I wish!
Just a hobby.
Although I do hope to
open an exhibit one day.
[TILARNA] If you do,
I'm gonna come see it, okay?
[ZOEY laughs] Would you like
a print of one of my pieces?
Really?
[ZOEY] As a thank you.
I owe you more than a burrito.
[TILARNA]
How can I choose, though?
[TILARNA gasps]
Not one of these. I want to
take a new photo for you.
[TILARNA]
Huh?
It'll take some time,
but I promise I'll do it.
[giggles]
[ZOEY]
For just a hundred dollars!
[TILARNA]
What?!
[ZOEY laughs]
I'm just kidding!
[door clatters]
[KEI]
Assistant Prosecutor Gardner!
[GARDNER]
Sergeant Matoba.
So, where is Exedilica?
Uh... She's out on patrol.
[ZIMMER]
On patrol?
Want me to call her?
No, this won't take
very long at all.
You can brief her later.
[ZIMMER] It's about the
Mozeleemay case.
His lawyer's been pitching
a fit to the media,
saying the police roughed
him up, that he's being framed.
The works.
Sounds typical.
What's the problem?
Oh, nobody here is implying
there's a problem.
Not right now. We do have
incriminating evidence on tape.
With the uh...
Socks.
[GARDNER] Exactly.
[KEI, GARDNER laugh]
Video alone isn't enough
proof these days.
There's gotta be something
more substantial.
A client list or money trail.
[exhales] Unfortunately,
they've covered their tracks
with encryption
and cryptocurrency.
We don't have enough yet to
convince a judge. Sucks.
[KEI] Right, but Mozeleemay
doesn't know that
at this point in
the game, does he?
Why not just bluff?
Yeah that's the plan.
If we push hard enough, there's
a real chance he'll give in.
We might be able
to get good intel
on some of his connections.
[ZIMMER]
I like it.
And we're the only ones with
any data from the brothel.
As far as I know. Is that right?
[KEI grunts]
Yeah, that should be true.
[GARDNER] Okay. I'll keep that
in mind as we move forward.
[KEI groans]
Hm?
[horn honks]
[TILARNA gasps, giggles]
Perfect timing.
[KEI]
Who was that?
[TILARNA] Zoey. A girl
from the brothel.
[KEI]
Oh, a sex worker.
She's planning to quit.
She and I have become friends.
[KEI] Friends, huh?
Does she know you're a cop?
[TILARNA]
There's no need to worry.
She still buys my cover:
I'm some rich girl who ran away
from home to the city.
[KEI]
Don't meet with her again.
[TILARNA]
What?
[KEI] I told you not to
meet with her again.
We've got Mozeleemay's
trial coming up soon.
And, if the DA gets lucky,
then that girl could end up
taking the stand
as a key witness.
[TILARNA] Why does that
mean we can't be friends?
[KEI] If she finds out
about you, she'll feel betrayed.
If that happens,
she may refuse to testify.
But I... I am a
Knight of Mirvor.
If she knows justice
is important to me.
I'm sure she won't
fault me for my choices.
[KEI]
That's ridiculous.
You think she'll be so impressed
she'll forget what you did?
[TILARNA grunts]
Listen to me, Tilarna:
don't get involved with the
people you're investigating.
But‐‐
You can't realistically be
friends with people like that.
You come from different worlds.
Different worlds, huh?
Sounds to me like you and I
can't be friends, either!
Well, no.
That's completely different.
It's not different!
It's the exact same thing!
She's my friend. I don't
care what you say.
[TILARNA]
Isn't it expensive?
[ZOEY]
Hm?
[TILARNA]
The rent for this place.
This location, the view.
[ZOEY]
I guess.
[TILARNA] Are you going
back to your old job?
[ZOEY]
I dunno. Are you?
Not sure.
[ZOEY]
You should give it up.
You ran away from home and your
rich parents, isn't that right?
[TILARNA gasps]
No judgment. I get it.
I, too, thirst for adventure.
It's powerful. That pull.
[TILARNA gasps]
[yawns]
Not getting enough sleep?
[TILARNA]
I don't know.
I know you've been hanging
out with Zoey every night‐‐
staying out way too late
for your own good.
You'd better knock it off‐‐
[TILARNA] Are you my
mother or something?
Huh?
That's what you
always say to me!
I don't want any
lectures from you.
[KEI]
Listen, here‐‐
‐‐[phone rings]
‐‐Hm?
Gardner.
[GARDNER]
We've got a problem.
[FEMALE NEWS ANCHOR A]
In responding to the data leak,
San‐Teresa poli‐‐
What the hell is this?
We don't know yet.
Most of the names on the list
that's in circulation are fake,
but some of them are real.
That's what makes
this all so bad.
So, Mozeleemay.
Now he can claim he's one
of the names that are faked?
The preliminary
hearing's coming up.
The judge is not going
to be happy about this.
We might not even be able
to prosecute him now.
[TILARNA] He won't face justice?
He'll get away with it?
Will you just relax?
All we have to do is locate
the source of the fake list.
But, still...
[ZIMMER]
We'll just keep working, then.
[GARDNER]
Yeah. Let's find these punks.
[MOZELEEMAY] Are you certain
you're not being followed?
No idea.
But you're the one who wanted
to meet in person, after all.
[MOZELEEMAY] Your information
was very helpful.
[ZOEY]
Then give me the rest.
What?
Not till you give
me all of the info.
The list you gave
me was incomplete.
For another 20 grand.
[MOZELEEMAY] It's already
in there. Count it for yourself.
Wow, you came prepared.
[gasps] There's more here
than there should be.
I think you know
what that's for.
[ZOEY]
Do I?
You agreed to meet 'cause
you wanted it, right?
[ZOEY]
Stop it, Mr. Mozeleemay.
[MOZELEEMAY] If all you
wanted was to make a deal,
you could have done it online.
But you haven't been able to get
me off your mind, have you?
[ZOEY]
That was just business.
I quit that line of work.
[MOZELEEMAY] Why not get back
into it, just one more time?
I can satisfy you. Wasn't I
always a good customer?
Huh? Yeah?
Look.
[MOZELEEMAY gasps]
[ZOEY] You know,
you're far too careless.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Give me that!
This one's free. Cheers.
You bitch. Screw you!
You'll pay for this!
I'm being nice. Trying to
teach you a valuable lesson.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Get out!
[ZOEY] Gladly, you'll get the
data you want very soon.
[MOZELEEMAY]
I said get out! Now!
[ZOEY grunts]
A pleasure!
[KEI] Uh‐huh. Got it. Take care
of that, too, would ya?
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI groans]
Another dead end.
I'm starting to think
Mozeleemay and his people
might not have access to
any of our data after all.
Kei.
Could the person
who's leaking it,
be one of the girls who
used to work at the club?
[KEI] You think one of the
workers had the client list?
I don't know.
If they were smart,
they'd get into another line
of work after getting busted.
[JAMIE] Listen, about that.
Can I butt in?
Whatcha got?
I was looking through
the hard drives of the PCs
we confiscated. Or copies
of them, specifically.
I know that. Spit it out.
[JAMIE] I was able to restore
the logs from the webcams.
I found photos of everyone
who accessed the client list
before we got it.
Most of the time it's the owner
and her cronies, but, look.
One of the girls also accessed
it several times. There she is.
[gasps]
Zoey.
[GARDNER] At this rate,
we won't be able to prosecute.
We have to find some way to
convince the judge what's real
and what's fabricated.
Or, at the very least...
...we'll have to prove
that the list going around
isn't actually a leak from
the police or the DA's office.
[KEI] I have an idea.
Try to buy me some time.
You okay?
[TILARNA]
With what?
[KEI] I can talk
to her, if you want.
[TILARNA] No. I think I
should be the one to do it.
[KEI sighs]
Okay.
[knocking]
Zoey...? Hello?
[gasps]
‐‐[camera snaps]
‐‐[TILARNA gasps]
Gorgeous! Don't move a muscle!
[TILARNA]
What are you doing?
I should be asking
you the same thing!
What is that sword for?
Never mind, look.
Remember what I promised you?
It's ready.
Zoey, we need to talk.
I had a hard time deciding
which one I should give to you.
In the end, I made
the obvious choice.
[TILARNA]
Zoey!
What?
[TILARNA] The client
list from the brothel.
Did you sell it to Mozeleemay?
What do you mean?
[TILARNA] Don't play dumb.
I know the answer.
You a cop...?
You are, aren't you?
I'm sorry I lied.
You disgust me.
It was a coincidence.
I promise‐‐
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI grunts]
[phone beeps]
I'll get them. Don't leave
her side, you hear me?
[TILARNA]
But‐‐
But nothing, shut up
and stay put!
[KEI]
Police! Freeze or you're dead!
I thought we were friends.
You're just a cop‐‐
[TILARNA]
We are friends!
I thought you had
quit that business!
[ZOEY] A rich girl like
you wouldn't understand.
Do you have any clue how hard it
is to go straight in this town?
It's almost impossible.
Zoey!
[MALE ASSASSIN A pants]
[ZOEY] I've got nothing
to be ashamed of.
[TILARNA]
Zoey, stay with me!
[ZOEY]
I didn't do anything.
Zoey, no!
Tell me who you're
working for! Tell me!
[sirens blaring]
Shit!
Yeah? Mozeleemay.
Oh. I see. Thank you.
[MOZELEEMAY] Our informant has
been shot. She's badly injured.
[MARLA]
Oh, is she?
[MOZELEEMAY]
If she doesn't make it,
I might avoid prosecution.
They won't be‐‐
[MOZELEEMAY]
Don't tell me. Was it you?
[MARLA]
What are you talking about?
[MOZELEEMAY sighs]
[MARLA] Don't think about
another thing, dear.
It's better that way.
[KEI] That look on
your face scares me.
Looks like you're about
to track Mozeleemay down
and beat the shit out of him.
He sent an assassin
to murder Zoey.
[KEI]
Can you prove it?
No, but... I know.
[KEI sighs] If that was
good enough to convict,
you and I wouldn't have jobs‐‐
[TILARNA]
Is this what you call justice?
Can't let him get away with it.
He deserves to pay for what
he did! Zoey is... She was my...
She was my friend,
and now she's‐‐
[gasps]
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.