[MALE TV PUNDIT A]
That's absurd!
If they don't like it here,
they're free to leave!
[MALE TV PUNDIT B]
Poverty is a form‐‐
[MALE TV HOST A] Why don't
we all just take a breath
and ask the people
what they think.
I'm voting for Coal Mozeleemay.
He cares about Semanians.
He's willing to fight
for their rights.
I heard that Kahns'
assassin was a Semanian.
I'm for Tourte. I want
those aliens outta here.
I don't really care
who wins it,
as long as they do something
about the crime here.
[MALE TV HOST A] Interest in
the upcoming election
continues to increase.
[MALE TV PUNDIT A]
It's what the people want!
Every day there are more
anti‐Semanian protests!
It's violence‐‐
[TILARNA] This is what
democracy looks like?
Turn that crap off, let's go.
[TILARNA]
Okay.
[NARRATOR] Fifteen years ago,
a hyperspace gate appeared
in the middle of
the Pacific Ocean.
Beyond that gate lay
a mysterious world
filled with fairies
and monsters.
The city of San‐Teresa
on Kariaena island
became known as
"Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of races,
cultures, and species,
the haves and the have‐nots.
San Teresa is the world's
newest "city of dreams."
But, in the shadows, lurk all
kinds of crimes and criminals.
Drugs. Prostitution.
Weapons smuggling.
The San‐Teresa
Metropolitan Police force
maintain a specialized unit
to deal with the seedy mayhem.
Interesting. I gotcha. Okay.
But you've still gotta do it.
Sorry. Nobody can get any info
on the weapon used to
assassinate Khans.
This gets weirder the
more that we dig.
What do you mean?
[KEI] They should at least
be able to figure out
whether the gun was
smuggled in or stolen.
They've checked all
the normal channels,
but nothing turned up.
Just dead ends.
[TILARNA] It's seems like a
common weapon. But, then...
[KEI] That campaign slogan
seems awkwardly suggestive
for a guy accused
of sex crimes,
but it kinda makes me
wanna vote for him.
[TILARNA]
It does?
Can't you tell when
I'm joking yet?
[KEI]
This is it.
[REPORTERS chattering]
Listen, Kei.
If we do get a chance to
meet with Mozeleemay...
[KEI] Do me a favor and
forget about Zoey for now.
I can't just‐‐
You're gonna have to
compartmentalize all that.
Are you picking up any "dead guy
puppet" stink around here?
[sniffs]
I don't think so.
At least, I smell no latena,
if that's what you mean.
Detective.
[KEI] Hm? Oh, hello.
Wait, don't tell me, Randall?
Yup. Kevin Randall.
Good memory you got there.
It's been a minute.
[KEI] This guy's a journalist
who interviewed me
once upon a time.
Can't really chat now, Kevin,
we're on the clock.
[RANDALL] So they got
you on the case.
Looking for the culprit in the
Kahns assassination, I mean.
[KEI]
No comment.
Hi, there! I'm guessing
you're Matoba's new partner.
You look like a Semanian,
how interesting.
My name is‐‐
No comment.
Hey, Detective. I'm gonna
shoot you an email.
You and I should talk soon.
[KEI]
Sure, sure, we'll do that.
[RANDALL] I'm serious,
it's really important.
You'll see in my message.
[MOZELEEMAY]
So, I told him,
"Fine, but you have
to vote for me!"
‐‐[knocking]
‐‐Yes, who's there?
[KEI] Detective Matoba.
San‐Teresa Police.
Nice to see you again.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Huh? Ahem. Uh, sorry, guys.
Give us the room for a few
minutes, if you wouldn't mind.
[MALE ATTENDANT A]
Sure.
[MOZELEEMAY] You said you're
with the San‐Teresa police?
[KEI] That's right. I'd like
to ask you a few questions
about the mayoral race.
I've nothing of note to
say on the subject.
If you have specific questions,
you're going to have
to email my staff.
[MARLA] Darling, what's the
harm in talking with them?
[MOZELEEMAY]
Marla.
You have nothing to hide,
so I see no reason why
you shouldn't cooperate.
Avoiding them just
looks suspicious.
You're a hero of the people.
A politician who stood up
to help Semanians
living in poverty.
Now then, Detective,
ask whatever you wish.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
I'd like to start with
Kahns' assassination.
Look, that‐‐
[MARLA]
Just awful, such a tragedy.
Since it happened,
we've increased security
measures substantially.
We're triple‐screening
everyone who comes onsite.
Good for you, but according
to the rumors.
You're gonna get at least
200,000 more votes
now that Kahns is
out of the race.
Got any comment on that?
That's true, but the new
polls suggest that Tourte
stands to gain 300,000.
My husband is in
danger of losing.
We've actually been
brainstorming ways
to turn things around.
Well, if Tourte is the
next one to bite the dust,
you won't have to worry
about it, will ya?
Listen, we Mozeleemays
are civilized people.
And if everyone resolved
differences of opinion
with guns, then the world
would devolve into a war zone.
If one possessed the power
to control the dead,
then weapons wouldn't
even be necessary.
[MOZELEEMAY]
Control the dead?
[MARLA]
Oh, yes.
I've heard there are mildey
out there like that.
However, you are aware that
regular Semanians don't possess
the ability to use it, right?
Bonah Exedilica.
[TILARNA grunts]
[MARLA] Now, I don't
mean to run you off,
but I'm afraid we're out
of time. Right, Darling?
[MOZELEEMAY]
Oh... Yes.
[KEI]
What's your take?
[TILARNA]
One thing is abundantly clear.
Mozeleemay is no leader, and his
wife is running the show.
[KEI]
You think?
She's got that man by the balls
and isn't afraid to squeeze.
If anything...
[TILARNA]
You felt it, too?
[KEI]
Yep. Marla Mozeleemay.
Her shit stinks worse
than her perfume.
So, then, Zoey was
a victim of...
Calm down. What we
need now is more info.
I think our next step
should be talking to Tourte.
[gunshots]
[CROWD yelling]
Wait! We need to figure
out what's going on!
[KEI] San‐Teresa police.
Help us out.
[CREWMAN A gasps]
Police? Well, um...
Who was just shot?
This is all so insane.
It was Mr. Mozeleemay.
The opener had finished, and he
was just taking the stage.
[CREWMAN B]
Whoa, check this out.
Can you follow the perp?
[CREWMAN A] We're trying to,
but I don't know if there's
a clear enough shot of him for
our AI to make a positive ID.
Ugh. I used his height and
clothing to run a search,
but that turned up 91 hits.
Wait, sorry, 92.
[KEI]
Walking speed.
[CREWMAN A]
Uh?
Eliminate people walking
over six miles per hour
or who pushed the
person in front of them.
After the crime,
assassins rarely run away.
They try to blend in
with the crowd instead.
[TILARNA grunts]
[CREWMAN A]
We've narrowed it down to 31.
[KEI] Let's look at the number
of times they turn around.
Remove anyone who does
it three times or more
within ten seconds.
[CREWMAN A]
Now it's 17.
People breathe through their
mouths when their heart rates
go up, so knock out
the mouth breathers.
[CREWMAN A]
Uh. We're down to three.
[KEI]
Let me see those close up.
[KEI grunts]
Where was this guy?
[CREWMAN A] In the first floor
lobby on the north side,
but he may have made
it outside by this point.
[TILARNA, KEI grunt]
[TILARNA]
Where's the north side lobby?
[KEI]
That way!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[MALE COP A]
This area's dangerous!
Follow police
instructions exactly!
[KEI] Police coming through!
Get out of the way, now!
[MALE COP B]
Remain calm! Do not panic!
[KEI]
Hey!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[gasps]
There he is! Kei!
[KEI gasps] You, there,
in the black suit, freeze!
Put your hands above
your head, nice and easy.
[TILARNA]
Shoot him, now!
[KEI grunts]
[CROWD gasps, chatters]
[KEI]
Shit!
Kizenya!
[MAN A gasps]
Dammit!
[CROWD gasps]
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA]
Let's follow him!
What the hell, something's off.
[DRIVER A]
Oh?
[KEI]
I need to borrow your car!
I've no cash!
What? No, your car! I'm a cop.
Please be careful with her!
[KEI]
Thanks for your cooperation!
Tilarna Exedilica's location.
[DRIVER B gasps]
[KEI]
V‐twenty‐one to headquarters!
I'm in pursuit of the suspect
who shot Coal Mozeleemay,
approaching the vicinity
of New Compton!
Suspect is a Semanian male,
approximately five foot nine,
in a black suit.
He's armed and dangerous.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Roger that.
Dispatching backup
to you right away.
[KEI]
Hurry, please!
[gasps]
Gotcha!
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA grunting]
[ASSASSIN grunts]
[shouts]
[ASSASSIN shouts]
[KEI grunts]
[KEI]
Don't move!
‐‐[gunshots]
‐‐[ASSASSIN groans]
[shouts]
[ASSASSIN grunts]
[KEI groans]
‐‐[slicing]
‐‐[ASSASSIN groans]
[TILARNA] Curses of Bedayah,
be visited upon your soul!
[KEI]
Don't do it!
Why did you stop me?
[KEI] 'Cause you were about
to murder him. Chill out.
What, the suspect's
fundamental rights again?
[KEI] I'm trying to help
you be a good person,
even if it feels
terrible in the moment.
[TILARNA]
I'll remember that. Although...
[TILARNA] ...do you
honestly expect this guy
to tell us who's behind it?
[KEI] Hey, you got any
last words? We'll listen.
Leeze.
‐‐[TILARNA gasps]
‐‐[KEI] Huh?
I thank you.
What the hell? His face is‐‐
[TILARNA]
Mildina zarhf.
[KEI]
What's that mean?
[TILARNA]
Transformation magic.
It seems to have worn off
partway through.
I noticed that at some
point in the pursuit.
[KEI]
Wait, this guy's an Earthling!
[TILARNA]
I know. And he's a warrior.
He was using mildey
all by himself.
No one controlled him
as he fought me.
Zelada's puppets
couldn't do that.
This man was something
I haven't encountered. Ever.
I thought humans
couldn't use magic.
You remember Elbaji? He had no
trouble with human science.
I think Earthlings can
plausibly do the reverse.
Perfect.
[TILARNA] Let me see that.
It smells strongly of latena.
[KEI] Hm? Okay, just don't
touch the trigger.
[TILARNA]
Take out the bullets first.
[KEI] This thing
is evidence, you know.
Don't tell anyone we did this.
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[KEI gasps]
What do you think you're doing?
Man, I told you
that was evidence!
[TILARNA]
It's Vaifaht steel.
What's that mean?
[speaks Farbani]
[KEI]
The gunpowder, too?
[TILARNA] How dare they.
Vaifaht steel is sacred.
It shouldn't be used
for such awful things.
[KEI] So, that's how this
guy smuggled a gun past
the security checkpoint.
You clever bastard.
[TILARNA] His methods
were beyond masterful.
The greatest vaifaht
blacksmiths in my country
couldn't make this.
A human? Unheard of.
[KEI]
All right, change it back.
[TILARNA]
But...
[KEI] Just do it. You can
play with it again later.
[TILARNA]
Oh, fine.
[speaks Farbani]
Something else I
should mention.
The last word he said
before he died, Leeze‐‐
[MALE FBI AGENT A]
Hold it right there!
[CHAN]
This the FBI.
Whoa, bossy.
Is that how they teach you
feds to treat a fellow cop?
I don't consider ineffectual
morons who murder their suspects
fellow cops, buddy.
[KEI]
Hey, what are you doing?
[CHAN] None of your business.
This case is our jurisdiction.
So, take your city cop ass home,
if you'd be so kind.
[KEI grunts]
[police sirens]
Took you jokers long enough.
You kept your mouth shut
like I told you to, right?
[TILARNA]
Kei. I'm tired of saying it.
Isn't there something you
need to tell me first?
[KEI chuckles] When you're
mad your face looks funny.
I am mad, aren't you?
[KEI] Nah, just regretting
my choices.
When Coal got shot I should
have pretended to be deaf
and gone out for
a nice big steak.
[TILARNA] Tsk! You're pathetic.
Unworthy of upholding justice!
[ZIMMER]
Quit your bickering you two.
I want a report from both of
you jerks by 19:00 tomorrow.
[KEI]
Yeah, and then what?
Are you gonna take us off
the case or something?
[ZIMMER]
Oh, you wish, don'tcha?
We're gonna solve
this one as a team.
They may have made
off with the body,
but we have the photo you
took of the guy's face.
Not a great clue,
but it's something.
I did good police work, huh?
Don't be a dumbass, Kei.
If you'd done a better job
cornering the suspect,
we might have gotten
more out of him.
Well, you're not wrong.
But, Chief! That wasn't
a possibility here!
Our opponent was
a skilled warrior
who could even use mildey!
We stopped him from escaping!
Yeah, yeah... Ugh.
Coal Mozeleemay is dead.
The Paramedics were
able to transport him
to Patterson Hospital,
but he died there.
[KEI]
What a nightmare.
[ZIMMER]
The commissioner's getting ready
to give a press conference.
If you're curious, you can
ask your ex about it later.
She's probably surrounded
by a bunch of VIPs,
telling them the size of
the guy's ass again.
[KEI]
Sounds fun, but no.
C'mon, Tilarna,
back to the station.
[TILARNA]
Right.
[ZIMMER]
Matoba!
Yeah, what is it?
You sure your ass ain't
hiding something?
Man, you're good.
Yeah, we are, actually.
[ZIMMER]
Well?
Listen. I can't tell you here.
Let's talk about it
back at the office.
It's rather difficult
to explain.
Earthlings have trouble with
the concept of vaifaht steel.
The closest thing you have in
your world is the material
you just explained to me:
the shape‐memory alloys.
However, vaifaht steel changes
in response to latena,
rather than temperature.
[ZIMMER] So, it's like a
magic metal? Ridiculous!
This whole thing's ridiculous!
Hey, calm your tits.
[ZIMMER grumbles]
[TILARNA] Vaifaht steel is
extracted from certain trees,
and its raw form has a
texture similar to cotton.
From that, it's processed
into thin, strong fibers.
[TONY] I get it. Then you
weave it, like cloth.
[TILARNA]
Correct.
It's woven into cloth
with a special loom.
At this point,
the final shape of the item
you're making is decided.
Occasionally,
it's made into art,
but most of the time,
it's weapons.
[speaks Farbani]
[ALL gasp]
[JAMIE] So, um, the mass
of the object itself
doesn't really change?
[speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA]
As my fellow coworkers,
you get the special
privilege of touching it.
‐‐[TONY] Oh?
‐‐[JAMIE] Huh?
[CAMMY]
Huh?
[ZIMMER growls]
[TONY]
Heavy!
[TILARNA] All vaifaht steel
weapons are woven by
specially trained
Lahge craftsmen.
No two weapons in the
universe are alike.
[JAMIE grunts] I'm amazed
your shoulders don't get all
knotted up, wearing this
all the time.
[TILARNA] Well, I do train
on a daily basis.
That explains why
you're so short.
That thing stunted your growth.
[TILARNA grunts]
[TONY]
Just to make sure I understand.
You're saying vaifaht steel
items, weapons and other things,
are extremely difficult to make.
[TILARNA]
Correct.
Creating something with
precision parts, like a gun,
for example,
would be impossible,
even for a Lahge craftsman.
Now you know why
this is so strange.
[JAMIE] So, do you think
that gun is maybe a hybrid
of Earth and Semanian
technology, then?
Could it be possible that one of
these Lahge guys is working
with someone from Earth?
I guess... Possibly.
I don't quite see how a Semanian
could make a weapon like that.
Not without the help of someone
well‐versed in your technology.
[clap]
[ZIMMER] Okay, we know what
the next step is, then.
Get to work investigating.
Dismissed. Get lost.
Hold on, Matoba.
[KEI]
Yeah, what?
I want you to pay Tourte
a visit tomorrow
and ask some questions.
I secured permission from his
people for an interview.
[KEI yawns]
[TILARNA]
What do you want me to say?
I don't know! I don't! I‐‐
I'm hanging up.
Damn, who was that?
[TILARNA] An officer
from precinct 14.
They got a complaint from the
owner of the three‐wheeler
you commandeered.
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA] They said he was
furious about the whole thing.
What should we do?
[KEI]
Hm. Yeah let's just ignore that.
[PROTESTORS]
Go home! Go home! E. T. go home!
Go home! Go home!
E. T. go home...!
[TILARNA exhales]
[KEI sighs] I don't want
any trouble, okay?
Ignore that, too.
[TILARNA]
Yeah, I know.
[CROWD chanting continues]
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.