[PROTESTORS shouting]
[KEI] Domingo Tourte.
Got his start as a boxer
or competitive yachter
or something,
then became an entrepreneur.
He's been in politics for
about ten years or so.
Well, what is he like?
Since Kahns and
Mozeleemay are dead,
isn't he the last major
candidate in the race.
Tourte's your
typical right‐winger.
He gets in trouble and gets
bashed in the media for his
extremist comments, but some
people are crazy about him.
Why, though?
[KEI]
'Cause his position is simple.
[TOURTE] A Semanian cop, huh?
Well, now I've seen everything.
Does she even have the capacity
to understand Earth law?
[TILARNA gasps] I understand
the 15th amendment.
I've heard that one
about a million times.
Who was it that killed Kahns?
A Semanian, of course.
They have trouble
grasping the rules here.
That's why they always turn to
crime, or accept below‐poverty
wages, stealing jobs and money
from hard‐working Earthlings.
For some reason, they think
the city belongs to them now.
The city that Earthlings built.
They'd do well to remember that.
This land originally
belonged to Semanians.
[TOURTE]
That's a lie. You're on Earth.
On an island in the
Pacific Ocean.
If you want the seawater and
fish that got sent to your world
from ours, you can have it.
Do you have no shame?
Sounds like another of your
made‐up earth rules.
All right, calm down.
Listen, little girl.
The government's taken care
of the Semanians who
lived here before.
They were paid reparations.
We even have a system
to send you back.
But to no one's surprise, none
of you ever want to go home.
And you know why?
It's because you like the way
we do things better here.
You want to take
advantage of Earth's
advanced civilization so
you can live the good life.
That's a lie!
[TOURTE]
No, it's the truth.
My point of view is
incredibly simple.
Sure, enjoy our world,
but you had better obey
the law of the land,
don't like it, leave.
That's all I'm saying.
[TILARNA gasps]
[TOURTE] So, you tell me,
is anything I said wrong?
[TILARNA]
But, it's just‐‐
[KEI]
I apologize, Mr. Tourte,
but I think she learned a thing
or two from what you said.
I hope so, for her sake.
Hey, Dom. It's time to head out.
[TOURTE grunts]
Mind if I ask you
one last thing?
If it's really the last thing,
and not a three‐parter,
then, sure.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Just this.
When you think about what
you consider yourself first,
would you say you put
being a politician
before being an Earthling?
[TOURTE]
Hm.
Well, Sergeant Matoba,
that's a very unique question.
Never gotten that before.
[KEI] Thank you.
What's your answer?
[TOURTE] Hm. I guess I'd
have to say a politician.
You wouldn't say Earthling?
[TOURTE] Correct.
I believe that's who I am.
Even if I had been born in
the other world, odds are,
I would have chosen
the same path.
Ah. Thank you for
your cooperation.
[TILARNA grunts, speaks Farbani]
Domingo Tourte is every bit
as bad as people said,
and you're no better than him!
[KEI sighs]
"I think she learned a thing
or two from what you said."
How dare you?
I've got nothing to learn from
that puffed up old bigot!
What do you want from me?
I blame the idiot
who picked a fight
with the man we
were questioning.
[TILARNA] You've got no
right to call me an idiot!
Why not? You are one.
Anyway, did you learn
anything in there?
I mean, do you think
Tourte's behind all this?
Not sure.
There weren't any dead people
around him, I know that.
And there wasn't any latena,
or, I didn't smell it.
I see.
Kei, that last bit.
What was the question about?
Do you remember
the night Roth died?
The last conversation
I had with him?
[TILARNA]
Yeah. He said the opposite.
That being an Earthlings
was more important to him
than being a police officer.
[KEI] He abandoned his duties
because he was concerned
about Earth's future.
And, knowing him,
I'm sure he wrestled with
that decision a lot.
Remembering that
made me curious.
I wondered how Tourte would
answer the same question.
[TILARNA] So then you think
he's innocent because
he answered the way he did?
[KEI sighs]
I wouldn't go as far as that.
But it is something
to keep in mind.
[TILARNA]
Kei.
[KEI]
Yeah, what is it?
Just. No, never mind.
[STREET WOMAN A]
Um. Yeah, I've seen him.
Like, last week? I wanna say
he's one of Lu's clients.
[CAMMY]
Lu? You serious?
[STREET WOMAN A]
Maybe? Ugh, I can't be sure.
I only caught a quick glimpse
of him when she was getting
into his car, so who knows?
There's no answer.
I think we'll just have to
ask her face to face, then.
Thanks, hon. Bye!
That was fun, gimme a heads
up for the next raid!
[giggles]
[GODNOV] A venture company, huh?
That's interesting.
[TONY]
Yeah, but there's a ton of 'em.
Gonna be hard to sort through.
[GODNOV]
You have no connections?
[TONY sigjs] Well, there is this
one guy I know who works in
high‐tech venture capital, but
he's an old flame from college.
[GODNOV]
Ah. Awkward.
[TONY] If Ken found out
I was contacting an ex,
he'd be pissed, and no
one wants that, trust me.
Wait. Who is Ken?
He's my boyfriend, duh.
He does hair.
Huh? What happened
to the hot dancer?
[TONY]
Mike? Yeah, don't ask.
[GODNOV]
I'm impressed.
You go through them
like toilet paper.
How dare you?
I've told you a million times,
I'm looking for true love!
It's this damn job,
if you must know.
The hours are terrible,
and it's just so dangerous!
Hm?
[GODNOV]
You can use my phone.
That way Ken won't find
out you called an ex.
Go, get on with it.
[TONY]
Hmph!
Ugh, again? Another riot,
this time in Eastrock Park.
A riot?
A clash broke out between
protestors and police.
Some guys got too riled up and
started tearing things apart.
An appliance store,
a drug store.
[JAMIE] Look. There's footage.
That's from ten minutes ago.
Apparently there's similar stuff
happening all over the city.
[CAMMY]
Damn, you're right.
Ugh, how awful. Looks like
somebody died. A Semanian, too.
[MAN A]
Shut up, bitch!
[LU] I am sick and
tired of your shit!
[MAN A] But you love my money!
[LU] Kill me if you want.
I don't care!
[knocking]
Hey, shut the hell up in there!
Take your lovers' quarrel
somewhere else!
[MAN A]
What? Piss off!
What'd you say to me?
Fine, then, how 'bout
I call the cops?
[MAN A]
Fine, do it!
N‐Nah, wait. Just hold
on a second. Damn.
So, who the hell
are you bitches?
Lu's co‐workers or something?
She ain't here, so get lost.
Yeah, well, we're here to
take out the trash, baby dick.
You wanna say that
shit to me again?
Why, are you deaf
and dickless?
I called you baby dick, as in
a coward with a tiny penis
who gets off on
beating up women.
[MAN growls]
What, bitch? You're dead!
[grunting]
[CAMMY]
Time for bed.
[LU gasps]
Cammy! Jamie!
[JAMIE, CAMMY chuckle]
[LU sobs]
Thank you so much, Cammy!
You're so strong‐‐it's amazing.
[CAMMY]
That'll teach him.
[LU chuckles] I love you!
Please marry me?
You gotta get out of
the business first.
So. I have a few questions.
They're about a client
of yours from last week.
This guy. Know him?
[LU] Uh. Yeah. I never got
a name from him, though.
Do you remember
any details? Any at all.
[LU]
Well, let's see.
He had good manners,
and amazing stamina, too.
[CAMMY] He didn't tell you
anything about himself?
Like where he's from,
or what he does.
[LU] Nope. He was quieter
than most of 'em.
H‐Hold on. Right! He did
have a tattoo on his arm.
Right here. A bulldog.
It looked mean and wore a
stupid‐looking hat.
That is something, but tattoos
are pretty common these days.
[JAMIE] Might be a clue
that he's a marine, though.
[CAMMY]
Yeah, why?
Because, bulldogs are
kind of an unofficial mascot
for the marine corps.
And if the tattoo was below
the guys' elbow, then...
...he may have joined
a while ago.
The rules changed recently.
They're not allowed to have
tattoos that can't be covered
by a t‐shirt now.
Are you into military guys?
No, I'm just a
Wikipedia addict.
I learned about all that Marine
corps business, when I fell down
a rabbit hole researching
the M4 carbine for work.
Oh. So, it went, M4 carbine,
American Military Weapons,
Marine Corps?
[JAMIE] Mm‐mm. M4 carbine,
American military weapons,
inertial navigation system,
laser gyro, Sagnac Effect,
Einstein, gravity, astronomy,
solar system, Oort cloud,
asteroid, dinosaurs, Saurischia,
pelvis, fetus, Cesarean Section,
bulldog, and Marine.
[CAMMY, LU gasp]
Y'know. One thing's
quite clear to me.
[KEI]
Mm?
As far as I can tell, I am an
incredibly fortunate Semanian.
[KEI chuckles]
Where is this coming from?
Think about the people
I deal with every day.
Nobody really treats
me like an alien.
Sure, Inspector Zimmer
may make comments,
but he still treats
me fairly, overall.
[KEI]
Yeah, that's his way.
Even O'Neill and the others.
They do make fun of where
I come from sometimes,
but I know they don't
mean any harm by it.
[KEI sighs]
[KEI] Remember the
first time we met Kenny?
Same day I met you.
[TILARNA]
Uh. Yeah. In O'Neil's club.
He said, "You're an alien.
I really hate those guys."
[KEI] He still feels that way.
Doesn't like Semanians.
A drunk one stabbed him once.
That's the only reason why.
[TILARNA]
I had no idea.
He's never said
anything about it to me.
[KEI chuckles] He would
never mention that to you.
He likes you. He doesn't want
you to feel weird around him
or act differently.
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI] Anyway. I bring
this up because,
since you started coming
around more often,
he's even been nicer to the
other Semanian customers.
That's not nothing, you know?
If he were to vote‐‐
not that I think he will‐‐
he wouldn't vote for Tourte,
I can tell you that much.
Does that make you feel better?
Yeah, it does. Thank you.
[NEWSCASTER A] Protests across
the city are escalating
in number and intensity,
and clashes with police
are becoming more
and more frequent.
The riot in Eastrock Park
is due in large part
to the recent assassination
of Cole Mozeleemay,
former mayoral candidate
and staunch supporter of
Semanian rights.
His wife, Marla Mozeleemay,
has entered the race in
his stead, and is gaining...
[TILARNA] What? His wife
is running for mayor now?
Is that kind of thing
even allowed?
She was probably already
registered as an alternate.
They spent a ton of
dough in this race,
and they weren't about to
flush all that down the john.
I'm sure she didn't
have a choice.
She's getting a
sympathy boost,
but her policies are
pretty well thought out.
I think she's the best candidate
in the race, to be honest.
Increased wages
for Semanians,
expanded vocational
training programs,
dozens of new free
clinics all over the city,
you get the gist.
She's got great ideas.
Tilarna?
[TILARNA] To a lot of
Semanians in San‐Teresa,
I can imagine she
represents a renewed hope.
[KEI]
Yeah, you're right.
[TILARNA] But, even though
I don't have any proof,
I have this gut feeling she's
the one who hired the assassin
who murdered Zoey.
Still, that doesn't mean I
would ever vote for Tourte.
It's all so confusing. I don't
know what to think anymore.
Sounds like you're starting
to grasp how democracy works.
What do you mean?
Politics is never ideal.
More often than not,
you're just picking the
lesser of two evils.
[TILARNA sighs]
[KEI] Right, I see.
That's good news, I guess.
Okay, talk later.
What news?
[KEI] There's been a pretty big
break on the vaifaht steel
side of things, and Cammy and
Jamie think they've uncovered
a clue about the assassin.
I'm glad.
[phone rings]
[KEI]
Hello?
[RANDALL] Detective Matoba!
It's me Randall!
Did you read my message?
Ah, not yet. Sorry, man.
[RANDALL] Will you hurry up
and read it? Like, right now?
Can't, Randall, I'm driving.
And plus, I've got a ton of
other work to catch up on.
[RANDALL] Forget your
other work! This is serious!
Sorry. I'm in a bad way.
I've been freaking out
all morning‐‐not pretty.
I have this creepy feeling,
like someone's watching me.
[KEI]
Watching you?
[RANDALL]
My computer's acting weird, too.
My anti‐virus software
keeps popping up
with strange warnings.
[KEI]
Stay on the line.
[KEI] Hey, man. I don't have
any messages from you.
[RANDALL]
What? That can't be!
I swear, I sent it
around midnight.
Just look harder!
I did, there's nothing.
I'm sure. So, what's going on?
[RANDALL] Look, It's something
really bad.
I can't say over the phone.
Can we meet now? Please?
[KEI] I gotcha. Do you remember
the place you interviewed me
back when we first met?
[RANDALL] Yeah, I think so.
It was at White and‐‐
[KEI] Don't say it! I just
wanted to make sure you knew.
I'll meet you there.
Meanwhile, turn off
your phone, just in case.
[RANDALL]
Right. See you soon.
[ZIMMER] Moirai Materials?
That's an interesting name.
[TONY] A venture capital company
that's made a fortune off
metal and carbon
fiber technology.
My source says it's the only
place that could handle
something like vaifaht steel.
Got it. Go ahead and
take care of things.
[TONY]
Will do. I'm pulling up now.
Hey, Chief! We've got a
positive ID on that assassin!
Well, we're 90 percent sure!
[ZIMMER] Sergeant Ethan Dole.
Member of Third marine division.
Force Recon Unit.
Served in the second
Farbani Conflict,
and then he went MIA
in Operation Mirage?
[CAMMY] He's technically
considered dead which is why
the department's database
didn't pull up a match.
We were working in the
middle of the night,
and the marines were
no help whatsoever.
But, we did a ton of research,
and found this!
Why didn't you think to
ask me for help?
[CAMMY, JAMIE]
Hm?
[ZIMMER]
I'm a former marine, after all.
I've got all kinds
of connections.
I know a guy who works
in personnel over at
Norfolk Marine Command. He could
have found this in no time.
What the hell? Why would
you hide that from us?
Jeez. I wasn't
hiding anything!
Jerk! We had no idea!
If we had, we would have woken
your ass up at three AM
to ask you about it!
Maybe then we could have gotten
at least a little sleep!
[ZIMMER] Um, well. I don't
know what to say. I'm sorry?
Anyway, all that crap aside.
This guy went missing
in Semanian territory
during the conflict
six years ago.
Now he just shows up as an
assassin with the ability
to use magic, not to mention
a crazy‐ass sword.
Oh, like, what the hell?
Yep, it makes no damn sense.
Matoba and Exedilica said
they were gonna be late
for the meeting, huh?
[JAMIE]
Right.
They mentioned something
about a new lead, I think.
Okay. We'll talk more about it
as soon as they and
McBee's team get back.
You two go take a nap.
[CAMMY, JAMIE sigh]
[TONY] All right. We're here
as investors today
because a friend told us
about the company. Clear?
[GODNOV]
What a pain in the ass.
[TONY]
Come on, honey, smile!
You've got the worst case
of resting bitch face
I've ever seen. You're much
prettier with a grin.
[GODNOV]
Heh!
[TONY]
More, show me those teeth.
[GODNOV]
Heh!
[TONY] Okay, you look like a
moron now. Perfect. Keep it up.
It hurts.
Think about your kid, all right?
Imagine he's here now, saying,
"Daddy, I love you!"
It doesn't hurt!
Okay, let's do this.
[RANDALL grunts]
Ahem... Uh...?
Detective Matoba!
Don't make a scene,
just sit back down.
Right. You watch our backs.
Got it.
So, what?
[RANDALL] The email that
I sent you, or, tried to.
It was in regard to a certain,
recent scandal.
A scandal? Which one?
It involves Cole
Mozeleemay's wife.
Marla?
[RANDALL] Yep. She's been
meeting with this man.
A secret tryst in a fancy hotel.
I got the photos to prove it.
[KEI] Ooh, juicy. Doesn't look
like a planning meeting for her
husband's campaign, does it?
[RANDALL] Detective Matoba!
This is a serious situation!
[KEI] So, Marla was
cheating on her husband.
What's that got to do with me?
[RANDALL]
What do you mean?
You're the one who busted
her husband at a brothel,
didn't you? I thought you
might know more about this.
Like, maybe the guy in the
picture was one of our
undercover agents or something.
Sorry, I've never seen this guy.
Kei?
[KEI] Hm... A bulldog?
Cammy mentioned that!
[RANDALL] This is bad.
I'm freaking out.
I knew this guy was involved
in the case somehow.
I'm right about that, aren't I?
[KEI]
Yeah, sure looks that way.
This is the guy who
assassinated Mozeleemay.
[RANDALL] Shit! They're gonna
bump me off next!
You telling me I'm in possession
of photographic evidence
showing the assassin conspiring
with the target's wife?
[KEI]
Come on, Randall, calm down.
Hey! Listen to me!
You have the
original image data?
No, I deleted it,
the data in the cloud, too.
I printed it out so I
could show it to you,
but that's the only
remaining copy there is.
[KEI sighs]
Look. Now there're two copies.
And if I post it to some social
media site, there'll be more.
There's nothing to
be afraid of now.
What are you talking about they
were able to delete the email
I tried to send to you!
This organization is huge!
They'll delete it all!
There's no way we can beat them!
[KEI] Randall, please,
you have to stay calm!
I'm perfectly calm!
Kei.
What now?
Uh...
[CHAN]
FBI. Hands above your head.
[RANDALL]
Don't shoot. Don't shoot!
[KEI]
You guys again? Great.
[TILARNA gasps]
Come on, Tilarna,
keep it sheathed.
[TILARNA] But Kei.
One of them is a corpse.
Wait, which one?
[TILARNA] I can't tell just yet,
the latena is distorted.
[KEI]
Still. Don't do anything rash.
Put down your sword.
[TILARNA grunts, speaks Farbani]
So, Matoba. Why do we
keep meeting like this?
[KEI]
Hey, I never got your name.
I'm sorry, FBI Special
Agent Ronald Chan.
You're coming with us now.
How 'bout you take
off the handcuffs?
One of the men with you...
He's a ticking time bomb.
Time bomb, huh?
A drug addict.
Take him away.
[KEI] You're impeding
an investigation!
You can't just‐‐
Kei. I figured out
who the corpse is.
Yeah? Which one is it?
[TILARNA]
All of them.
Everybody except
the main agent, Chan.
You kidding me?
[gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
[ZELADA] Why, hello there,
Lady Exedilica.
[TILARNA gasps]
Zelada!
[KEI gasps]
It's lovely to see
you again, like this.
[KEI, TILARNA gasp]
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.