Is that thing... a mummy?
[TILARNA] It appears to be
some kind of princess to me.
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A slurping]
[gasps]
[CECIL screams]
Cecil, no!
The body! Chapman is...
[TILARNA gasps]
[TILARNA grunts]
[TILARNA]
Did I...?
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A growls]
[TILARNA shouts, grunts]
Damn you, monster!
[KEI]
Tilarna!
Stay back!
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A growling]
[grunts]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A grunting]
[KEI]
Shit!
[KEI] What the hell
was that thing?
Lauden neiven.
Your people refer to
them as vampires.
Wait, a vampire?
I just figured she was
some kind of exhibitionist.
[POLICE chattering]
[KEI]
The naked lady who attacked us
was actually the dried‐up
corpse we found before?
Did she plump up like an
instant noodle or what?
[TILARNA]
It wasn't a corpse.
Lauden neiven possess terrifying
powers of regeneration.
They can repair damage to their
bodies by absorbing latena,
by draining the
life force of humans.
[KEI gasps]
So there really are vampires.
They were thought
to be eradicated.
It seems one must have survived.
I should have been
more cautious.
I should have
realized it sooner.
I failed and someone died.
[KEI]
You still saved Cecil, though.
[TILARNA]
Yes, but...
[KEI]
Cut yourself some slack.
[TILARNA gasps]
Anyway, the more
important issue right now
is that the monster is still
on the loose somewhere.
We've got a warrant out, but...
[TILARNA] There's no way your
forces will be able to
capture her with doreany
weaponry alone.
[KEI]
You sure?
My gun and your sword seemed
to mess her up pretty good.
I don't think she'd last long
under fire from a whole
SWAT team.
[TILARNA]
SWAT?
See those guys?
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI] Handpicked for excellence
in physical condition
and marksmanship.
If a slob like me can hurt her,
SWAT will end her.
[TILARNA exhales] It's not
a matter of marksmanship.
What matters is your
sense of smell in combat.
Like when you came down
to save me and brought
a fire extinguisher.
That was just... I don't know.
I guess you could
call it a hunch.
[TILARNA] That's what I
mean by sense of smell.
Yours is quite formidable,
so I guess there is one
respectable thing about you.
[KEI]
That was almost a compliment.
[speaks Farbani]
But I'm still worried
about the wellbeing
of those other bolicemen.
I see.
[TILARNA]
These creatures are terrifying.
[KEI grunts]
Hey, you okay?
I'm fine, just getting
a ride home.
Oh, and Tilarna, thanks so much.
[TILARNA]
Mm.
Seems they've found
another victim.
[KEI]
Where?
[SUPERINTENDENT A]
Alamo Park.
She killed a truck driver.
In front of witnesses, too.
[KEI] Alamo? That's
outside the perimeter.
How'd she get that far?
[ZIMMER] You're here to
help us figure that out.
Could she move that fast
with one arm gone
and a bunch of holes in her?
I don't know.
They're an ancient race.
[SUPERINTENDENT A] "I don't
know" isn't gonna cut it here.
If we don't find her,
more people die.
What's your solution?
[TILARNA]
Right now, we're‐‐
[SUPERINTENDENT A] This is why I
was against this from the start.
It's ridiculous trying
to put Semanians
on a human police force.
Their brains are different.
They don't know how to
live in a civilized society.
So now we gotta babysit
this little brat‐‐
[ZIMMER] That's enough out
of you, Superintendent.
What are you gonna
do to fix this,
besides bitching and
moaning like a baby?
[SUPERINTENDENT A]
What was that?
[ZIMMER] Cecil Epps would
be dead if that girl hadn't
been there, the vampire would
still be on the streets now,
and we wouldn't know
about it till morning.
[TILARNA gasps]
[ZIMMER] But you didn't even
think about how much deeper
we could be in this shit.
[SUPERINTENDENT A gasps]
Inspector Zimmer,
with all due respect‐‐
Shut your mouth! You don't
discipline my people!
If you've got a problem with
Exedilica, you come to me.
[SUPERINTENDENT A gasps]
[ZIMMER]
Let's go.
Didn't see that coming.
[ZIMMER]
That kid's always been a punk.
Just about piss his
drawers every shift back
when he joined LAPD.
You got something to
say about it, Matoba?
Not a thing, sir
[ZIMMER] Assuming makes
an ass out of you, son.
[KEI chuckles]
Sir, yes, sir.
[ZIMMER] So how the hell are
we gonna find this thing?
[KEI] I don't think the
vampire knows how to pass
for a human.
She's probably just trying
to stay out of sight.
A K‐9 unit could track her.
[ZIMMER] We've already
got the dogs out there.
[KEI]
There's a better one right here.
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI] So she killed the guy
driving the truck she was in,
and ran it into a pole.
Our vampire doesn't
seem too smart.
I'm not so sure.
She didn't attack the
witnesses after the crash.
Maybe she meant
for this to happen.
[KEI]
Let's ask 'em.
[MALE WITNESS A] Huh? No,
she definitely had both arms.
[TILARNA]
She must have regenerated it.
She got out of the truck and I
swear she looked straight at us.
But then she took off.
Going that way.
[KEI] Was the woman naked
when she left the scene?
[MALE WITNESS A]
I actually couldn't tell.
It kind of looked like she
had a little black dress on.
[FEMALE WITNESS A]
But not like a normal dress!
There was this haze
floating around it.
And it kinda shimmered,
like, I don't know...
Like a flame?
[FEMALE WITNESS A]
Oh my god, exactly!
It was like black flames
wrapped around her body!
"Vau e Deie."
[KEI]
"Vau e..."
What's that?
[TILARNA] It's a basic
illusion spell that can also
be worn as clothing.
Meaning, she's recovered
enough of her powers
that she's now able
to use magic again.
Do you know how to do
that spell? The Val, er. Vow.
[TILARNA]
Vau e Deie, and I do.
Can you show me?
[TILARNA] No I can't. It won't
work if I have my clothes on,
and it disappears
if you're not focused.
[KEI]
Is that so.
[TILARNA]
Don't imagine it.
[KEI]
Don't flatter yourself.
No. I can see it on your face!
You were picturing me naked!
Ugh. What gives a commoner
the right to even think about
seeing me nude? Get my body
out of your filthy mind‐‐
[KEI]
Whatever man, enough.
We've got a vampire to
catch here. Where'd she go?
Ah, yeah, you're right.
Let me see.
[TILARNA]
That big building.
[KEI]
That's called a shopping mall.
[TILARNA]
I think she's hiding there.
The witnesses said she took
off the other way, though.
The dogs, too.
[TILARNA] But if she wanted
a view of this area,
she would have gone
to that building.
[KEI] So what you're getting
at is she left the body
for us to find because she
wanted to see how the cops
would react.
Yes. She's done feeding for now.
So she'll be trying to gather
information about the city.
I don't think she's worried
about anyone catching her.
Even if they manage
to surround her.
[KEI]
I see. Good detective work.
That's sarcasm.
[KEI]
No, I'm genuinely impressed.
Liar. I know when you're
making fun of me, you vile man.
[KEI]
On my life, I swear it's true.
Screw it, let's just
get to the mall.
[KEI]
Yes, everyone.
As many guys as you
can give me, right now.
Just make sure nobody
goes in alone.
And if you run into her,
don't try to catch her.
Kei.
[KEI]
One second.
[TILARNA] I picked up
the smell of her latena.
This is where she went inside.
[KEI]
Got it.
[TONY] Security cameras
aren't showing a thing.
She hasn't tripped any
of the lasers, either.
[KEI]
You sure?
[TONY] You think vampires
can see infrared?
[KEI] We'll just have
to go in after her.
Let me know if you
pick something up.
Anything?
Yes, she's close by.
Not sure what direction.
A trap?
Maybe. Stay sharp.
[KEI]
You walk slow.
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI]
Hm?
[TILARNA]
Quit stepping on me!
[KEI]
Hm?
[TILARNA]
It's stronger here.
[KEI]
What is?
[TILARNA]
Her presence. Be careful.
How much more careful can I be?
[TILARNA]
Kei!
[chuckles]
[KEI gasps, grunts]
Kei!
[yells]
Damn you!
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A laughs]
[TILARNA grunting]
Kei! Hey, Kei!
Come on, you're alright!
Wake up!
No luck. Try kissing him, Tony.
Sleeping Beauty kind of thing?
Um, Alex. That's called
sexual harassment.
[GODNOV] You doing it
or me saying it‐‐
[TONY]
Oh! Oh, thank god, he's awake!
[KEI coughs]
[KEI grunts] Tony. Godnov.
What are you guys doing here?
[KEI coughs]
[TONY] You stopped responding,
so we came in after you,
and found you just floating
there in the fountain.
[KEI grunts]
Where's Tilarna?
[TONY] I don't know.
We didn't see her.
[KEI grunts]
Then she was taken.
The piece of shit vampire.
It must have run off with her.
[coughs]
I'm gonna take that
thing out, no matter what.
You fell from all
the way up there?
How are you still alive?
[KEI]
Got a light?
[TONY]
No. I don't smoke.
[KEI]
How are you still alive?
[grunts, gasps]
[BOTH speaking Farbani]
[TILARNA grunts]
[KEI]
Tilarna!
[TILARNA]
Kei!
[KEI speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA]
No! She's invincible right now!
[speaks Farbani]
[MALE SWAT A grunts]
Can't see her!
Withdraw. All of you back off!
[grunts]
[KEI]
There. We've got her.
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A groans]
[KEI] Hit her with
everything you've got,
then reload and do it again!
[TILARNA gasps]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A groans, growls]
[SWAT TEAM shouts]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A shouts]
[KEI]
Damn. She got away again.
Tilarna! Are you okay?
[TILARNA]
I'm fine.
[KEI grunts]
We have to follow her. Come on.
Now! Move your ass!
I heard you! Stop yelling!
[speaks Farbani]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A pants]
[footsteps]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN VAMPIRE
A speaks Farbani]
[ZELADA speaks Farbani]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN VAMPIRE
A speaks Farbani]
[ZELADA speaks Farbani]
[KEI] We've got eyes
all over the mall.
So how the hell have we
still not found her?
She might be gone by now,
but I think I know where.
There's a subway 00 meters
south of you, and the mall's
ventilation system happens
to run all the way out to it.
[KEI]
So, she took the ducts.
You can cut her off.
Circle around to the
East Plaza Station
and set up an ambush there.
I'll send you a map.
[KEI sighs]
Let's go.
I've never been
about healthy living.
All this running really sucks.
I don't know why
you're complaining.
It's better than riding
in those awful car things.
[KEI groans]
I can smell her.
She's close, stay alert!
So we guessed right.
I'm not sure whether to be
happy about that or not.
[TILARNA]
Kei.
[KEI]
What?
[TILARNA] If it's possible,
I want to capture her alive.
Are you kidding me? We can't
afford to pull our punches.
That thing's strong
enough to kill us all!
[TILARNA] Like I said:
If it's possible.
What, so now you're
coming down with
Stockholm Syndrome
or something?
Taking pity on the poor little
lost vampire in the big city?
[TILARNA]
I just...
[KEI] Don't forget.
She's already killed two people.
[TILARNA]
I know that.
[KEI] She damn near
killed Cecil, too.
[TILARNA]
I know that!
There's just something
I need to ask her!
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[speaks Farbani]
[BOTH speaking Farbani]
[TILARNA]
There's another body.
[KEI] Transit worker?
No, looks like‐‐
[TILARNA]
Monster!
Hey, hold on! Damn it.
[chuckles]
[TILARNA shouts, grunts]
[KEI]
Get out of the way.
[grunting]
[KEI]
Nailed her!
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A grunting]
[KEI]
Why won't you die?
I'm gonna run out of guns!
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A yells]
[KEI]
You've got to be kidding me!
[KEI speaks Farbani]
[spaeking Farbani]
[KEI grunts]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN VAMPIRE
A speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA shouts]
[FEMALE SEMANIAN
VAMPIRE A screams]
[KEI exhlaes]
Is she dead for real?
[TILARNA]
I think so.
Those pieces are too
small to regenerate.
And you seem just fine.
So maybe you could show a
little bit of gratitude
for not being splattered all
over the tunnel, like her.
It's not like I
asked for your help.
Are you serious?
Do you not understand how
decent people act,
or do you just‐‐
[KEI]
Thanks.
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI] For letting me cut off
your little lecture right there.
I'm calling in the cavalry.
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA]
Then I'm never saving you again!
Next time you try to
get yourself killed,
I'm just going to let it happen!
[KEI]
Fine by me!
Not like you can save me
from all this paperwork.
[KEI yawns]
[KEI] Makes me wish I
could hop into a coffin
and hide from the sun all day.
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.