Zelada!
[ZELADA] Why, hello there,
Lady Exedilica.
It's lovely to see you again.
[KEI]
You!
[ZELADA] And Sir Matoba,
you're looking well!
Zelada!
[ZELADA chuckles]
As terrifying as ever, I see.
I am sorry, but you
leave me no choice.
[gasps]
Tilarna!
You piece of shit!
I'll kill you for that,
Zelada, do you hear me?
I'll make you pay!
[ZELADA] Well, I don't
like the sound of that.
Why don't you lie down for
a nice little nap instead?
[KEI grunts]
[ZIMMER] You got your
hands on a suspect
in the gun smuggling case?
[TONY] Yes. We're trying to
get more information out of him,
but, you see‐‐
[GODNOV] Eugene Bolai.
A Semanian immigrant.
He's one of those Lahge guys.
[TONY] He was using the
company's equipment
to make that steel
a little at a time.
The history's been
deleted already, but‐‐
Wait, so you're not investors?
So, you just lied
right to my face?
[TONY]
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
We're actually cops, hun.
Understood. Yeah, okay.
Bring him in, then.
‐‐[ZIMMER sighs]
‐‐[phone rings]
Damn, what the hell are Matoba
and Exedilica doing over there.
They're not picking up.
[ZELADA speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[speaks Farbani]
Blow it out your ass, Zelada,
you nasty old geezer.
Get on your knees and press your
hideous face to the ground
and beg for mercy while
you piss your pants!
Oh, it breaks my heart to see.
I've always said nothing good
ever comes from spending
too much time on this
despicable planet.
What have you done with Kei?
Tell me now so I can send you
to hell where you belong!
[ZELADA]
Where is Sir Matoba?
[ZELADA chuckles] Well,
I certainly hope he's doing
all right. But that FBI
agent seemed violent,
don't you think? He didn't
strike me as the type who would
interrogate a prisoner
with any sensitivity.
The same one who
called himself Chan?
So, what are you two
planning together?
[ZELADA] The same thing I
was planning with Sir Roth.
My interests align with
Mr. Chan's, too, you see.
[CHAN]
I don't have any ideals really.
At the end of the day, I just
want to live a comfortable life.
[KEI] Is that why you
teamed up with Zelada, then?
He's more cunning
than you think.
[CHAN] You can't get
anywhere in business
without taking a few risks.
Our original plan hinged
on Coal Mozeleemay
becoming mayor of San‐Teresa.
All because he's incompetent.
Easy to manipulate.
If Kahns and Tourte had
died in unfortunate accidents
during the election, Coal would
be a shoe‐in for the job.
Zelada insisted that the
assassins use Earth weapons
to carry out the murders.
He was adamant in fact.
[KEI exhales]
Why would you ever
want to do that?
To ensure everyone
starts to hate each other.
The Semanians and
the Doreany, that is.
[exhales]
[KEI]
And the vaifaht steel gun?
Mrs. Mozeleemay wanted
to gain Semanian support
by any means necessary.
She kept her eye on
every craftsman from
the other world who
wanted to come here.
She would even offer them work.
[KEI] When you say craftsmen,
are you referring to the Lahge?
[CHAN] I was astounded by the
complexity of this little thing.
Who'd buy that it could be
a gun? It's real‐life magic.
[KEI gasps, grunts]
[CHAN]
Gimme a good laugh.
One... Two... Three.
[KEI grunts]
[CHAN laughs] I guess it can't
fire bullets unless it's a gun.
Amazing, right?
That thing killed Coal,
your puppet.
[CHAN] Ethan made that
choice against our wishes.
Ethan, huh?
The assassin that you and your
partner killed, remember?
Ethan was a former marine who
suddenly went missing in action
while over in the Semani
world eight years ago.
Then he inexplicably resurfaced,
with a bunch of knowledge about
magic and swordsmanship.
[ZELADA] Ethan Dole. A man
with incredible potential
as a warrior, for a
Doreany, anyway.
[TILARNA]
Was it you, then?
Were you the one
who trained him?
[ZELADA]
Of course not.
I'm perfectly abysmal
with a sword.
You've figured it out,
haven't you?
You of all people should
have recognized that style.
[TILARNA gasps]
Leeze.
[TILARNA]
Leeze. That's a Mirvor word.
It translates to "master."
Which means that. It means‐‐!
[ZELADA]
Lady Exedilica.
[gasps]
[ZELADA] The time has
come for me to share
my true feelings with you.
To be honest,
I fear for our world.
For Leto Semani.
I have a gnawing,
abiding terror about its future.
So, you resort to terrorism?
[ZELADA] I'll say it as
many times as I have to.
The Semani and the Doreany must
be led to hate one another.
If they do not, it will be
impossible to protect our lands
from their ever‐encroaching
civilization.
I beg pardon?
[ZELADA] Oh, but surely
you know about the tragedy
that's unfolding in
your homeland, my dear.
Earth, its Doreany weapons,
Doreany "tools,"
sickening pornography
everywhere you look.
Atrocities like this.
‐‐[music playing]
‐‐[TILARNA grunts]
[ZELADA] Have you ever heard
anything so utterly revolting?
[music stops]
[ZELADA] And yet, the Semanian
people are devouring it all
without even a
second thought.
Sir Elbaji was a
skilled warrior.
A highly intelligent man,
no doubt, but he spent too
much time exposed to the
wickedness of the Doreany.
Men like him will soon
be found on every corner
in our world if nothing is
done to stop this scourge.
[TILARNA gasps]
[ZELADA] "Decadence."
That word lies at the very core
of Doreany culture and society.
I have committed
acts of great evil.
I have killed innocent beings.
But never have I allowed myself
to be guilty of the
sin of decadence.
On my life, not even once.
[CHAN] Now, then, let's cut to
the chase, Detective Matoba.
I'd really love to
talk business with you.
[KEI]
What can I do for you, sir?
I want the photo, sir.
Randall's pic of
Mrs. Mozeleemay.
I need to have the
one and only copy.
I can't let anyone else get
their grubby little mitts on it.
Then, I guess you need
my passcode, right?
To delete that stupid picture?
Along with every other
account you can find.
[CHAN]
Hacking a city cop's phone
isn't the easiest thing to do.
As we speak, Marla is taking
the lead in the mayoral race.
Isn't that awesome?
She's got the sympathy vote.
At this rate, she'll win
by a landslide.
[KEI] Marla used to be a
client of yours, didn't she?
And now you're going
to blackmail her.
We're incredibly greedy,
obviously. We can't have you
or Randall owning a copy
of something so precious.
Oh, I get it. You can
torture me all you want,
but if I were to hold out
four more days,
until the election is over,
then you'd have a
problem on your hands.
Guess I'm getting through
that thick head of yours.
From the looks of it,
this Marla Mozeleemay woman
is one hell of a nasty bitch.
Couldn't say.
But I can say that I don't give
a shit who the next mayor is,
as long as they have the
sense to play nice with me.
Now, just give me your passcode.
That's all it'll take,
and I'll set you free.
I'll pay you for
your trouble, too.
Half a mil.
It would be smart for you
to get in on this action
on the ground floor.
Well, you've convinced me.
The code's seven characters.
[CHAN]
Hm.
[KEI] The first letter's F,
and the second one is U,
then you've got C, then a big K.
Now‐‐
[Kei grunts]
It's not wise to fuck with me.
Nah, I'm serious.
You feds are so paranoid.
I'm sorry that you refuse
to negotiate. What a shame.
Come on, did you really think
I would negotiate with you?
You'll free me if I give you
my password. Five‐hundred K.
You're already beating
the shit out of me,
there's no need to insult
my intelligence, too.
[KEI grunts]
Tell me.
[KEI]
Already did. F‐U‐‐
[CHAN grunts]
[grunts]
That one smarts.
[KEI groans]
[CHAN]
Tell me. What is it?
Nice work.
[CHAN]
No more jokes. Wake up!
[KEI grunts]
[CHAN groans]
No!
[KEI] That feels different
that heading a soccer ball.
Ow, jeez.
[gasps]
Randall. I'm sorry.
[grunts]
[ZELADA] Hatred. Sometimes it
can be a powerful tool,
and it's the only thing that
can save our homeland
from the plague of
Earthling decadence.
[We must make our kind hate
Doreany culture so much
that they wouldn't even look
upon a tool from Earth.
In my opinion, that's the only
chance we have for survival.
Lady Exedilica. I would
hate to imagine
that you take no issue with the
scourge of self‐indulgence.
That path leads
only to depravity.
Really? Depravity, is it?
[ZELADA]
Indeed.
The introduction of Doreany
culture into the purity
‐‐of our homeland will‐‐
‐‐[TILARNA] That's enough!
Call it what you want,
but it's nothing more than
your own fear of change.
[ZELADA]
Nonsense, my dear!
[TILARNA] It's true.
You pathetic, old coward.
All this talk of doing evil
for the sake of your cause
is a mask for your terror
of a changing world.
I have no such fear. I know
you'll be proven wrong.
There's plenty that shines
through all the filth.
[ZELADA] Impossible.
You are in denial of reality.
Nothing could ever
prove me wrong.
You want to talk about reality?
Well, then, here it is.
The gateway between worlds
has been blown wide open,
and it's not closing
anytime soon.
Things are changing, and we
must adapt, or we'll die!
It's the only choice, and I,
for one, am glad to accept that!
[ZELADA]
I see.
I must admit, I'm disappointed,
Lady Exedilica.
Then kill me if you must,
but I hope you never forget.
You couldn't even make a strong
enough case to change one
young woman's mind.
If you can't do that,
then how do you expect
to sway the masses?
[ZELADA exhales] This is
such a shame. But so be it.
This is farewell.
[TILARNA grunts]
Interesting. Apparently, you are
under the protection
of the grace of Kizenya.
‐‐[TILARNA gasps]
‐‐[gunshots]
It seems Sir Matoba
has found us.
He's tearing through my
puppets like paper dolls.
Hurry.
[KEI shouts, grunts]
[MALE SERVANT A growls]
[KEI]
Zelada!
[KEI grunting]
Zelada! Wow.
You need dance lessons!
[ZELADA]
This is a disaster!
My servants are
being mowed down,
one after another,
before I can blink.
[TILARNA]
Naturally.
Did you think those corpses
were a match for him?
They cannot possibly
stop Kei Matoba!
[ZELADA] So it would appear.
What am I to do about this?
[pants]
Kei will be here soon.
Surrender, and perhaps
he'll be merciful.
[gunshots]
[ZELADA] Well, then,
my last servant has fallen,
and the demon is
now at the door.
[ZELADA chuckles]
I hope you'll forgive my mirth.
I admit, I'm a little tickled
because I've been fretting over
which one of you I should
exterminate first.
[TILARNA]
What?
I tried to imagine
Matoba's reaction
if he were to show up after
slaughtering my servants,
only to find your corpse.
And then, I considered
the reverse:
what would your reaction
be if you were forced to
watch helplessly as your partner
perished in front of you?
I find it amusing that it's been
such a difficult choice for me.
[TILARNA]
You're scum.
[ZELADA chuckles] Well. I think
I've just made my decision.
I'd rather see the anguish in
Sir Matoba's eyes
upon finding you dead.
So, your time has come...
...Lady Exedilica.
[speaks Farbani]
[ZELADA] You need to learn
when it is time to give up.
It isn't like you
to try and run.
[grunts]
[ZELADA] You're certainly
hanging in there!
So, perhaps,
Zestamariyesmedhu!
[TILARNA yells]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[KEI]
Zelada!
Ah, welcome, Sir Matoba,
you're quite early.
[KEI growls]
[ZELADA gasps]
I'm in dire peril.
No matter.
Zolus verde zolus medhe!
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA]
Kei, look up!
[music plays]
[ZELADA gasps]
[TILARNA]
Thanks.
[KEI sighs]
We'll use sprinklers.
When we spot Zelada, attack at
the same time as me!
I'm sorry. I can't stand.
My strength's not back.
[KEI grunts]
Right. So... just me.
[ZELADA] How could you
assail my poor old ears
with this cacophony? So unkind!
[KEI, TILARNA grunt]
[ZELADA] For a moment
I was afraid that my
eardrums would burst! I shall
send you to hell for that,
and ensure you suffer
as much as possible!
[KEI grunts]
[ZELADA] You still
haven't learned? How sad!
[pants, grunts]
[ZELADA]
Exceedingly clever of you.
And yet, you still cannot
take aim at me from there!
[pants]
I can't.
[ZELADA gasps]
Kizenya. I beg you,
please forgive me.
[ZELADA grunts]
[ZELADA]
It can't be. Unbelievable.
[KEI pants]
[ZELADA]
There's no way.
[gasps]
[KEI sighs] Nasty.
I'm gonna have nightmares.
Well, that's it, Rick.
I pulled it off.
[KEI]
Can you move?
Yes, a little.
[KEI exhales]
Here you go.
I'm so sorry.
[KEI grunts]
It's nothing.
[TILARNA] Uh, no.
I was talking to the sword.
[KEI]
Uh! Of course.
Right.
It's gonna be a while
before they send backup.
But, why?
Because of the damn
riots and whatnot.
All the cars are out
on calls right now.
[KEI] They said it'd
be about half an hour.
This city's done for, I guess.
[TILARNA]
Maybe. And Randall?
[KEI]
I wasn't able to save him.
[TILARNA]
I see.
[KEI]
Speaking of Randall, though.
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI]
What do we do with this?
What? Why are you asking me?
If I do what I'm supposed
to and give it to HQ,
it'll be made public.
That means Mrs. Mozeleemay's
career is done for.
Then Tourte will
win by a landslide.
So, are you telling me
you just want to delete it?
Legally, and, well,
ethically, it's wrong,
but it wouldn't be the first
time I've played dumb.
To be honest,
I don't care, either way.
I know the gods of Kizeyna
would never forgive
that kind of transgression.
Interfering with true justice.
But, really, it should be
my decision to make,
not the gods', right?
I think so, but who am I?
Well, then. You should
take the photo...
...and turn it over.
It's important evidence.
You sure that's what you want?
[TILARNA]
I am.
And even though this town's
a mess, right now, at least.
No matter who happens
to be mayor,
it's still a good town,
you know?
That's because...
[KEI]
Because what?
[TILARNA]
Well.
Because there are a lot of
good people living here.
You may be right about that.
[TILARNA]
But mostly...
...it's because
you're here, Kei.
[TILARNA] And so, peace was
restored to the city.
All the people who'd been
rioting and raging seemed
to disappear, but maybe
they're just content again.
Before this whole experience,
I might have looked
down on them‐‐
called them barbarians.
But things are different now.
They feel afraid. They worry.
They get confused.
Just like those in my world do.
At the end of the day,
we're all people.
The Knights always
taught me to wipe out evil,
no matter where
I might find it.
However, I'm
learning discernment.
Sometimes there's a
fine line between evil
that can be defeated and
evil that can be forgiven.
Do you think that makes
me weak? Who knows?
If being able to walk that
line also makes me smarter,
then it's a small price to pay.
So, Father. I beg you,
please don't be sad.
I've decided that I'm
staying in this town.
This crazy place
where so many weak,
foolish, and greedy
people live their lives.
I love them, and I'm going to
make my way among them.
Live my own life as
their fellow citizen.
I send my love.
Please give mother and
Shajinna my best wishes.
May the light of Kizenya shine
upon you in all that you do.
[KEI]
Time to go.
[SANDERS]
Uh... Hm... Um, 'scuse me.
Whaddaya want?
Sergeant Exedilica. I hoped I
might have a word with you.
Got a moment?
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA] He just apologized
for how he acted that day.
Oh.
[TILARNA] I think he feels
genuinely remorseful.
What would you do here?
[KEI] Hm... Have'm spin
three times and bark.
Then you two'll be even.
Excellent.
Uh... Hey, wait!
I'm kidding! Don't!
[TILARNA] Spin around
three times and bark.
[SANDERS]
Uh... One, two, three, woof!
[MALE COP A]
Huh?
[TILARNA giggles]
[SANDERS]
Huh?
Heh. Okay, Tilarna, time to go!
[KEI] Earthlings aren't so
bad after all, am I right?
[TILARNA chuckles]