[KEI]
All units, hold your positions.
When he cuts the engine, we go.
Once in a blue moon, O'Neill's
info's right on the money.
[TILARNA]
I'm tired of waiting, Kei.
Can we finish this
up and go home?
It ain't that easy,
this isn't a shopping trip.
Shopping's a lot
harder than this.
Truly. Your Doreany stores
have way too many choices.
You've been in our world for
four whole months already.
So, get used to it,
country mouse.
Country mouse?
I'm from Narma, which is a
major city, I'll have you know.
Just shut your trap and‐‐
[gasps]
[COP A] We just got made.
The target's onto us!
He's trying to make
a break for it!
All units, move in, now!
We've gotta stop the plane!
[COP A]
Permission to fire, sergeant?
[KEI]
No! Do not use your weapons!
Block the runway
with your vehicles!
I'll take care of
this one, Kei!
What the‐‐? Hey!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[KEI]
Get back here!
You crazy?
[TILARNA grunts]
[KEI] Hey, do you have a
death wish or something?
[TILARNA]
Watch the plane.
[KEI]
Uh...
Feast your eyes on the
strength of vaifaht steel.
[KEI]
Moron.
[NARRATOR A]
15 years ago,
a hyperspace gate appeared in
the middle of the Pacific Ocean.
Beyond that gate lay a
mysterious world filled with
fairies and monsters.
The city of San‐Teresa
on Kariaena island
became known as
"Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of races,
cultures, and species,
the haves and the have‐nots.
San Teresa is the world's
newest "city of dreams."
But, in the shadows, lurk all
kinds of crimes and criminals.
Drugs. Prostitution.
Weapons smuggling.
The San‐Teresa Metropolitan
Police force
maintain a specialized unit
to deal with the seedy mayhem.
[KEI grunts] Two hours making
mud pies in this freakin'
hellhole and not a
trace of the target.
If only someone hadn't been
a hero and brought down
the plane into a swamp.
[TILARNA] Hey! Say that
to my vaifaht steel.
This can't be the loot.
[KEI]
It's just a box full of junk!
[TILARNA sniffs]
[KEI]
What's up?
[TILARNA] I smell latena
coming from the box.
[HELLMANDES] Hey! You got
clearance to touch that?
[KEI]
Hm? Who's askin'?
CBP. Customs and
Border Protection.
My name is Officer Hellmandes.
[KEI] I don't need clearance
from your people
to do anything, man.
This case is our jurisdiction.
It was, but you just let
your target get away.
We'll take over from here.
[KEI] We haven't even catalogued
the recorded evidence yet.
Are you refusing to comply
with a CBP order?
[KEI] Of course not!
I'd never do such a thing!
It's a formality,
but my boss says I gotta.
Just takes time, you know?
[HELLMANDES] Get back to work,
and be quick about it.
[TILARNA] That is one
incredibly unpleasant man.
[KEI] No shit he is.
He's an elite investigator
clawing his way to the top.
They're all like that.
Well, you've got your
work cut out for you.
If you start right
when you get home,
you should be able
to finish tonight.
[TILARNA] I'm onto you, Kei!
It's my turn for first bath!
You set me up!
No way, it's past midnight.
Now it's my day!
[TILARNA] Rakebye!
That's not how it works!
Anyway, aren't you stupid
Doreany always saying,
"ladies first, ladies first?"
Have a little chivalry!
Don't you ignore me, Kei!
[KEI hums]
[TILARNA grumbles]
[KEI] Nighty night!
It's all yours, princess.
[KEI]
Oh, when you get out,
start your inventory of
that box of swamp junk.
I'm hitting the hay.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[KEI] What?
You're the only one who
could smell latena,
especially under that bog funk.
Anyway, you were snoring your
ass off the whole ride home,
so now it's my turn to sleep.
But‐‐ I don't snore!
And I wasn't sleeping!
[KEI]
Cut the crap.
We need to have that stuff
in the evidence lockers
by tomorrow morning at 11,
you got it? Goodnight.
[TILARNA hums]
[snores]
[humming continues]
Kei is so boorish and selfish.
Literally everything he does
grates on my nerves.
Does he annoy you, too?
[KUROI meows]
I knew it. Women mystify him.
We deserve respect
and courtesy,
which he can't
give anyone, really.
As a lady, yourself,
I knew you'd understand
where I'm coming from,
and why I find him so
utterly infuriating, but...
[TILARNA] Hm. I think I've found
the source of the latena smell.
[KUROI meows]
Kuroi, no! That's poor manners!
Kuroi, you're being bad!
You know you're not supposed
to be on the furnit‐‐
Stop it! Careful! Kuroi!
Why are you being a
bad kitty? Come on!
[KUROI meows]
Darn it!
[grunts]
What is this?
[TILARNA exhales]
[TILARNA]
Kei. Help.
[meows]
[KEI grunts]
Kuroi, no, go back to sleep.
It's early, I'll feed you later.
[gasps]
What the heck?
[TILARNA whines]
[KEI] Are you sleep walking?
Go back downstairs to your bed!
[TILARNA]
Huh? Kei.
[KEI gasps]
Tilarna? What the‐‐?
[TILARNA exhales]
[KEI]
Will you please knock it off?
[KEI groans]
‐‐[KUROI hisses]
‐‐[KEI gasps]
[hissing continues]
What is going on right now?
Why are you both freaking out?
[meows]
[KEI gasps]
[KUROI meowing]
Did I wake up in an
alternate universe?
We're late!
Hey, Tilarna! We have to go!
[meowing continues]
[TILARNA yawns]
[KEI]
Come on, what are you doing?
Hm?
[meowing continues]
[gasps]
[KEI] Okay, are you not
feeling well or something?
[KEI] I can't help if
you don't tell me.
[KUROI meows]
[KEI]
Shut up, I get it.
You're hungry,
just like every morning.
Will you relax?
Fine, stay home today.
I'll tell the chief you've got
some sort of weird
alien disease that's making you
act like you lost your mind.
Rest up, I'll see you later.
[TILARNA]
Meow!
[KEI] Oh, right! The trash.
Sorry about that.
[meowing continues]
[KEI groans] She left all
this crap out? What the hell?
[KEI] Kuroi, take care
of Tilarna. Be good.
[meowing]
[KUROI meows]
[TILARNA]
This is a nightmare.
That old crossbow,
it was covered in mildey
of Moz Nel Valva.
‐‐[TILARNA grunts]
‐‐[KUROI] Huh?
[TILARNA gasps]
She got on top of Kei
wearing practically
nothing at all!
But he thinks it's me!
[TILARNA panics] I have to
remain calm. I can fix this.
First, the crossbow...
It fell off the sofa.
And into the garbage! Right!
The bin next to the couch!
But wait, Kei took the bag!
[TILARNA]
Quenishuba. Quenishuba!
[TILARNA gasps, yelp]
Oh no. Don't do that!
[TILARNA] Is she going to...
Oh, please, no.
[TILARNA] Don't do it, Kuroi!
Come on, stop!
At least take off your
underwear before you‐‐
[TILARNA]
No, Kuroi! Please!
Gross!
[ZIMMER grunts]
A simple raid
turned into a plane
crash in the swamp?
What the hell
happened out there?
[KEI]
I already told you.
The local cops botched the stake
out and the target saw us.
[ZIMMER]
Shut up!
Don't you blame it on them,
you moron,
the Golanbiza County police were
blowing up my phone at midnight
putting it all on us,
and my wife was pissed!
I've been eating raw oysters
and taking zinc supplements
all week to give her
what she wanted,
and 'cause of you, I couldn't!
Wait a second. It was
just the county cops?
[ZIMMER]
What?
The complaints you were getting.
Hear anything from the CBP?
[ZIMMER]
You piss them off, too?
I was on the phone with their
guy, Hellmandes, this morning,
but he didn't say
crap about you.
[KEI]
Hm...
Hold on. Wait!
You got in some kinda fight
with 'em, didn't you?
Don't lie, Matoba!
If I find out‐‐
[KEI] Nothing happened with
the CBP, Chief, calm your tits.
Hey! I'm not done with you!
[sighs] There's no way
she's still asleep.
[TILARNA groans]
I can't take it anymore.
I have to do something.
[TILARNA]
I have to find that crossbow.
The trash people
come this afternoon.
The bag should still be
out in the dumpster.
But I have no way
to get out there!
I can't even open a door
with these useless cat paws!
[TILARNA gasps]
[meows]
[TILARNA] That's it.
I have to enlist help!
[CECIL] Tilarna? Weird.
She almost never texts.
[TILARNA] My apologies for
writing so suddenly.
I've a serious problem.
Come to my home immediately?
What is going on here?
[CECIL]
Don't tell Kei? Why not?
[KEI]
See you guys on the flip side.
[busy tone]
Who in the hell would
Tilarna even be talking to?
Hello? Tilarna? I got
your texts. What's going on?
[TILARNA meowing]
[CECILgasps]
[meowing continues]
Hello, kitty! You sure
have a lot to say, huh?
Can you put Tilarna on the
phone, I need to talk to her.
Wow. I'm just talking
to cats now, I guess.
Anyway, I'm heading over
to your house, all right?
Be a good girl
until I get there.
[meowing continues]
[phone buzzes]
[KEI]
Sergeant Matoba.
[HELLMANDES]
What the hell is going on?
[KEI]
With what?
[HELLMANDES] Yesterday there
were 28 Semanian items
on record from the plane
crash in the swamp.
But now there are only 27!
Where's the missing item?
Oh, I see. That is peculiar.
Well, sometimes stuff
just happens, you know?
Things were kind of
a hot mess yesterday.
[HELLMANDES] Cut the crap!
Get me the missing item now,
or I'll have you arrested
for embezzlement!
[KEI] Come on!
This is a minor screw‐up,
not some big conspiracy!
Take it down a notch, turbo.
[HELLMANDES]
Fine.
Just get it to me now and
there won't be any trouble!
[KEI]
What the hell's up his ass?
[bell buzzes]
[CECIL]
Tilarna? Are you there?
She's gotta be. Tilarna?
Still here.
[CECIL]
I'm coming in, okay?
Tilarna? Huh?
[meows]
Kuroi! What's wrong?
Did you make this giant mess?
[meowing continues]
[CECIL] Are you telling
me it wasn't you?
[CECIL gasps]
Calm down!
Logically, I know
this isn't possible,
but are you Tilarna, somehow
trapped in Kuroi's body?
[meowing quickens]
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I think you are.
[CECIL] You got this
way because of mildey?
[TILARNA meows]
And you need to get the crossbow
in order to switch back.
That's how you two switched
bodies to begin with.
It's in the dumpster.
The one outside?
Why would you put it out there?
The garbage truck should
be coming this afternoon!
If they take it away,
we'll be in major trouble!
[CECIL] I think it's safe to
say you do need it, Tilarna!
No "may" about it!
[CECIL]
Huh?
Ce... Ce...!
Wait, so if Kuroi is
really Tilarna,
then you must be...
[CECIL]
No, don't!
[meows]
[bell ringing]
[KENNY grunts]
What?
[KEI]
It's Matoba. Is O'Neill in?
Last I heard, he was
still at this address.
[KENNY grunts]
The boss? Hold on a minute.
Ugh. My head's killing me.
[knocking]
I let myself in.
[KENNY grunts]
Hey, Sergeant.
[KEI] Kenny. What's up
with that outfit?
[KENNY] What do you mean?
These are my jam jams.
I always wear them to bed.
I can't go to sleep
without 'em, dude.
This place is a mess.
[KENNY] Yeah. There was
a wild party last night.
That guy on the floor
a friend of yours?
[KENNY]
Nope. Never seen him before.
How did he get in?
[KEI]
Where the hell is O'Neill?
[KENNY] I haven't seen him
since last night. Ugh...
Last I remember, he had
just made a vodka soda
with ketchup and habanero
sauce in it and was doing
pelvic thrusts on
the coffee table,
but it starts to get
pretty fuzzy after that.
I would ask why
there's a goat in here,
but I'd rather not know.
[KENNY] Weird. It wasn't
here when I passed out.
What kind of party
was this, man?
[KEI]
O'Neill isn't here.
[KENNY] Heh. Maybe the goat
got hungry and ate him.
[KEI]
Oh You're hilarious.
I gotta find him. I need him
to check on something for me.
It's urgent. Get off me,
goat we're not friends
[BIZ chuckles]
[KEI gasps]
Did you hear something?
[BIZ groans]
Forgive me, Lord.
I am being smothered by
the abundance of your‐‐
Where the hell are you, O'Neill?
[BIZ grunts] My lungs.
It hurts to breathe.
I've been chosen to suffocate
for the sins of the flesh.
I come to you, Lord, to rest
in your kingdom forever.
[KEI]
O'Neill? You under there?
Hey, lady, get off
the man, will ya?
[KENNY] Can't help ya, man.
When the Virgin Mary
gets like this, she's out
for 12 hours, at least.
[KEI laughs] The Virgin Mary?
But isn't she a hooker?
[KENNY] Yeah. That's just
what they call her.
[KEI exhales]
[KEI]
This'll wake her up.
[chuckles]
[yells]
[BIZ groans]
[KENNY] Sergeant.
That was a mean trick.
[KEI] I didn't think
she'd flip out like that.
Is he okay? You think we
should call an ambulance?
[CECIL grunts]
[CECIL]
Huh?
That's right, you're Tilarna.
It wasn't a dream.
[TILARNA meows]
[CECIL gasps] Garbage truck!
Did it come yet?
[TILARNA meows]
Oh no! I might be able to
catch it. You coming, too?
[TILARNA meows]
Okay, if you insist!
First, we gotta find
that garbage truck.
I couldn't have been
out for very long,
which means it should
still be nearby.
[TILARNA meows frantically]
What is it?
Do you see the truck?
[meowing continues]
[CECIL] Mm? Lower the
blinds before we go.
If someone sees me up there
like that, I will die.
Jeez, we don't have
time for your pride!
[CECIL]
Done. Now, let's go!
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.