[NARRATOR] The city of
San‐Teresa on Kariaena Island
became known as
"Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of different
races, cultures, and species,
the haves and the have‐nots.
But, in the shadows of the
chaos lurk all kinds of
crimes and criminals.
The San‐Teresa
Metropolitan Police force
maintain a specialized unit
to deal with the seedy mayhem.
[TILARNA hums]
[TILARNA] I've only been in this
world a handful of months,
and yet so much
has happened.
[TILARNA] The first case I
took on with my partner,
Kei Matoba, was personal.
It involved tracking down
someone that I knew:
a fairy named Leahyah.
[TILARNA] She wasn't
just any fairy, either.
She was a noble fairy.
A member of a powerful
clan in western Farbani.
[TILARNA]
She was kidnapped.
A group of nasty criminals
took her from her home
and brought her into this world.
[CAPTAIN A]
There they are.
It's some important noble,
is that right?
I'll let you take it from here.
[TILARNA] In accordance with a
treaty struck between my land
and the entity called,
"The United Nations."
I was sent to the world of the
doreany, to carry out justice.
I stipulated that I only
wanted to work with a
"boliceman" who was
wise and just.
Someone who was strong and
experienced and well‐versed
in the ancient traditions.
But instead, I was paired
up to work with this man.
A foul‐mouthed cigarette smoker,
and the first person
I met when I arrived.
[KEI]
Where's the VIP?
[TILARNA]
Hey.
I am the one you seek.
Exedilica of the
Knights of Mirvor?
Do Earthlings have no
welcoming ritual?
[KEI gasps, grunts]
[TILARNA] Have they sent
a mute to retrieve me?
[KEI]
I talk.
[TILARNA] Then why don't
you answer? Well, then?
[KEI]
I didn't know you who were.
[TILARNA]
I see.
[TILARNA] My name is
Tilarna Barsh. Mirvor Lyata.
Imsedalya Iyeh Tebreina Devol.
Nelano Seiya. Nel Exedilica.
In your Earth language it's,
"Tilarna, eldest daughter
of Seiya,
of the House of Exedilica.
Heir apparent to the
bloodline of Duke Devol.
She of the glorious
Knights of Mirvor."
Now, then. You tell
me your name.
Kei Matoba.
[TILARNA]
Again.
Kei Matoba.
Is that it?
[KEI]
Huh?
Huh. Typically,
only people of low birth
have names that short, but I
suppose it's of no consequence.
It's a pleasure.
To simplify things,
you may call me
Tilarna Exedilica for short.
[KEI]
Huh?
Now, you will carry my
bags for me, Kei Imatuba.
[KEI]
Kei Matoba.
[TILARNA] I don't care.
Start carrying.
[KEI sighs]
[KEI]
Don't touch anything.
I'm not. You smell that?
[KEI]
Smell what?
I think it's latena.
Someone was here who's
controlled by an evil wizard.
I know it. Don't you?
[KEI]
What're you saying?
‐‐The enemy's near.
‐‐[elevator dings]
[speaks Farbani]
[KEI gasps]
Follow me!
[KEI]
Hey, wait!
Police! Don't move!
[KEI]
Get down!
Shit!
[gasps]
[ASSAILANT A grunts]
[TILARNA]
Goddamned corpse!
[KEI]
Get down, dammit!
[KEI, TILARNA]
Will you stay out of my way?
[TILARNA]
Let's get him!
[KEI]
I will, you stay here!
[TILARNA] No, I want to
take that thing down!
[KEI]
Just shut up and hang tight!
[TILARNA grunts]
[ASSAILANT A groans]
[KEI shouts]
[KEI]
Idiot! What'd I say?
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[KEI] You just went ahead
and sliced him open.
Okay, Miss Don Quixote.
Did it occur to you that we
might wanna question him first?
[KEI]
Hey, answer me!
Someone else was controlling
him via mildey.
Even if we had captured him,
we wouldn't have been
able to learn anything.
[KEI]
"Mildey?"
Yes. Magic used to
control the dead.
He'd been totally
devoured by evil latena,
and it transformed him
into a living corpse.
[KEI] So, you're blaming your
choice to shoot a perp
on some weird spell?
Pardon?
You're obstructing
the investigation.
I see what's going on.
This is about that fairy‐‐
someone's got a secret
and they sent you
to keep us from finding out.
What are you implying?
[KEI]
Nothing, I said it, flat‐out.
I wonder how much you're getting
paid to do it. Probably tons.
[TILARNA] Consider this your
only warning, Kae Imatoeba.
If you value your life, do not
insult my integrity again.
If you do, I'll kill you.
You and what army?
[snarls]
[KEI] Who knew a lowly Earthling
could get you so riled up.
Gotta admit, I'm flattered.
[TILARNA]
Silence!
[KEI]
Yeah, yeah.
[gasps]
[KEI sighs]
[KEI] Look, I just
need to know one thing.
What's that?
[KEI] You're serious about
finding these creeps
and getting that
fairy back, right?
Naturally.
[KEI]
Well, I am, too.
We want the same things,
so why are we fighting,
pointing our weapons
at each other?
[TILARNA] Kei and I
didn't get along at all,
but we were both committed
to solving the case.
[TILARNA] He and learned
something disturbing:
the fairies were being used as
weapons in the doreany world,
and we soon discovered that
a man named Zelada
was heavily involved
in the case.
[music blaring]
[chuckles]
[TILARNA] But, sadly,
the bolicemen seemed
more interested in arresting
Zelada and his fellow criminals
than they were in finding
and saving Leahyah.
[TILARNA] Under doreany law,
fairies are considered citizens,
with the same rights and
protections as anyone else
in that world.
But because of the
way they look and act,
they're treated more like cats
or dogs than actual citizens.
They're not often given
the respect they deserve.
[TILARNA]
In any case,
I wanted to save Leahyah,
no matter what it took.
Even if it meant forfeiting the
sword I valued as much
as my own life,
and embarking on a journey that
promised little hope of return.
[ELBAJI] ...you know
why that is, friend?
No.
Because I'm hot,
man, that's why!
[TILARNA]
She was important to me.
I cherished her more
than anyone knew.
I couldn't just let her
die in this world.
[KAREEM] Congratulations, but
I'm just here for the product.
Sorry, right. Hey, Zelada!
[ZELADA] Yes, my lord,
what may I do for you?
[ELBAJI]
Mr. Kareem,
allow me to introduce
you to Zelada the Sage.
[KAREEM] He's the wizard you
were telling me about?
[ELBAJI]
Yeah.
He's the greatest when it comes
to controlling the dead.
[ZELADA] Your words do me
great honor, sir. I'm grateful.
I only do what I can for
the sake of my master.
[KAREEM] He called them,
"the dead."
Was he talking about
fairy dust users?
Yes, indeed he was.
My magic has no effect
on the pure of soul.
Those who use the drug
fall right under my spell.
[ELBAJI] And that's
where this thing comes in!
And is that device
the fairy bomb?
[ELBAJI]
A prototype, but yeah.
And you're about to see
me put it to the test.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
[ELBAJI] I called these guys.
Dialed nine‐one‐one.
Told them some suspicious
people were causing trouble.
[COP A] This place is
off‐limits. Come on.
Hands above your heads,
all of you.
Check this, watch your eyes.
[COPS shout]
[KAREEM grunts]
It works immediately!
Verdict, Zelada?
[ZELADA]
A total success, my lord.
Judging by the look of them,
both officers are
already deceased.
How 'bout you have them give
us a nice, little salute.
As you wish, my lord.
Now, have one of them
shoot the other.
Yes.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[gunshots]
Poor bastard! He blew him away!
So, what next? How about this!
Make that stupid piggy
dance on the hood!
[ZELADA, ELBAJI laughing]
[ELBAJI]
Zelada, you call that dancing?
‐‐You need some lessons, bro!
‐‐[ZELADA] Apologies, sir.
[ELBAJI laughs]
Ah, man, that's freakin'
hilarious, right?
[KAREEM] How many can
he control like this?
[ELBAJI]
Ha!
Five, or ten thousand?
Really. As many as you like,
I've controlled up to
about 300 at once.
[KAREEM]
Good god.
And that's just the prototype.
Imagine the real thing, bud.
We use a potent fairy,
every inch of its body.
The blast radius. Bro, it covers
about five kilometers.
That's the size of a nuke.
We could overthrow
superpower governments
with this in our hands.
Do whatever you want
with it, my man.
Thing is, to work it, you'll
have to rent Zelada, too.
Just name your price.
All right. Good. Get the cash,
and it's yours.
[ZELADA] My lord. Have you
finished with this one?
[ELBAJI]
Yeah, take care of him.
[KEI]
Forest Tower,
one of the tallest buildings
in the whole city.
That's where he's
gonna use the bomb?
[TILARNA]
It may have more of an effect
from up there than
on the ground.
[KEI]
Interesting.
So, it's the same as
a nuke that way, huh?
[TILARNA]
What's this place like?
[KEI] Loaded with rich people.
Common folk never go there.
Heh! On second thought,
maybe we oughta let
him go through with it.
[TILARNA grunts]
[KEI]
Come on, that was a joke.
Better be... Kei.
[KEI]
What?
This Zelada. Do you know
him from somewhere?
[KEI exhales]
I might.
But that doesn't mean he's
different from any other perp.
[BOTH gasp]
[TILARNA] This is Zelada's
doing. I can sense it.
[KEI]
Inside!
Is he dangerous?
I do fear him. He's a wizard.
They can blind you,
shoot poison flames,
and sadly, your
weapons can't win.
Even this? It's a good gun.
I've been using it forever.
It's still a
doreany weapon. No soul.
Although, I feel a
faint latena from it.
[KEI]
Hm?
Feelings for a thing
create latena, no matter what.
[KEI sighs]
[elevator beeps]
Better stay close to me, Kei.
I'm the only one who can
spot the enemy's ambush.
Come on.
We're partners. Trust me.
[KEI grunts]
Got it.
[TILARNA gasps]
Back away!
Ahead! Hurry!
[TILARNA] That fire will
burn up your lungs.
You'll lose your ability
to breathe. It's horrible.
[KEI] You mean I'll
choke to death? Damn.
[TILARNA]
There she is!
[gasps]
Leahyah!
[KEI]
Wait! It's a trap!
[TILARNA] I don't care.
I have to save her!
[KEI]
I know that, but‐‐Dammit!
What do I do with this thing?
I don't know, just smash it!
[KEI]
Are you kidding?
That's a good way to
make it detonate.
Gotta disarm it somehow.
I don't know.
Is this even technically a bomb?
[ZELADA] What a reckless,
futile endeavor.
You cannot stop what's coming.
So, you might as well
run for it now.
Hurry and you'll escape, go!
[TILARNA]
Damn you!
[KEI] Something about that
stupid grin on your face
makes me even more
motivated to take you down.
[ZELADA] Charming, but we
both know you won't.
Shut up!
[ZELADA]
See? You're helpless.
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA]
It's an illusion!
There!
[KEI grunts]
‐‐[KEI yells]
‐‐[TILARNA] Kei!
[ZELADA] Well, that's
unfortunate, Sir Matoba.
It appears that you've
lost once again.
And now, for your
little friend...
I'll enjoy this part!
[KEI pants]
[KEI] Dammit, where is he?
I can't see him.
No. Don't rely on vision.
Follow the sound.
The sound.
[grunts]
[KEI]
Coming from over there.
[gunshot]
[ZELADA]
No! This searing pain!
[TILARNA shouts]
[groans]
[ZELADA]
Yes. Nicely done.
I haven't been wounded like this
in a hundred and three years.
You're wasting
your last moments.
It's time to make your
peace and prepare for death!
Not yet. I'm afraid
I cannot bring shame upon
the Marzeny Sect by dying at
the hands of a mere Barshe.
Therefore...
[TILARNA gasps]
[ZELADA]
...I must bid you farewell!
[ZELADA laughs]
[gasps]
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA]
Kei!
I got rid of Zelada.
But I don't have any elixir
to heal you. I'm sorry.
[KEI grunts]
Go. Run. Now!
[TILARNA]
No. No time for that.
I suppose we'll just spend our
last few moments together.
You should be grateful.
A boorish, uncouth,
sarcastic man like you
getting to die next
to someone like me?
Please go. You can make it.
[speaks Farbani]
[LEAHYAH gasps]
[TILARNA] As I promised.
I've come to rescue you.
When I was child,
lost in the forest,
you did the same for me.
You showed me the way out,
helped me get back home.
Remember the
promise we made?
That, no matter what,
we'd always be friends.
That's why I'm here. I had to
uphold the oath we swore.
At least I saved you
from dying alone.
So, please, Leahyah.
Don't be afraid.
We are together.
[sighs]
Leahyah? You can't. Stop this!
Don't do it! Leahyah!
[TILARNA]
Leahyah!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[grunts, coughs]
I'm alive...? What is this?
[TILARNA]
I used a healing spell.
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA]
I needed an elixir,
one that could counteract the
damage caused by the poison.
Something with very
powerful latena.
[KEI]
An elixir?
[TILARNA] I was able to
make one from her body.
So, the fairy died anyway?
[TILARNA sobs]
She did.
[TILARNA] The bomb needed a
living fairy as a catalyst.
I suppose she knew that.
[KEI]
Hm...
[TILARNA] She sacrificed her
life in order to save me.
To save all of us.
[TILARNA]
When I was a child.
Leahyah loved to entertain me by
doing the most magical dances.
When I was hungry, she brought
me nuts that she had foraged.
We made a promise,
that if we were in trouble
or found ourselves alone, we
would be there for one another.
Because we held our
friendship sacred,
no matter where we were.
[TILARNA] Kei Matoba.
Thanks for everything.
[KEI] Uh, sure. You, too.
I appreciate it.
[TILARNA]
I'm going home in shame,
instead of dying with
honor like I'd hoped,
but I leave knowing that there
are some good warriors
on earth, after all.
[KEI]
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
[TILARNA]
My brooch.
I pulled some strings
to get it from O'Neill.
This thing's worth a lot.
Wouldn't want to
lose it to that guy.
Yes, but‐‐
Just shut up and
take it, will ya?
[TILARNA giggles]
Bye.
[TILARNA]
I bid you farewell, and I thank
you for your gallantry!
[TILARNA sighs]
[KEI sighs]
[TILARNA] I could've just gone
back home at that point,
but I was curious about
the city of San‐Teresa.
And also, I found myself
becoming fond of Kae.
[TILARNA]
When I say "Kae."
I'm referring to my
partner's cat, of course.
[KEI]
Kuroi, you hungry?
[SPORTSCASTER A]
Slam dunk!
I haven't seen a play
like that in ages!
And nice rebound
from the Semanian.
Here comes the shot
from half‐court.
Boom! Two three‐pointers
in a row!
[KEI]
What the hell's this?
Some kind of sports game.
I can't tell what the
rules are, though.
[KEI]
Not that, moron, you!
What the hell are
you doing here?
[TILARNA] Oh. I see now.
I changed my mind.
[KEI]
Huh?!
We're not sure
Zelada's really dead.
And this city is still
full of villains.
I figured I could help.
So, I decided to stay.
[KEI]
You kidding me?
[KEI] You're a detective now?
And in my department?
Yes, it appears so. Therefore,
I'll be staying here a while.
Are there any
further questions, partner?
[KEI grunts]
Partner?
[TILARNA giggles]
[KEI] Well, we've got an
early morning tomorrow.
I'm gonna hit the hay.
[TILARNA] Yeah, sounds good.
Goodnight, Kei.
[KEI speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA giggles]
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.