[gasps]
[MALE ASSAILANT A grunts]
[TILARNA]
Goddamned corpse!
[KEI]
Get down, dammit!
[TILARNA grunts]
[KEI. TILARNA]
Will you stay out of my way?
‐‐[TILARNA] Let's get him!
‐‐[KEI] I will, you stay here!
[TILARNA] No, I want to
take that thing down!
[KEI]
Just shut up and hang tight!
[TILARNA grunts]
[MALE ASSAILANT A grunts]
[KEI gasps, grunts]
[KEI]
Idiot! What'd I say?
[shouts]
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[MALE NARRATOR]
The city of San‐Teres on
Kariaena Island, became known
as "Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of races,
cultures, and species,
the haves and the have‐nots.
But, in the shadows lurk all
kinds of crimes and criminals.
The San‐Teresa Metropolitan
Police force maintain
a specialized unit to deal
with the seedy mayhem.
[KEI] You just went ahead
and sliced him open.
Okay, Miss Don Quixote,
did it occur to you that we
might wanna question him first?
[KEI]
Hey, answer me!
Someone else was controlling
him via mildey.
Even if we had captured him,
we wouldn't have been
able to learn anything.
[KEI
"Mildey?"
Yes. Magic used to
control the dead.
He'd been totally
devoured by evil latena,
and it transformed him
into a living corpse.
[KEI] So, you're blaming
your choice to shoot a perp
on some weird spell?
Pardon?
You're obstructing
the investigation.
I see what's going on.
This is about that fairy.
someone's got a secret,
and they sent you to
keep us from finding out.
What are you implying?
[KEI]
Nothing, I said it, flat‐out.
I wonder how much you're getting
paid to do it. Probably tons.
[TILARNA] Consider this your
only warning, Kae Imatoeba.
If you value your life, do not
insult my integrity again.
If you do, I'll kill you.
You and what army?
[grunts]
[KEI] Who knew a lowly Earthling
could get you so riled up.
Gotta admit, I'm flattered.
[TILARNA]
Silence!
[KEI]
Yeah, yeah...
[grunt, gasps]
[KEI exhales]
[KEI] Look, I just need
to know one thing.
What's that?
[KEI] You're serious about
finding these creeps
and getting that
fairy back, right?
Naturally.
[KEI]
Well, I am, too.
[KEI sighs]
We want the same things,
so why are we fighting, pointing
our weapons at each other?
[KEI]
Atta girl.
Listen, I heard you about
this guy being controlled.
Matter of fact,
another one just like him
almost killed me the other day.
[gasps] What? Why didn't
you mention this sooner?
[KEI] You didn't ask, and I
don't have to tell you anything.
[sirens blaring]
[CECIL] Kei, take a
wild guess what I found.
[KEI]
I read the report, Cecil.
What I wanna know is what
these two have in common.
That's an easy one.
This man here, the one
who killed your partner.
And this one, who very nearly
killed you... were dead.
Quite some time
before they died.
[KEI] You're gonna have
to spell it out.
t's about their blood oxygen
and lactic acid levels.
Your shots should've
killed them,
but for some reason,
they kept moving.
And their blood only reached
the levels a dead person
would have after the fact.
It's a fascinating puzzle.
But, that's what they
have in common.
[KEI] So, they were
basically zombies.
I'm not quite sure. Depends on
the official definition.
I didn't see any signs
of major drug use.
They both seemed to
drink and smoke,
but that had no effect
on their health.
You're wrong about the drugs.
[CECIL]
Hey, um, who is this person?
Tilarna Exedilica.
Knight of Mirvor.
Ah. So, you're visiting us
from the other world, then.
But what are you doing with Kei?
On the hunt for magic, she says.
Um...
Don't gimme that look.
I'm not crazy.
[TILARNA] This one's
the same as the other.
I smell the evil latena on him.
[CECIL]
What's latena?
[TILARNA]
Latena is latena.
[KEI] It's some kind of magical
energy source or something.
I have no clue, either.
Fairy latena that's
been horribly warped.
These men ingested it
on a regular basis
and became dead men.
[CECIL ehales] Are you telling
me that it's some kind of drug?
A Semanian substance?
[KEI] Fairy dust. These guys
were habitual users, right?
[TILARNA] If you can
call the dead "users,"
then yes, they were.
The Marzaney Sect has spells
that can control the dead.
[CECIL] Well, that would
explain why it didn't show up
on their labs. That drug is
a complete mystery to us.
All we know is that
it's made from fairies.
What terrible people.
To do that to a fairy.
[KEI]
So, can you use magic, too?
[TILARNA] It's called mildey,
and I can use it a little.
[KEI] Then why don't you
act as my police dog‐‐
use your mildey to follow the
trail of this latena stuff?
[TILARNA] Quite an imagination
for an idiot, Kae Imatoeba.
Mildey is powerful, but it
can't make one omnipotent.
I know you have a small brain,
but try to remember that.
[KEI] I don't take
advice from useless,
alien aristocrats, but thanks.
[CECIL] So, I guess you
two aren't what I'd call,
"friends," then?
[KEI] You've always been
so observant, Cecil.
Are you implying that
this man has friends?
That some people like him?
Sort of...
Kei?
[KEI, TILARNA]
Hm?
You doing all right?
I think so.
I'm here, if you need to talk.
Yeah, appreciate it.
[TILARNA]
What was that exchange about?
[KEI]
Don't worry about it.
[TILARNA]
No, I'm curious. Tell me.
[KEI]
Fine, she's my ex.
[TILARNA]
Hm? What is an ex?
[KEI]
Forget it.
[ROTH] The timing of the
attack is the problem here.
They were either watching
Alvarez or there was a leak.
[KEI] And there's no way
to tell which it was.
Could be either, or any
number of other possibilities.
But you can rest easy about
our brave little E. T. knight.
She doesn't even know
how to make a phone call.
[TILARNA] I do, so.
I read a book about it.
Oh, really? Wow, she knows
how to read! Whoa.
That's great.
So, anyway, I'll be keeping
my reports to a minimum, boss.
[ROTH] Sounds good.
Just be careful out there.
[KEI]
Roger that.
Well, what do we do next?
[KEI] Nothing exciting,
just police work.
But, it's late.
We'll start tomorrow.
I see.
[KEI] Where are you staying.
I'll drop you off.
[gasps]
[KEI] This is my number.
I don't want any trouble,
so do us both a favor and go to
your room and straight to sleep.
Don't worry. I'm not a child.
Well, you look like one,
and that worries me, you know?
[TILARNA]
For your information, I'm 26.
Yeah, and that's only 18
in Earth years. Later.
[TILARNA]
Wait!
[KEI sighs]
It's so damn cold tonight.
[phone rings]
Hello?
[TILARNA]
I got kicked out of the hotel.
Huh?!
[TILARNA] They say you can't
have weapons in the building.
They demanded to
hold onto my sword.
[KEI] Then just let
them hold onto it.
[TILARNA]
I can't do that!
A knight's sword is as
valuable as their life!
Then find a park bench to
sleep on. I don't care.
‐‐[TILARNA] Bu‐‐
‐‐[phone clicks]
[sirens blaring]
[KEI grunts]
Damn. Damn!
[car horn honks]
[TILARNA gasps]
[KEI groans]
[KEI] The sleeping quarters at
the station are always full.
And a lot of those guys
don't like Semanians.
You can stay at my place.
[TILARNA]
What? Sleep at your place?
[KEI] Don't freak out.
I'm not some pervert.
[TILARNA]
That's not what bothers me.
I don't want any
rumors or scandal.
Anything that could damage
my honor or reputation‐‐
[KEI] Then just keep it
to yourself, if you know how.
[KEI] Come on in. You can
get your stuff later.
[TILARNA exhales]
What do you need a mask for?
[KEI]
'Cause I'm allergic to cats.
Huh?
[KUROI purrs]
[TILARNA]
Kae!
[KEI]
Hm? What?
Oh, I meant the cat.
"Kae" is the word for
cat in my language.
[KEI] I thought you
were saying my name.
[TILARNA] Your kae‐‐cat.
What is its name?
[KEI]
Kuroi.
What's "allergic" mean? Huh?
[KUROI purrs]
[KEI] I have trouble
breathing around cats.
It's something I was born with.
I'm confused.
Why do you have a cat if it
affects your breathing?
[KEI] You're always full
of questions, aren't you?
Gimme a break, will ya?
[KEI]
About three months ago, I think.
I was chasing after
a drug dealer.
Kuroi was a stray, and the
perp hit her with his car.
And then what?
[KEI] I caught the guy,
and she survived.
No one else in the
department wanted her,
so I brought her here.
It's only temporary, but until
I find her a better home,
I'm looking after her.
Even though you're allergic?
[KEI]
What else am I supposed to do?
It's partly my
fault she got hurt.
I've been asking around but
haven't had any luck yet.
[TILARNA giggles]
[KEI]
What?
[TILARNA]
Nothing.
[KEI]
What's so funny?
Sorry, Kei. It's just funny.
[KEI grunts]
[KUROI purrs]
[TILARNA giggles]
[speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA]
Kae Imatoeba,
you're more sensitive than
you seemed at first.
[KEI]
No, I'm really not.
I just wouldn't be able
to sleep at night
if I had thrown an injured
cat out in the cold.
So, it's selfish of me, really.
[TILARNA] You're saying
I'm just like Kuroi, then?
[KEI] If you don't like it,
the park's an option.
[TILARNA]
No, I'll stay here. I like it.
[KEI]
Hold on, you like my place?
[TILARNA]
No. This kae.
I like her enough to make
it worth staying here.
[chuckles]
[KEI] Okay, find a place
to sleep. Anywhere's fine.
And don't let Kuroi
in the bedroom.
[TILARNA]
Kei Matoba?
I was feeling a
little lonely earlier.
[speaks Farbani]
[KEI] You're welcome.
And uh, "good night" is.
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[KEI]
Oh, right.
[KEI speaks Farbani]
[gasps]
[KEI] "Kae Imatoeba"
means "fearful kitten."
She's been making fun of
my name this whole time.
[music blaring]
[grunts]
[music stops]
[ELBAJI] Hope I didn't keep
you waiting, Mr. Kareem.
[KAREEM] Just don't waste
any more time, Mr. Elbaji.
Let's get to it.
[ELBAJI chuckles]
Okay, terrorist guy.
I love cash payments, don't you?
You can pay us the rest of
it when you get the goods.
Of course. You seem to be
doing well for yourself.
[ELBAJI] I guess so.
Thanks to those poor fairies,
we can all live the good life.
Their loss is our gain.
That brand new car, for example?
Three‐hundred thousand.
These flashy kicks?
They're 3,000.
But I can have a good time
with a chick for three bucks.
You know why that is, friend?
No.
Because I'm hot, man.
That's why!
And you do know
what they say, right?
Earth girls are easy.
They only care 'bout looks.
Advantage: me.
[KAREEM] Congratulations, but
I'm just here for the product.
Sorry, right. Hey, Zelada!
[ZELADA] Yes, my lord,
what may I do for you?
[ELBAJI]
Mr. Kareem,
allow me to introduce
you to Zelada the Sage.
[KAREEM] He's the wizard
you were telling me about?
[ELBAJI]
Yeah.
He's the greatest when it
comes to controlling the dead.
[ZELADA] Your words do me
great honor, sir. I'm grateful.
I only do what I can for
the sake of my master.
[KAREEM]
He called them, "the dead."
Was he talking about
fairy dust users?
Yes, indeed he was.
My magic has no effect
on the pure of soul.
Those who use the drug
fall right under my spell.
[ELBAJI] And that's where
this thing comes in!
And is that device
the fairy bomb?
[ELBAJI]
A prototype, but yeah.
And you're about to see
me put it to the test.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
[ELBAJI] I called these guys.
Dialed 9‐1‐1.
Told them some suspicious
people were causing trouble.
[COP A]
This place is off‐limits.
Come on. Hands above
your heads, all of you.
Check this, watch your eyes.
[COPS shout]
[KAREEM grunts]
[ELBAJI] It works immediately!
Verdict, Zelada?
[ZELADA]
A total success, my lord.
Judging by the look of them,
both officers are
already deceased.
How bout you have them give
us a nice, little salute.
As you wish, my lord.
Now, have one of them
shoot the other.
Yes.
‐‐[gunshot]
‐‐[KAREEM gasps]
Poor bastard! He blew him away!
So, what next? How about this!
Make that stupid piggy
dance on the hood!
[HENCHMEN laughing, chattering]
[ELBAJI]
Zelada, you call that dancing?
‐‐[ZELADA] Apologies, sir.
‐‐You need some lessons, bro!
[ELBAJI laughs]
Aw man, that's
freakin' hilarious, right?
[KAREEM] How many can
he control like this?
Five, or ten thousand.
Really. As many as you like,
I've controlled up to
about 300 at once.
[KAREEM]
Good god.
And that's just the prototype.
Imagine the real thing, bud.
We use a potent fairy...
Every inch of its body...
The blast radius...
Bro, It covers about
five kilometers.
That's the size of a nuke.
We could overthrow
superpower governments
with this in our hands.
Do whatever you
want with it, my man.
Thing is, to work it,
you'll have to rent Zelada, too.
[KAREEM]
Just name your price.
All right. Good.
Get the cash, and it's yours.
[ZELADA] My lord. Have you
finished with this one?
[ELBAJI]
Yeah, take care of him.
♪
[KEI] It's not the first time
I've been a pallbearer
for a coworker.
Probably not the last.
It's what we sign up for.
[KEI] That's three
casualties this month.
Morale's in the gutter,
we're spread thin,
some are starting to crack.
I hear you, Matoba.
But the city council's trying to
cut the budget even more.
They don't have to live the
harsh reality we do. Bastards.
You good?
Yeah. Don't worry just
focus on the case.
[KEI exhales]
[TILARNA]
Are you all right?
[KEI sighs]
What do you mean?
[TILARNA]
Nothing.
Let's go.
[TILARNA]
Was it very long?
[KEI]
What?
[TILARNA] Your friendship
with the deceased.
[KEI] I guess...
Rick was a stand‐up guy.
Although he always rooted
for the wrong baseball team,
no matter how bad they sucked.
[TILARNA] In my country,
it's said that those
who are mourned by many,
reach a place of peace and
eternal spring after death.
Detective Fury.
He's one of those.
You trying to cheer me up?
Is that bad?
'Course not.
What should you say to someone
when they're trying to help?
[KEI] Dasch zanna .
Thank you, I guess.
[TILARNA]
Well done.
[phone rings]
[TILARNA, KEI grunt]
[JAMIE]
Kei, got a sec?
What's up, Jamie?
[JAMIE]
You remember that patrol car
that went missing last night?
[KEI] Yeah, the one from
the twenty‐second precinct.
[JAMIE] Right, well, they
recovered it in Eastrock Park.
With two dead officers inside.
All we know right now is
they were murdered at a
construction site in Redmoor.
Whoever did it brought them
here in their squad car
and rolled the damn
thing right into the lake.
Sure it was double murder?
The angle of this one's wound,
it looks a lot more like
a suicide. Seems odd.
[DETECTIVE A]
Not sure.
We'll just have to
wait on the autopsy.
Well, lemme have my police
dog take a look. Tilarna!
[gasps]
Uh...
Good job. I'm impressed that
you even remembered my name.
[KEI] Spare me and a look
at the bodies, will ya?
Bonah Tilarna . That's what
I told you to call me.
Enough talking, start looking.
These were dead, too.
Exactly the same as the
assassin and the drug dealer.
You mean, they were
regular fairy dust users?
They were cops.
Yes, I'm sure of it.
If a cop were using,
his coworkers would
be onto it right away.
Maybe they used gold jewelry.
Gold jewelry?
[TILARNA] It can enhance
the power of latena.
But if you want
something this potent,
you must be perfectly
precise in crafting it,
with no mistakes.
Not even to the width of
a single human hair.
Even the best craftsmen
in my country would fail.
I could always
be mistaken, though.
Well, hold on. A craftsman
might not be able to do it,
but a computer‐controlled
machine could, for sure.
[TILARNA]
Huh?
[KEI]
There you are, bingo.
What's that mean?
Not many hits for people
buying manufacturing machinery,
but I found someone using a
dummy corporation. See?
Dennis Elbaji.
A Semanian club owner.
What the hell else
would a guy like that
want with manufacturing
machinery?
[TILARNA]
Let's arrest him!
[KEI]
Yeah? What for?
Anything! We need to
capture and question him!
We can't do that.
On this planet, we worship a god
called "fundamental rights,"
which dictate that you have
to have evidence to bring
someone in for questioning.
[TILARNA]
But we're running out of time!
There's a whole lot
of paperwork involved.
[TILARNA] Don't you get it?
Her life is in danger!
Her life? You mean the fairy?
Seems like this is personal.
[TILARNA]
Do you even care, Kei?
If that fiel, or fairy, dies,
would that mean nothing to you?
I would feel responsible.
Well I'm... especially liable.
[KEI]
You going to the restroom?
[KEI grunts]
[KEI gasps]
[KEI] I thought she valued
this thing more than her life.
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.