[KEI]
We better follow him.
[TILARNA]
Zelada?
[KEI] He's gonna use that
bomb any minute now.
Better stay close to me, Kei.
I'm the only one who can
spot the enemy's ambush.
We're partners. Trust me.
[KEI grunts]
Got it.
[gasps]
Leahyah!
[KEI]
Wait! It's a trap!
[TILARNA] I don't care.
I have to save her!
[KEI]
I know that, but‐‐Dammit!
What do I do with this thing?
I don't know, just smash it!
[KEI]
Are you kidding?
That's a good way
to make it detonate.
Gotta disarm it somehow.
I don't know. Is this even
technically a bomb?
[ZELADA] What a reckless,
futile endeavor.
You cannot stop what's coming.
So, you might as
well run for it now.
Hurry and you'll escape. Go!
[TILARNA]
Damn you!
[KEI] Something about that
stupid grin on your face
makes me even more
motivated to take you down.
[ZELADA] Charming, but we
both know you won't.
Shut up!
[ZELADA]
See? You're helpless.
[KEI gasps]
It's an illusion!
There!
[KEI grunts]
[KEI yells]
[TILARNA]
Kei!
[TILARNA grunts]
[ZELADA] Well, that's
unfortunate, Sir Matoba.
It appears that you've
lost once again.
And now, for your little friend.
[ZELADA grunts]
I'll enjoy this part!
[KEI] Dammit, where is he?
I can't see him.
No. Don't rely on vision.
Follow the sound.
The sound...
[KEI grunts]
[KEI]
Coming from over there.
[KEI grunts]
[gunshot]
[ZELADA groans]
No! This searing pain!
[TILARNA shouts]
[ZELADA groans]
[ZELADA]
Yes. Nicely done.
I haven't been wounded like this
in a hundred and three years.
You're wasting
your last moments.
It's time to make your peace
and prepare for death!
Not yet.
I'm afraid I cannot bring
shame upon the Marzeny Sect
by dying at the hands
of a mere Barshe.
Therefore...
[TILARNA gasps, shouts]
[ZELADA]
...I must bid you farewell!
[ZELADA laughs]
[TILARNA gasps]
‐‐[KEI grunts]
‐‐[footsteps]
[TILARNA]
Kei!
I got rid of Zelada.
But I don't have any elixir
to heal you, I'm sorry.
[KEI grunts]
Go. Run. Now!
[TILARNA]
No. No time for that.
I suppose we'll just spend our
last few moments together.
You should be grateful.
A boorish, uncouth,
sarcastic man like you
getting to die next
to someone like me?
Please go. You can make it.
[speaks Farbani]
[LEAHYAH gasps]
[TILARNA] As I promised.
I've come to rescue you.
When I was child lost in the
forest, you did the same for me.
You showed me the way out‐‐
helped me get back home.
Remember the promise we made?
That, no matter what,
we'd always be friends.
That's why I'm here. I had
to uphold the oath we swore.
At least I saved you
from dying alone.
So, please, Leahyah.
Don't be afraid.
We are together.
[LEAHYAH sighs]
Leahyah? You can't. Stop this!
Don't do it! Leahyah!
[TILARNA]
Leahyah!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
[grunts, coughs]
I'm alive... What is this?
[TILARNA]
I used a healing spell.
[gasps]
[TILARNA]
I needed an elixir.
One that could counteract the
damage caused by the poison.
Something with very
powerful latena.
[KEI]
An elixir?
[TILARNA] I was able to
make one from her body.
So, the fairy died, anyway?
[TILARNA whimpers]
She did.
The bomb needed a living
fairy as a catalyst.
I suppose she knew that.
[grunts]
[TILARNA] She sacrificed her
life in order to save me.
To save all of us.
[TILARNA] Kei Matoba.
Thanks for everything.
[KEI] Uh, sure. You, too.
I appreciate it.
[HARBOR]
[TILARNA]
I'm going home in shame,
instead of dying with honor like
I'd hoped, but I leave knowing
that there are some good
warriors on earth, after all.
[KEI]
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
[TILARNA]
My brooch.
I pulled some strings
to get it from O'Neill.
This thing's worth a lot.
Wouldn't want to
lose it to that guy.
Yes, but‐‐
Just shut up and
take it, will ya?
[TILARNA giggles]
Bye.
[TILARNA]
I bid you farewell, and I
thank you for your gallantry!
[KEI exhales]
[KEI]
Kuroi, you hungry?
[MALE SPORTSCASTER A]
Slam dunk!
I haven't seen a play
like that in ages!
And nice rebound
from the Semanian.
Here comes the shot
from half‐court. Boom!
Two three‐pointers in a row!
[KEI]
What the hell's this?
Some kind of sports game.
I can't tell what the
rules are, though.
[KEI]
Not that, moron, you!
What the hell are
you doing here?
[TILARNA] Oh. I see now.
I changed my mind.
[KEI]
Huh?!
We're not sure
Zelada's really dead.
And this city is still
full of villains.
I figured I could help.
So, I decided to stay.
[KEI]
You kidding me?
[MALE SPORTSCASTER B]
A nice rebound!
They're not gonna let up.
[KEI] You're a detective now?
And in my department?
Yes, it appears so.
Therefore, I'll be
staying here a while.
Are there any
further questions, partner?
[KEI grunts]
Partner?
[KEI grunts, sighs]
[TILARNA giggles]
[KEI] Well, we've got an
early morning tomorrow.
I'm gonna hit the hay.
[TILARNA] Yeah, sounds good.
Goodnight, Kei.
[KEI speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA]
Hm!
[knocking]
[KEI]
Open up in there! Police!
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG A]
Shit! It's the cops!
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG B]
Who the hell ratted us out?
[KEI]
Go! Go! Go!
[TONY grunts]
[GODNOV]
Freeze!
[KEI grunts]
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG A gasps]
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG B grunts]
[TILARNA grunts]
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG B screams]
[TILARNA]
One move and you're dead.
That's your only warning,
you hear me?
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG B whimpers]
[MALE THUG A groans]
[MALE THUG B grunts]
[TILARNA exhales]
[KEI sighs]
Gotcha, copy... Matoba!
Exedilica, you too! Come here!
[KEI groans]
[KEI]
Hey, Chief Zimmer. What's up?
Can it!
Word is you chopped off one
of the gang member's arms.
It wasn't me, actually.
It was her‐‐
[ZIMMER]
Shut up!
I don't care which one of you
did it. You work as a pair.
You see, if that alien decided
to rape a hundred‐year‐old man,
I'd treat you like you're
the one who did it,
and I'd be calling
you a freakin' sicko
for the rest of
your natural life.
‐‐[KEI] Wait‐‐
‐‐Don't get worked up.
I'm a fair boss, Kei.
So, if you decided to
take a shit on the floor.
I'd make that alien clean
it up with her toothbrush.
Are we clear?
[KEI]
Sure.
[ZIMMER]
I'm glad.
So, then, why'd you
chop off the guy's arm?
His lawyer's gonna have
a field day with that,
and there'll be hell to pay.
[TILARNA] It wasn't his
whole arm, just a finger.
Also, Chief Zimmer, don't call
me an alien anymore.
It's racist, you know.
Oh, oh, oh!
I said something racist?
Thank you for pointing that out!
You know Garner from the
District Attorneys
office, right?
I'll have a talk with him,
but you better have a report
on my desk by 9am tomorrow,
do you understand?
It better not be a
single minute late!
Yeah... Got it.
[ZIMMER]
Alien! You, too!
Hell maybe Matoba can teach
you how to write one!
That guy sucks.
But hopefully he's not a
mole like our last boss.
How dare he chastise
me so harshly?
I was carrying out justice!
Yeah, well,
you took it too far.
Because you let
your guard down!
So it was your fault! And‐‐
I don't seem to remember
asking for your help
in the first place.
[TILARNA gasps] Excuse me,
but I was not finished.
Would it kill you
to say a simple,
"thank you" for
once in your life?
You're nothing but‐‐
[TONY]
Kei!
Over here!
We're being called.
You can berate me later.
[grunts]
He is such a jerk...
[KEI grunts] Hey! Geez!
What is your problem?
You are!
[KEI grunting]
Stop! You're embarrassing me!
[TILARNA]
Rakebye!
Why are you flirting with her?
What?! I'm not!
Did something happen?
[TONY]
We're not quite sure.
This garage belongs to
the guys we just cuffed.
[KEI]
Hm?
A coffin.
[TONY sighs] It gets a
whole lot weirder than that.
Do you think it
belongs to a Semanian?
[TILARNA]
I don't know.
I've seen letters like
these in ancient texts.
Moon. Forbidden. Blood.
That's all I can decipher.
[KEI]
What's inside?
[TONY]
Could be some valuable artifact.
We have to be careful with it.
[GODNOV] Who gives a shit?
Just smash it open.
[TONY sighs]
[TILARNA gasps]
Is that thing... a mummy?
[TILARNA] It appears to be
some kind of princess to me.
[CECIL] At this point,
I'm not totally certain,
but it looks like
a Semanian woman.
Oh, you really think so?
It's a mummy we found
in a Semanian coffin,
wearing Semanian clothes.
What else would it be?
[CECIL] They have a different
number of teeth.
Humans have 32 teeth,
but Semanians only have 28.
[KEI]
Hm!
[TILARNA]
Uh?
[gasps]
[CECIL] I can perform
an autopsy, if you want,
but we typically deal with
fresh corpses, not mummies.
You might be better off taking
her to an archaeologist,
don't you think?
[KEI] We can send her to
a lab when you're done.
Time of death,
cause of death, age.
I want that stuff tonight,
if possible.
Kei. Just for your information,
I've been on the clock
since this morning.
Well, hey, isn't that a
weird coincidence? I have too!
[CECIL]
You are such a jerk.
I heartily agree.
Thank you!
I'm totally shocked that
you decided to stay here
and work with this guy!
It was temporary insanity.
I deeply regret that choice now.
[CECIL] I know, right?
He's mean and cold‐hearted.
But every once in a while he'll
be nice and catch you off‐guard.
It's exhausting,
but don't let him fool you.
[TILARNA] I don't quite follow,
but I'll keep that in mind.
Hey.
You would never believe what
he did the first day we met.
He comes in here with the
cadaver of some gang member
he had just killed, and do
you now what he says?
"Don't steal the change from
his pockets." Like, what?
I know what you mean!
I literally saved
his life today.
And all he said was he didn't
"ask for my help"!
So the next time, I think
I'll just let him die.
[CECIL]
Yeah, you should.
And then maybe we can
dissect his body together.
Let's cut him open
and take a selfie!
[TILARNA] Great idea,
Bozah Epps! I can't wait!
You can call me Cecil,
Miss Exedilica.
[TILARNA] Okay, Cecil.
And you may call me Tilarna!
[KEI] Oh, great.
You're best friends now.
Uh, Dr. Epps, the results
for the lab work came in.
Glad you're so friendly
with our clients,
but don't forget that we
have other work to do here.
I won't forget.
I'll be right there.
[CHAPMAN]
Tsk.
[TILARNA] What's his problem?
Isn't he your apprentice?
[CECIL] My assistant.
He doesn't like me.
No idea why.
Or maybe he does.
Seems to me like he might
have a crush on you.
Oh. You jealous?
Ah, come on now.
I'll wait to hear from you.
[TILARNA]
I'm a little concerned.
Bodies like that aren't
something to be taken lightly.
[KEI] If you're worried about
bacteria or something, don't.
Cecil's a pro.
[TILARNA]
Not that.
The spirits of the dead
are drawn to corpses.
It's not wise to touch them.
[KEI] That isn't an option.
The corpse is evidence.
Anyway, she might belong
to some noble somewhere.
I've been wondering.
[KEI]
Huh?
Are you and Cecil
particularly close?
I already explained that,
didn't I?
[TILARNA]
Oh, yes, that "ex" word.
It wasn't in the dictionary.
[KEI] Don't worry about it,
all right? We're still friends.
[TILARNA sighs]
Wait. "Still friends".
What does that mean?
Just forget it.
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG A]
Oh, hell no, man.
I ain't talking to no cop.
Bring me my damn lawyer, bitch!
[KEI groans]
[TILARNA shouts]
[gasps, grunts]
Villain! You'd better
start talking, fast!
You know what happens to
criminals who defile corpses?
I'll tell you, but I don't
think you'll like it!
[TILARNA] Their limbs get cut
off while they're still alive,
then they're stuffed into a
barrel with poison insects,
left overnight, then thrown
into the Obiza swamp!
If you don't want that
to happen to you,
start talking about that coffin!
So I'm the good cop now?
[CECIL]
A body of unknown origin.
Kept in a Semanian coffin for an
indeterminate length of time.
The teeth and the cervical
vertebrae suggest that she's
most likely a Semanian female.
Simultaneous signs
of desiccation
and aging are present,
and mummification.
A form we don't see on Earth.
This is an archaeological
examination not
requiring autopsy.
[CECIL]
Chapman!
Yeah?
Would you mind running
a CT scan of the body?
Sure thing, in a bit.
Sorry. I need it now.
[CHAPMAN sighs]
[thudding]
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG A grunts]
Okay! Please don't
hurt me, lady!
We stole the coffin,
but I don't know whose it is.
We just heard it was worth
a lot of money, that's all!
Where did you steal
it from?! Talk!
Doras Derill. A graveyard
in Doras Derill!
[TILARNA]
Wait, what?
[MALE SEMANIAN THUG A grunts]
A corpse from Doras Derill?
What does that mean?
Cecil is... in danger.
What?
Hurry!
[KEI]
Hey...! Well, shit.
‐‐[clattering]
‐‐[CECIL gasps]
[CECIL exhales]
Is everything okay?
Chapman?
[CHAPMAN groans]
[CECIL gasps]
[CECIL]
What's going on?
[CHAPMAN grunting]
[gasps]
[CECIL gasps]
[CECIL shouts]
[TILARNA grunts]
[speaks Farbani]
[TILARNA gasps]
[CECIL screams]
Cecil, no!
[CECIL gasps]
Tilarna?
The... body! Chapman is...
[BOTH gasp]
[TILARNA grunts]
Run, Cecil!
But... I...
Now!
[TILARNA speaks Farbani]
Nii farba. Milemen douma.
Gaana mobih.
[TILARNA]
The old language...
[gasps]
[TILARNA grunts]
[shouts]
[TILARNA]
Did I...?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.