[KEI yells]
Tilarna!
[TILARNA]
Jeez! What's your problem?
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA]
What. Kuroi okay?
[KEI]
You let her in here didn't you?
I'm allergic‐‐
you trying to kill me?
[TILARNA]
Let's pause and evaluate.
Are you having
trouble breathing?
[inhales, exhales]
You don't seem to be
allergic to cats anymore.
Remember, up on that roof,
when you were at death's door?
The elixir I gave you
must've fixed that too.
You "fixed it? Hey, wait.
That whole damn rooftop fiasco
happened over a month ago.
Yes, it did.
Why didn't you say something?
I've been wearing that mask
every night like an asshole!
[chuckles] Yeah, and I've
been laughing at you.
Huh?
[meows]
[SHOPKEEPER A]
Pitas!
[KEI] When we talked last week,
you said it was fine!
What changed?
The consulate's vouched
for her and everything.
Come on, that's housing
discrimination... Man!
[KEI]
Hm?
Who were you just talking to?
A real estate agent. I'm looking
for an apartment for you.
[TILARNA] I'm perfectly
content with where
I'm living at the moment.
[KEI]
Yeah, well, I'm not content!
You're freeloading!
I'm doing this
for your own sake!
[shouts]
[RADIO A]
All emergency vehicles, code 32.
Semanian suspect, in white
truck, fled traffic stop.
Pursuing officers requesting
back up, code three.
Hey, um...
[KEI]
He'll pay for that!
[TILARNA screams]
[TILARNA whines]
Slow down! Or just kill me!
The window's right there!
You're free to jump!
[TILARNA screaming]
[KEI]
Ha, ha!
Keep an eye on the car.
[KEI]
Huh? Where is he?
Shit...
[siren blarring]
[KEI]
Hm?
[COP A]
Hey, you mind moving this car?
Sergeant Kei Matoba with
the Special Vice Squad.
[COP A]
Oh, hey.
Man, you made a mess here.
Where's the perp?
[KEI]
He split.
Oh, dang. What do we have here?
[KEI]
Porn, dummy.
I know. Supposedly, it was
stolen from some warehouse.
Just a bunch of titty mags?
Seems weird.
[KEI]
It's all legal, too.
Nothing too hardcore
about any of it.
[COP B] I dunno,
this is pretty hardcore.
[KEI]
Which one?
[COP B]
This one right here.
[KEI]
Come on, that?
[COP B]
That ain't normal.
My girlfriend would never be
down for that is all I'm sayin'.
[KEI] Sounds like you
need a new girlfriend.
I do not‐‐ she's as
freaky as any other chick!
[TILARNA]
Hey, Kei!
[KEI gasps, clears throat]
Uh, hey. What's up?
They told me we had to
move it, so I did it myself.
[KEI]
Hold on. Moved what?
The car, duh.
[COP C shouts]
You know how to drive?
I've been practicing
in secret.
It's pretty easy if
you're not going too far.
[COP B gasps]
[KEI]
Hm? What the...? No!
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[explosion]
Doreany machines
burn easily, don't they?
[ZIMMER]
So, you two.
Guess what I'm
feeling right now.
[KEI sighs]
[TILARNA] Hm... You look
a little nauseated.
[ZIMMER]
I'm pissed! Any guesses why?
Because of you two
dumbass cowboys!
I've been getting angry calls
all day because of your
car chase stunt! And they're
making me take that case!
Now, I've gotta waste resources
on a bunch of porno mags
that were gonna end up under
some 12‐year‐old's mattress!
Now you see why I'm pissed?
You still think
I look nauseated?
Do you? Answer me!
[KEI grunts]
When are we gonna talk about
my freaking car, man?
[ZIMMER]
Hm?
[KEI] I've been asking the
department for years
for a car to use on
undercover cases,
and I always got the run‐around!
So, I had to resort to
using my own damn car,
because I had no choice,
and look how that turned out!
Then I'm paired up
with this damn alien.
I leave her alone
for one second.
And crash, she's dead!
[KEI sobs]
Matoba?
[KEI]
She was such a wonderful car!
The perfect partner,
always there for me
when things got rough!
And now‐‐now she's...
[sobbing continues]
There, there, it's all right.
[KEI shouts]
Shut up!
You killed my best friend in
cold blood, you dirty alien!
Stop being racist, Kei!
You take that back
right now, or I'll‐‐
[KEI] Or you'll do what?
Kill me, too, just like my car?
Throw me in front of a truck?
Will you be satisfied then?
Since you're hell‐bent on
destroying me. You murderer!
Psychopath! Cold‐blooded killer!
[ZIMMER]
Matoba, that's enough!
I'm sorry it happened,
just stop crying!
[KEI]
I'm not crying!
[ZIMMER]
You are literally weeping!
We'll get you a new car,
so cut the diaper baby shit!
You mean it?
[ZIMMER] There's a police
auction coming up.
If there's a suitable
car up for grabs,
I'll make sure you
get first dibs.
Ha! That's exactly what I
was hoping to hear, Chief.
You know, life's easier when
you've got a great boss.
[ZIMMER] You're like a little
kid begging for a toy, man.
Shit! Anyway, you're still in
charge of this porno mag case.
Huh?
[ZIMMER] It's dumb as hell,
but a crime is a crime!
[KEI exhales]
[ZIMMER] You can enlist
help if you need to.
And Exedilica.
For crissakes, go get
a damn license.
A license?
Yeah. A driver's license.
[KEI] Honestly, the world would
be safer if they didn't let you
have a license. That's like
giving Jeffrey Dahmer
a permit to open a restaurant.
[TILARNA]
Who's that?
[KEI]
Look it up.
Anyway, I guess we'd better
get started on this stupid
porn theft thing. Ugh...
Kei. I have a question.
Yeah, what?
What does this "porn"
word even mean?
[OFFICE]
Huh?
[KEI groans]
[KEI]
This is porn.
[KEI] Drugs and guns
are our jurisdiction,
but we get to tackle all the
smut cases, too. Fun, right?
That one's not even illegal.
This magazine is...
indecent and repulsive!
I cannot believe this!
You're barbarians!
All earthlings are insane!
[KEI grunts] Your own mom and
dad did some version of that,
just so you know.
[TILARNA]
You're lying!
How dare you insult
my parents like that!
That's beyond the pale,
even for you!
My mother and my father?
Never! Ever!
Just keep telling
yourself that.
You must've been formed by
cell division or something,
I guess, like bacteria.
I mean, that makes more
sense than the normal way,
to be honest.
Hey. You all right?
[TILARNA]
This can't be. It just can't.
[KEI] Now that I think about it,
your world doesn't have
a lot of photographs
in general, does it?
Makes sense that porn
would be so shocking.
[KEI]
Hey, Cammy, whatcha up to?
I'm not helping you
look for porn, vete.
Jamie, how's my
favorite colleague?
Forget about it, Kei.
Drowning in paperwork.
O...kay.
[KEI sighs]
[KEI]
Hey, friends‐‐
[door clatters]
Uh... Oh, Tony!
Is it me, or have you
gotten even more handsome?
That tie is really something!
[TONY] Oh, this old thing?
I've had it for ages,
but it's great with
my complexion, right?
I think so. But, Kei, you're
kind of creeping me out.
[KEI]
Am I really? Not my intention‐‐
Look, I was hoping you could
help me with something.
[TONY] Kei is officially
the absolute worst!
Flattering me into
his porn mag trap?
The perps are probably
a buncha 12‐year‐olds.
I bet it was bound
for Leto Semani.
If they could smuggle porno
in there, they'd make a fortune.
Most people in that world
don't even have TVs.
[TONY] I guess men are morons,
no matter what world they're in.
[GODNOV] Are you surprised?
We're ruled by our balls.
[phone beeps]
[TONY sighs] And there it is.
That's from O'Neill.
He is fast.
[TONY]
They're not far away. Gun it.
[TONY sighs]
[GODNOV]
You seem upset.
[TONY] Of course, I'm upset.
You know I hate being McCloud.
He's the scum of the earth.
I don't disagree, but I
do like his sense of style.
[TONY grunts]
[clears throat]
[GODNOV]
Transformation complete.
Good luck, Detective McCloud.
Cut the crap. Or do you want
me to put a bullet in you?
[GODNOV] Here let me take
a pic for your boyfriend.
Don't you dare! It's secret!
[GODNOV] I'm messing
with you. We're here.
Enough small talk.
Just introduce me to
this little thief. And fast.
[BIZ]
Hey, detective McBee, my man.
No, wait. Are you going by
McCloud now? I forget.
Well, I did what you
wanted me to.
I made some enquiries
of my flock if anyone
was trying to
offload some porno.
Social media?
[BIZ] Mm‐hm. Social media.
Nothing's faster. You see?
Your guy.
[GAVIN whimpers]
[GAVIN]
Hm? Who're you?
Did I say you could
sit down there?
[TONY]
Don't look over your shoulder.
[GAVIN gasps] You're the
moving man? Or, the fence?
[TONY]
What's your name?
Uh. It's Gavin.
Well, I'm McCloud.
This is Ivanov.
We don't do handshakes.
Why don't we get right
down to business?
Yeah, okay, sure. I need
to sell the stuff, fast,
but I need proof that
you've got the money.
Hey, now. You sayin'
I look broke?
I've been in this business
since you were a little brat,
hangin' offa your
mama's titties.
Better not piss me off.
Right. Sorry. It's just. I'm in
a hurry to offload, is all.
[GAVIN yelps]
[TONY] I'm really a
nice guy, I promise.
Can't say the same
for my partner, though.
Last week he got in a fight
with some punk‐ass thug,
and ended up eating his
eyeballs right outta his skull!
You wanna keep your
pretty eyeballs, don'tcha?
[GODNOV]
Hey, handsy, we're working.
[gasps] Anyway, kid, how 'bout
you show us the goods now?
[GAVIN]
Sure, here you go.
Earth has got porn everywhere
you look, but not in our world.
There, even regular
photos are still rare.
That's what gave us the idea.
[TONY]
Hmph.
A little while back, a group
of nobles paid a ton of money
just for a few nude
shots of Miss July.
Enough dough to
buy a giant estate!
I wanted a piece of that
pie for myself, you know?
Porno mags, huh?
Not gonna lie, I've got a major
hard‐on for Miss July, too.
Total boner material.
[GAVIN]
Really? You know who she is?
Sure do! Those boobies
are famous in this world,
little buddy.
Pitched a huge tent.
Took me from 6 to midnight
[TONY, GAVIN laugh]
[TONY]
"Total boner material?" Gross!
I'm traumatized!
Boobies and dick jokes?
Makes me sick!
Sex isn't about objectification!
It's about intimacy!
Two hearts connecting
through physical communion!
It's the strangest thing,
my friend.
The more you hate it, the more
realistic your acting gets.
Such irony, yes?
[TONY] I wish I'd chosen
a life on the stage.
No, don't say that! At least
we have found our next step.
[TONY sighs] I need some
sugar to calm my nerves.
Take me to the donut shop.
[GODNOV]
Your wish is my command.
[KEI] All right, then.
Get it all set up. Talk soon.
[KEI grunts]
You about ready to head home?
[TILARNA]
No, I'm meeting Cecil tonight.
Cecil, why?
‐‐[door clatters]
‐‐[ZIMMER] Matoba.
Is this what I think?
[ZIMMER] Your new ride's in
the parking lot. Take a look.
[KEI chuckles]
Sweet!
I liked your old car better,
it was a lot cuter. So...
[KEI chuckles]
[engine revs]
I'm taking her for a spin!
Have fun with Cecil!
Later, nerd.
[TILARNA gasps]
[CECIL] Okay, gently press
down on the gas pedal.
[TILARNA]
Okay.
[CECIL]
Just like that.
Now, press the brakes, gently,
and turn to the right.
Ah! Too far!
[TILARNA]
Oh, no. Sorry!
[CECIL] No, it's all right.
What's on your mind?
[TILARNA gasps]
You could practice driving
with Kei, couldn't you?
So why me? I was a
little surprised, to be honest.
There's nothing on
my mind, really.
No, there is.
Listen, Kei seems to think of
you as a friend he can trust.
[CECIL]
A friend he can trust, huh?
Am I wrong?
Yes and no.
We used to be lovers.
[TILARNA gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[CECIL]
What's wrong?
[TILARNA] Uh. Sorry!
I just... You and Kei?
[CECIL]
Are you surprised?
[TILARNA]
Is that what an "ex" means?
I didn't think he was saying you
two'd been together in that way.
I'm not saying our
relationship is like that.
[CECIL] Right, you're talking
about your relationship
as work partners, then?
[TILARNA]
Yes, exactly! Partners!
[CECIL]
You have nothing to worry about.
When Kei doesn't like someone,
he makes it blatantly obvious.
He shows no mercy.
[TILARNA sighs]
[CECIL] If you don't mind
my asking, do you like him?
Like him? What kind
of question is that?
[CECIL]
You hate him, then?
[TILARNA] No. I don't
hate him. I don't think.
I'll admit, I do want to
slap him sometimes.
But, at the end of the day,
I just want him to
see me as an equal.
That's the real reason I decided
to practice driving a car.
I feel bad about what happened.
About wrecking the
car he loved so much.
[CECIL] You two are like a
brother and sister team.
It's kinda sweet.
[TILARNA]
We are?
You're the strong‐willed,
little sister type,
that's for sure. Wow.
You know, that makes sense.
Don't tell him I told you this,
but Kei had a little sister
who died about ten years ago.
[TILARNA]
Huh?
[CECIL] She was lively
and willful, like you.
So maybe he sees something of
her in you, and that's painful.
[TILARNA] That does make sense,
but he's never mentioned it.
‐‐[engine revs]
‐‐[ALL] Hm?
[door opens, shuts]
[car beeps]
You're late, Kei.
[KEI] Oh, yeah. Sorry, I was
riding this girl hard all night.
[CAMMY] Seriously?
Who says crap like that?
Eyes here, people!
It's almost time for that gang
of smut thieves to get here.
I need all you guys
to be our backup.
[KEI]
Hey, how'd it go with Cecil?
Oh, shut up.
C'mon we're on the clock.
[KEI]
Hm?
[KEI] I've got eyes on
the target. Stand by, kids.
[KEI]
Looking good.
Crap. Hold on. What's this?
[CAMMY] I think somebody got
double crossed. He's pissed.
Not good! All units,
head in! Go, go, go!
[COP F]
Don't move! This is the police!
[COP G]
You bastard!
[KEI]
No!
[KEI grunts]
[TONY gasps]
[GODNOV gasps]
[KEI]
After them! Tony's in danger!
I'm sorry, Sergeant!
[KEI]
Dammit! My eyes!
[TILARNA] Better leave
the driving to me!
[KEI]
Tilarna?
[TILARNA] Come on!
We have to save Tony, right?
[KEI]
Wait! What are you doing?
[TILARNA]
Let's go!
[KEI]
It's in reverse! Reverse!
That's what I meant to do!
[KEI yells]
[KEI]
Hm?
[yells] You're on the wrong
side of the road! Other side!
[KAI gasps]
I've got the hang of it.
Now I understand
this "speed" thing!
Hey, Kei. Is this what
it feels like to be high?
I would rather
you just kill me!
The window's right there.
Feel free to jump!
[KEI gasps]
[TILARNA]
I got 'em!
[KEI]
No! Stop!
[TILARNA, KEI yell]
[KEI]
Shit!
Hey. Tilarna.
[TILARNA groans]
[KEI grunts]
[KEI]
Tony. Are you okay?
[TONY] Sorry. I didn't
expect things to go south
the way they did back there.
It's fine. Just keep still.
Now, then.
[TILARNA exhales]
[KEI] We're lucky that
nobody died in all this.
Never drive like that again,
you understand me?
I've been quite useful
in this case!
[KEI]
Useful? Don't be ridicu‐‐
Stop treating me like
nothing but a burden!
[gasps]
[TILARNA]
I don't just mean with driving.
I'm studying hard. Every day!
You of all people
should get that.
And if you don't, no one will!
[KEI grunts] Sorry. I guess
I went a too far before.
I don't think
you're useless, Tilarna.
Really?
[KEI]
Yeah.
You're not messing
with me right now?
That's what I said.
Forget about wrecking
the car, it's no big deal.
I think the new
one can be fixed.
Once it's out of the shop,
I'll take you out to
practice driving.
Do you mean that?
[KEI]
Don't get too excited.
But you have to promise
you'll be safer next time.
[electic buzz, explosion]
[gasps]
[KEI]
No, please, no.
The damage seems to have
gotten a little bit worse.
Can it still be fixed?
[KEI] Like hell it's fixable,
you goddamn alien!
[KEI]
I'm back.
Kuroi... Hey!
[KUROI meows]
[KEI]
Hm?
You're finally home.
[KEI] I had to deal with the
aftermath of the car chase,
then I got into a fight
with the real estate agent
about your new place.
What exactly are you doing?
I'll show you. Follow me.
[KEI]
Hm?
[TILARNA] Well? From now on,
this is going to be my room.
You're only the second guest
I've ever had, after Kuroi,
of course. I hope
you feel honored.
Um, technically this
is still my house.
[TILARNA]
Don't worry about that.
It doesn't bother me.
For crying out loud.
[TILARNA]
What?
Don't tell me you're still mad
about that silly car thing.
Don't call it
"that silly car thing!"
[sighs] No, it's gone, and it's
never going to come back.
I'll get over it someday.
I see! I'm happy to hear it!
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft.