[CECIL]
Huh?
It's not in here, either.
We may not be able to find it.
[meowing]
Calm down,
we're not giving up yet.
I know exactly what to do next.
[phone ringing]
[MALE WORKER A] Hello.
New Compton Waste Disposal.
Um, hello. I accidentally threw
something in the trash
that's incredibly important,
but unfortunately,
the garbage has already been
collected for the day.
[MALE WORKER A] Aw, I'm so
sorry to hear that. Goodbye.
Wait! I'm desperate,
please don't hang up!
[MALE WORKER A]
Was there something else?
[CECIL] I told you.
It's really important!
[MALE WORKER A] Sorry, but when
your trash gets picked up,
you lose all rights to
the contents. Okay gotta go.
[CECIL] Did you not
hear me? Oh, I know!
Look, I'm talking about
crucial evidence here.
[MALE WORKER A]
Huh?
[CECIL]
Yes, my name is Cecil Epps.
I'm with the San-Teresa
Metropolitan Police force--
deputy coroner.
Look. If the evidence
I'm referring to is lost,
it will jeopardize
an investigation,
and something really
bad will happen,
so you need to cooperate, or you
could be held accountable!
[CECIL pants, exhales]
[TILARNA meows]
[BIZ groans]
Grant me mercy, Father God!
Please save me, Lord!
Hey, O'Neill.
I came here to ask
you a question.
Take a look at this.
It's the tip you gave me.
Need more information
about the guy you told me
was working with the smuggler.
[MALE PARAMEDIC A]
Sir, I need you to stand back.
The patient is in a lot of pain.
Come on, the guy's
got a hangover.
Hey! Look at my phone, man!
Can you tell me if this is the
guy you saw with smuggler,
or not?
[BIZ]
If I tell you what you want,
Will you promise me one thing?
That I get into heaven.
And travel in first class.
[KEI]
Yeah, man.
With all the fancy wine and
cognac you can guzzle.
[BIZ groans] No way,
I'll never drink another drop.
You better answer me before
you puke, you hungover asshole!
[MALE PARAMEDIC A]
Detective!
[BIZ groans]
[MALE PARAMEDIC A] Great!
Now he's hyperventilating!
Mr. O'Neill! Stay calm and try
to breathe! Everything's okay!
[KEI]
Shit.
[KENNY] Well, that's that.
There he goes.
Hey, Kenny, you happen to
remember the girl O'Neill
went out on a date
with a few days ago?
There's a chance she may
have seen the smuggler
and can help me out.
Oh, yeah, that would be the
S&M queen you saw upstairs,
the one in the kitchen.
I'll assume you're referring
to the lovely lady
who had her head
stuck in the fridge.
Wait, what the hell?
[CECIL]
My name is Cecil Epps.
Well that ID looks
real enough, if you ask me.
I mean not that I've
ever seen one before.
So, Ms. Epps,
What's your home address?
[CECIL] Uh, it's uh,
One seventy-two Caster Street.
Okay, let's see.
Well, Hunter Waste Management
handles that area,
so that's gonna be truck
number three, right over there.
Right In front of the WDT.
[CECIL]
The WDT?
[MALE WORKER A] Stands for
waste disposal terminal.
Everything we collect
gets dumped in there
and then compacted.
[CECIL]
Compacted?!
Wait! Stop! I need to
get something out!
[TILARNA meows]
[CECIL gasps]
[CECIL]
Stop it! I'm begging you, stop!
[MALE WORKER B]
Huh? What the hell?
[gasps]
[TILARNA meows]
[CECIL]
Tilarna!
[KEI]
Chief, it's me, Matoba.
It's about Hellmandes
and the CBP.
[ZIMMER] Oh I know it is, I just
got another call from him.
Guessing you did get
in a fight, then.
He just called you?
[ZIMMER] He said you
won't answer his calls,
and wanted to know whether
you were home or not. Hello?
You listening to me, Matoba?
[KEI]
That means... Uh, yeah.
I hear you, chief, but I'm gonna
have to call you right back.
Hey, Cecil.
[CECIL] I'm so sorry, Kei.
We need to talk about Tilarna.
What happened?
So, you're telling me
that Tilarna and Kuroi
switched bodies? By magic?
I'll buy anything these days.
So right now, it's Tilarna who's
really Kuroi at my house?
Sounds dangerous.
[CECIL]
Why do you say that?
[KEI] I'd better hurry.
Hang in there, Cecil.
I'll call you back.
[CECIL] No, Kei! Kuroi--here at
the dump. I'm afraid she...
Please don't be angry.
I tried to stop her,
but I wasn't able to.
[KEI]
Ah, don't worry about it.
[gasps]
[KEI] It's Tilarna's
brain in there, right?
I'm sure she'll be all right.
We'll talk later.
[MALE WORKER A]
There! I found your cat!
[CECIL]
Tilarna!
[TILARNA] I can smell it.
The scent of latena.
Don't use your nose, though.
Find it with your heart.
[TILARNA]
That's it!
[meows]
[TILARNA meows]
[TILARNA]
Oh, no.
[TILARNA meows]
[TILARNA grunts]
Damn you--tell me
where it is!
[TILARNA grunts]
I know you have the
damn crossbow, give it to me!
My life is on the line here!
Is this...?
[speaks Farbani]
[HELLMANDES] Your little crazy
act won't get you out of this.
Give me the crossbow!
[TILARNA]
Don't touch me.
[HELLMANDES]
What now?
--[TILARNA grunts]
--[HELLMANDES groans]
[TILARNA]
You saw, didn't you?
[HELLMANDES]
Sorry?
[HELLMANDES groans]
I don't know what's
going on here,
but you're in for
a world of pain!
[HELLMANDES groans]
[HELLMANDES]
Please! Don't hurt me!
[TILARNA]
Shut up!
[HELLMANDES grunts]
--I just wanted to make money!
--[TILARNA] I don't care!
[HELLMANDES grunting]
[HELLMANDES pants]
Have mercy!
[TILARNA]
You get no mercy!
[HELLMANDES pants] Please,
you don't have to do this!
Please, Miss!
[gasps]
You're going to die like
the insect you are.
Without a shred of
dignity or grace.
[HELLMANDES yells]
[TILARNA] Curses of Bedayah
be visited upon you!
[KEI]
Stop! Don't kill him!
[HELLMANDES whimpers]
[TILARNA gasps]
That's Tilarna, right?
You're back?
[HELLMANDES sobs]
Yes, Kei.
[HELLMANDES] She spared my life.
She spared my life!
What a dumpster fire.
You'd better clean this up.
That freaky crossbow
only activated because
of your carelessness.
Shut your mouth!
What in the hell is the
matter with you, anyway?
This morning I was
desperate for your help,
and you left for work without
even noticing anything was off!
You think I should have
known that you and the cat
switched bodies? Okay.
[TILARNA]
N-No, but...
[KEI] You were all over
me in your pajamas,
and to be honest, it was
freaking me out. I had to leave.
Was it really freaking you out?
Huh?
Uh, nothing... Hmph.
Whatever. So, what happened
to the crossbow?
Destroyed. Might be
why I switched back.
There's no way to find out
for certain, though--not now.
[KEI]
It is what it is.
[TILARNA] I need to learn
better self-control.
Thanks to you, I didn't
even get to kill that man.
You know that would've gotten
you a murder charge, right?
Hold on a second. He didn't do
anything pervy to you, did he?
He didn't attempt
anything of the sort,
he just saw me in a
state of--never mind,
but he did not violate me!
State of what?
He saw me in a state
that no one ever should,
and that's all you
need to know!
Man, you give me a headache.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you mad that some
strange man saw my butt?
You and I are partners!
You would be just as angry as I
am if you weren't such a cad.
Why should I care?
Shut up! He stole
my dignity, you rakebye !
[KEI]
Whoa, dramatic.
Hey, are we
forgetting something?
Stop trying to change
the subject, Kei!
[KEI, TILARNA]
Wait! Kuroi and Cecil!
[CECIL] Please forgive me,
Tilarna. I failed you.
I tried to save you,
but I couldn't.
[KUROI meows]
[CECIL sobs]
Tilarna!
[CECIL]
I can't believe this.
What if you have to live out
your life this way? I'm sorry!
I don't-- I don't even
know what to say to you!
[gasps]
Huh?
[KUROI meows]
[NARRATOR]
15 years ago, a hyperspace gate
appeared in the middle
of the Pacific Ocean.
Beyond that gate lay
a mysterious world
filled with fairies
and monsters.
The city of San-Teresa
on Kariaena island
became known as
"Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of races,
cultures, and species,
the haves and the have-nots.
San Teresa is the world's
newest "city of dreams."
But, in the shadows, lurk all
kinds of crimes and criminals.
Drugs. Prostitution.
Weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan
Police force maintain a
specialized unit to deal
with the seedy mayhem.
[PARTYGOERS chatter]
[KEI] Man, you're way
overcooking those patties.
Matoba, you wouldn't
be insulting
the Zimmer family recipe,
now, would you?
Is that what they call
"burning it" in your family?
Put it on a tray, lower the
heat, and close the grill cover.
You gotta get that
hot air flowing
over the top of it
to cook it evenly.
Gah, that meat looked
so freakin' tasty, too.
[ZIMMER] Shut up! Whenever you
talk about cars or food,
you sound like a
damn crazy person.
How 'bout you not be a
control freak for once?
[KEI]
I am not a control freak!
[ZIMMER] Yeah, yeah,
that's what they all say.
Anyway, you're in
my house, punk.
That means I'm in
charge of the food!
Now quit your bitchin'
and go get me another beer.
I paid for that meat.
It was expensive, too,
and now you're ruining it.
[TONY] Get in the pool, Kei!
The water feels great!
I'll get in later.
You're a loser.
[TILARNA]
Just ignore him.
He thinks he's too
cool for the pool.
--[JAMIE grunts]
--[BOY groans]
[GODNOV]
What's wrong?
You scared of the
tickle monster?
You are! You got a poopy?
I'll make mommy change you.
[KEI] Hey, who took the
towel off of the clams?
[WOMAN A] That would be me.
Is that a problem?
[KEI] I covered them on purpose.
You have to make it dark
in there or the clams
won't spit out the salt.
[WOMAN A] They already spit
out the sand, didn't they?
[KEI]
Yes, but not the salt.
[JASMINE] Who cares?
Is it that big a deal?
Of course it's a big deal, those
clams are full of salt water.
You gotta make 'em spit
it out before you cook 'em,
or they're inedible!
Look, just don't put any
extra salt in there
and it should be all right.
Actually, don't salt
them at all.
Here we go again. You're always
such a pain in the ass
when it comes to cooking, Kei.
Has anyone ever tell you that?
Yeah, you really are
a control freak.
I hope my son doesn't
end up like you.
I am not a control freak!
[JASMINE] That's just what
a control freak would say.
[WOMEN laugh]
[KAHNS] Good citizens!
San Teresa city...
[KEI]
The mayoral race?
[GODNOV] Yeah, but it's a farce.
No one worth voting for.
This Kahns guy seems
like the best of the bunch.
Nathan Kahns. He was
mayor of Seattle
for two terms, then a City
councilman here for two years.
He looks like the kind of
guy who can't get a date,
no matter how rich
he happens to be.
Maybe, but he's got a lot
of political experience,
and he knows what
he's talking about.
My wife and I are
going to vote for him,
he's a far better choice than
any of the others, right?
[KEI] Mozeleemay's in
the running, too, right?
[GODNOV]
Yeah.
[KEI] I still can't believe
that guy has the balls
to keep running for office.
I hear ya. There's also that
far-right winger, Tourte.
The guy who thinks aliens
should be sent back to space.
What?
[MALE NEWS REPORTER A] Let's go
live with Breaking news!
[FEMALE NEWS REPORTER A]
I'm hearing that...
Did he literally just get shot?
It appears that Kahns
was put in an ambulance.
According to witnesses,
he is unresponsive right now.
[muted] God. How terrible.
I can't believe this happened.
Wow. I just--
Uh, can we cut?
[ZIMMER] Meat's done,
no thanks to you, Matoba.
And where's my beer...?
What's going on?
Well, according to these jokers,
something terrible--
[phone rings]
[ZIMMER] Emergency briefing,
people!
A mayoral candidate
has just been shot.
[ZIMMER]
The shooter is John Ennaji.
He's a male Semanian,
32 in Earth years.
Single, a clerk at a
convenience store.
No criminal record, except for
a few speeding tickets.
Everyone who knows him
says they can't believe he
would do something like this.
Got no underworld
connections, either.
This isn't our case. There's no
role for us here, but...
What, is there a problem?
I read your old report, Kei,
about your former partner, Fury.
Zelada?
We never found his corpse.
I wouldn't be the
least bit surprised
if he survived that
fall somehow.
So, is that what you're
trying to get at, Chief?
You think the shooter who
killed Kahns was manipulated
using magic, like those others?
I didn't wanna say it, but...
...we're just
covering bases, got it?
I want you and Exedilica to
head to the coroner's office
and see what you can figure out.
You want us to go now,
dressed like this?
That's exactly what
I want, Burger Boss.
[TILARNA] I had a strange
feeling it might have been
another controlled
corpse, as well.
I didn't expect Zimmer to
pick up on that, though.
[KEI] Sometimes it's surprising
how perceptive he can be.
Man, I really wanted to go home.
[TILARNA] You mean you're
not excited about the chance
to catch whoever was behind
Kahns' assassination?
[KEI] I'd rather not
waste a weekend off
avenging some politician's
demise, to be perfectly honest.
Kei.
What? I'm kidding.
[TILARNA] I have to admit,
I've been pretty impressed
with the way your
democracy works on Earth.
I think any system that truly
reflects the will of the people
is a good thing.
And this shooting feels
like a declaration of war
against that system.
[KEI]
That's a good speech.
Or, it would be, if you
weren't wearing a swimsuit.
Stop staring, people.
That's precisely why I
didn't want to come here.
[TILARNA]
I don't get what you mean.
Are you saying these people
are mocking our clothes?
Just forget it.
[knocking]
[KEI] You in there, Cecil?
We're coming in.
[CECIL]
Kei? Stop!
And, who might you be?
Uh, we'll be quick about this.
Hot enough for ya out there?
[TILARNA] The chief was
right about this case.
[KEI]
Hm?
This man was already dead.
His corpse was taken
over to murder Kahns.
[KEI]
By Zelada?
I can't be entirely certain.
Although, this form
of magic is rare.
I can't think of any
other obvious suspects.
[KEI, BUSINESSMEN exhale]
Urgh...
[TILARNA]
So, what now?
[KEI] We have to go
to Chief Zimmer first.
Tsk. Damn alien.
[TILARNA sighs]
[KEI] Wait a second. You!
What did you just say?
[SANDERS stammers]
Nothing.
[KEI] Don't lie. What did
you say when you saw her?
[SANDERS]
I-I don't know.
[KEI] I heard you, you coward.
You called her a "damn alien."
You too scared to repeat it?
You insulted my partner.
What made you think
that was cool?
Officer Sanders.
Sanders, Sanders, Sanders,
my friend.
Wanna tell me why you said that?
Look, bro I'm sorry!
[KEI]
Answer me.
[SANDERS]
Please. I just--
Kei. Stop.
[KEI] Officer Sanders, I asked
you a question! Tell me why!
[SANDERS]
Please! Please forgive me!
My family's conservative.
We were really excited
about voting for Kahns!
And, then I dunno, man.
After what happened today,
with the killer being, you know,
from another world, I just.
[KEI] So, you think my
partner killed Kahns?
No, I don't.
[KEI] Well, did she do
something to hurt your family?
[SANDERS]
No.
[KEI] Christ. So, you had no
real reason to insult her.
What the hell is your problem?
Is this how you treat
the citizens you were
sworn to protect?
Kei.
That's enough--let it go.
I just can't.
It's okay,
we've got to work.
[KEI grunts]
You embarrassed me. I wish
you wouldn't have done that.
[KEI]
Sorry.
But I still appreciate it.
I didn't do it because I
wanted your appreciation.
It just pissed me off.
Heh! I knew you'd say that.
Seems kinda
hypocritical, though.
You call people
"damn aliens" all the time.
[KEI] That's different.
It's just me teasing you.
Like when a gangster calls his
girlfriend a bitch because he's
trying to look
cool or something.
But if somebody else says the
same thing to her, he gets mad.
It's sort of like that.
[gasps]
[elevator dings]
Except I'm not your woman,
so it's not like that.
That's not what I meant.
It was just an example,
come on. Forget I said it.
[TILARNA grunts]
Fine, I'm willing to let
you off the hook for now.
Thank me later, doreany .
[KEI]
Be quiet, you damn alien.
[ZIMMER sighs]
I see.
[TILARNA] It was probably
Zelada, we think.
So, Chief Zimmer, It looks
like your hunch was right.
That's a shame. I was really
hoping I'd be wrong about that.
Oh? But why?
Because it's a pain!
Now I have to go around to
every department involved
and brief them on it.
Which means telling them,
"Watch out for wizards."
Better you than me.
Oh and don't forget the
Semanian who shot and killed
a candidate for mayor, kids.
It's gonna be a trash fire.
What makes you call it that?
It'll cause racial tension.
Like what you saw earlier.
Know what I mean?
Oh...
[ZIMMER] Even if Zelada,
also a Semanian,
is behind the whole thing,
we have to get to the bottom of
it all as quickly as possible.
[KEI] But how do you propose
we even find the guy, Chief?
It's not like you can just
catch a wizard with
security camera footage,
we all know that.
It seems like the best
thing would be to go back
to the basics
of police work.
Basics? How so?
Well, what's the motive?
Who stands to gain the most
from Kahns' assassination?
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft .