[KEI]
They're late.
Can you take it easy
for once, man?
These people'd be late to
their own mother's funeral,
for Christ's sake.
[KEI]
Yeah, I know the type,
but I've got somewhere
to be after this.
Hot little lady?
[KEI]
That's one way to put it.
She's got me wrapped
around her little claw
and I love every minute of it.
Oh, the cat, I shoulda known.
Finally, here those punks are.
Let's get to it so you
can feed your cat.
[RODRIGO]
Hey friends. You got the cash?
[KEI]
You shitheads are late.
The cops'll be sniffing
around here any minute.
[RODRIGO]
Where's the cash? Let's see it.
[KEI]
You first. You got the stuff?
High quality, right?
Shipped straight
from the source.
[RODRIGO] Show us the cash
and we show you the stuff.
Don't make me come get it.
I told you to calm down.
I got your dough right here.
All 50,000 in cold, hard cash.
[KEI]
Your turn, let's see the merch.
[CARLO grunts]
[RODRIGO]
Whatcha think, friends?
A real-life fairy.
That's pretty good quality.
Don't you think?
Oh, hell yeah.
A higher life form.
You could make some
primo drugs with this.
Where'd you guys get it?
I can't say. Trade secret
and all that jazz.
[KEI]
Whatever, We'll take it.
Rick?
[RICK]
Right.
[CARLO, RODRIGO chuckle]
[RODRIGO] Pleasure doing
business. Thanks a lot.
[RICK]
Yeah, glad it worked out.
[KEI exhales]
Yeah, me, too.
Now that that's done, let's get
down to why we're really here.
[BOTH gasp]
[KEI]
San-Teresa Metropolitan police.
Show me your hands.
[RODRIGO]
You bastards are cops?
You punk's under
arrest for kidnapping
and human trafficking.
This little fairy is a
Semanian citizen, after all.
[RICK] On your knees,
hands above your heads.
C'mon, let's go!
[CARLO grunts]
Damn it. You dirty
shithead pigs set us up!
You've got quite a
potty mouth, don'tcha?
Rick, wanna read these
idiots their rights?
You can do the honors, Kei.
[grunts] Okay, listen up,
for your own good.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything that comes out of that
dirty hole in your face may be
used against you
in a court of law,
so shut up and stop making
more trouble for yourself.
[KEI] You have the
right to legal counsel.
If you can't afford one
of those scumbags,
a subpar public defender
will be provided.
[RODRIGO, CARLO grunt]
You're welcome. Aren't we nice?
You fascist pig!
I hope you burn in hell!
[CARLO shouts]
Doreana meta badely na !
--[RICK] Hey.
-- Doreana meta badely na !
[CARLO, Rick grunting]
[KEI]
Rick!
[CARLO]
Doreana... Doreana...
[snapping]
[CARLO growls]
Doreana meta badely na .
Zona zanieyen biye
genna neylie .
That language.
It's not from Earth.
Beyzennaly nozey daal
fiel mezeyda dehmameiya
leymeh noi agusica .
[KEI]
Shut your mouth, damn alien.
[CARLO growls]
[KEI grunts]
Rick... Rick!
[KEI]
Dammit!
[NARRATOR] 15 years ago,
a hyperspace gate appeared
in the middle of
the Pacific Ocean.
Beyond that gate lay a
mysterious world filled with
fairies and monsters.
The city of San-Teresa
on Kariaena island
became known as
"Earth's Front Door."
Over two million citizens from
this strange world live here.
A melting pot of races,
cultures, and species.
The haves and the have-nots.
San-Teresa is the world's
newest "city of dreams."
But, in the shadows, lurk all
kinds of crimes and criminals.
Drugs, prostitution,
weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa
Metropolitan Police force
maintain a specialized unit
to deal with the seedy mayhem.
[ROTH]
Hey, Matoba.
They found the perp's body lying
in the road in Apple Hills.
[KEI] Apple Hills?
That's two miles away.
Chief Roth.
I got three clean hits on that
guy with a nine millimeter.
No way in hell he got that far.
If he was a normal,
human criminal, no.
[KEI] So, It was another
one of those damn aliens.
[ROTH]
That's my guess.
Think he was controlled
by a Semanian wizard?
[KEI]
The perp spoke Farbani,
and used words only spoken
by the intellectual class.
He said that fairy was special.
[ROTH]
Hm. I'll handle things here.
Matoba. You go get some rest.
[KEI]
Chief. My partner of four years
was just murdered
in front of me.
I'm gonna make his killers pay.
That's an order.
You hear me Sergeant?
I'm Sorry about Rick, but you
need to decompress. So do it.
I gotta tell his wife.
What the hell do I say?
[ROTH]
I'll take care of that, too
[KEI] No. She'd rather
hear it from me.
Don't forget your report.
Have it in by nine sharp.
[KEI]
Yeah, yeah.
[DRUNKARD A grumbling]
[KEI exhales]
[KEI]
Shit!
[KEI groans]
[THUG A] Hey, man,
need a car wash tonight?
It look dirty to you?
[THUG A]
Oh, I think it does. You see?
[THUGS laugh]
That's 300 dollars.
Cough it up, or you might not
like what happens to your car.
[THUG B]
You heard him, let's go.
[THUG C] What's wrong,
you scared, doreany?
[KEI] Fine, I'll pay it,
just calm down.
[THUG A]
C'mon, Hurry up!
[KEI sighs]
Where'd I put my cash?
Oh, right. Here it is.
[THUGS]
Huh?
[KEI]
Go get it, dickless.
[THUG A]
Bastard!
[THUG A groans]
[THUGS grunting]
[KEI]
You're Semanians, right?
Earthlings may be
weaker than you,
but some of us aren't,
don't forget that.
[THUG C]
Whatever.
[KEI]
I think you meant, "Yes, sir."
[THUG C]
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
[KEI]
Get lost.
[THUGS grunt, whimper]
[sighs]
How pathetic.
--[phone rings]
--[KIDS giggle]
[RICK'S WIFE]
Oh, Kei!
Rick's not home, but I'll
tell him you called.
Are you okay?
Please, no. It can't be.
[KEI]
I'm sorry.
[RICK'S WIFE sobs]
[KEI exhales]
[phone rings]
[KEI]
Hello?
[ROTH] Listen, about tomorrow.
There's been a change of plans.
I need you to meet
a noble for me.
[KEI]
What'd you say?
[ROTH]
I said you're meeting a noble.
A VIP from the Farbani Kingdom
gets here in the morning,
you're gonna meet them.
[KEI] You want me to go pick
up some alien aristocrat?
What am I, a diplomat now?
[ROTH] We've got a shortage of
detectives who speak Farbani.
[KEI]
That's my curse.
Can't you just let me hunt down
this guy who killed Rick?
[ROTH] This VIP could be
connected to that somehow.
[KEI]
What?
[ROTH]
Just go pick them up, will ya?
I've already alerted
the coast guard.
[phone clicks]
[KEI exhles]
Bossy bastard.
Hey.
[meows]
[CAPTAIN A]
We're coming up on the gate now.
Have you ever been to their
world before, officer?
Sure have. Former military.
Went in the war, huh?
But I didn't get to see
the gate, back then.
I was in a transport plane
with all the other saps.
[CAPTAIN A]
No one has ever seen it.
The Mirage Gate's invisible.
We have to rely on data from
our observation satellites.
[CAPTAIN A] But those damn
aliens know where the gate is.
They can tell by the wind and
the tides, even with our tech,
they can find it
faster than we do.
[KEI] I guess that's what
keeps you coast guard guys
so busy all the time.
[CAPTAIN A] Smart man.
And we still don't get 'em all.
If we wanted to catch every damn
smuggler and illegal immigrant,
we'd need more than
twice the funding.
[CAPTAIN A]
There they are.
It's some important noble,
is that right?
I'll let you take it from here.
[SAILORS chattering]
[SAILOR A]
Doreany shii doreany !
[SAILOR C]
Hey. Rakebye !
[SAILOR D grunts]
A kid? Is she a servant?
[SAILOR A grunts]
[SAILOR B grunts]
[KEI]
Where's the VIP?
[TILARNA]
Hey.
I am the one you seek.
Exedilica, of the
Knights of Mirvor.
Do Earthlings have
no welcoming ritual?
[KEI]
Heh?
[TILARNA] Have they sent
a mute to retrieve me?
[KEI]
I talk.
[TILARNA] Then why don't
you answer? Well, then?
[KEI]
I didn't know who you were.
[TILARNA]
I see.
My name is... Tilarna Barsh.
Mirvor Lyata.
Imsedalya Iyeh Tebreina Devol.
Nelano Seiya.
Nel Exedilica.
[KEI]
Hm?
In your Earth language it's
"Tilarna, eldest daughter
of Seiya,
of the House of Exedilica,
heir apparent to the
bloodline of Duke Devol,
she of the glorious
Knights of Mirvor."
Now, then. You tell
me your name.
Kei Matoba.
[TILARNA]
Again.
Kei Matoba.
Is that it?
[KEI]
Huh?
Huh. Typically only people of
low birth have names that short,
but I suppose it's
of no consequence.
It's a pleasure.
To simplify things, you may call
me Tilarna Exedilica, for short.
[KEI]
Huh?
Now, you will carry my
bags for me. Kei Imatuba.
[KEI]
Kei Matoba.
[TILARNA]
I don't care. Start carrying.
[KEI groans]
What'd you say?
[POLICE CHIEF A]
You not hear me?
Clean out your ears.
I said you're standing
beside your new partner.
You'll be working
together from now on.
Get used to it. She'll take
Sergeant Fury's place.
What, me? Work with
a damn alien?
[POLICE CHIEF A grunts]
We don't tolerate racism here,
Sergeant Matoba!
I'm sorry, but he's stupid,
so you can't really fault him
for what comes out
of his mouth.
[ROTH] Jeez, Kei. She came
here to find the fairy.
[TILARNA]
The fiel . Fiel queze badely .
It translates to
"most noble fairy."
That fairy's special.
Equivalent to a VIP
in the Semani world.
Someone kidnapped it over there,
and smugglers brought it
through the gate to our side.
Tilarna's a Farbanian knight.
She was sent over by her
people to recover the fairy.
Now, then, did I
get all that right?
You're correct.
As per our treaty with a body
called The United Nations,
as Knights of Mirvor,
we possess the authority to
dispense Justice here on Earth.
Therefore, I, Tilarna Exedilica,
humbly request your assistance
in the name of the
Farbani Kingdom.
What a giant crock of bullshit!
Rick was my partner, the guy
I worked with for four years.
Now he's dead, but now you
want me to babysit some kid?
These are your orders, Kei.
[KEI] Well, you can
blow 'em out your ass!
C'mon, Chief don't you want
to avenge Rick's death
as much as anyone else?
I can't believe you're
telling me to--
That's enough. I worked with
Rick for 20 years, Kei.
[KEI exhales]
I understand where
you're coming from.
I wouldn't make you
do this unless I had to.
But...
I feel that my wishes are
being ignored, as well.
I want to work with the top
boliceman in your city,
and this is truly the best
that you have to offer me?
I cannot even imagine it:
this boorish Earthling
acting as my guard?
[POLICE CHIEF A]
Oh, I apologize.
We can find you another
partner if he isn't suitable--
[ROTH] No, there's no
one better than Kei.
[ROTH] Or would you rather
a guy with perfect etiquette
who's completely
useless otherwise?
[POLICE CHIEF A]
But, Inspector Roth.
[ROTH]
If that's what you want, fine,
but you won't be getting
your fairy back that way.
[TILARNA sighs]
[TILARNA]
Uh?
[KEI]
Don't touch that.
[TILARNA gasps]
[COP B sighs]
[KEI]
Don't touch that, either.
[COP B]
Huh?
[TILARNA grunts]
I said don't touch anything.
--[footsteps]
--[cardoor clatters]
[phone rings]
[KEI]
Tony, what's up?
[TONY]
He talked,
but was too scared to say
very much, unfortunately.
That fairy was stolen.
Supposedly.
And, get this, he says it was
from a gang of Mexicans
in a Ridgeline. He doesn't
know any names, though.
[KEI]
Thanks.
Huh...? What?
Huh? Nothing. We should go.
[TILARNA yelps, grunts]
[TILARNA] So, tell me.
Where are we headed?
[KEI] We're going to talk to
the fairy's original owners.
How many gangs of Mexicans
can there be driving around
in Ridgelines, you understand
what I'm saying?
[TILARNA]
What is a Ridgeline?
[KEI]
A kind of car.
[TILARNA]
What's a Mexican?
[KEI]
A person from Mexico.
[TILARNA]
What's a gang?
[KEI] Enough. Just sit
there and shut up.
[TILARNA]
What's this?
[KEI]
No!
[truck horn blaring]
Rakebye ! Are you
trying to kill me?
[KEI] I told you not
to touch anything.
Don't do anything, either!
[KEI]
You'd better wait here.
[TILARNA]
I don't take orders from you.
[KEI exhales]
[TILARNA] I'm going with you,
Kei Imatuba.
[KEI sighs]
Fine, whatever.
Just, try to walk as far
away from me as possible.
I wouldn't want anyone to think
we're friends or something.
[TILARNA] What a coincidence,
neither would I.
[KENNY] Hey, we don't open
until seven. Get out of here.
[KENNY gasps]
Oh, sorry, Mr. Matoba.
Hey, Kenny, does O'Neill
happen to be in?
Yeah, he's back there,
but he's on the phone.
Whoa, hold on. That's an alien!
I really hate those guys,
you know that.
[KEI] Throw her out if
you want, or whatever.
Hey, hold it right there,
little girl.
Yes, What is it?
[KENNY] He's allowed
to go back there...
...but your kind's not welcome.
[KEI grunts]
[TILARNA grunts]
[KENNY]
Hey, did you hear what I said?
Get the hell outta
here or I'm gonna--
[KENNY gasps]
[TILARNA] Would you like
to repeat that? Go on.
[KENNY]
Feel free, Miss. Please.
[TILARNA]
Very good.
[TILARNA] Did you think I would
be afraid and beg for your help?
[KEI]
Mm-mm.
[BIZ] Yes, good deal.
Should be lucrative for us both.
This gift of 50, 51 inch TVs
brought to us by those
sinful children are
truly a gift from God.
We'll can sell them
with ease, I'm sure.
The Lord says--
Oh!
These aren't TVs
in a literal sense.
That's just a metaphor
for God's grace.
Listen, I've got visitors.
God's blessings be with you.
Sergeant Matoba! Are you
feeling the breath of God
down the back of
your neck today?
And who is this
lovely young lady?
It's a pleasure, welcome to my
humble house of faith today!
May I offer you a drink?
O'Neill. I'm looking for
information on a Mexican gang.
I heard they drive a Ridgeline.
Probably transporters.
Know something?
I see.
Well, they're a particularly
violent bunch, you know.
I'd prefer not to
get them riled up.
[KEI]
Then, you do know something.
It's difficult to say,
but with the right donation
amount maybe God would talk.
Whisper a little something, and
I could share His word with you.
I think about 300
would do the trick.
If you don't know anything,
then you'll face the wrath
of the Goddess of
the Courtroom,
who keeps her sword sharp
for creeps like you.
You're on probation,
right, O'Neill?
That's an illegal threat,
Sergeant Matoba,
and you know it.
Someday Satan's gonna
get his claws in you,
and you'll be sorry!
Satan can suck my dick.
Now what did I hear
about those 51 inch TVs?
'Cause my friends in the
burglary division are curious.
[BIZ]
Oh, lord...
[TILARNA] You're willing to
believe the word of a thief?
[KEI]
He's an informant.
[TILARNA]
But he's still a thief.
[KEI sighs] Look,
O'Neill may be a criminal,
but he has a strong distaste
for drugs and murder.
So, he can be trusted,
to a point.
The kind of guy you can't bring
yourself to hate, I guess.
[TILARNA]
I don't understand.
Isn't the point of your position
to be an enforcer of justice?
Yeah, well.
I was told that there
were warriors on Earth
who fought on the
side of justice.
Who helped the poor and who
went to battle against evil.
That's what you
"bolicemen" are, right?
I expected a little
more from you.
[KEI grunts]
So, I can't believe I'd find
you making deals with a thief.
Do you take no pride
in who you are?
[coughs]
It's complicated.
[TILARNA grunts]
What is?
Everything.
In the old days, I'd agree.
But, now, it's more complicated.
[TILARNA]
I still don't understand it.
[TILARNA coughs]
[KEI]
Nobody does.
[ROTH] The address is five
eighty-one Mason Street.
Room six-oh-three.
Antonio Alvarez.
You gonna need backup?
Nope. But if you don't hear
from me in an hour and a half,
then you can send someone out.
[ROTH]
Roger. Be careful.
Thanks, boss.
You stay here.
Shoulda known you
wouldn't listen.
[TILARNA]
You're learning.
Mm.
[KEI]
Don't touch anything.
I'm not. You smell that?
Smell what?
I think it's latena.
Someone was here who's
controlled by an evil wizard.
I know it. Don't you?
[KEI]
What're you saying?
The enemy's near.
Logo daitey .
Rabuna iyeh kizenya .
[KEI gasps]
Follow me!
[KEI]
Hey, wait!
[TILARNA grunts]
Police! Don't move!
[TILARNA shouts]
[KEI, TILARNA grunt]
[KEI]
Get down!
Shit!
[KEI]
Next time, on Cop Craft .