♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi's
team is in great danger
as they battle Team Masho
in the Dark Tournament.
Kurama fought
the Ice Master Touya
under all but
impossible conditions,
finally planting a death
seed into his own body to win.
But the price of
victory was high,
as Kurama slipped into a
coma while still in the ring.
Now the next opponent
steps forward,
planning to murder
Kurama in his sleep.
Not much of a challenge
for me... I like that.
Don't you touch him!
[RISHO] This win
would help us greatly.
[Bakken laughs]
[KOTO]
Stop!
I'm all for extreme pain and
torture, you disgusting horse,
but this guy's not
even awake to enjoy it!
I'm taking a ten count!
Count yourself out then!
We're making the
rules now, not you.
[BAKKEN] I won't risk
enjoying myself any longer.
I'll just break your face.
[RISHO]
Bakken. Stop.
But why Risho?
[RISHO] Lay him
outside of the ring.
But he's killed
our sect members!
[RISHO] Yes. And if you
had landed that punch,
you would have died as well.
[BAKKEN]
What?
[RISHO] Or do you
think you would have
survived a bullet in the back?
It's clear Yusuke cares
more about that demon's life
than this tournament.
He's ready to fight
every apparition
in this stadium if he must.
We need to win--
not be involved in a revolt.
You're getting soft, Risho.
You'll end up
like Gama and Touya.
If this prize is
what we really want
then we shouldn't
be making concessions.
[BAKKEN] Fine. Take
your precious buddy.
Well, I think
we can all agree
Kurama will be
staying outside the ring.
Just change the
blasted board already!
[CROWD CHANTS] Kill
the traitor! Kill the traitor!
You'll be okay.
[RUKA] Your friend got
a lucky reprieve.
[HIEI]
So did you, witch.
Or should I say, so did
everyone else in this stadium.
[MASKED FIGHTER] Yusuke wasn't
the only one about to fire.
So was Hiei, and
their combined power
would not have been
contained in the ring.
Risho felt it. Didn't you?
Hiei mounting an assault--
why that's very funny.
Have you forgotten you're
trapped inside my force field?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Drop the act, Ruka.
You've already realized
you can't keep us
in here for much longer.
Our powers are returning.
And yours will stay
as meager as always.
I guess it's my
turn... Wish me luck!
I think bone-cracking
is a good sign to rest.
Yes ma'am!
Oooh, what a scary look!
Am I supposed to be
shivering in my bootstraps now?
Or should I just be
running for my life?
[Bakken laughs mockingly]
Why don't we let
the fight answer that.
And the third match--Bakken
versus Yusuke... You may begin!
Oh wow Botan, do you sense that?
No... you'll have to fill me in.
There's some
kind of strange power
coming out of Bakken's sweat.
His strength's abysmal
compared to Yusuke's.
You do know that, don't you?
[BUTAJIRI]
Who gives a damn...
Bakken's special technique
should take care of that.
He should pop any time.
[YUSUKE] What's wrong Bakken?
We haven't even started yet and
you've got a nervous sweat.
Do you give up?
You really are an
idiot aren't you?
Mystical powers of
Shinobi! White Mist!
Hey, where'd he go?
He must be using the
mist to hide himself.
Well, Yusuke's won in
the dark before, right?
Oh, now this is
perfectly charming.
It smells like sweat.
[KOTO] Pure insanity!
The ring's been devoured
by a giant layer of mist!
Urameshi has absolutely no idea
where Bakken's first
attack will come from!
In fact neither do I!
I can't even see my
microphone in front of me!
Damn it... how am I supposed to
fight now? I hate saunas.
Guess I'll wait for somethin...
Like that, for example!
[BAKKEN] You didn't see that
coming at all. Try again!
[BAKKEN] Yes. That one hurt a
little more, didn't it?
You couldn't even
manage a block.
[Yusuke laughs]
[BAKKEN] It doesn't
make any difference
that you saved Kurama.
New person, same result.
Your team is just one
big punching bag for me.
[Bakken laughs]
[Yusuke laughs]
What's so funny?
Have I knocked you witless?
I'm laughing 'cause
I'm relieved...
You had me worried when
you were punching Kurama,
but now that I know
how soft your fists are
I feel a lot better.
Now I see why you were scared
when Jin touched you before.
I was not!
Oh come on, your
whole robe was shaking!
I mean I don't blame you.
This stupid sweat-fog
is your only trick,
and I bet Jin
could knock it away
with one little gust of wind!
[Yusuke laughs]
You better shut your trap!
You're not a
wind master, are you?
So you're getting ready to die!
[BAKKEN] We'll see how
soft my punches are!
Spirit Gun.
Ha! You've just shot in
completely the wrong direction!
[Bakken struggles]
I don't understand
what just happened.
[crowd murmurs in disbelief]
All my mist! It's disappearing!
A brilliant strategy by Yusuke!
He's used the force
of his Spirit Gun blast
to blow the mist right
out of the stadium!!
Damn that boy!
Where'd he go!
[YUSUKE] Let me explain
what's about to happen.
You basically have
two real options here.
[YUSUKE] You can
either turn around
and have me beat
the crap out of you,
or you can get on your hands
and knees and start begging.
And maybe, just
maybe, I'll listen.
You dirty little son of bi--!!!
[Yusuke chuckles]
I think it's clear what
that huddled over pose means--
I only wish
everyone in the audience
could've heard
those cracking bones!
[YUSUKE] Damn... I missed a few.
You know those lower
ribs are harder to reach.
Stay away. Please I think I
must've punctured something.
Just have some mercy on me.
Right, mercy like the
way you kept beating Kurama
when he was laid
out on the floor.
[BAKKEN]
No, it wasn't like that!
I wasn't cruel to him.
I was just excited!
It was the heat of battle--
I don't even remember what
I did to him! I promise!
I don't even remember,
and whatever I did,
I didn't mean it!
[BAKKEN]
I'm so sorry!!
Hey! Calm down buddy!
You're embarrassing me here!
Cheer up Bakken.
Your brain's just small.
It's not your fault
you can't remember
all those things
you did to Kurama.
So, I'm gonna
refresh your memory
by using your
body as an example!
See first you jumped in and
grabbed him a little like this.
And then--
Out of the ring!
Naturally I'll take a ten count!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
That's a pretty good fight.
Ten! And the
winner is Urameshi!
How you doin'?
I'll survive.
Sorry I couldn't finish
the first three of them
as I planned.
[YUSUKE] Shut up.
How are the wounds?
My injuries from Team
Masho are nothing
compared to this Death Plant.
It will take a
great deal of energy
and concentration to remove.
I suppose we really do
reap what we sow, right?
Listen, just get
some rest okay.
These last two guys are gonna
be fish meat pretty soon.
Be cautious with them Yusuke.
Whatever plans the Shinobi
have for this island,
they want it very badly.
And these last two members are
without a doubt the strongest.
[HIEI THINKS] Perfect.
Just a little bit more...
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
Now this is something I
didn't count on...
Hiei's right arm is improving!
Ironic.
The type of energy Ruka's
exerting into this medical tent
actually has a healing
effect on his wound.
Ruka must've
sensed it too late.
She knows that if she
cuts back her force field,
Hiei will overcome her.
All she can do now is
hold on for dear life,
and pray Hiei's power
doesn't increase any more.
[crowd yelling]
Finally Jin's ready to fight!
He's going to tear
Urameshi into pieces!
Might as well give up
now, Spirit Detective!
No one beats the wind master!
[KOENMA] What is the big
hip-hurrah over this Jin guy?
How scary can moving air be?
Is he a master of fire or
darkness or something, too?
No sir, just wind.
[KOENMA]
Groovy.
But Koenma sir,
this is still an extremely
dangerous fight for your team.
I'm not sure feasting
now would be appropriate.
[KOENMA] I guess you're
right. We'll wait.
I've been looking
forward to this one.
I can assure you
we all have, Sakyo.
Jin's gonna hang
this boy up by his toes.
My first three demons
were the chump-change
compared to this guy.
[CROWD CHANTS]
Kill Yusuke! Kill Yusuke!
Lucky eyes you got.
Damn it, I can't believe the
ruckus they're washing up
you can't even make a thought!
Ah course I wouldn't mind
if it weren't for the ears.
See they're all
pointy up and wiggling,
unlike they were before.
Get in that way when
I'm happy or excited,
and I haven't been
either in a very long time.
But saw biggy flying
up all the way high
and past "whew" almost lost it!
Well didn't you hear me?
I'm talkin' about the way
you knocked away Bakken's fog
and then took him
for a first class ride
on your fists, you know.
I never did like that guy.
The wind around his
pores was pretty stinky.
Actually, I'm kind
of glad you waxed him.
Oh, don't tell Risho
I told you that, huh?
[both laugh]
Why's he laughin'
with the bad guy?
You're a crazy bastard,
you know that?
You went and got
me all in a good mood,
and I was about to
use my anger at Bakken
to pound you into the ground!
[JIN] Nah, don't lump
me in with biggy.
He was just a jerk.
Going in bearing a grudge is no
way to start fight so it says.
You'll never have any
cheering up that way.
Just good old fight to
find the strongest guy is all.
I guess you weren't kidding
about the wind
master thing, huh?
[KOTO] Wow! Hold onto
your hair, people!
Jin is unleashing his power!
He's floating several
inches off the ring floor,
supported by his terrific wind!
And I haven't even
started this match yet!
Here we go, Jin. I can't
say my ears are pointing up,
but I'm looking
forward to this challenge.
[JIN] That's the spirit.
Let's have some fun then.
If I lose my
whole team's screwed
and if I win I
have to fight again.
Yeah, that sounds like fun!
[KOTO] Match four!
Yusuke versus Jin! Let her rip!
Oh wow! Jin easily
dodged Yusuke's attack
by shooting
straight up into the air!
But, he doesn't
seem to be stopping!
So this is what
the wind in the
big bright and open
feels like, huh?
[JIN]
I always wanted to know.
Could really all be ours.
Might be worth having
the old Shinobi job
with a place like this.
[KOTO] Don't worry people,
I can still just barely see him!
He's the size of a tiny gnat!
[YUSUKE] Hey, come on!
You've got a fight to lose!
Sorry Urameshi,
but I'm getting my prize!
[KOTO] Hold on.
Where'd he go? Wait!
He's using the sun
behind him as a blinder!
He's coming down fast!
Let's do this.
[KOTO] Hold on a second!
Jin's deliberately
avoided hitting Yusuke!
What could be going
through the wind master's head?
Damn he's fast'!
[YUSUKE]
What's he doing?
Nothing to be in a
fuss for Urameshi.
Man's just got to get in
right spirit before he fights.
Don't you think it so?
You know one of these days
I'm gonna fight someone who
talks like a normal person!
Okay, heard that loud and clear.
Keep punching like
that and we'll enjoy this.
[NARRATOR] Jin, the Wind Master,
is now revealing
his incredible powers,
while the team leader Risho
still waits in the wings.
Yusuke is the only one
still able to fight.
Can he stand up to them both?
Hello everyone, it's Botan.
The big battle against
Jin is cranking up,
and our one of a
kind Spirit Detective
is certainly going
to have his hands full.
How can Yusuke
fight a person who,
in addition to having
powers that rival his own,
also has that even rarer trait--
a personality that
Yusuke actually likes?!
It's going to be a fight
where friend and
enemy often intertwine--
with plenty of big
explosions to boot!
It's the next
Yu Yu Hakusho,
and I'm sure you
won't want to miss it!
♪