♪
[NARRATOR] Four Saint Beasts
threaten to invade the Earth.
The second's name is Byakko,
a ferocious white
tiger who can destroy
molecules with a
blast of his voice.
Kuwabara stubbornly
took on this beast
through a series of battles,
the last of which took place
in Byakko's smoldering lair.
In a daring move
Kuwabara knocked the beast
into a pool of molten lava,
barely clinging
to his own life.
The mission continues.
Those boys are amazing sir!
Ogre! That's enough
with the optimism!
Go do something useful!
Do you suppose they'll make it
all the way through Maze Castle?
Do you sir?
Unfortunately I can't
suppose anything
because we never
found any information
on the Four Saint Beasts.
Now what do you suppose
is in your hand there?
Oh yeah, uh sir I meant to
tell you about it earlier,
yeah, turns out we do have
a little something written
about the Four Saint Beasts!
What?! Two whole battles
and you're only now
telling me about this?!
[KOENMA] No, Fig, Flour,
Four Saint, ah-page 42.
Instructions, a very difficult
but rewarding challenge
with only one real
weakness. Hard to boil.
[KOENMA] This says
Four Saint Beets.
You've given me a cookbook!
Oh sir!!
One hundred spankings.
Oh please sir, have mercy on
me! Anything but spankings!
Maybe you misread it!
What?! You're kidding me!
It appears we have found
a maze in Maze Castle.
Well I guess that makes sense.
We must beware...
It's something of a legend.
[KURAMA] In the beginning,
before the barrier wall
was erected around
the city, hundreds of
bounty hunters came
in search of the beasts.
None succeeded...
But the beasts never
left their tower,
letting anyone who
made it into the castle
forfeit their lives
to this Maze.
[KURAMA]
There are fifteen doors,
all but one leads to a dead end.
There are no second attempts.
Unavoidable traps line
the incorrect passageways...
[bounty hunter
cries out in pain]
[KURAMA] So you see, a poor
choice seals our fate.
Okay Mr. Sensitive,
this one's all yours.
[KUWABARA THINKS] That door's
got a big feeling behind it.
Kinda like the
first two monsters.
The second door on the left.
You heard the man! Let's go!
[HIEI] How do we know he's
not making a mistake?
I'm sorry shorty,
maybe it's not your thing
but you're just gonna have
to trust me on this one.
I know, there's somethin'
big behind that door.
Somethin' scary.
[mouse chirps]
I hate mice!!!
Gee Kuwabara, and that speech of
yours was getting so dramatic!
[SUZAKU]
Very surprising.
Somehow they have
chosen the correct door.
We can hardly have it said
that the Four Saint Beasts
welcome guests so
far into their home.
I'm sorry, the Two Saint
Beasts is more accurate now.
[SEIRYU]
I shall take them, master?
You and I both know
that Genbu and Byakko
had become soft in these
years of containment.
[SEIRYU] Their tenderfoot
mistakes shall not be repeated.
[car horns honking]
[BOTAN] I'm afraid
the news isn't good.
The Makai Insects
are moving too fast
for me to battle everyone
who's been taken over.
All I can do now is contain
them into one part of the city.
Very well...
We'll just have to hope
Yusuke destroys the whistle
before the city
bursts into flames.
[KOENMA]
But that's no guarantee,
so keep exterminating
what you can.
I understand, over and out.
Are we supposed to be scared?
Perhaps, that is the
mark of the Blue Dragon.
And judging from the odor
I'd say the beast is inside.
Yeah and he doesn't
feel very nice.
This fog's alive.
Must be a form
of Spirit Energy,
coming from our beast's body.
[SEIRYU] You have done very
well to come this far.
But I shall no longer allow
you to disgrace my master.
Where's that voice coming from?
I don't know--
Come out now Dragon!
This whole hide-and-seek
thing's getting pretty lame!
As you request.
A giant!!
You may call me Seiryu.
I am here now to end
your lives intruders.
Well, he's no dragon.
But he is ugly.
[SEIRYU] It is not wise to say
such things to your executioner.
It appears we have
another guest.
[panting]
Guys I'm uh, not sure
how to tell you this, but...
[HIEI] It's coming
from behind us.
You must help me.
You're joking.
[BYAKKO] Please Seiryu,
these cowards,
they tricked me in my own lair.
They hid their true powers
from me until the end.
You must help me recover.
I knocked that guy into lava!!
What does it take
to kill this guy?
Weakling! How dare you
dishonor us further!
Please Seiryu!!
You are no longer wanted here.
You are a disgrace!
No Seiryu, I can help
you destroy them!
It was a small mistake!
Ice Dragon!!!
What the...?
[Byakko cries out in pain]
He's frozen!
You were right about
my fog of energy.
By lowering it
to subzero temperatures,
I can wrap my enemy in ice.
You heartless bastard!
How could you kill
off your own friend?
Seiryu.. why?
[SEIRYU] He was a
weapon, not a friend.
And like a cheap sword,
he rusted.
This race of beasts
has no loyalty.
Alliances are formed
strictly to gain power.
I don't care what
kind of race they are.
It's never right to
kill your own teammate,
especially when they come
asking you for your help!
This guy's pushed me too far!
He's dead!!
[HIEI]
Save your anger.
You can take their leader.
I insist this fight be mine.
[SEIRYU] Ah.
Shall you be first, Hiei?
What was that?
Tell me you're not feeling
sympathy for this amateur.
From your actions
at the Gate of Betrayal
I was hoping you had more
of a warrior's spirit.
He's a puzzle, isn't he?
In times before I've seen
Hiei act with similar cruelty.
But something about
Byakko's execution
has caused great anger in him.
Hiei seems to live by his own
code with very complex rules.
But one thing is for certain.
Never before have I
seen Hiei begin a fight
using such an extraordinary
amount of his Spirit Energy.
[YUSUKE] Good. As long
as he kicks some ass.
I assure you, Hiei, it is not
too late to join our ranks.
Prostrate yourself
before my master
and he shall you give
you power and fame
beyond what you
have ever tasted.
[HIEI] Is that all
you have to say?
They're last words you know.
Fine! So that is your choice!
Then you shall meet your
death with the other weaklings.
Hey! Be careful!
Try blocking this!
That freeze technique! Run!
Ice Dragon!!!
I'm sorry, I had forgotten
of your impressive speed.
Now let's try again!
He's gonna turn the whole
room into a hockey rink!
Not just the room!
Man I wish I had my jacket back!
Hiei--
Hey, he's okay!
Yeah, don't scare
us like that!
No, his leg. He won't be
able to run away anymore.
You see, no one ever escapes.
Only beg for mercy.
With your leg frozen
you can't possibly move.
I suggest you start groveling.
What can he do?
Ice Dragon!!
Now you end!!
Hiei!
You have escaped.
But you are wounded.
[Hiei laughs]
Why are you laughing?
So what if your ice trick
can kill your wounded friend.
It won't kill me.
That's impossible!
I shall give one final blow!!
I don't think so.
When did he attack?
Don't feel bad Kuwabara,
I couldn't see it either
after the initial hit.
Shorty's a lot cooler
than I thought!!
You made french
fries out of that guy!!
Hiei how many times
did you cut him?
Only sixteen.
[YUSUKE]
Sixteen?
Damn it, and here I could only
keep track of seven or eight.
That's nothing meager.
After the first hit I
only saw flashes of light.
I couldn't even see the flashes!
Man, this isn't good.
If you use those moves
the next time we fight
I'm gonna be screwed!
Maybe.
Hiei.
I thought for sure
he was going to say--
"Well of course you fool!"
Hiei is going through
a tricky change.
It appears he is
beginning to like you.
[SUZAKU] This ceases
to be entertaining.
These nothings
are ruining my plans!
Suzaku! I'm back!
What is it?
You sound gloomy.
Guess I don't need to ask
if the guests are still here.
That's true Murugu. All my men
have been killed. Now go away.
Not just yet!
I have gathered
the information you
requested on Yusuke Urameshi.
[MURUGU] It turns out our boy
wonder has few friends,
but one great weakness.
Her name is Keiko Ukimura,
and she's very close
to Yusuke's heart.
She is pretty.
I suppose so.
The important part is he'll
do anything to save her.
[SUZAKU]
Good.
Then why don't we
test his concentration.
How well will he fight
here inside Maze Castle.
While back on the Earth.
His dear Keiko screams in agony.
I know the perfect song to play,
on this Makai Whistle.
It's titled Prelude to
Keiko's Suffering, in A Minor.
Listen to me Koenma!
I have to abort this mission!
The humans taken over
by the Makai Insects
are starting to work together,
and their numbers
continue to grow!
Understood! Get yourself
to higher ground Botan!
I can't afford to lose you now!
My thoughts exactly!
Botan! I said run!!
I'm not sure how
feasible that is.
[KOENMA]
Botan!
And where do they
think they're going?
Yusuke's middle school.
[IWAMOTO] Miss Ukimura.
You're still at school?
Yes, Mr. Iwamoto.
Go on home and get some sleep.
Our big test is tomorrow.
You want to score high
and bolster our school's
ratings, don't you?
Just as soon as I finish my
student council work, sir.
Any news on Urameshi? I notice
he's skipped for several days.
I don't know anything about him.
Perfect.
He's a roach, Ukimura.
I'd hate for you to be
infected with his disease.
Yes sir.
These flyers will be perfect.
[door opens]
Mr. Iwamoto... You...
look... pale.
I said... you need to...
get some sleep!
O... kay...
You've been spending too
much time with that cockroach.
He's made you bad... Yes...
You will need... correction.
[KEIKO THINKS] Something is
very, very wrong here.
Ukimura.
They must be those fanatics they
mentioned in the newspaper!
But, how do they know my name!
Wait Ukimura. It's time
for your detention.
What now? Got cramps?
My whole brain just
felt like an ice cube.
Something bad's happening,
I think back on Earth.
No telling how
long we've been here.
The beasts have most
likely organized
a counter assault
using the Makai.
Only one more,
let's not waste time.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I just hope
Keiko's all right.
[NARRATOR] Yusuke
is right to worry.
With the power of
the Makai Whistle,
the last Saint Beast
has redirected
the entire zombie army
to one sinister goal:
the death of Keiko.
[BOTAN]
Things are getting nasty
as the fight with the Saint
Beasts reaches it's peak!
I'll do my best
to keep Keiko alive,
while Yusuke confronts the
fiercest beast of them all!
Suzaku! He's the mastermind
behind this entire invasion,
and if Yusuke doesn't
do something quickly,
his entire city could
go up in flames!
But all isn't lost!
It's Yusuke's first big fight
since his training with Genkai,
and our first chance to see the
new powers at his finger tips!
That's next time,
on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪