♪
[NARRATOR] A tunnel forming
between the Demon and Human
worlds threatens to
decimate the earth.
To stop it, Yusuke and
his friends must defeat
the seven powerful
psychics behind the plan.
Searching Mushiyori City,
Yusuke's team was quickly
steered to the hospital,
where a trap awaited.
The Doctor.
A human with great
psychic powers
who has mysteriously
turned to the demon side.
He has super strength,
feels no pain,
and has infected the entire
hospital with a deadly virus.
To save his friends, will
Yusuke have to kill him?
[collision]
[THE DOCTOR] You're as
dangerous as Black Angel said.
But I have one more
talent to show you.
It's simple...
As a doctor, anything I cut,
I can stitch back in place.
I think it's time
for a dissection.
[SHIZURU] Come on,
a little faster, Keiko.
[KEIKO]
I'm going!
[SHIZURU]
Wouldn't you know it.
Keiko, get us an elevator.
[KEIKO]
Okay!
[PUU]
Puu! Puu!
There must be
hundreds of them.
[SHIZURU] I guess
that bought us a little time.
This is awful. I hope
Yusuke's all right.
[SHIZURU] Kid, don't you
ever think about yourself?
Oh no.
[KEIKO]
I'm cold.
These powers we
psychics have acquired.
I think they relate to our
own talents and personalities.
Like me, a doctor.
I developed the
power to save patients
who would otherwise
die on the table.
But then, I chose to
use my gifts to kill.
So, tell me...
Which one of your friends
is pulling your strings?
Really--which one?
Is it Sea Man,
Game Master, Gourmet?
You're not sane enough
to be the leader.
[THE DOCTOR]
You know their names?
[YUSUKE] All seven. But I need
you to fill in the other blanks.
[YUSUKE] What's your boss' name,
and how is he
planning to beat us?
What's his power? And where
the hell are you hiding out?
I'll tell you.
[YUSUKE] I don't know how
to break it to you, Doc,
but that's really not how
you answer a question.
[The Doctor chuckles]
Come on!
Yes, I know...
That hit was too hard.
I shouldn't be standing.
But after blocking
pain signals,
and an extra jolt
of endorphins,
I feel pretty good!
Call off your Territory.
Let these people get
over your sickness.
And I swear I'll let you live.
[THE DOCTOR] Yes, but you
won't let me go free.
Of course not.
You're going where
straightjackets are dress code.
But that won't help.
Once I spread my virus,
I can't reverse it.
Even if I leave here,
the Territory stays.
Besides, I've never liked
those padded rooms.
You're telling me there's
no way to stop this?
Not while I'm conscious.
And by manipulating
my brain's chemicals,
I can always prevent
myself from going under.
[THE DOCTOR] You're only
choice is to kill me. A human.
But you can't do
that, can you?
If you've got any
fears about death,
you better work them out.
You missed me, I think
you're the one who's afraid.
[Genkai cries out]
Great, only thousands more.
[elevator ding]
Shizuru?
Oh, thank goodness!
Genkai, Keiko is sick.
I think she's
in real trouble.
We're all in real trouble.
There must be some place
those bugs haven't gotten to!
Yes, in here...
For now.
We're trapped?!
All right, let's go.
Wait.
What? I'm ready!
Just listen,
it's too quiet.
Well, I'll give
you that.
Quiet is perfect!!
It's a hospital,
not a race track!!
It's the cause
without the effect.
[KUWABARA]
What do you mean???
We saw Yusuke's Spirit Gun
blast through a window
in the middle of the day.
Yet there are
no doctors, nurses,
or guards taking a look at it?
So what?!
So curiosity is one of man's
most predictable forces.
If people don't come to see it's
because they are not able.
We assume the worst for
everyone in that hospital.
They're either detained,
hurt, or dead.
And that is why we are
not being followed.
Well, that does
make sense.
They wouldn't walk into
their own trap.
[KURAMA] It's too
dangerous for us all.
Especially with
Kuwabara's condition.
Geeze, condition makes
me sound like I'm rabid.
You three stay back and
watch for developments.
I'll go take a look around.
Hey!
That's not a
team decision!
Please be careful.
[KURAMA THINKS] The front
entrance won't be safe.
Neither will the back.
[KURAMA THINKS]]
A psychic's Territory.
I must take care.
They're keeping distance.
They're avoiding
the Doctor's trap.
This Kurama won't
be easily ambushed.
Well that's perfect.
The tunnel's our
major objective,
but it's not the only one.
Sir, let's do it now.
We'll catch them off balance.
The Doctor's outnumbered.
Yusuke could kill him.
Then let him die.
The Spirit Detective must be
enlightened one lamp at a time.
Yes sir.
Ten more minutes, Yusuke.
Then everyone with
my virus will be dead.
And I know that includes
a few of your friends.
You can't avoid it any longer.
You have to kill me.
Cross the ultimate line
that divides all men.
But you've never killed a human,
and once you do that...
You can never go back
to the other side.
It's like a narcotic.
You just have to
keep on killing,
or else the guilt
will overcome you.
At least, that's
the case with me.
[YUSUKE] I've kinda learned
to respect people, but not you.
Oh good, he speaks.
I was beginning to think
I was talking to myself.
[THE DOCTOR] We've
already been through this.
This time I won't miss.
This time I'm gonna
blow your head off!
You're... serious.
Tell me you have a plan for us.
I'm leaving you here,
I'm concerned about
Yusuke and Kido.
[GENKAI] You should be safe.
I don't think the bugs can get
in the elevator while it's shut.
Just don't take
any pleasure strolls.
But Keiko, she looks bad.
[GENKAI]
Don't worry.
She'll recover fully once
I get my hands on that Doctor.
[GENKAI] You better
shut the door.
[SHIZURU]
Wait! Genkai!
What a mess!
Puu! Puu!
[KEIKO]
Yusuke.
[SHIZURU]
I'm telling you, girl.
You just focus on getting
better. Yusuke's gonna be fine.
[KEIKO]
Yusuke...
Easy, Yusuke. You don't want
to go through with that.
Think about your future.
You'll be put in
jail as a murderer.
Planning out the future's
never been my style.
[YUSUKE] I hope
you like cremation.
[NURSE 2]
Doctor... help.
[YUSUKE]
No!!
That's very good, Yusuke.
Raise that finger again
and I'll cut off her head.
Quite a complication...
You must be glad to have
an excuse not to kill me.
[AYAME]
Koenma, sir.
What is it?
I've received the latest
update on the tunnel report.
May I ask you why
you're out here, sir?
I just needed a
place to think. Shoot.
The tunnel's expansion
rate is not only high,
it's consistent.
It seems this psychic
never needs to sleep.
A combination of
stamina and might
that a hundred typical
psychics couldn't match.
That's why Sakyou tried
to dig a tunnel with money.
Not even he could imagine
a psychic as an option.
I understand this person
has tremendous powers,
but we still have the
Kekkai Barrier to stop them.
You don't think the psychic can
break that too, do you sir?
Surely not. No one in
existence could do that.
Knock on some wood.
[PUU]
Puu!
[SHIZURU]
Get out!
Shizuru, get out of here.
Save yourself.
Shut up! That disease
is making you retarded.
I'm already stung. It makes
no sense to try to protect me.
Maybe so, kid.
But I'm too stubborn
to admit I'm wrong now.
Kurama!
What on earth are
you two doing here?
Bastard!
Do you even know what the
guys you're helping are doing?
This tunnel they
want to open...
...it's gonna turn the Earth
into Demon World's whipping boy.
[Laughing]
[YUSUKE]
You think that's funny??
These big freaks are gonna kill
you just like everyone else!
I hope so!
What the hell is wrong
with you? You wanna die?
[THE DOCTOR]
Everyone goes.
After all these
years as a doctor,
that's one thing I know,
and in so many bad ways...
Dysentery, strokes, aneurisms,
I'd lost all sense of hope.
Then I learned the
real reason for disease.
Mankind deserves to go.
That's what they've shown me.
I've never had purpose
in my awful life,
but I'll have
purpose in my death.
Then just die alone!
[THE DOCTOR]
You bitch!
[YUSUKE]
Yana!
I... just wanted to help.
[THE DOCTOR] These devils.
They're everywhere!
They want to
ruin our dream! No!
What a sad puppet you've become.
You're not leaving now.
[YUSUKE] Yeah.
This is your last chance.
You find some way to
get unconscious
and call off your virus.
Or you die.
Okay, fine,
so I have lied a little.
There is a way to cure them.
But you have to
promise to let me live.
You better convince me.
Look!
It's the anti-virus.
Enough for everyone.
You can have it.
[THE DOCTOR THINKS] ] Fool. I'll
gut him as soon as he takes it.
Don't get closer!
I could read his thoughts!
He's planning to kill you!
Those vials are nothin'
but glucose! Sugar water!
No!!!
Your last chance just
flew out the window.
No!
[THE DOCTOR]
Devil!
[THE DOCTOR] Yes,
waste time. In seconds,
everyone
infected will die.
Hey, the color's wearing off.
Does that mean what
I think it does?
[people moaning]
[PATIENT 1] Those men.
Are they dead?
[NURSE 4] It was Doctor
Kamiya. I saw what he did.
[PATIENT 3] Somebody
call the police!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it.
I had to do it.
I had to kill him.
[YUSUKE]
Grandma!
We don't have time to have
death on your conscience.
[GENKAI] Don't you dare question
yourself. He'll be fine.
You took the right action.
You saved countless
people's lives.
[KUWABARA] Hey!!
Urameshi!!
[BOTAN] Should I even ask why
Yana's in a nurse outfit?
[YUSUKE] Ah, you know.
Playing doctor,
and one thing led to another.
[GENKAI] Botan, he could
use your healing powers.
Right!
Puu!
Well. This certainly
is a reunion.
[KUWABARA] Oh hey sis,
why are you here?
You sick?
Yeah, bro.
Sick of tracking you down.
What trouble are you in?
[KUWABARA] Well, uh, that's a
pretty long story, actually.
You know, tunnels and stuff.
Keiko?
Damn it, Puu!
You're like their
get-in-danger tour guide.
Don't you blame
this on him, Yusuke.
We only came because we
were worried about you.
[GENKAI]
We better move it.
This is a crime scene we
don't want to be a part of.
I'll stay here and make sure
Kido gets good treatment.
[YUSUKE] Yeah. We'll just
hope he can walk again.
[screeching brakes and sirens]
[POLICEMAN] Let's go, let's go!
Bravo team, follow me!
[DETECTIVE] Okay, Doctor,
let's go over this again.
You say you slashed
up your colleagues,
gave a nurse a three-foot scar,
and paralyzed a boy...
...because you
were helping them?
[THE DOCTOR] Detective, have you
ever looked in the mirror?
I mean really looked.
We're diseased.
We're suffering.
If you knew what's best,
you'd take that gun
from your little holster
and do yourself a favor.
Erasing every human, that's
the only way to save us,
or we'll eat and destroy until
nothing is left but piss.
Capturing me has only delayed
the inevitable. For us all.
[NARRATOR] Yusuke and his
team have defeated
the deranged human
psychic, Doctor.
But six still remain.
And the completion
of the Tunnel
draws nearer by the hour.
[KUWABARA]
Move over, posers,
the real man's
takin' the stage!
You didn't really
think I'd let Urameshi
do all the hero stuff, did you?
Hey look, there's
me beating him up.
Anyway, now that we've
taken out one of their own,
the psychics are
making a counter-push
to get this end-of-
the-world over with.
And that means we'll
have to push harder!
It's a Sea Man ambush,
and it's all up to me.
I may not have many powers, but
I've got a whole lotta guts.
Don't miss it.
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪