♪
[NARRATOR] Shortly
before the final round
of the Dark Tournament,
Yusuke's mentor
Genkai was killed,
leaving him with all of the
Spirit Power she possessed.
Since then Yusuke and his crew
have been rigorously training
for the upcoming battle.
Suzuki, a member of the
recently beaten Team Uraotogi,
has helped by offering two very
powerful, yet unstable weapons,
hoping that Team Toguro
will finally taste defeat.
[crickets chirping
on a quiet night]
[SUZUKI] ...and that one is
called the Trial Sword.
Made from a Japanese Cedar
that grew to great heights
by sucking up the
surrounding life.
For Shishi Wakamaru it
became the Banshee Shriek,
but for you it should
be quite different.
And probably without the demons,
this fight was the first
time those items were used.
I can't tell you
exactly how they work
or what side effects they
could have upon their user.
Uuuhhh, you're not
gonna blow up on me are ya?
Enough with this
sissy stuff!! I'm not scared!
[KUWABARA THINKS] I just
have to pretend it's
an extension of my arm,
channel my spirit energy,
and see what the heck happens!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
It absorbs my power, right?
So whatever it makes should
reflect my real strength!
Whoa!!!
[KUWABARA]
Awww, no way!!!
[KUWABARA] Urameshi! Man, he's
not gonna believe this!
Urameshi wake up! You've
got to check out my new sword.
And brace yourself 'cause you're
about to get insanely jealous!
Hmm. He must've left.
Hey you sneaky little punk,
is that you over there?
I've got something to tell you!
Whoa! What the heck is goin' on?
[Kuwabara cries out]
[rocks tumbling]
Stupid...
rocks.
[YUSUKE] So,
you forget how to walk?
Someone should really
put a sign up there.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Something
strange is goin' on around here.
Since when did Urameshi
become so freakin' powerful?
[KUWABARA THINKS] I guess this
new power must be the reason
he could shoot his
spirit gun like a canon.
Hey genius, you gonna say
something or just stare!
Your bad attitude's not
gonna to ruin my day,
'cause I found my
secret weapon!
And here it is...
My totally fresh,
bad-guy slicin' and dicin',
mega awesome super sword!!!
Do you think it's possible
that you could shut-up?
Hey Hiei.
[KUWABARA] You really shouldn't
sneak up on someone
who's holding the world's
most powerful sword!
[KUWABARA] What the heck
happened to your arm?!
It wouldn't obey when I
gave it a specific command,
so I decided it
needed to be punished.
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Okay he's weird.
Way too much information for me,
let's stick to something
safe, like, where's Kurama?
[KURAMA] Kuwabara,
I've been standing next
to you for some time now.
A bit nervous, are we?
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Whoa, I couldn't even
feel his spirit energy!
[KUWABARA]
Alright then!!!!
Now we just need the old lady!
[KUWABARA]
Has anyone see her?
[YUSUKE]
She's not coming.
She's not well.
She just needs
some time to rest.
[BOTAN] Yusuke would
not bring himself
to tell his teammates
the truth about Genkai.
Somewhere, deep in his heart,
he held on to the hope
that she would return,
and he would hear her
make a snide remark
or give a piece of
wisdom once more.
Truthfully, Yusuke
could not tell them,
because if he did,
he would then be
admitting to himself
that she was gone for good,
and that was something
he did not know how to do.
[BOTAN] However, Yusuke
was not the only one
who felt a tremendous
weight on his shoulders.
They had all gone
through so many trials
during the course
of this tournament,
as a group and individually.
They had come to the realization
(each in their own way)
that they were approaching
the final test of their will.
There was nothing
left to be done,
no more practicing,
no more second chances.
They knew that this was
the beginning of the end.
It's time to kick some ass!
Right!
[knock at door]
[KOENMA]
Botan!
Oh, hello Koenma.
I trust Genkai's journey to the
Spirit World was a safe one?
[BOTAN] Yes. I'm sorry
I'm such a mess,
but it was the most difficult
task I've ever had to carry out.
I mean... that part of my
job has never been pleasant,
but it's never
hurt like this before.
[KOENMA] How many times
do I have to tell you--
you knew Genkai
would be leaving
as soon as she felt
Yusuke was prepared.
[BOTAN] Koenma,
but why?
Uuuuh!! How
should I know?
You need to
face reality
and start behaving like
a professional--like me!
All of this blubbering and
crying won't bring her back.
I know, you're right.
Koenma sir, I don't mean
to interrupt, but it's time.
Ah, keep your undies on.
I'd love to stick
around and chat Botan,
but I've got some important
business to attend to.
[Koenma giggles]
Why, it's practically
unheard of for Koenma to work.
I wonder if he is feeling
a bit under the weather?
[thunder]
[crowd cheering]
[JURI] Well, looks like we're
in for some nasty weather--
I hope you outside-people
brought umbrellas.
I tell you what,
if this line doesn't
start moving soon,
the fight will be over
before everyone finds a seat!
Speaking of the fight,
I think it's time
for me to get in there!
If I could have
everyone's attention
at the front entrance please.
I'm making my way there
and I need all of you to help
clear a path for me to get in!
Everyone, please make way!
Uuh, excuse me!
Announcer coming through!
Okay! Well I've just
checked my watch people,
and it looks like
we're moments away
from the ensuing blood bath!
The outcome is uncertain,
but the lovely
carnage is guaranteed
I'm not sure if I can take it--
I might faint from anticipation!
One question.
Have you arranged for
a substitute for Genkai
since she won't be
joining us today?
I did, but the little twerp
should've been here by now.
Well, I don't see
why the old broad
doesn't have to be
here like the rest of us.
She's sick.
I told you that.
Ah hah! It just so happens
I know a secret remedy
that can cure all
kinds of sickness!
Let me think,
first you hang
upside down for awhile...
then you eat five large lemons,
drink some two day old
tea with pepper in it,
and wrap your body in seaweed.
So tell me, what's it like
living in a constant
haze of stupidity?
Ahhh! I've had enough
of your lip half-pint!
Now, with no further ado,
the moment you've all been
waiting for! So let's begin!
[JURI] On my left,
Team Urameshi!
[crowd boos]
You guys have just
signed your death warrants
by showing up here!
You, Yea you!
Rest in peace!
Let's see some blood!
[crowd chants]
Kill them! Kill them! Kill Them!
I'd really like to show
every one of those jerk-faces
a thing or two about
minding their manners.
Besides, all their shoutin's
givin' me a headache.
What's the hold up, sister?
I came to see those punks fight,
not just stand around!
He's right! Let's get
this party started!
Ahem... Your attention please...
Please put your hands together
for everyone's favorite,
Team Toguro!
[crowd erupts in cheers]
Enough already!!!
Die!!! You hear me
Team Urameshi? Die!!!
Wait, something's
wrong here...
One, two, three, four...
...One, two, three, four...
Both sides are short one;
there should be five
fighters for each team!
What's the deal?
Without five, they
shouldn't be able to fight!
You know what?
If you don't figure
out what's going on soon,
we're bound to get
really pissed off!
Ahem, everyone please calm down
and I'll get to
the bottom of this.
Uuuh, let me see, according
to the tournament rule book..
Each of the ten
players must participate
in a one-on-one match,
assuming five
matches are necessary.
The first team to win three
matches will be the champions.
Sorry, about that.
Since it's the final and neither
side has used their substitution
you must have five or
your team will forfeit.
Hey, you did say you
got somebody for Genkai,
but I just want
you to know
that imaginary
friends don't count.
Riiight. I think it'd be best
if you didn't talk for
the rest of the tournament.
Great, so we're
already experiencing
officiating difficulty!
In case anybody
upstairs is curious,
I do have the entire
tournament rulebook memorized.
[DEMON] Come on, buddy!
Can't you make one
small exception?
I'll even give
you the money
I planned on buying
my ticket with!
You can't beat that!
Have a heart, I've been
here since last night!
Yeah, well I've been
waiting here for two nights!
Aw lighten up, dude.
We won't tell if you won't.
How many times do I
have to tell you jerks!!
You best back up or
I'll take your heads off!!
If you ain't got no ticket,
you ain't got no seat!
There's no ifs, ands,
or buts about it, got me?
Oh, it sounds like it's
impossible for us to get in.
I'm sorry girls,
I was so preoccupied
when I spoke with Koenma
that I totally forgot
to ask him about tickets.
I'm afraid we won't be
able to watch the finals.
Well, you know what they say.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
You're not gonna charge
the bouncer again are you?
Unless you have
another bright idea.
No...
[YUKINA] Attack really
is our only option.
[BOTAN] Why, Yukina! You're
just full of surprises!
Well, what do we have here,
it's the oh-so-lovely
friends of Koenma.
You know, this day just
keeps on getting better.
Uuuh!! I know you.
You're that sleazy scalper
who tried to con Koenma
into buying those
fourth-rate tickets!
How nice of you to
remember me, I'm touched.
I don't mean to
be presumptuous,
but I couldn't
help noticing
you foxy ladies are
in need of a hand, eh?
Well we sure as hell
don't need one of yours.
Oh, I see, my mistake.
Well, then I guess you won't
mind if I sold these elsewhere?
Um, are those what
I think they are?
You bet they are, sweet-stuff,
and they happen to be four of
the best seats in the house.
And for you, I might be
willing to part with these
for about five
thousand clams apiece.
Geez, I'm such an idiot.
Can you believe that the tickets
were in my hand
this entire time?
Hey! You'd better
give those back!!
I guess I could be wrong,
but these look an awful lot
like our tickets, don't they?
Botan?
Uh, yes, yes those are
definitely our tickets,
our tickets definitely!!
Alright, girls that's very
funny, but the joke's over.
Just give me back
my tickets, okay?
But our names are on
them--they must be ours.
What do you mean?!
[SHIZURU] Look.
Here.
See.
[BOTAN] Told ya so.
Thanks for holding
'em for us though.
Sorry buddy,
but you gotta admit their
names are on the tickets--
and common property laws--
[SHIZURU] You see.
We really didn't need
your help after all.
Thank you so much
for our tickets.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
Hope you learned it won't pay
to take advantage of people.
I can never resist the
charms of one beautiful woman,
much less four crafty ones.
But they've got no
problem resisting you!
Shut up!!!
Both teams need to
find another player soon.
Because if you don't I'll
be forced to disqualify you
and forfeit this match,
and that's not good!
That's all you had to say.
Our reserve team member
is always ready to
join us when required.
It's him!
Right, uh-which him?
What's going on-- why is
everyone just standing around.
I suppose we'll
know soon enough.
[YUKINA] Does anyone know
who that strange
man at the gate is?
No, I don't really
know who he could be,
he's very good-looking.
Yes he is. Do you think
he's someone important?
Hurry.
[SAKYO]
Come on!
[SHIZURU] Let me
guess, human?
Yes, but remember
that down here,
we're in the minority,
so be careful.
[SHIZURU]
That's right.
Just walk away like all
the beautiful men in my life.
[KEIKO] Hey Shizuru,
earth to Shizuru.
Is something wrong?
Just a little dizzy.
[DEMON FAN] Hey big shot!
Do you even know
how to fight?!
Well, to be honest...
I have no intention to
participate in this match.
Granted, my presence
allows Toguro to continue,
but all it means for
me is a much better view.
I'll stake my life on
Yusuke's team being defeated
before my turn arrives.
Now let's begin.
That's what I call putting
your mouth where your money is!
Toguro is prepared!
Now present your fighter
or the finals are over!
Uuuh, what now
Mister Team Captain?
We've got like two seconds
for this guy to show up!
Hello!
Since Team Urameshi
has failed miserably
to produce a fifth player,
Team Toguro will be named
the winners by default!
[KOENMA] Hold it, missy!
Patience is a virtue.
[KUWABARA] Wow Urameshi,
this fighter you got even shoots
out some kind of magical smoke!
[KOENMA]
Um, not exactly.
I just thought dry ice
would be a nice touch.
It's the giant Koenma!!
So, what kept you,
a diaper change?
Great.
[KOENMA] Look Yusuke, you can
cool it with the wise cracks.
I don't have to
be here, you know.
I'm doing this as a favor.
Highly important
people like myself
shouldn't risk their lives,
but Genkai was a friend
and Toguro is a jerk.
So this is
what he meant
when he told me he had
business to attend to?
Way to go Koenma, sir!
You knock 'em dead!!!
[BLUE OGRE] This is the
proudest moment of my life!
Are you sure this
is a smart idea?
We don't even know
if he can fight!
[KOENMA] Believe it or not,
fighting isn't way up
there on my list of priorities,
so I've implemented
an escape route.
[KOENMA] The KOENMA-TRON five
thousand. What d'ya think?
[KUWABARA] I think we're in
deep trouble, that's what!!
Okay. Forget what I said.
Let's go!
Wait a second!
You can't just switch!
The rules say that a new
player may only be brought in
if an original
fighter is dead.
Well, about that.
It doesn't matter.
[KARASU] Their team will
never get to the fifth match,
so it won't be necessary
for junior to fight.
We all know he's just
here to take up space.
[KOENMA]
Anytime, mask boy.
What's wrong with you!!!
Alright! There's
finally a full roster,
so get ready to feast your eyes
on the Dark Tournament's
bloodiest massacre yet!
Ladies and gentlemen, it's taken
us seven long days to get here.
Welcome to the finals!
[buzzer]
[KARASU]
Bang.
Awe, look at him tryin' to
scare us with his dumb finger.
Man, I'm gonna beat him
until his mother
doesn't recognize him!
No.
I will handle him.
It has been decided--
we will begin the final with a
match between Team Toguro's...
Karasu!
And from Team
Urameshi's side... Kurama!
[NARRATOR]
After much anticipation,
the long-awaited
final has begun.
Kurama has claimed
the opening battle
against the charismatically
powerful Karasu.
But can he overcome
his new rival?
[BOTAN]
Hello everyone, it's Botan!
Well, it looks like the
final is finally here!
Anyway, don't be fooled
by the earlier confusion,
because now the teams are set
and the Dark Tournament's
greatest action begins!
Anyone who's followed
since we first landed
on Hanging Neck Island
knows how much we've endured,
and this climactic final is
guaranteed to topple it all!
Carnivorous plants
the size of buildings,
explosive bats,
and you can bet that steely
Yoko Kurama will appear!
Next on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪