♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi's
crew fights Team Masho
in the Dark Tournament.
But Kuwabara's injuries,
and a scam trapping Hiei
and the Masked fighter,
made Kurama and Yusuke
the only ones who could fight.
Kurama defeated the
first two opponents,
but in the process
sewed a Death Plant
into his own body.
The third opponent, Bakken,
hoped to murder
the unconscious Kurama,
but Yusuke stepped in
and saved his friend's life.
There are two opponents
left from Team Masho.
Yusuke must face
them both on his own.
[JIN]
N, I, C, E.
Might be worth having
the ol' shinobi job
with a place like this.
[YUSUKE]
Hey! What's up?!
I thought we could fight
if you're finished sight seeing!
And all I have to do is
beat Urameshi to get it!
It's about time.
[KOTO] Jin's coming down with
his famous nose-dive descent!
I'd say he's ready to begin!
Wha--? It's some kind
of circling pattern!
He's trying a distraction!
[YUSUKE] How 'bout a trade?
[KOTO] Yusuke makes
a valiant attempt,
but he proves unable to compete
with Jin's swift aerial attack!
[JIN THINKS] Took a punch
straight in the face
just for a chance to kick me.
He's a crazy rat for sure.
I admit that one didn't
have much of a chance.
Nice punch though,
this is gonna be fun.
Yusuke's elbow
and kick combination
came from an almost
impossible stance,
nearly unheard of in
the martial arts schools.
I can't imagine any master
teaching him that one!
We're a pair in a pod Urameshi.
Never wanting to do anything
the way people tell us to.
Even if we don't make sense!
[JIN] Better to be messy
on your own then right
under someone's
watch. Am I right?
Well yeah. Why let some
teacher get the credit?
I figure I've been doing
all right on my own so far.
[CROWD CHANTS]
Kill Yusuke! Kill Yusuke...!
What in the world are
they talking about up there?
They're both smiling!
I think Urameshi finally found
somebody he can complain with.
He's been a loner for about
as long as I've known him.
I mean Keiko's the only one
who could talk to him,
and I'll be darned if I
understand that relationship.
But this Jin guy's just
the same-- like a twin.
Well that'll make
fighting with him difficult.
What's wrong Kurama?
Are you alright?
Just laughing.
It seems that you don't know
brothers very well, Botan.
[KOENMA] I guess wind has
some perks, after all.
Jin seems to be a
pretty strong opponent.
Yusuke will have to be on
high guard if he wants to win.
Jin's a cheater
if you ask me, sir.
He flies around in the air
and Yusuke can't touch him!
[KOENMA] Well as usual I
didn't ask you, Ogre,
but the fact is that Jin
uses his own energy to fly.
So it's totally legal.
All the same, sir.
Yusuke's still
at a big disadvantage
because he can't fly!
What should he do?
I don't know.
Let me show you
something I picked up,
without any help from
any bosses flapping their gums.
Wow! Is that what
I think it--? Yes!
Jin has actually
created a miniature twister
around his entire right arm!
The wind is tremendous!
This is one of my favorites.
Tornado Fist's the name.
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Could be bad for Yusuke.
That attack Jin's using is much
more powerful than it appears.
So you ready?
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it! I'm
flopping around like a windmill
and he barely scratched me!
Better avoid a direct hit.
[KOTO] Looks like Yusuke's got
a date with the cement!
[KOTO] Nicely played! He's
clung like a fly on the wall.
But I don't suspect he'll
be staying there for long!
Here comes Jin
for a second helping!
[cries from the crowd]
[KOTO]
I love it!
There's the
audience participation
that makes the Dark
Tournament so special!
I imagine any of you who survive
that attack will remember
it for years to come!
[BOTAN]
Audience participation.
I hate that girl!
This is bad. It doesn't mater
how strong Urameshi is,
or how much fun he's havin'.
If Jin hits him straight
on with that Tornado Fist,
it's over with.
Stupid.
Long time since
I could fight somebody
and actually have up some
cheering about it you know.
I think I do.
They might as well fork
over the money to me now.
Yusuke's the only
boy they've got left,
and Jin's impossible to
beat when he's having fun.
Besides, I'm pulling the
whole tournament committee
along by their ass hairs.
You know it's not too
late to place a bet Sakyou.
I'll stay with my own
arrangements, thank you.
Ooooh. So the highest
roller of the betting world
is playing it safe for once?
I don't take chances Butajiri.
I just happen to
be well informed.
Remind me to quote you on
that when I'm rolling in green.
[BUTAJIRI THINKS] I'm
manipulating this whole round.
How better informed
can a person be?
I've decided I
should have the power
to control wind too,
Ogre. Look into it.
What for sir?
Well I'm sure I could do
all sorts of heroic things.
But more importantly I'd
get free air conditioning.
That's noble of you,
Koenma sir. Very noble.
There! Both fighters
are back in the ring
and ready for some
fresh new injuries!
[JIN THINKS] Whew!
that's a wiggle!
Not this time, pal!
And they're charging up!
It's becoming too fast to see!
But then, I guess you people
in the audience are
used to that by now!
Kuwabara, you can follow
their movements, right?
Me? Uh yeah!
I'm spiritually aware!
Good. You can inform me.
You mean right now?
Well uh, they're just...
They're both punching
each other very rapidly.
That's very perceptive.
Thank you!
[HIEI THINKS] On the ground
Yusuke has the greater speed.
But unless he can clip
Jin's wings it's pointless.
Here's my chance!
And there's my chance
going airborne, damn it!
Jin's been hit hard!
Taking refuge in the air
until his squashed
diaphragm can recover!
Listen miss Koto!
Why don't you stop the
sadist routine and do your job!
[KOTO]
Excuse me??
Jin's been out of the
ring for half of the fight!
Did it ever cross your
mind to count to ten?
Article 4: Fighters
are outside the ring
when any part of their body
comes in contact with any solid
surface other than the ring
itself. And air is not solid.
Stick to what
you're good at, honey.
Like dying your hair
unnatural colors, for instance.
I swear I'm gonna get her!
Hey... what is this?
How's Urameshi supposed
to have a fair fight
if Jin can run
whenever he wants!
It's not a wonder why
Biggy was taking a
dive in the seats then--
Yusuke having punches like that
is enough to kill any mug.
Guess I'll just
rest up here a bit.
Think myself up another plan.
Hey!
Bingo!
I knew he'd do that!
Jin! Move, darn it!
Yes! In that stuttering,
off-guard position will Jin
be able to move back in time?
Not too likely!
That's right, I'm cool.
Always underestimating the wind.
Hey, I needed that!
Real heart-pounder that one was.
Did we get that on video?
Please tell me
we got that on video!
Jin just used a wall of wind
to turn Yusuke's
blast into a space cadet!
Don't get all big eyed.
Any attack has to travel
through air to get to me right?
I control the air so
you might as hand them over
and say do whatever
you want with them Jin!
[JIN] Do whatever you
want with them, Jin!
Urameshi's little light
shows won't do anything
against Jin's wind defenses now!
Good. I've been
waiting too damn long
to see that boy
get put in his place!
Not just him, either!
There's no one left on
Urameshi's team who can fight.
Once Yusuke's
finished, they all are!
Rip off his ugly human head!!!
Well they don't have to
act like it's already over!
Yes, I thought the: "Kill
Yusuke!" Chant was a lot better.
[KOENMA] I always thought of
wind as a sort of gentle breeze
on a summer's day kind of thing.
What about Hurricanes
and Tornadoes, Koenma sir!
Jet streams! Gale force winds!
That's serious!
Entire houses can be torn
to pieces like match boxes!
Pencils can be shot
through solid brick walls!
Calm yourself Ogre,
you're spitting on me.
Anyway, the problem here is that
Jin can use his powers over wind
for excellent offense and
defense against Yusuke.
That's not a happy combination.
So Yusuke can't use
his long range attacks
because Jin will
deflect them with wind.
Yeah the Spirit Gun is
pretty much a waste of time.
He'll have to stick to
the old fist-fighting action!
But every time Yusuke
gets close enough
for a final punch
Jin flies away!
Well yeah, that's true.
So how in the world is
he supposed to hit him??
I don't know Botan!
Don't yell at me!
The Spirit Gun should not be
completely useless against Jin.
There is one way to
get past his defenses.
But it will not
be exactly safe.
Don't have to worry about
Yusuke being afraid, at least.
Risking his life is the
only constant strategy he has.
Been a blast playing defender
but I think I'll
get on with my attack.
Here we go! Jin's winding up for
another smashing Tornado Fist,
but this time he's doing
it while still in mid-air!
Hope you're
thinking quick Urameshi!
[YUSUKE THINKS] There's
one way to do this.
[KOTO] Jin's on the move!
He's headed straight for Yusuke!
And yet the Spirit Detective
is refusing to back down!
He's not even guarding
himself! Has he gone berserk??
Don't be stupid Yusuke!
What is he doing??
Now I understand.
[JIN]
Hold on! Don't be crazy!
So, if he fires his attack
point blank into Jin's tornado--
The energy will be caught in
the wind current as it ignites,
causing the explosion
to surround them both.
[YUSUKE] Let's see who can
take a bigger ass kicking.
Spirit Gun!
[HIEI THINKS]
At least you tried.
[KOENMA]
Is it safe yet, Ogre?
I don't think you
want to look.
[KOTO]
Oh my, people!
Both fighters have been
obliterated in the explosion!
Nothing is left of their bodies!
Not even a pile of ashes!
Oh hell.
[KOTO] Wait! I stand corrected!
Yusuke Urameshi has survived!
Only Jin's been incinerated!
[KOTO] Never mind again!
Jin is alive and looking
quite perterbed!
I thought I was crazy Urameshi
but you take the prize!
The hell was that?
You don't make bombs
go boom in your face!
Damn? At least one
of us should've died!
He is no amateur opponent.
I'm not saying he is--
but that was a clean shot!
[HIEI] Yes. But Jin saw your
strategy in the last moment,
and took evasive action.
Rather than guard himself,
he tilted the air stream,
sending most of
the blast upward,
probably saving both your lives.
So he's funny and smart.
That hardly seems fair.
As a Shinobi he
has much experience.
A simple trick isn't
going to beat him.
I hope you have
more extensive plans.
Ah, come on! It's Yusuke here!
I don't have a clue!!
You might not be so proud
after you're defeated.
Shut up. Something always
comes to me at the end.
Well yes,
even a fool has to admit a
certain truth to that, Yusuke,
so go ahead and be
as reckless as you want to.
If you do get killed.
I'll be taking your spot
in the next fight, anyway.
What?
Please-- even if
you could escape me,
it's illegal to return
after you've been
ruled unfit to fight.
[HIEI]
Illegal?
Listen Ruka.
My power has nearly returned
and I'm going to fight.
And anyone who says otherwise...
Well, I think
you know the rest.
[MASKED FIGHTER] You truly have
a way with women, Hiei.
[KOTO]
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
[KOTO] After seven counts
Yusuke returns to the ring!
Don't get too excited, Hiei.
I'm taking on their leader
just as soon as I beat down Jin.
Oh? Just as soon as
you beat Jin, you say?
Better pinch
yourself quick then.
Last I remember
it was you running
round the floor
tryin' to stay up.
Yeah, but this time
I thought I'd try.
[JIN] Funny man Urameshi!
Then I'll try as well!
[KOTO]
Fight!
Don't guess the finger gun
can handle two
these dallies at once?
[KOTO] Ooh, baby! Two Tornado
Fists buckled on at once!
Think we've got a challenge!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I'll say.
There's no way I
can deflect both
of those with my Spirit Gun.
Spirit Grenade Launcher,
maybe, but definitely not a gun.
Yusuke's having enough trouble
as it is with just one tornado.
Yeah, we better hope
that he's feelin' creative.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Two big
shots with one attack.
Come on Yusuke, you
know it's the only choice.
Even if you don't
really know how to use it.
[KOTO] Wait! Now
this is unexpected!
Yusuke is taking a stance
I've never seen him take before!
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
He's going to try it!
Genkai's signature.
Yusuke's handled elements
of the move countless times
in his training,
but I know for a fact he's
never used its full form.
With his utter
lack of discipline,
Genkai was never led to
believe Yusuke was ready for it.
She still doesn't believe it,
I would even venture to say.
The move could
definitely compete with Jin
but it could also destroy
Yusuke's body from within.
Holy smokes, that pose!
It does look curious
sir. Is it yoga?
It's a fighting stance, you oaf.
And it happens to be for
Genkai's greatest specialty.
I could never forget that one.
Uh, you're talking about the
Spirit Wave, aren't you sir?
[KOENMA]
Exact-amundo.
And Yusuke specifically
told me he hadn't learned it.
He can stand upside down
with his thumb up
his ass for all I care.
He's not gonna win.
I never seen Urameshi
do that crazy stuff
with his hands before.
Me neither.
Have patience.
He certainly has a
history for surprises.
[JIN] Eye at the wind
on him now, so I say!
He's wrapping around like
a one big tornado of his own.
Whew and wee, and fun sorts!
Flying that power
like crazy he is!
I can't be waiting anymore!
Let's play it!
[NARRATOR] After the long
and unusual battle,
Yusuke must brace himself
for one final charge.
Is he truly ready to
advance in his training,
and perform his
teacher's secret move?
[KOENMA] Greetings,
all you ordinary people.
Koenma speaking.
It looks like Yusuke's got
a mighty task before him,
in a crunch to perform
the incredible technique
that he was too lazy to
learn when he should have.
What? Not enough to
tantalize your senses?
Well how about
the sudden arrival
of the Ice Apparition Yukina,
who-get this-is searching
for her estranged brother!
It's Yusuke's first
rip-roaring Spirit Wave,
and some good
long-lost family drama.
Plus Team Masho's leader
is about to remove his cloak.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪