[KUWABARA yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Yu Yu Hakusho...
[grunting]
[URA-OTOKO screeches]
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi! Get out of the way!
[gasps]
No...
He can't be... He can't.
[SENSUI]
Trial of humanity.
The defense rests.
[SENSUI] There's little time
for closing arguments.
The tunnel is open.
[SENSUI] Are any of you brave
enough to lead the way?
Attempt to finish what your
late friend could not?
Sure...
Bravery is the only
thing we got left.
[gasps]
Ah...
[SENSUI]
Incredible...
Their Demon Energy has
jumped to A-Class levels.
Hey...! Wait for me, you guys!
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi.
You died a hero's death,
sacrificing your life
to save billions of others.
You've lit our torches, and I
won't let your death be in vain.
Even if it means I'll
be joining you soon.
Sensui, you're gonna
regret makin' me mad!
[yells]
[yelling]
Dragon of... the Darkness Flame!
[DEMONS screeching]
Here's a one-way ticket
for you straight to hell,
you bastard!
[DEMONS screeching]
Huh. Not a bad way to travel.
[yelling]
[KUWABARA]
Guys, where're we goin'?
[KURAMA]
We're going in.
[KOENMA gasping]
[SEA MAN]
Hold on!
Are you gonna be
all right, Mr. Koenma?
And what will happen to us now?
The world didn't come
to an end when the tunnel
opened up, I don't think.
These things don't just
happen in an instant.
It's not like
dropping an atom bomb
at a certain time and place...
The battle will be
drawn out and those beasts
Hiei deep-fried were
just the first wave.
More of the cannon-fodder
will follow soon,
but they aren't the ones
we need to worry about.
There are Demons of
far greater strength
and intelligence, lurking in
the depths of Demon World.
Laying low and waiting
until they know it's safe
for them to pass
through to this world.
And then...
...they'll unleash a
terror more destructive
than any weapon man
has ever forged.
And that is how
the world will end.
But, what about
the Kekkai Barrier?
Won't that keep the
really bad Demons
from escaping?
I thought that's why they
wanted Mr. Kuwabara's power.
So they could use it to break
the net that's in their way.
But since that never happened...
The barrier must still
be intact, right?
[KOENMA]
Kuwabara will slice through it.
Why would he do that?
In order to avenge
his friend's death.
He wouldn't do
anything that rash!
You obviously...
don't know Kuwabara.
I'm in no position to stop them.
The last of my authority
died with him.
Where are we?
In Demon World?
No, we're in the Pseudo-Space.
It's a neutral zone between
the two worlds, a limbo.
Right, who cracked
open an Idunn Box
and turned you back
into your foxy self?
[KURAMA]
I've not become Yoko Kurama,
I've merely taken on the
appearance of my Demon form
while retaining my
human personality.
It's a side-effect of this
increase in Demon Energy.
There he is.
Huh? Whoa.
It's like bein'
inside of a video game.
[HIEI]
No. Trust me, it's not.
[gasps]
What's that?
[HIEI]
It's the Kekkai.
Then how the heck did he
make it through here?
[SENSUI]
I'm glad you asked.
As you remember, my energy's
of the Sacred kind.
Fortunately, the brains
in Spirit World only made
this net to filter
out Demon Energy.
That's why I passed
through unscathed
while Hiei's attack burned
out when it hit the net.
[HIEI] If my best technique
can't even singe his ass
through this fence, how are
we supposed to fight him?
But you and your friend
should take some consolation
in the fact that this Kekkai
is only sensitive to the energy
of A or S-Class Demons.
[SENSUI] Which means, that
in killing your friend,
I've awakened the potential
you've both dreamed of.
Your silence is all
the thanks I need.
Ironically though, now that
your powers are finally
strong enough to match me,
you can't get close.
Heh.
Hey, what are you doing?
He's right, we're trapped.
The only way you'll
get to me and satisfy
Yusuke's dying wish
is if Kuwabara can get
his Jigen-Tou up again.
Ha! Yeah, well I'm 100% human,
so I can still make it through
on my own.
Urameshi couldn't
take me on his own.
What makes you think you
stand a chance in hell?
We'll see when we get there!
[KUWABARA grunts]
[KUWABARA yells]
I could handle you
myself, but this way,
even if I die, they can
still use your skull
as an urn for Urameshi's ashes.
Huh.
This is where you end, Sensui.
[yells]
[KING YAMA]
Does your being here mean my son
has used his Mafuukan?
I'm not sure of that,
King Yama, sir.
All I know is that
there was an earthquake
coming from the cave...
But I'm positive Yusuke
will do something.
[KING YAMA]
That's what I'm afraid of.
I can no longer trust a
cataclysm of this magnitude
in that boy's hands.
[BOTAN]
But, sir, Yusuke...
[KING YAMA]
...is no longer on this case.
I have no choice but
to call in my own men.
The... Spirit Defense Force?
[BLUE OGRE]
The SDF? Things are bad!
The prince's slack
leadership has wasted
too much time already.
--[gasps]
--[BLUE OGRE whimpers]
It's worse than we thought...
My son made a very grave
error when he recruited
that Spirit Detective.
No one could predict Sensui.
[KING YAMA]
You understand nothing.
If only we had known earlier...
Known what?
[BLUE OGRE]
What should we have known?
[ALARM VOICE] Attention: The
situation in Living World
has reached code red.
This is not a drill.
Special Defense Force
personnel please report
for immediate deployment
to Living World
by order of his royal
majesty, King Yama.
The King would like
to thank you in advance
--for performing this civic duty
--[CAPTAIN] Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[ALARM VOICE] to him and
to all of Spirit World.
[NARRATOR] The Special
Defense Force. The SDF.
Revered by citizens of
Spirit World and feared
by denizens of Demon World.
Their mission, primarily
a peace-keeping one:
patrolling the occupied
territories of Demon World
and terminating any Demon
who gets in the way
of Spirit World's expansion
of the controlled zone.
[NARRATOR]
In the rarest of times,
the King may deploy SDF troops
to Living World if a Demon
poses a major threat
to the human population.
However, their presence on
Earth is quite conspicuous,
and thus, very rare.
[KING YAMA]
Believe me, I do not enter into
such decisions lightly.
Every casualty grieves me as
though it were my own child.
But the cause is righteous,
and this action, necessary.
[BOTAN] I've never seen
the SDF mobilized.
I hope they can give Yusuke and
Koenma the backup they need.
[BLUE OGRE]
I want my mommy!
[DEMONS growling]
[DEMON A]
Look at those C-Class trash,
clamoring for a
piece of human flesh.
They give all of us
Demons a bad name.
[DEMON C] Haven't those
short-lived cretins
ever heard of overpopulation?
From what I hear, the streets
up there are paved with people!
[DEMON B]
Speaking of which,
shouldn't we get in line?
[DEMON A]
Like lambs to our slaughter?
I don't think so.
Why's that?
For all we know, this
could just be another
of Spirit World's
Demon-eradicating trap.
Oh, yeah.
[gasps] There's four powerful
beings heading this way.
Two of them's got Demon Energy,
one's Spirit Energy,
but the last...
[gasps]
[DEMON B] I don't know what
kinda energy he's got,
but it's a lot,
and I don't really wanna
stick around to find out!
[DEMON A]
You heard him, guys.
Let's not be the
Welcoming Committee.
[DEMON C]
Catch 'ya on the flipside!
Where's he takin' us now?
What's that thing?
The exit.
[SENSUI]
So this is Demon World.
I hope...
...that I will find what
I'm looking for here.
[SENSUI] I need to see where
they live, Mr. Itsuki.
I need to breathe their air.
I will find a way
into the Demon World.
They don't deserve you...
How can you protect the
humans from themselves?
Make amends and fight on
behalf of the demons!
No, kill the Demons!
Fight the real enemy!
The Demons are the enemy!
[SENSUI] The depths of my soul
are rooted in dark thoughts.
But then, we all have
darkness and light in us.
If we are all light
on the outside,
there is nothing but
darkness underneath.
There comes a time when the
darkness must come to light.
Hey, has anybody noticed
that we're falling
very, very, very fast?!
Hiei, do you know where
in Demon World we are?
Yes, I believe I've been
to these parts before,
and if I'm right,
then we're rather lucky.
It's the Forest of Fools,
just low-level Demons
who won't present any
kind of challenge to us.
I know we're about
to die and all,
but I really hate it
when you guys ignore
what I have to say!
[KUWABARA screams]
Hold on tight.
[yells]
Fox, then a butterfly;
is there any animal
you can't metamorph into?!
I haven't turned
into a butterfly...
This is merely the
leaf of a plant,
doubling as a glider.
Look at that cocky punk,
just free-fallin'
without a care in the world--
but I'll betcha he
wishes he had somethin'
to catch him now!
[gasps]
What did he do?
[SENSUI] You begin to see
what my Sacred Energy
is really capable of.
I don't have a bag of
tricks or packet of seeds
and I don't need them.
I can fly without
any roots attached,
without even the
help of my maker.
That's why they
call me Black Angel.
If we lived in
less cynical times,
the gift I'm preparing for
the world might've been
labeled for what it
really is: a miracle.
You think you can scare us
with that holy one crap?
Does he really believe
we'd turn around
after all we've been through?
Who cares what he is
as long as he's dead.
I admire your electric
enthusiasm, Hiei,
but I don't wanna hurt
these beautiful woods.
You mind if we finish
this fight over there?
Oh, I see. The Plateau
of the Beheaded--
a fitting battleground, indeed.
Come to think of it,
it's giving me some ideas.
I got some of my own.
This is not something
I usually do...
Fighting opponents who I know
have no chance of beating me.
But I'm making
exceptions for you,
to offer some modicum of peace,
that you at least tried to
avenge your friend's death
before your own.
Oh, come on now! Is that
supposed to impress us?
[KUWABARA groans]
[gasps]
Sacred Energy Armor!
[KUWABARA] Am I the only one
not doin' a costume change?
The great thing about this armor
is that it not only
strengthens my defenses,
but boosts my offense as well.
You can't stand up to me!
I'm a living, breathing,
sentient tank!
Well, I think you
might want to consider
spinning your turret around.
[HIEI growling, yelling]
The Dragon...?! Another one?!
[KURAMA] This may be the
first time Hiei has ever
been willing to die for
anyone but himself.
[HIEI yelling]
[groans]
You're just addin' more
debts to your tab!
The Binding Fist
of the Demonic Vine!
[KUWABARA]
And I think you know this sword.
[KUWABARA yells]
[KUWABARA]
Huh?
[KURAMA yelps]
[SENSUI]
Twisted Twister!
Kurama!
[groans]
Now you are really
starting to piss me off!
[gasps]
[yells]
[gasping]
[HIEI groans]
[panting]
[coughs] Sensui really
is invincible now.
[HIEI groaning]
Nothing worse than being strong,
but not strong enough.
It only prolongs the
inevitable conclusion.
But be sure...
This will be your inevitable
conclusion no matter
how long it takes
us to reach it.
[growling]
[NARRATOR] Even though they
have him outnumbered,
Sensui has Hiei, Kurama
and Kuwabara overpowered
on the battlefield
of Demon World.
This is one foe they may
not be able to defeat,
but they'll die before
they ever give up.
Yusuke's death
hangs over them all.
A reminder of what
they're fighting for.
But will they be
joining him soon?
[BOTAN]
Whew, this is way too much drama
for one afternoon, as the war
intensifies on all fronts.
In Demon World, our boys
try their hardest
to beat Sensui, but this guy
doesn't even need a Band-Aid!
On the surface, Puu
shows signs of life,
but what does that
mean for Yusuke?
And back in the cave, the SDF
arrive with special orders
that will turn everything
we know upside down:
And don't think that's
the last surprise!
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho.