[YUSUKE yells]
[yells]
My Absorbing Wall is
invincible to any attack.
Then you won't mind if I try!
It's no use.
What?!
[YUSUKE yells]
[YOMI groaning]
He broke through!
Yes, of course!
He's mixing his Spirit Energy
together with his Demon Energy!
A combination that only someone
of Yusuke's odd
origin could make.
He's not such a fool after all.
[YOMI groaning]
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE yells]
[YOMI groans]
[KOTO] In what looks to be
an act of mutual destruction,
Yusuke's Spirit Gun
blast was so robust
it consumed him along with Yomi.
This could be the tragic
end for two brave warriors.
Father.
[gasping]
He's okay.
[laughs]
[SHURA]
Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
You aren't such
a pale substitute
for your demon father,
after all, Yusuke.
Here I was, beginning to think
the same thing about you.
[KOTO]
Looks like you'll be getting
your money's worth
today, fight fans.
They're poised for a new round!
What d'ya say we finish this?
[YUSUKE yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[YUSUKE screams]
[YUSUKE]
Huh?!
[YUSUKE screams]
[BOTH grunting]
[YUSUKE groaning]
[YUSUKE yells]
--[YOMI yells]
--[YUSUKE gasps]
[YUSUKE yelps]
[YUSUKE yells]
[CROWD murmurs]
Looks like we're gonna
be here for a while.
[panting]
Urameshi! Don't give up now,
you've almost won!
Hail Yomi!
[CROWD cheering, yelling]
[MUKURO] I don't foresee
Yusuke lasting much longer.
There's no way he can win,
not in his condition.
It seems that he's the only
one who isn't aware of that.
Yomi's greatest power
has yet to be revealed.
[YUSUKE]
Bring it on.
[MUKURO]
Is he still trying to win?
[KURAMA]
It's much more than that.
[HIEI] Perhaps the detective
understands honor after all.
[YOMI]
What's going on?
I'll tell ya!
He's gonna kick your butt
like the regular-named guy
--in a wrestling match!
--[gasps] What the...? Kuwa?
[GENKAI]
Yusuke... Listen to me.
This isn't about you.
Every decision you make...
[BOTAN, KOENMA ] You can do it,
Yusuke! Don't be a moron!
[CHU]
Give it a fair go, mate.
[KURAMA]
We believe in you, Yusuke.
[KUWABARA, YUKINA, PUU, SHIZURU]
Urameshi!
[JIN]
A friend to the end, so I say!
[SUZUKI]
It's beautiful.
[KAITOU]
Simple, really.
[GENKAI]
Do you understand?
--[BOTAN] Bingo!
--[JORGE] He's amazing, sir!
[GENKAI]
You have to...
[KAYKO]
Yusuke!
[YUSUKE]
I have to, what?
[GENKAI] You're fighting
for them, Yusuke...
for their future.
What's that?!
Sensui's Sacred Energy!
No it's not. This is
something brand new.
[YOMI]
Uh!
Whatever it is go with it!
You got this biggie now!
[YUSUKE growling]
[YUSUKE screams]
It's disappointing that our time
together must come to a close.
Defeating you will be
an honor... Yusuke.
You can't end a good party
without someone on the floor.
I suppose not. [yells]
Now! Come on!
[YUSUKE growls, yells]
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE, YOMI grunting]
[YUSUKE groans]
Urameshi! Take him
down, Urameshi!
[YUSUKE groans]
[CROWD cheering]
[HOKUSHIN]
Yusuke...
If only your father
could see you now.
[YUSUKE, YOMI grunting]
[yells]
[YOMI groans]
[KOTO]
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
--Nine...
--[groaning]
[panting]
I guess you're feeling better.
--[TOUYA] Well, well,
--[CHU] Ace!
--finally awake.
--[FRIENDS laugh]
--[CHU] How you feelin', kid?
--I'm not sure.
'Bout time you woke up.
What the hell's going on?
Is this a dream?
Dream it's not. You were
knocked down and out, Yusuke,
that's the truth.
Your loss was a week ago.
You've been asleep ever since.
[gasps]
I lost?
We thought you'd both crash,
but Yomi managed to stay up.
I think hearin' his runt
scream is what saved 'em.
Uh. Father!
That's fine.
[JIN]
Too ra loo!
T'was the best fight
I'll ever see!
Your battle with Yomi changed
everything, how everyone fought.
It defined rippa!
[YUSUKE] So where are we
at now on the tournament?
Is it the semi-finals yet?
No, Yusuke.
The tournament is over.
What?!
[DEMON CROWD cheering]
Well the fights have been long,
the fights have been tough,
but as all great things do,
this romp has come to an end!
And so I present to you the
winner of this tournament,
and our new sole ruler
of Demon World... Enki!
[DEMON CROWD chatting]
I thought for sure
it'd be Yomi.
He lost in his first
match after you.
Who was it?
An inconsequential foe he
had no business losing to,
but his injuries from
you were too much.
Your punch didn't earn a win,
but it did defeat
him in the end.
And Mukuro?
She gave her all
to beat Natsume,
then lost to him
in the next round.
Well... Here I am,
by strange circumstances and
the mystery of the matching.
But I've come to believe luck
is just as important as planning
in this life. So I'm taking
this leadership over us,
but I'm making it only
a three year term.
Three years?
Then what? Then we have
to do it all again?
Sounds great! You can
sign me up to fight!
Why? So you can get your butt
kicked in the prelims again?
[PINK-EYED DEMON]
Shut up!
Well, the rule was
whoever wins,
no matter what, all demons
have to obey his or her laws,
and so I'll hold you to that.
Now it won't be
hard to remember.
I'm only enforcing
one great law.
[coughs] My law is, from now on,
there will be no mischief
in Living World.
[DEMONS]
Uh...
What?
[ENKI] We've been
fighting for too long.
It's something I learned
from an old friend.
This is how I'll
honor his memory.
I'll create a council and
figure out the particulars
of this in a week.
Where's Yomi? I'd like
to see his reaction.
He left, soon after his loss.
Where to?
He described it as a "Journey of
New Truths" with his son.
A good name.
[YOMI]
Yes.
My fight with Urameshi made
me reevaluate things.
I'll train Shura to beat
him, in the right way.
Huh! Give me credit.
I can beat him right now!
I'll train so I
can beat you, dad!
And of course I'll be tougher
than you, Kurama!
[KURAMA] Hm. Something
to look forward to.
When Urameshi wakes, could you
relay a message for me?
That he gave me a sense of peace
I've never had before...
And I'd love to fight him again,
though I doubt I could win.
As for you...
I want you to know that
I respect your decision
to leave your past behind.
[KURAMA]
Same for you.
Kurama...
I'm happy that you
took my invitation.
[ENKI] Well thank you
for coming, everyone,
and listening to me.
Things are going to start
getting better around here.
[DEMON CROWD cheers]
[JIN] Well I'm not sure when
I'll be seein' you again,
Yusuke, but you'll always know
that I see you as a friend.
Gotcha'.
It's not like it's
goodbyes for good.
There's another tourney
in three years, ace.
[TOUYA] If you're not
still in love, Chu.
I was only training
for a tournament.
I didn't expect a revolution.
But I do feel like myself again.
So it's back to Living
World for you, Kurama?
Yes, it's time I chose a home.
[TOUYA]
Yeah.
--[CHU] See ya, bludgers!
--[SUZUKI] It's been real.
[JIN]
Farewell, you two!
[JIN] I'll be up for
playin' any time!
[YUSUKE]
See you guys! You're the best!
[YUSUKE laughs]
So Yusuke's going
back, after all?
[KURAMA]
That's what he says,
after he takes care
of some things.
[HIEI]
And I guess you're off, too?
That's right. To my family.
[KURAMA]
Hiei...
I can't accept this.
I value our friendship,
and all we've been through.
[HIEI gasps]
But I'm not interested
in you that way.
You fool, I'm not giving
my stone to you!
[KURAMA]
Relax, it's a joke.
You want me to give
this to Yukina, right?
That's right!
I want you to tell her
that her dear twin brother's
been dead for years.
Why don't you return it
to her yourself, Hiei.
I'm staying here in Demon World.
I want her to call off her
ridiculous search for me.
Even if you did want that,
I won't shut this door for you.
You'll give this to her...
At your own pace.
You're the same way you
were the first day we met.
A pain who speaks the truth.
[KOENMA]
Happy with yourself, Yusuke?
[KOENMA] You realize you
took a serious gamble,
arranging this tournament.
If another demon had won,
all three worlds could have
been plunged into a war
of unspeakable horror.
Ha! Look on the bright side!
That's not what happened is it?
--[KOENMA] You idiot!
--[YUSUKE] Uh?
[KOENMA] Once again,
you didn't use your brain!
You acted on heart,
and dumb instinct.
In fact, all of you did.
[sighs] But somehow it worked.
Without you, Kurama, and Hiei
fighting on emotions alone,
this peace wouldn't
have happened.
Yusuke, what you've
managed to do is--
Spare me the gratitude. Like
you said, I wasn't thinking.
So my punching Yomi knocked
him out of the race...
And me powering up got
the others to max out
before the final round.
That's nothing I could've known.
I was just fighting.
[KUWABARA]
These fellas won't ever get it.
Winning's never been the
real reason I fight him.
[YUSUKE]
That's just the kinda guy I am.
I can't take thanks for it.
Come on! You saved the world,
so take the credit! [laughs]
[KOENMA]
I understand, Yusuke.
You two could live
a thousand lifetimes
and still never run out
of things to fight about.
That's what makes hanging
out with you so much fun.
I'll miss it.
[KOENMA] As for your detective
gig, your firing is permanent.
That's good.
I was just about to
tell you I quit.
[KOENMA] Guess our next
meeting will be more formal.
Right. When my time comes.
[YUSUKE]
Just make sure you
actually have a space
for me next time.
[KOENMA]
Sure.
Who knows? Maybe by then you'll
be out of your diaper phase.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[KOENMA] Well, I'd say
that's a good end
to a detective's career.
What should we do with all the
footage we've compiled, sir?
[KOENMA]
Package it.
[NARRATOR]
And so, indeed,
Yusuke's journey as a
Spirit Detective is done.
What lies ahead as he
grows from boy to man?
Not even the supposedly
wise Koenma could know that.
I won't give you the narrator
job if you annoy me!
[laughs]
[RAIZEN]
Hey, son.
Just gonna stand
there looking stupid?
Your dumb war is over, Dad.
I wasn't tough enough to
take the crown, though.
Huh. Well of course
you aren't yet...
You'll need another 300 years.
So, what will you do
in the mean time?
[YUSUKE] Don't know.
I'll think of something.
[RAIZEN] Come on,
you can tell your old man...
There's a trip you need
to take, isn't there?
[YUSUKE]
A trip?
Okay.
You got me... There's one.
Tell her how you feel.
She's the best thing you've got.
Guess the apple doesn't
fall too far from the tree.
We're both jerks for love.
[RAIZEN chuckles]
See ya, Dad.
[RAIZEN]
Hey.
Don't worry, I'll come back.
Yusuke, Sir.
I know, save the speech.
Demon World is vast with lots
of great places to explore,
and I should stay and get
stronger, and not leave.
Right?
Actually, no, Sir.
We've come to say
have a good trip,
and we'll keep training
for your return.
Someday.
Farewell.
[YUSUKE]
Aw, thanks.
[NARRATOR]
As a fourteen year-old boy,
Yusuke Urameshi
was struck by a car.
Now, with friends and memories
locked in his heart,
he looks ahead to a new
adventure: Being all grown up.
[YUSUKE]
The secret's out.
And all this time you've
been watching clips
from the Spirit World's Records
department, about my life.
Botan begged to do
this preview, but--
[BOTAN]
I wasn't begging--
[YUSUKE] But the last
one's gotta be mine!
[KURAMA] Then perhaps
you say what happens?
[YUSUKE]
You're here, too?
Well obviously no one's gonna
miss the last episode!
I mean you guys wanna see
what happens to us, right?
Because there are
more surprises--
[BOTAN] Not to mention
the most romantic smooch--
[YUSUKE]
Shut up!
[KUWABARA] Urameshi,
your face is turning red!
[BOTAN] See you there,
on the last Yu Yu Hakusho!