♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi's
team fights their opening battle
in the Dark Tournament
against the Rokuyukai Team.
In the third match,
Hiei faced their
apparent leader Zeru,
and unleashed the fearsome
Dragon of the
Darkness Flame to win.
But a new opponent,
loudmouthed and drunk,
claimed he was
the true captain.
Yusuke awoke from
his deep slumber
and stepped into the ring.
Now the game-point
fight begins.
[crowd cheering]
It's leader vs. leader!!
Yes! Blood! Blood!
Kill Urameshi!
Kill him for us all!!
This is so exciting!
I've never heard such an
uproar for an early fight!
I can't hear myself!
I could say horrible things
and no one would know it!
[KOTO] Ever so slowly the
crowd is calming down.
And it seems the same
is true for Chu--
Why--his previously
glazed-over eyes
could almost be called sober!
Suddenly I fear
this Chu won't be so easy.
Yeah, I here ya.
You know. I've
heard lots about you.
'Course, I think you're a scared
little kid who gets lucky.
Now, now. Try
to loosen up.
It's going to be hard for
Yusuke to survive this one.
Why do you say that?
Well it's just a hunch.
But, mine are usually right.
The boy has become
Genkai's apprentice,
and he's undergone
her training two times now.
But up to now we
haven't seen its results.
Surely he must have
learned her special technique.
Oh that's right, you
mean her Spirit Wave?
Of course I---
Hey! How can
you be chowing down
during such a crucial
moment for our team!
Obviously I'll have
to confiscate it!!
[BLUE OGRE] Please Koenma sir!
I brought that from home!
[KOENMA] Bad Ogre! Bad!
Let the fight begin!!
At last he shows himself.
I've never sensed
spirit energy of this kind!
Watch carefully...
I want to know what you think
of my stumbling little feet.
What the--?
That guy's fast.
Notice how his body flows.
Yes, and his speed only
adds to the problem.
Good luck trying
to hit him.
Finally! Chu's started
acting serious!
Wow, people. I guess
the loon has talent after all!
His moves are
so fast and bizarre
I can't even tell where he is!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Focus, Yusuke.
You've gotta find this guy.
[CHU] Have another cop!
[HIEI THINKS]]
Five. Impressive.
Even from this killer view.
I couldn't track
Chu's strange moves!
But I suspect we've missed some
of Yusuke's fantastic agony!
Let's double-check
with our slow motion
Instant Replay feature!
[KOTO] Yes! Chu actually
gave five quick wallops,
then finished with a to-die-for
blow to the back of the neck!
Amazingly painful,
don't you think?!
[crowd cheers]
Quite a beating.
Yeah, he's not
even fighting back.
[KURAMA THINKS] No.
I wouldn't exactly say that.
Had enough, have ya?
[YUSUKE]
Of course not!
This game has just begun!
What the hell is with this guy?
[YUSUKE] Would
you stop jiggling?!
Damn.
Try using your feet!
Or your elbows maybe!
Ya he wouldn't expect that!!
[YUSUKE]
Kuwabara--
Do me a favor
and shut the hell up!!
Alright!
My! Such a delicious attack!
I wish we had time
to watch every blow
on the Instant Replay screen!
Suffice to say Yusuke Urameshi
has been buried
in a pile of rubble!
Ah, did everyone
else feel that?!
Chu must be five times stronger
than that brat
I went up against!
Oh, we're in some trouble!
Hey Foxy, can you
lend me a hand?
Right, I still need another one!
Let me translate again...
As with all Suiken Fighting
Masters, Shaku gets more
effective the more he drinks.
I believe he's asking
us to be more
patient while he acquires
the rest of his clumsiness!
Exactly!
With Chu listed
as the alternate,
it was so easy to
overlook this team.
Perfect way to scam
the other gamblers!
Hypothetically, of course!
What do you think the chances
are of us gettin together, lady?
Slim to none!
[DEMON FAN 4] Hey lovebirds!
He's out of the ring!
Oh wake up, jerk!
I was checking on Chu to
make sure he was fit to fight!
Now moving on!!
[KOTO]
One!
I hope Urameshi
doesn't get stuck out
of the ring like I did.
Then one of you would
fight Chu in a tiebreaker.
Yeah, I was
thinking about that.
That's why I hope
he gets himself up!
[KOTO]
Five!
Come on now, kid!
I thought you wanted to see
some challenging techniques!
[KOTO]
Seven!
[CHU] I haven't done
nothin' bonzer yet.
[KOTO]
Eight!
Nine!
[YUSUKE]
That was close!
I could have been killed
if I didn't guard myself!
I get it!
The old see it coming and
block with the shoulder trick!
What a champ, right?
Yeah! Rip him a new one!!
There you go girl.
Sorry. It's exciting.
One dumb mistake and
I'm pushin' daisies, right?
Yeah, pretty much, kid.
You know, this whole
life-or-death thing.
I'm starting to like it.
Let me guess you too?
Never any pleasure in
playing if it ain't for keeps.
That's good drunkie. We finally
found something in common.
You can fight at any time!
[crowd reacts]
Hey! Why the heck did
he go and waste his bullet!
Good question--I'll assume
it wasn't a matter of bad aim.
My Spirit Gun.
You better get to know it...
I got three more left, and
one could probably kill you.
Not too long ago I could only
fire one of these a day, but,
well I was just
so scrawny back then.
Just like Chu,
Yusuke has introduced his move
before using it on his enemy!
But this is the Dark
Tournament, not the Happy Game!!
Where are the dirty cheats?!
The blackmail threats?!
The backstabs?!
Darn it Urameshi!
I'm the one who's got
the Honor Code! You copier!
Everyone's shoutin' at ya now,
but you wanted a fair fight!
Oh, think that
terp I drank wants
to come back and say hello.
Right, it's about time.
You got your secret technique...
Okay... So turns out I got mine.
I don't believe it! He's
really gonna' do the move?
And... so soon!
Watch me carefully.
It's complicated.
So what's this special
technique he's so proud of?
I don't know
but it must be good.
As much as he's
building it up.
This... Is the strongest
alcy ever made...
It's called Ogre... Killer.
Oh yeah people
that's some strong stuff...
Take a sip of that and you'll
wake up in jail
the next morning,
in the arms of a hairy demon
you really don't want to know.
And he's definitely
taking more than a sip!!
What?
This Ogre Killer...
I take it's not something you
drink for nutritional value.
No sir, not if you consider...
The liver damage.
[KOENMA THINKS]
This one worries me...
Drinking it as if to reach
some darker beast inside of him.
Something very
strange is happening.
The entire stadium is
being eclipsed by Chu's aura.
What is
happening to him?
Don't know. It
just feels weird.
The entire audience
can only wait in a hush
as Chu reveals his technique.
Dare we hope for
something truly horrific?
[throwing up]
Tell me he didn't!
Oh brother! I need to start
telling Chu to bring a bucket
or something when he
uses his special technique...
Happens every time!
I can't believe apparitions pay
money to see this filth...
Hey! Hey! Surprise time is
over! Get off the ground!
Sorry Koenma sir,
my horn got stuck.
I wonder if vomiting was
Chu's secret technique?
Need anything Chu?
A wet towel maybe?
He may feel pretty
terrible now, but actually
Chu's becoming invincible.
His secret technique isn't
the drink, of course.
It's his true form the
drinking brings out.
Better get off me, ugly!
Shut up!! I don't
care how popular you
and your friends are
getting around here,
I'm still the boss of this turf.
And I'll knock you flat on your
ass whenever I'm in the mood!
Wanna bet?
[goblin thugs laughing]
[CHU] That crap's awful!
Who the hell are you?
Say how'd you pick
this place, kid?
Their terp smells like piss...
Guess I'll have
to drink it in bulk.
That's enough! Guys,
get rid of this scum!
You better try me all at once.
Hell of a party!
[RINKU] He beat the
whole gang in one shot.
And now that he's powering up
you'll be just another
chalk mark on his wall.
[CHU] By the way, doll.
You sure smell great.
Yeah? Must be
the shampoo.
[CHU]
Now back to the biz.
Suddenly he's sober again...
Alcohol does not affect
him in the normal way...
Somehow it serves
him as a catalyst.
How odd... So the chemicals in
those drinks actually
bring out his energy.
[KOTO] Chu proves resilient
after his hacking spell--
ready to fight again!!
I think you should
act more excited, kid.
After all it's what
you've been waiting for.
Now we're definitely
in for some action!
Chu is revealing
an entirely new attack!
I can't tell exactly what it is
but heads will
definitely be rolling!
Hey what is that stuff?
His energy, you lump.
He's creating
his finishing move.
If you look closely and
I bet you can see
alcohol actually
mixed in with his energy.
Whoa! That blast he's holdin'
looks a lot like
Urameshi's spirit gun.
And approximately
equal in force.
What? Don't you think we
should tell Yusuke that?
Time for us to test our powers!
I was waiting for the invite!
Yusuke already knows.
[CHU] See you
on the other side!
Spirit Gun!!
My! The two fighter's energies
are actually duking it out!
Get 'em Urameshi's energy!!
It's a draw.
Look at 'em!
They're charging each
other at the exact same time!
My gosh!
They're not even bothering
to block those headshots!
This is pure offense.
They gave up fighting with
their brains a long time ago.
Now it's simply a matter of
who can endure the most pain.
It's impossible to count
how many punches have landed!
Or to tell who's winning
or in fact anything
significant at all!
I don't even
know why I'm talking!
Bad move.
Now I have you!
This is it!
Finish that idiot, Chu!
This time Chu's spreading his
energy into a much larger blast.
It's amazing, how much
control he has over the size.
It is, and by the sheer volume
Yusuke won't be able
block it with his Spirit Gun.
Try not to
sound too worried.
[CHU]
One last go!!
Dammit!
He's off-balance.
He can't defend!
[HIEI THINKS]
Do something Yusuke. Hurry!
Just get out of the way!!!
Oh, Yusuke!
[CHU THINKS]
There's nowhere to run.
And it'll take more
than your little bullet
to stop this train.
Yeah! You did it Chu!
You beat him!
No one can get
away from that blast!
[YUSUKE] Spirit Gun!
Double!!
What?
[CHU]
Double?
It's breaking through!
Careful Urameshi!
His blast is still goin'!
Too late.
Double devastation!!
No way man! He hit him!
They're all gone!
They've been disintegrated!
Don't say that Kuwabara! I
don't care if it's true or not!
No trace of either warrior
can be found! Nothing!
Not even a little pile of ashes!
Has this fight
truly ended in a draw?
Up there!!
Unbelievable! Both
of them have survived!!
Well they've burned their skin,
shortened their breath,
and somehow lost their shirts-
altogether I'd call
it a successful fight!
With that two for one shot
you've used up all
the ammo for your Spirit Gun.
Maybe you can round
up enough energy
to swing your little dukes,
but that's about it, right?
Pretty much defenseless.
I can barely lift my arms.
[Chu chuckles]
[Yusuke chuckles]
Can you hear them?!
They're laughing at
their own helplessness!
It seems the strain of battle
has driven them into hysteria!
What is he doing?
Finish that stupid kid!
They're at the end of their
line. I know how this will end.
In a tie?
No, that's not
what he means.
This battle,
determines everything.
They'll refuse to give up.
Mate, I know a way we
can finish this for keeps.
I'm all ears.
[NARRATOR] What are
Yusuke and Chu planning?
Both exhausted,
both with nothing
but their fists.
Will the end of
this team battle truly be,
a fight to the death?
[KURAMA] When Yu Yu
Hakusho continues,
the end of the arduous team
battle will fast approach,
as Yusuke and Chu
agree to a bout
with deadly finishing terms.
With a pair of daggers
driven behind their feet,
they will be forced into
close fist-to-fist combat.
And whoever is knocked
beyond the daggers
will accept the
penalty of death.
All eyes in the stadium
will be on the center ring,
as these two perfectly
matched opponents
fight desperately
for their lives.
♪