♪
[NARRATOR] To stop an Earth
invasion of Makai Insects,
Spirit Detective Yusuke
Urameshi and his crew
have journeyed to Maze Castle,
battling the Four Saint Beasts
behind the sinister plan.
Kurama, Kuwabara, and Hiei
have defeated the
first three beasts.
Only the leader remains.
But in retribution for
the death of his men,
the final beast
has turned the army of
insect-infected humans
on Keiko Ukimura,
the girl Yusuke
cares about most.
Can Yusuke overcome?
Hurry it up!
Shut up!
[YUSUKE] What the
hell is that thing?
It's the watchtower. I'm
sure that's where he's hiding.
Fine! Then let's drag him out!
Take your punishment, Ukimura.
There.
Hey. You're that girl!
Keiko, have they
hurt you in any way?
I think I'm fine.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Yusuke, this is Botan. You copy?
[ringing]
What now?
Small problem.
Keiko???
I had to pick her
up from school, Yusuke.
It seems every infected person
in the area is looking for her!
What?!
[BOTAN] And I don't think
they want to talk.
I'm almost certain
they mean to kill her!
Did you say kill??
So! That's what
my premonition was!
The beasts must be using
the Makai Whistle to order--
Cockroach!
You alright?
Come on!
Botan! Are you there?! Botan!!
I don't have a good
feeling about this!
We've got to smash that
whistle as fast as we can!
[KOENMA] Oh dear.
Botan! You get
that girl out of danger!
[BOTAN]
I'm trying!
We cannot afford
to lose Keiko's life!
Why not sir?
You know how Yusuke
is with authority!
If I let Keiko die,
that delinquent will never
take orders from me again!
[BLUE OGRE]
Oh.
But our only chance is for
Yusuke to get that whistle!
So keeping Yusuke
only depends on Yusuke!!
Oh dear, I better
see how he's doing.
Hey, somebody took
my remote control!
Sir, that is the third
time you've lost it today.
Can't you hear right! I said
someone's taking it from me!
But sir, wouldn't it be easier
to just press these buttons
on the front panel here?
Don't you believe in
progress? Oh, here it is!
[BLUE OGRE]
I already changed it.
The looks on their faces
have certainly changed.
[SUZAKU]
Yes, from bold confidence
to panicked desperation.
I can hardly wait to see
his face when she's dead.
I would hate
for Yusuke to arrive
early to the presentation.
We will need something
to distract them all.
Well, you know the cultivated
humans are my favorite.
[SUZAKU]
Good idea.
[Suzaku laughs menacingly]
Okay guys, that is
a spooky watchtower!
The last beast should
be on the top floor.
Then let's climb some stairs!
[mindless groans]
Hey, who are those people?!
[NARRATOR] Cultivated Humans.
Demons grow these
bodies in large fields,
stripping them of their
free will at birth.
They are perfect,
brainless slaves.
Whatever those guys are,
there sure are a lot of 'em!
It's gonna take us about
a year to beat 'em all!
Yes, considering
our time restraints
this could be a real problem.
I've had dealings with
cultivated humans before.
They do not feel pain or fear.
How twisted do
you have to be
to turn humans into
monsters like that?
I think Keiko's in
some serious trouble.
Like hell she is!
Stupid monster humans
trying to slow us down!
I'm blowing 'em all
away with my shotgun!
Let's use our heads.
What--you want me
to headbutt them?!
It's not wise to waste
your Spirit Power.
The more impatient we are,
the more mistakes we will make.
Well how is
headbutting gonna help?!
My shotgun is the only
way we're gonna get past 'em!!
[HIEI]
No.
So you got an idea??
Set your eyes on the
first tower window.
[HIEI] That is your door.
Well I'm sorry Mr. Mysterious,
but as it turns out
I forgot my pogo stick!!
Yeah! How do you expect
him to jump that high?!
I'll need you to listen closely.
You best not blow this Kuwabara!
Don't worry I'm like an ox!
Just do me one favor you guys!
Try not to dig in
with your shoes, okay!!
Hey, shut up and keep running!
[KUWABARA] All right!
Let her rip!!
It'll be close.
We did it!!
Remind me to try out for
the cheerleading squad!
You guys have fun
with the veggie-heads!
Don't die on me! Okay?
Poor guys, I'm gonna feel
bad kicking your butts!!
[YUSUKE]
She better be okay!
Keiko! Botan!
[whistle plays]
Put that thing down!
So nice to see in you person,
after watching you attempt
to ruin my plans for so long.
I am Suzaku,
leader of the Saint Beasts.
And I am his dear Murugu.
I've been watching
your dear Keiko.
It's amazing how much
humans resemble animals
when they're being hunted.
[Murugu laughs]
Here's the deal.
Pull your zombies off Keiko.
And then I'll only
pull out one of your lungs.
And if I refuse?
Then hold your friggin breath!
Thanks for helping
me out back there.
You're that girl Yusuke was
with on the roof, aren't you?
Yes, but--
If there's something
going on between you and him,
well I can't stop that,
but please tell me where he is!
Well, I can guarantee
that Yusuke is all yours.
But why don't we
work out those details
after we escape from the
hundreds of infected humans
who want to kill you.
The phone-line's been cut.
I'm afraid they're
getting a lot smarter.
Maybe there's someone
in the teacher's lounge.
I've always loved
the way you think!
Excuse me.
Mr. Takenaka!
[KEIKO] Mr. Takenaka!
I need your help!
There's hundreds of people
outside, and they're trying to--
He's out!
Mr. Takenaka! Please wake up!
U-ki-mu-ra!!
[Keiko screams]
[Suzaku laughs]
You should feel
most fortunate, Yusuke.
Not everyone's girlfriend
gets to star in a horror movie.
[SUZAKU] Of course, the films in
my city are somewhat different,
Demons usually don't care
much for happy endings.
You think you can
control me, don't you?
[YUSUKE]
Control this, you bastard!!!
[SUZAKU THINKS]
He's fast.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I don't believe this!
He's blocking me
with one stupid hand!
[SUZAKU THINKS]
He's very fast.
Bad choice.
[YUSUKE] Funny thing about
hanging in the air.
It's really hard to dodge!
His Spirit Energy!
Spirit Gun!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Perfect shot.
What?!
Your blast is very powerful.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
He-knocked-my... that's bad.
You actually made my
hand numb with last attack.
It is a very good thing
you can't hit me with it
or I might be in some trouble.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Six months of
misery with that fossil Genkai,
and my Spirit Gun
still gets whacked!
Let me hold the Makai
Whistle for a moment
while you drain away his life.
Thank you Murugu,
but that isn't necessary.
I'll destroy him with one hand.
Oh hey, thanks a lot.
I just love the renovation.
My pleasure.
Ooh Suzaku! You're using
that technique on a human?!
You're going to die!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Give me a break!
Who does this guy think he is?
You can't hold lightning!!
[NARRATOR]
Storm of Torment.
Uniting the powers of
lighting with Spirit Energy,
a hybrid force is created
to envelop an opponent
in a wall of torture.
Escape is nearly impossible.
Are you ready?
Storm of Torment!!!
[Yusuke screams]
Look at him writhe, Suzaku!
I just love when they do that!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it, I
could've sworn he missed me.
Did you see what
happened to him?
I did, sir.
I really hate watching
violent scenes like that.
Yes, it looked painful sir.
Gee, did you see the way
his body wiggled around??
How can you have an appetite
after watching all that?
Regular meals are important
for my development.
Knock him flat, Yusuke!!!
You'll find that the
energy will seek you out
like lightning to a rod.
But take heart,
you are the first human
to ever survive my technique.
You must feel so proud.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I gotta
find a way to block that.
There's no way I
can handle another one.
You have much more
Spirit Energy
than the other pawns King Yama
sent after me in the past,
but it will never be enough
to ruin my great plans.
As soon as you rise
I'll have to finish this.
Why don't you stay down and
watch the end of Keiko's movie?
She won't be so easy to
shove in a corner you know.
Keiko's no fighter,
but she's plenty tough.
And she's not following
your stupid script.
She's not. And neither am I!
Let's do this asshole!
I trust you're
not being serious.
Don't you see what
he's doing, Suzaku?
He thinks he can block the
lightning with his rubber shoes!
You're truly an idiot!
You might as well block
a cannonball with paper!
[Murugu laughs]
Why don't you go lay
an egg or something!
[SUZAKU] Yusuke Urameshi. You
are my perfect justification.
You are why demons should take
the place of humans on Earth.
You're an idiot race
that deserves extinction!
Prepare yourself!!
[BOTAN]
Here we are--in a corner.
I'm the person these
sicko's are following.
Let me lead them to one
side so you can get away.
I'm sure you'd make
a wonderful distraction,
but it's much more
important that you survive.
We'll have to find some
way to fight them together.
We're reasonably athletic girls
with a couple good sets
of fists, aren't we?
Yes, honestly I was hoping
you wouldn't accept my offer.
There must be something.
Keiko, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
We'll separate on the
count of three, okay?
One, two, three!!
[Keiko cries out]
Die at the hands of Suzaku,
leader of the Saint Beasts!!
What the--?
[BOTAN]
Hurry! Let's go!
Hold on Botan!!
It's my turn!
[SUZAKU THINKS]
Of course!
This boy is smarter
than I thought.
He used Spirit
Energy in his fists
to make a shield
against my attack.
The shoes were just
a ruse to hide behind.
A stellar hit, Keiko!
You should fight
on the boxing team!!
I just hit a teacher.
Come on!
Sorry beast-boy,
but your movie's a flop.
I'm assuming you won't mind too
much. If I make a few changes.
[NARRATOR] Everything the team
has fought for in the battle
with the Saint Beasts
is coming to a head.
As Yusuke begins
his counterattack
against the powerful
beast Suzaku,
one question must be asked.
Even if Yusuke
can claim a victory,
can he do it soon enough?
[KOENMA] Yes, Koenma here.
I tell you this fight
is getting hard to watch.
Not only are there
three separate fronts--
But seven Suzakus!!
It's enough to make
you nauseous--hold on,
let me put away this food.
Okay, like I said,
Yuske's fighting seven
different Suzakus,
Hiei and the gang
are to trying chop through
an army of cultivated humans,
and Botan and Keiko are
running through the school
trying to avoid some zombies!
It's perhaps the
craziest episode ever,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!!
♪