♪
[NARRATOR] One day,
Yusuke Urameshi was killed
in a car accident
after saving a boy's life.
He awoke as a ghost,
and traveled with a
guide named Botan
to the mysterious Spirit World.
There, the child ruler
Koenma gave Yusuke an ordeal
that could win back his life.
Hatching a Spirit Beast.
If Yusuke is bad,
then a monster will hatch
to devour him forever.
But if he's good,
then a guide will emerge
to bring him back to life.
You know it'd really be
embarrassing to get eaten by
somethin' that came out
of an egg this tiny.
[BOTAN]
Well Yusuke...
If you'd do some good deeds
then you wouldn't have to worry.
Please! I hate people who
call themselves Do-Gooders!
They say they care but they're
always out for themselves!
Everything's half-empty
with you isn't it, Yusuke!
As long as you keep
this crummy attitude
you'll never get your life back.
That toddler Koenma has got
me by the balls and he knows it.
He's just another idiot
that's abusing his power!
You've got to watch
that tongue Yusuke.
Who cares! We're alone!
We don't know that for sure.
Koenma is probably
sending investigators
to check on how you're doing.
Investigators?
What do they look like?
[thunder]
They look like that.
Like what?
Hey, pleased to meet you!
That was quite an entrance.
Who the hell are you?
The Investigator!
[YUSUKE]
No joke.
So you're the one, huh?
The one Koenma sent to
check on Yusuke's progress?
I'm Sayaka!
These kids!
Then why don't you tell me
what you're gonna
investigate, Sayaka!
I'm sorry.
But that's a secret.
Botan if you would help.
Which one is
Yusuke's girlfriend?
Girlfriend? I don't-- What
are you talking about?
Which of the girls is Keiko?
Not that again!
Why can't you spirit people
get it through your thick heads!
She's just a friend!
Right down there.
[BOTAN] Keiko's the
one in the middle.
It's hard to believe
that a girl with her
kind of positive markings
would even go
for a guy like him.
[YUSUKE]
I heard that!
Now are we absolutely certain
that Keiko wants Yusuke
to come back to life again?
After all, there's a great
deal of manpower involved
in making one of these
life-recoveries run smoothly.
There's no point in doing it
if the people closest
to you don't care.
Hey look, this ordeal
thing wasn't my idea
so don't throw me a guilt trip.
And as for Keiko,
how am I supposed to know?
It's clear if she had any
sense she'd want me gone.
She wants you back.
[YUSUKE]
You think so?
She always looks
at me like this--
Hey Yusuke, come to school!
Hey Yusuke, that's
not the right uniform!
Yeah she probably just wants
me around so she can yell at me
and get a better
reputation with her teachers.
Why do you say
things you don't mean?
You know she only scolds you
because she actually
cares about you.
Sayaka, I've learned not to
listen to him most of the time.
He's just embarrassed is all.
He's got the cutest
crush on Keiko!
Botan!
Why don't you nail your
stupid mouth shut!
Why don't you get
over your stupid cuties
and admit that
you like her, Yusuke!
The nature of this
relationship between Yusuke
and Keiko doesn't seem clear.
I'll have to
investigate it further.
[KEIKO]
And the tranquil waterway
leading to the uttermost
ends of the earth
flowed somber under
an overcast sky--
seemed to lead into the
heart of an immense darkness.
And that's Heart of
Darkness people!
Perfect reading
as always, Keiko!
[girls laugh]
Come on Keiko can I pretty
please see your math homework?
Sorry, but you have to
learn to do it for yourself.
Keiko, help.
I can't figure
out this question.
Let me see.
Smart. Athletic. Friendly
but stern with her friends.
Her scores are next to perfect.
This attraction between Yusuke
and Keiko must
obviously be one-sided.
I can hear you!
[SAYAKA] Here comes a handsome
boy. This should be interesting.
Excuse me... Keiko.
[HANDSOME BOY]
Do you have a minute?
Yeah, of course.
[HANDSOME BOY] I heard
you reading in class today
and it made me
sad when you stopped.
And it wasn't the book because
I thought it was lame.
See I've fallen in
love with your voice.
[HANDSOME BOY] Will you
be my girlfriend, Keiko?
[KEIKO]
Sorry, but no.
[HANDSOME BOY]
What?! Why not?!
Don't tell me I've come too
late and you like somebody else!
I do.
NOOOO!!!
Yusuke, you're so lucky!
Keiko chose you even over
that charming handsome boy!
Now don't go jumping
to conclusions!
She said she liked somebody
else! She didn't say who!
You can't keep
pretending forever, silly.
"I like Keiko" is written
all over your face.
Leave me alone!
Feelings on both
sides are strong
but for the most
part misunderstood.
Suggest serious counseling.
[KEIKO]
What is that smell?!
I don't even think you can get
to the other side of the room
without stepping on some
half-chewed food
or broken glass.
[ATSUKO] Keiko,
be gone for a little while.
Take care of Yusuke for me!
Guess she's back to normal.
You don't seem to have
a very responsible parent.
Very observant!
[KEIKO] This is terrible! Even
Yusuke's covered in garbage!
What kind of parent
leaves their child like this!
I swear it should
be some kind of felony!
Yusuke! Hold on Yusuke,
I'm coming! Are you all right?
[KEIKO] I'm going to have
to come here everyday,
or Yusuke won't have
a body to come home to!
Oh, just look at his face!
It's all covered with dust!
Keiko's been coming
frequently to check on his body
ever since the
day he reached her.
There you go, Yusuke.
You're all clean now.
[KEIKO]
Such a beautiful face.
Whoa-Whoa-Whoa-Whoa Keiko!
Get the hell away from there!
That's my body--
Quiet down! This is a perfect
chance to investigate her!
She can't hear us anyway.
[NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH
GUY] Attention everyone!
This is the Neighborhood
Watch Committee announcing
a general heat advisory for
the rest of the afternoon!
Please keep children and
pets inside or well-watered.
Also keep in mind the added
risk of fire in this dry heat.
We've had two fires
break out already,
and foul play is suspected.
So please be careful.
Thank you and
come back any time,
Neighborhood Watch Committee!
Oh, pinch yourself Keiko.
What in the world do you
think you're doing here?
Oh yes, shopping!
My mother wanted me to
go shopping after school.
Yes, I'll have to clean
this room later on.
There, you see? Her
feelings are very confused.
Well of course they are!
It's just young love, isn't it,
Yusuke you big cutie!
[YUSUKE]
Who was that?
The house is on fire.
Yes it, seems so.
My house is on fire!!!
My mom didn't
even have the decency
to lock the windows for me!
[BOTAN] Yusuke. Maybe we should
focus on other things.
This is great! My body's
about to be firewood!
Hey wake up stupid!
You wanna die?
It, isn't working.
I'm, definitely still asleep!
Hey wait a second.
Can't I just possess myself?
It doesn't work that way!
You can't revive
until the egg hatches!
Then what am I supposed to do?
You've got to get in
contact with someone!
What about Kuwabara!
He'll sense you!
He's probably on the other side
of town! There's no time!
I'll get him anyway!
Right! Do that! And what
am I supposed to do?!
Come on let's go!
There's a fire on 4th Avenue!
[MAN 2] That makes
a dozen just today!
The fire department
can't get to them all!
[WOMAN 1]
This is eerie.
[WOMAN 2] Yeah. I can't help
feeling like we're under attack.
Yusuke lives on
4th Avenue. What if he's...
So Urameshi? You ready
to fight back now?
Kuwabara! We've got
an emergency!
[BOTAN] Hey! Listen to me!
Hey!!!
[BOTAN]
Listen!!!
Oh no! I've got
the tickle feeling!
Yusuke's house is on fire!
If you ever want to fight
him again, go help!
Something tells me
I should go that way.
I hope it's not too late.
[YUSUKE] So just trust me and
take care of my body until then.
I will.
Yusuke!
Interesting.
Keiko has come back.
Yeah, great.
Move! There's still somebody
inside of the house!
No it's too dangerous!
You cowards!
Keiko, don't!
Yusuke!
Keiko! Forget about me!
You're a lot more important
to this world than I am!
Don't be stupid!
Go back!
You do know that
without your body
you can't come back, don't you?
What's the point
of being alive if Keiko
has to get killed for it?
[MAN 4] The fire's
blocking the door!
[MAN 5] I told that girl!
I told her!
Urameshi's house!
Kuwabara! They say
Keiko's trapped inside!
Keiko?
Urameshi's girl? The one
we saved from those thugs?
[KOMADA] Y-Yeah. I think!
[Keiko coughs]
Yusuke!!
[KEIKO]
Oh Yusuke!!
Here we go--
Botan! Please! There's gotta
be something I can do!
I'm sorry Yusuke. I've tried
everything in my power.
[SAYAKA] There is one way.
But you may
not be willing to do it.
I'll decide that
for myself!! Tell me!
You can save her life by using
the power that's been gathered
by the Spirit Beast
you've been carrying with you.
What? You mean this little guy?
Throw it in the fire
and it will unleash from
the egg, and save her.
And that's all I have to do?
Why didn't you say so?
But if you hatch the Spirit
Beast now, before it's ready,
it won't be able to
perform its usual duties.
So does that mean,
if he saves Keiko's life,
the beast won't be
able to bring Yusuke back?
Right, Yusuke will
never have a chance
to be alive in this world again.
[YUSUKE]
So my life or hers, huh?
Wish someone had
told me this morning
I'd make this kinda choice.
[SAYAKA]
Your time is short, I'm afraid.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Oh well,
it was a good dream.
Keiko!
Can this be real?
[KEIKO]
We'll make it, Yusuke.
We will.
Keiko!
Kuwabara!
Dear!
Someone's coming!
They're both okay,
we really pulled it off.
[YUSUKE]
Well I sure am... relieved.
[sirens]
[KUWABARA] Typical. Now the
fire trucks arrive.
Hey, whatcha got under
the blanket, anyway?
What are you doing
with Yusuke's body??
I promise I'll tell you
everything, but not right now.
We've got to get
him somewhere safe.
Are you some type
of sick grave robber...?
Well come on! We can't let
the police get a hold of you!
[YUSUKE]
Whoa Kuwabara!
Who said you could hold
Keiko's hand like that?
Don't start getting
fresh with her!
She's not your type!
[BOTAN]
Yusuke.
Things aren't going to be
so easy on you for a while.
You can't just wander
around here anymore.
I'll have to take you back.
I don't know who Keiko
will love in the future
but you cannot interfere.
There's no point in
her saving her heart
for someone she
will never have, like you.
Oh, no. I didn't think.
Sayaka, is there any other
way to make this work?
So it's really over.
[YUSUKE] Figures, just
when it was getting good.
[ATSUKO]
I'm so sorry
I put both you
kids at risk today,
just because I was out on
one of my stupid escapades.
And Keiko, your hair.
It's okay.
Yusuke's body is safe
and that's what's important.
I saw a road of
blue fire leading me out.
It was like a big explosion
and I was surrounded
by his presence.
Yusuke saved me because
he knows he's returning.
[KUWABARA]
I still can't believe it!
Yusuke, you old rascal!
Oh son, sorry about that fire
but you're okay
now at least! Right?
This is so stupid!
Isn't someone gonna tell them
they're just talking
to a dead body!
Stop apologizing mom!
I'll never be around to say
it's okay! I'm dead for good!
[BOTAN]
It's so sad.
[SAYAKA] It can't be helped. He
made this decision on his own.
[YUSUKE] Okay Botan,
just take me to Heaven or Hell
or wherever it is I'm going.
I'm tired of being here.
[KOENMA] Yusuke Urameshi,
there's no reason to
act like a baby.
What? Koenma?
[BOTH]
Koenma, sir!
[KOENMA] Sayaka, I have
received your report.
Yusuke, you've shown to have
more character than I thought.
I've been trying
to figure out whether
people around you
really want you back.
Contrary to my personal
opinion, they actually do.
More importantly, you've
exhibited astounding potential
to be a decent human being.
Because this trait is so rare,
I've decided to give
you another chance.
In retrospect, it was
a very good thing
you threw this
egg into the fire.
If you had allowed it
to hatch, the Spirit Beast,
which had been feeding off your
constant negative energy,
would not have
been a pretty sight.
It would have bitten
your head off.
But as you and I both know,
that's not what happened.
You threw the egg into
the fire without hesitation,
saving Keiko's life
at the cost of your own.
You have a special quality
buried underneath all that crap,
and your added
experience with death
could make you very useful.
You think I'm useful?!
So are you giving
his life back?!
[BOTAN] Oh Koenma!
You're so gracious!
[KOENMA] Just as
long as you don't call
me a toddler anymore, okay?
Yeah!
[BOTAN] Yusuke!
I'm so happy for you!
You did it! You really did it!
Yusuke!
Hey! Come on! Don't cling to me!
It's embarrassing, okay! Yeah!!
[YUSUKE]
Okay, here's the deal!
Koenma supposed to get
me back in my body, right?
Well it turns out there's
some crazy rules!
Like someone
I know has to kiss me!
And man I hope
it's not Kuwabara!
But as always, I've got
myself in a tight spot,
and there's not much time till
I miss my window to revive.
And if I do, I'll have to
wait another fifty years!
You know, it'd be really helpful
if I had some sort of phone
where I could call
these living people
when I needed, but anyway.
Can Keiko contact me
before everything's messed up?!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪