[NARRATOR] After a year
of training in Demon World,
Yusuke has made great strides,
becoming even more powerful
than he was before.
But he was powerless to stop the
death of his ancestral father,
Raizen, whose passing has set
Demon World's other rulers
scrambling to assert
their dominance.
Yusuke, too, as his
territory's new king,
set in motion his own plans.
Hokushin...
I need you to take me somewhere.
To the house of Yomi.
Yomi! You son of a bitch!
Can you hear me?!
'Cause I'm comin'!
So, boil up a
kettle of tea, Yomi!
Kurama, this friend of
yours seems rather silly.
Can he really be the
descendant of Raizen?
But let's assume it is true,
doesn't his presence here
confirm that Raizen is no more?
I suppose so.
Well, then...
I am eager to hear what
Raizen's heir has to say to me.
Youda, prepare to welcome
our guests in proper fashion.
Yes.
Inform the sentries at the
gate to give them no trouble
when they arrive.
Just measure Urameshi's
energy at the door.
As you command, sir.
Kurama, I want you
to have your men
standing at the ready
in the next room.
[gasps]
If he tries anything,
I won't hesitate
to issue the
assassination order.
And I know as Chairman
of the joint Chiefs of Staff,
you won't hesitate to act on it.
[KURAMA] You haven't
changed at all, Yusuke.
Only this time,
your impetuous nature
may trigger a full-scale war.
[CHU]
He wants us to off the bloke?
And at the first meeting?
Well, first, let's
see how things go.
Who knows, maybe
Yusuke will treat
Yomi with grace and humility.
Not likely.
Look on the bright side,
at least you'll get to see
Yusuke again like you wanted.
Too right! I bloody
miss the fella!
Aye! Make that a double.
I'll want to be seein'
him, too, I say.
[CHU]
She'll be apples, she will!
[HOKUSHIN gasps]
[YOUDA gasps]
[YOUDA]
Two hundred K?
[gasps]
[MUKURO]
Hiei!
I'm coming with you.
I want to see my competition
with my own eye.
All right, suit yourself.
Strange, I would've thought we'd
encounter a welcoming party.
[MUKURO scoffs]
He knows we're here.
And believe me, we'd know
if he didn't want us to be.
I present your tea, sir.
Uh... I guess you
do have good ears.
Mukuro's arrived, sir.
I am aware.
Keep your eyes on them.
[YOUDA]
Of course.
[laughs] Been so long
since I seen him, it has.
But he's not changed
one itty-bitty bit.
[CHU]
'Cept he's even stronger!
Bloke's built like
a brick shithouse!
[BOTH laughing]
[TOUYA]
That's all well and good,
but what will we do if Yomi
gives the order to attack?
[KURAMA]
I've been pondering that myself.
I did swear my allegiance...
...to Yomi.
And I would enjoy sparring
with Yusuke in his new state...
...but not to the death.
--[RINKU cries]
--[CHU] Ya don't hafta write out
the dramatic pauses, bludger!
[KURAMA]
To be honest, I'm torn.
Which is why I want to know
what you all are thinking.
If it comes to that, whose side
will you be on: Yomi or Yusuke?
[ALL]
Yusuke!
[RINKU]
Do you even have to ask?!
[SHISHIWAKAMARU]
Undecided.
[SUZUKI]
I mean, Yusuke.
[KURAMA]
Thank you.
[JIN]
No sweats, pal.
[YOMI]
So, why have you come to see me?
And please, be direct.
I have neither time
nor patience to waste
beating around the bush.
Well, Raizen is dead now...
And you know, as the
new king on the block,
I thought it'd only be fair
for me to tell you in person
exactly how I'm gonna
rip you off ya throne.
Oh?
[KURAMA]
That's far too direct.
He's going to get
himself killed.
[YOMI] All right, then in the
interest of full disclosure,
allow me to show you
how I plan to stop you.
[KURAMA] Yomi is powering
himself up to take Yusuke out.
[ALL]
We have to do something!
[HIEI]
Fool!
You're playing right
into the enemy's hands.
Heh.
That's cool, but first,
I got something for ya...
We'll call it a gift.
[KURAMA]
A gift?
He couldn't be naive
enough to give Yomi a...
[YOMI] ...peace offering.
No, he's smarter than that.
It's a trap.
How thoughtful of you! Would
you mind unwrapping it, too?
I'm afraid I can't see things
as well as I used to.
Sure.
Now, they might scatter a bit,
so I hope you don't mind.
But that's our entire
national treasure!
All our Rurimaru stones!
Do you have any idea how
rare and valuable those are?
[YOMI]
So, this is a sincere offering.
He'll be easier to
crush than I thought.
I thank you Mr. Urameshi,
for this most generous of gifts.
Ooh, I can tell this Rurimaru
stone is real by its touch.
But what is your true
purpose and offer?
[YOMI] There's something
carved in this stone.
It says "Mukuro."
And that one says "Kurama."
And "Touou."
"Hokushin."
"Hiei."
You engraved names in
all of these stones?
Yeah, well, I would've
just painted 'em on,
but I thought this way,
you could read 'em yourself.
[gasps]
[screams]
You desecrated the treasure!
How could you do such a thing?!
[YUSUKE] Look, I'm not a
particularly bright guy.
And just because
I'm Raizen's heir
doesn't mean I'm
qualified to replace him.
So, maybe it's time
we found another way of
crowning the big
cheese around here.
Each of these has
the name of someone
from Demon World on them.
We'll all face off in
a big tournament,
representing not
kingdoms, but ourselves.
[gasps]
And the one who
wins the tournament
will be the one to rule us all,
for a period of time, at least,
until the next tournament
when we all do it over again.
From what I understood
in social studies,
it's called "democracy," and
it's all the rage back home.
Except we'll cast our
votes with fists.
What do you say, big guy?
[YOMI] He would be willing
to surrender his own power?
He can't be serious.
Do you honestly
think that I or anyone else
will go along with this?!
[JIN]
Sign me up, so I say!
[laughs]
[YUSUKE]
What are you guys doin' here?
To see you, pal!
Jin! How ya doin' man?
--[CHU] Hey!
--[YUSUKE, JIN laugh]
--[CHU laughs]
--[YUSUKE] Chu! Are you sober?
[GROUP laughs]
I'm sorry, Yomi,
but from now on,
I represent only Kurama's side.
But if you don't go along
with this, I promise you...
None of us will hesitate to
take his side over yours.
Kurama... Not you...
[laughs] Yomi doesn't
know what hit him!
[MUKURO]
Hiei...
Spread the word.
From this point on, Mukuro
is just another apparition.
That sounds good to me.
[MUKURO]
Like the rest of the masses,
I'll be fighting for myself.
I accept Yusuke's terms.
[YOMI]
Damn you, Mukuro!
Fine...
I accept.
[NARRATOR] Less than a
day after Raizen's death,
word spread throughout
Demon World that his regime,
along with Mukuro's and
Yomi's, has been dismantled.
Control of the entire
land is now up for grabs
in a worldwide tournament.
[YOUDA] It is only a matter
of days now until he awakes.
[YOMI]
Mhm...
[YOUDA]
Your son, Lord Yomi...
Lord Shura.
I'll begin his intense training
regime as soon as he wakes.
Time is of the essence.
Check his energy
level again, Youda.
[YOUDA]
Yes.
It's up to 80,000
points now, sir,
and who knows how
high it will get
by the day of his emergence.
He's not just my son;
he's my ace.
Even if everyone in Demon World
competes in this tournament,
the final match will no doubt
come down to Mukuro and myself.
And that chaos-preaching tyrant
will be a tough opponent,
even for me.
However, if I can raise my son
up to my energy level in time,
then I'll be twice as
likely to defeat Mukuro,
and seize control of
the entire Demon World.
It seems Urameshi's plan may
turn out to be the best thing
that ever happened to me...
Right, Shura?
[YUSUKE]
Guys, lighten up, will you?
And stop looking at
me like that!
Raizen left me in charge,
and I did what I think is best
for every one of you out there!
[SEITEI] Nothing we can
say will change your mind...
But we're concerned
about your prospects...
For winning the tournament,
which is why the four of us
will fight on your behalf.
Have you guys not
heard a word I said?
This is going to be a battle
between individuals, not kings!
We are leveling
the playing field.
Do you honestly believe
that Yomi and Mukuro
have actually
abdicated their power?
[YUSUKE gasps]
[HOKUSHIN]
You can be certain that
they will be using every
advantage at their disposal.
That may be, but I'm
stickin' to my proposal.
And besides, I think Mukuro at
least is someone we can trust.
I mean, you were at
the conversation.
Sorry, but I will
never believe a word
that comes from that beast.
[MUKURO] It is truly a pleasure
to meet you, son of Raizen.
[MUKURO] Please place these
at Raizen's grave for me.
[MUKURO]
He was a great leader, like you.
But he died a fool.
In any case, we
shall try our best
to help you win this
tournament, Your Majesty.
And if that's what
we individuals want
then are we not complying with
your wishes for independence?
I don't want you to do this
just becase I want you to,
I want you to do what you want.
You know what I mean!
[KOKOU]
We're here!
[gasps]
It's an invading army!
--[footsteps]
--[GUARDS murmuring]
Just who the hell
or what are you?!
When we heard that
Raizen croaked,
we set out for this dump
as fast as we could
to pay our respects.
Hello, my name's Enki,
and this little firecracker's
my lovely wife, Kokou.
[HOKUSHIN]
And what exactly is the nature
of your relationship
to our late king?
Well, we used to be sparring
buddies back in the old days.
[gasps]
[ENKI] Sure we were strong,
but he was stronger.
I'll tell you,
if Mukuro and Yomi had
seen Raizen at his prime,
they would have
pissed their pants,
if you'll excuse my
colorful language!
That was until he went all ga-ga
for some cheap little whore
that he met up in Living World!
So, he comes back and dumps me
like I'm yesterday's garbage.
Got any clue how
insulting that is?!
Jeez! You smell like booze!
After he rejected me,
I didn't give a crap anymore,
so I married this lug.
But I don't care 'cause
I've been drinkin' ever
since and feel great!
[sighs]
Your loss, Raizen!
[ENKI]
Please...
Forgive my wife, she's
really not always like this.
[ENKI screams]
[ENKI]
Now be a good girl, sweetie.
[KOKOU]
You be a good girl!
[sobs]
Why?! Why have you
abandoned me twice now,
and this time for good?!
[sobs]
I loved you, Raizen!
You're the only man
I ever loved!
[sighs] And she promised
that she wasn't gonna cry...
You see, when Raizen
first told us
he was through eating
humans and fighting,
it went against
everything we stood for,
and we took it as an insult.
And so we left, and cut
off all ties with him.
[ENKI]
But after we parted,
we lost our passion
for fighting, too.
We've come to lead a
quiet and peaceful life.
I wish we'd have told him
that while he was still alive.
[ENKI]
It's funny.
We thought he'd lost his mind,
but maybe this was his
intention all along.
To change the way we lived,
through example.
[GROUP]
Hello!
This time I'm sure!
It's an invading army!
It certainly did take them
all long enough to get here.
An army of freaks!
Hope this is a social visit.
Do you know these guys?
Yeah, all of them used to
fight with Raizen as well.
So then, am I right to
say you're Raizen's son?
Something like that, why?
Oh, you know it's just that
you remind me so much of
him when he was younger.
[ENKI laughs]
[YUSUKE]
Hokushin...
[HOKUSHIN]
Yes?
I always thought Raizen
was just a bastard,
but I really didn't get
to know him at all.
There was more to him,
and now seen through their eyes,
I can't help but feel...
...proud... of my father.
I think, in a way, I can
finally call him that.
Right everyone, that's
enough grieving for one day,
don't you think? And besides...
I believe we all had another
reason for coming here today,
isn't that right?
[ENKI]
Ready?
Hey!
Raizen Junior!
[gasps]
Guess what, we're all gonna be
taking part in that tournament!
[gasps]
I'm warning you, though,
I'm not gonna go easy on you!
I don't care who you are,
I'll kick your ass!
And the same goes
for you, mister.
I'm not cutting you any slack!
I'd have it no other
way, my darling!
All's fair in love and war.
Let's make this tournament
so brutal and tough
that Raizen rolls over in
his grave in jealous rage,
what do you say?!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
Now, why don't we dust
off our rusty powers,
and see if we've still
got it like we used to?
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[ENKI]
And... go!
[ALL yelling]
[YUSUKE, HOKUSHIN gasp]
[YUSUKE yells]
[YUSUKE grunts]
[ALL yelling]
[YUSUKE gasps]
[ENKI yells]
Aww... Sweet! [laughs]
Now this... is getting good!
[MUKURO]
Quite impressive, isn't it?
A beaut! A real beaut!
Youda! What the
hell is going on?
A surge of power
from Raizen's region!
And it's a big one!
[YOUDA] The energy
level is off the charts!
[YOUDA yelps]
That's impossible!
Such displays.
Each one of their energy
levels, close to mine.
How could I have known?
The only Demons with such powers
have been in seclusion
for centuries.
Yet, I... feel invigorated.
[YOMI]
My warrior's spirit's returning.
But do I dare go into
this as an individual,
merely to prove myself?
[SOLDIER]
Lord Yomi!
What is it?
Quick! It's Lord Shura!
Is he hurt?
[SHURA laughing]
[YOMI]
My son,
you're experiencing the
same feelings I am.
[YOMI]
Youda.
Yes?
[YOMI] I'll no longer
need your services.
You're free to go.
[gasps]
You and I, we are now...
...considered as equals, Youda.
Does this mean that you'll be
playing by Mr. Urameshi's rules,
and fighting as an individual?
Yes, it does...
You may have just witnessed the
most foolish choice of my life.
[NARRATOR] Yusuke's unlikely
proposal has been embraced
by Yomi and Mukuro, preventing
a full-scale Demon war.
But the battle for control of
Demon World now begins.
Who will win the tournament
and attain complete power?
[CHU]
G'day mates!
Your ole pal, Chu, here.
And if you thought the
Dark Tournament was a blast,
wait'll you take a squizz
at Demon World's go at it!
It's so bloody fierce!
The first round will toss
49 gladiators together,
with only one codger
coming out on top,
while the others go home
to cry to their moms!
All your favorite fighters'll be
there, including yours truly!
Believe me, you're in for
one rip-snorter of a tourney
on the next Yu Yu Hakusho,
'cause the winner decides the
future of every bloke there is!