♪
[NARRATOR] Game Master,
Sniper, Doctor, Gourmet,
Sea Man, Gate Keeper,
and Black Angel.
These are the seven psychics
trying to forge a tunnel
between the Human
and Demon Worlds,
letting loose an
army of demons
strong enough to
annihilate Earth.
Yusuke has defeated
the crazed Doctor,
a human anxiously foretelling
the end of his own kind.
But somewhere in Mushiyori City,
six psychics remain.
Yusuke's team
must find them.
[YUSUKE] Well excuse me
if I'm not a college-boy
philosophy grad,
or some church dude talking
about a higher calling.
But to me, none of
this makes sense.
This Doc knew he'd die if he
opened that tunnel, he knew!
That's freaky...
I just figured if they
had a human on their side,
they weren't telling him
what he was getting into.
But he knew?
Um-hmm. The whole shebang,
he said we all deserved to go
'cause we were diseased
or something.
Sounds like
fanatic cult stuff.
Amen.
I don't get it.
If they're so bummed
about their own lives,
they should just take up
rock climbing without ropes.
Risk themselves, instead of
blaming it on innocent people.
Or at least only pick
on us tough guys. Jeez.
Emergency!!
What is it, Botan? They run
out of your hair dye?
There's no time for jokes.
The tunnel to Demon World
will be finished in a week!
What??
[YUSUKE]
But...
[BOTAN] No time for buts,
either. Just listen!
[KOENMA] Yes, Yusuke, listen.
That's Botan's natural color.
It doesn't make
sense to tease her.
What is this? What's she talking
about one week, Koenma?
You told us three weeks
just the other night!
That's the thing about
the information business...
Always subject to updates.
Look, Yusuke, we goofed.
We assumed the
tunnel's center point
was on the earth's surface.
It was only after Kurama's
team visited the site
that I ordered a depth analysis,
and found the center to be
five hundred and fifty
meters underground.
Here's an overhead view
of the distortion zone
we see on the surface.
Here's the actual zone
at the center point.
Deceptively larger.
I was being simplistic
when I said the distortion
takes the form of a circle,
it's really a sphere.
The circle or dome
we see on surface
is just a cross
section of its tip.
Urameshi, tell me
what's on the screen!
I can't see without my Spirit
Powers. Like what's he saying?
Spheres and stuff.
Geometry's next year!
Okay.
Oh, it's basic math to show
why we only have a week.
Why can't Keiko be the
one with the Spirit Gun?
He said five hundred meters
under the ground, right?
That's one crazy sewer.
[KOENMA] It's a cave system.
The closest entrance is in
a suburb of Mushiyori City.
A feeder cave with a
most appropriate name.
Go on!
[KOENMA]
Demon's Door.
Well we won't save the
world resting our asses.
[YUSUKE] Botan,
let's get the crew together.
Looks like we're
heading for Suburbia.
Will do.
[KUWABARA]
Bye guys!
Kuwabara, hold up!
[YUSUKE] Kurama's school
is this way, stupid.
Don't tell me your direction
has gone south, too.
[KUWABARA] Sorry, I can't
go with you guys today.
Got the runs or somethin'?
No, it's just, you know!
What the hell
does "you know" mean?
That time of the month for you?
You're being a pig!
This is why.
Floor tickets...
For Megallica's world tour!!
[KOMADA]
There you are, Kuwabara.
[MIYAMOTO] Come on,
let's be first in line!
[OKUBO] I'm getting a
T-shirt and a long-hair wig!
See you guys!
[YUSUKE]
You forgot something.
We're saving the planet!!
No pop bands!!
[KUWABARA] Pop band?!
You dare call
Megallica a pop band!!!
Wow.
Yeah, their fights are great,
it's really an art form.
Don't just stand there
and look impressed!
What if I told you I
had front row seats
to the Martial Arts
World Championship?
Would you turn
that down?
Some hero!
[KUWABARA]
It's a once-in-a lifetime shot.
I bought these
tickets a year ago,
and there's no way
I'll miss 'em.
Even if the end of the world
was tomorrow, I'd still go!
That just makes
it more important!
Whatever, groupie,
go head-bang.
Just don't expect me
to save your ass
when it's demon season.
Like I'd need
help from you!
I'm so sick of your
big-man crap!
Maybe I won't help you
tomorrow either,
let you see how
you need me!
[BOTH]
Fine!
And that's how the
human race ended.
[SENSUI] I've just
been to town, Itsuki...
It's filled with
demon insects.
It seems you're
expanding the tunnel
even faster than we expected.
It's hard to explain,
Mr. Sensui.
I feel most peculiar.
My powers seem immersed
in this rapid stream.
Like the tunnel has a life of
its own. Like it wants to grow.
[SENSUI] Then all we need is
someone to break that net.
[SENSUI] I'm sending
out our colleagues.
They're exploring the area
for a capable psychic.
They're also fighting Yusuke's
team any chance they get
because I have a suspicion our
two needs, are actually one.
[YUSUKE] Give me a break!
What do you mean he's missing?
[KAITOU] He didn't
come to school today.
Hiei, then Kuwabara,
and now Kurama.
You can't count on anybody!
I just need to do this alone!
[GENKAI]
Shut up.
Now that we know where
these psychics are hiding,
we can mount an attack.
But it must be
carefully planned.
[YANA] I've heard of
Demon's Door Cave.
It's like an urban legend.
It's said scorned
lovers go there to die,
which shows our
enemies like irony.
If we go unprepared,
it'll be suicide as well.
Hey, I don't need a lesson
from you too, rookie.
Stupid freckles.
Hold on, Yusuke.
Damn it!!!
[YUSUKE] Everyone just leave me
alone. I'm going to the arcade.
I don't know what's
gotten into him.
He shouldn't be going
out alone, should he?
Give him space.
If he's that dumb,
he deserves to die.
[GENKAI] But I suspect he's
worried about Kuwabara.
[BLUE OGRE] Please not Records!
Koenma will discipline
me if he finds out.
The other day he
disciplined me so hard
my hip popped out of socket,
and I couldn't fit
into my loincloth.
And looks are
important to us ogres,
especially when
courting the ladies,
and I haven't
gotten married yet.
My mother's
hounding me.
Do you know where
I could find a new job?
I need one, I think he likes
the new girl more than me.
He always calls
her by name!
Would you can it, George!
[KOENMA] Kurama.
Why are you here?
I've come to pose a question.
Oh, brother.
I believe you know
the true identity
of the mastermind
of this tunnel.
Am I right?
[KOENMA]
Don't be ridiculous.
If I knew who he was,
don't you think I would've told
you so you could stop him?
Perhaps not, if you
feared he would defeat us.
Your behavior has
been an erratic blend
of urgency
and silence.
I think you're
scrambling
because you don't
know how we can win.
That means you know
things we do not.
Like his identity, and his past.
[KOENMA] How dare you accuse me
with some groundless hunch!
But I'm right, am I not?
[Cheers]
April showers.
[SENSUI] Is this a
good time for you?
[SEA MAN] Yeah, probably.
Mister Sensui.
I won't be needing that.
I look forward to
great results, Sea Man.
[excited yells]
My life is complete!
We were so close he
could sweat on us!
Hey, let's hit the Karaoke
Bar to top things off!
I don't know.
Only if we sing the
Megallica hits
in the order they played!
[ALL] Yeah!
Did you guys see that girl
in the black Megallica shirt
who ran up on stage?
[MIYAMOTO] Yeah, she sure
seemed happy to be there!
[OKUBO] I bet working
security for those shows
is the best gig
in the world!
Nah, roadie's
the way to go!
[KUWABARA] Dummies!
I'd be in the band,
playing tambourine!
Hello?
[KUWABARA] Think about
it! It'd be awesome!
[KOMADA]
Help me!
[MIYAMOTO]
Komada?
[KUWABARA]
Hey, what's the hold up?
Our pants are soaked
through anyway.
There's no need to stop!
Kuwabara! Help! There's
somethin' comin' after me!
[MIYAMOTO]
Kuwabara, no!
I don't get it.
What was that??
Kuwabara, you're hurt!
And where's Komada?
That's enough.
Show yourself, freak.
[footstep in puddle]
[SEA MAN] I'm so glad the
weather man was right today.
My powers work
best in the rain.
I really hope I'm
having a nightmare.
[KUWABARA]
Komada!
Honestly, you should be
focusing on your own short life,
rather than worrying about his.
Say what?!
Let me introduce
myself to you.
Everybody should
at least know the name
of the person
who kills them.
You killing me?
That's a joke.
[SEA MAN] Why the
bluffs, Kuwabara?
I know all about
your lost powers.
Kiyoshi Mitarai...
Nick name: Sea Man.
One of the seven.
I got a bone to pick with you.
[Door opening]
[KEIKO] Shizuru.
Hey guys, you know
where my bro is?
At the rock concert,
so I thought.
Oh yeah, Kazuma did mention
something like that.
You look really
worried.
[SHIZURU] Me? No.
Just a bad vibe, that's all...
Maybe we should
escort him home.
Good idea.
Sit down...
You remember the trouble
we had with the Doctor.
Your friend's still
confined to a hospital bed.
Kuwabara made his
choice tonight.
We can't split
our group further.
But he's defenseless right now.
And Shizuru has a feeling!
We'll have to leave
this one to Yusuke.
He's grown up a lot
from the tournament,
and he's protective
of Kuwabara.
Unless he's an
absolute dope,
he didn't really
go to that arcade.
How well do you know him?
[video game sounds]
[ARCADE GAME]
Welcome to Goblin City.
Where your team of seven
heroes must clash iron
with the evil Goblin King,
and restore the
peace to the town.
[YUSUKE] Damn it! I'm setting
this game's records for sucky!
[SEA MAN]
Poor thing.
It doesn't seem
any of your friends
are going to save you tonight.
You were very foolish
to move without them.
I've been following you.
Waiting for the moment
you'd go out alone.
Something about you
drew my attention.
Maybe your naïveté.
What is that?
It can't be real.
Whatever it is, it's real
enough to have our friend!
I'm glad to know
you're interested.
Let me show you how
the monster's made.
[SEA MAN] My blood,
mixed with water.
The more blood,
the bigger the beast.
The more moisture,
the easier it spreads.
That's why I am Sea Man.
Master of the floods.
Listen, I've got brothers
and sisters to take care of.
[SEA MAN]
I know, Okubo.
But that honestly
doesn't matter.
They won't live past
the week, anyway.
Come on, Kuwabara.
I'd like to know
your opinion.
Which one of my monsters do you
like best? Little or big?
Because that is the one
I'm going to kill you with!
You're exactly like that
Doc Urameshi fought.
A self-righteous nut.
Don't you ever lump
me in with that freak!
I have reasons, good ones.
[SENSUI] Yes. It's what they've
taught you your entire life.
The cruelty of man.
Early on they excluded you
for some arbitrary cause.
And once marked, they all
eagerly joined in the ridicule,
circling like buzzards
over a lame calf.
[SENSUI]
No one ever helped you.
They all took part
in humanity's darkest
indulgence, torture.
[SEA MAN] Who are you?
How do you know all this?
[SENSUI] Come. Let me
show you the answer.
I just want it
all to stop.
I want it to stop.
But it never will,
that's what he showed me!
It's human nature to lie,
and bully, and hurt people.
You're protecting a fallen race.
That's why you must die.
I hear ya', but I'm
the one you're after.
You can let these
friends of mine go.
And I'll give you
the fight you want,
I accept your challenge.
You really don't get it.
I'm not here to compete.
I'm here to wipe out
every human being.
Not if I have
a say in it!
No! Stop!
You punk--haven't you
ever heard of a code??
That's called
honor kickin' butt.
Hit it all you like.
It always comes back.
What??
No...
No!!
All four of you combined
can't stop it...
I won't have any elitist
groups bullying me anymore!
I'll take you out
one at a time.
I'll make you all scream
until you see your nasty souls.
You're full of it,
sayin you got right cause
guys bullied you around,
but you're just like them now.
Don't you say that, no.
Don't you ever question
my motivations again!
You haven't lived
through my life.
Made into an outcast
at every turn...
I'm on the good guy's team!
Picking on the
weak is never good!
Ha! Then I'd say we have
a war of convictions.
What you call injustice,
I call getting even!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
There's no chance this way.
What's wrong with me?
Why can't I use my powers??
The psychics have
taken advantage
of the fracturing
team's poor decisions,
and Kuwabara's lost powers.
Will he be the
Sea Man's next victim?
[KUWABARA]
Don't count me out yet.
So I don't have my powers,
or understand why they
vanished in the first place.
And my best friends since way
back are drowning in a monster,
and no one's gonna rescue us.
But there are two
things I do have.
Guts like steel,
and honor on my side.
And I will find a way to win.
Cause somewhere inside me,
a new power is forming.
Oh, yeah!!
Move over, Urameshi!
I'm getting an upgrade!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪