[NARRATOR]
Control of Demon World
is divided among three rulers:
Raizen, Yomi and Mukuro.
From his deathbed, Raizen has
invited his descendant, Yusuke,
to return to Demon World
to train under him
and defeat his foes.
Deciding to go, the young
Spirit Detective said farewell
to the one he loves.
By my eighteenth birthday,
I'll get back here.
I'll find a way. I promise.
[KUWABARA] FOIL: First, Outside,
Inside. What's the "L" for?
[groans]
I know this...
It's not the
speed of light, is it?
[SHIZURU]
Kazu, are you studying?
Of course.
Here's your reward.
[KUWABARA]
Mmm, that looks great!
Thank y--
[yells]
What the heck was that for?!
It can be your
reward if and only if
you promise to
finish reading this book
on twentieth century
geopolitical shifts
by morning.
Tomorrow morning?!
But I'm doing my math!
You'll read this in addition
to doing your math work
because you know
the prep school
that you want to get into
is looking for only
well-rounded students,
and you are already far
behind the other applicants.
[KUWABARA] Fine. I'll do it.
I promise. Happy?
I'm ecstatic.
[SHIZURU]
Cover to cover.
She's such a nag!
I guess she does know me,
though. Gotta hand it to her.
She knows the best way to get
to me is through my stomach.
I guess she forgot
to use the sugar.
[purring noise]
Eikichi!
Come here, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Come out and play.
Here, kitty!
[meows]
[KUWABARA]
Oh! Botan!
I was just looking
for my contact, that's all.
That'll have to wait,
I'm afraid.
You've been summoned to
Master Genkai's compound ASAP.
[KUWABARA]
Why?
Dunno.
What am I saying?
I can't go out--I'm gonna be
up studying all night as it is.
Some other time.
[BOTAN]
All right...
I'll tell Yukina you
were too busy to see her.
[KUWABARA gasps]
Yukina's gonna be there?!
Why didn't you say so?!
But you're too busy
to come tonight, right?
How dare you
put schoolwork ahead
of the girl I love
more than anything?!
Don't you know the best
way to get me to do anything
is through my heart,
for I am the warrior of love!
Driver, take me to Genkai's
place now, and step on it!
We're not going anywhere
'til you say "please."
Kazuma, I forgot
the sugar for your...
[gasps]
Botan?!
We'd better get
a move on, Botan.
Away we go!
[SHIZURU] Hey!
Get your asses back here!
Shizuru! Please forgive me!
[KUWABARA] What do you mean
you're going back there?!
When we were there,
you said you wanted to go home,
and now that you're here,
you wanna go back--
Maybe you're just a spoiled brat
who can't be happy anywhere!
I've decided...
Despite your kind and heartfelt
tribute, I'm going back.
So what're you gonna do there?
You gonna turn into one of them
and then come back
and attack us? Huh?
I don't know.
You don't know?
[gasp]
[chuckles]
I think I'll miss
your weak-ass punches
most of all, Kuwabara,
so I guess I'd better savor
this last one while I can.
[YUSUKE]
Anyway...
I don't know
what will happen to me
when I get there,
or what to expect.
That's why I'm going--
To find out more about myself
and what I'm capable of.
What I do know
is that I'm no good
to you or anybody else
as long as I can't even
keep control of my own body
or its actions--you get that?
And what about
your duty to protect?
In all your selfish plans,
you've forgotten that you're
still the Spirit Detective.
[KOENMA]
Not anymore, he's not.
[KUWABARA gasps]
[KOENMA] Spirit World has given
him a dishonorable discharge,
relieving him of his
duties as a Spirit Detective.
Still, there's
the pesky little matter
of the death warrant my
father placed on his head.
[gasps]
There's a death warrant?
[YUSUKE] Yeah, I didn't wanna
make a big deal out of it.
And I'm not using it
as an excuse,
but the fact that every second
I spend here brings me closer
to assassination does make
Demon World pretty appealing.
[GENKAI] Do you remember
when you first came to me?
Before your Awareness
had fully developed,
you had such difficulty
fighting in the darkness.
Since that time, I've guided
you through the shadows,
tried to shed light
on what you could be.
But now Yusuke
has gone beyond us all.
And as he's discovered,
sometimes the more you see,
the less clear things become.
Yusuke thought he knew it all.
He thought he was just
some dime-a-dozen punk.
But the more he
learns about himself,
the more confused he gets.
I think we owe it to him
to allow him the chance
to fumble around in the
darkness for answers,
because the truth of it is--
We can't stop his Demon blood
from causing him to do wrong.
We just have to have faith.
Is that too much
to ask, Kuwabara?
And how do you
propose gettin' back
to your precious homeland?
In case you've forgotten,
the border tunnel between
Living World and Demon World
has been sealed back up!
Then we'll just have to
go unseal it again, won't we?
Wha--What are you talking about?
[KUWABARA]
The Spirit Defense Force?
Well, Mr. Urameshi,
are you ready to go?
Oh yeah... Anytime you are.
You've gotta be kidding me!
You freaks wouldn't really
open the hole to Demon World!
[KOENMA chuckling]
Not only would they do it,
they volunteered
for this mission.
Could you guys
be any stupider?!
What, just 'cause you tools
are too weak to kill him,
you're gonna give him a
free ticket to Demon World
so he's out of your hair?
I'm not going to deny that.
Faced with the
possibility of a Mazoku
on the loose,
the Great King Yama
in his infinite wisdom
granted Yusuke fair passage,
thus containing him
and preserving peace in both
the Spirit and Living Worlds.
This is all to
preserve the peace
of the Living World?
And what about the next time
somebody like Toguro or Sensui
decides to pass
through there, huh?
You just expect me, Kurama and
Hiei to fight them off alone
with our bare hands?
That won't happen.
Kuwabara, the intricacies
of Demon World politics
are complicated,
and their impact can be
quite far-reaching.
What's that got to do with this?
[rustling]
Hi, Hiei.
I was personally
invited to return
to Demon World as well.
Don't tell me...
You're gonna fight
on behalf of
Urameshi's dear
Demon daddy, too?
Actually it's the opposite.
The invitation was from
one of Raizen's major enemies...
Mukuro.
[KUWABARA] You really
aren't gonna accept that,
are you, Hiei?
[HIEI]
In fact, I am.
I belong in Demon World,
not this one.
Even if that means going up
against your friend Urameshi
when you're there?
If that is our destiny,
then so be it.
After all, I always
have wanted a rematch.
Maybe my destiny, too.
[KUWABARA]
Kurama, too?
[KURAMA] My presence in Demon
World has also been requested.
And at the behest
of the third leader...
Lord Yomi.
An old acquaintance.
I feel... like the
ugly one at the dance.
[KURAMA] I'll be leaving
for Demon World myself,
though probably some time
after Yusuke and Hiei do.
I don't believe
what I'm hearing!
Have you all gone
totally bonkers?!
I thought we had a good thing
going! I thought we had a team!
We were gonna fight
the good fight together,
but it turns out
you'll fight any fight
even if it's fighting
against each other!
I consider you my friends,
but you're no
friends of mine!
Somehow I think I'll
manage to live with that.
I'm gonna kill you,
you little punk!
[GENKAI]
Stop!
We have no reason to believe
they're abandoning
the good fight.
Get off it, old lady,
they're going to Demon World!
Evil's all they do!
Kazuma, just because
someone is born a Demon
does not necessarily
make them evil...
Or have you forgotten
that I, too, am of Demon World?
[KUWABARA]
Uh... but I didn't...
Listen, pal...
Whaddaya want with me,
you traitor?
Study hard so you can
get into that prep school.
--[KUWABARA gasps]
--[YUSUKE] Shh!
How... did you
ever hear about that?
Kayko told me about it.
Now don't let those brainiacs
turn you into a nerd,
but do us all proud and go on
to become a doctor
or lawyer or something.
I'll be back
in three years, okay?
And the first
thing I'm gonna do
is make sure you
got into that school,
and you're on
your way to college.
[laughs]
Three years exactly?
All right, I'll hold up
my side of the deal,
but here's one for you.
If you gotta go,
don't come back
until you're the
king of all the Demons.
Oh, and hey,
while you're there,
could you track down
Yukina's long lost brother?
[YUSUKE] Um, uh, yeah, if he's
even there at the same time.
[YUSUKE] I'll bet even his
third eye is glaring at me!
Why does everyone
always get all weird and nervous
when I bring up
Yukina's brother?
[laughs nervously]
Shizuru.
So Yusuke's really
going to just keep on flying
in the face of danger?
Honey, if Yusuke
ever weren't in danger,
he'd up and die of boredom.
[SHUNJUN]
Mr. Urameshi.
The time has now
arrived for your departure.
All right, soldiers!
Double time!
Let's go.
Does anyone else
think it's kind of ironic
that someone as strong as Sensui
had to go through
all that trouble
to open up a hole
to Demon World,
but these little weak
security guards can do it
with barely a
snap of their fingers?
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi.
Forget what I said before.
We may have chosen to
follow different paths,
but you and I
will always be...
Kuwabara...
[KUWABARA] I'm sorry. I just
got some dirt stuck in my...
...contact lens, that's all.
You don't wear contacts.
He doesn't?
The portal is ready now, sir.
[SHUNJUN]
Good job.
All right, Mr. Urameshi.
[YUSUKE]
Right. I guess... that's my cue.
Well, Kurama, Hiei...
See you on the flip side.
[PUU squawks]
[SHUNJUN] Not that you'd
ever take my advice,
but for what it's worth,
don't ever come back here.
Ha!
You're right,
I wouldn't take your advice,
but if I do come back,
I'll get here on my own,
so shut the door behind me.
Yes sir.
Oh, Yusuke...
You aren't really going
to leave us, are you?
[YUSUKE]
I'm afraid so.
Catch ya later, guys.
[yelling]
Yusuke!
[SHUNJUN]
There goes one brave fool.
I may hate what he
stands for, but I respect him.
It's funny...
We're told he's supposed
to be this horrible monster,
but from here,
he looks more like a hero.
Well... you heard the man!
Seal her up, boys!
[BOTAN]
Poor Yusuke.
[HOKUSHIN] We had planned
to escort you here ourselves
in a week.
You'll learn I do
things on my own schedule--
When and where I want.
Yet another
prime example of how
you are truly your father's son.
Now please do come with us.
King Raizen is
awaiting your arrival.
The latest hush-word
at the office
is that the Special Defense
Force let Yusuke go--
And not only that,
they actually opened the gateway
to Demon World for him!
But that can't be true,
can it, sir?
They're doing
much more than that.
[BLUE OGRE]
No!
The SDF is going
to escort Hiei and Kurama
to the other side, too.
[BLUE OGRE]
Really?
It's my father's way
of responding to requests
from Demon World.
What kind of requests
do you mean, sir?
[KOENMA]
He received messages
from the three kings
of Demon World,
all on the same day,
each seeking an extradition.
Raizen wanted Yusuke.
Yomi wanted Kurama.
And Mukuro wanted Hiei.
Individually,
they made these requests,
and individually offered
my father the same proposal.
They each suggested it would
be safer for Living World
to have these powerful and
potentially dangerous Demons
quarantined forever
in Demon World.
And my father agreed to that.
[KOENMA] The Mighty King
of the Spirit World
bended to their whims
and made a pact with
the Lords of Demon World.
You can't ever tell
anyone about this, Ogre,
do you understand?
[BLUE OGRE] But, sir, I'm sure
that the Great King Yama
must have had a much better
reason to agree to such a thing.
I can only hope so.
Uh, guys, how much
further do you think
we have to run
'til we get there,
'cause I mean it feels like
we've been sprinting for hours.
[HOKUSHIN]
Not too much farther.
If we keep running,
we should arrive in four days.
Four days?!
We gotta keep running
for four more days?!
I didn't know that
would be a problem for you,
but if you need a rest
we'd be happy to stop.
Ha! Me?
I was born on a treadmill!
[HOKUSHIN]
In that case, let's go faster.
Here we are, Mr. Urameshi.
That's incredible.
We ran as fast
as we possibly could,
and yet despite our efforts
to leave you behind...
You not only kept up with us,
but you did not break a sweat.
You should take some of
that quickness from your feet
and stick it to your brain
and then maybe you'd learn...
I'm not the one to
turn down challenges.
[distant rumbling]
What's that rumbling sound?
A thunderstorm?
[HOKUSHIN] That's the sound of
King Raizen's empty stomach.
Ever since he
stopped eating humans,
his belly growls like
that at every mealtime.
We use it as a clock
to mark the passing of time.
There...
...in that tower,
our King is waiting for you.
[HOKUSHIN] From this point,
you are on your own.
[YUSUKE]
Knock, knock.
[RAIZEN]
Welcome, my son.
What's the matter?
[chuckling]
You too big and cool to
give your old man a hug?
[YUSUKE]
You're not my dad!
Now tell me...
Why did you
have to get involved?
When I was fighting Sensui,
what did you do?
Tell me or I'm gonna
kick your ass!
[choked yelling]
[RAIZEN chuckling]
[RAIZEN]
That's why I did it.
For your own good,
you ungrateful bastard.
That human would've killed you.
You may have
inherited my genes,
but you haven't the slightest
idea what do with them.
Shame to waste them
on a weakling like you!
[YUSUKE yells]
I'll waste you!
[crashing noise]
[HOKUSHIN]
Well that sounds about right
for a father-son reunion.
[YUSUKE yelling]
[RAIZEN]
Had enough, boy?
See how your feeble skills
pale in comparison to mine,
or was my lesson
too dense for you?
The only thing I see is
an over-confident dead man.
[RAIZEN]
I'll make you a deal.
If you can move me
from my throne,
I'll more than gladly give it
to you, son, along with my life.
[YUSUKE]
Keep your throne.
Ha! Your life is
good enough for me!
[YUSUKE yelling]
Well...
Not sittin' so pretty now.
[RAIZEN] You hear,
but you don't listen, child.
You moved the throne, not me.
A tedious
technicality to be sure,
but we are men of honor.
Don't you worry, though.
We'll get your prize yet.
As long as my body continues
to shrink at this pace,
I'll no doubt be dead
within the span of a year.
Right...
The low-human diet's
working wonders for you.
As for the
matter of my throne...
you'll have to get much stronger
if you're to
fend off my enemies.
[NARRATOR]
For the first time,
Yusuke has met face to face
with his ancestral father.
But as Raizen attempts
to make Yusuke stronger...
the other two Demon lords
make their own preparations.
[HIEI] At last I return to the
world where I belong, my home.
There's just one thing
that I didn't miss
about the land of apparitions:
being haunted by
ghosts from my past.
And unlike in the
death-defying battles
I've become accustomed to,
there's no escape in sight.
The memories assault my senses
when I'm at my most vulnerable.
So if you're feeling
particularly sadistic,
then by all means, please join
in my personal nightmare
on the next Yu Yu Hakusho.