♪
[NARRATOR]
Fighting his second consecutive
match of the semifinals,
Hiei faces Kuro Momotaro,
a mediocre fighter with
a devastating weapon.
By exposing himself
to Hiei's attacks,
memorizing the pain,
then consuming one
of his Steaming Spheres,
Kuro Momotaro
develops Beast Armor
that is invincible
to Hiei's attacks.
With Hiei too drained
to use the Dragon
of the Darkness Flame,
is there any way
he can survive?
[Kuro wails]
If you thought my Armor
of the Ape was badass...
Wait'll you see my second armor:
The Armor of the Phoenix!
Kuro has
morphed once again.
But I think the
burning question is:
Was there anything
wrong with his original,
fairly hot muscular body?
Man, here we
go again!
If Kuro keeps this
up Hiei's finished!!
We shall see.
Colorful get-up
you've got there,
but it doesn't look so tough.
Wanna see what it can do?
[Kuro laughs insanely]
Poor.
[KURO THINKS] You're trying to
confuse me, it's not working.
I can see that
you are in fact...
Right here!
[HIEI]
Left yourself open.
How about Double Fists
of the Mortal Flame!
What?
[KURO]
Gotcha!
[HIEI THINKS] My Mortal Flame
truly is useless now!
You convinced yet?
There's nothing
you can do to beat me.
You might as well
stay on the ground
and think of a
nice way to beg.
Never! You'll have to rip
my limbs off to keep me down!
Shouldn't give him any
more suggestions, Hiei.
Yeah, that's
a good point.
It appears Hiei is
simply unable to compete
with the strength and power
of the new and improved Kuro!
Amputation seems
to be guaranteed!!
No! This can't be!
Ogre! You know about these
Steaming Sphere thingies!
Isn't there a
way to stop 'em?
So now you care!
I don't know!
Those things are
pretty much unstoppable
from what I've heard.
You idiot! Why
didn't you say so?!
[ONJI] This
match is ours.
Now Kuro is
immune to both
Hiei's sword and his
Fists of the Mortal Flame.
Hiei is far too weak now
to deal with the dragon flame,
and he knows it.
There is simply nothing
left for him to do.
It still bothers
me, though.
No fighter should
ever have to use
more than one Steaming
Sphere on one opponent.
Yes, this Hiei character must
be a pretty decent fighter
to have scared Kuro into
using two in one fight.
[ONJI]
I'd say more than decent.
Make no mistake--this is
still Kuro's match to lose.
I have faith in those weapons.
But I'd feel much better
if he'd stop showing off
and take care of his business.
[KURO] Too bad you can't
call up that little Dragon.
I'd like to show the
world I could beat you
even with a level
playing field.
But then again, it might
just be fun to go all the way.
Prepare yourself for
the next Kuro Momotaro.
I'll take great
pleasure in killing you.
First he was an ape,
and then a phoenix.
What will Kuro
transform into now--
could it possibly
be a purple hippopotamus!
Poor Puu. I hate
to see you like this.
It may have been best
to keep him in the room.
[KEIKO] He isn't just
nervous, Botan.
There's something
really wrong with him.
We need to get to the fights
and see Yusuke
as soon as possible.
[Yusuke screaming in agony]
[GENKAI THINKS]
Oh Yusuke, I warned you.
[GENKAI] The agony of this
absorption is beyond words.
It could go on
for hours or days.
If your body cannot handle it
you will be eaten
away from the inside out.
And the only thing you will
pray for is a quicker death.
[GENKAI] It's too much, your
body cannot take any more.
[YUSUKE] Give that
back to me, you old bitch!
You're not my
freakin' mother!
[GENKAI THINKS] I made the first
mistake by testing you too soon.
You made the second by
not letting me take it back.
Sorry Yusuke. There's
nothing more I can do.
[Kuro laughs wickedly
as he transforms]
[KURO] Now I'm protected with
the Third Beast Armor.
The Armor of the Wolf!
I'm a hell of a
lot stronger than before!
And as you can see I've got a
few sharp new toys on my hand
that I'd love to
share with you--
if you're in
the mood to play.
I promise I won't
miss your flesh again.
Just needed a moment
to get used to this body.
I've never known Hiei to
back away from a challenger.
Well, he does have
a lot of teeth!
What the hell.
Does that mean the great
Hiei is ready to quit?
No you incompetent, but I will
give you one last chance to.
That's very
sporting of you--
I think I'll pass however.
Your memory isn't like mine,
so I'll give you a hint.
If your sword didn't work on
my first Beast Armor,
it sure won't work
on the third.
I know, I hate
to use this attack.
I find it totally devoid
of any taste or artistry.
Well that's
hard to believe.
There's actually a move
that's too barbaric for Hiei!
Then it's probably
going to be very messy.
Ha! Don't hold back on me
because something's offensive.
I'm no snob. I was planning
on a vulgar move myself!
Onji.
No! It couldn't be!
I'm confused.
[HIEI] Sword of
the Darkness Flame!
What's goin' on??
Now I understand.
Hiei did summon
the Darkness Flame
from the pits
of Spirit World.
[KUWABARA] I thought you
said that was impossible
'cause he'd be swallowed!
[KURAMA] That's why he
didn't use his arm.
Hiei transferred his
energy into his sword
to lure the Darkness Flame,
containing it
apart from his body.
It wasn't as strong, but--
Hiei's weapon became
powerful enough
to pierce the Beast Armor.
Kuro was dead even before
his teeth sank in. Ingenious.
I don't know about
this genius business.
I mean it isn't
all that different
from what I do
with my Spirit Sword
and nobody
calls that genius.
Hey, wait a second!
Were you saying back there
that that my Spirit Sword
didn't have any
taste or artistry?
Ha, of course I did.
Okay, that's it!!
Since all pieces
of Kuro Momotaro
have stayed down for
more than ten seconds,
the winner of the match is Hiei!
[Angry crowd yelling]
I'm sorry folks, but
the rules are the rules.
If it makes you feel any better,
Hiei looks like he
hurt himself pretty bad.
[SHISHIWAKAMARU THINKS] Perhaps
that pathetic beast
was an asset to
our team after all.
[KEIKO] Um, Botan, are you sure
you know where you're going?
It feels like we've
been walking for hours.
[YUKINA] What if we don't make
it to the stadium in time?
Then we'll unfortunately miss a
few more pulse-pounding seconds
of people cramming their
fists into one another,
and then I might just have
to stick my head in an oven.
Don't worry, we'll
be there in a jiff!
This way, everyone!
We just went that way, Botan.
Do you think that's
the reason why
we passed by the
same rock formation
three times on
the way over here?
Honestly Botan, this short cut
isn't exactly turning out
to be what I
would call short.
I know exactly
where we're going.
We just have to keep walking in
the direction that I'm pointing!
Oh! You really
have no idea, do you?
If we head back to the
hotel and go the normal way,
we might make it by sundown.
That's right!
We just need to see this
as a learning experience.
[Yusuke screaming in agony]
I refuse, I won't give up!
Come on, roll the dice again.
I have an urge for three in row.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Don't roll
my name yet. I wanna go last.
The team leader
always goes last.
I am the team leader
and I wanna go last.
[HIEI THINKS] Let it be me.
[KURAMA THINKS]
Please, fall on mine.
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Don't let it be me!
Yes.
Yes!
Damn!
[JURI] After rolling the dice,
both fighters are in place
for the third match
of the semi-finals!
Now fighting for
Team Urameshi, Kurama!
And for Team Uraotogi,
Ura Urashima!
It's nice to see that fate is
cooperating with us today, Onji.
I admit, everything
is falling into place
more or less as we
hoped that it would.
Those first two accomplished
exactly what was intended.
It's a pity we
couldn't tell them
they were only here
to drain Hiei's energy.
And now the dice
have chosen Ura Urashima,
the one best suited
for killing Kurama.
He'll finally put
our team on the board.
By the authority of
the Tournament Committee,
let the third match begin!
Start your fight!
[KOTO] It looks like this match
is going to be a duel
of lashing weapons,
with Ura Urashima
twirling his fishing line
and Kurama wielding
his trademark Rose Whip.
This one's gonna
be all about skill!
Wow! This is
an incredible display
of equally matched talents,
and while there's no
blood to speak of yet,
those sparks keep me hopeful!
Whoa, this is a fight!
Kurama needs to
stop fooling around
and start
fighting for real.
What? He's whip-swingin'
like a maniac!
Have you
learned anything?
It's Kurama's obnoxious habit.
He never creates
his own strategy
until after he fully
understands his opponent's.
[KURAMA THINKS] Peculiar.
Ura Urashima doesn't
even seem to be trying.
[URA THINKS] Kurama. Keep
fighting as you listen to me.
I have a favor to ask.
[KURAMA THINKS]
Telepathic communication.
I don't believe that's
legal in the ring.
[URA] I'm begging you--
please kill me!
[URA] Don't stop fighting
or they'll get suspicious.
[KURAMA] Why?
[URA] When I joined this team,
I had no idea what
I was getting into.
I needed money to support
my sick grandmother,
and Shishi Wakamaru
promised me riches.
At first it was just stealing,
which I knew was wrong but--
then things got worse.
They convinced me to do
many things I'm not proud of.
Though I have no one to blame
except my own weak disposition.
But I can't go on.
For the first time in my life
I'm doing the right thing.
[KURAMA] Suicide
is not the answer.
There is neither honor
nor redemption in that.
[URA] You don't
understand, Kurama!
If I don't kill you,
they're going to
hurt my poor grandmother.
But this guilt I feel
is too much for me to bear.
As I watched my
teammates fall today,
I realized that
being killed in battle
is the only way out.
Please. Take
pity on a lost soul.
[KURAMA] I'll help you,
but not by death.
This world has enough of that.
You can keep your life
as long as you change
the way you live it.
It's never too late.
Believe me.
As for your
grandmother's well being,
we can fake your death
I can sting you
with my Rose Whip
in a manner that will
knock you out temporarily.
[URA] You are indeed
a good man, Kurama.
Here we go!
Yes.
What?
Kurama!
And he's down!
I studied your fighting
and found your only
weakness is your kindness.
In that regard
I'd suggest you
change the way--
The way you
live your life.
[URA] But it's too late now.
How did you put up with
this goody-two-
shoes crap?
I had to choke back
some major chunks
while I was pretending
to be an upstanding citizen,
but does it feel
good to be bad again!
You're gonna die
just like Grandma!
[URA] Come on Kurama,
give me some credit here!
You didn't think I was
really trying to hit you
with those
attacks, did you?
Hook, line, and sinker.
And you're the stupid fish.
This was not part
of my job description!
Isn't there anybody who can
break me out of this thing?
I am not supposed to be in here!
[URA] And before
you get any ideas,
know that my force field won't
be shredded nearly as easily
as that
enchantress, Ruka's.
In fact it's impossible to
break out from the inside,
so get comfortable.
And let me introduce
you to the Idunn Box.
Anybody other than the
possessor who breathes its air
will quickly return
to their younger age.
Back to those awkward
adolescent years,
the terrible twos,
or even infancy!
Once infected,
you'll be so tiny
and inexperienced,
it'll be like
taking candy from a...
Oh well, there's not point
in cliche expressions.
You'll see soon
enough what I mean.
[URA] You can't hold
your breath forever!
[Ura laughs]
Why isn't that stuff coming
any closer--is it scared?!
Maybe you don't understand
the concept of force field.
Poopy, how do they
expect us to watch
with that smoke everywhere?
And why is it, the less I
see, the more I want it!
No clue, sir.
Way to go, Ura,
I really did it!
I can feel his Spirit
Energy getting weaker!
[KURAMA'S MOM] You're gonna
be late for school, Suichi.
[KURAMA] I love you, Mother.
[KURAMA'S MOM] Today is the
most joyful day of my life.
I'll call him, Suichi.
You know, maybe I have
gone a bit too far this time.
Hold on, his Spirit
Energy completely vanished.
That's not supposed to happen.
What the...?
[KUWABARA]
Do you feel that too?
[crowd in chaos]
Where in the world did
this power surge come from?
Could've sworn I felt
his power weakening
as he regressed
all the way back.
[YOKO KURAMA] I think perhaps
I've regressed further
than you intended.
And just as I had come to
accept my human captivity.
'Yoko has
returned, they cry.
Did you say Yoko?
Yoko the Spirit Fox?
Yoko The legendary
bandit Yoko??
What'd you do with Kurama?
I like him a lot better!
[YOKO KURAMA]
Oh, he's here... He's me.
Only now you've brought me out
in full. Thank you for that.
[NARRATOR] After fifteen years
in his borrowed human form,
the demon Yoko
Kurama has returned.
What could this mean
for Team Urameshi?
[KOENMA]
Yo. Koenma here!
You'd think VIP box seats
would entitle me to a
sweet view of the action,
but I can't see a thing!
There's obviously a lot of
excitement brewing down there,
now that Kurama has
transformed into Yoko,
the powerful and
coldhearted Spirit Fox.
It's just not fair
that I manage the team
and I can't see diddly
while you get a great view,
what'd you ever do?
Sit on your butt and
turn the television on?
Anyway, this next
Yu Yu Hakusho
is clearly gonna
be a groundbreaker,
so don't miss it.
♪