[NARRATOR]
After walking away the survivor
from a life or death
battle with Sensui,
Yusuke returned to
Living World only
to find the day-to-day grind
to be much more unfulfilling
than he expected.
Following Genkai's advice,
Yusuke went to visit Kuroko,
the first Spirit Detective.
Here, Kuroko displayed her knack
at savoring the
routines of daily life.
And as Yusuke was beginning
to learn a few things,
three strange visitors appeared.
[HOKUSHIN] We have come here
on a mandate from Demon World.
I have come to tell
you your destiny,
and take you to the place
where you actually belong.
The place where I belong?
So you guys came here
from Demon World?
That's true.
[YUSUKE]
Oh, I get it.
They must be kickin' out
all the rejects, right?
No.
Don't be rude, Touou.
See, you come in here,
saying you're from Demon World,
but you got the spiritual
presence of piece of gum.
How can I blame
your lack of trust,
having never set eyes on us?
According to the standards
set forth in Demon World,
These two behind me, Seitei
and Touou, are both A-class.
And I, Hokushin, am what
would be considered S-class.
You are an S-class?
[HOKUSHIN]
I am.
Okay, well, I must be
the idiot here
because I had it in my head
that the tunnel between
Demon World and
Living World had been
sealed off for good.
[YUSUKE]
Although...
...I shouldn't be surprised
when the story changes anymore.
Now, S and A class spirits
can enter Living World?
No, that's not quite
what's happening, Yusuke.
[HOKUSHIN]
In fact,
we came here without using
the dimensional distortion.
We are here by a much
easier and discreet way.
And that is?
[KUROKO] I don't
mean to be rude,
But there's more than
one person in the room.
Could you back it up a
step and explain for us?
Well, it's just that it's
kind of a long story
and I don't want to bore you.
I'm hardly bored.
And since I did bother to
ask you to explain, maybe
--Right.
--you'd be polite and do it.
In my day, I never
heard anything
about a tunnel between
worlds and S-class ghosts.
It's been more than
ten years since
I retired from your
position, Yusuke.
I think too many things
have changed since then.
[laughs] Right.
Back to business.
Now tell me who you are
or I start knockin' heads.
[HOKUSHIN] It's actually
quite simple, Yusuke.
A time ago, fear grew of the
consequences if the S and
A class spirits were allowed
through to the Living World.
Therefore, the Kekkai
barrier was erected,
allowing only Demons lower
than D-class to pass through.
All we had to do to get here
was alter our power to a
level lower than D-class.
[YUSUKE gasps]
[gasps] What the hell is that?
This is an organic device
that all but disables
our demonic power.
It must be worn until our
return to Demon World.
There are other ways to
enter the Living World,
but the rules forbid us.
This device, however, has no
rules written against it.
This is what we must endure in
order to visit the Living World.
We have these placed on us,
but, like all things,
they are only temporary.
So, you put a gross
thing on you to get here.
Now, tell me what
this has to do with me.
There is someone
residing in Demon World
who has requested to have an
audience with you, Yusuke.
[SEITEI]
Hm.
[HOKUSHIN] Of course, I am
speaking of your ancestor.
You're saying,
He sent you here to escort
me back to Demon World,
is that more like it?
Yes, it is.
[YUSUKE] Like they say,
"The fool hunts for misfortune."
I'd love to get my fingers
around his throat!
So the old bastard
is still alive, huh?
Yes, of course he is.
[YUSUKE] He's still got
some power left in him?
[HOKUSHIN]
Yes, Very much.
Fine! Let's go, now!
I'm gonna follow up on my
"fingers around
his throat" idea.
You needn't hurry. Take the
time to hear our words first.
We limit our time in and
out of this place because
we abide strictly by the
rules of Demon World.
And to these rules,
we make no exception.
If you do return
with us, Yusuke,
it is then that you
will become one of us.
[YUSUKE]
I'm not following you.
To see your ancestor,
to return with us,
you must become
as one of us.
No one we bring back
to the Demon World
can be an outsider.
All these rules...
I didn't know Demons
thought so logically.
These are the written
rules of our territory.
And our territory
is no different
from the other two that
exist in Demon World.
So there are three of 'em?
You believe that there is no
order to be had in Demon World.
This is quite true,
but for Demon World, the chaos
that reigned was the best law
to be laid, because
it put everything
into its natural place.
But recently the times... they
have been changing drastically.
[HOKUSHIN] The struggle
between three Demons
has been shaking our
world to it's foundation.
Just three?
That should be over in no time.
Those are true words.
It should've ended.
The problem exists in that these
three battling Demons are the
three kings with the ruling
power over all of Demon World.
Their hatred for each
other runs very deep,
for several reasons.
But the one issue that brought
about this falling out
is the issue central to
all living things, food.
All three of these Demons
find the satisfaction to
their hunger in human beings.
[HOKUSHIN] One day, one of
these Demon kings spoke...
[RAIZEN] I think we should stop
all this feeding on humans.
[HOKUSHIN] But one of the other
kings objected immediately...
[GHOST B] I can't stand to
have anything but human.
And you won't believe it,
but I've already taken steps
to curb my appetite of them.
[HOKUSHIN]
But the third one said,
without a thought
to the contrary...
[GHOST C] We should
eat as many as we want.
They multiply like they're
fighting extinction as it is.
[HOKUSHIN]
It was always this way.
Three Demons in constant
disagreement with one another.
And considering that each
kings' strength was comparable,
the balance among the
three was barely stable.
If two of the Demons
were to fight
and only one emerged alive,
the third would be waiting
in the wings for the single,
unguarded moment.
The moment of victory.
Therefore, they continue
to push in a stand off
that has lasted, at this point,
for over five hundred years.
Five hundred years?!
How have they not gone crazy?
Because these three
Demons share the ability
to ground their emotions
in caution and patience.
Recently, the balance of
power has been shifting.
The spirit who had
the dissenting opinion
about feeding on humans
is on the brink of death.
That spirit is the
king of our territory,
the master of war,
Toushin Raizen.
This is your ancestor, Yusuke.
His illness is caused
by severe malnutrition.
Our king hasn't eaten anything
for nearly a thousand years.
He continues to reject the food
no matter who tries
to get him to eat.
We do not understand why he
stopped consuming humans,
knowing it would risk his life.
[SEITEI]
Mm.
[HOKUSHIN]
However,
if all of this turmoil
is our King's decision,
we shall obey his every order
to the letter and to the end.
Great. So what do you
want me to do about it?!
If our King dies, then
we shall fight for him.
But in our current conditions,
we are not strong enough.
Your ancestor is aware that you
have been to Demon World once.
I remember.
And thank you for
opening an old wound!
[HOKUSHIN] I understand
he had felt at the time,
your power was not great enough.
However, he foresaw you would
become a savior to
us in the fut--
[YUSUKE]
I don't like it.
[gasps]
[YUSUKE]
You sound desperate.
I bet you'd take
help from anybody.
You know you don't have a
chance at coming out on top,
so you're just
clutching at straws.
To be honest with
you, that is true.
I could not come anywhere
close to the power
of the King and the other
two, and neither could you.
You are far weaker
than I am, right now,
but this, I am sure,
you already know.
This is the reason why we
want you to train yourself
in Demon World.
Something... isn't clicking.
But I can't put
my finger on it.
You're not jerking my chain.
You're telling me the truth?
You must trust us with
what we have spoken.
[YUSUKE] Hmph. There
is one part of your story
I don't have to trust, but
I can find out on my own.
It won't take much
time out of your day
to see who's
stronger between us.
Like to try, Yusuke?
Now, that's more like it.
[YUSUKE]
I hope you don't think
I'm going to pull
any of my punches.
That is what I would expect.
[KUROKO]
Wait a second, you two.
You can't do this
inside our house.
It's just that
the kids are upstairs
trying to get some sleep.
Don't worry, they can sleep.
We'll take this outside.
Let's go.
[HOKUSHIN]
Hmph.
That was neat!
Have you ever thought of
including a story like that
in one of your books?
That? I don't think so.
Something like that is
just way too unrealistic.
You think Yusuke will be okay?
[KUROKO]
He'll be fine.
He's an effective
Spirit Detective.
Not to mention, he has the
blood of a Demon World king
coursing through his veins.
Yeah, but didn't it
kind of seem that
blood is just what
those three are after?
[KUROKO gasps]
[KAYKO] I can read you
like a book, Kuwabara.
I know you're hiding
something from me.
[KUWABARA] I told you,
I don't know anything!
Well, I called Yusuke earlier,
but he still hadn't
come home yet.
He's missing classes and we've
got mid-terms coming up.
Has he gotten himself
mixed up in another case?
I would expect you to be
honest with me if he has!
[KUWABARA sighs]
No, Kayko.
I'd be with him if it was
a case, you know that.
[SHIZURU] Kazuma, you better
be studying up there!
[KUWABARA grumbles]
I would if you'd
stop bugging me!
I have dedicated myself,
heart and soul,
to the preparation
for mid-terms!
Listen, Shizuru is all
over me about studying hard
since I was gone for so long,
so I'm gonna have to
get off the phone.
But I'll go find Genkai tomorrow
and ask her if she knows
anything about Urameshi.
Deal?
[phones clicks]
[phone beeping]
[KAYKO]
Hmm.
So, you gonna take
that nasty looking
pacemaker off your chest?
Cause I sure as hell wouldn't
want to be in your shoes
if I were less than
D-class Demon.
I cannot remove this until
I return to Demon World.
But, given your power, I can
leave it and still beat you.
Watch your mouth if you
want to live through this.
Now that is how I
want you to fight me.
I am serious about this,
and I'd like you to come at me
with everything you've got.
Because with my
current power,
you will slice through
me as if I were butter.
I mean, you could, if you
were quick enough to catch me.
[YUSUKE gasps]
I might be D-class,
but don't ever underestimate
the power of the desperate.
[gasps]
[HOKUSHIN grunts]
You will be beaten
before these leaves have
the opportunity
to hit the ground.
[YUSUKE grunts] Those
are pretty strong words.
Let's see you back 'em up!
[HOKUSHIN]
Haa!
[YUSUKE]
He's slow.
Maybe he lost some speed by
downgrading to a D-class,
or he's just not
giving it his all.
Either way, I'm still
granting his wish.
He's pissed me off enough today!
Come on! [grunts]
[YUSUKE yells]
[gasps]
What?!
[YUSUKE]
Tch...
Not quite what you
expected, is it?
--[YUSUKE] Right...
--[HOKUSHIN] This is my power.
[YUSUKE yells]
[HOKUSHIN]
I could stretch
and pick up a stone
twenty yards away.
So, I could crush your skull
and you'd never see it coming.
Let's find out!
[YUSUKE growling]
[HOKUSHIN]
No matter how hard you try,
it won't matter.
[YUSUKE]
Yeah?! We'll see!
[YUSUKE grunts]
[yells]
You know, the more you fight,
the more wound up
you will become.
[YUSUKE growls]
[YUSUKE grunting]
[gasps]
[YUSUKE]
Oh, great.
[YUSUKE grunting]
[HOKUSHIN]
Heh.
[yells]
[YUSUKE gasping]
Checkmate, friend.
So, are you starting
to believe me?
It's merely a toy.
[YUSUKE grunts]
Were I back to my S-class level,
I would have forgone the knife
and could have strangled you
to death with relative ease.
But at most, now I'm
only capable of this.
Now you're just being a prick.
I am simply practicing
basic psychology.
Finish the battle
quickly and efficiently,
illustrate an example
of my power,
and my opponent feels defeated.
Although, that has
yet to happen.
So, are you convinced?
Not one bit!
Well, then.
You will just have to come
with us to Demon World.
There I can remove this from
my chest and prove to you...
...that I have not lied.
We can fight for as
long as we wish there,
and you will come
to accept defeat.
That's some mouth on you!
And you're not gonna trap
me into your dirty game.
Dirty game?
You can't admit your defeat.
Sounds like a sore loser.
Losing a fight is
something I can handle.
I was talking about
your "BS" story.
--[TOUOU growls]
--[SEITEI] Hm.
[HOKUSHIN]
My story?
[YUSUKE] Yeah, I had a
feeling something was off
when I was listening
to you earlier.
And I think I just
now figured out why.
Would you care to explain it?
You said that my ancestor,
the king of your territory,
was the kind of spirit that
feeds on human beings.
That I did.
[YUSUKE] You also said it's
been about a thousand years
since your king
stopped eating,
and because of
this malnutrition,
he's busy these days
knocking on death's door.
Again, you are correct.
And that three of
you came here to
abide by the wishes
of your dying king.
All true, but you
have yet to speak
of the story's "dirty" part.
Yeah, but I have a question.
I want to know why
you eat human beings.
[BOTH grunt]
Maybe you need a
minute to answer?
[HOKUSHIN] Heh. No.
You have done good work.
One time I fought a Demon
that ate human beings
and I never forgot the stench.
The same stench
of rotting flesh
that came out of your mouth
when you got close to me.
[HOKUSHIN gasps]
I don't know what you're
up to Hokushin, but nothin'
gets on my nerves more
than a deceptive stranger.
You liar!
Now stand your ground!
Please, wait one second.
Let me explain myself.
I cannot say--
--[YUSUKE yells]
--[HOKUSHIN grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[HOKUSHIN grunting]
[YUSUKE] And that was
me taking it easy on you.
I'll decide whether
or not to kill you
after I've heard
your real story.
Now! You start talking
or I start punchin'!
[NARRATOR] As Yusuke's
ancestor, a Demon king,
is locked in a life
or death struggle,
these three messengers have
been sent to bring Yusuke
back to Demon World.
But it seems as if Hokushin's
words have been laced with
half-truths and even lies.
Can Yusuke trust any of
what he has been told?
And if so, will a
journey to Demon World
reveal Yusuke's true destiny?
[YUSUKE] As if telling a guy
that his ancestral father is
some kind of people-eating
Demon isn't enough to ruin
an appetite, I can't shake
the feeling that these
three Demon World lackeys are
still hiding something from me.
Anyway, one thing
I know for sure,
something huge is
about to go down.
And I already
know I'm in for it.
I just don't know who's
gonna take the news harder;
Kayko or Kuwabara!
Oh well, somebody's
got to tell them.
Here goes nothing!
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho.