♪
[NARRATOR] The Four Saint Beasts
have made a bold demand:
bring down the barrier that
imprisons their fortress city,
or witness a plague
of monstrous insects
spreading terror on the Earth.
Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
and his friend Kuwabara have
gone into the forbidden city,
hoping to root out
the terrorizing beasts.
Joined by two strong demons,
they must now endure
the Gate of Betrayal.
[EYE-BAT] This has always been
my favorite part of the trial.
Watching the
way you squirm
as your muscles
begin to pop and tear
under the ceiling's weight.
[EYE-BAT] But of course,
the best is your eyes.
Seeing the gears of
thought turn in desperation,
thinking, questioning yourself.
How long can I hold this?
Will I die this way?
Will one friend betray us
and escape while we flatten?
Or should I be the one?
Just ignore that punk!
Stick together!
And if anybody tries to run
I swear I'll drag
them back myself!
And I suppose you think it'd be
noble if we all died as a team.
That's right!
Here's a thought. Let's
shut up and find a way out!
[YUSUKE THINKS] If we could
just find a way to that switch.
Hiei!
You're a lot
faster than any of us!
We'll hold the ceiling up while
you go and flip the switch.
You crazy?! We can't
trust that guy! Just look!
He doesn't care at all about us!
Your ugly friend has a
good point, detective.
[KUWABARA] Who's ugly?!
Come here you mouse!!
Are you sure you
want to trust me?
I've already vowed my revenge on
you. Maybe I'll handle that now.
Yeah but I don't think
quick deaths are your style.
I'll let out all the
Spirit Power I have left
to buy us a little time
while you run to the switch.
Just don't trip.
I trust you. Now go!
[Eye-Bat- laughs]
What's the deal?!
Pull the stupid switch already!
There is no need to make
snap judgments, my friend.
What have they
ever done for you?
Leave them, and you can come
with me into the castle.
[EYE-BAT]
With the invasion of Earth,
the Four Saint Beasts will
control the future. Be smart.
Join us. Perhaps you can be the
General of our demon army.
Don't you dare you creep!
If it hadn't been for our help
you'd still be here
screaming with the rest of us!
[Hiei chuckles]
[KUWABARA] What are
you laughing about?!
Take a guess, you fool.
Damn you!!
[EYE-BAT] Yes, you find
amusement in their pain.
Now imagine the
satisfaction that will come
from their final screams.
[Eye-Bat laughs wickedly]
Hiei!!!
[EYE-BAT] A wise choice.
The boulder would have
crushed you anyway.
Thanks for the clue!
He came through!
[YUSUKE] Hiei!
[Eye-Bat cries in pain]
Tell your masters...
This is their chance
to beg for mercy.
Hey, are you all right?
Oh yeah, I just can't
feel my arms right now.
I knew you'd save us! Ya' punk!
But you did have me worried!
Hell of an actor.
Ya know not everyone can pretend
to laugh at their dying friends!
Friends are just a crutch for
the weak. And I wasn't acting.
Say what??
Don't confuse it.
The only reason I saved you was
because I might need your help.
It's his way of saying
you're welcome. You will learn.
Right.
Well, he still ticks me off.
[SEIRYU] They passed the
Gate of Betrayal, master.
What shall we do?
[SUZAKU]
Do not fret, Seiryu.
It only means we can
entertain our guests longer.
Someone go play with them.
[BYAKKO] That one called Hiei.
He mocked us, actually
telling us to beg for mercy!
I'll go down
and drain his blood.
[GENBU]
No! Let me handle this!
I am the only one who ever
reaches outside of the castle.
Let me bring their bodies
to the head of the tower.
I'll hang them on pikes as a
message to all of Spirit World.
[Genbu laughs wickedly]
[Communication Mirror rings]
What is that thing? Is it safe?
It's just the Communication
Mirror that I got from Botan.
Hello Yusuke! It's Botan here
in the living world. You copy?
--Yeah! I--
--Hey what's up Botan!
This is brave Kuwabara
reporting at your service.
I'm taking very
good care of Urameshi.
I'm so glad to hear that!
I've got things under control
here as well, more or less.
The Makai Insects
only like to nest
in depressed people's minds.
That narrows down
my search a bit.
I've also found another
spy for the Saint Beasts.
I just can't figure out
how they're getting
past the barrier.
See, I think they're demons
from outside the city
taking orders along the wall.
[KUWABARA AND YUSUKE]
Watch out!!
Don't worry.
Those guys are weaklings.
The real challenge is
finding those Makai Insects.
I've only caught
fifteen of those buggers
and I've been searching
for nearly an entire day!
[KUWABARA]
Don't worry, baby, you'll--
[YUSUKE] Fifteen?
That's not much help.
Yusuke, fighting
people controlled
by the insect takes time.
That's why you need
to get that whistle!
Okay, we're trying, but this
castle is kinda' rough!
Well of course it is!
No one's survived before!
Hey! I see you!
Ha! Nothing beats bug
spray from the Spirit World!
[BLUE OGRE] Koenma sir!
I've just heard!
[KOENMA] Should I look
under Four or Saint?
[BLUE OGRE]
Koenma sir!
The news just came in!
Yusuke and the others
have entered Maze Castle
and they've gotten
past the front gate!
[KOENMA]
Whoopee. You may leave.
May I ask what you are doing
up here in Records, sir?
[KOENMA] No, but I'll
tell you anyway.
I'm looking for information
on the Four Saint Beasts.
You mean you
don't know anything
about their strength
or special powers
and you already sent
Yusuke to fight them!
[KOENMA]
That's right.
But sir, that's just terrible!
He's fighting blind!
[KOENMA] Those beasts
have already begun
an invasion of the Earth!
I didn't have a choice.
If you'd prefer I can
send you there instead.
No sir! You're right!
[KOENMA]
Of course I am.
Now make yourself useful and
look through that book stack!
[BLUE OGRE]
Okay!
[KOENMA] What sort of
creatures were they?
For some reason
I'm drawing a blank.
Kurama, what do you know
about these four Saint people?
Botan pushed us down that
hole like a couple of cows.
And I didn't have
a chance to ask her.
She wouldn't have told
you much I'm afraid.
Ever since the barrier wall
was raised around the city,
Spirit World Intelligence
virtually forgot
this place existed.
What do you know?
Let's just say that when
you see their bodies
you may be very surprised.
[GENBU] Terrified.
Isn't that more like it?
Who said that?!
[Genbu laughs menacingly]
[GENBU] There's a door
behind you. Please take it.
Ladies first.
[Genbu laughs menacingly]
[GENBU]
Welcome, trespassers.
Okay I'm surprised!
I am Genbu of the
Four Saint Beasts.
Do you have a request
before you die?
Yeah, tell me how a beast
is a saint. I'm lost.
This stairwell is the
only way to the castle tower.
You can either defeat me
and go up on your own,
or be dragged there once
you've stopped breathing.
Why don't you all
attack me at once?
Then the last one
left won't feel lonely.
He's a rock Urameshi!
How are we gonna fight
against a talking rock?!
I will fight him.
Are you sure?
It would be ill-advised
for all of us to attack
without first
knowing his power.
Besides, I can hardly let Hiei
get all the credit
for this mission, now can I?
You want to die one by one?
I can do that too.
Hey, wouldn't we be better
off trying to lure him back
to that drop-down
ceiling or something!
Obviously you are
underestimating Kurama.
Do you know why I chose
him to be my partner?
To avoid fighting him myself.
[HIEI] Watch.
He's more cutthroat than
I am when it comes to battle.
And unbelievably precise.
I don't know guys,
he's still a talking rock.
Sir, the first move is yours.
Hey! Stone-man's doing
somethin' freaky with his tail!
Kurama!
Thanks to my
body's structure,
I can become one
with any type of rock.
With a little rearranging,
I can make any stone my tail.
Yeah, we're in trouble!
And since this whole
chamber is made of stone,
I have you surrounded.
There's nowhere to run!
Oh man! Now he's wounded!
Maybe we should help.
There is no need,
I've been hurt.
But he will not take
me by surprise again.
Wait until you see the
full extent of my power.
Then you won't be so confident.
He's gonna put
himself into the floor!
Do something Kurama!!
Now he could be anywhere.
I can't even since
Genbu's energy!
Same old trick.
Watch for his tail!
He's getting attacked
from both sides!
Where'd that freak go now?!
[Genbu laughs]
[GENBU] You'll never defeat
me by just running away!
Yes Genbu,
I believe you are right.
A flower?
Now, that's weird.
If he's trying
to win the beast over
I don't think
that's a good idea.
[Hiei chuckles]
It's no ordinary flower.
[harp music]
[KURAMA]
Rose Whip!
Well, everything's
coming up roses.
It smells girly,
I don't think I like it.
Oh sure, I guess he should
be a tough guy like you
and be obsessed with kittens.
Shut up!
[KOENMA]
Oh, it's Gorgeous!
I remember hearing about
this kind of weapon.
Don't Animal Spirits use it?
[KOENMA]
Mm-hm.
[Genbu laughs]
[GENBU] You still don't
understand your problem!
What good will a
fancy whip do you
if you can't tell where I am?
Yes, not being able to
find you is a problem.
[GENBU] You just can't
be scared, can you?
Well, I'll soon change that!
Found you!
It's over, the thorns
on Kurama's whip
can slice through any substance,
including solid stone.
Rose Whiplash!
How did you find me?
Your smell,
after filling the room
with the rose's sweet aroma,
your putrid odor
was easy for me to find.
Well that's no fair.
Why isn't that any of my
fights end that quick?
Beat him in one blow!
Now that's what I call a wimp!
You idiots,
it only looked easy
because Kurama
was the one fighting.
If you had fought you would have
died in under a minute.
Why does everything you say
make me want to
bash your face in?!
Listen! I just
happened to place third
in Master Genkai's
Fighting Tournament!
The only ones who beat me were
Yusuke and an evil monster!
What's you point?
You little-- !!!
Children!! Would you mind
saving it for the bad guys!
[KUWABARA] Okay.
But he started it.
I guess now we
go up the stairs.
[KURAMA] It seems
my fight is not over.
Who's beaten?
Not me!
Uh guys I think he's putting
himself back together?!
You can disassemble
me all you like.
I'll come back
together every time!
Actually, it makes
for a very nice attack!
Rose Whiplash!!
Right in the head!
Let's see him come back now!
[GENBU]
Want to try again?
Okay, that was luck!
Let's end this. How'd you
like to be stoned to death?!
They're coming back!
Kurama!!
What the hell's he doing?!
He's gonna get killed!
[GENBU] You're not even
fighting back now.
Those blows must
have made you insane.
Yes, I'm sure of it. Now
you're laughing at nothing.
[GENBU] Wait! How'd
you get on the ceiling?!
What's wrong?!
I've heard of brass balls,
but come on!
Yeah I'd like to
see him use a toilet!!
What did you do to me?!
I took this.
What's that?!
[KURAMA] I believe this
is the equivalent
of the hypothalamus
portion of your brain.
It regulates all the
functions of your body,
including the process of
putting you back together.
But--
[KURAMA] It seems to relay an
energy signal when you separate,
making it very easy to find.
You-Can't-Do this!!
Give it back to me!!!
Give it back!!!
Farewell.
I don't think he liked that!
Good work Kurama!!
[YUSUKE] Are you okay?
If Kurama is injured we're
going to have some problems.
I'm sorry, Yusuke.
Nah... You've earned
yourself a break anyway!
Yeah, I'll handle the next one.
[NARRATOR] Thanks to the
clever moves of Kurama,
the mighty Genbu
has been destroyed.
But somewhere in the twists
and turns of Maze Castle,
three Saint Beasts
still remain.
[BYAKKO]
Please. Let me go next.
[Byakko laughs menacingly]
[BOTAN ]
Botan here.
While I'm fighting the Makai
Insects back on Earth,
Yusuke and the boys must
walk a thin line of peril
as they struggle their way
through the heart
of Maze Castle.
As the situation over
a collapsing bridge
threatens their lives,
Kuwabara will reveal some
surprising new abilities.
And I'm certain
he'll need them all,
as he faces off against
the next Saint Beast himself!
This ones name is Byakko and
he's a ravenous white tiger.
You'll be dying to see
him in the next episode
on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪