[NARRATOR]
At the urging of Genkai,
Yusuke paid a visit
to Kuroko Sanada,
the first Spirit Detective.
But their meeting was
interrupted by the arrival
of messengers from Demon World.
They told of three Demon
rulers who have maintained
the balance of power
for over 500 years.
Only now, one of those rulers
is on the verge of death,
That ruler is Raizen,
Yusuke's ancestral father.
However, Yusuke is skeptical
if all they say is true...
Why is it I don't think
you're telling me everything?
Liar!
[HOKUSHIN grunts]
[YUSUKE] And that was
me takin' it easy on you.
I'll decide whether
or not to kill you,
after I've heard
your real story.
Impressive, I couldn't
tell you'd held back
until I was already beaten.
No matter how many times I do
that, it still makes me dizzy.
As you've deduced, I haven't
been entirely forthcoming.
But only because
I didn't think you'd trust
us if you knew how we fed.
[YUSUKE]
Give me some credit, baldy.
I get it. Food is food.
And to you, people is food.
[gasps]
[YUSUKE] Look, I've gotten
plenty of dirty looks
from vegetarians while
scarfing down a burger.
I feel ya.
So you guys need to eat people,
it's not like
you've got a choice.
I mean, your king went anorexic
and look what's
happening to him.
And even though
those other two rulers
still have pro
people-eating platforms,
you guys are backing
the un-cannibal.
Now that's loyalty.
So all I'm saying is,
I would've had a lot
less trouble trusting you
if you had just been straight
with me from the get go. Got it?
Now,
we've all learned a valuable
lesson about telling the truth.
I can see you are truly the
son of the great King Raizen.
You two are much alike.
Stop calling him my father.
[HOKUSHIN]
It is quite an honor
to be compared so
favorably to our King.
That is our highest compliment.
[YUSUKE gasps]
[HOKUSHIN]
When you spoke before,
I could tell that you share
your father's gift for
fairness and reasoning.
[YUSUKE]
Hm.
And from what we've heard
of your battle with Sensui,
not to mention what
we've witnessed firsthand,
you have inherited his
warrior's strength as well.
Strength that we will need
on our side if we're ever
going to defeat those
other two ruling Demons.
I guess I don't know
what the big deal is
I mean, why do you want
these two guys dead so bad?
[HOKUSHIN] Because our
King does not like them.
And if our King does not like
someone, then neither do I.
Well, how very
lemming-like of you.
You cannot understand the
intricacies of our world
until you are a part of it.
We will be back here in a week
which should give you enough
time to make your decision.
[TOUOU, SEITEI]
Hm.
[HOKUSHIN] I'm sure you've
already made up your mind,
but since you will be
leaving this world,
there must be many things
you need to attend to.
[HOKUSHIN] The King looks
forward to seeing you.
[gasps]
You have to go.
Kuroko?
How long you been
standing here?
Long enough. I heard
everything that you said.
You would be better
off in Demon World.
[KUROKO] Without hesitation,
you described people as food.
That's not something an ordinary
person would just accept.
I'm afraid you don't belong
in this world, anymore.
Maybe you're right.
I wasn't going to
say anything to you,
but you weren't the first
visitor I received this week.
Who's there?
[gasps]
Yusuke Urameshi must
be killed immediately.
[KUROKO]
But isn't he Spirit Detective?
Not anymore, he isn't.
He's become a danger to
himself and to others.
He's a Demon, now. A Mazoku.
I've retired from Spirit World
and no longer answer to them.
Now, leave me alone.
[YUSUKE]
Huh, I guess Koenma was right.
Those guys really do
have it out for me.
You know, it makes a
guy feel kinda special,
to be wanted like that.
[KUROKO]
I told them I wouldn't do it,
then I called Master Genkai,
to learn more about this
notorious, Yusuke Urameshi.
So? what did
the old bat say?
Master Genkai told me
that I'd relate with you
the moment that I
met you in person.
And she was right. I was
convinced when we met
that you really were
somebody worth protecting.
At first anyway, but...
...I'm really sorry, Yusuke,
But I don't trust you, and this
is one time I can't just go on
Master Genkai's faith alone.
[KUROKO]
It's different now.
I have children and I have to
think about their safety first,
and I don't think
that they can be safe
while you're around.
That's ridiculous. I'd never
do anything to hurt them!
[KUROKO] Yes, but are you
always yourself, lately?
[YUSUKE sighs]
I hoped that because of
our shared experience,
I could offer some advice,
but it seems you have a lot more
in common with those three,
now, than you do with me.
There is nothing to say.
It's all good.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Hold on, Yusuke, please!
[YUSUKE grunts]
Don't you want me to finish
telling you your fortune?
Why not?
The danger I spoke of--
I didn't get a chance
to tell you it could
come from close in.
I saw a great separation
developing between
you and your friends.
And what could cause that?
Uh... I don't know, but it was
a separation made in blood.
[train whitsles]
You must be stealthier
than that to surprise me.
I hope you have good reason
for approaching, stranger.
[YOMI MESSENGER]
For you,
A "Spirit of Words,"
from Mr. Yomi.
[gasps]
You said "Yomi?"
[YOMI MESSENGER]
Our work is done.
[KURAMA] What could he
possibly have to say to me?
[KURAMA]
Yomi....
[YOMI]
It's been a long time, Kurama.
Too long... It's good
to see you alive and well.
Of course, I can't actually see,
as this is just a
spirit of words.
Regardless, I hope to
meet you in person soon.
Back when you knew me,
neither of us was very powerful.
But that's changed.
I've grown stronger.
Much stronger.
Strong enough to rival
Raizen and Mukuro for
control of the Demon World.
[YOMI] You remember
those names, don't you?
They were already in
power when you left.
But several hundred years ago,
I joined their ranks.
And now, I'm prepared
for my next ascension.
I'm planning to
dethrone the two of them,
and then will unify all of Demon
World as one nation under me.
But if I am to succeed in this,
I will require your
assistance, Kurama.
And so, my friend, I plead
with you to join my crusade.
If you believe in
the unification,
then I beg you to return to us.
Oh, and one more thing.
I almost forgot to tell you.
I apprehended the one who
stole the light from me.
I think you'll be amused, as was
I, when you see who it was.
Another incentive to come
back to Demon World, I guess.
[HIEI]
An old friend of yours?
Hiei.
[laughs]
Caught you off guard.
Now don't feel too special,
you weren't the only one who
received a midnight visitor.
[HIEI]
Messengers came to me as well.
Though, in my case, they
were sent by Mukuro.
Mukuro?
[HIEI]
See for yourself.
[MUKURO]
Greetings, Hiei. I am Mukuro.
I would've been there in person,
but I seldom show
my face in public.
Not out of fear,
but out of annoyance at
being mobbed by adoring fans.
Huh...
[MUKURO] Your recent appearance
here has come to my attention,
and I had to wonder: Why
aren't you working for me?
Think of it.
You could be my right-hand man.
I'll even let you in on a little
secret. For your ears only.
Raizen is on the brink of death.
And when he has breathed
his very last breath,
I will strike Yomi
with full force.
He pushes for a peaceful,
unified Demon World.
I'm sure the mere thought
of such a desecration
of our homeland disgusts you.
[MUKURO] If I am correct
in my assumption,
you should join me.
What a talkative and
self-important fool he is.
Was he always like that, Kurama?
And much worse.
Mukuro has always been a
dangerous, tyrannical ruler.
You have no idea, Hiei, of the
damage Mukuro could do.
Demon World thrown in chaos.
Then I suppose this is
going to be interesting.
Well I'm off to visit him now.
Goodbye.
You can breathe, you know.
I'm not going there to help him.
Yes, that is good thinking,
it will be beneficial
for us to have a man on the
inside whom Mukuro trusts.
Just be sure to get
as much information
as you can without
raising suspicions.
Oh, I'll be sure to use
him for everything I can.
[KURAMA] Now I'm not
sure who to fear more,
Mukuro...
...or Hiei.
[snoring]
[EIKICHI hisses]
[KUWABARA grunts]
You scared the
heck outta Eikichi!
Yeah, I'm sure "your
cat" will get over it.
Now get out of bed.
You wanna fight,
sis, I'll fight.
I been holdin' back!
'cause you think
that you're a lady.
Listen, Kazuma,
do you want to get into
a decent high school?
Yeah, so what?
Then you're gonna have to
start studying a lot harder.
'Cause I'm stupid...
I get it! Huh?
Aren't you gonna call me stupid?
Baby brother...
I do know that...
...no matter what I
say, you're not stupid.
Huh. Well, it's about time.
But it will...
...be stupid if you let
your smarts go to waste.
Yeah, I know,
spare me the lecture.
If you know, then why
don't you act on it
before you're a
deadbeat loser like me!
I didn't help raise
you for nothin',
and if you keep fighting Demons,
you're on your own, so decide!
The exam for the magnet
high school's coming up!
You pass, or you get out!
[KUWABARA groans]
[sighs]
The window's coming
out of your allowance.
[KUWABARA farts]
[KUWABARA]
That's what I think of that!
All right, Kuwabara, you're 15.
Maybe it is time you
finally started thinking
about your future, you know?
Stop fighting all the time
focus on your schoolwork
and apply yourself and--
Oh darn it! I hate it when
she's right about something.
[PEOPLE chatter]
So, I don't see you for days
and all of a sudden you call
me up and expect me to be fine?
I'm going through a
major change, Kayko.
Huh?
I mean, remember how when
I came outta the cave,
I looked a little bit different?
Okay...
Does long hair and
tattoos ring a bell?
[KAYKO]
Okay, so you're a Demon.
What exactly is different
about you now?
[YUSUKE] Eeh, I guess
basically I'm the same.
[KAYKO]
Then what's the problem with it?
I hope to find out.
That's why I have to go
back to Demon World.
When?
[YUSUKE]
Tomorrow...
Oh, well have you told your
mother that you're leaving?
[YUSUKE]
Yeah...
though I don't think she really
got where I was goin, 'cause she
asked me to pick up a six-pack
for her on the way back.
When... will you be coming back?
[HOKUSHIN] To see your
ancestor, to return with us,
you must become as one of us.
[gasps]
Can you come back?
Sure... Maybe.
Oh, I see.
[YUSUKE]
Kayko...
[KAYKO] I hear Kuwabara's
taking the entrance exam
for the University's
prep school.
[YUSUKE]
Get out! What about you?
I'm trying... Dai-ichi
School for Girls.
You really wanna go
to an all-girls school?
An all-boys school
is right next door.
[KAYKO]
Well...
Be sure to give me a call
whenever you get back, Yusuke,
so I can introduce you
to my new boyfriend.
Nice knowing you.
[KAYKO sighs]
[YUSUKE]
Kayko...
Please, Kayko, don't leave me!
Look! I'm a crab!
[YUSUKE grunts, yells]
[KAYKO]
Oh, my Prince Charming. [laughs]
Bye.
[YUSUKE] Well... You sure
messed that one up.
[KUWABARA]
Of course!
A squared plus
B squared equals...
C squared!
[door clatters]
We're closed.
If you're hungry, try cooking
for yourself for a change.
Hey! It's Yusuke Urameshi!
Long time no see!
You still want the usual?
[YUSUKE]
Yes, sir.
Hey, Kayko, get down here!
We got a special customer!
[YUSUKE] Oh, y-you don't have
to bother her, Mr. Ukimura.
Nonsense, she'll love it!
Hey Kayko, get your butt
down here, right away!
[KAYKO] I'm trying to
do my homework, Dad!
If getting into that
school means turning your
back on your old man,
you don't need high
school, anyway!
Look it's your friend, Yusuke!
[KAYKO] You interrupted
my studying for him?
He wants an order of
grilled beef with rice and--
[KAYKO]
I know what he wants.
[MR. YAKIMORA] Watch it,
sweetie, or you'll burn it.
If you keep cooking like that,
no man will ever
want to marry you.
[KAYKO]
How enlightened of you.
Now your mother,
she can cook!
[KAYKO]
Please, Not now, Dad.
Here's your food.
Enjoy. Don't choke on it.
I'd enjoy it more
if you sat with me.
[KAYKO]
Why?
Just because, okay?
This looks great!
This is the best food I've
ever tasted in my life!
Can I go now, Dad?
[YUSUKE]
Want some?
Want some what?
[YUSUKE]
Your loss...
Uh, so, Kayko, I guess
you know tomorrow is
my birthday, right?
Yeah, I knew that.
So, uh...
So what?
So by my 18th birthday,
I'll get back here.
I will find a way...
I promise to.
And, then what?
Then let's get married.
[KAYKO gasps]
[sighs]
Yusuke, I don't
know how my new...
...boyfriend is going
to feel about that.
[MR. YAKIMORA laughs]
Been a while since
last time I heard one
of Yusuke's proposals. [laughs]
He used to play that card every
time you two had an
argument as kids.
[laughs]
You haven't changed.
[YUSUKE]
I'm serious.
Three years and I'll be back,
and we'll get married.
I don't know, buddy, I'm
going into high school.
A lot could happen in that time.
[YUSUKE] Kayko... You
know I love you, right?
[KAYKO]
Yeah, yeah, me too.
[YUSUKE laughs]
[MR. YAKIMORA laughs]
[sighs]
[door clatters]
[KAYKO]
Yusuke, just give me a sign
that everything's
gonna be all right.
[gasps]
[YUSUKE] Well, the time has come
for me to go back to Demon World
and Kuwabara's got
problems with it.
But then again, Kuwabara's got
problems with lots of things,
so let's focus on me, okay?
Looks like I get quite a sendoff
from all my friends at home,
which I'll have to enjoy while
I can, 'cause when you hit
the ground running in Demon
World, they mean it literally.
But it'll be worth it when
I come face to face with
the bastard that
hijacked my body during
my fight with Sensui:
My ancestral dad.
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!