♪
It must've been
a sad existence.
After you made
your decision
and had started your
glorious new life.
What did you think about when
you couldn't fall asleep?
Because I know
that it happened.
Tell me--what went
through your head?
For a very long time I
only thought of you, Genkai.
A major reason why
you have to die.
[KUWABARA] Urameshi!!
Come on, this isn't funny!
Man, I bet this is a plan by
all four of those jerks-faces
to have a secret meeting
and leave me out of it.
[KUWABARA] Probably learnin'
some cool new attack.
That's a bad sign.
He's mumbling and
walking backwards.
Yukina!!! Hey and you brought
your three servants, too!
For a joke to get old
it has to be funny in
the first place, baby bro.
Why were you
talking to yourself.
Well Urameshi ran away--I was
just trying to catch him!!
Yusuke isn't in the hotel?
Well if he is I've sure
been yelling for no reason.
Perhaps he just left
to get some exercise.
No, it was more
urgent than that.
First Genkai steps out,
then Yusuke wakes up,
calls me an idiot
and leaves too.
I know I'm
missin' somethin!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
What is she thinking??
Do you have any
other distractions?
Or can I stay
powered-up this time?
No, everything I
needed has been answered.
Excellent, I'd hate to
leave an old hag unfulfilled.
I'd like you to
watch me very closely
as my muscles
increase this time.
See the power
you could have had.
I was such a
foolish little girl.
I should have been able
to see from the start
how you'd turn out.
You had it written in ugly black
letters all across your soul.
[TOGURO 2] You were
good in there, Genkai.
Our teamwork is
even more in tune now.
It isn't going to
take us much longer.
Soon every fighter
will know of our names.
[GENKAI]
And then what?
[TOGURO 2] We do the only
thing we can. We go further.
Our bodies are
at their peaks now.
You tell me you don't
think about that.
From now on we only go downhill.
Until one day a
weakling takes our life,
or we rot away in our own skin.
I won't let it happen.
You're a beautiful
girl, Genkai.
Thank you.
And I can't help but think
that our human lives are
nothing but a cruel joke.
Here just long enough
to know what we want.
Then it erodes.
[GENKAI]
You'll age as I will, Toguro.
That's how it is and you'll see.
We'll be okay.
How moronic I was to
think you would change.
You were just selfish--
selling your soul
for a moment's strengh.
[TOGURO 2]
Oh, that stings.
The way I see it,
you didn't have
the guts required
to get everything that
you wanted and I did.
[GENKAI THINKS] I have enough
energy to fire three blasts.
I'll have to use them well.
I see after fifty years
you've improved your dodging.
That swipe I just made was
supposed to remove your heart.
[TOGURO 2] Oh,
and you were right.
The committee was quite
thorough with my request.
To keep me young,
they even gave me a body that
was extremely quick to heal.
There really isn't
anything left of you.
Such an enormous power.
What the hell is going on?
[KURAMA] There must be an
effective weapon somewhere.
That power. I've never
sensed so much before.
Someone is in
considerable danger.
[KUWABARA] Urameshi!
Come on, don't leave me
out of the loop again!
Hey, I got a pretty good feeling
I shouldn't be going this way.
I got goose bumps
all over my skin!
Eighty percent of my strength.
Only four living souls
have seen this level.
My older brother.
Karasu and Bui.
And you.
Though needless
to say, Genkai...
[TOGURO 2] Technically...
You won't count for long.
[TOGURO 2] Demon Energy
may not always be stronger
than a human's Spirit power.
But it gives a much more
pleasurable sensation when used.
[TOGURO 2] Strength
to make the most
learned techniques outmoded.
That is strength absolute.
Is that all
you have left?
You and I used to be
nearly equal in strength.
And now look at you.
But then again,
you're not Genkai anymore.
You're just an
empty and outdated shell.
The pitiful preserved remains.
Do you know why
demons want you dead?
It's not because of
the fights you won.
It's because you gave up
the chance to be truly great.
Great by your crap
standards, not by mine!
There's no point
in us shouting back and
forth anymore, is there?
This is your
final moment Genkai.
I hope you're at least happy
with the way you've
wasted your life.
[GENKAI] Only one
regret, Toguro.
Despite all the abilities
my Spirit Wave afforded me,
it never gave me the power
to do the one thing
I hoped it could do
from my first hour of seclusion.
[YOUNG GENKAI] One day
I'm going to help you, Toguro.
I'm going to come back
and heal you from your madness.
It's Genkai.
You okay over
there, Botan?
You've arrived too late.
[TOGURO 2] I will never
forget her expression.
It was clear she was trying
with every ounce of
her energy to stop me.
But she didn't even
scratch my body
with the final
attack of her life.
[TOGURO 2 THINKS]
He's swift.
Genkai you're alright
I'm here now.
You're gonna be fine,
trust me Genkai.
Come on!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, Dim-wit.
Yeah, that's right.
I knew you were too stubborn to
be killed by a jerk like that.
Come on, we'll get Botan
or Kurama to heal you.
Or Yukina!
Hell we got a
whole E.R. unit now!
It's okay, Yusuke I knew.
What do you mean??
They came to inform me,
three months ago.
[FEMALE REP] We represent the
Tournament Committee.
We come as a special
favor to Toguro.
I trust you have a moment.
Hear me, Master Genkai.
You'll soon be
given the opportunity
to fight in this
year's Dark Tournament.
It is highly requested
you take the offer.
[GENKAI] Clearly you're
an imposter.
Any true affiliate of
the Tournament Committee
would know that I
won half a century ago.
And that the only
prize I requested
was to never be bothered
by their organization again.
So buzz off.
Of course--that's why for
you it's only a request.
Your student Yusuke will
be invited too, by the way.
Though for him it
will be mandatory.
Toguro talks most excitedly
about this tournament.
He feels it will be
the most competitive yet.
A Shinobi sect and
an extremely creative doctor
have already made their bids.
And with the
controversial apparitions
Kurama and Hiei joining Yusuke,
his team could
be formidable;
though Toguro feels
without a strong fifth member
they will not live for long.
[FEMALE REP] But as
you said, Master Genkai,
the choice is yours.
[GENKAI] When an old teammate
traps you into a tournament
after fifty years,
you don't take it lightly.
I knew I would die here.
[YUSUKE] Hey, you're
not makin' any sense.
What are you
saying-old teammate?
You can't mean
you and Toguro!
[ANNOUNCER] Winners of the
Dark Tournament! Team Toguro!!
Please, name your prize!
[YOUNG TOGURO 2]
You will turn me from a human
into the highest class of demon.
A kind that lives for
centuries and whose body
will practically
never age.
A kind with
strength absolute.
It's the truth Yusuke.
That was my wish fifty years ago
when my team became
the champions
of the Dark Tournament.
Suffice to say your teacher
didn't exactly
agree with my choice.
Yusuke!
Hey, try and save your energy.
Damn it, Yusuke.
Listen to me.
Every one has
to fight with time.
To find their place
before their inevitable death.
Toguro, he ran
away from that fight.
Don't you ever do the same,
no human is ever
a one man show.
Every decision that you make...
Will affect the countless
people who care about you.
Do you understand?
You can't be a...
cocky kid anymore.
You have to...
I have to what?
Genkai has been finished.
Her energy is completely gone.
[KOENMA] She's dead.
Oh, Genkai.
[Botan begins to weep]
[TOGURO 2] You have no more
reason to mourn for that woman
than I do, Yusuke.
She died a
long time ago.
Decades before
you were even born.
A fighter only has two
choices in their life.
Either die or get stronger.
And Genkai chose the former.
Ever since she
abandoned her potential
and hid herself like
a frightened animal
in that mountain compound.
She's been nothing
but a walking corpse.
[YUSUKE]
Shut the hell up.
You think you know everything,
but you don't have a
friggin' clue!
Don't fear
the truth Yusuke.
All I did was clean
up the filthy mess
that she left behind.
[YUSUKE] You don't know
anything about her!!!
[Toguro 2 laughs]
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Genkai.
[Yusuke cries out]
[thunder]
[TOGURO 2] Very
impressive, Yusuke.
But your heart clearly
wasn't in that fight.
[Toguro 2 laughs]
[TOGURO 2] At last,
I will be able to do battle
at one hundred percent.
[TOGURO 2]
I've waited too long.
Puu.
Oh, what's wrong
with you now, Puu?
You look worse than when
Yusuke was having his test.
[PUU]
Puu.
I think there's something
really wrong with Botan, too.
[Botan weeps]
Darn it, where's Urameshi?
I hope he's nowhere near
that huge energy I felt!
It's messed up.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Genkai.
Use the Spirit Wave to
float on top of the spike.
[GENKAI] Good. Now we'll hold
this for twelve hours.
[YUSUKE] I hate you!!
[GENKAI]
This will be an exercise
in blocking energy attacks.
Careful. This could kill you.
[GENKAI]
Bonehead!
We're not going to stop this
until you don't move an inch!
Now get up!
[YUSUKE] You people
are all alike!
Tryin' to take control and tell
me how I am! You're wrong!
Look at all the
energy you still have!
Shows you're doing your
training like everything else.
[YUSUKE] Shut up!
[GENKAI] Yes, kill me
to avoid your problems.
[YUSUKE] Shut UP!!!
It's time you bit the bullet
and started caring
about something
with all your heart and energy.
But you can't care about it
if you're always
holding yourself back
in case it doesn't work out!
[YUSUKE] But if it
means I gotta take out
the only person who ever
taught me anything useful...
Yusuke.
[YUSUKE] You're my teacher.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry but I give up.
You will remember everything...
[GENKAI] Everything that
went through your head.
[NARRATOR] Two days
before Yusuke's team
enters the final round
of the Dark Tournament,
the mentor he has
come to depend on
has been slain by the
opponent he must now face.
Can Yusuke heed
Genkai's final warning,
and put an end to
this fifty-year fight?
[YUSUKE] I'll never
forgive you, Toguro.
[KOENMA] This is serious stuff
we're delving into
now, my loyal fans.
Yusuke must realize
the true potential
Genkai has left him with,
the gift of her
Spirit Wave Orb--
But not unless he can first
overcome the incredible grief
that threatens to
paralyze him altogether.
And don't think Yusuke is the
only one with issues, either.
Kuwabara, Hiei, and Kurama
all have their own
demons to confront--
no pun intended--
and a couple unexpected guests
just might have the
answers they need.
All that and more,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪