♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke's Spirit
Detective Team
is battling
the Rokuyuakai Team
in the opening of
the Dark Tournament.
Kuwabara lost the first fight,
and Kurama stepped forward
in an attempt
to even the score.
The wicked Roto
paralyzed Kurama
with a threat to
his human mother,
but Kurama secretly planted
a deadly seed inside his body,
and overcame the danger.
What will happen next?
Would the next fighters
please come forward!
[DEMON FAN 1] Get yourselves
together, Rokuyuaki!
[DEMON FAN 2] You're a
disgrace to all apparitions!!
[DEMON FAN 3]
Pull your head out your ass!
What's this nonsense?
They had better get
out there and score!
Next fighters forward!
Hello?!
[KOTO THINKS] What's a girl
gotta do for new blood!
[demons whoop it up]
What? Their team
leader is fighting now?
But he should go last!
Maybe there's a mistake--
[HIEI]
No.
Zeru is definitely the
strongest of the four remaining.
He's fighting angry--
It's obvious he's not
taking this seriously enough.
Yes, and we're just the
picture of professionalism!
Urameshi Team, can
we get on with it here?!
I'll go, this one's
been irritating me
ever since last night.
[KOTO] Team Rokuyuakai, Zeru!
Team Urameshi, Hiei!
I know a great deal
about your technique.
Let's just say that tomorrow
will see you strongly
resembling your coffee cup.
What?
You harnessed heat energy
with such great precision
that it resembled a knife cut.
But one of the edges
was sloppily melted.
You have your flaws.
As do you, I don't
think I need advice
from someone who
has to use a fake eye.
Fight!!
Not intimidated yet?
[DEMON FAN 6]
Wait! What's he doing?
[Hiei with cocky laugh]
I wouldn't laugh just yet!
Unfortunately Hiei was
not charred by the fire!
But there's more coming his way!
These are some good seats.
[Zeru chuckles]
Zeru's blows are fantastic
and Hiei must run for his life!
Along with a good
deal of the fan base.
You've become so quiet now.
Too frightened to notice
any more of my supposed flaws?
Actually, I'm bored.
Actually you're dead!!
[KUWABARA]
This guy's kinda crazy.
What's this?
Oh, wow! His skin
is changing color!
He seems to be
engulfed in heat!
He's glowing like a poker!
Nice one!
I'm not finished yet.
Wow Zeru! You never told
us you could be so savage!
[KOTO]
I love it!
No--no I can't believe it!
[KOTO] You see it yourself,
people. Hiei is done.
You really think he's beaten?
I'm afraid he's a
little more than that.
Well in the unlikely event
I were betting
on a team like that,
I'd be pretty damn pleased
with them now, don't you think?
What a weak thing!
You can rest in Hell.
Well yes, that
fight wasn't a long one.
But when you've got
scorching moves like Zeru's,
a little goes a long way!
[HIEI]
Yes.
[HIEI] He's so talented I'm
reluctant to make the kill.
Oh my!
[KOTO] Hiei's survived!
He's on his feet! He's...
Smoldering!!
My fire! He survived it all!
How could you?
I believe we've covered that.
So my Jagan Eye
may not be natural.
But it does give me
exactly what I need!
[HIEI] Dragon of
the Darkness Flame!
I don't believe it's true!
He's going to attempt
the Darkness technique!
The Darkness?
What does that mean?
Dragon of the what, sir?
Dragon of the Darkness Flame.
It's incredibly dangerous.
My father talked of it once,
but I didn't think
anyone could do it!
Black flames! But they're...
From the deepest pits of
Spirit World! Oh help me!
You know it's impossible
to control it completely!
Once I release it I have no say!
I have the power to
pull you into oblivion.
I assume just
my right arm will do.
You should never have
insulted the Jagan Eye.
Because you see, in a
way it has its own mind,
and loathes disrespect.
Resisting it is not
something I would do.
I realize I'm
supposed to stay.
But in light of this
little situation we have here--
Retreat!!!
Dragon of the
Darkness Flame!!!
[KURAMA] Hiei
has succeeded.
Where's Zeru?
[KOTO] There's his
outline, at least.
Man he's exed.
Well, he's definitely
out of the ring.
Believe me he's
not coming back.
That cinder is
all that's left.
Yes, then I suppose
counting to ten
would be a little ridiculous.
[KOTO] Let's give it
up for Hiei!!
I honestly don't
know how to react.
Goodness. That
fight was so intensive
I don't even remember
eating my Squid-on-a-Stick.
Who's up for a second helping?
Yeah! We're punchin'
our way to the top!
Hiei can beat
anyone with that move!
Hiei can beat anyone with that
move. Am I listening to myself?
What if he decides
to be a bad guy again?
What if he decides to
shoot us with the Dragon?
Don't worry fool.
We've entered into an alliance
and I'm not the
type to break it.
Of course after we
win the tournament
I can't guarantee a thing.
They got Zeru.
Yeah man, they
got him really fast.
We're not nearly
as strong as him.
Tell you what Rinku, we'll let
you handle the rest, okay?
[RINKU] Wait! Don't
leave me here!!
[punching sounds]
Ah crap... it's bright out here.
You're here?!
Hey, would you
explain it to those guys
not to run away again?
There's a fight to fight.
You know...
it's not my fault...
[glass breaks]
Someone put a
small wall in the way.
Okay, upsy daisy!
Ah... no need to
make the ring taller,
let's just have some fun.
It is bright here.
Oh dear!
A drunk madman
has escaped to the ring.
Hey announcer shela!
You look pretty hot.
Can you come here a second?
I got a question for you!
What kind of question?
Two of their fellas
just died on accident.
[KOTO]
Really?
How can their team continue?
[burps]
Doesn't matter how many die.
Each team's allowed
only one alternate fighter...
Rokuyukai can fight
with Rinku and one alternate
if they find one.
You sure about that?
I am a walking rule book!
My entire life is this
Tournament! Of course I'm sure!
Yeah!!!
That means I can fight
these last two boys myself.
I think that's really ripper.
Thanks for everything, shela!
Prick.
He looks like a clown,
but there's something
dangerous there.
Everyone must be worried.
[KOENMA]
I love squid.
His spirit power's
a lot less than Zeru's,
but for some reason
I got a creepy feeling.
Watch out, you guys.
What could you be worried about?
He's the alternate fighter.
And secondly, he's a lush.
I don't know.
[HIEI THINKS] The fool may be
right. Something is foul.
Even when he
killed his teammates,
I couldn't feel his strength.
I was hoping he'd show!
Now you'll see the true
engineer of the Rokuyukai Team!
Let's go, you sooks.
I wanna get a good brawl in
before my fun wears off!
In that case, they better
all fight me at once!
So, who's gonna take him?
It hasn't been very long
since all three of
us fought our matches.
Guess we could draw
straws or something.
Hurry up!!
Chu seems extremely
impatient!
What'd you say?
I only say it as I see it.
Don't go on confusing
me with big words!
Just get me a fighter!
Right!!
Pretty tail she's got, that one.
Think I might
fall in love with her.
Urameshi Team,
present your combatant!
Well we still have
that Masked Fighter guy.
Come on man,
it's your turn!
If you can't give me someone
I'll have to disqualify!
No no, hold on a second!
I guess I'll have to
take control of this fight!
Unless of course I can
get Urameshi to wake up!
That's weird, where'd he go?
Well that's unexpected.
Indeed.
Waking up from
the smell of alcohol...
can't help but feel
a touch of home.
[KURAMA THINKS]
After all the explosions,
stink wakes him.
Hey all you stupid demons!
I've been trying to sleep
through your clever
trash-talk long enough!
And I'm ready
to kick some asses!
Great way to make
friends, Yusuke!
It's perfect! Tell 'em, kid!!
Are you certain
you're ready to fight!
You've been sleeping
for almost a day now!
Ah, give me a break!
That's why I'm takin' this jerk!
I always get some light
exercise in the morning!
Ning-nong.
[crowd chants] Kill Yusuke!
Kill Yusuke! Kill Yusuke!
Yusuke! Kill Yusuke!
When I told him
of the tournament,
his powers were
far from impressive.
Let's see how three
months of training paid off.
Gee, that's intimidating.
Never heard so many voices
hate one person so much!
But can you really be surprised!
Yusuke's become something of
a boogeyman for the apparitions.
Yeah, I guess he has beaten
a bunch of their
bad-guy role models.
But I've been helping Urameshi!
Why didn't they scream kill me?
Perhaps because you lost!
Hey now! They didn't
know that before the fight!
[KURAMA THINKS] Yusuke,
you must be cautious.
[KURAMA THINKS] Hiei
would never admit it,
but attempting
the Darkness technique
is not something
he ever desired to do.
So my Jagan Eye
may not be natural.
But it does give me
exactly what I need!
[KURAMA THINKS] In truth,
he had no other choice.
[KURAMA THINKS] To defeat
Zeru's substantial power,
Hiei had to
unveil the technique.
And it has cost him dearly.
[HIEI] I assume just
my right arm will do.
[KURAMA THINKS] The Dragon
of the Darkness Flame
is not meant to be controlled.
He may never be able
to use that arm again.
[KURAMA THINKS] If this
Chu is the true team leader,
as I suspect he is,
then his powers must be
even greater than Zeru's.
[KURAMA THINKS]
Please Yusuke. Be wise.
Stay there for a bit.
I forgot something.
Sorry shela, I gotta borrow.
Eww... Please,
don't call me that.
Um, okay, I just wanted
to set the record straight
before we get this thing going!
Right, basically it's
that I'm a really ace person,
and the only thing I suck at--
is paper rock scissors!!!
What the hell is he saying?
Uhh... Let me try to translate
for the drunkard here.
Earlier this morning,
the Rokuyukai Team
decided on their roster
through paper rock scissors.
Chu lost pathetically
and became the alternate,
but he wants you
to forget all that,
because he is number one!!!
Yeah!!!
No need to thank me-
that's why I'm here!
Wow, she's a really
perceptive person, isn't she?
Oh no, Chu is gonna
start acting dopey again!
I can feel it!
I'm strong okay!
Do you even get what
I'm trying to yab to you?
Yeah stupid, I understand!
It's not too difficult you know!
You were scared
to fight me before,
and you're blaming
it on some dumb game!
Nah! That's not right!
Didn't you hear what
the foxy was saying?
Paper, rock, sissors.
[GREEN DEMON] Oh, come on!
This substitute fighter's
a pathetic drunk!!
[CHU] Who said that?
Ratbag! I heard you!!
No it wasn't me!!
This substitute's
a pathetic drunk huh?
Take that back!
I am NOT a substitute!
I meant to do paper,
but my hands got
stuck on scissors.
Damn thing could
happen to any bloke.
Right then--now you figure
it all out perfectly, don't you?
Hey! That's my drink!
Come on! At least
let me stretch my muscles!
Nah... this is plenty great.
You don't think I can
fight either. Do ya'?
Well let me tell
you something mate...
I'm... I'm like a master
at drunken fighting.
Sui-ken technique, that's the
official name I think.
You get distracted
by my irregular moves.
Crap of craps
it's bright out here!
Listen to this
joker--he's insane!
Well I know from
school seminars
drunk driving kills people--
Maybe drunk fighting's
kinda the same thing.
This is embarrassing.
Yeah wobbly, give me a break...
So the tipsy fighting
thing might be weird
but I've still
heard of it before.
You better have somethin else
to make this a real challenge.
I didn't come all this way
just to babysit a drunk.
Then wait a minute...
You won't yabber that
once I hit my groove. 'Course,
I got to stumble into it first.
Watch his movements.
I know. He's beginning.
[NARRATOR] One obstacle
stands in the way
of defeating
the Rokuyukai Team.
Can Yusuke overcome?
Or could Chu's growing power
and bizarre fighting style
permanently seal the
Spirit Detective's fate?
[BOTAN] Hello everyone.
The Dark Tournament
is truly gearing up,
when the battle against the
Rokuyukai and Urameshi Teams
jumps into its finale!
Don't forget, we haven't
seen Yusuke in action since
his three months of training
with the psychic Genkai,
and I'm sure he'll need every
one of his learned lessons
to handle this
strange drunken threat.
Will Chu get a hangover? ?  I
leave that as a cliffhanger!
It's going to be a struggle only
the bravest can overcome,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues.
♪