♪
[NARRATOR] His name was
Amanuma. The Game Master.
A psychic child
recruited by Sensui
to help forge the apocalyptic
tunnel to Demon World.
Kurama realized the boy
had no understanding
of what he was involved in.
But to save the human race,
Kurama did the
only thing he could.
He beat the boy at his own
game and took away his life.
Now Yusuke's team moves
to the heart of the cave,
with the child's death weighing
heavily on their souls.
Get me off this boat!
[demons laughing]
[YUSUKE THINKS] Those demons are
just lining up for a shot at us.
Not the kind of crowd you want
to be stuck in a cave with.
In case you're feeling you've
done this before, don't.
The world ahead of you is
nothing like Maze Castle.
They have tapped into the
true depths of Demon World.
Ordinary humans will shrivel up
just by inhaling
its rotten wind.
We're getting to the real
grit of the film, Yusuke.
Yipee.
[SENSUI] The finale's
in about half an hour.
[explosions and guns shooting]
[VIETCONG]
Surrender!
The most repulsive part
is they weren't even
fighting for anything real.
[SENSUI] They
were killing out of fear,
of an idea that
threatened their greed.
It only gets
crueler from here.
And then the whole thing wraps
up with a rather beautiful song.
That's oddly inappropriate.
I've always thought
it symbolized hope,
which is why I've
timed to tunnel
to open when the music begins.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
What? He's saying
we only have thirty minutes?
What's the problem?
It doesn't make
sense to me.
[SEA MAN]
How's Mr. Itsuki standing up?
He does have legs.
But every time
I've seen him
since I was first
brought to the cave,
he's been sitting in that boat,
creating the tunnel.
The portal is alive now.
It's out of my control.
When the time is right,
it will manifest on its own.
Even if I wished to,
I couldn't stop it.
Kuwabara!
[RED BULL] Human flesh.
Let me taste!
Get away from their hands!
[KUWABARA]
Don't you think I'm trying??!
[SENSUI] Those must be
C-Class apparitions vying
for his attention.
Simple, characterless creatures,
governed solely
by their appetites.
[KUWABARA] I don't wanna
be eaten by C-Demons!
Hey! Let him go!
Oh, thank goodness you're back!
Give me a full report.
How did it go?
We made it half-way down,
no one on our side was hurt.
Urameshi and the others
should have reached Sensui's
hideout by this point.
Dear, I almost forgot.
Koenma's gone
into the cave, too.
Yes, we passed him on
the way back up here.
He had such a determined
look on his face.
He said he might remove
his pacifier for this.
Wow, have things
really gotten that bad?
Yes!
So tell me,
Master Genkai,
what actually happens when
Koenma takes away his pacifier?
Beats me.
[GENKAI THINKS] But I know
this: that tunnel opens soon.
Time to show your
mettle, Yusuke.
When the judgment comes,
you simple apparitions
can eat whatever you like.
Until then, don't spoil dinner.
[SENSUI] C-Class
apparitions are like seeds.
Abundant and worthless.
But one of every hundred
grows into a B-Class,
with brains and strength that
can easily surpass a human's.
Want to tell us first-hand,
Hiei and Kurama?
And then from the B-Class,
a handful take
the next big leap.
Intellect close to omnipotence,
bodies of huge size and power.
Creatures fit for
human legend...
like the Titans of Greek Myth.
I'm getting really tired
of hearing you talk.
They are the A-Class demons.
They're probably
watching us right now
from the pits of
Demon World,
waiting for the chance
to rise to glory.
Spare me the pep rally!
You're gonna kill the people
you're supposed to protect!
My job was to protect the
universe as a whole,
and that's exactly
what I'm doing.
I've been trying to
enlighten you, Yusuke.
Don't you remember
the Doctor's words?
Humanity is a disease.
Can't you guys do
this debate thing
after you're done saving me!
Killing humans can't be
that horrific to you, Yusuke.
You would've killed the Doctor
if Genkai hadn't been there.
And Kurama killed a human child.
[YUSUKE] We had to.
It was for the greater good.
And what if every
human was bad?
I don't deal with what-ifs.
Mr. Makihara.
That's Gourmet.
Oh great, does he cook?
If you can kill
Mr. Makihara right now,
I'll give Kuwabara back
to you, unharmed.
What?
Say yes! Say yes!
[SENSUI] It's your choice.
If you refuse the challenge,
I'll deflect any other attack
you make by using Kuwabara
as a human shield.
[ITSUKI THINKS]
Clever tactic, Mr. Sensui.
Control their actions by making
them believe they have a chance.
Instead of trying to
predict their next move,
you make it for them.
[Whispering] Don't
trust Sensui's word.
We'll make a push for Kuwabara
the first chance we get.
In the meantime,
just play along.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Kurama's got his cool back.
Good. We can't afford to
have him flippin' out.
Touching, Sea Man.
You want to save
Kuwabara so very badly,
because he saved you.
But at the same time,
you're terrified of
letting Sensui find out
how much your new buddy
means to you, aren't you?
What?
You're scared
Sensui will kill him
to punish you for
being a traitor.
But you've got a juicier one,
don't you Kurama?
You're a lot more torn up
from killing Game Master
than Yusuke believes.
[GOURMET] Not only
are you riddled with guilt,
you're embarrassed!
Yoko Kurama would
never be so weak.
[YUSUKE THINKS] It's like
he's liftin' thoughts
straight from our brains.
The only one I know
who can do that is...
Murota!
Bingo! That old flimsy...
Haven't you wondered
where he's been
since the hospital let him out?
It all comes at once, like
it's one big conversation.
[MAN 2] Gotta get the money.
Gotta get the money.
[WOMAN 1] Ugly creep.
How 'bout I mace you!
[MAN 3] She looked
at me! She likes me!
Eating my teammate...
That's on my ass kick list.
I'll take this one, Yusuke.
And don't argue,
I am not in the mood.
Whatever you say.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Kurama
hasn't looked that serious
since the two of us took on
those stupid ninjas.
What Captain Appetite said
really must've pissed him off.
But how can he win, when this
guy can read his thoughts?
[GOURMET THINKS] That's weird.
He's not thinking anything.
He took out Gourmet
so quickly!
I didn't see the whip
'til it was all over!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Mental note:
Never tell Kurama he's
letting his fox side down.
Rely on impulse, and not even
your thoughts can betray you.
Now come out, Toguro.
Did you think I
wouldn't notice?
I could smell your stench
since we entered the cave.
[Toguro 1 laughs]
Good, Kurama. It seems
your powers have improved
even in your human form,
though the red hair isn't
nearly as pretty the silver.
[Toguro 1 laughs]
Guess he missed his
Toguro vaccination.
Gourmet must've eaten him
to take on his powers.
Right, little Sea Man.
But much to fatty's
disappointment,
I'm the one who got
the run of the ship.
Then this entire time...
Yes, I play a real
good game of pretend.
[TOGURO 1] The fantastic
tale starts months ago,
when a man driven to insanity
by a whore and her student,
hurt his dear old brother.
I regenerated
slowly in the sea,
sending out a special energy
wave that only powerful,
and how should we say,
evil beings could hear.
I was resigned to
wait for years,
but my rescue was
surprisingly quick...
A human of all things.
But he said he could
give me my vengeance.
Isn't that how you
remember it, Sensui?
When Toguro told me about
the many achievements
of the new Spirit Detective,
Yusuke Urameshi,
I could feel the hands of the
universe tugging at my arm.
[SENSUI] In the trial
against humanity,
the defense now had
an able attorney.
At last, I could begin...
The sentencing.
Sensui gathered up a bunch
of these new psychics
for his plan, including
this brainless lump.
You see we both agreed
my regeneration
was taking too long.
I needed another body.
So, Sensui let
this ogre take me,
making him think that I
was the one being betrayed.
Merciless, really...
The poor ape had no idea
what he'd swallowed.
I'm like a cockroach
with a brain.
The best was when he
realized what was happening.
That's when he became afraid...
Fear is pleasure
enough from the outside.
But I felt his
terror from within
as I slowly took him over.
It was palpable!
[Toguro 1 laughs]
[TOGURO 1] A fear so
thick I could eat it!
That is enough.
You've survived
for far too long.
And now it ends.
Uh oh, the fox
thinks he can finish me!
But I am better
than before!
Yes--recovering from what
brother did to me
has made me stronger!
Now I can regenerate
from anything--
even if you pierce
my brain and my heart,
I'll still survive!
I'm invincible!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Great.
A Toguro brother who can't die.
And he's got the power of two
other psychics chipping in.
I'm optimistic.
Thanks to this lard I can
absorb any power I want!
I'll start with yours!
What?!
Let me guess,
he brought roach spray.
No you fool,
it's a smoke screen.
One of his older tricks.
[YUSUKE] Well, it's
definitely working.
[SEA MAN] But, how will
we know if he needs help?
[TOGURO 1 THINKS] You've
regained your calm now, Kurama.
That prized calm, that normally
makes you such a deadly foe,
able to keep your poise
and outwit anyone.
But now, with poor
Murota helping me,
it will be your doom.
[TOGURO 1 THINKS] You were so
angry during that decapitation
that you acted on impulse.
But now you're back to
your usual strategies,
so I can read along.
[KURAMA THINKS]
Hide myself in the smoke.
Keep my distance with
the aide of his smell.
Always stay behind him.
[TOGURO 1] Ah-ha!
I've found you!
Your thoughts tell me
exactly where you are!
[Toguro 1 laughs insanely]
Score!!
[TOGURO 1 THINKS]
I've done it! A fatal wound!
I'm sorry... Was that
supposed to hurt me?
So your body is tricky
like mine, is it fox?
What's wrong with you??
Why don't you scream and die??
[Toguro 1 laughing insanely]
That freak's screams
are all I hear!
Either he's beating the
hell out of Kurama,
or someone's found
where's he ticklish!
That's it,
I'm goin' in.
If it pisses off Kurama,
he can sue me.
Wait.
Why don't you look to your left.
[Toguro laughing and deranged]
[TOGURO 1] Die!
Kurama??
[Toguro screaming]
The deed has been done.
And what does that mean?
I'd sure like to know
who he's screaming at.
I've got a few creative ideas.
[Toguro screaming]
Why won't you die??
Damn you fox!
It's the Sinning Tree.
[YUSUKE] The Sinning Tree.
Sounds a bit heavy.
It ensnares your mind with
hallucinations of wickedness,
while it sucks away your life.
Wow, that's freaky.
He still thinks he
fighting you, even now,
when he's all wrapped up?
[KURAMA]
Yes.
But how did you get
him hooked up on it?
I used my Rose Whip to
plant the seed inside him
when I took off
Gourmet's skull.
[YUSUKE] Wow.
Talk about planting ahead.
[Yusuke laughs at his pun]
[HIEI] Clever.
The smoke screen wasn't only
to mask your whereabouts.
It was a catalyst for the
tree's hallucinations
to take effect.
I didn't want to leave
things to chance.
He certainly is something,
isn't he, Mr. Itsuki?
[ITSUKI THINKS]
That boy's eyes...
Immeasurable mercy and
guilt hidden deep behind...
Murota's power
can't read his mind.
The layers are too
complex, controlled.
We know only what
he wants us to.
[Toguro 1 screaming]
[TOGURO 1]Die! Die! Die!
[KURAMA] The Tree won't stop
until its host is dead.
But as you said, Toguro,
your regenerative powers
make you unable to die.
I feel so weak...
[KURAMA] You will
suffer for eternity here.
Torn between your hate,
and your agony.
And so be it, rogues like
you deserve to be dead.
[NARRATOR] Kurama's anger
has sentenced Toguro
to an eternity of suffering,
forever chasing
his foiled revenge.
But the tunnel to
Demon World is opening.
Can Yusuke's team still
save the human race?
[YUSUKE] Okay,
Earth's code red.
You've only got time to
watch one half-hour show
before you're eaten.
Which one do you choose?
And yes, that is a
giant face on the floor.
But Sensui's let Kuwabara go.
He says that special sword
wasn't first on his list,
neither was the tunnel,
though I think it's
too late to stop that.
He's got some real
head-case issues,
and the only cure is a show
down between Spirit Detectives.
Just as long as
he doesn't kill me.
'Cause I've done that once,
and it kind of sucked.
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪