♪
[NARRATOR] The Ice Apparition
Yukina, Hiei's sister,
is imprisoned by the
greedy human crime lord,
Gonzou Tarukane.
Yusuke's Spirit Detective team
has entered
Tarukane's stronghold
and defeated three infamous
demons known as the Triad.
Now, only one obstacle stands
in the way of rescuing Yukina
and closing the detective case.
The mysterious Toguro Brothers.
So I guess this
is the big finish!
I can't wait!
Hey! Toguro! Don't blow this!
Poor Tarukane.
He's going to have a conniption
before this is finished.
Can't blame him.
It's not often that your
whole financial future
is bet on one match.
Sixty-six trillion dollars!!
The loser's got
to sell everything
from their cufflinks
to their organs!
Imagine that on your back!
But Sakyo doesn't
seem to mind! Do you?
[Club men laugh]
Hey, who are those people?
They're watching us risk
our lives like it's funny!
It's awful!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Have faith, Yukina.
I'm gonna be with you soon!
If we get tired,
please allow us to tap out.
Don't listen Urameshi.
I got a feeling these
guys are up to something!
No joke.
Do you need a backrub,
Koenma sir? You seem tense.
Yusuke can beat them, right?
Well, probably not.
[KOENMA] But then, I've only
seen them fight once,
and that was many years ago.
But judging from their Spirit
Energy we shouldn't worry.
They're weaklings!
No wait.
I can't really explain it.
But my whole body's
getting this weird vibe.
It's like there's
something big in here.
[KUWABARA] I don't feel nothin.
Ready, brother?
What's that little guy doing?
I bet he's really
popular at parties.
You see my brother is able to
transform the shape of his body.
It's nothing, really.
[KUWBARA] He just
turned into a--a sword!
This is my brother's
specialty. And mine...
Oh, dear!
Further, my Spirit Energy
surrounds my brother
and makes him indestructible.
You see, the Toguro's
truly fight as one.
Whoa, you feel this?
What's up with his power? Dammit
this isn't going to be easy.
Botan step back!
I'll try!
They're fast.
Spirit Sword!
Too slow!
No!!!
Managed to step back just
enough to avoid a fatal blow.
I'm surprised you had
enough intellect to do that.
But you won't have to scrape
along the floor much longer.
Come now, brother.
Let's send him to Spirit World.
[YUSUKE] Hey forgetting
something, stupid?
Spirit Gun!!
Maybe I didn't
make myself clear!
Shot gun!!!
Son of a bitch!
Yes he must think
quite low of us, brother.
As if we can't
deflect a little energy.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it...
Guess there's just
one good way to stop him.
How about point blank?
Spirit Gun!!!
What???
All right!!
Hard to block, huh?
Don't worry, I hear
headless is in this year!
What the--?
[YUSUKE] I don't believe this!
He turns into a shield, too?
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi!!!
Did I forget to tell you?
My brother makes an
excellent defensive weapon.
You're heartless!
Yusuke!
[TOGURO 2] I was only
being a professional.
Though I was hoping
you would provide me
much more
entertainment than this!!
They're helpless!
Oh no!!
[TARUKANE] Those
Toguro's are invincible!!
I can already smell
my new money comin' in!
[Tarukane laughs]
[TARUKANE] So how you gonna
pay me the trillions, Sakyo?
Cash or credit?
[Toguro 2 laughs]
[KUWABARA THINKS]
I've got to do...
Something!
They're not going to make it!
Are they?
You certain it's them?
The brothers?
I'd never forget that face.
[KURAMA] Yusuke is
not ready for them.
[KOENMA] Well of course
he isn't! No one is!
Now why hasn't Hiei shown up?
Not that he could put a dent
in the Toguro Brothers either!
Where are you going?
I don't belong here. Voyeurism
has never been my strength.
Excuse me.
I wonder where
he's going, sir.
Over to Tarukane's
stronghold, idiot!
Oh, can he get there
in time to save Yusuke?
At this point that
might be impossible.
I just hope he can save
the human crooks from Hiei.
[HIEI] Be strong,
sister. I'm coming.
Let him go!
[TARUKANE]
Feel free to take a little
extra time with them, Toguro!
I know how all you demon
creatures are in to torturing!
Besides, my Black Black Club
could use some good dirty fun!
Why aren't ya lookin', baby?
I know it's the way you like it!
Humans getting
killed 'cause of you!
Just like that last one.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Her
memories, I can see them.
My people tell me
these Talisman Cards
can burn the skin right
off an Ice Apparition
with just a
friendly little touch!
Let's try.
Get away!!
Please. Stop!
Put the cards all over her cell!
That'll keep her
from goin' anywhere!
[GUARD] I've
brought you some food.
You know you're not going
to be in here forever, Yukina.
You know I've got a
little sister back home
who's about your age now.
[GUARD] Our chance has come!
Tarukane's left
the country on a trip.
Most of the guards are gone!
We can't! You'd be in great
danger! What if they caught you!
Come on! Can't you think
about yourself for once?
[TARUKANE] Let's show this
boy what we do to traitors.
[Toguro 2 chuckles]
[TOGURO 2] Tarukane's wrong.
I don't like torture.
At least not when
they're too pathetic
to even defend themselves.
[KUWABARA]
Disgraceful.
And you call yourself a man.
Seeing you live makes me sick.
Interesting, your Spirit
Power has increased greatly.
[Toguro 2 chuckles]
You'll be much more
fun than this carcass.
[BOTAN]
Uh... oh...
Get lost, I'll
have to deal with you
and your brother
some other time.
[KUWABARA] Tarukane's the
one I was talking to.
What? You wanna beat me up?
Sorry kid, but I'm
too expensive! Toguro!!
I want this creep
fried extra-crispy!
You heard him.
We don't have a choice.
Get out of my way!!!
Your attacks are very slow.
We can easily predict
your every move.
Kuwabara!
Hey, Urameshi.
I need a favor.
Okay Toguro!
You've had enough fun!
I want to start
collecting my money!
Come on, brother.
It's too dangerous! Let's wait!
You know how
fast they move!
This'll only get
you killed quicker!
You haven't seen what I have!
You don't know what
they've done to her!
Please!
Fine, then I've got your back!
Are you ready?
Yeah.
They want to die with honor.
Yes brother.
We will respect their wish!
The battle ends!!
Kuwabara! Here it comes!
[TOGURO 2]
Ingenious plan.
You fighters
are truly something.
What, just happened?
Simple, old friend.
You've lost the bet.
I believe that Sixty-six
trillion, fifty billion...
and two hundred million is
the total you now owe me.
Well, I know that you
founded the Black Black Club.
However, I'm afraid we
can't associate with poor men.
Bye! Have fun standing
in the bread lines!
[Club men laugh]
Now Sakashta! Move to plan B!
Start the chopper and
make sure Yukina's with us!
Nobody's gonna shut
down Gonzou Tarukane!
The game's over. You ugly fool.
I saw the Talisman Cards
hung in the tower.
That explains why I couldn't
find her with my Jagan Eye.
But, you can't run
from death forever.
Wait! I don't know
who the hell you are.
But if it's money
you're after. We can talk!
Listen here.
That broad behind
you makes jewels
you wouldn't
even believe!
I could pump
millions from her!
Oh goodness! Hiei!
Hiei's here?!
We have to do something!
Regardless of what
Tarukane deserves,
Hiei is forbidden to
take human life...
He'll be punished severely!
Perfect.
[YUSUKE] Stop it Hiei!
Don't kill him!!
They're just afraid of justice.
[YUKINA] No!!!
Please!
No more. I beg of you!
Are you crazy?
Is this not the
man who tormented you
and made you his slave?
He is, I have to bear that.
But taking his life can't wash
away all that he's done to me.
It will only bring more pain.
Just more nightmares.
Please no more!
I can't take it!
Understood,
I won't make you cry.
He's too worthless for that.
How can I ever thank you?
Looks like things
have turned out okay.
Yeah.
You seem familiar.
But I'm not sure why.
Who are you?
No one...
[HIEI] Just a member
of the team.
Oh no! I forgot
about them!
[KURAMA] I guess I didn't
need to come here, after all.
How long have you
been standing there.
Long enough, right?
Why don't you want
to tell the girl?
She deserves to
know she has a brother.
She deserves to be happy.
[KURAMA] I thought
the two were the same.
This is the way I want it.
Everybody's okay.
But, why don't you
go see him to make sure.
Yukina!
Stay still, I can use some of
my power to heal your wounds.
Hey, let's go see
what's happening upstairs.
Oh yes, of course!
Good old upstairs!
I'm sorry, you were
hurt because of me.
[KUWABARA]
Your burn.
You got that from
Tarukane, I saw it.
I'm the one who
should be saying sorry.
For not saving you earlier.
[KUWABARA] You probably
hate humans, don't you?
[YUSUKE] Wow! We've
got a full house, huh?
[KUWABARA]
I can't blame you for it.
There's lots of
stupid humans out there.
Heck, most the guys I know.
But there's, there's
some good ones, too.
Don't hate us! I can
show you the good side!
Don't worry.
Really, I like humans.
Very much.
Thank you.
[YUSUKE] Well that wraps
my casework work for now,
but I hope everyone's
ready the next one,
because you haven't
seen anything yet!
A giant new adventure
is about to begin,
filled with a couple
villains you know already,
and about thirty
more that you don't!
I'll have to take a trip
to my favorite psychic fossil,
after a special visitor
shows up on my home turf
with a very deadly threat!
It'll be training, fighting,
and plenty of my killer jokes,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪