♪
[NARRATOR] In his
determination to forge a tunnel
between the Demon
and Human worlds,
former Spirit Detective
Shinobu Sensui is waging war
with Yusuke Urameshi
and his friends.
Sensui fired the opening shot,
striking Yusuke's apartment
with his powerful
Reikou-Resshuuken,
attempting to both assassinate
his own captured henchman,
Sea Man,
and to weaken Yusuke's team
by endangering their friends.
The attacked continued
on several fronts,
successfully splitting
up Yusuke's team
and distracting
them long enough
to capture their
true objective,
the one person capable
of tearing apart
the barrier to
Demon World--Kuwabara!
Yeah!
You're drivin' on the wrong side
of the road you half-pint loony!
I can make a right on
red, right? Hold on!
[Kuwabara cries out]
[drivers dismayed and talking]
[YUSUKE] Hey!
Stupid rubber-neckers!
Get outta my way!
[SNIPER]
Let's roll.
[KOENMA] That Reikou-Resshuuken
sure packs a whollop!
[GENKAI] Yes.
Too much for Yusuke,
even if he is on
a "serious" binge.
So what's his strategy?
Why aim for the apartment when
Yusuke was standing right there?
[KOENMA] Must've been
targeting Sea Monkey, again.
Sensui certainly is
persistent and goal-oriented.
I'll give him that.
Just two of the many qualities
I avoided when I hired Yusuke.
Drama prince.
Fiat lux!
[KOENMA] You do
know a lot of tricks.
Hiding in a compound
can do that to you.
[KOENMA]
Oh my!
Botan!
[KOENMA] Hey,
are you all right?
I think we should
take that as a "no."
Okay, wallflower...
You just sat there
on your sorry ass
watching this poor
girl suffer?
What's wrong with you?
But what if... I don't know.
I thought I was your enemy!
Set her on the floor,
face down, gently.
[KOENMA]
Right.
Ugh!
I'm sorry. I'm so confused.
I work for Sensui.
[KOENMA]
Does he know that?
'Cause from where
I've been standing
it looks like he's
trying to terminate
more than your employment.
Puu!
Puu?
What is it?
Puu flew off!
[GENKAI]
All better.
Oh Genkai, thank goodness.
I'm so glad you're here!
Why might
that be?
Not Botan!
Hold off the water works.
She'll be conscious in a minute.
[KURAMA] Master Genkai.
I hope there's
strength for one more.
[KOENMA]
Shizuru!
This whole rag-tag team is
falling into pieces aren't we?
Just put her
down on the bed.
I'm up! Hey, when did
all of you get here?
Glad you're okay.
Huh? And why
wouldn't I be?
Your formerly fractured back is
one good reason I can think of.
[KOENMA]
When we came in,
we found you lying under
this very heavy bookshelf!
That's a silly
place for me to be!
[KOENMA] You don't remember
how you were crushed?
Seems that would make
an impression.
[BOTAN] I don't know. Doesn't
sound like something I'd do.
I know. She got trapped while
she was trying to save me!
When the bookshelf
started to topple,
she shoved me
out of the way,
and she got crushed
instead of me!
I don't understand.
It's not how he said.
First Kuwabara
and now you do it!
Why do you people
keep saving my life?
[SEA MAN] It's not how
he said. Why?
'Cause that's just
what people do.
[BOTAN] Ooh, but I think I'm
starting to remember.
[Botan and Sea Man cry out]
[BOTAN]
Look out!
So that's what happened.
I just acted without thinking.
[KOENMA]
I'd believe that.
I like to think
it's a good trait
not to overthink everything!
I'd say it is like that
for a great many people
when another being's life
is put into jeopardy.
Well, that's never been the case
in my experience growing up,
and not on that videotape!
[KOENMA] Chapter Black
is a one sided argument.
It's part of a set, never
meant to be seen alone.
No! That's all a big lie!
[KURAMA] Mitarai,
I understand your dilemma.
You've witnessed the worst
mankind has to offer,
in life and on tape.
But if your eyes remain open
you'll see the best, all around.
Speaking of, has
anybody seen Yusuke?
I'm not goin' too fast for
you, am I, baby doll?
Oh! I love it!
Go faster!
[horn honking]
[YOUNG MAN] That ass
thinks he can pass me!
Suck my dust!
I swear that never
happens to me.
It's just a one-time thing.
That pickup must have
one huge engine on it.
I got smoked by a
guy on a bicycle.
Just take me home.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Sensui,
you made a big mistake
messing with one of my friends.
And I'm gonna kick your ass
twice as hard for it!
Hold on to what you got!
Drivin' a real
car's pretty much like
the racing game
at the arcade.
[KUWABARA] You've
never driven before?
Of course not, dumbass!
I'm only eleven years old!
Aw give the poor backseat
driver a break, Game Master.
He's probably just
a little on edge
because his seat belt's
fastened too tight.
[Gourmet laughs]
[GOURMET] I wanna
see his full power,
even if I have to
squeeze it up out of him
like that last stubborn
glob of toothpaste in the tube.
[Gourmet laughs]
[Kuwabara cries out]
Please, Gourmet,
give him a break.
Your torturing my
ears as well.
[KUWABARA] Why don't
you just kill me?
You fail to see your
destiny, Kuwabara.
You're going to help us put
our cursed race to an end.
And you don't understand who
I am. I'll never help you.
But you're meant to.
Don't you see?
That's why you've been
given these powers.
The universe wants human
atonement just as badly as I.
You're pitching the same
crap you did to Mitarai.
But I don't bend!
Silly me.
I must've given you
the false impression
we need your
consent to help us.
We have other ways of
making your power ours.
Just ask your friend,
elder Toguro.
Huh? What do you mean? That
freak's been dead for months!
Look down at your bondage.
Don't those fingers
bring back memories?
Aw, I do remember!
Another few inches
and I can pick out your heart!
Oh man! I knew these
creepy fingers were familiar.
But how can your guy
have Toguro's hands?
Because he swallowed him.
The same way he's going
to swallow you, Kuwabara,
as soon as your
power is completed.
No, I won't let you!
You crazy freak!
[Gourmet laughs]
[KUWABARA]
Let me go!
Oh, it's mouthwatering.
He's getting tenderized.
Uh oh. Is he a world
champion cyclist or what?
Damn it.
[KUWABARA] Help!
I'm in a pickup truck
full of psychic cannibals!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Hold on,
Kuwabara! I'm coming for you.
Urameshi!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I just hope
these wheels don't melt.
He's got some kind of iron-man
guts chasin' us on a bicycle.
Hey boss, think we
should shake this loon?
That's not necessary.
He's playing into my
contingency plan.
Just let him continue
to follow us.
He will be dealt with.
[KUWABARA] What, you couldn't
find a little girl's scooter?
[YUSUKE]
I don't know?
You couldn't go a week
without getting snagged
by the forces of evil?
Consider this your first
and only chance to
get out of this thing alive!
Now pull over or I'll
run you off the road!
He can't possibly do that
with a bicycle can he?
I don't know,
but if we don't
lose him quickly
he'll follow us to our secret,
ex-secret hideout.
I told you I have
it under control.
[YUSUKE]
So close.
Prick!
Whoa! Weird.
What'd you do to me?
I just marked
my territory Yusuke.
Well, that's gross.
Death Print Bull's-Eye.
[YUSUKE] Oh great!
I always wanted tattoos.
[SNIPER] Those, my
friend, are targets.
For what?
For me to hit of course,
and at any time and at any range
without me having to aim.
Oh, and with any
ammunition I so choose,
like these rocks for instance.
Hey... nice catch.
Now as long as you never
ever let your guard down,
you have nothing to worry about.
Freak.
Come now, let's not
resort to name-calling.
My proper name is Kaname Hagiri,
but my victims call me Sniper.
[NARRATOR] Kaname Hagiri.
Codename: Sniper.
His Territory encompasses
a five hundred meter radius.
Once he has marked
his victim's body
with the Death
Print Bull's-Eye,
he can shoot anything at that
target without ever missing.
From this moment on you'll
never again be able
to go anywhere without
looking over your shoulder.
Enjoy living in fear Yusuke,
while you still can.
Hey, get back here!
You don't scare me!
Welcome back.
What about Kazuma?
I'm afraid he has been captured
by Sensui and his men.
I'm sorry. We made a valiant
effort but could not stop them.
Don't beat
yourself up over it.
If I hadn't have been
standing under falling debris,
I could've warned
all of you that Kazuma was
the one they wanted
this whole time.
But why is Kuwabara on
everybody's A-List now?
Not that I'm jealous.
Because of what he can do.
Sensui needs him to
carry out the plan.
Kuwabara is a lot stronger,
a lot more important,
than any of you seem
to give him credit for.
[SEA MAN]
After all, he beat me.
And in that fight,
he awakened a new power...
...the power to slice
through dimensions,
cut down Territories,
psychic barriers--
the very power Mr.
Sensui was seeking.
You're killing me.
If Kuwabara can do that,
and they've got him,
they can crack
the Kekkai Barrier
we raised to seal
off Demon World.
Then all hell will
break loose, literally.
There'll be no
stopping the A-Class
or, heaven-forbid, S-Class
Demons from destroying mankind.
I trust Yusuke with a lot
these days, but not this.
Then we must
come to his aid.
[GENKAI]
If we can find him.
We'll round up Kaitou and
Yana while we're at it.
Yes.
[GENKAI]
Keiko. Shizuru...
You stay here in case Yusuke
comes back looking for us.
Okay.
[SEA MAN] What about me?
Is there anything
I can help you do?
You should search your soul
for the answer to that.
You are free to go with us
or you are free to be our foe.
But if you chose
the latter,
the next time we meet
I'll show you no mercy.
You must choose what you
believe, and make your stand.
[GENKAI] Let's go.
Oh god! What am I
supposed to do with this?
How 'bout pretend for a
second that you're a man...
And hurry it up.
[SHIZURU] Make your
choice. Are we that bad?
[KOENMA] Now which way
are we supposed to go?
[GENKAI]
Beats me.
[KOENMA] We have no
idea where Yusuke went.
[SEA MAN] Wait up!
Please wait for me.
Or is it too late now for me
to go along with you guys?
[KURAMA] It's never too late to
reform one's ways. Trust me.
Welcome to our team.
[footfalls]
[Yusuke breathing heavy]
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Where are you, Sniper?
[Leaves rustling]
Just the wind.
[birds cawing in a panic]
[Yusuke cries out]
[YUSUKE]
Stupid birds!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Man.
I hate the countryside.
Enjoy living in fear Yusuke,
while you still can.
Oh screw up!
Now show your face you
big some of a bitch!
[HIEI]
Hmm.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
He's around here somewhere.
I can feel his eyes on me.
Just the wind again.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Sniper's ride.
Then he really is nearby.
But where? And when?
[YUSUKE THINKS] I had to ask.
Well, don't I feel special?
My own private, personal,
localized meteor shower!
Keep 'em coming. I'm just
starting to get a good workout.
Oh please, more rocks?
Come on! This guy really
needs a creativity consultant.
Those aren't rocks!
[NARRATOR] Yusuke has
found himself in the
merciless Territory of Sniper.
And as he runs for his life,
Genkai and the rest of the
team try to track him down.
Can Yusuke escape
Sniper's endless barrage,
reach Sensui
and save Kuwabara,
not to mention the
entire human race?
[YUSUKE] Didn't this Sniper
guy's mom ever tell him
not to play with sharp objects
'cause he'd poke his eyes out,
or more importantly,
someone else's?
I mean, I've been told I
have deep penetrating eyes
but I'd like it if they
weren't penetrated themselves!
And hey, speaking of,
is anybody wondering what
ole' Three Eyes was doing
lurking in the
trees back there?
Find out next time
on Yu Yu Hakusho,
which is heading your way
faster than this speeding
oil tanker is riding my ass.
Don't you want to see how
I get out of this one?
[Screams]
Don't you?
♪