♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi and his crew
face the Dr. Ichigaki Team
in the Dark
Tournament's second round.
But an ambush on the
outskirts of the island
by one of the doctor's
deformed creations
has kept Hiei and Kurama
from reaching the arena.
Yusuke, Kuwabara,
and the Masked Fighter
have been forced to fight
the mind-controlled humans
in a three-on-three match.
But with their opponents
displaying disastrous power,
and Yusuke unable to
fire his Spirit Gun,
it's a desperate struggle
just to stay alive.
[crowd cheers]
Damn. If you get
any good ideas Kuwabara.
Feel free to share.
That's right my boys.
Follow your design.
Kill them! Massacre!
[YUSUKE]
This is gonna suck.
Angel Blades!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Jump!
[MASKED FIGHTER] Those Angel
Blades are the only attacks
Yusuke and Kuwabara can see.
[MASKED FIGHTER] The blades
come first as a distraction,
then they surprise
with the invisible attacks.
It's a brilliant pattern.
All three of their team members
are fighting evenly with Yusuke.
Wouldn't you call that
surprising, Koenma sir?
Yes I would.
Which makes the fact
that they're actually
beating him a real kicker.
[BLUE OGRE] Beating
him sir? Oh shoot.
[ALL] Kill... Kill... Kill...
Kill... Kill... Kill...
Uh--hold on a minute guys.
Are you sure
you want to do that?
I know on the
inside you don't.
[MASKED FIGHTER]
What are you doing?
Get out of the way! Hurry!
One at a time!
What is wrong with
the Urameshi Team?
Have they forgotten
how to throw a punch?
How to do anything but run like
sissies?! Give us some offense!
Oh Yusuke what's
the matter? Fight back!
They're going to
lose this one.
It'd be a hard match even
if Yusuke and my brother
were fighting with
everything they have.
But they're not--they just
feel too sorry for these guys.
Sorry for what?
I can imagine the
fun my robot's having
right now with Hiei and Kurama--
Against their statistics
his percentage of victory
was just over 80 percent. Yes.
[DR. ICHIGAKI] All my
inventions are doing splendidly.
My Verrucae most of all.
Millions of microelectronics
pumping through their blood,
controlling the nearby cells.
The circulatory system
reaches a human's every inch.
Control the blood,
and the body is yours.
[DR. ICHIGAKI] I can't help
myself! I have to see it again!
What a lovely number!
[M-3] Kill... Kill... Kill...
[M-3]
Kill.
[M-3] Kill!
Grizzly Claw!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Got me.
The masked guy!
He really saved me.
In a selfless act unprecedented
in the Dark Tournament,
the Masked Fighter has
taken a direct hit from M-3
in order to save his teammate!
Naturally I'll go check on the
gruesomeness of his injuries!
Mankind killing itself.
This year's tournament
is turning out to be
interesting, isn't it?
Yes. You should
read our history books.
We humans have always
found brutalizing each other
to hold a certain charm.
[ALL]
Kill.
Do it now!
Come on you guys,
just snap out of it!
You still have your feelings!
You don't have to
listen that doctor!
[M-1]
Do it now!
Give my invention
its credit, dear boy.
It's scientifically impossible
for a person to resist
the control of the verruca.
It's zero percentage!
Try your feely
mumbo jumbo all you want,
the fact is I'm in
control and I make them kill!
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs]]
Alright boys that's enough!
Get in there and fight!
I don't care if
they're under control!
They're still going to kill you!
They shouldn't have let it
happen in the first place!
You didn't see what I saw.
They're good people, Botan.
They'd never do this if
they were given the choice.
[KUWABARA] When the
doctor found them,
they were really
upset and vulnerable.
Quite possibly I'm the
answer to your prayers.
A doctor who can alleviate
your poor master's disease.
Don't toy with us!
It's free.
[KUWABARA] All they wanted
was to be with their master.
Ichigaki acted like
it was a little thing,
and then they'd
be back together.
You might not
be interested.
Tell us! If there's anything
we can do to save him, we will!
I would like to use this
gentleman. And this one.
And you, my good sir,
over there as subjects
for a little experiment.
I bet he never told them
they'd be forced to murder,
and that they'd never see their
master again! It wasn't fair!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Stupid troll doctor!
Ugly people shouldn't be
allowed to smile that much!
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs insanely]
There's gotta be
a way to reach 'em!
Don't just stand there! Move!!
Invisible Slash!
[MASKED FIGHTER] I suppose
your sympathy's admirable.
But what do you dimwits plan
to achieve by not fighting.
They'll still be controlled.
And you'll be dead.
He's...
...a she!
[KOTO]
A shocking turn of events!
Damage from the recent attack
has given us a glimpse at the
Masked Fighter's true identity!
It's a young woman with
brown eyes, and pink hair!
But who could she be?
Weird.
She's gorgeous!
What's going on sir?
I had my bets on it
being the old psychic Genkai!
Who's this strange
young lady?
Well, people, I'm shocked!
This fight couldn't
get any weirder!
I think that's the
missing combatant, M-5,
from the Dr. Ichigaki Team!
Dropping from the sky
and into the stadium wall!
Forget what I said before!
Now this fight
couldn't get any weirder!
Whoa, I wonder
where he came from.
What now?
My robot! Gatasubal!
What's happened to you?!
Hey guys, you're late.
The missing members
of the Urameshi Team
have appeared as well!
Hiei and Kurama, can you
tell us where you've been?
Sorry. A thirty-foot killing
machine wanted a word with us.
M-5 told us everything.
I'm relieved your
three are still alive.
Those Verrucae on the
human fighters' backs
are the source of
Dr. Ichigaki's mind control.
And in their present state
I'm afraid it'd be
fatal to remove them.
[KURAMA] The three are
completely innocent.
They didn't know the
implants would control them.
They were told it
was blood research.
I told you guys!
That no-good liar!
And that's not the
extent of it, I'm afraid.
Seems the doctor caused
their master's illness
in the first place.
[DR. ICHIGAKI] It sounds
so amusing when they say it!
Go ahead, tell the
world my ingenious scheme!
It will make no difference
on the result of this fight!
I can't take this Urameshi!
He doesn't have a soul!
Listen to that
power-tripping laugh!
The guy thinks he can
use people however he wants!
[DR. ICHIGAKI] Your unscientific
minds are so trivial.
Fully blind to
the larger picture.
So maybe I did infect Mitamuru!
Maybe I lied to get their
bodies and maybe I enjoyed it.
Who cares!
Behind every lab discovery
are a few poisoned rats!
Shut up Ichigaki! You're
full of crap and you know it!
You don't care about
this science stuff!
You're just trying
to win the tournament!
Means to an end,
boy, means to an end!
I have no expectation
for winning this!
I'm sure these three will be
killed long before the finals!
I only need them
to win this match
so I can have Yusuke's body!
What?!
They're strong
but they have nothing like
the potential you have, Yusuke.
I'll probably dispose of
them myself once I get you!
You what?!
Damn it... That's it!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Stop and think, boys!
He's manipulating your emotions.
You're losing what
little focus you have!
[YUSUKE] I don't care
if it's a trap or not!
His troll face
is meeting my foot!
YOU MONSTER!!!
Oh my! The mad doctor's words
have thrown Yusuke and
Kuwabara into a blinding rage!
They're abandoning
their true opponents
to bludgeon Ichigaki instead!
Now!
I'm sorry guys,
but they've already agreed
on a three-on-three fight.
Step in the ring now and
your whole team forfeits!
You're a heartless mess,
you know that!
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs]
Please, don't blame her.
I'm the one who got your apish
friends to accept those terms.
Naturally.
Hey Kuwabara, I think
doc just called you apish.
Yeah, like I need another
reason to pummel his head in!
Give me a break! You're
still protecting this guy?
Come on guys, at
least say something!
You heard the doctor himself!
He doesn't care about--
Have you
learned nothing yet?!
Nothing you say can matter!
Their old selves
aren't in control!
As the blood from the Verruca
enters the subject's skull,
the microelectronics alter
the brain's chemistry!
Their entire
personality is changed!
[DR. ICHIGAKI] This
isn't a simple hypnosis,
or one
suggested command.
I'm talking about a constant
voice in their head
at every waking moment,
controlling them
from the inside.
They're not protecting me
because I've given a command.
Their new brain actually
wants to! You see!
Therein lies the
beauty of my invention.
They don't have to listen
to me or anyone else!
The command has become
a part of who they are!
So kill them if you can!
Their humanity is already dead!
I can't! That isn't true!
I know there's something more!
Right there...!
That image--I see it again!
It's stuck in my eyelids!
Every time I blink it's there!
Wait... Wait, I
understand now, Urameshi!
It's not a dream,
it's a message.
[KUWABARA] Ichigaki's wrong.
Their old selves haven't
been erased--just covered up!
After all I've said you're still
clinging to pathetic hopes.
Avoid anything as long as it
makes you feel better, right?
Well then let your compassion
lead you all the
way to your graves!
[ALL]
Kill... Kill... Kill!
Move!
[KOTO] The Urameshi Team
is forced to retreat again!
Wait a second! Kuwabara
isn't moving this time!
He's decided to hold his ground
against the
death-dealing attackers!
What the--?
These guys chose me
to send their message to.
I'm all they've got!
And now, I have to accept
my responsibility as a man!
What is he talking about?
This is not wise!
Why doesn't he run?
Brother!
Okay guys, I hear
what you're sayin' to me!
But you've got to
tell me how to help!
Angel Blades!
Kuwabara!
No!
Please!
I know it feels like
you're beat but you're not!
This is still your body! Please!
Think about your
master, everything you--
[YUSUKE] Enough of this!
I'm coming in to help!
No--stay back! I'm the
only one who needs to do this!
This is for you!
Kuwabara!
Please, no!
Kuwabara goes down!
His plea thrown in his face
with a sensational
three-on-one attack!
[DEMON FAN]
Now kill the rest of them!
Did you see that sir?
He just stood there and
let himself be railroaded.
The boy was too kind-hearted
for this Tournament!
[KOENMA] There comes a time
when everyone has to stand
up for what they believe in.
Kuwabara may just have
stood on the wrong foot.
Stupid.
Sorry, I tried.
How could you do that!
You're the bastards
who asked him for help?!
Tears of blood?
Kill... Kill us...
[ALL]
Kill... Kill... Kill us.
Kill us... Kill us... Kill...
us... Kill us... Kill us...
What is this? Actually feel
guilty now? When it's over?!
[MASKED FIGHTER] No Yusuke. It's
not over. For Kuwabara, anyway.
They've deliberately missed
his vital points. He will live.
Amazing! Kuwabara's
plea really worked!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Not completely.
Their true selves have awoken,
but they're not in control.
I'm afraid this surfacing of
emotion will not last for long.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
These guys must be in
a war with their own bodies.
And they're losing.
[ALL]
Kill... Kill us... Kill!
Really! The human's
emotional brain
is the only part throwing
a wrench in my socket.
Millions of microelectronics
sending control through
their neural paths,
and yet that feeling crap
manages to poke out its head!
The Verrucae will soon fix that!
This is the one chance
you guys get to talk
and all you can
say is to kill you?
It must be hell in there.
Stupid doctor thinks
he can torture like that!
No way!
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
Yusuke's maximum Spirit Power
is skyrocketing! Finally!
His emotions have
broken the wall.
Don't take this personally!
Grizzly Claw!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I can see it!
[YUSUKE THINKS] It's just like
an energy bomb in his hand!
That's easy enough!
Angel Blades!
[YUSUKE THINKS]  Only two of
the blades are real!
The others must be
tricks to confuse us!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
And jerk number three--
Looks like we're featuring
the old energy javelin!
Invisible Slash!
[YUSUKE THINKS] You know,
it's a hell of a lot easier
when you can see the attacks!
Absolutely amazing! The fight's
been flipped onto its backside!
Suddenly wonder-boy Yusuke
is taking on this
whole team by himself!
[DR. ICHIGAKI]
But, I don't understand.
How can a person's
ability to sense energy
attacks increase
midway through a fight?
This isn't in my calculations!
No worries, let me just
refigure the equation here.
Ah--Here we go!
Fifty-two point seven-t--
Fifty-two point
seven two five percent?
[KURAMA] Percentages
are for poker, fool.
You can factor strengths
and stamina doctor--
I'll give you that.
But determining the
true heart of a person
is quite a different thing.
Buzz off! I must have
punched a wrong number!
What's the delay you
lab rats! Destroy him!
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
His right hand is emitting
energy almost
out of instinct!
His Spirit Gun will
be stronger than ever!
I've never seen anyone
increase his power so quickly!
Lucky for you guys I'm pretty
good at avoiding my feelings.
Otherwise I'd be getting
sick on myself right now
for what I've gotta do.
I'd say this is gonna hurt
me more than it hurts you.
But I don't like to lie.
[YUSUKE] Yeah, that's right.
The doctor and his
walking torture chambers
have got me pretty pissed off.
And I'm about to unleash
a gigantic Spirit Gun
to blast 'em out
of their misery.
Unless, of course,
some genius can figure out
a another way to stop them--
besides making me the
doc's next experiment.
And that's only half the fun!
Seems there's one last player
to step up for the other team,
and he used to be such
an adorable little troll!
It's a finale you
don't want to miss,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪