[NARRATOR]
Finally reaching Sensui's lair,
Kurama mercilessly killed
the psychic Gourmet
to free Kuwabara,
but a surprise emerged.
The elder Toguro had
actually taken over Gourmet
from the inside,
and sought revenge.
Regeneration made Toguro
unable to die,
so Kurama condemned him
to an eternity of pain
in the arms of
the strange Sinning Tree.
Now, with the tunnel to demon
world moments from completion,
the final battle begins.
[TOGURO 1 groaning]
I'll kill you!
Why won't you die?!
[TORGURO 1 groaning]
Such a malignant soul
will never accept the truth.
The more he lashes
out in his mind,
the more painful the Sinning
Tree's effects become.
It hurts!
No! I'll show you!
[TOGURO 1 screaming]
[TOGURO 1]
I'll tear you apart!
[screaming]
Such is the plant's nature;
only your own sins can hurt you.
Uh, Kurama, if I ever did
somethin' that pissed you off,
I'm sorry.
Me too.
[TOGURO 1 yelping]
[TOGURO 1]
You're cheating me!
You can summon your friend now.
[KUWABARA muffled yelling]
Now only two remain
in our path.
Right.
Your end of the world
party's dwindling, Sensui,
and I trust you don't
wanna be plant food.
Give Kuwabara back to us
like you promised.
[SENSUI] Ha. No need
to get heated, Yusuke.
I've kept my word. He's no
longer in my possession.
What?
--No...
--But I never saw him move.
You bastard.
Look, there.
[YUSUKE] Kuwabara! What the
hell are you doing over there?!
[ITSUKI chuckles]
Jeez, not bein' able to
tell you guys how to fight,
that's worse than dyin'!
Stay focused.
How did you get over here?
[KUWABARA]
I don't know really.
One minute I was
sittin' in the boat,
the next thing I was
all mixed around. Dizzy.
Soon as I got my wits
together, I was here.
Did you see something?
[KUWABARA]
Well, uh--
Look, Kurama.
[YUSUKE, KUWABARA gasp]
[KUWABARA]
Yeah, maybe something like that.
[YUSUKE] Okay, another
thing on my "weird" list
just got checked off.
[ITSUKI chuckling]
[YUSUKE]
Yup. There goes another one!
[SEA MAN, KUWABARA yelping]
[YUSUKE screaming]
[YUSUKE groaning]
[YUSUKE]
Stupid.
[ITSUKI]
I'll leave you two alone.
[gasps]
[grunts] I dunno know what
you did with my friends,
but I tell you now. For every
one you hurt, I'm taking a limb.
You're misunderstanding it.
Your friends
haven't been touched.
I'm not interested
in their fates.
I just don't want distractions.
[YUSUKE]
So... then it's time.
Dear... they've been
down there forever.
What's taking them so long?
[GENKAI] Patience, Botan,
it's the end of the world.
You can't just flip
it off with a switch.
I know...
We have to trust
the weapons we've got,
and cross our fingers.
[KOENMA]
Keep holding him, Yusuke.
Your cavalry's coming.
Uh.
[KOENMA] I'll just hope
Kurama didn't run out of seeds.
[SEA MAN]
What is this place?
Looks like the
dark bowels of Hell.
You mean that?
Well, guys, wherever we are,
I would really, really
like to be untied.
We are in the bowels
of something, Kurama.
I'd say it's a Dark Soul.
Dark Soul? What's that?
Sounds terrible.
[HIEI]
An old apparition.
It lives beneath
the surface of the earth,
collecting human trash.
But we were not
swallowed by chance.
Someone else must be
controlling this creature.
--[ITSUKI] Creature?
--[gasps]
[ITSUKI]
Please, call him Ura-Otoko.
That's his proper name.
He's my pet.
I tamed him myself.
Itsuki.
You're not truly
a human, are you?
Do you think a human
could'ave produced that tunnel?
[NARRATOR]
Yaminate.
The "Devil with Six Hands".
This rare, super-sensory breed
of demon has six arms,
which can move independently
of their master.
He is an actual Yaminate.
Ta.
I don't care if he's a unicorn,
let's start this fight!
We'll see how special he is
when I'm smashin' him.
[ITSUKI]
Calm your anger, Kuwabara.
I'm not here to fight.
[KUWABARA]
What?
Then why the heck did you
bring us to this freaky place?
We sightseein'?
'Cause I've seen enough.
[ITSUKI] I'm protecting the
fight between our detectives.
[KUWABARA]
Huh?
[ITSUKI] Though we are
on different sides,
we serve the same
cause, do we not?
Protecting this battle
through its completion,
without bickering
amongst ourselves.
Yusuke deserves it.
Sensui deserves it.
Ta! He doesn't deserve bunk.
You tell me one good
feature that traitor has.
One decent thing
that makes you follow
his end-of-the-world crusade.
[chuckles]
He has everything.
Sensui can be violent,
courageous, spiritually pure,
and even fragile.
He can be a graceful
spokesman with charisma
to bring anyone to his side.
Indeed, I have been drawn to his
aura like a moth to the flame
since the very first
moment that we met.
[ITSUKI]
I first saw him in the darkness,
forging a path of light.
I would follow him for
hours, unbeknownst to him.
Just watching him work
made me feel alive.
[whimpering]
[SENSUI grunts]
[DEMON screaming]
[DEMON groaning]
[ITSUKI]
My obsession grew.
I began helping
from the shadows,
killing apparitions
who wanted him dead.
[ITSUKI] Of course, when he
caught me, he wasn't grateful.
I was just another
demon to judge.
[ITSUKI groaning]
[SENSUI] Do you have anything
to say before you die?
If it's possible,
let me have one more day
to live, Mr. Sensui.
[SENSUI]
Why should I?
Tomorrow, my favorite television
show airs its final episode,
and I'd like to see how it ends.
[ITSUKI chuckling]
[SENSUI laughing]
[SENSUI] You're the first
demon to ever make me laugh.
And so he let me live.
I suppose I was his first step
in realizing his relationships
of good and evil could not
be so... traditionally defined.
You mean there's all kinds
of apparitions, good and bad?
[ITSUKI] Who could have dreamed
that a hunter I admired
for physical prowess,
this killer of killers,
could also be warm.
Compassionate. Intellectual.
Open to broadening
his view of the world.
Yes, I admit my attraction
was not purely academic.
I always wished he
would become my lover.
Okay, you can stop right there.
I don't think my ears
are old enough for this.
If you truly care for Sensui,
then help us stop him.
This path he's chosen
will destroy him as well.
[ITSUKI]
You can't save the damned.
Don't you see? I'm expecting
him to act terribly,
and hurt people.
Even to his own end,
there's no way to stop it.
Why not?
Because Sensui must follow
his soul's true course.
Drop ink on the finest
snow white paper
and it will inevitably
absorb into black.
Its purity demands it.
Tainted men have immunities.
Black does not absorb black.
Sensui's change is but
proof of his perfection,
and you cannot stop him.
The ability to
prevent this demise
would show purity did not exist.
Purity is worth the world.
And worth it ending.
[growls] You're really
making me nauseous.
All of your fancy lies.
You can't excuse him!
He's a monster, cut and dry.
[ITSUKI] You're not
listening to me, Kuwabara.
I'm not excusing him.
Then what the heck
do you call that?!
[ITSUKI] Sensui is indeed
becoming depraved.
But I must let that happen.
Because I know, whatever
he does to the world,
even if it kills us all,
is what we deserve.
You should know I will kill
you if I can, without remorse.
You will do what
you must, Kurama,
but whether I live or die,
the battle will not be affected.
My Ura-Otoko will
make sure of that.
You see, I'm the only
one who can control him.
If we kill him,
I get the first hit.
I'm afraid these surrounding
are making us stir-crazy.
Let's have a better view.
[KUWABARA, SEA MAN gasp]
Simply looking at me fills you
with fury, right, detective?
You know, Yusuke, if you
continue this work
as Spirit World's agent,
you'll eventually share my fate.
The things you see
grow a canker on your soul,
and you cannot heal the sore.
Do you want to know why?
Because the canker keeps
growing and consumes you.
The evil you're chasing
becomes who you are.
Just picture where
you were a year ago,
before any of your noble
detective work began.
Would you ever have imagined
murdering another human being?
Now your team's killed
three in under a week.
Imagine ten more years
on that steep decline.
Those were all set-ups.
You fixed it so that killing
them was our only choice.
[chuckles]
We humans can justify
anything, can't we?
That's how our
corruption begins.
That's why I like demons.
They make no excuses.
They accept their wickedness.
Just as you will, in time.
[YUSUKE]
No!
[SENSUI] Remember this always,
Yusuke, if you survive this day.
Your immorality
is your strength.
The moment you accept it,
your confusion will subside.
No longer filled
with guilt and anger
over what you're becoming,
you'll focus more
on your fighting.
You'll at last have your peace.
[SENSUI laughing]
[YUSUKE]
Wrong!
[KUWABARA] Yeah! Now that's
a statement punch!
[YUSUKE]
Maybe there have been times
when I've been pissed
and hated things,
but it wasn't from this work.
My dad's a no-show, my mom's
a lush, and school sucks,
but this job is the one damn
thing I've ever been good at.
And if all the crap in my life
hasn't screwed me up yet,
then neither will this.
And neither will you.
[laughing]
You take things so
seriously sometimes.
[grunts]
[SENSUI] You see?
That's precisely what I mean.
Once you've accepted
your evil nature,
you'll feel much more relaxed,
no matter the odds.
Take me, for instance.
If your power ranking's
a ten, mine is a six.
[YUSUKE grunts]
[SENSUI]
Speed, strength, stamina.
You beat me in all three.
And yet you're
still going to die.
Why is Sensui talkin' so much?
You think he's buyin' time?
I don't think that's it.
He's exuding as much
confidence as ever.
[ITSUKI]
You're right, Kurama.
I haven't seen Sensui
this happy in a long time,
as he's getting to kill
and prove a point.
Shut up! From now on
you're in quiet time, okay?
Don't listen to 'em, Urameshi!
Just do what you're
best at: kickin' tail!
[SENSUI] Despite
advantages, you can't win.
Want to hear
a list of reasons?
Ha. We've talked
so much already.
I don't think my attention
span can take it!
[YUSUKE]
So, let's just skip to the fun!
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE grunting]
Bring it on!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[YUSUKE yelping]
--[thud]
--[YUSUKE grunts]
Well, that didn't work!
[groaning]
Damn it!
First you say I'm faster,
then you get the heads-up on me
like I'm an old lady
crossing the freeway!
For once I want some
honesty from the bad guys!
You are faster, Yusuke,
but it doesn't matter.
Reason one why you
don't stand a chance:
I can predict your moves.
[growls] Nobody can
predict my attacks!
I'll have you know I beat
a mind-reader, okay!
I'm too crazy to call!
[SENSUI]
It's not about being a psychic.
It's about experience.
When you dodged my kick,
I knew you'd answer
with your favorite finish:
a right-hand hook to the jaw.
Despite your speed,
my knowledge of this allowed me
to turn just enough
to make your fist slide off.
I played a detective
just like you, and like you,
decoding my opponent's
fighting style is my strength,
but I've been doing it
for decades longer.
Heh.
So, I guess
I can't surprise you.
Then I guess you know this, too,
that trusting what people tell
me has never been my thing!
Yeah! Bring it to him, Urameshi!
Just do anything obvious,
unless he thinks you won't
'cause then you should!
[growls]
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE grunts]
You're up!
[SENSUI]
Huh?
Uh!
That's called a fake.
--[YUSUKE yelling]
--[SENSUI groaning]
Jeez.
Now that's a hit!
It's about time you listened
to me and did somethin' right!
Now finish him so we can leave!
I haven't eaten since
they kidnapped me!
[YUSUKE]
What's that, Sensui?
You forgot how to swim?
You drowned?
Great, we'll pack up and go!
You heard Kuwabara,
he's starved.
[SENSUI]
Good hits, detective.
Between that and the water,
my shirt practically dissolved.
[yelps]
[KUWABARA yells]
Gross. Look at
the scars he's got.
Guess he wasn't lyin' about all
the fights he's been through.
[SENSUI]
Don't you know what they say
about assuming, Kuwabara?
These wounds
aren't from enemies.
No one's ever hurt me that bad.
I gave myself these scars
as a part of my training.
[YUSUKE]
Great, a masochist.
True, though,
his body's well trained.
It's like punching
a tractor tire.
[SENSUI] Let's fight like
there's a little more at stake.
[YUSUKE grunts]
[NARRATOR] After diversions,
kidnappings, trials and tests,
and with the tunnel to Demon
World racing to completion,
the deciding fight
has finally begun.
The battle between
Spirit Detectives.
[KUWABARA] Man, Sensui's
about to rip into Urameshi
with powers you've never seen.
Now, let's recap.
Itsuki's actually
a demon with extra arms,
we're trapped inside
of a shadow's belly,
Gourmet was actually Toguro,
and Sensui doesn't seem
to care about his plan!
How's he gonna cut the barrier
and let the big demons out,
if he let the guy
with the sword get away?
Well, you better watch
the next Yu Yu Hakusho,
because, believe it or not,
we haven't gotten
to the big surprises!