[KUWABARA]
So that's it? You all lost, huh?
True. Our victories were
not of the winning kind.
Wow, so even Urameshi
ate some dirt?
Guess it's a darn good thing
I didn't take part in it.
You might've made
the difference.
Ah, come on, I'm
not the same joker
who doesn't know my own
strength. Not anymore.
Kazuma's here. Nice surprise.
Hey.
Oh yeah, hey ladies. What's up?
Where you headed to?
Nowhere, you know.
So, guess that's your
girlfriend there?
You goin' on a date now?
[KUWABARA grunts] He's a man,
okay? And a tough one!
No, come on...
You're sure of that?!
He does look kinda
cute, I think.
Well, no one told me
you swung that way.
Hey, look, I like girls, okay?!
And he's jus... he's got
delicate features!
You gotta hang with us,
Kazumo. Word is your cool.
See you, boys.
[GIRLS giggle]
Sorry about that, man.
Don't be.
I see you're doing better with
the girls these days, though.
Yeah. Well, when
I was a freshman,
I used my awareness to
predict an earthquake.
I've been kind of a
fascination to 'em ever since.
You really do seem
to be enjoying
your high school life, Kuwabara.
I guess.
[KURAMA]
Since your school's partnered
with the university here,
you should be a shoe-in.
Yeah, people always think that,
but we still have to pass
the entry exams just
like everyone else.
That's one thing I've learned,
though. I can beat tough odds.
Can't believe it's
been two years.
[KURAMA]
What?
Two years since I've
talked with Urameshi.
[KURAMA]
Time does fly by.
In ways it doesn't seem
like it's been that long
since all the times
you've come back
to give me the latest news.
But I do miss the guy.
Well he hasn't changed
one bit, if that helps.
Does he ever say anything
about coming back?
Every time I see him,
he says he has something
different to take care of.
Of course I heard of
his promise to Kayko,
and his maybe-true proposal.
Sometimes I think
he has cold feet.
So he won't come back
for a whole nother year,
and then maybe not at
all? Guy's repressed.
For once, he should make a
choice not about fighting.
You know, Kurama, I'm surprised
Kayko hasn't gotten fed up him
and left him yet.
[bell rings]
[GIRLS chatter]
[GIRL C] Kayko. Aren't you
gonna wait for your friends?
[GIRL D] So, Kayko, do
you wanna go downtown?
I hear there's a lot happening.
[KAYKO] Sorry, I already
promised I'd meet someone today.
Uh-oh... Is this a date?
No secrets now, did you finally
find yourself a boyfriend?
No, unfortunately.
[GIRL D]
Not Kayko.
She hasn't shown interest in
a guy since I've known her.
What's up with that, Kayko?
[GIRL C]
Standards are too high, I think.
She's still waiting
for Prince Charming
to sweep her off her feet.
[KUWABARA]
Okay, there's still one thing
I can't put together here.
[KURAMA]
What?
Two years back we had this
whole fight to stop Sensui
from diggin' a tunnel that would
let loose the strongest demons.
At the end of the day,
they sealed the tunnel
and the barrier net.
So how come you, as
powerful as you are,
have been able to come
and go as you please?
Ah. It's because Spirit
World has brought down
the barrier between
the two worlds.
Oh, okay. Well,
that makes sense.
What?!
What do you mean they
brought down the barrier?!
So we're completely
unprotected?!
So they can use us
like a feed store?!
[SHIZURU]
You know, bro,
one of these days you're
gonna blow out a lung.
[KURAMA]
Shizuru. It's been too long.
Yeah. How is my
favorite redhead?
There's no time for
pleasant greetings, sis!
We've gotta watch out. There
could be demons everywhere!
Did you eat too
much sugar today?
Rest assured,
you don't have to worry.
There's been a new sort
of honor agreement.
Every demon has now
taken a sacred oath
to cause no trouble
in Living World.
[SHIZURU] Sounds bunk to me,
but I'll believe it if you do.
Well, why didn't you tell me
bout that in the first place?
[knocking]
[SHIZURU]
Is that Kayko?
[KUWABARA]
Uh?!
Wow! Her hair looks a
whole bunch longer now!
Yeah, so do her legs.
I grew, too! Three
inches this month!
[WOMAN] Thanks. Here you go.
Enjoy your trip.
[SHIZURU]
Oh. The paper, too.
[KUWABARA panting]
It's not like family trips, sis!
You can't make us
miss the train!
Thanks for the grub, though.
I don't care what other
guys say about you.
You're a pretty
decent human being.
Oh, uh, by the way guys,
do you guys want any of these?
Cause I don't mind
eatin' eat if you don't.
Eat, bro.
I got it so you wouldn't
talk all the way there.
[SHIZURU gasps]
You are not gonna believe this.
What'd you find?
The center page is always
alien sightings and stuff.
It isn't true.
Oh my gosh, Hiei is in here!
What?!
[KUWABARA] "Short,
three-eyed alien sighted."
Yeah, that's him. I thought
he was in Demon World.
Hiei is serving on a
patrol duty right now.
A human must have stumbled into
Demon World since the barrier's
been down, and somehow
escaped with his memory.
I doubt that will happen again.
I'm picking up a human scent.
It's close, around ten o'clock.
Huh. Not again.
[HIEI]
Put him into protection.
[BLUE DEMON]
What about medical?
[HIEI] Don't bother.
If he dies, it's his fault.
[OLDER MAN groaning]
Don't worry,
old fool, you're not dead.
We'll get you back
home quickly enough.
But first I have to do a
little procedure to make sure
you don't remember any of these
fun things when you wake up.
Pleasant dreams.
[NARRATOR] According to
the laws proclaimed by Enki,
victor of the tournament,
all human beings who enter
Demon World by mistake
are to be protected and returned
safely to Living World.
To that end, a patrol
team was created,
and those who lost
in the tournament
became the first patrolers.
[DEMON A] Three years
on patrol. It's too long.
[DEMON B]
Yeah, after three years
I won't be able to wash
off the human stink.
[KIRIN] Don't complain.
It's our faults for losing.
They could have taken our lives.
[DEMON A] Nothing about that
tournament made sense.
Enki is strong, no doubt,
but if Lord Mukuro had
fought with all her energy,
she could have beaten him.
Cut him wide open.
[KIRIN] No. Lord Mukuro
didn't hold back.
She fought with all
she had at the time.
[DEMON A]
I don't believe it.
[KIRIN] Lord Mukuro's
strength is tied directly
to her state of mind.
When filled with hatred,
her powers are unmatchable.
But in that tournament,
for some reason,
she only had half her
strength, at most.
And I don't think
we'll see her full power
anytime in the
near future, either.
[DEMON A]
Why not?
[KIRIN] I've seen her.
Something's changed.
Her eyes have become
unbelievably calm.
[DEMON B]
Well, what's happened to her?
[KIRIN]
Damned if I know.
[MUKURO]
How's the patrol?
[HIEI]
Nonsense.
[MUKURO] You could go
back to Living World.
I'd make certain no one
came looking for you.
Hmph. That's not why I stay.
Uh... He's on patrol...
Sounds bad, but trust me,
he's doing quite well.
So, did Genkai tell you the
reason for this whole meeting?
No, she just said she
wanted all of us
to visit her together.
I have no idea what it's about.
She wanna show us her new
set of dentures or somethin'?
We'll know soon.
Not a bad place she's got here.
Yeah, coming here
always calms me down.
Hey, guys!
Ah! Yukina!
[KUWABARA laughing]
[YUKINA]
Hello, Kazuma. Hello everyone.
How have you all been?
[KUWABARA]
Well, I've been just great!
[YUKINA]
Good. And everyone else?
Still alive.
And what about you?
I figured you'd be bored
out of your mind living
here with just Genkai.
Oh... We get by.
Besides, Kazu's come up
pretty frequently to visit.
Oh?
Still trying to work that famous
Kuwabara-family magic,
are you bro?
[laughs] Workin' magic.
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
I've been tryin' to
relay Kurama's news.
Oh, and that's not cologne you
smell, it's my natural scent!
[KURAMA]
Yukina, is Master Genkai here?
Of course. Here she is.
You're late.
[GENKAI] I see. So Yusuke
still hasn't come back?
What the hell is he working on?
No one is really
sure, specifically.
Oh, come on, we know
what he's doing.
He's picking fights.
It's not like he cares
about anything else now.
[SHIZURU clears throat]
[KUWABARA]
Uh?!
[KAYKO] You don't have
to protect me, guys.
I'm just glad to see Genkai.
Let's focus on that.
Yeah, me too.
It's a relief to see
you're still well.
I'm happy every day
you're alive!
[GENKAI] Hm. Well that's
a peachy spot I'm in.
Sticking around just so
you don't have bad day.
[KURAMA, SHIZURU, KAYKO laugh]
[KUWABARA]
That's not what I meant!
Well! I didn't know all
of you would be here!
[KAYKO]
Hey, Botan!
Hello, Kayko. Love the hair!
That's convenient.
I guess Genkai called you
the same time she did us.
--[KOENMA] Me, too.
--[KUWABARA] Huh?!
[KUWABARA]
Koenma? Where did you come from?
[KOENMA]
Well, that's a lengthy story,
you'll just have to ask my dad.
You cheese-ball.
[GENKAI] Good. You're
all here. Now sit down.
[GENKAI] There's only one
reason I asked you all to come.
These recent years have caused
me to think about my legacy,
and so I want to tell you
what to do after I die.
Ah. Genkai,
you shouldn't talk like that.
It brings bad luck.
You won't die soon.
You look good.
You look better than
I do on some days.
Ah. Just shut up and
let me get this done.
Once you've given me
a teary-eyed funeral,
I'll be leaving this
whole estate to your group.
[ALL gasp]
[GENKAI] That includes this
temple and all surrounding land.
A shore on one side and
a stone wall on the other
will tell you where it ends.
Leave nature as it is.
It takes several hours by car
to reach the closest town.
Not a convenient place
for humans to live,
but perfect for apparitions.
The Kekkai Barrier is down,
but it will take a long time
for humans and demons
to live in peace.
I spent my life trying to
understand a demon and failed.
Make this a safehouse, to bridge
the gap as I never could.
[KURAMA]
Amazing.
All of this land, far as
we can see, belongs to her.
[KUWABARA] Yeah, definitely
something we won't be
chopping down. We'll do
a lota good stuff here.
We have time. We could
go down to the shore.
Yeah! Let's go!
You game, Yukina?
It's guaranteed fun!
Sure.
[BOTAN] It's weird hearing
Genkai talk about death.
As healthy as she lives,
she could outlast us all.
[SHIZURU]
Makes me want to quit smoking.
[BOTAN, KAYKO, SHIZURU laugh]
[KURAMA]
Something wrong, Kuwabara?
I met Genkai for the first
time ever after going up
these stairs. And I ended
up fighting against Rando.
Though I didn't
know it at the time,
it was the first case Urameshi
and I worked on together.
After that it was Maze Castle.
I met you, and called Hiei
a runt-boy for the first time.
And then Tarukane,
and my pinky string,
and meeting the love of my life.
And then it was the whole
Dark Tournament with Toguro,
and then Sensui, and now this.
This treaty sounds great,
but it means that's all over.
We gotta move on. It's just...
It's just hard to believe.
[KURAMA]
True.
But when we need to, as you
just have, we can remember.
[KUWABARA]
Yeah.
[BOTAN]
Hey!
Enough flirting, boys!
Hey, if you want,
the four of us
can just go to the beach alone.
[KUWABARA]
No, no! I'm coming!
Uh, Yukina, you didn't by chance
pack a bathing suit, did ya?
[BOTAN, KAYKO laugh]
[SHIZURU]
You're so pathetic.
[KOENMA]
They're a good group of kids.
Yeah.
Oh, my. Perfect ending
for a perfect day.
A sunset by the ocean.
It's the most romantic
thing I've ever seen.
Most romantic, huh?
This is gonna be my hour!
Wanna get your feet wet, Yukina?
Yeah.
[KAYKO, YUKINA laugh]
Best take advantage
while the sun's up!
I will! I'm gonna
find me a starfish!
[YUKINA]
Uh!
It feels like ice!
[YUKINA] You think I'll
ever be with my brother?
[KAYKO] I think you will,
when he's ready. Now have fun.
That's the one bad
thing about sunsets.
They make you think too much.
Let's come back soon,
in the day.
Sure.
[KUWABARA]
Yukina! Ha, ha.
I caught the world's
biggest starfish!
I sensed it under a rock!
And I found shells
to make a necklace!
Oh, cool! Wait for me!
[KAYKO]
Yusuke...
This is the end!
[KAYKO] I'm tired of
waiting for you, Yusuke!
Half my life I've waited
for you to come around!
Even when you were here
you weren't really!
You weren't here for me!
Go on fighting!
But it's time I get what I want!
I could cry.
[YUSUKE] I don't want
you to wait, either.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
See? Don't have to.
[KAYKO whimpers]
Yusuke!
[KAYKO laughs]
One of us has gotten more
athletic since I've been gone.
[BOTAN]
Bingo.
[KURAMA, SHIZURU laugh]
Oh, you're gonna pay
for that one, Kayko!
You stole that
lip-time from me!
--Now come here!
--[KAYKO laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
[KAYKO]
Come get me, tough guy.
Now you know I could dump
this whole ocean on you
if I wanted.
[BOTH laugh]
[KUWABARA laughs]
Bang!
[KUWABARA growls]
That's it!
--Come on.
--Mm-hm.
[KUWABARA growls]
What's wrong, Mister Mazaku?
I thought you were goin' to
Demon World to become the king!
I will someday, but then who's
gonna be here to kick your ass?
Well if you're goin' back, I
better give you the beatdown now
I was always too nice to give!
[YUSUKE]
You can try!
[KAYKO laughs]
[BOTAN laughs]
[YUKINA laughs]
[KUWABARA grunts]
Heh, heh, yeah!
[KUWABARA groans]