♪
[NARRATOR] As the Dark
Tournament continues,
the ominous Toguro
displayed his power
by fighting his first
team battle alone.
While outside the ring,
Yusuke found he couldn't
fire his Spirit Gun,
and Hiei struggled
against the agony of
his crippled right arm.
But Toguro's quick victory
has sped the tournament
to its second round,
giving Yusuke's wounded
crew little time to rest.
Now they must face the
bizarre Dr. Ichigaki team.
[KUWABARA] No--Tell
him to go away!
They shouldn't be here.
It just isn't right.
What's your problem Kuwabara?
You don't like croissants?
Stupid name,
but they taste good.
I had a dream
last night Urameshi.
[YUSUKE]
Was she hot?
It was about our
next fight, okay!
[YUSUKE]
Ah, a nightmare.
Must suck to get beat
up in your dreams, as well!
Hey, shut up! That's not
what it was about!
Sorry man, I don't feel
like playing councilor today.
Well fine then, your dumb ass
couldn't understand it anyway!
Where's Kurama and Hiei? They're
good with stuff like this.
Not here.
They're not here?
Well where'd they go?
Hell if I know.
What's with you people?!
Doesn't anyone know how to
write notes when they leave?!
Take a relaxer.
Our fight is starting soon.
And demons aren't
exactly trusting.
They'd never let us fight alone.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
They're probably just
gonna meet us in the arena.
Now let's go kick some ass!
[cheering crowd]
Looks like we have a fan.
[KOENMA] I'd say I'm a little
more than that, Yusuke.
Wait a minute, "Junior" on the
forehead and a squeally voice.
You're Koenma's older brother!
As far as I am aware Koenma
doesn't have any brothers.
And I should know-
I'm him, as a cool teenager!
Yeah, is that
pacifier for raving?
Can it, boy!
Yo--Kuwabara,
Thanks for helping out
Yusuke all the time. It's nice.
Hey, no problem.
Give me a break. All you do is
give me someone else to rescue.
That's not true!
[KOENMA]
Boys. Please.
So, sucker-mouth,
what are you doing here?
[KOENMA] One, I'm your
Spirit Detective boss.
Two, I'm the owner of your team,
and three, I have a way to help.
Yusuke Urameshi,
your egg is about to hatch.
[YUSUKE]
Excuse me?
Your golden egg you moron!
The egg of your Spirit Beast
I gave you during
your life ordeal, remember!
I have no clue!
Brief recap: I gave you an egg
that would hatch a Spirit Beast
that would probably
bite off your head.
But wisely you chose to
forgo your chance at revival
by hatching the
beast prematurely,
thus saving Keiko from a fire.
This sacrifice was the true
answer to the ordeal, and boom!
You're back to life.
But the egg stayed with me.
See it never actually hatched-
only its Spirit
Energy was unleashed.
[KOENMA] Ever since you became
Spirit Detective, the egg,
unbeknownst to you, has been
feeding on your soul's merit.
And now, after nearly
a year, it will hatch.
Hey, that's pretty slick!
Taking care of my egg like that!
You coulda' scrambled it
and I woulda' never known!
[KOENMA]
How insightful.
But it's not hatched yet.
You'll have to depend
on the skills Genkai
has taught you for now.
Hopefully the
Spirit Wave Technique
will be enough in this fight.
Right, Spirit Wave. Never
actually perfected that one.
We were busy.
[YUSUKE] Thanks for the
info though, Koenma.
That egg thing
sounds pretty cool.
[KOENMA]
Yes well, good luck.
[KOENMA THINKS]
He didn't complete his
training with Genkai?
I have a feeling this
fight could be messy.
But I suppose if Yusuke is
ever to reach his full purpose,
this is the only way.
[KURAMA]
Is this wise, Hiei?
What do you mean?
It won't be easy to keep winning
without the use
of your dominant hand.
Perhaps you should withdraw.
Ha, you heard what Toguro said.
We don't have a choice.
If we don't make it
through this tournament.
He will kill us all.
Fighting is our only way out.
Seems the doctor's
team has gotten lost.
Yes, what a horrible
coincidence for us both.
[crowd cheers]
[DEMON FAN 1] Why aren't
they fighting already?!
[DEMON FAN 2]
Look at 'em! Dumbass!
Both teams are incomplete!
Urameshi, they're for real.
Fox-girl's?
The three fighters on that team!
They're exactly the same
as the ones from my nightmare.
I remember the entire thing!
What?
[M-1]
Master Mitamura! Please!
[MITAMURA] It's okay, son.
Let me stay awake for now.
[M-3] Master, I want
you to get better.
I need you to get better!
[MITAMURA]
Need, son? No--
You sell
yourself too short.
You all do.
You're fully capable
of standing on your own.
Enough of this nonsense
Mine are the only
dry eyes in the room.
How could I ever be afraid
when I'm blessed
by students like you?
I talked one last time with
the hospital ward this morning.
I had to tell them
we could never afford
the seventy thousand.
[M-3] Damn it! None of this--
Not one piece is fair!
How can I expect to
live with myself now?
The man who's raised us and
taught us like his own sons
is dying and I can't
do a thing to help him!
I know it's hard
for you to take.
And knowing that you
care about me so much is--
Listen, sometimes things
happen we can't control.
Things we can only accept.
I won't! I'll never accept it!
I'll make you better!
Somehow I will!
[evil laugh]
[MITAMURA]
Who are you?
Quite possibly I'm the
answer to your prayers.
A doctor who can alleviate
your poor master's disease.
[M-2]
Don't toy with us!
It's free.
[M-1] All right! We'll take it!
There is, however,
one stipulation.
[M-3]
What is it?
You might not
be interested.
[M-2] Tell us! If
there's anything we can
do to save him, we will!
I would like to use
this gentleman. And this one.
And you, my good sir,
over there as subjects
for a little experiment.
It's the only
way I can help you.
And don't worry, your bodies
will stay perfectly intact!
[evil laugh]
I'm positive that
dream was the truth.
Time is up.
Both teams, step forward.
Team captains, please
decide the terms for battle.
Isn't this mysterious.
Both of our teams
are missing two members.
What do you say... we fight
with the people we have.
Winner is the best of three.
What about you?
Don't the ugly pointy-eared
trolls like to fight, too?
Only when we have to, boy.
I prefer the managing position.
Never any reason to do the work
when you can watch
somebody else do it for you.
Hence the guinea pigs.
So it's true.
They say that the Spirit Energy
a human body is
capable of producing
is far greater than
that of an apparition?
A fierce monster of power
locked within you all!
It's only the human conscience
that will keep
this power at bay.
Take away free will and
the monster will say hello.
How 'bout "ass-kicking"?
Do they say that too?
Every genius has his critics.
I am but an inventor
seeking to create the
perfect fighting vehicle.
[DR. ICHIGAKI] No compassion
or fear to hold it back!
A human's Spirit
Power on cruise control!
Does it come with A/C?
Mock me all you want!
It'll be a different story when
you're the one I'm controlling!
Say what?!
[DR. ICHIGAKI]
Let's make this interesting.
Your power fascinates me.
If my team wins I
get to use your body.
[YUSUKE] Why not?
And if my team wins we
get to rip off your face.
Yes, I can live with that.
[DR. ICHIGAKI THINKS]
And the blind fall
effortlessly into my trap.
Without Kurama or Hiei here,
my chance at victory
is calculated at
exactly 98 percent!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
We have one more condition.
We combine the three matches
into a six-person battle royale.
One fight determines it all.
Perhaps.
Hold on little guy.
You mean all three of us
fighting their three in the
ring at the very same time?
[DR. ICHIGAKI THINKS]
That drops their chances
to just point-zero-five percent!
I will accept. Your masked
friend drives a hard bargain.
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs]
[DR. ICHIGAKI THINKS]
The unscientific mind
can be so amusing!
They themselves
ask for a situation
that yields me a 99.95
percentage of victory!
Yes. A hard bargain, I said.
The Spirit Detective's
body will soon belong to me!
Kill Urameshi! Team-up on him!
Tear off his fingers!
And shove 'em down his throat!
Damn. Well, at least the
fans are getting creative.
[KUWABARA THINKS] That masked
guy made a pretty good call.
With us all fighting together
we can watch each other's back,
especially while Yusuke
tries to get his
Spirit Gun workin' again.
But I still can't
figure out these fighters.
Ichigaki said they've
turned into monsters,
but something about
them still feels--
These three competitors.
I met them before.
You did?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Their instructor, Mitamura,
was a famous martial artist.
He said training good character
was more important
than physical skill.
I was always struck by his
student's respect for life.
They would never kill,
no matter what.
That explains it.
The weird feeling
I'm getting from them--
it's like a
whisper in their guts.
They don't want
to be fighting here!
They're being forced to murder
while their minds just watch!
That's right, baby brother,
you feel it too.
Pardon?
Do you think that there's
something wrong with Kuwabara?
It's difficult to explain.
There're some
very strong emotions
buried down there in the ring.
My brother--he can sense it,
and, it's getting to him.
Well you're oddly emotional
yourself. What's going on then?
Is it something
between him and Yusuke?
No, it's from the other team.
Just imagine a desperate
scream from far away.
You can't hear what its saying
but you know what's
about to happen
is gonna be really painful.
That does sound horrible.
Yeah, can we do
something to help?
[SHIZURU THINKS]
Be careful bro, okay?
Don't get so caught
up with their well-being,
that you forget about your own.
Last team with a
standing member wins!
Ready? Begin!
Grizzly Claw!
[YUSUKE THINKS] So what?
I guess I'm not supposed
to shake his hand?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
I suggest you move.
Damn?!
Incredible!
Unfortunately some of the moves
were too fast to
see with our eyes.
But it was smashing team work
by the doctor's crew for sure!
What, the hell was that?
[YUSUKE] I didn't even see
that last guy's attack!
[KOTO] Seems Dr. Ichigaki's
team has a real advantage!
They've knocked down
two of their opponents,
team Urameshi is
completely on the defensive!
Oooh, that combo kills 72
percent of the time!
Yusuke's biology
is so remarkable!
I can't wait to exploit it!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Are you all right?
Yeah, thanks
for the warning there
I had no idea how powerful
that guy's hand was gonna be.
Yeah, we'll send
you a "thank you" card.
Drop the jokes, Yusuke.
They're coming again.
Angel Blades!
Offense really isn't an option
for the Urameshi Team right now!
It's just run or be gutted!
Now M-2 steps up and
hurls Kuwabara into the air!
[KUWABARA]
Spirit Sword!
[KOTO] A last-ditch effort
has kept Kuwabara
inside the ring,
but that may not have
been the wisest choice!
M-3 is headed his way!
Not on my watch!
[KOTO] Now it gets thick!
While the Masked Fighter
tussles with M-1 and M-2,
Yusuke braces to fire
his trademark Spirit Gun!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
No. I still get nothin'!
For some reason Yusuke
decides not to fire his energy!
Leaving his friend and
teammate absolutely defenseless!
Kuwabara!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Too late!
I'll never reach him in time!
Wow! That was awesome!
The only chance for
you two is to focus.
Try to find a small
trace of their energy,
then trust your instincts
to keep you alive.
Maybe you can clear
something up for me, genius.
Those guys are human, right?
With Spirit Energy like us?
Of course.
Then why can't we feel it?
I'm a Spiritually Aware person!
That's what I do!
Why can't I now?
That doctor's made it
completely unfiltered.
The size of their
power is, frankly,
more than your rookie
brains can comprehend.
Perfect!
So if we can't
sense all their energy,
how are we supposed to win?
[MASKED FIGHTER] Sorry. I
don't have all the answers.
[KOTO] Get ready
for more spills!
The Ichigaki Team is
poised for another round!
[YUSUKE THINKS] All right,
Spirit Gun!
You can come back
when ever you're ready!
What the hell?
And that was using
my left arm, Kurama.
I'm sorry,
I used my right.
Next time I'll
use my left to be fair.
Would you like to try us next?
Thanks, but I'd rather not.
Death gives me the shivers.
Gatasubal is what
we like to call him.
One of the doctor's
earlier projects.
Part demon, mostly machine, no
feelings. No pain and no fear!
Go Gatasubal!
Destroy those two low-lives.
[HIEI THINKS] Not a scratch!
Gatasubal's whole body
is covered with a special
formula of hybridized metal.
Combining the hardest steel
with actual living cells--
No substance in the
whole world can break it!
Maybe I can't kill the beast.
But at least I
can still kill you!
[Hiei cries out]
Hiei!
[M-5 laughs insanely]
[M-5] See the genius
of the doctor's work!
It has no feelings
or thoughts to distract!
It thinks only of the kill!
I can appreciate that.
Hiei! Don't!
Kurama!
[M-5 laughs insanely]
[M-5] Excellent Gatasubal!
Now kill the other one, too!
[M-5] What's wrong with
you! I said kill!
[KURAMA] You were
wrong on two counts.
I'm wrong? What do you mean?
What just happened?
Even the hardest
substance can be broken.
When crashed into itself.
And the ability to feel
pain is not a weakness.
It's a strength. Pain tells
a creature its vulnerabilities.
And not to expose
them to attack.
Your robot is dead...
[KURAMA] And so,
I'm afraid, are you.
Okay!
Forget this!
I can't watch this way!
Wait! Botan!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I'm so
tired of falling on my ass!
There's got to be
something I can do here!
Excellent. Like always.
[NARRATOR] In a fight
where their odds of victory
are calculated at
point-zero-five percent,
what can Yusuke's team possibly
do to escape with their lives?
[BOTAN] Hello everyone,
Botan again.
Don't expect the
odds to improve much,
when the
fight against the
mind-controlled humans rolls on!
As if the teamwork
of the three blank-faced
fighters wasn't enough,
Kuwabara suddenly
refuses to fight!
Sensing the inner torment
of these transformed men
and overcome with sympathy,
he instead makes
a desperate plea
for their humanity to arise!
And while Kuwabara
pays for this risk,
an unloosed cloth
gives a first glimpse at
the fighter behind the mask!
♪