♪
[NARRATOR] As the Dark
Tournament continues...
Spirit Detective Yusuke Urameshi
and his crew faced the
Dr. Ichigaki in
the second round.
Realizing the human opponents
were innocent men under mind
control, the Masked Fighter
employed a complex technique
to restore their free will.
The Spirit Detective's
team has survived,
but now they must
fight their next battle
with zero time to recover--
against a mysterious new foe.
Easy now.
[YUSUKE] Oh look,
he's off his sick bed.
Now that he's fully recovered
I'm sure he'll be great help.
Kuwabara is not the
only one low on his power.
That special attack
drained her considerably.
So it's three non-gimps
against five of them??
[KURAMA THINKS] Worse.
Hiei still can't use his arm.
[BAKKEN] Who wants to begin?
The first can be captain.
I'll go and take
those humans then.
Jin the Wind Master. Well that
would explain who this team is.
You know these jokers?
Indeed, most demons do.
Team Masho must be a
pseudonym for this tournament.
Their actual names are the
Shinobi of the Spirit World.
Shinobi? So what the
hell does that mean?
[KURAMA] They are
stealth fighters,
deadly mercenaries
to the highest bid.
A dispute arises
in Spirit World,
and they "solve" it, in secret.
You're familiar with their other
name, aren't you? The Ninja.
Team captains, please
decide the battle terms.
Let's fix these
stakes simple enough.
One to one to one
till I'm a tower
on my feet holding the five.
Whatever he said.
Jin has asked for a
series of one on one matches
with the advancing
team taking five wins,
and Yusuke gives the nod!
They're on a roll,
Shizuru. They can do it!
I'm not sure what
tournament you're watching.
Half the team I'm cheering
for can't even walk now.
A darn near pleasant
wind be filling the air now.
Tell a person by the wind and
yours the kind I like Urameshi.
[bells ring]
[SPEAKER] May I have your
attention, please.
The Tournament Committee
will be instituting
a medical examination
before the next round.
What is this, gym class?
Due to the Urameshi Team
fighting without rest,
and in accordance to section
13 of the Tournament Index,
report to the medical tent.
As they long they don't grab
my balls and make me cough.
Scratch that.
Wow! Hot mamma!
[RUKA]
Hello, gentleman.
Yes, you two fighters.
Would you please follow
me to the medical tent?
Don't be ridiculous.
We need no attention.
Why don't you go nurse
the fool lying on his back.
Because his wounds
do not interest me
in the ways that
yours do, Hiei.
Maybe I can help you.
[CROWD] What's the big deal?
Get on with the fight!
Quick Ogre, hit me.
What?
Right in the noggin. Hurry!
What are you talking about sir?
I order you to hit
me in the head you oaf!
I don't understand, sir,
but if you order me I guess,
just don't get
mad at me later!
[KOENMA] Look what
you've done you blue idiot!
You've given me a bruise! Guess
I'll have to go see the nurse!
Koenma!
[RUKA] Are you
experiencing any fatigue,
or sharp or recurring pains?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
No.
And you Hiei?
Surely that last attack
had some effect on you.
Why do you ask?
Isn't it your job to know?
It must be hard to fight with
your arm in excruciating pain.
Clearly you will
both have to stay with me
until your health is improved.
I don't go where
people tell me to, lady.
You can treat yourself.
[HIEI]
What?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Quickly! It's a trap!
[YUSUKE] Damn it! What's
happening to them, Kurama??
It's a force field.
Well isn't that convenient!
[YUSUKE]
Hey! Red-head!
Why do I get the feeling
you're not a licensed nurse!
That's correct, Yusuke.
Enchantress is more like it.
Yeah, uh, that was
my second guess.
[RUKA]
Ruka is my name.
Regarded as the most
talented creature
alive in spell
defense incantations.
Spell defense?
What is she talkin' about?
It's a different
way to manipulate energy.
She doesn't
have any attack powers,
but her defense is so top notch
that nothing can break
through her force field.
I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Give me my damn team back!
Didn't you hear the
announcement, Yusuke?
They're both very sick.
They're going to need
a little time to recover.
[RUKA] Sokujyujyo!
That energy thread.
It uses their own
Spirit Energy against them.
The more they struggle, the
more powerful it will become.
[KOENMA] It's horrible!
She isn't really a nurse?
That means I got this
bump on my head for nada!
Ogre! How dare you punch
your boss in the head like that!
But Koenma sir,
you ordered me to!
I told you that you couldn't
get mad at me, remember!
[KOENMA]
I get paybacks!
[SPEAKER] As a result
of the medical examination,
Hiei and the Masked Fighter
have been ruled unfit to fight.
They will sit out for
the duration of the round
while they are suitably treated.
[Butajiri laughs]
[BUTAJIRI THINKS]
Friends in high places!
Yes sir, that's the key!
The committee
making this sudden fight-
The beautiful Ruka
capturing their team--
It's amazing what money can buy!
Oh, what the hell is this?!
[KOTO] How can you let
them lie like that?
I've already told you
I don't have anything to
do with these decisions!
Really! I'm completely neutral!
[YUSUKE]
Wrong stupid answer!!
It's all right.
Says who??
Obviously the
committee is against us.
However, we have not been hurt.
Truthfully the
Masked Fighter and Hiei
are in no shape to
fight at the moment, anyway.
[KURAMA] Think. Why would she
only capture two of us,
when she had the
chance to do more?
Perhaps her power is not great
enough to restrict us all, and
she took a pair who were too
weak to resist the force field.
She's helped less
than the committee thinks.
This will only give Team Masho
a false sense of security.
The advantage is ours.
[Bakken laughs]
[BAKKEN] Two against five now,
Jin. You can destroy them all.
Nah! I'm having
to change my mind
if its going be a fix like that.
I don't give a damn.
Somebody else go.
I'm sure I'd
rather be the watch now.
[BAKKEN] It wouldn't
be wise to think you
can disrupt the sect this time.
Don't ya ever put your
gritty hands on me again.
[TOUYA] Do not get
too upset, Bakken.
He wants only a true
challenge in his battle.
[BAKKEN] I could care less.
Who's fighting them first?
[GAMA] Please.
The master of disguise will.
You're on!
What are you doing?
[KURAMA] You must leave
this one to me.
We're going to have to play this
round very carefully, Yusuke.
Let me fight them
as long as I can--
and ascertain their weaknesses.
You'll take over when I fall.
And it's Kurama versus
Gama! You may begin!
Tell me demon traitor,
what does the word
makeup bring to mind?
[GAMA]
Human females, no doubt.
A little gloss to
attract the next mate.
Disgusting isn't it?
The way humans
manage to bastardize
everything they touch.
Over centuries
the human influence
has infected the
Spirit World as well.
Now few demons even
know its original power.
Allow me to show you.
Now I haven't
seen that one before!
Gama's covered his body
with some sort of face paint!
And now his spirit
energy is going insane!
[KURAMA THINKS] His spirit
energy is strong,
but does not extend
far from his body.
Close combat is
clearly his strength.
Gama's decorations really
seem to boost his power!
Kurama can't even
squeeze in a counterattack!
[HIEI THINKS] You're playing
a dangerous game Kurama--
waiting to gauge the enemy's
weakness before you attack.
You could at
least draw your weapon.
I know all about you and
your plant concoctions, Kurama!
And I don't plan to
give you time to make them!
Let me demonstrate what I mean!
[KURAMA] If you
don't mind me asking,
what exactly have
you done to me?
Your leg feels like a giant
block of lead, doesn't it?
[KURAMA]
That smell.
Let me get this straight.
You can't move
any part of your body
that gets marked
up by that junk?
[Gama laughs]
Why try to fight the inevitable?
[GAMA] The Makeup of Death has
already marked you Kurama.
There's no hope for escape.
Kurama!
Gama's makeup seems
to take a reverse effect
when painted on his enemies!
And with Kurama
barely able to walk,
Gama is slowly
moving in like a tiger,
stalking his wounded prey!
Rip him apart!
[TOUYA] Kurama's
struggling is pointless.
The makeup seeps
through any clothing
and attaches to the skin.
Transmitting
Gama's spirit energy,
as if he were gripped
by Gama's own fist.
[GAMA]
The costume is completed.
The Makeup of Chains.
Go ahead--just
try to limp away now.
Kurama!
Get rid of the outfit!
Don't be naive.
Even if he had the strength to,
it wouldn't change a thing--
Nearly 2000 pounds of weight
is chained directly to his skin!
[Gama laughs maniacally]
Yes, that's better.
Finally accepting your fate.
Kurama's arms and legs
are completely useless!
He can do nothing but stand
and wait for his bloody demise!
Don't leave me
alone with these guys!
If he dies we're done for!
And now you die, demon traitor.
[KURAMA]
Rose whip!
[Gama cries out in pain]
But... The Makeup of Chains.
Only an amateur depends
on arms and legs for victory.
Way to go Kurama! One down!
An unbelievable 180,
people! Kurama has
somehow taken control
of this fight!
Damn you...
Don't take the
credit for this...
I've killed myself today,
by the mistake of not
sealing your energy as well.
Don't waste your breath
in conversation.
I know with the power
you're using to restrain me
you could easily
heal your injuries.
Release me and I will let
you walk away with your life.
Convincing, aren't you?
But the battle isn't over yet.
Even with my
arms and legs bound,
you are in no shape to fight me.
Don't die pointlessly Gama.
You're too intelligent for that.
I... appreciate
your... confidence!
Don't move!
You'll bleed to death if
you keep trying to fight!
It's of no use. Be wise.
That was the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
[KOTO]
Uh, one...
You were correct, after all.
It's wholly your fault that you
die in vain. I cannot pity you.
[KOTO]
Four...
Five...
[KOTO]
Six...
Seven...
The death is yours!
What?
You never asked what
gave my makeup its power,
what made it different from
the makeup of those human fools.
The difference is
the main ingredient, Kurama.
It's made of my blood.
I have given you...
The Makeup of the Seal.
I am definitely not
liking the sound of that!
[GAMA] It's what I should
I've done from the start.
I've sealed your Spirit Energy.
Kurama.
[GAMA] Your entire power
trapped inside your body.
Even as I fade,
the affect will live on.
I've secured victory
for my Shinobi sect.
And so I die, knowing
it is not in vain.
[KOTO]
Nine...
Ten.
Urameshi Team
takes the first point
Will the next fighters
please approach the ring!
[KOENMA] But Kurama can't
even defend himself!!
It's Touya, the Master of Ice.
Get him out of there, Yusuke!
You fought bravely, Gama.
I assure you that
your death will be honored.
Kurama, will pay.
[NARRATOR] A new opponent
from Team Masho steps forward.
As Kuwabara lies severely
wounded on the sideline.
Hiei and the Masked fighter
stay trapped within
the force field.
And a paralyzed Kurama
stands helpless in the ring,
his energy locked inside.
What deadly powers will
the Ice Master unleash,
and how will Yusuke's
shattered team survive?
This is bad.
[YUSUKE] In case you
stepped out to the bathroom,
my team's running
pretty damn thin--
And now ice guy's stepping
in trying to make it worse!
You know those
inflatable punching toys
that you hit
and they bounce back,
and you hit him
again, and they bounce back--
it's gonna be a lot like that.
Of course, unless Kurama
can use that big brain of his
to figure a sweet way out.
Meanwhile, I'll try to get
the Masked Fighter and Hiei
away from spaghetti
girl's stupid force field,
and there's drama
you won't want to miss!
That's all next time,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪