♪
[NARRATOR]
Tension is mounting
as the Dark Tournament
edges closer to its end.
After great pains,
Yusuke has narrowly passed
Genkai's final test
and absorbed her
Spirit Wave Orb.
Meanwhile, Hiei,
Kurama, and Kuwabara
continue the semi-final round,
persevering through
Team Uraotogi's strange,
mystical items
to take a 3-0 lead.
But now match
four pits Kuwabara
against their cutthroat leader.
Hey Genkai, you take
care of this guy for me?
Anything you want Yusuke.
You've completed
your training under me.
Nice.
[YUSUKE] Screw this test!
I'm getting' us out of here!!
You'd better rest easy
until the final round, Yusuke.
I'll make sure your
team gets that far.
Puu.
[GENKAI] Same for you,
little one.
Guess I owe Koenma
one for getting you here.
You really are a guide for
your more thick-headed self.
[GENKAI]
The last chapter starts.
[GENKAI THINKS] Thanks, now an
old lady can die in peace.
Wow!!
Hurry and beat
that ugly dude!
[GIRL DEMON 1] Do you think
he can really hear us??
[GIRL DEMON 2]
Oh yeah!
[GIRL DEMON 3]
Give me your belt, Shishi!!
Well Shishi Wakamaru,
those girls are really into you.
Too bad after I'm done you'll
be chopped Sui-wakamaru!!!
No!
Hurt one hair on his pretty head
and we'll kick your nasty butt!
[GIRL DEMON 3] No
one wants to kiss you!!
That's not true!
I've got a girl who wants
to kiss me all day long,
and she's a lot
cooler than you!!!
Let's get started,
my defective friend.
I've got fame to achieve.
Oh, that is so it! You
are totally going down!!
Come on!
We've got the fourth match--
Shishi Wakamaru versus
Kuwabara! And begin!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Better start cheering Yukina.
I think I'm gonna need
all your help on this on.
Not much of
a turnout.
What happened? Is it
possible we've come too late?
No, absolutely not--the one
thing that I'm sure about
is three o'clock sharp,
and that was less
than an hour ago!
Maybe it took less than an
hour for the fights to end.
Wait a second,
the semi-finals!
Weren't those supposed
to be different?
A true gumshoe as
always, Keiko! You're right!
All we have to do now
is go to the new stadium!
Great and where is it?
This is bad.
Got 'ya!
Don't be ridiculous.
And here's my brand of fighting!
No tricks or troublesome fog
just an open neck and a sword!
Shishi can read
his every maneuver.
That's it.
My head as a trampoline
is where I draw the line!!
[KUWABARA] What are
you doin' to me!
I'm not ugly, okay!!
Nice last words.
I've lost all trace of him.
It's as if he's ceased to exist.
Um, what's the
rule on this one?
He was in the ring,
but now he's not--but that cloth
he was wrapped in
still is--uh...
[SHISHIWAK]
He lost.
Clearly, he's not in the ring.
As to where he actually is,
I don't know or care.
You'll have to ask
the Cape of No Return
for such trivial details.
Somewhere in this
world or maybe the next,
or maybe another dimension.
I just know he's uncomfortable.
[KOTO] Juri, we're
waiting for a decision!
Right. Well Kuwabara is
indeed not in the ring
and hasn't been
for over ten counts!
I say Shishi Wakamaru wins!
[DEMON GIRL] Look at me Shishi!!
Look at me! Look at me!!
Good and well,
you got the first one!
Now on these second two,
I wanna see blood!
Give us the kind of
pain we can remember!!
Guess I'll have to entertain the
demon boys with this next one.
[KUWABARA]
Somebody catch me!!!
You're gonna pay for this Shi--
What the...?
[BOTAN]
Yoo-hoo!!
Hey Kuwabara!
You wouldn't happen to know
how to get to the new stadium,
would you?
Hey Yukina!
Did you and the others get
lost in the cape thingy too?!
What do you mean the others?
We're not
lost, either!!
Long time no see, tulip!
Hey baby!!
Felt my rockin' rhythm
and had to follow?
Actually, we just went to
the wrong ring on accident.
Now, now, there's
no accident here.
No, it's a thing
we call destiny!
Lost another fight,
didn't you baby brother?
Well, I guess
you could say that.
Our lives on the line and you're
fighting like a fifth-grader.
[SHIZURU]
Keep your guard up!
Jab with your left,
follow with your right!
What's so hard about this?
I guess we know where
Kuwabara gets the motivation
to win so badly.
Sorry sis, my fault.
I'm sure I'll do better
on the next one--okeedoke.
Hey sweetie, do you have any
more of that healing power?
Team Uraotogi
receives a free space,
and for Team Urameshi
it's the Masked Fighter!
I'll be happy to go again.
How about yourself?
I said from the start I
would be the substitute.
I just didn't know it
would be this much fun.
Assuming you don't mind Kurama.
[GENKAI]
Wait.
Just who the hell are you?
I hope you don't
expect me to believe
you're the same Masked Fighter
who was on our team
before, you imposter.
She had
tremendous power.
You're a weakling.
[GENKAI]
Yusuke has it now.
[KURAMA THINKS]
She could be telling the truth.
It's the same
smell, only older.
How awfully disappointing.
I wanted a good match...
I can feel your fragility
from here. Although--
I don't know who you are.
What do you say we
remove that little mask?
[JURI] It's match
five, everyone!
Shishi Wakamaru versus
the Masked Fighter!
Let's go!
[GENKAI] He's swift!
[KOTO] Now it's Team Urameshi
who's running from the blade--
though I'd say this young lass'
dodging techniques are
a little more extensive.
You seem to have lost
a great deal of strength
since I last saw you fight.
But more importantly.
The intrigue of your identity
is stealing my spotlight!
Wait a second, didn't she
have pink hair last time?
She's old!
[HIEI THINKS]
She is an imposter.
[GENKAI THINKS] Didn't realize
how much older I'd feel
without my Orb.
Hopefully I don't need to tell
you that's a different person.
Their team is obviously
using that mask
as a way to sneak additional
players into their rotation.
Um, and that's against
the rules, isn't it?
Even if this woman is the one
substitute they're allowed,
she cannot
enter the ring
unless the one she
replaces is already dead!
That is what
the book says.
I demand to see proof of
their team member's death.
Otherwise I am forced to ask
for their disqualification.
Okay, let
me see here.
They're cheaters!
They've broken the rules!!
The penalty for
cheating is death!!
Yeah, he's right!
String 'em up!
Let's send a message
to these human filth!
Kill 'em!!!
Well, this is a
little unexpected.
The legality of
the Urameshi Team
has been called into question,
and the bloodbath's been delayed
in the hopes of some
kind of group lynching!
Kill 'em all!!
[KOTO] A replay of
Team Urameshi's fight
against the Dr. Ichigaki Team
is now on the jumbo-screen!
This was the first time
we saw beneath the mask,
and as we see, it was
definitely a much younger girl!
I've just received word
from the Tournament Committee.
They are reviewing the
situation as we speak
and ask for your patience as
they come to a final decision.
And in the meantime,
as your--groovy broadcaster--
I'll be panning the
audience for your opinions.
How do you call it?!
What about you, sir?
What was the question?
[KOTO] The two different
fighters under the mask?
How do you think
it should be called?
Ah yes of course!
There's really no question.
The younger girl
is far more attractive.
Kay.
What about you?
Any thoughts on this?
The Old Man and
the Sea, Hemingway.
[KOTO] Perhaps we should just
sit and be quiet, instead.
I don't see what's
so hard about it--
First we had the
hot young Genkai.
And now we've got
the old one. It's easy!
They're the same?
[KOENMA] Yusuke must have
completed his final test,
which means the bulk of
Genkai's energy is now in him.
Genkai can't return
to her younger form
because she
doesn't have the power.
Sir, if that's true
you need to hurry and tell
the Tournament Committee!
They're probably
going to disqualify us!
[KOENMA] Holy smoking
ogres, you're right!!
I am the owner
of the team aren't I??
Koenma sir, may I ask what
you're doing in the corner?
I'm getting ready!
[BLUE OGRE] But aren't we
kind of in a rush?
This is the Committee
we're talking about!
They're serious high rollers !
You don't think they'll
listen to a baby, do you?
No way.
[KOENMA] Let's go
makes a difference.
[KOTO] Alright people!
I've received the final
word from the committee!
[KOENMA]
Oops!
This is crazy, kinda
feels like an award show.
Well anyway, I'll just
go ahead and read here.
By the authority of
the Tournament Committee,
in unanimous decision, the
Masked Fighter's eligibility,
and Team Urameshi's
future, is ruled.
[KOENMA] Move over!
No problem! The fight
between Shishi Wakamaru
and the Masked
Fighter will continue!
Are you serious?!
They would never say that!
It's Koto! She sided
with Yusuke last time!
She cheated! She read it wrong!
Human--
sympathizer!
My goodness-- where do you guys
get these things to throw at me?
Let's execute her
with the rest of 'em!
[TOGURO 2]
That isn't very polite.
It's Toguro!
Oh man, you don't think
he heard us, do you?
Just shut up, hear
what he has to say!
[TOGURO 2]
Team Urameshi did not cheat.
I wanted you all to know that.
To understand why, you merely
have to know who that woman is.
While employing the
technique she's so fond of,
the body of the user does
a most impressive thing.
Its cells return to the moment
when they were strongest.
The young girl
you saw before,
and the old woman there
now are the same person.
The human psychic who
created the Spirit Wave.
It's been such a long time since
we've talked, hasn't it Genkai.
[DEMON 2]
The Genkai?
[DEMON 3] But, why would such
a legend hide behind a mask?
Hold on, did I
miss something here?
Why does Toguro act
like he knows her?
You're the renowned
psychic Genkai--
so fate smiles on me after all.
I won't have to wait for Toguro
before I get my celebrity!
You seem like just
an old woman to me,
but your name is known
by nearly every apparition.
And now I will be famous too,
as the one who killed you.
I won't dally around
with you any more.
We'll need to give
an appropriate death!
That weapon...
The Banshee Shriek--I think it's
such a lovely name for a sword.
It has the power to
beckon lost demon souls
into the ring with us.
It should be the perfect way
to make myself a reputation.
I've seen a sword
like that before,
and I don't believe he
understands the danger of it.
It has more power than he does.
It should be pretty close.
We better not have missed it
because of your little detour.
Hey, I just
went the way I felt!
I'm sure they're fine, anyway--
Hiei was all fired up.
Hiei--He's the quiet one with
the gifted eyes, isn't he?
The one who didn't want
to play cards with us all.
Oh sure, if by gifted
eyes you mean freakish!
Why you all
interested in him?
Listen, don't start thinking
he's cool or anything.
He's scary and he'll
bite off your head!
[YUKINA]
Oh.
Take that back, Kuwabara!
That's no way to talk
of a perfectly decent guy!
Decent guy? That's not
what you said before!
Uh--you must be confused.
I've always thought
Hiei was a swell person,
and you should too,
especially since
Yukina happens to be...
Yes, tell them
I'm her brother.
I'll rather enjoy
torturing you to death.
[KEIKO] What's wrong
with her, all of a sudden?
[KUWABARA] Maybe
she ate some bad meat.
Who knows, maybe
I ate it too.
My stomach's felt squirmy
ever since we started walkin.
[KUWABARA]
Hey! Urameshi!
Is he okay?
You--
It's all right, you guys.
He's just sleeping.
[KEIKO THINKS] You gave
us a real scare, Yusuke.
[KUWABARA] Okay,
what is it with this guy?
At first he doesn't
show for our match,
and then he's
daydreamin' under a tree!
Oh, look at those cuts! Gross!
But what in the heavens
could have happened to him?
Something very painful--
something that
made him stronger.
Thanks a lot,
misses psychic reader.
Well okay guys, we better
get to the stadium.
Pretty important
fights, you know.
[KEIKO] Puu--
I didn't even see you!
Did you take care
of our favorite boy?
Fatso.
[crowd noise]
Sounds like another
match is gettin' started.
[GENKAI THINKS] If I convert
everything I've got
left into energy blasts,
I'll have three shots.
That's all. I
better not waste them.
Are you ready?
[GENKAI THINKS] I have
to survive this fight.
And face him once more.
[NARRATOR] As reunited
friends return to the
stadium with Yusuke on arm,
Genkai will fight with
her identity revealed,
and her power
already given away.
[YUSUKE] Once upon a time,
I compared this guy's
team to a boy band
and he made a nasty face at me.
Well now the nasty's
in full swing,
and I'm just thinking
the boy band thing
fits better than ever--
he's even got a
fancy light show!
Granted the lights are
actually evil demon souls
wanting to devour my mentor,
but hey, every group's
got their own spin, right?
Anyway, you need
to check this one out,
as the old grandma who can
change into a hot chick at will
takes on the
fame-crazed front man--
Without her energy
uh, no thanks to me.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪