♪
[NARRATOR] Seven psychics
are forging a tunnel
between the human
and demon worlds,
hoping to annihilate
the human race.
One of the psychics, Sea Man,
can make indestructible
monsters by mixing water
with his own blood.
He has attacked Kuwabara
and his friends,
who foolishly left
the safety of the group
for a night on the town.
With Kurama missing,
Yusuke storming off in anger,
and Genkai protecting
the fractured group,
no one is coming to the rescue.
And with Kuwabara still unable
to use his Spirit Energy,
he cannot save himself.
[GENKAI] Dimwit!!!
What the hell's your
problem, old lady?
I thought you were leaving the
group to look after Kuwabara.
I said I was going out to
the arcade, Miss Senile!
How old are you??
Kuwabara can't use
his powers right now
and killers are stalking us.
Ergo, you choose
to play pinball?
It's his fault!
He shouldn't have left me
hanging for a stupid pop band!
Besides, he's lost all his
juice like you said.
Why would those guys waste
their time on a non-fighter?
[GENKAI] He hasn't lost it.
It just hasn't awakened yet.
Yusuke, notice your friend's
energy next time you see him
It's like a hatching egg.
There is perfectly good reason
his power has been gone
since the Dark Tournament ended.
Kuwabara is gifted with
unparalleled Spirit Awareness.
I believe his body sensed
the coming danger months ago,
and began a transformation
to prepare for it,
without him
consciously knowing.
What I fear, is if the
enemies realize this,
he won't be their
last target then.
He'll be their first.
[thunder]
Well thanks for
telling me so soon.
[BOTAN]
Yusuke, wait...
I'm gonna get you...
You know that.
[SEA MAN] Why aren't
you trying to run?
If you try to save your
friends, you'll die.
[KUWABARA]
You can't bury honor.
Hey, it's okay man.
We know there's no chance
to save us. Just go.
One of us should live on, right?
We've been best friends
since our first street brawl.
Whether it's livin' or dyin',
we're doing it together.
You can't mean that.
You're a human like us all.
No one would make that
kind of sacrifice.
[thunder]
No!!
Kuwabara!
--Please just go!
--Run away!
See what your friendships
did for you? You're beaten!
[SEA MAN] Why are still trying?
You're powerless!
You can't win!
They're my friends.
Enough of your
puffed-up ideals.
That's not what the
world is really like.
So your friends
keep you going, huh?
What the??
[all cry out]
[KUWABARA]
No!
[Sea Man laughs]
You're motivation's
gone, Kuwabara!
They're going to drown,
and you can't get them out!
Ah, I forgot about his tail!
How sad...
You couldn't think
of anything better to do
than running
into a deathtrap.
Now that's survival
of the fittest.
Oh, don't be stupid.
You're inside my Territory now.
A dimension made
entirely of water.
You can no
sooner escape it
than you can leap
into another dimension.
The Territory remains
unless I'm knocked out!
But you can't reach me now.
You have to escape to beat me,
and beat me to escape!
A real bind!
I guess we've shown whose
convictions win in the end.
Look, your friends
have already drowned.
Guys!! No!!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
I can still save 'em.
I just have to act now!
I have to get us out!
I have to be stronger!
What's wrong with me??
Wow! You really don't learn!
I told you it's impossible!
Your lungs must be
filling up with water now.
Come on, beg for me to save
only your life and maybe I will.
[SEA MAN] Show me your true
self-centeredness and beg!
After all, you are a human.
It's how we are.
[SEA MAN]
No. What is this?
He's in another dimension.
He can't possibly break through.
[SEA MAN] Unless...
unless he's the one.
We're in need of a
psychic who can slice
the Kekkai Barrier Net
into Pseudo Space.
Someone who can
dispel dimensions.
Then he's the one...
The one Sensui's looking for.
[SEA MAN] But I'm
not ready for this...
What the??
Tremendous energy!
[YUSUKE]
Come on!
He broke it.
He broke my Territory.
He swung his sword
across two dimensions.
He is... The one, Sensui...
I didn't know it
until it was too late.
[SEA MAN THINKS]
He's going to kill me.
Your life's in my hands now.
And I'd like nothing
more than to give you
just what you deserve,
after all you've done.
You deserve to die!
But I can't.
You can't?
[KUWABARA] Boy, it's
gonna be a long walk home.
You're actually saving me?
But I just tried to murder
you and your friends.
How can you even
want to help me?
[KUWABARA] When men do
what they're supposed to do,
it's not always about
what they want.
[KUWABARA]
Jeeze!
[YUSUKE] What is this,
why are we back here?
[BOTAN] Well we tracked the
signal. Maybe he made it back.
[YUSUKE]
Kuwabara!
Damn it!
What the hell
happened out there?
I... saved 'em all.
All by myself, Urameshi.
But whose energy was that?
[SNIPER] Mr. Sensui.
[SENSUI]
Hello, Mr. Hagiri.
Sorry if I don't call
you by your nickname.
I'm in a more somber mood.
Now that we've found our
man, we can progress.
Right, that's why I've brought
our colleague, Gourmet, with me.
[SENSUI]
Good.
Toguro, it's time we ask you to
contribute to our valiant cause.
Of course.
I'll do anything to
get vengeance on Yusuke
and his piddling gaggle.
I need more time, though.
In this state I'm useless,
but once I can regroup...
[TOGURO 1] What is this?
Put me down, you brute!
No! What are
you doing??
[Screams]
Welcome back.
[SEA MAN]
You're Yusuke.
That's right, Goldie.
And that's my bed
you're sleeping in,
thanks to the human freight
train there dragging you in
so we could stitch
you back up.
Bro finally did
something helpful
without his girl being around.
[KURAMA] His companions, your
victims, have survived as well.
They informed us all of
the encounter with you.
Then we erased their
memories of last night,
so they wouldn't be
burdened by the darker truths.
Like another human fighting
for the wrong side.
Kuwabara saved your life
after you tried to kill him.
You think your psychic pals
would've done that?
You owe him big.
So start talking.
[KUWABARA] Yeah!
Come clean!
Yeah, I gotta clean my socks.
You what?
Sleep talking: Sleep walking
without the bruises.
You don't understand.
You haven't seen what I have.
We should all die.
Clarify all, you mean
your fellow psychics?
No, I mean all
of us. Humans.
You'd all think so too
if you saw the videotape!
[BOTAN] What video?
[YUSUKE] Yeah. And say
it with more feeling.
It's the video they
label Chapter Black.
You've seen it?
[SEA MAN] Yes I have.
Every single minute of it.
[KURAMA] Chapter Black.
Amazing.
I'm guessing you've
heard of it.
It is legendary,
Hiei's wanted to get his hands
on that tape for years.
[YUSUKE] That good
a flick, huh?
It is a piece of
intelligence,
supposedly kept in
the deepest bowels
of Spirit World's
Records Department.
Over its millennia of existence,
the human race has committed
very heinous crimes
against others and their own.
This videotape
is a compilation.
It documents the most
unspeakable acts of all.
It is said to run
thousands of hours.
I knew well of the
tape's existence,
but never imagined it could
be an impetus in this case.
So many horrifying things
marching across
that giant screen.
You don't know
how we really are.
What we're capable of.
[SEA MAN]
I saw it all.
If you saw it, you'd
think differently, too.
You'd understand we're doomed.
And so we have to--
[YUSUKE]
Have to what, sir judge?!
Have to get us all
eaten the hell up
by some bloodthirsty monster?
That's right!
You're defensive cause
you don't know the truth!
Humanity only
seems good to you
because you were born
in a peaceful time.
But war's our nature,
it'll always come back.
[SEA MAN] Have you ever seen
hundreds of frightened people,
standing in line to
be killed in a camp?
Have you seen horsemen
raid and destroy a village,
dance on the bodies
of their victims,
crushing them as they
celebrated victory,
singing happy songs?
Have you seen a gigantic
bomb wipe away millions
who had never even
picked up a weapon?
Civil war,
where a mom is hacked
down in front of her child,
or a child in front of his mom?
And the soldier...
Breaking up a family
who loves each other,
leading them into a fire.
And his eyes,
enjoying the torture.
Come on, kid. I think you're
passed your sympathy limit.
[YUSUKE] And you
think you're better than
those people on the tape?
Well I know I'm not,
neither are you,
no human can be.
[YUSUKE] What about Kuwabara?
He saved you, right?
And you know, last night
when he came to for a minute,
I asked him,
'Stupid, why the hell
did you save that jerk?'
And he said,
'Because, Urameshi, in his
eyes he was crying for help.'
I thought it was a pretty stupid
thing to say at the time,
but now that I see how scared
you are, I kind of follow.
A big oaf like
Kuwabara,
he's got that bully
look you must hate,
but he cared
about you.
Bet you weren't
expecting that.
[SEA MAN] Every night I see
them. The victims on that tape.
I've always seen
myself like them.
But then in my nightmares,
I'm the one holding the weapons.
You know?
Like all along it's been me who
was doing those terrible things.
And I feel dirtier
and dirtier.
Like I need to make
up for something,
but I don't even know what.
Like I'm the bully.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Perhaps we should
leave him now.
Yeah.
Clearly, he must face his own
demons before he faces us.
[YUSUKE] I see stuff every night
on the stupid six o'clock news
that pisses me off about people.
And that video's got
our all-time worsts.
That's gotta be a
pretty rough experience.
I would imagine so.
It's said it will
turn an average man
against his own kind in
five minutes of viewing.
Hell that's cheery. You may
turn me just talking about it.
Don't worry, Yusuke.
The capacity for evil is but one
ingredient in the human soul.
I... I hope so.
Still, the greatest
concern in my mind
is that the Chapter Black video
is in the enemy's possession.
It clearly has the
ability to turn
almost anyone to their side.
The footage must
be provocative.
I confess there was a
time even I wanted to see.
Was! Was!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Jeez,
he's making me paranoid!
Anyway, a more
pressing matter...
...you never asked me
where I went yesterday.
Oh yeah...
Truth be known, I went
to speak with Koenma.
You went all the
way to Spirit World?
Why didn't you just
use my briefcase thing?
[KURAMA] I needed to
confront him face to face.
He could never put
my suspicions to rest,
and speaking with Sea Man
has now made me certain...
Koenma knows the exact
identity of our foe.
He what??
[KURAMA] I've planned
a formal meeting to...
[YUSUKE] Earth to
toddler bitch!
You better speak now before I
forever put that pacifier
ten inches down
your throat!
[KURAMA THINKS]
Not quite what I planned.
[KOENMA] Hey Yusuke,
I'm glad to see
you've regained some enthusiasm.
It's good in small doses.
Kurama says you knew who was
behind this from the very start.
Why the hell haven't
you told me?
[KOENMA] I wasn't positive
until the video tape.
Only one man has a copy of that,
I just didn't want
to believe it.
Cut to the meat, pal!
[KOENMA] As you wish, Yusuke.
The name of the mastermind:
Shinobu Sensui.
He was the Spirit Detective of
the earth before you came along.
This is a photo of Shinobu
Sensui in high school,
when he began working for
me as a Spirit Detective.
That face, the one who
confronted us in the fairway,
but he looks a lot older now.
[KOENMA] He was gifted with
an incredibly strong sense
of right and wrong.
Perhaps too strong.
It was about ten years ago
when he simply disappeared.
In the weeks leading up to that,
I remember he always
asked me the same question.
[KOENMA] Are we
even worth protecting?
Then the Chapter Black video
vanished from the vault,
and so did he.
We tried to track him down,
but to no use.
I hoped he'd gone
into seclusion,
content to never be bothered.
But why would he
resurface now?
You have to be careful, Yusuke.
He is incredibly lethal.
I'm leaving for Human World now.
A detective...
Well I'm sure as hell
not gonna let some idiot
just like me be the
end of the world!
[SENSUI THINKS] I've given
you a chance, Koenma.
I've waited until you
found my replacement.
Now it's time to
settle the question.
Should human beings live or die?
[NARRATOR]
Shinobu Sensui...
At one time a Spirit Detective,
just as Yusuke is now.
With all the sins of
humanity as a weapon,
can Yusuke bring him down?
[BOTAN] Oh dear,
as if the tunnel
threatening to
unleash giant beasts
on the Earth isn't bad enough!
Koenma makes a rare trip to
Living World in his teenage form
to tell the rest
of the chilling tale,
of the wicked deeds,
familiar faces,
and a young man's
descent into madness.
And what about Sea Man?
Will he join us, or turn
back to his hatred?
Sensui's plan runs deep,
don't forget what he's
done to Elder Toguro.
There's still much to reveal,
as Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪