[NARRATOR]
With little time remaining
until the tunnel to
Demon World is complete,
Kuwabara was finally rescued.
However, his freedom
was short-lived
as he, Kurama, Hiei, and Sea Man
were swallowed by Ura-Otoko,
a dark soul apparition
tamed by Itsuki.
Isolated from their friends,
Yusuke and Sensui are locked
in a one-on-one showdown.
[SENSUI]
I can predict your moves.
Decoding my opponent's
style is my strength,
but I've been doing it
for decades longer.
Then I guess you know this, too,
that trusting what people tell
me s'never been my thing!
[YUSUKE yelling]
[SENSUI groaning]
[NARRATOR] And one of these
Spirit Detectives must fall.
[YUSUKE]
Jeez.
What's that, Sensui?
You forget how to swim?
You drowned?
Great, we'll pack up and go!
You heard Kuwabara,
he's starving.
[SENSUI]
Good hits, detective.
Between that and the water,
my shirt practically dissolved.
[gasps]
Gross. Look at all those scars.
Guess that he wasn't lying
about all those fights
he's been through.
[SENSUI]
Don't you know what they say
about assuming, Kuwabara?
These wounds aren't
from enemies.
No one's ever hurt me that bad.
I gave myself these scars
as a part of my training.
[YUSUKE]
Great, a masochist.
True, though,
his body's well trained.
It's like punching
a tractor tire.
[SENSUI] Now, let's fight like
there's a little more at stake.
[gasps]
[KUWABARA]
Oh, just great!
Now he can make things move
without touchin' 'em.
And that won't be all.
[HIEI]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[SENSUI groaning]
What?!
It multiplied!
Sensui's surrounded
himself with a minefield
of little energy balls. How's
Urameshi gonna get to him now?
The real task will be...
getting away from him.
Perhaps it's time
I stepped up my game.
[grunts]
[SENSUI]
Watch closely.
Splinter Resshuuken!
[YUSUKE] All right, this is
just like playin' dodge ball
in gym class.
[YUSUKE grunting]
[YUSUKE]
Too bad I always skipped gym!
[YUSUKE grunting]
[grunting continues]
[groaning]
[groaning continues]
Oh! Urameshi!
It's really quiet.
Almost eerily quiet.
So what do you think?
Should we take that as
a good omen or a bad one?
Well, I would think
the apocalypse would have
to make a bit of noise.
So, maybe they beat Sensui,
and resealed the hole
to Demon World.
Yeah. I have a feeling
everything worked out
exactly according to plan.
[BOTAN]
Mh-hm.
[GENKAI] No, the hole's
still open, wider than ever.
It's dilating even faster
than it was before.
But how can you tell all
that for sure, Master Genkai?
From the smell.
The smell?
The smell. The Demon World
has a very distinct odor,
and it's growing
stronger from that cave.
[YANAGISAWA sniffing]
Smell anything?
Nothing unusual.
[BOTAN] Genkai, is there
any way you can smell
how much longer it will be
until the tunnel is fully open?
[GENKAI sniffing]
[GENKAI]
Less than ten minutes now.
[BOTAN]
Uhh!
I hope Koenma can make it there
in time with his pacifier.
[KOENMA]
I guess this is where
Kurama's Lamp Weeds
come to an end.
This must've been the
Game Master's Territory.
[KOENMA] All right, if I was
a malevolent crackpot,
where would I set up evil shop?
[KOENMA]
Dank tunnel number three it is.
Hang in there, Yusuke.
Urameshi... Please, don't
tell me that he's... you know.
Poor Mr. Urameshi.
Don't be worried yet.
It will take more than that
to keep Yusuke down.
Are you sure?
[KURAMA] How much more it will
take... that I'm not so sure of.
[YUSUKE grunts]
Is that all you got?
[SENSUI lauging]
[SENSUI]
You are foolishly cocky.
A regrettable sin.
Now, reason number two
why you cannot beat me.
When attacked
from multiple angles,
your defenses are
negligible at best.
What?
[SENSUI]
You think too linearly.
Pitiable. You've been spoiled.
As a fighter you've grown
a little too comfortable
with these gentlemanly
one-on-one duels of yours.
[SENSUI yelling]
[gasps]
I needed to fight many opponents
at once, when persuasion failed.
So, this technique was born
out of that necessity.
Ah, come on. You just did that.
Can we play another P.E.
favorite besides dodge ball?
You know, I play a real
mean game of four-square.
No time for jokes, Yusuke.
[SEA MAN, KUWABARA]
Uh?
His energy is so
much stronger now.
Which brings us
to reason number three.
Why you don't even stand
a slim chance of beating me.
The gap between
your Spirit Energy
and mine is far too great.
If your Spirit Energy
could fill a fishbowl...
...mine would fill the ocean.
Which ocean are we talkin' about
'cause, buddy, some
of them aren't as big.
There's no way! The difference
between them's too much!
He'll-He'll be murdered!
Splinter Resshuuken!
[YUSUKE grunting]
[groans]
[YUSUKE screaming]
You enjoy that as much
as the first time?
Because there's plenty more
where that came from if you did,
so don't be shy.
Hey, get up!
Don't quit now, Urameshi!
Thanks for the hint, Kuwabara.
I never would've thought
of that on my own.
If that's all your Energy can
do, what's that say about mine?
I've beat Saint Beasts
and technique collectors.
I beat Toguro at his best.
I took their hits and
I can sure take yours.
There's a difference.
I fight with divine
justice on my side.
And justice kills!
[SENSUI yells]
[YUSUKE yells]
[YUSUKE]
Here goes nothin'!
Uh.
[grunting]
Surprise!
Maybe I can't defend against
attacks from multiple angles,
but sometimes a good defense
is just kicking ass!
[KURAMA] Individually, those
energy blasts aren't so bad.
It's only when they reconvene
and attack Yusuke all at once
that their power is too strong.
You see? I knew
Urameshi could take him.
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE]
Now it's time for my list!
Reason number one why
I'll smash your face:
I'm just better than you!
And I'm not as predictable
as you'd think.
[YUSUKE grunting]
Bet you didn't see this comin'!
[KUWABARA]
Huh?!
[YUSUKE] You still think you
know what I'm gonna do next?
[YUSUKE laughing]
Hey! Stop clowning! This is
no time to be takin' a dip!
He's never been one
for good manners.
Ahh. I've got to admit,
that was very refreshing.
And now I'm ready
to go a few more rounds.
[yelling]
And now we return to your
same old conventional punches.
[yelling]
It's unfortunate, honestly, to
see that your brief spontaneity
was merely a passing reprieve.
That's way too many
big words, pal!
[chuckles]
So, he went swimming
so he could snap his shirt
like a wet towel?
That should halt Sensui's
Resshuuken blocking,
for the time being, at least.
What is this mockery?
This isn't martial arts.
No, it's called street fighting!
Guess you didn't see it comin'!
[SENSUI grunts]
[coughs]
And you can't get away!
[grunts]
No more fancy blocks!
[yelling]
[SENSUI grunting]
Yeah! Come on, Urameshi,
what are you waiting for?!
Hurry and finish him!
I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know!
[SENSUI grunting]
[YUSUKE] I never pegged you
as being this much of a wuss!
[gasps]
[KUWABARA screams]
[groaning]
Urameshi!
What was that?
It appears he's transformed his
arm into the barrel of a gun.
[HIEI]
It must've taken restraint
to hold back on that
for as long as he did.
[YUSUKE groaning]
Stop your whining!
You're acting like
a little bitch!
Suck it up and get off
your stinkin' ass!
[KUWABARA grunts]
[KURAMA]
His tone has changed.
That doesn't sound like Sensui.
[KUWABARA]
Yeah, he's got potty mouth now.
[ITSUKI]
It's not him.
He has been substituted now.
The only person who can
produce that weapon
is the ruffian known as Kazuya.
Kazuya?
What are you blabbering about?
There's no substitution!
We've been watching
this the whole time
and nothing's come or gone.
Except maybe your marbles.
[gasps]
Multiple personalities?
What?! Oh, don't tell me
this is gettin' weirder.
[ITSUKI]
Indeed.
There are seven. All coexisting
within Sensui's brain.
Each with distinct
traits and talents.
There's seven of him?!
I can't believe this.
I had no idea.
His subconscious created them
to cope with the madness.
It's an impulsive
defense mechanism.
The brain's own primitive
survival instinct.
Witnessing something
beyond the range
of normal human experience,
most will go into shock.
[ITSUKI] Sensui has seen
much in his lifetime,
but nothing like that night.
[screaming]
[ITSUKI]
He created the others
to bear the brunt of that
trauma, and, ever since,
he escaped from
personality to personality,
searching for answers to the
dilemmas that plague his soul.
[SENSUI]
This oughta plug up your wound!
[YUSUKE groaning]
[KUWABARA]
He's got an insanity tag team!
Kazuya is by far
the most ruthless
and cold-blooded of the seven.
He's been known
to torture small children,
purely for its
entertainment value.
[YUSUKE yelps, screams]
[YUSUKE groaning]
[KUWABARA grunting]
[SENSUI laughing]
--[KUWABARA grunting]
--[SENSUI laughing]
[KUWABARA yells]
[YUSUKE groaning]
We ain't officially met yet,
though we do have
a friend in common.
[KUWABARA]
I'm slicin' us outta here!
[KUWABARA grunting]
Minoru's a little
too chatty for my taste,
but I dug that list of his.
I got one to add.
The fourth reason why
you're gonna get skinned.
[laughing]
Because, kid, you ain't
totally off your gourd yet!
Get me out of this
dark soul mess! Come on!
[HIEI]
Step aside!
Uh?
[ITSUKI]
You're wasting your time.
Those dreary weapons
and your faith in them are
nothing more than an insult
to the indestructibility
of my dear Ura-Otoko.
[grunts]
Uh. No.
[SENSUI laughing]
So, now that you're the one
lying there takin' it,
tell me, how's it feel?!
You-You look at me
like I'm crazy.
You think I've gone
off the deep end?
You think you're better than me?
[screaming]
[SENSUI]
♪ Ohhh! ♪
No. I can't bear to watch this.
Is there anything
we can do to help?
[YUSUKE groaning]
[laughing]
You'll never experience
any pleasure
without feeling a little pain!
I'm enjoyin' this way too much.
[SENSUI]
Now come to daddy.
My, you've got the face
of a little angel on ya.
[laughing]
[groaning]
Too bad. I gotta bust it.
Open your mouth.
And close your eyes.
Not this way.
But he's our hope.
Uh.
Urameshi!
[KOENMA]
Shinobu!
[SENSUI]
Heh?
[KOENMA]
Let him go!
[SENSUI]
Shinobu ain't here.
Nice timing.
[NARRATOR] Koenma has
arrived at the last moment,
as one of Sensui's
seven personalities
is a trigger away from
ending Yusuke's life.
But is the Prince of
Spirit World strong enough
to stop his former
Spirit Detective
from killing the replacement?
And if he can't, who will
prevent this mad man
from unleashing the Demon horde
and destroying living world?
[YUSUKE] I never thought
I'd need a toddler to save me,
but now he's all I've got.
Well, besides myself,
and don't forget, there's
still my trusty Spirit Gun.
Hey, sure, it's not a real
gat growin' out of my arm,
but at least I can still make
obscene hand gestures, right?
And as if a barrel
to my head isn't enough
to keep you glued
to the television set,
we finally get
to see what happens
when Koenma takes that
baby toy out of his mouth.
My money's on
his head deflating,
but apparently it's something
a bit more... captivating.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!