♪
[NARRATOR] In the first
match of the final round,
Kurama used every tactic
and energy he possessed
to bring Karasu down.
But a technicality
gave Karasu the win
and Team Toguro a 1-0 lead.
The second match paired Hiei
against the quiet power, Bui.
Hiei's explosive attack
destroyed Bui's axe
and kept him in the game.
But now Bui's
removed his armor,
and the two hardened demons
prepare for their last stand.
Time is wasting.
Let's go ahead and finish.
Quiet, fool! I don't need
to be told to hurry up.
It's in my nature.
[HIEI]
And now the end.
It's been pulling at
the bandages for some time.
I couldn't hold it for long.
You're the next sacrifice
to the Dragon of
the Darkness Flame.
Wow! Fire is leaping
from Hiei's arm
and excited goose bumps
are screaming from my mine!
The big boy is back!
It's even more than before.
Without control
he could kill us all.
That's cool.
Please no eat me,
please no eat me, no!
Koenema-tron 5000 jetpack
ready for take-off.
What's wrong Shizuru?
You look pale.
I feel so cold
all of a sudden.
Do you need a doctor?
No thanks.
No, I feel it too. Something
very dangerous is coming,
and her gift of awareness
only makes it scarier.
The Dragon of the
Darkness Flame.
Getting to see that from
ringside should be interesting,
to say the least.
Yes.
Now I know I can get
fighting moves confused,
but didn't we see
this before?
Tournament's first round,
against Zeru of Team Rokuyukai.
So my Jagan Eye
may not be natural.
But it does give me
exactly what I need!
From the deepest of
pits of Spirit World!
You know it's impossible
to control it completely!
Once I release it I have no say!
[HIEI] In a way,
it has its own mind.
Resisting it is not
something I would do.
Dragon of the
Darkness Flame!!!
Ah, yes, I made quite
a bit of money off that.
This will be the first
time he's used it since,
I guess he finds this
match to be important.
[SAKYO] Good for him.
But Zeru is no Bui.
What an attack!
Our state-of-the-art ring is
already crumbling
under it's power!
This could mean
surprise injuries galore!
Juri, get back! This isn't
a safe place to be right now!
I can't Koto! I don't wanna be
a pretty referee girl anymore!
Okay!
Let's go!
Shouldn't we hide
under somethin'?
Wait, give him
his due time.
It could be
advantageous after all.
[KOENMA] Hold on! You said
it'd kill all of us
if he lost control
like last time!
Yes. But it appears that in
his short training since then
he's learned how to
master it better.
Oh, better!
That's reassuring, yeah!
[KOENMA]
Yusuke. Shut up.
[crowd quivers]
Take it from someone who
was in the ring the first time!
This attack is not the same.
It's like a super
hyper mega dragon!
You ready?
[BUI THINKS] The dragons of
Spirit World devour anyone
who cross their path.
Even the wielder.
[BUI THINKS]
Return it his direction...
And he'll be swallowed
by his own cursed flame.
Dragon of the Darkness Flame!!
[Bui cries out]
Damn... who is
this Bui bastard?
He's actually stopped it.
I didn't think it was possible!
I'm not scared, but we should at
least find a rock to get under!
[KOENMA]
Anytime now. Anytime.
I hope you don't think
that dragon is completed!
[TOGURO 2] I won't
finish you yet Bui.
You have more power than
you're capable of realizing,
I'd like to bring it out.
It will not happen again.
Amazingly Bui's avoided
instant vaporization!
But the dragon's
strength is immense
and it's bulldozing
him around the stadium!
Something has to give!
This is the end, everyone!
That traitor will
destroy us all!!
Well, I guess
the stadium gave!
Alright, people,
this is the mayhem
you can only
expect from the final!
The weaker ones in the crowd
are being instantly incinerated!
It's hell in a basket
and I love it all!!!
You defeat me now,
or become my slave!
Success!
A victory.
Hiei first, Toguro soon after.
What a maneuver!
Bui managed to force the
Dragon of the Darkness Flame
away from himself
and directly toward Hiei
causing the
three-eyed warrior
to be swallowed by his
own beast of destruction!
It's all clear now, Juri.
Time for you to
make the official call!
[KOTO]
Juri!
Tell work I'm sick today, mom.
Juri, we can't have
this gore-fest without you.
[KOTO] Juri, all the rich and
cutie boys will be watching you.
[JURI]
Where?
Well, we see where your
motivation lies, don't we?
Right, I'm coming! Okay.
Hiei can't compete
without a body. So...
The official winner
can only be...
[Juri cries out]
This brings up my next attack.
It's a little different.
Now that's cool!
Explain this!
I can't really articulate
what's happened here, people.
It looked like the
dragon had eaten Hiei!
But now the demon's back
and appears to be unharmed!
[BLUE OGRE]
Go get 'em, Hiei!!
Nice to meet you.
Something gigantic
is still here.
I can't explain it, but
Hiei's attack is on its way.
He, looks wrong.
Why's that Yukina? I don't
think he looks any different
from when he
disappeared a minute ago.
Except that wound on his
arm isn't there anymore.
Come on Bui, don't be a ninny
now! He doesn't have any power!
Yeah, his dragon is gone!
Just rip off his head!
A new attack? Wait, did
he do what I think he did?
It's true, Hiei has consumed
the darkness technique.
[KUWABARA] What?! You
mean he ate the dragon?!
Apparently he's learned
what no one before him has.
The only way to gain real
control of the darkness flame
is to trap it within.
Now the dragon is inside him,
and at his full disposal.
Even Bui must accept
what that means.
Countless centuries.
Countless masters trying
to harness the power
of the Darkness Flame.
Only I have had the courage,
the strength, and the abandon
to realize it's
glorious potential.
I have the power
of the black dragon.
Because now I am the dragon.
[BUI THINKS]
Don't be frightened.
Even if he has attained the
Darkness Flame within his body,
it still isn't stronger
than my Battle Aura. Nothing is.
[HIEI]
Right.
Nice.
And Bui unloads like an angry
toddler in a therapy session!
But Hiei is
absolutely unaffected!
Insane! Hiei has actually
sucked away Bui's Battle Aura,
the secret of all his power!
Come now.
Can't you even test me?
Both are outside the ring!
I'll start the count, uh...
Finish.
The first time
Toguro beat me,
he told me I had the
potential to get stronger.
He was right.
It took someone like him to
show me how weak I was.
[BUI] He kept me at
his side while I trained
hard to kill him.
And I know I reached my max.
But every time I would
get stronger, so would he.
I'm sure it was just
bait to keep me improving.
[JURI]
Four!
[BUI] Now you've beaten
me. What's the point.
Come on, hurry up and kill me.
No... if you want
to die, kill yourself.
Eight! Nine!
I don't take orders,
especially from those I beat.
And ten!
The second fight is over!
Hiei takes the point!
Did you hear that, Toguro?!
We're lookin' at
a tie ball game!!
Uh, wait, this is a
no-dragon-man area okay?
Really awesome, Hiei.
Yeah, awesome.
Uh, why don't you go
about twenty yards that way
and fight the rest of them!
That's against the
rules now, you cretin.
Besides, my attack expired.
Expired?
I don't know if your
brains can imagine it,
but this attack drained
a good deal of my energy.
I'll require some
hibernation to get it back.
Think you can manage
finding a safe place
for my body where it
won't get stepped on?
Did you say
hibernate?
Fancy word
for being lazy.
Listen to me as closely
as you can, you two.
I'm trusting you against
my better instincts
only because I
have no other choice.
Take care of
the Toguro Brothers.
If I wake up and we've lost,
I swear I'll kill you all!
That's Hiei for you.
He faints but he still
has time for threats!
Hold on. So nothing
we do will wake him up?!
[KOENMA] Not long ago
he was on streak of terror.
If he'd had this power then,
it would have been disastrous.
Now it's our asset.
Can I give him a moustache?
[NARRATOR] By finally realizing
the power of the dragon,
Hiei has won the second
match and tied the final round.
Now only the Toguro
Brothers and Sakyo remain.
[SHIZURU] Hi. It's Shizuru.
You know. The older sister.
Well, after an excessive
display of strength
by the guy with
eighties sunglasses,
baby bro gets forced into
fighting the elder Toguro.
You know, he's the freaky
one with straggly hair.
My brother unveils
his new sword,
but straggly hair
can do anything,
and when he puts
on a puppet show
to reveal the
truth about Genkai,
well, there's a good chance my
brother will screw things up,
and everyone will die.
That's next time
on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪