[NARRATOR] Former Spirit
Detective Shinobu Sensui
is in his final stage of
opening a tunnel to Demon World,
and ending the human race.
Current Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
is the only one
who can stop him.
In a cave deep below the city,
the battle has been intense.
But the gap between
the detectives' powers
has proven too great.
Just as Yusuke seemed to find a
detour around Sensui's defenses,
Sensui underwent
a transformation,
not of the body,
but of the mind.
He in fact has seven
different personalities.
Kazuya, the cruelest and
most violent of them all,
has emerged to send Yusuke to a
place he's been once before:
his grave.
Get it, Koenma?
Just stay back.
Shut up, you little shit!
[KUWABARA] No! Get that gun
away from him, you wack-job!
We can't even help him!
I can't take it!
But you don't have a choice.
As you see, I haven't lied.
This specter's belly
is a separate reality,
and we are trapped inside.
The only way to transfer out
of it is through my power,
which I'm sure
you'll never possess.
You... traitor!
[KUWABARA grunts]
What's that for?!
I'm gonna smash him!
Why don't you think a little.
Ituski's the only one
who can free us.
Kill him, and we'll
be trapped here.
[KOENMA]
Please, Sensui.
Doesn't humanity have
enough sins already?
This ain't a sin.
It's just the first step
in pushing justice and
order into the universe.
If it makes you feel better,
we can just call it
capital punishment.
[KOENMA]
No! Don't do it!
There's nothing much I like
better than brains on a wall.
[SENSUI]
Huh?
[YUSUKE]
Spirit Gun!
[YUSUKE groaning]
[KOENMA grunting]
[YUSUKE]
Shoulda' been his head.
[BOTAN]
What's that?
Yusuke's Spirit Gun.
There's no mistaking it.
Must've fired the big one.
You think it was enough
to have defeated Sensui?
I'd like to say so.
A blast like that was enough to
cut down Toguro at top strength.
But Sensui's signal
still feels the same,
and after that shot, Yusuke will
be as good as a toy pistol.
Heh. I didn't realize you
still had so much energy left.
You nearly caught
me by surprise.
Yeah? Well, imagine
my surprise, pal.
I had a whole mental picture
of what you'd look like
as a heap of charcoal.
The look really suited you, too.
[KOENMA]
No! Get up!
[SENSUI laughing]
[KOENMA]
Bad time for laughter, Sensui.
Do you really think
I'll let you go on like
this one moment longer?
[KOENMA]
I'm no human.
I don't have their limitations.
I'll stop you whatever the cost.
[laughing]
[KOENMA] Since I helped make
you, I'll give you warning.
Stop this plan before
I am forced to act.
"Helped to make me."
Yeah, you got no idea
how right you are.
It's just freaking hilarious.
Can't get me if you
don't know what I am.
[KOENMA]
What do you mean?
I know you enough.
Nah, you know that
goody two-shoes Shinobu,
but you don't got
the smallest tip-off on me.
So, let me give you
the first peak.
Name's Kazuya, and Shinobu's
taking a little nap right now,
which was my idea.
I show when the other
six can't handle it.
[KOENMA]
Hold on, the other six?
That's right,
it's a party in here.
And don't get me wrong,
some may rub me the wrong way,
but we see enough in common.
We all sprung
this plan together.
All seven of us.
So, that is what he meant.
The thought Murota read from
his mind was misinterpreted.
By seven, we assumed he meant
the psychics he recruited.
[SENSUI] Let's dig
a hole. Each one of us.
Seven graves will be
a decent start.
We assumed Sensui
cared for his team,
but, in truth, the seven
were his own personalities.
The psychics were expendable.
He planned to be sole
survivor from the start.
That's correct.
As his partner from
the naïve years,
I'm the only one who realized,
but I can take care of myself.
It was the night of
the raid when it began,
when he learned his murders
as humanity's defender
could not be justified.
[ITSUKI] The guilt was
too much for Shinobu,
so Kazuya was created
to take responsibility
for these deplorable acts.
[ITSUKI]
Yet, as the plan fermented,
he saw violence
would not be enough.
He needed to recruit help
through lies and manipulation.
More sins Shinobu
could not face.
So, Minoru appeared: the orator.
[ITSUKI]
And so it went.
At every moral crisis that stood
in the way of Sensui's plan,
a new personality would
be forged to do the work.
It solved the paradox
of how one can punish,
if doing so requires you
to commit the very same sins.
This way, his core soul could
remain morally undefiled.
Of the seven personalities,
one of them is a girl.
She has a beautiful mind,
capable of the most delicate
and loving thoughts and poetry
that I've ever heard spoken.
She would talk to me
in the dead of night,
always crying, venting sorrows,
that, if not expressed,
would've killed Sensui
from a broken heart.
Besides Shinobu,
I favor her the most.
Sometimes I think we're in love.
What are you saying?!
No, don't answer. I don't wanna
catch your crazy disease!
[KOENMA]
I don't doubt you, Kazuya.
I honor your true existence, and
I admit I can't relate with you.
Call Shinobu. Please,
I need to speak with him.
Ha!
Hey, Shinobu. You awake yet?
Shinobu!
[laughs] He's sayin' he
don't wanna talk to ya.
He sayin' he hates you too much.
[KOENMA] But he pays
attention to what I say,
doesn't he, Kazuya?
Shinobu, listen to me.
This isn't the answer
you're seeking.
It's not too late to stop--
[SENSUI]
Sorry, princie.
But you're wrong about that.
[DEMONS grumbling]
The calming period is
over, it's stabilized.
Face it, little prince,
we've all chosen our fate.
[KOENMA]
Then so have I.
[NARRATOR]
The Mafuuken,
also known as the Conscious
Ring, or the Wicked Seal.
When fully powered, it is
the strongest defensive spell
in all of Spirit World.
For centuries, Koenma has
transferred his Spirit Energy
into his pacifier, the vehicle
for his Mafuuken spell.
A precaution for darker times.
When released,
the Mafuuken will create
a Kekkai Barrier Net to
ensnare the encroaching enemy.
Far more powerful than
the Kekkai between worlds,
it specializes on demons,
and can even trap
the S-Class with ease.
[growls]
If I engage this Mafuuken,
it will first seal
the precious tunnel
that you've poured
your life into creating.
Then, I'll trap you
inside the net,
and you'll never move again.
[SENSUI]
Huh?
I've kept this thing
between my teeth
for most of my existence,
giving it my Spirit Energy.
It was for humanity's next dark
day in a few hundred years.
Yet, you give me no choice
but to use it now.
Well, you're just as
stupid as Shinobu says.
You can't use that fancy
weapon on little old us.
Who's gonna save the humans
in that supposed dark time now?
We must handle each new
dilemma as it comes to us.
If your plan is
allowed to continue,
in a few hundred years there
will be nothing left to save.
This way your
conspiracy will end.
You're finished, Sensui,
unless you plan to kill me.
My, my. You really
ain't screwin' around.
You should consult
with your other sides.
Are you really ready
to be damned?
Because surrender and torment
are your only choices.
We'll chat it over.
[KOENMA] If only I could
rearrange the gears
turning in your head. I don't
want to use this on you.
Please, return to
the Sensui you were.
[KOENMA] If there has
ever been a human destined
to be Spirit Detective,
it was you.
You were born with
incredible powers,
and an obsession for making
things right... and just.
[KOENMA]
It was my fault.
I was too eager
to close the case.
How could I not have
known how you would react
when you saw the
darkest vices of man.
When you realized
your life's work
of protecting humans from demons
was not a crusade of pure
justice, but a study in gray.
[SENSUI yelling]
[SENSUI]
It is a war waged against evil,
yet the evil is within.
[SENSUI] How else can I justify
what I've done but to continue.
Then, shouldn't all humans die?
[KOENMA]
But there has never been a light
that did not cast a shadow.
Darkness, by its nature,
must always be
entwined with good.
And I must take the burden
for what you are now.
I exposed you to that truth
your idealistic mind
can't understand.
So, if you continue this battle
for unearthly principles,
if that's what you decide,
then I will go with you.
[KOENMA] I'll trap myself
in the net with you,
share the pain of being trapped
without movement for eternity.
It's the least I can do.
[KOENMA]
Please, Shinobu. Come around.
We've come to our choice.
It's unanimous
between all seven.
[KUWABARA grunts]
[laughs]
We're continuing our plan
as soon as I kill you off.
[chuckles]
[KOENMA]
I feared as much.
[yells]
[KOENMA]
Mafuuken!
[KOENMA grunts]
[gasps] What the hell?
[SENSUI]
Huh?
Go!
Urameshi!
What'd you do that for?
Guess he's recovered.
Idiot! Why did you interfere?!
Maybe I got a concussion,
but the way I remember it,
I'm the damn detective
and this is my case to solve.
If you go wastin' away, Mr.
Pacifier, that means I failed.
[grunts]
Though it's nasty that
it's covered in spit.
Hey, you should thank Koenma.
He bought me time
for some beauty sleep.
Right.
I forgot you inherited that
wench's Spirit Wave technique.
Makes you a real
good healer, don't it?
Just give yourself
a pat on the back.
Don't bother with the bull.
Let's get back to
killing each other.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're no match for him.
Give me back the Mafuuken, now!
I'm trying to do
this the nice way.
And what's the alternative?
You gonna tie me up
with your shirt?
Not exactly.
Actually it goes a little
something like this.
[KOENMA grunts]
[grunts] You have no idea how
long I've waited to do that.
Now, it's just the way
it should be. You and me.
One of you in there
said you didn't care
about the tunnel now.
Well, that's exactly how I feel.
The world ends, the world
survives, I don't friggin' care.
All I care about
is that you are beaten!
Well, that's awfully reassuring.
Yeah, considering
he's our last hope,
his priorities are
a little skewed.
Your name's Kazuya, right?
The guy with the gun?
Well, go get me someone else.
Say what?
That's right, take
your gravelly voice
and run back to your biker bar!
Show me the top man!
You're really a brainless
bitch, aren't ya?
I'm out now 'cause
I do the sick work.
You don't get it.
I can't waste time on you.
You're too easy.
[growls]
I'll blow your skull off!
[YUSUKE yelling]
[SENSUI groaning]
[YUSUKE]
Damn!
[YUSUKE groaning]
[grunts] I'm not hurt,
I'm humoring you.
[SENSUI groaning]
Be nasty all you want.
I don't care if you
torture cute animals.
That doesn't make you strong.
--Now, show your real leader.
--[SENSUI] No!
I wanna to beat your strongest
side so I know it's done.
You got it?
[SENSUI]
Uh! I can take him! I can--!
Which freak am I talking to now?
My name is Shinobu.
It's an honor to meet you.
He's the true mastermind, right?
I guess I've never heard
the real him until now.
[ITSUKI]
Huh.
[SENSUI] My colleagues have
told me so much about you,
but, at last, we can be
properly introduced.
To be honest,
this is the first time
I've shown my face
to anyone in months.
The pleasure's mine.
What? This is like a prisoner
tipping his executioner
to get a clean cut.
[laughing]
[yelling]
[YUSUKE groaning]
No, he's gonna kill him!
The pleasure's mine.
Bastard!
[YUSUKE grunts]
[SENSUI] Itsuki, may I have
the arms and spare clothes?
[ITSUKI]
Hm.
It's so weird. I've never
seen Mr. Sensui like this.
Yes, his countenance
has changed from before.
I dare say he sounds innocent.
That's because he is.
In his reality, Shinobu has
never committed a crime.
He knows his other
sides have done wrong,
but he's separated from it,
able to blame them and
grieve for what they've done
while realizing it's necessary.
Such a complex side. I guess
that's why I like him the most.
What? That doesn't make sense.
If this side's so darn pure,
how did he get away
with hurting Urameshi?
Not that it matters.
Just goin' by this new name
can't make him
any stronger, right?
Don't worry, Urameshi!
Whoever he says he is, it's
all part of the same Sensui!
You can take him out!
[YUSUKE] I sensed it that first
time I met him in the city.
He's been hiding somethin'. His
curve ball. And now I can tell.
He's finally ready
for the wind up.
Definitely somethin' more than
the rest of his peanut gallery.
This is gonna be fun.
Be honest. Are you still
strong enough to face me?
A funny thing about that.
I did a little power
inventory, and it turns out
I have exactly enough to
cream your face into the wall.
Oh? You mean you really
believe that's possible?
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
[NARRATOR] At last, Yusuke comes
faces to face with Shinobu,
the original and
purest personality
in Sensui's fractured mind.
What does Shinobu have that
his other sides do not?
And how can Yusuke defeat him
with the tunnel's completion
only minutes away?
[YUSUKE]
Two words: holy crap!
I've been calling Sensui's
secret a curve ball,
but cannon ball's more like it.
And while the cave sides are
giving me deep-tissue back rubs,
Koenma's powering up
in ways we've never seen,
determined to unleash
this Mafuuken
and spend the rest of eternity
trapped with Sensui,
but I won't let that happen.
So, while my team's stuck
in a ghost's stomach,
and thousands of
demons count down
to all-you-can-eat dinners
at the human buffet,
I'm gonna show you moves
like you've never seen.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!