♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke
has started his second
case as Spirit Detective:
Infiltrating the compound of
the powerful psychic, Genkai.
Deciding to pass her technique
to one person before she dies,
Genkai is holding a contest
to find the most worthy pupil.
Yusuke must win
to ensure her powers
don't fall in
the wrong hands,
because Spirit World has
discovered a disturbing fact.
One of the eight finalists
could be a demon in disguise.
[YUSUKE THINKS] None of 'em
really look like a demon.
From here on you
can forget about sympathy.
The final test
will be a tournament
between the eight of you,
until one is standing.
You'll fight until your opponent
is dead, or incapacitated.
I don't care which.
[GENKAI]
Come on now! Walk!
[KUWABARA] Hey! What's
wrong with the lights?!
I don't like that lady!
[YUSUKE] Yeah Grandma! You
expect us to fight in the dark?
Yes you little crap,
that's exactly what I expect.
You must use your
Spirit Awareness to see.
Use weapons if you've got 'em.
Hit 'em where you
like, anything goes.
The winner is the one
who can walk back alive.
Sounds like a typical
Saturday-morning street fight,
Huh, Kuwabara?
I'm not sure Urameshi,
I've got a bad hunch.
Like some of that that
scary stuff from the forest
has followed us
here somehow. You know?
Like some beast has
been stalking me all this way
but he's too
afraid to attack me.
Well that proves it then.
After all those tests
Rando must still be
after Genkai's technique.
Who's Rando? Is he the beast?
Somethin' like that.
I don't have
time to explain now.
Just tell me, is that hunch
coming from one of those guys?
[KUWABARA] Hard to say,
I think the feeling
is hidden really good.
It's just hanging in the air,
and I can't tell
where it's coming from.
Sorta' like a...
Sorta' like a fart in
a crammed elevator?
Well yeah, I guess so.
[GENKAI] Now before we start.
You all introduce
yourselves, and speak up!
Name's Musashi.
I'm a fourth-degree black belt
under Kendo of
the Shibattou school.
I hunt down evil
beings and destroy them.
I am Shorin,
a psychic-in-training.
I have traveled the world in
search of a perfect instructor.
People call me Kibano.
I'm a master in
every style of martial arts,
and I live to
test my own limits.
Chinpoh the Wanderer.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm Kazemaru of the Ninjas.
Bodyguard of
government officials.
I've been trained in
the Ninjitzu art of stealth.
My name is Kuroda.
Contract killer.
Kazuma Kuwabara, the worst
punk of Sarayashki Junior High.
Yusuke Urameshi.
The much, much worser punk
of Sarayashki Junior High.
Now everyone pick up
the arrow you think is pretty.
That'll decide the order.
Koenma sir! Can I get
your seal of approv-huh?
What's going on here?
He says there's
no time for business.
Koenma sir. We have the
match-ups for the tournament.
[KOENMA] Bring up
the first match.
[KOENMA] And the results
from the power tests.
[BLUE OGRE] Kuroda.
Spirit Awareness 12 to 3.
Spirit Strength at 142,
and Growth Potential
at a lower 40 points.
Kazemaru, also a
12 to 3 Spirit Awareness.
Strength is at a lower 130.
But Growth is at 100.
Pretty closely matched then.
It'll be interesting.
No stalling you two.
Step up to the plate.
Let's make this clear.
In my line of
work I've been taught
not to quit until they're dead.
And fighting a trained bodyguard
I can't help but
feel it's professional.
If you're asking about
killing I've already answered.
Feel free to use
any force necessary
to defeat your opponent
and ensure your victory.
Yes you've said that twice,
but will you hold it against me
if I turn out to
be a cold-blooded killer?
[GENKAI] Young man, I am a
psychic, not a saint.
I'll train whoever's strongest.
Regardless of
any moral shortcomings.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I don't believe this hag!
Now I really have to win!
I'm very relieved
to hear that.
So I can win the fight
without holding myself back.
Talking is only a
means of delay.
Are you ready
to fight yet?
Of course!
Risking my life is the
nature of my profession.
Mine as well.
Good, then I won't feel so bad
when I carve out your heart.
You may start!
This is pointless.
We can't see a thing.
Yeah, well it's not
exactly a spectator sport.
The hitman is pushing
back the bodyguard.
Are you telling me
you can see in there?
[KUWABARA]
Yeah. Kinda.
He's got the Spirit Gun!
No, it's too
powerful to be like mine.
Winner: Kazemaru!
I was trying not to
use that technique so soon.
What a strange power.
I've seen it once before.
It's a mass of Spirit Energy.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Yeah,
maybe it is the Spirit Gun.
[BOTAN] Same
theory, at least.
Hey, is that you?
Urameshi where do you
think your going?
I'm impressed Botan.
You didn't say Bingo.
Well that's just because your
answer wasn't completely right!
It looks like
Kazemaru can send out
his Spirit Energy
through his entire palm.
The exceptional
amount of force he can create
shows that he's had
quite a bit of training.
But the real kicker is that
after he's done he
still has plenty of strength.
So I better not
fight him with energy.
[BOTAN]
Bingo.
[KUWABARA] Urameshi!
You can't chicken out on me!
Oh, your just talkin'
with this hot girl.
Damn you punk! Keiko's supposed
to be your girlfriend!
[YUSUKE] Calm down
Kuwabara. This is Botan.
[BOTAN] Nice to meet
you, Kuwabara.
Actually, I've
seen you several times
and I've been quite
impressed by your actions.
Hey she's floating in the air!
Urameshi! Is she a--
well, you know--yeah
I think she's a witch.
Oh don't be
such a dope Kuwabara.
Botan's not a witch,
she's the Grim Reaper,
and she's my assistant
as Spirit Detective.
[KUWABARA]
Detective?
Yeah.
You were telling me you
got a pretty bad feeling
from one of those
guys in there, right?
Well there are these
things called demons
and there's a really bad
one's hiding in there.
So my job is to
figure out which one he is
and keep him from
getting Genkai's power.
Gee, that sounds tough.
But the important thing is that
you're not cheating on Keiko
with this new girl!
And as for you.
Uh... why are you
staring at me like that?
Beautiful lady...
will you be my wife?
I'm a strong and fearless man
and I'll be good to you.
Are you boys happy
with disqualification?
If so, stay where you are.
So he's Koenma's boy.
I didn't know I was
attracting celebrities.
You may begin! Fight well!
[fight sounds]
[GENKAI] Winner: Shorin!
[SHORIN]
Just, barely escaped.
KOENMA]
That boy is too modest.
Sure he lacks
fighting experience,
but he still had
a decent advantage
in two out of three categories.
[GENKAI] On to the third match!
Kuwabara versus Musashi!
Try not to get
killed, Kuwabara!
Don't worry, I have
to beat you before I die!
Don't you think
he's a bit mismatched?
Well he's never
been as tough as me,
but he does have
a lot of determination.
I just hope that's
enough to win.
I'll give you one last
chance to walk away, kid.
After that I'll have to consider
you an obstacle in my path
and I won't hesitate
to cut you down.
[KUWABARA] I'm not
going anywhere, old man.
I may be a kid,
but I've been fighting
on the streets my whole life.
Plus, I've got powers.
In fact I can see
you right--huh?
Wait a minute.
At least I saw you.
Before.
What happened?
It's a trick!
Where are you?
I know all about
your Spirit Awareness, kid.
[MUSASHI] But I too have a
power. I can mask my own energy.
So I can't see you.
And unlike you, I'm used
to fighting in the dark.
[KUWABARA]
You!!
[fighting sounds]
Be careful Kuwabara!
Stop yelling so much!
It makes you easy to find!
[KUWABARA]
Will you guys shut up!
I'm trying to concentrate,
and you're not really helping!
There isn't any use.
In the dark I can
strike you a hundred times
and you'll never
be able to block.
Beat me up all you want old man,
your sissy little punches
don't hurt me at all.
It's just crummy chump change
compared to all the days
Urameshi rubbed my
head into the concrete.
It's true, I've
punched him quite a few times.
Then you leave
me no choice.
A big stick?
[MUSASHI] Now is no
time to play the fool, kid.
This is a wooden sword
carved from an ancient tree
and cleansed in a sacred stream.
It's a conduit
for Spirit Energy.
The perfect weapon
for striking down evil!
Hey! I'm not evil!
[MUSASHI]
Shibattou Shining Sword!
He actually broke the sword!
[MUSASHI] His Spirit Power
must truly be strong.
You haven't
gotten rid of me yet!
What kind of
evil creature are you?
No one has ever survived my
Shining Sword Attack. Oh well.
I'm confident you won't
live through a second strike.
[KUWABARA THINKS] I gotta
find a way to defend myself!
Why couldn't he
crack off a longer piece!
What is that?
I--I don't know!
[MUSASHI]
What are you?
Materialization.
What the hell's that?
[GENKAI] Normally, Spirit
Energy cycles through the body
and is very hard to control.
But when his
life was endangered,
he instinctively used
his high Spirit Awareness
to manipulate his
energy into a solid object.
In this case, into a sword.
[Kuwabara breathes heavily]
[KUWABARA]
Pretty cool.
But how am I
supposed to turn it off?
[GENKAI THINKS]
I suspected this would happen.
Guess he just needed that wooden
sword's focusing power
to give him an extra push.
[GENKAI] Winner: Kuwabara!
I guess Kuwabara won't be so
easy to beat from now on, huh?
Well at least he's still ugly.
You better not
lose before our fight.
[YUSUKE] Please. Like I'd miss
a chance to beat you up.
Let's not waste my time.
The fourth match is
Kibano vs. Dim-wit.
I think that's you.
And I thought my
name was Yusuke.
May the strongest man win.
[KUWABARA] What are
you waiting for Urameshi?
[KIBANO] Have
you decided not to fight?
Oh no. I was just
praying for your mortal soul.
[BOTAN] Yusuke!
Stop clowning around!
Moron!
Hey!
[GENKAI] Any more delay
and I'll take it as a forfeit!
Gee! Something tells me
you're still mad about
that grandma comment...
You really need to
enjoy life more, old lady.
[YUSUKE] Yup.
It's dark, all right.
But at least the
other guy is in the same boat.
[KIBANO]
You're wrong about that.
I can see exactly where you are.
Give me a break.
You're Awareness
isn't any better than mine.
Only weirdoes like
Kuwabara can see in the dark.
[KIBANO]
You stepped backward.
Fine. Good guess.
[KUWABARA] Watch out for him!
He's got some sort
of mask on his head!
My own invention,
it blinds my sensory organs.
All the brainpower normally
concentrated on sight, sound,
and smell is redirected
to sensing a person's spirit.
I've even installed
a targeting device
to direct my
senses to a single point.
Now let's see.
Yes, you have
a very unusual aura.
As if your body has
been through great danger.
Perfect, that'll
make you easier to find.
See? It's very useful.
[YUSUKE]
Okay, I heard that!
Hey! Did I hit you?!
[KIBANO]
Sorry.
I've got you!
Yeah!
Don't celebrate
just yet.
[Kibano laughs]
What!!
[KIBANO] You found me
by my voice, no doubt.
But your hearing will
never be accurate enough
to give you a
decisive blow.
This punk's not playing fair.
That helmet is protecting
his head from attacks.
Even the best kind of armor
should have a weak point.
But I'm scared Yusuke is going
to have a tough time finding it.
He can't even see his
own hand in front of his face.
[BOTAN THINKS] Yusuke, how are
you getting out of this one?
Here's another technique.
Uh-oh.
[KUWABARA] Something weird's
happening to Kibano's muscles.
[BOTAN] What?
[GENKAI] It's a basic
enhancement technique.
He's pulling in Energy
from the matter around him.
It gives a quick
boost of strength.
Darn it, where is he?
I'm right here!!
[KIBANO]
Big Arm Bomber!!!
[NARRATOR] Will this be the
end of the fight for Yusuke?
Will we witness
his first defeat?
With Rando
lurking in the shadows,
we have to hope
the Spirit Detective
can continue his case.
But how will he fight,
when he can't even see?
[KOENMA] Yo, this is the
great Koenma speaking.
Yusuke's case
gets very desperate
when Kazemaru shows
he's an expert
at the deadly
Ninja Throwing Star.
Of course,
that's the semi-finals.
First he's got
to figure out a way
to stop the
energy-pumping Kibano
from flattening
his skull into a pancake.
How can Yusuke
fire his one-shot
Spirit Gun in absolute darkness
and actually hit the target?
I'm not sure,
but I hope he is.
Because Rando
is getting closer!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪