♪
[NARRATOR] In his second
case as Spirit Detective,
14 year-old Yusuke Urameshi
fought hard against
the evil demon Rando,
who had entered the Genkai
Tournament in disguise.
The winner of the fights would
become Genkai's student,
and learn her
incredible psychic powers.
After a laborious battle,
Rando fell victim to his
own shrinking technique,
and was crushed by
Yusuke's final blow.
But Yusuke's rest
will not last long.
I just don't think
it's very considerate.
Today makes six months.
And Yusuke swears
it's something important.
[KEIKO]
I know, but...
He gives me a phone
call every couple weeks
so I know he's still alive.
I wish he'd tell me
what kind of camp this is,
but that's Yusuke for you.
Oh Atsuko, I
can't help wondering
if it's even worth
waiting for him.
Ah Keiko, cheer up!
One thing I've
had to learn now
is that Yusuke
always comes back.
Easy for her to say that.
Mothers are obligated to care.
Long time, no see, huh?
Yu-Yusuke!
[KEIKO] Three chocolate
shakes, please.
So do your arms bend
in the right direction now?
Yeah, with Genkai's
healing powers
I was only in bed for
a day after the fight!
And I think she even
made me stronger!
I can try 'em
on you if you want!
Buddy, I'm afraid
they'd send me to jail!
After what I learned
from the old lady,
fighting you would be cruel!
So, was the
training very hard?
Let's just say I'll
be having nightmares
for the next four years cause of
all the crap I went through.
Use the Spirit Wave to
float on top of the spike.
[GENKAI] Good. Now we'll
hold this for twelve hours.
I hate you!!
[GENKAI]
This will be an exercise
in blocking energy attacks.
Careful. This could kill you.
We're not going to stop this
until you don't move an inch!
Now get up!!
Then I sat and meditated
on a bonfire for a week.
Oh and I had to sleep with
snakes for three weeks.
Okay forget I asked!
Just listening to everything
you did gives me the creeps.
Yeah, but it was worth it for
all the tricks I learned.
Oooo... Now that's
what I wanna see!
[KEIKO]
See what?
Yeah! Kuwabara was saying
he wanted to see a movie, right!
Yeah--movies! I love 'em!
I know a great foreign Art Film!
Oh, great.
I haven't seen Keiko
this happy in months.
You guys must
really have somethin'
for her to be that way.
Don't act like
you're not excited too!
How do you think Keiko feels
when you pretend you don't care!
Hey! You're squishing
my milk shake!
[KEIKO]
Yusuke!
Stop wrestling, the
movie's about to start!
Hey, Keiko! I've gotta grab
something at the store first!
[KEIKO]
What?
Yeah and Kuwabara has to
get something too, right?
We'll be back in
five minutes, tops.
Would you mind
saving us some seats?
Well if it's quick
I'll come with you.
No, you see it's kind
of embarrassing actually.
It's a guy thing you know.
We'll be back soon okay!
Fine I'll be in the center row!
So what things you want
to buy with just guys, huh?
What do you need some
itching cream or something.
Shut up, I'm not buying stuff.
We're being followed.
[KUWABARA]
What?
I caught a glimpse of
them at the movie theater.
Well we've got the time. I say
we have some fun with them.
[KUWABARA] You
jokers are in trouble now!
My name's Kuwabara!
The number one thug of
Sarayashki Junior High!
No sense telling lies.
I don't think these guys
are playing around.
We haven't even started and
they're already pulling knives!
Must kill.
Must kill. Must... kill!
Are they human?
[EVIL THUGS]
Kill. Kill. Kill...
What do we do now?
Now we leave it to me.
Hey! Is this one of
your new techniques?!
I'll take that
as a stupid question.
Shotgun!!
Oh wow! That's crazy Urameshi!
It's like your
shooting a whole spray
of Spirit Gun
bullets all at once!
Well yeah, like I said.
It's a Shotgun.
That's pretty neat.
[YUSUKE] But who
the hell are these guys?
Hold on!
I feel something
really strange around us.
I don't think it's very human.
Something like that!
Get him!!
Now that is teamwork.
Botan!
Hey it's the pretty girl!
Have you thought about me?
I've been shadowing that one
since he slipped through
the barrier two days ago.
[KUWABARA]
So what is he?
He looks like he grew up too
close to a nuclear plant.
I'm quite certain he's a spy
from the place you'll be
going as your next mission.
Okay Botan you
can stop right there!
I got back from Gramma's
evil boot camp today!
And I deserve a vacation!
Why don't you
call back in two years!
Then I guess you don't mind
everyone in this city
being turned into a zombie?!
Does that question have a point?
Koenma was given
a message yesterday...
It was sent by an agent, much
like the one we just walloped.
Uh Koenma sir! A letter!
Stamp? Sure! Stamp?
Sure! Approval? Sure!
Appeal? Sure! Come
back from the dead? Why not!
[BLUE OGRE] It's from the city
of Ghosts and Apparitions!
What?!
It came from the Four Saint
Beasts, didn't it sir?
What do they want?
Immediate immigration
into the living world.
That's ridiculous!
Tell Botan to capture
the spy she's following!
And get Yusuke on this at once!
I don't see what
the fuss is about.
If Koenma's in charge
then why can't he turn
down their request?
And who are these
stupid Saint Beasts?
[BOTAN] They are four of the
most notorious criminals
in all of the Spirit World.
The title Saint was given
to them by their followers.
Years ago they were chased
by a coalition of pursuers,
and evaded capture
by locking themselves
into a booby-trapped fortress.
Since then a whole
city has formed at its base,
filled with vile crooks who view
these beasts like gods.
The City of Ghosts
and Apparitions.
Hey, aren't you gonna
finish your story?
Why don't you take a look at
these boys you knocked out.
Tell me I didn't just see
a bug crawl from his throat!
They're called Makai Insects,
a parasite from the darker
parts of the Spirit World.
They bury themselves
under the skin
and then nurture a
person's primal desire.
[BOTAN] Minds occupied
by this parasite
develop a need for destruction,
physical power, and murder...
It will be a disaster.
Well can't we tell people!
I mean there's gotta be a cure.
[BOTAN]
There is...
But ordinary people
can't see the insects.
The inflicted will be
seen as merely psychotic,
and I'm afraid a cure will not
be first on the human's mind.
Then what the hell are
we supposed to do?!
The only way to rescue this city
is to kill the Makai insects,
and the only way to do that is
by destroying the whistle,
which the enemies possess.
A whistle?
Without the whistle's
sustaining frequency,
the Makai can't live
outside of Spirit World.
So, how long do we have before
these beasts leave their castle
and come to Earth themselves?
At this point they can't.
For years we've had them
trapped inside the city
with a barrier wall.
[BOTAN] Now, with this
threat of insect invasion,
they hope to force
us to open the barrier.
I see. So they give you the
whistle if you open up the wall.
Instead we'll make
a small breach
in the wall to let you in.
Eventually they'll find
this hole themselves.
And what if I'm not
able to beat them?
I don't think I have to
tell you what would happen
if all the demons from that
city were unleashed on Earth.
I have to be honest Botan. This
takes the record for confusing.
Yes, just try
and remember the basics.
You're good and
that entire city is bad.
Destroy the whistle
and defeat the beasts,
and the case will be closed.
Okay, I just can't
believe Koenma
expects me to take on a whole
freaking city of demons alone.
Don't they send teams out
for this kind of thing!
What about
me, Urameshi?
Oh Kuwabara! There's
no such thing as demons!
Yusuke and I were just joking!
[KUWABARA]
Look I'm not dumb.
Or blind.
We all know I can
see supernatural stuff
a whole lot better than Yusuke.
And I'm not gonna
sit around my house
while Yusuke doesn't see things
and lets big monsters and
insects take over my city!
'Cause I'm Kuwabara
and in case you guys forgot.
I've got a sword!
Well Yusuke,
I guess there's no point
arguing with the eager.
Watch for dust.
[YUSUKE] Gee,
thanks for the warning.
[YUSUKE] Banging on the
floors of random warehouses.
Seems like fun to me.
This is where they
were supposed to put
the breach in the barrier.
[BOATN]
Bingo.
You are they gonna give us
a rope ladder or something?
No, jumping down
should land you safely
on the outer bank of the city.
You know you don't have
to go through with this
if you don't want to. No one
will hold it against you.
Oh, Okay! Good bye!
[BOTAN]
Not you!
The Spirit Detective doesn't
have a choice in this.
Kuwabara does.
Don't worry about me lady.
I sort of feel like a
Spirit Detective myself now.
And as for detectives
there's no turning back!
[BOTAN]
He really jumped.
Maybe he'll be okay alone.
Okay, okay.
Not yet!
Here! I'm supposed to give
you this Communication Mirror!
Geez! You nearly forgot
to give me this thing?!
Let me guess--without
it I'd probably be killed!
No.
It's not a weapon, it's
just a Communication Mirror,
so I can keep in contact with
while you're on the other side.
Yeah yeah, leave me on my own
while you go do
other things... Oh no!
What's the matter now, Yusuke?
Keiko! I just dumped her
off at the movie theater!
Yusuke you brat!
Hey Botan, tell you what,
why don't you go take care
of things with her and
I'll go down here.
Now wait!
Yusuke! I don't want to do that!
[thunder]
Oh damn!
[YUSUKE] Well,
I guess this is the place.
[muffled grunts and groans]
Yes, we've found a treat!
What, are those things?
I'm not exactly sure,
but they're not friendly.
We will dig in.
[Kuwabara cries out]
Urameshi!
There's too many of 'em!
And I'm not sure but I
think they want to eat me!
I'm coming!
This is gonna be pretty lame
if we get killed before
we reach the stupid castle!
[Fugaki cry out]
That worked... whatever it was.
[KURAMA] It seems
you could use some help.
[HIEI] If those nothings
were too much for you,
we're going to have
some serious trouble.
[thunder]
[YUSUKE] Well, well,
well! The thieves!
Hello.
Well, what are you doing here?
Even that fool Koenma knew it
would take more than human power
to kill the Saint Beasts.
By aiding in this mission,
Koenma has assured us
we can clean our
slates in Spirit World.
I guess Koenma
heard me complaining.
Hey Kuwabara, let me
introduce you to these guys.
That's Hiei,
and his name is Kurama.
A pleasure.
Well I don't have
a clue what going on,
but it sure is nice
to have a helping hand!
Helping is not the right word.
Koenma may regard us
as equals but I do not.
Once inside the castle I
suggest you let us do the work.
As far as I'm concerned
we're baby sitting.
Listen you puny jerk-face,
I'm gonna have to beat you up
if you keep talking
down to us that way!
Let's avoid fighting.
You're not worth it.
Oh that's it!!
But you, Detective,
are a different story.
I plan to take
my revenge on you,
so consider this fair warning!
You wanna ignore me, huh?!
Hiei, we must face
this current business
before you start your own.
Don't worry three-eyes,
if we survive this
I'll be glad to take you on!
Now is this a
perfect team or what?!
[GENBU] What a strange
group of visitors.
No match for us, of course.
[SEIRYU]
Master, what shall we do?
[SUZAKU] Byakko is correct.
They are no reason to worry.
Look at them fighting
one another already.
They'll never even
pass the front gate.
[Suzaku, Seiyu, Genbu laugh]
[YUSUKE] Wow now
this place homey.
[KUWABARA] So I guess were
just gonna walk right in?
Any prize that's worth having
usually requires a risk.
I say we make 'em come out here
and fight us up front like
they're not a bunch of sissies!
Your sense of
strategy is amazing.
Are you talkin'
to me, runt-boy?!!
Let's go.
Stupid dwarf.
[EYE BAT]
Welcome to Maze Castle.
Whoa, it talked!
[EYE BAT] Those who enter
Maze Castle must be tried
by the Gate of Betrayal.
What do you mean tried?
Urameshi.
Why did you have to ask?
The ceiling!
[EYE BAT]
Heavy, isn't it?
Sensors in the corridor
are most intelligent,
and a complex
assembly of gears
adapts the ceiling's
weight precisely
to the strength of its victims.
[EYE BAT]
Of course, there is a catch.
Just enough lee-way remains
for one person to escape,
leaving their friends to
be crushed by the weight.
Damn it!
[EYE BAT] But decisions
must be made quickly.
Not even the four
of you combined
can hold the ceiling for long.
Insist on teamwork,
and everyone will be crushed.
Only by turning
against your friends
will one of you
be able to escape.
Only the traitor among you
deserves to enter Maze Castle.
That's why it's called
the Gate of Betrayal, you see?
[Eye-Bat cackles]
Boy I'd like to get my
hands on that bat-thing!
Stay focused on the weight
or you'll kill us all!
Oh sure blame me!
I bet I'm holding up a
lot more weight than you are!
Shut it Kuwabara!
Well I'm not about to die
for the sake of
you worthless humans!
Don't you even
consider it, Hiei!
Oh man! I knew we should
have played some trust games.
[NARRATOR] How can this
unwilling troupe of fighters
survive such
an impossible trap?!
Will one betray the others?
Or will the
gate crush them all?
[YUSUKE] Okay some how
some way we'll all escape
from the gate of betrayal.
But deep down you
probably knew that.
I'm not to sure about
this next one though.
When Kurama faces
one of the saint beast
and he's using a... rose?
This beast is made of solid
rock and he can do it all
but Kurama's got a few
surprises of his own.
It's going to be
an unbelievable fight--
let's just hope the castle
doesn't crash down too.
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪