♪
[NARRATOR] In the House
of Four Dimensions,
three human teens
with unusual powers
kidnapped Yusuke Urameshi,
and forced his friends
to play a series
of peculiar games.
The Spirit Detective's crew
has narrowly survived,
only to learn
the shocking truth.
Yusuke's mentor Genkai
was behind the ordeal,
using it to send a warning...
Someone is carving out a
tunnel to the Demon World.
A tunnel? But how?
There is a border zone
dividing our world and theirs.
Somehow, a giant breach
is opening in that zone.
It is known as the Pseudo Space.
Tiny portals have been opened
in it from time to time,
allowing demons such as Hiei
and myself to slip through.
But they are rare, and
quickly close, trapping us.
You're wrong, old hag.
If there were a hole
out of this vile world,
I would have taken it.
Getting you to believe me
would be a pain in the ass...
I'll let you see it yourself.
Enough suspense,
where is it?
Mushiyori City.
What? That close?
That's like a Sunday
afternoon drive from here!
[suspenseful electronic drone]
Not now, not this fast.
How could we have missed this??
We know the size of the border
zone fluctuates over the years.
We know it's the greatest
threat to humanity,
and yet we didn't see this?
Are we as dumb as
my ogre monkey boy??
Dumb as George Saotome!!??
Sir, that's the first time
you've ever used my name.
SHUT UP!!
[RECORDS GIRL]
It's true, sir.
There are times in human
history when demons
are more able to roam.
But their people's next
dark age is not scheduled
for several more centuries.
And not even those times
have a hole this big.
[KOENMA] Then we need to
know who's behind it.
[beeping]
I guess that's Koenma.
Botan! Is Yusuke with you?
It's an emergency!
We're all here, Koenma.
Want to tell us about
the border tunnel?
Genkai! I forgot I
brought you back to life!
You're slow on the
uptake this time.
It seems whoever is doing
this has used the typical lull
after a Tournament to
catch even you off guard.
In the last month, over thirty
humans have come to me for help,
suddenly finding themselves
to have an assortment
of supernatural powers.
These two are
prime examples.
The traits of
the affected vary,
but they share
one thing in common.
They all come from
Mushiyori City.
[KOENMA] I guess an
itsy bitsy part of me
is happy that the
opening's influence
hasn't stretched
any farther yet.
But that means we've already
advanced into Stage Two.
Stage Two, what does that mean?
You moved to training pants?
No, no it doesn't,
but I'm not sure how
much of it I can reveal.
It is secret
classified information
from the highest
echelon of files
in Spirit World Intelligence.
Well how can I help you
if I don't know anything??
You make an
interesting point.
Okay everyone, here's
how it shakes down.
There are four stages to
such an apocalyptic breach.
[KOENMA] Stage One: Demon energy
thickens in the human world,
allowing demon
parasites to thrive.
As the size of the
breach increases,
we move to Stage Two,
in which normal humans
find themselves blessed
with unusual powers.
Now Stage Three is where
things really heat up.
Demon energy floods the streets,
and low class
monsters spawn at will.
They aren't smart, or strong,
but they are
excessively violent.
[KOENMA] In the
fourth and final stage,
the border tunnel breach
achieves a stabilized
diameter of over two kilometers,
allowing total passage.
Total passage
for whom?
Yeah, just who do
I have to fight?
With a tunnel that gigantic,
apparitions all the way through
the C and B-Classes
will be able to pass
between worlds en masse.
Classes?
[KOENMA]
Spirit World ranks every
demon according to their power.
I've never told you this
because there wasn't any point.
But, here's a nifty
frame of reference.
All the demons in the
upper level B-Class
are the same strength as Toguro.
Toguro is just a B-Class?
Nearly killed us all
and he's just a B class?!
[KOENMA] The Demon World
is an ancient land,
and its depths are endless.
In truth, there are vast
parts of its territory
that Spirit World has
absolutely no control over.
Well I never knew that.
[KOENMA] Think of
the Demon World as a
giant underground building,
basement after basement,
stretching downward into
an infinite void.
Out of all that, we only control
half of the first basement.
Then you're a
pretty crappy ruler.
[KOENMA] It would be
bloodbaths and Armageddon
if we tried to take
it all at once.
Our only choice has been
to hold our ground
and expand gradually
over the centuries.
We cannot awake the anger of
the A-Class and S-Class,
or Super A-Class demons,
who live at the bottom.
Not even my father
and all his armies
could defeat the S-Class demons.
Now Koenma, you and King Yama
are not the idle type.
If you knew of such a danger,
surely you have
taken precautions.
[KOENMA]
Sure...
To seal off the Pseudo Space
around Demon World,
Spirit World has raised a
powerful Kekkai Barrier.
Oh great! Barriers!
And you've had us
worrying over nothing...
Hold on. So why are
demons still passing through?
[KOENMA] We had
to make priorities,
and stop the A and S-Class
demons above all else.
Even our resources are limited.
The only way to make a
barrier large enough
was to spread the
energy into a net.
I see. Like a filter.
[KOENMA] Yes. While B-Class
demons can squeeze through,
the larger A and S-Class
are held at bay.
No! How could you sign
off on a plan like that?
You intentionally made it
so that hundreds of demons
like Toguro could just
prance on over here
whenever they want?!
[KOENMA] You have to imagine
the alternative, Yusuke.
If just one S-Class demon
crossed into the living world...
[people screaming]
[machine guns firing]
Would somebody please just tell
me what you're talkin' about?!
Geeze, man, you know
it's not my fault
my powers aren't
working right now
and I can't hear
what Koenma's saying!
We're a team, and teams don't
leave a pal in the dark!!!
Just keep me in the loop!!!
Okay, now I'm worried.
What's wrong guys?
[TOGURO 1 TELEPATHIC] How's the
tunnel? Going as planned?
[TOGURO 1 TELEPATHIC]
They'll interrupt.
They're very good at that.
They are tricky fellows.
They even made my brother crazy.
Just look at what
they made him do to me.
Mr. Sensui,
you must avenge us.
[SENSUI] Soldiers
take orders. Not me.
But lucky for you,
nothing could deny me
the pleasure of this kill.
[TOGURO 1 TELEPATHIC]
I thought you'd say that.
[Toguro 1 laughs wickedly]
[SENSUI THINKS] Never
satisfied, never full.
They eat and destroy
with grubby hands
until nothing is
left but piss.
But now...
The judgment of
all humans has begun.
My life, it's just starting.
There's still
things I need to do!
I need to marry a girl!
Grow my first moustache!
But now you're tellin' me that
someone's making a big hole,
so that pretty soon a whole
buncha' demons just like Toguro
can start attacking
us all at once?
And then there's
the A and S guys
not even Spirit
World can control?!
Has hope truly left us??
Is this the end
of everything??!!
[GENKAI] Get over it.
We'll talk about
our plan in a minute.
But I need to
rescue Kaitou first.
Oh right, the bookworm.
I forgot about him.
A full house.
I take it everything went just
as you planned, Master Genkai.
[KURAMA] You
played your part well.
You lost, but it was a
stirring introduction.
I wasn't playing along,
I tried my hardest
to defeat you.
For once I wanted
to see you lose,
but I'll just have to
wait a little longer.
Nice thinking brain boy, so
you put your soul on the line
because he's beaten you
on some math quizzes?
What if grandma hadn't
been here to save you?
Simple. He would have
faded into nothing.
Kaitou's a risk taker.
That's why these three
came to me for help.
He'd removed his own soul,
and they didn't know
how to put it back.
A soul is fragile without a
body or ghost to protect it.
In one full day,
it would break apart.
And yet, your curious
mind could not help
but pose the question.
Real discovery takes risk.
I had to know what would
happen if I broke my own rule.
Let me introduce myself
formally to the group.
My name is Yuu Kaitou,
I have the power of Taboo.
My name's Asato Kido,
my power is Shadow.
Mitsunari Yanagisawa,
and I call my talent Copy.
Like I told you, they
all live in Mushiyori City.
It's been a full month since
they developed their powers,
and there are many
others like them.
That's only a few weeks
after the closing of
the Dark Tournament.
Yeah, and that was the
beginning of Stage Two, right?
So that means it was just
days after I fought Toguro
when this whole tunnel
business got started.
[beeping]
Koenma's not wasting
any time, either.
[KOENMA] We've just
finished calculating
the growth rate
on that tunnel, guys.
It's bad.
As is, it will reach
Stage Four in three weeks.
Only three weeks?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Three weeks...
Even Toguro gave me
more warning than that.
And there was only one of him.
There's gotta be
something we can do!
Can't you like close
the hole back up?
[KOENMA] The only way is
to stop the tunnel's creator.
This isn't a normal hole,
it's not physical yet.
It's a distortion
in space-time,
one point three
kilometers wide.
But once it hits two
kilometers, it stabilizes,
changing from energy
conduit to a physical space.
You don't use a drill
to make a hole like this.
You use a psychic,
nested at the center-point.
So you know where the guy is,
and if he's beat
down we're all okay?
Then all I have to do is
turn his brain into mush!
Not so fast, Yusuke.
You guys know the
city, right?
So then take me
to that hole.
Damn it! What is this?
Be a Bitch Day??
Here's a brilliant concept!
Try learning from your mistakes!
What I wouldn't give for
a successor with a brain.
You know how much I trouble I
went to, planning this ordeal?
The whole point of tonight
was to teach you one thing.
You cannot go into this
without understanding
your enemy's powers.
You will lose!
[YUSUKE] And you've
gone deaf again!
Koenma said
we can't wait!
[KUWABARA] If the tunnel
completes we're doomed!
That still allows
us three weeks.
And three questions to answer...
How many fighters
in their group?
Who is their leader?
And what's the true
nature of their powers?
Without those answers,
attacking would be suicide.
[HIEI]
Koenma.
If these fools are done,
I have my own question.
In what class do you rank me?
[KURAMA] Hiei...
What? It's a fair question.
If his Spirit World lackeys are
going to place a letter on me,
then I deserve to know.
[KOENMA] Oh very well,
Hiei. I'll tell you.
As I've said,
the Toguro Brothers were
considered in upper B.
And as of the end of
the Dark Tournament,
you are ranked in the
middle of B-Class.
Underestimate me even now?
For the record,
when you fought Yusuke,
you only had an upper
D-Class ranking.
But in less than a year,
you've jumped up
nearly two full classes.
Quite an astounding
feat, to be sure.
You have much to be proud of.
You're a child.
Don't father me.
Come on...
You already have your fox,
your clown, and your hag.
I'm a moot point.
[KUWABARA] You're just
gonna walk away??
This is your world
to look after, not mine.
I don't intend to
hinder your cause,
but I am not going
to help it, either.
Coward! Real men help
where they're needed.
Save that idealism
for your fairy tales.
Well I'm not gonna
shed any tears, Hiei!
In fact, I'm happy you're gone!!
He's the same selfish
punk he was from the start.
Yeah, he's the same.
He'll come rescue us at the
end when he need him the most.
It's hard to predict
what he'll do.
Humanity's destruction
was Hiei's former dream.
These new developments
leave him much to consider.
[KOENMA] Maybe I
should have told him
he was in the upper B-Class.
Or the special upper B-Class.
That sounds good!
[BLUE OGRE THINKS]
I need a new job.
[KUWABARA]
So, what now?
We move into the city at
sunrise and begin scouting.
These three will go with us.
They could be of some use.
You guys game for that?
What do you think?
It's our home town, man.
We're not gonna watch it
turn into some demon parade.
Yes, we've already been
given our powers.
The way I see it,
we can either help out the
humans or the demons,
and to tell you the truth,
I prefer my own kind.
Same goes for me. I'm not
letting anybody take my turf.
Nice, now the next
job for all of you
is to get what sleep you can.
In the morning we'll
divide into two teams
so we can cover more territory.
Until we know more,
no one goes home and
no one leaves the group.
Goodnight.
[KUWABARA] We're all sleeping
in this freaky house?
But I didn't bring
my special pillow!
[KUWABARA] Um, Botan, would you
pet my hair until I fall asleep?
[Slap]
[BOTAN] Yukina wouldn't
appreciate that!
[KUWABARA] I meant in
a mom kind of way!
[SENSUI]
Itsuki, how's it coming?
Mr. Sensui...
We have an obstacle.
[SENSUI]
Tell me.
[ITSUKI]
A Kekkai Barrier.
So strong, it's intoxicating.
I can't break it.
We need someone else,
Mr. Sensui,
someone with talent like my own.
So while I concentrate
on the tunnel,
they slice open the net.
Then we can
raise our glasses.
Someone who can break
a Kekkai Barrier.
Very well, I know people.
I'll find your man.
And in the mean time,
I'll start judgment on
anyone who's in our way.
[KEIKO]
Puu?
You look horrible,
what's wrong?
[PUU]
Puu!
You don't forget that beak.
[SHIZURU]
Hey, sweetheart.
Shizuru!
I talked to Yusuke's mom.
He never came home last night,
and Puu's acting really strange.
Yeah, Kazuma didn't
come home, either.
Wanna play follow
the pudge-ball?
If it's anything
like usual,
he should take us right
to Yusuke and my bro.
Is something
wrong, Shizuru?
That's a nice way
to put it,
I just got an awful
premonition...
Even worse than
the tournament.
[KEIKO THINKS] Yusuke...
[YUSUKE] How come every case I
get is even more impossible
than the last??
I think Koenma hates me.
We'll make the sunrise
march into Mushuyori City,
and humans with insane
powers are everywhere.
We can't tell
who's on our side
and who's fighting
for the demons,
and there's no time
to figure it out!
Every minute the
tunnel's getting bigger,
and the mastermind
is coming for us.
Who's he gonna get
to slash the barrier?
And how am I gonna
punch him in the face?
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪