[NARRATOR] As Sensui threatened
the lives of Kuwabara, Kurama
and Hiei, Yusuke miraculously
returned from the dead,
revealing an astounding secret.
Yusuke was somehow part Demon.
The two resumed their battle,
though now evenly matched
as Yusuke displayed the energy
of his mysterious birthright.
With both fighting at a level
equal to S-Class Demons,
the fight was an
explosive stalemate--
until something strange stirred
within Yusuke and spoke to him,
guiding him toward
a transformation.
[yelling]
Urameshi!
[yelling continues]
[KUWABARA coughs, gasps]
[KUWABARA]
Look!
[SENSUI gasps]
[YUSUKE] I've waited
a long time for this.
What in the heck's
goin' on here?
And what's with that hair?!
Looks like he played
with an electric socket!
I don't know what
triggered this,
but it appears Yusuke's
body has finally accepted
the transformation
the Mazoku desired.
This is perfect.
[KUWABARA]
Did you guys see that?
Sensui cracked a smile when
he saw our freaky half-breed.
He really is an arrogant
creep, isn't he?
Pretty much, but that's
beside the point.
It's not Yusuke's change
that Sensui smirks at.
Even from this vantage point,
I can tell that Sensui has
undergone a profound
transcendent metamorphosis.
A "Spiritual Awakening,"
if you will.
[KUWABARA]
"Spiritual Awakening?"
[KOENMA]
Back in the cave,
his fighting was
filled with such...
...loathing and
callousness. Self-hatred.
His heart was so dark,
even for a bad guy.
But now, that's gone.
Yes, as if he's suddenly
come to terms with his place
in the world and achieved
some sort of balance.
What a jerk.
Ha! You are indeed the
descendant of the Mazoku.
And I couldn't be happier.
[YUSUKE laughs]
[YUSUKE] And what's
so funny about that?
[SENSUI]
Not so much funny as...
...divine, that fortune
would smile upon me.
[YUSUKE]
How's that?
I'm fighting a beast
that only appears
once every forty-plus
generations.
That's no mistake.
Ha! You should be
careful what you call
a fortunate opportunity.
Your luck could run out.
[YUSUKE yells]
[yelling]
[SENSUI grunts]
[YUSUKE grunts]
[YUSUKE yells]
[grunting]
[SENSUI grunts]
[YUSUKE yelling]
[YUSUKE yells]
[SENSUI grunts]
[YUSUKE grunting]
[yelling]
[SENSUI grunting]
[yelling continues]
Unreal... Completely unreal!
Why can't guys have these
powers at the start of cases?
His ancestor must've
been an extremely brutal
and formidable warrior.
As a mere human, Sensui doesn't
stand a chance of beating him.
Let's hope so.
[YUSUKE laughs]
Do you still think
that challenging me
is some great
opportunity for you?
Well do you?
[gagging]
Playtime's over.
[YUSUKE huffs]
[YUSUKE gasps]
[YUSUKE]
What's happening?
Who's doing this?
Hey! Give back my body!
[DEMON] Shut up.
This doesn't concern you.
[YUSUKE]
The hell it doesn't!
So long!
[gasps]
Outta the way, dumbass!
[ALL gasp]
Damn... You idiot.
I don't get it,
why's Urameshi having second
thoughts all of a sudden?
I mean he hit his mark
head on, didn't he?
It's what he wanted.
Puu, take us down there, now.
[screechess]
[KUWABARA]
Look at that.
Urameshi's Spirit Gun cut a
path through half the forest.
There's no way anybody
could still be alive
after gettin' hit by
something like that.
Over there, Puu.
[KUWABARA]
Huh?
Hey Sensui, wake up!
I said wake up you stubborn
son-of-a-bitch! I'm warning you,
I'll bust into Spirit World and
pull you back out myself!
You can't be dead!
Not this way!
What are you saying, man?
Has your brain gone
as fuzzy as your head?
We wanted him dead
and so did you!
Whoever may have killed
him, it wasn't me.
But we all saw you.
It looked like me
'cause it was my body,
but it wasn't me in
there when it happened,
I mean, it was but it
wasn't, you understand?
Look Urameshi, I think
you need some rest.
[coughing]
He's alive!
Kurama, can you use some
kind of healing plant on him?
He's not dead,
he just needs a boost.
Unfortunately, I used
up most my energy
when I was fighting him before.
The most that I can do for him
now is give him something
to ease his final pain.
What good're powers if you can't
use 'em when you need 'em?
But if that's it, fine!
Just give him what you've got.
Gladly.
[ITSUKI]
That won't be necessary.
[YUSUKE gasps]
[KUWABARA]
Don't tell me...
Itsuki!
[ITSUKI]
Please, just let Shinobu go.
If I'm gonna kill a human,
even an evil one,
it's at least gotta be me
pulling the trigger...
I'll never know it was me,
who made that choice.
Don't torture yourself.
Shinobu had only half of a
month left to live, anyway.
[ITSUKI]
Shinobu was suffering from
a rare and terminal disease.
Dr. Kamiya confirmed that,
though not even
he could cure it.
An ordinary person
would have the lost
the fight a long time
ago, but not Shinobu.
Is this your idea of a joke?
[SENSUI grunts]
He's telling the truth.
[YUSUKE gasps]
But I'm not making
excuses for my loss...
Your final attack, Yusuke,
with it you proved yourself
to be much stronger than I.
But, that wasn't even my power!
I had no control over my body...
You and I, we
aren't finished yet.
I need to know
who's really stronger.
Trust me, consciousness
exists on many levels.
Part of you that was ready
to make the choise,
must have taken control.
But it was definitely you,
a Demon you, who killed me.
Damn it, you're not listening
to me, it wasn't me!
I can't be happy!
I'll give you time to heal up.
You take some painkillers,
now, and then we'll do it over!
Only Yusuke would still want
to fight a man after he's dead.
Wake me when it's over.
Don't just stand there
Koenma, you've gotta have
some kind of powers
that could bring him back!
I did, but unfortunately they
were stored in my pacifier
which I drained empty in
the cave trying to stop him.
He's the author of his
own fate, once again.
I doubt I would've had
enough energy even before
the Mafuukan spell, I drained
so much on the way down.
What? Is this a confession?
[grunts]
[gasps]
Have a good nap, kid?
I-I don't get it: Why?
Koenma brought you back to life.
As for, why, I couldn't say.
Lost soul, now retrieve!
Maybe I've been wrong.
[GENKAI] The battle
must be over by now.
So you wasted it all saving
that brat kid's life?
[KOENMA]
Pretty much.
[SENSUI laughs]
[KOENMA]
You think that's funny?
You see I realized
your Mafuukan,
would be my greatest obstacle,
I arranged Amanuma's
death to drain your energy.
You were already riddled
with guilt over me.
I knew you would feel
compelled against all logic
to save the boy.
It was the only way
that I could ensure
my ultimate passage
to Demon World.
[KOENMA]
Shinobu,
I do not understand
why coming to this place
would matter so much to you.
You went through so much
trouble, and risked the
destruction of all of
Living World to get here. Why?
Because it's home.
[SENSUI]
Home to the apparitions whom
I've been taking life
from since I was a child.
[SENSUI] When I was younger,
I always wondered: Why me?
Why do these horrible
creatures pick on only me?
Why do they hate me?
Why do they want me to die?
But I was a child and I
never tried to ask them.
I never gave them
a chance to speak.
Instead, I improved
my fighting techniques,
while I grew to
hate them more
and wanted them
to die even more.
When I became a Spirit
Detective, they told me:
"They are not like us,
so they must be against us.
Their difference threatens our
sameness. It is us versus them.
Humans are good
and Demons are bad.
We are just and
they are unjust."
But I was an adolescent
and did not even think to
question such simple binaries.
I could not have
been more wrong.
I discovered the humans
I was sworn to protect
were, in truth, the
greater monsters.
And if that were so,
then I had to
question everything
I knew of the monsters
I'd been fighting.
My world turned inside out.
The truths I'd held to be
irrefutable were all inverted.
When I learned that
I was going to die,
I knew that I needed to collapse
those boundaries between us
and them, thus the tunnel.
And then, I could
come here to die.
I thought if I could see the
world through their eyes,
be a stranger in a strange
land, then maybe I could
understand them better,
and thus understand myself.
Dying by Demon hands,
I could then make
penance for my sins
[gasps]
[SENSUI]
But then I saw you, Urameshi.
First demonized in
a human's body,
and then humanized in a Demon's.
You dissolved the
barriers between us
in ways I never imagined.
And now, I can finally rest.
Shinobu...
Urameshi, you are the
justice I could never find.
Great changes will
come through you.
Someday when you're
lying in my position,
you'll know a dying
man's need for closure.
But until then, thank you.
[gasps]
I'll take you myself.
[ITSUKI]
I won't let you.
Shinobu's dead.
You got the end you desired,
so don't you think he
deserves the same?
He devoted the
last ten years
to refuting everything
you believe in.
He didn't live by your standards
and he certainly didn't
want to die by them.
So, I won't let you take
him to Spirit World,
for you to judge
him in your way.
See?
Being defeated by the Mazoku
was precisely the cathartic jolt
he needed to resolve his inner
turmoil, and pay off his guilt.
He finally conquered those six
personalities and emerged as
Shinobu, his original,
untainted self.
So, in a way, he's
already been redeemed
and doesn't need you
people to do it for him.
[gasps]
Where will you take him?
[ITSUKI] Somewhere his
soul won't be subjected
to your overbearing
scorn and judgment.
Where it will be safe from
hypocritical administrators
who train a boy to be a killer
and then hunt him down
for being one as a man.
Your people do not
deserve Shinobu's soul.
Your Spirit World will have
to create another enemy so
you can keep on fighting, as
that is, after all, what you do.
But Shinobu and I
grow weary of that.
We are going to spend
the rest of eternity together,
in solitude, and in peace.
Damn it.
If I kicked his ass, why do I
still feel like he won?
It's true, in a way, Sensui
achieved the very thing
that he intended by
initiating all of this.
Uh... Question, Urameshi.
What is it?
I was just wonderin'
if you feel kinda' weird.
Now that you mention it...
yeah, somethin' on my
back's really been makin' it
itch quite a bit.
[gasps]
I must look like I've
been playing around
with an electric socket!
See you guys, that's
exactly what I said.
That's just the
physical resemblance
to your ancestor rising
to the surface, Yusuke.
Though, I'm beginning to suspect
that he's still alive
somewhere in this world.
So then,
he must've been the guy who
turned me into his own personal
marionette during that
last shot on Sensui.
What makes you so sure?
Oh, just something
that the crazy voice
in my head said to me,
but you'd never know.
You're hearin' voices?
[RAIZEN]
You are the one.
At last.
Who are you?
[RAIZEN] You don't know
how to use your power.
Let me show you.
And those words are the
last thing that I remember
hearing before everything went
silent and I blacked out.
Then what?
[gasps]
Hey watch where you're
pointin' that thing!
You asked what
happened next, right?
Well this is how I
was when I woke.
I'd just finished
shooting my Spirit Gun.
I saw the blast
heading for Sensui
like it was in slow motion,
but I realized I wasn't
the one who fired it.
Let's go!
[KUWABARA]
Uh?
[KOENMA]
Go where?
If my ancestor is here and still
alive, we have to find him!
[KOENMA,KURAMA gasp]
Oh... come on Urameshi!
We closed the case
and saved the world.
Can't we at least take a nap?
I'm not gonna rest until I
get to the bottom of this.
My ancestors got in the way of
my fight and I can't let him get
away with that, no matter
who he's related to!
If you aren't with me, fine.
I'll just stay and
find him on my own.
You know Yusuke...
[YUSUKE gasps]
...you may want to give
this decision more thought.
The S.D.F. have no doubt
been busy little beavers
while we've been gone,
damming up the tunnel
on Living World side.
[KOENMA] Now those toadies
may be many things,
but they are not inefficient.
That hole will be
filled in like a cavity
within a matter of days.
[KUWABARA]
Wait a minute.
If the hole is sealed up,
t-then we... uh...
Won't ever be able to
return to Human World again.
You mean I'll never eat another
double cheeseburger?
[KOENMA] You can go
back to Human World now,
or stay here in
Demon World forever.
But you have to choose.
[KOENMA]
I'll give you a couple minutes
to think it over, Yusuke.
Ha! I don't need it, I've
already made up my mind.
[KOENMA]
What?!
Load up, Puu.
Let's go back home.
[NARRATOR]
Another case draws to a close.
Sensui has been defeated and
Human World has been spared
cataclysmic destruction, thanks
to Yusuke and his friends.
Now that the battle is over,
life for our heroes
can return to normal,
at least, until the next dark
cloud appears on the horizon.
[YUSUKE] Back at school,
and I could use the sleep.
You think we're all
wrapped up, right?
Well, what about
Doctor jail-busting
and meeting Sniper in the woods?
Or Game Master fitting
into normal life?
Is Kido still paralyzed?
And can Mitarai
do school work
without attacking
his classmates?
Where did Itsuki go with Sensui?
And will King Yama disown
Koenma for going AWOL?
Eh... Can I even stay
in this world at all?
So yeah, there's just a
few loose ends to tie up,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!