♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi is a
boy who used to be dead.
Thanks to his own selfless acts
and the love of his friends,
he's been given
a second chance.
Now returned to
the living World,
Yusuke possesses
strange new powers,
and is appointed Spirit
Detective of the Earth.
His job--tracking down
supernatural creatures
who have gone astray.
Koenma has spoken. Yusuke's
first case begins today.
[OGRE ANNOUNCER] Code red
emergency. Code red!
[HIEI] All right, Gouki!
That's enough!
[KURAMA] Yes,
our time runs short.
[OGRE ANNOUNCER] All guards
report to the palace perimeter!
Seal the doors!
They've taken all three of them!
[ATSUKO] Yusuke.
Yusuke. Wake up!
Please, Yusuke don't leave me!
What's the deal?
You're back.
Thank goodness.
Yes Mother, I'm alive
just like yesterday.
Don't normal people
sleep at six?
But I, but I had a dream
you asked to go away again.
Because of me.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
She's done this every morning
since I came back to life.
Oh well. Guess it beats being
passed out on the floor.
[SCHOOL BOY] Dude! A
golden-dragon fountain pen!
I heard these things
bring good luck!
Yeah, my uncle gave
it to me in his will.
You're like a walking bank now!
It's a good
thing Urameshi's gone!
Yeah he'd beat me up,
steal the pen,
and melt it down
into gold coins.
Or into a weapon!
[YUSUKE] Hey boys, mind
if I join in the conversation?
It's, just so clever!
[SCHOOL BOYS]
It's a ghost!
They act like I've
been dead or something.
[KEIKO] Let's be
honest, Yusuke.
I don't think they felt
much safer around you before.
You just didn't care.
Keiko.
What are you staring at me for?
Oh no reason.
If it's about the skirt
I don't want to hear it.
Hey-but, it wasn't!
[students murmuring]
I guess you're right.
Not much has changed.
But you've been
so nice to them.
Maybe I should
have stayed dead.
Kuwabara!
I hear 'ya. Life's a drag.
But don't worry,
you'll be in ghost-land soon!
After I put you there myself!
Kuwabara, shouldn't
you be thanking him
for rescuing your kitten?
I'll thank him as soon as
I'm finished beating him up!
[KUWABARA]
Geeze, guys!
Not much has changed at all.
[MR. TAKENAKA]
Don't be foolish.
First period begins in
one and a half minutes.
I'm sure you'll be
in your seat by then.
Dammit! Takenaka, I'm
thinkin' I'm gonna have to skip.
You can at least go to
your first day back!
[KUWABARA] Yeah
I thought he'd be smarter
after being dead! Right?
[MIYAMOTO, OKUBO, KOMADA]
Right.
[YUSUKE]
Ooh. That was cute.
[MR. IWAMOTO THINKS]
It doesn't make sense.
He's like a cockroach.
But one day,
oh, I'll squash him.
[GYM STUDENT 1] Where's
Urameshi? I thought he was back.
[GYM STUDENT 2]
Yeah, but it's gym class.
[GYM STUDENT 1]
Oh. Right.
Oh man, I hate gym class.
[BOTAN] Sorry to wake you,
but I just couldn't wait!
This better be good, Botan.
I just wanted to
cheer you up a little!
So I've brought
you a super-wonderful
present from Mr. Koenma!
Something up the sleeve, and--
Tada! Detective item number
one. Isn't it great?!
It's called a Psychic Spy-Glass.
Look through it, and you
can see through walls,
clothes-well anything, really!
You must use it wisely.
Two questions. One, are you
sure you're the Grim Reaper?
And two, did I agree to
this Spirit Detective thing?
I'm ignoring
both of those questions.
If you don't want to do this,
I'll just have to take
you back to Spirit World.
I'm going to bed now.
[BOTAN] Oh! I just
knew you'd agree!
Just one more thing to say!
Using detective items
will take spirit energy,
so you'll have to master them
one by one until you beef up.
Now sleep tight!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Alright Botan.
You're the boss!
[SCHOOL BOY 2]
Dead! I am so dead!
Lose your medicine?
No dufus, my lucky
golden-dragon pen!
I had it before gym class,
and now it's gone!
Hey, my watch is gone too.
And I can't find my key ring!
[Yawning] I'm here.
Alright, what's
with the staring?
You guys think Yusuke
did it! He's no thief!
He's a thug, Keiko.
And I don't know that
there's much of a difference.
He did skip gym.
Hey!
What's this racket about?
[YUSUKE] Get off me
lug-head! I didn't do it!
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Don't--LIE!!
Mr. Iwamoto.
I trust you found
evidence before punishing.
Yes, all the evidence
I need, Mr. Takenaka.
There was no trouble
at school when he was gone
and the minute he's back,
look what we have!
This poisonous weed was the
only student skipping gym
when the items were stolen.
Must've learned this trick
from his tramp mother.
You can do whatever
you want to me.
[MR. IWAMOTO THINKS]
]Yes. Punch me.
Hit your way out of this
school forever.
But I won't let you
lie about my mother too!
Hey Yusuke!!
Koenma?
I've got a big case for you!
Three criminals have
stolen the great artifacts
of darkness from my
father's vault,
made slush out of the guards and
escaped to the Living World!
Can't you see I'm busy
with this asshole here!
Don't worry about him Yusuke.
Right now he
can't see or hear us.
Well anyway, can't you call
back later or something!
Stupid! This is
much more important!
If these stolen artifacts
are used to their potential,
the entire living
world will be in a
state of chaos and suffering.
Lost lives, captured souls,
and a bunch of other
unpleasant things. Got it?
I'm not going anywhere
for some dumb theft case
until I clear up my own, okay?
Well there's your
culprit right there!
Take out your Psychic Spy-Glass
and look into his left pocket.
[YUSUKE]
I don't believe it!
Now hurry up and do your thing!
Hey! What are you--
An explanation, Mr. Iwamoto?
Well come on isn't it obvious?
This master thief here
has slipped it into my pocket!
Yes in fact I'm so mad about it
I can't even look
at him anymore!
Hold on, Iwamoto.
I'm afraid we have
more to discuss!
He really tried to set me up!!
You've been freed from the
charge. Now go to work!
Okay, okay I'll get to it!
But before that, he pays.
That's not smart policy Yusuke.
Assaulting a teacher
when you've been set free!
I can't just let
him go like that!
Then attack him invisibly.
Give me a break!
Do I look invisible?!
It's one of your new abilities.
Try to take control
of your Spirit Energy
and then gather as
much as you can
into your right index finger.
Hey. It's getting warm!
Good, now all you have
to do is aim and shoot.
Imagine the trigger in your mind
and then pull it tight.
Pull, huh?
Iwamoto!
Iwamoto, are you
alright? What happened?
It worked.
It's your Spirit Gun.
My what?
[KOENMA] A human being,
as I've explained before,
emits both body
and spirit energy.
While a ghost, you became more
aware of your Spirit Energy,
and can channel it into your
finger, hence the Spirit Gun.
It's far more powerful
than a normal punch,
but until you increase your
spirit muscle, so to speak,
you can only use it once a day.
[KOENMA] Your chief concern
will be recovering the items.
The Shadow Sword will make a
monster from whoever it cuts.
The Forlorn Hope emits a
cryptic power at full moon.
And the Orb of Baast
can capture living souls,
especially those of children.
[YUSUKE] Cheery.
Who came up with that one?
[KOENMA]
Understand, Yusuke.
These artifacts were
forged from darkness,
and prey on the
weak and desperate.
They were created eons ago
by the universe itself,
and serve a vital role
in balancing life.
But in the wrong hands
they can also destroy
and tip the scale towards evil.
Get them Yusuke.
As a living human you're
the best chance we've got
while they're on Earth.
Don't say anything more.
You brought me back
to life, right?
Well I'm guessing I can
do something useful
to earn my keep.
It's in your hands, Yusuke.
All these rich kids.
All shopping.
How does Koenma expect me
to find them in this mess?
Some help he was!
We think they're somewhere
in uptown, he says.
Hello, that
feels a little awkward.
[PEDESTRIAN 1] Someone call
an ambulance! It's a kid!
[PEDESTRIAN 2]
What happened?
[PEDESTRIAN 1]
I don't know. He fainted!
[KOENMA] The Orb of
Baast can capture living souls,
especially those of children.
I think that's what
they call a lead, folks.
[YUSUKE]
Hey! Wait up!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Uptown
became downtown real quick.
He's a monster!
[YUSUKE THINKS] There it is!
The Orb thingy!
Here goes.
Hey kid, you got
some cash for me?
Sorry Minor-League,
I don't have time for you.
That's the wrong answer.
Well don't say I didn't
give you guys fair--warning!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Damn.
Koenma sir. We've got
data on the criminals.
Good, show me at once.
[OGRE CLERK]
Of course.
[OGRE CLERK] His name's Kurama,
and that's all we know.
Somehow he's avoided
all of our files.
Hiei is another mystery case.
No criminal record,
origin unknown,
though informants all describe
him as a real cut-throat.
Definitely a loner.
Last we've got Gouki.
Now here's your
run-of-the-mill crook.
Twelve previous convictions,
killed his last ten pursuers--
murder seems to be his hobby.
It's a rough bunch, sir.
Oh yes, I expected as much.
You must be out of your mind!
Botan--you came.
[BOTAN]
Well yes!!
Did you think I wouldn't when
you sent my best project
to a pack of wolves!
All three of these
criminals are pushing
out tremendous
amounts of energy.
They'll rip Yusuke into pieces!
[KOENMA] Yes yes, I understand
the odds are against him,
and I would have preferred to
start him on smaller cases
until his abilities grew.
But with this new case,
I had no choice.
[BOTAN]
Fine. Give him the case.
But at least let me train
him for a while, first.
How much could he learn
in less than a week?
Less than a week?
Surely those criminals
can't cause damage
in that little time, can they?
The crooks aren't
the problem.
In a week my father
comes back from vacation.
King, Yama is coming back?
The one thing he always tells
me is protect the King's Vault.
But I didn't think someone
would actually break in!
[BOTAN] Will we be scolded
really badly? Do you think?
I'm afraid ours will
be a minor issue.
If dad gets angry,
the whole world will suffer.
Can't you just, explain it?
You know how my dad can get.
[KOENMA] Everything's fire
and brimstone with him.
He might sink an
entire continent
to get those three
artifacts back!
That's why I had to send Yusuke
out without the proper training,
and that's why he
only has a week
to return those artifacts.
He's got to,
for the sake of his planet!
Yusuke must defeat
those criminals,
even at the
cost of his own life!
I understand, Koenma.
I'll go back to the living world
and help him as much as I can.
He's our one hope. Don't forget.
[rain pouring]
Great. This stupid rain's
gonna wash away his tracks.
[Gouki laughs creepily]
[HIEI]
Oh yes. This is perfect.
If the sword can make
demons from trees,
just think what
it'll make from humans.
I say we go to
the next big city
and carve out a
thousand of them.
Imagine raising an
entire demon army!
I like the way you think, Hiei.
If we teach them to eat souls
I even know how
we'll feed them all.
The Orb of Baast!
And once the
moon becomes full,
we can use Kurama's weapon
and supposedly get complete
control! Isn't that right?
Sorry, I must withdraw
from this alliance.
[BOTH]
What?
[HIEI] What is that
supposed to mean?
Surely you're not
dropping out of the game
when we've come this far!
[KURAMA]
Yes.
You coward.
Your years of hiding
yourself in this human world
have made you just like them,
Spineless and ready
to be walked on.
I don't give a flip
if he leaves,
but he's got no
right to the loot.
Give us the pretty
little mirror.
I can't, I have great
need for it myself first.
Alright. Then I'll
punch it out of ya'!
[YUSUKE]
Excuse me, neighbors!
Couldn't help but notice
there's no rain falling here.
Maybe the next time you guys
go stealing some magic toys,
you should hide where it's not
so obviously sunny. Just a tip.
Who are you and how do you
know about the artifacts?
Give us your name!
Oh thank you, hoped
you'd ask. Hello boys!
The name's Yusuke,
I'm a Spirit Detective.
Spirit Detective?
Don't worry, he's just
one of Koenma's fools.
He must have been the only
human they could round up.
His spirit energy is pathetic.
Hey! Where are you going?
[KURAMA] Sorry. I don't
have time to be arrested.
Stop Kurama! You can't
just walk out on our plan!
[YUSUKE] Hey, don't leave yet
you guys! I just got here!
So much for manners!
[Gouki laughs]
Don't feel bad, kid.
I'm much more polite
than those two brats.
I'll turn myself in nice
and neat if I can't
rip off your head.
Sounds like a deal.
Just don't pull my hair.
But if you don't mind waiting,
I need a little snack.
What do you mean?
I find this orb very useful.
I never have to cook anymore.
People don't realize how hard
it is to eat human souls.
You gotta cook the
humans so they taste good,
but not enough to kill them.
But this--It takes all
the guess work out of it.
Pulls 'em from the
body still alive
so all you get is
good, clean soul.
[YUSUKE] Is that--is that
the little kid?!
They're the best!
Monster!!
Spit him out!!
And that's a knockout.
That's right little boy,
you're safe now.
Just fly on home to your body.
Two more to go.
For a human,
you're pretty decent.
What's your problem?
Get back on the ground!
I hit you too hard for
you to be on your feet!
[NARRATOR]
Kyukonki.
These dark, primitive beasts
feed on living souls,
ripping the victims apart
and devouring them while
they're still alive.
I think I'm in trouble.
Next time I see Koenma,
I've got to remember to ask
him how to fight monsters.
Easy kid, you run away.
That's right!
The Spirit Gun thing!
[YUSUKE]
Hey! It's not working!
[KOENMA] You can only
use it once a day.
Damn it, Mr. Iwamoto
screws me once again.
Do you know what the best
spices for a soul are?
Some fear and a dash of pain.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I'm really going to die. Again!
[KOENMA] Oh, I've got
news for Yusuke!
If he thinks this Kyukonki
monster tests his stuff,
wait until his show-down with
the wise and mysterious Kurama.
Botan even takes a human form
to give the rookie some help,
which of course he'll need.
Yusuke learns the lines between
good and evil often cross,
as the red-haired rogue
reveals his ancient past.
And calls on Yusuke to make
an ultimate decision.
The cryptic powers of the
Forlorn Hope are unleashed,
so don't miss the
next Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪