♪
[NARRATOR] Up against a
seemingly invincible opponent,
Kuwabara managed to paddle
the elder Toguro brother
into the ground, taking
the lead for Team Urameshi
in the Dark Tournament finals.
Before the fourth
match could begin,
Sakyo placed a bold
wager with Koenma.
The owner of the team
who loses the next match
will give up their own life,
rendering this fight
between Yusuke and
Toguro the ultimate one.
Now, the two competitors
brace themselves
for the final showdown.
[KOTO]
Greetings everybody
from the heart of
the Dark Tournament
where the moment you've
all been waiting for
has finally arrived.
Toguro versus Urameshi.
Will the reigning champions
steal another victory,
or will this year's
now-favored guest team
pull the upset of the century
and walk away with the prize?
There's two points and one
championship on the line!
I can't take this
kind of pressure;
it wreaks havoc on my ticker!
On top of that I've got ulcers.
Will you look at that? You know
he just thinks he's so great.
But he's not?
Put your shirt
back on!
Puu! Puu!
Urameshi!
Don't be intimidated
by that stupid steroid
half-naked freak!
[HIEI THINKS]
You must concentrate.
[KURAMA THINKS]
I have faith in you.
[KOENMA THINKS] Don't blow
this one, Yusuke.
Ah man!
Are we late?
If we aren't, it's not thanks
at all to the aussie demon
that traded our tickets
for a couple of pints.
Will you shut it!
We're standing here, aren't we?
No, really, I have to check!
Yes, we are.
It certainly was kind of
that usher to let us inside.
Right. Didn't even have
to break the other leg.
Yeah, whooptie-doo.
You just got lucky he was fat.
Right now your griping's about
as useful as tits on a bull.
Let's find us some seats.
It's Chu!
[FAN 1]
And Touya! And Jin!
[FAN 2]
And the Yo-Yo kid Rinku!
Oh, there's some!
This time's for real.
Are you guys ready?
Okay then! Begin!
[crowd erupts in cheers]
Well done Yusuke. At last
the two of us fight again.
Only this time things are
going to be different for you.
I'm not throwing
this fight for anyone.
Good. Cause now,
for me, it's personal.
You don't think this
is personal for me too?
[TOGURO 2] I'll start
with 80 percent.
Look at that!
Toguro's really powering up!
Kill Urameshi!
Amazing! Toguro's Demon
Energy is so strong that
it's literally melting the flesh
off the weaker apparitions.
[KURAMA]
They're not the only ones.
I can't take much more
in my present state.
Not a problem!
I can handle it!
[KOENMA] Well actually,
no you can't, Kuwabara.
Now all of you,
stick behind me!
[YUKINA THINKS] If his Energy
can have this kind of effect
on hardened demons, there's
no telling what it might do
to ordinary humans!
We have to get you out
of here and quickly!
Puu! Puu! Puu!
Oh, uh never mind...
I see Puu has everything
neatly taken care of.
No need for alarm.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
As strong as this guy is,
I really should
be getting scared.
Like pissing my pants scared.
But I don't feel anything.
In fact, I'm starting
to creep myself out
with how not scared I am,
Genkai definitely didn't
say anything about this.
[KURAMA THINKS] I can't
believe the extent
to which Yusuke's
technique has improved.
What? Are you crazy?
There's no way in heck
that you could block
his straight on punch!
[TOGURO 2] I see the way you
look at me, in judgment.
But you have no idea
what it's like, do you?
To lose your beloved?
No, and I never will because
I won't let that happen.
[YUSUKE] I actually look
forward to growing old with her.
[TOGURO2] You say that now.
[YUSUKE] Stop it. This is
between you and me.
Whoa!
Now Toguro has stopped mid-punch
to chat with Urameshi.
I wish you could hear what
they were chatting about!
Those fools!
Why don't they stop
dancing around each
other and fight?
One must never let
emotions enter the ring.
That was a mistake.
[HIEI THINKS] I should have
known better than to hand
this match over to Yusuke.
Toguro has yet to
reveal his true power
in this or any tournament,
though I venture it
would dwarf any one
of his opponent's
in comparison.
Maybe, but then again there's
also Yusuke's Spirit Wave
to toss up in the wind.
And let me tell
ya now that's nothin'
to shake a stick sideways
at neither, or so I say.
What both of youse is
failin' to see is that Yusuke's
a good bit stronger now than he
was when he fought against us.
It's time. You have something
to prove to me Urameshi.
Show me that your master
did not sacrifice her
strength for you in vain.
Right.
I'll show you.
You all right?
And you?
Following an
action-packed beginning,
what we've got on our hands here
is a good old-
fashioned stand off!
But now it seems that
Yusuke's focusing his energy
into that trusty
right index finger.
Use it.
Blast him with your Spirit Gun!
So, she didn't teach
you any new tricks?
I want to see everything
that Genkai gave you.
Hold on, Urameshi got somethin'
from Genkai before she died,
like a gift?
[KOENMA] Yes, but not
exactly the sort of gift
with wrapping and
a bow, Kuwabara.
More like her gift, you know,
what made Genkai special,
she gave him the energy
she had stored for decades.
How much power
did she give him?
I don't know, but
I'm guessing it all.
[KURAMA THINKS] Genkai's
powers were phenomenal.
If Yusuke truly
received all of them,
he might just stand a
chance against Toguro.
This should be fun.
Fry him!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Are you
watching this, Grandma?
Fire!
Again he resorts to
his reliable Spirit Gun.
Mates, did it always glow
this brightly before?
[TOGURO 2 THINKS] He'll never
hit me from that distance.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Only four shots left.
I can't miss even one.
[TOGURO 2 THINKS] He uses his
head in battle, I like that.
[TOGIRO 2]
Oh come on.
Let's kick this up a notch!
Shall we?
[Juri screams]
Come out, come out, Yusuke.
Spirit Gun!
Bull's eye!
[KOENMA]
That's a direct hit.
[Toguro 1 cries out]
[KOTO] The usually rather
vibrant crowd looks on
in stunned silence.
I don't think anybody
saw that one coming.
Especially not Toguro
who's been blown
right out of the stadium!
I knew that the boy could do it.
Where am I? And who am I?
Hey lady get up, and snap out
of it! You've got a job to do!
There's a fighter
outta the ring
and you'd better start countin'
like you're always doin' for me!
Take a moment to look
where Yusuke's standing.
[KUWABARA] Hey! How the heck
do you get back in the ring?
[KURAMA] In this final battle,
there will be no boundaries.
The only rule is
kill or be killed.
Wow! Now that's an
attack to remember!
I'm so happy I got
beat by Urameshi
before he got the
super powers.
Yeah, if he was that strong
when I fought with him,
that'd by my
clacker on the barbie
and I'd be sittin' here today
on two extra-toasty buns!
I can see now that
I underestimated him.
But I don't know it
all just seems short
of the spit to me, somehow.
We won! That'll show
those nay saying demon fans!
Well, that's done,
let's pack up,
grab some over-priced souvenirs
and forget our heartbreak.
Puu! Puu!
Yusuke is much stronger now
than I ever imagined
a human could be.
[KURAMA]
Yet...
Toguro didn't even bother
to block his attack.
[HIEI] If Toguro can escape a
blast that powerful unscathed,
there's no telling what
else he might be capable of.
Look, will you stop being
such a glass-is-half-empty
kinda guy for two seconds?
Accept it! There's
absolutely no way in heck
that guy's ever coming back in
anything other than an ashtray.
[YUSUKE THINKS] No.
Is that all you've got for me?
I expected more from Genkai.
He's invincible! That's the
only explanation for it.
[KOENMA] That's not good.
Whoa! Look at it people!
Toguro has miraculously
risen from the dead.
Runs in the family I guess.
There's not so much as a
scratch on this giant brute,
the only difference
is his shades are gone!
And what piercing
eyes he has!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it! He just
dissolved my energy shield
with a mere flex of his power.
I'm gonna have to
throw it into gear
if I wanna stick
around and get this done.
[TOGURO 2]
I was foolish to depend on
you rising to this occasion.
I wanted to test you to see if
you were really strong enough
to compete with me.
Obviously my standing here
means that you've failed,
So there's no need for
me to go to full power.
I'll finish
this as I am.
[NARRATOR] Even possessing
the Spirit Energy of Genkai,
Yusuke seems unable to inflict
any damage on the mighty Toguro.
Can this possibly be
the end of our hero?
Will he avenge
his master's death,
or join her as one of
Toguro's many victims?
The clash of these two
great warriors wages on!
[YUSUKE] Hey guys! I'd say
it's goin' pretty well.
I'm getting' in some
pretty good cracks in.
But this Toguro guy
isn't that tough.
Look, he's even starting
to show his vulnerable side.
Hmm. Strike that.
Guess we'll
finally see that 100%
he's bragged about after all.
Probably intimidated by
my sheer brute strength.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm not worried, even if my
friends and teammates are.
See, I'm hiding
something myself.
These people can't
believe what they're seeing
and neither will you,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪