[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
has gone undercover
in the Genkai Tournment,
to stop the
evil demon Rando
from stealing
Genkai's psychic powers.
After discovering
his true target
has been fighting in disguise
as the young Shorin,
Yusuke went to great pains
to put Shorin on the ground.
It seemed he'd
solved the case.
But now Rando has dropped his
disguise and shown his true,
monstrous form.
The final fight begins.
So that's Rando.
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi.
Are you ready to fight yet?
'Cause I'm ready
as soon as you are.
Even when losing consciousness
that boy has a one-track mind.
[BOTAN THINKS] Be brave, Yusuke.
At least for Kuwabara's sake.
This is always the hardest part.
Choosing what
technique to use first.
[RANDO] Like a drooling
boy in a candy store.
Perhaps you can give
me a good suggestion.
Shut your mouth.
And here's the kill!
So there.
Oh, crap.
This battle isn't
going to last very long
if only half of you
can still throw a punch.
[YUSUKE]
What?
Those punches had
absolutely no Spirit Power.
You've gone dry.
[KOENMA]
What is Yusuke thinking?
Without the strength of Spirit
Energy behind his attacks,
He couldn't
hurt the ghost of a fly,
let alone an expert
human-hunter like Rando.
The only problem, of course,
is a serious
shortage in his supply.
And a very high demand.
Alright, I've just thought of
the perfect technique for you.
Well, how pretty.
What, is it?
That is life-force thread.
An archaic form of
materialized spirit energy,
no doubt taken from
a very ancient psychic.
Damn it!
That's no good.
I can't move.
[RANDO] Needless to say, I could
crush you in an instant,
but I'd rather
test my techniques.
It's been such a long time.
This thread is
connected to my own energy,
and no human
efforts can sever it.
Yeah, I noticed.
[YUSUKE] Seems kind
of boring that way.
Yes, I shall have to
add more excitement.
[Rando laughs]
[RANDO]
How's this? Better?!
[Yusuke cries out]
Is this boring you?
Or is this?
What about this?
Or this one?
Or this? Or this? Or this or
this or this or this or this?
[Rando laughs]
Tell me how it feels human!
I'm dying to know!
Goodness,
Yusuke truly can't keep up
this beating much longer.
Genkai, you
have to do something!
Rando's only going
to come after you next!
I won't.
Whoever wins this
fight is the one I teach,
and it would be wrong to
interfere with the selection.
I'm getting old now.
My powers have to
be carried forward,
even if they
must stay for a while
in the hands of the wicked.
[BOTAN]
Listen to yourself!
If Rando gets your techniques
there's no telling how
many people he'll kill with it!
Innocent lives that you
will be responsible for!
There are things
you do not understand.
[BOTAN]
Like what?
Progress is what must prevail.
It's a story I cannot change.
No, you're wrong.
There, you see?
It's amazing how indestructible
these threads are.
[Rando laughs]
So how do you feel?
[YUSUKE]
Why do you keep asking?
I'm hanging upside down from a
tree! Take a guess! You freak!
Ooh, hostile.
We're not there yet.
(Chanting)
Why do I get the feeling he's
not just doing that to be cute?
Hey, what's cooking?
What the hell are those?
[RANDO] I brought them from
the depths of Spirit World.
They're called Hate Fish.
Hate fish?
And through another technique
I've created a Trainer Demon.
They're controllable
and very fierce.
Watch!
As you can see
they're very hungry.
And the demon
could defend himself.
Imagine if he had been tied up.
[RANDO]
But enough about that.
I want to try a move I
learned much more recently.
The Spirit Gun!
How can he--?
That's it! That's the look!
You have surrendered
to your fear.
That move,
he must have learned it
simply by watching
Yusuke perform it just once.
It was also several
times more deadly.
[GENKAI] This creature's
adaptability
and knowledge of the
human spirit is incredible.
[BOTAN]
It's awful.
[GENKAI] If he
does learn my power,
he will no doubt take it
further than I could ever go.
The fear-screaming
from a victim's eyes.
[RANDO] Increased
power is wonderful,
but it's the fear
that makes me hunt.
You have shown me that fear.
Now die.
Yusuke!!
[YUSUKE]
Yusuke Urameshi. Age 14.
Survived by his
mom and everybody.
After going through a big ordeal
to get back his life back,
Yusuke had a brief second chance
until he was eaten by a fish.
That's right! No heroic death!
No fighting evil
villains. Fish food.
This is dumb!!
Yes, eat all you want
my precious Hate Fish.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Hate Fish...
What a stupid name.
It can't be...
You fool! At least
pull him from the water!
Whose is that?
A soul?
[YUSUKE THINKS] Okay.
Here we go again.
[KUWABARA] Urameshi!
Hey, I'm talking to you!!
[YUSUKE]
Kuwabara??
So are you giving up already?
Oh man, you are
a freakin' disgrace!
I can't believe
I've spent so much time
trying to defeat such a coward!
Now get up there and fight!
I can't even move!!
Lame excuse!
You're only stuck because
you can't see your own energy!
You're an idiot!
Hey, watch it.
Go ahead and die with
your tail between your legs.
Maybe they'll make
me Spirit Detective
because I'm not such a wuss!
[Kuwabara laughs]
No way!
[YUSUKE]
Dumb Kuwabara!
This is my job!
[blast]
That's Yusuke's energy!
All he needed
was a good insult.
So much Spirit Power couldn't
have come from that boy.
His crippled friend
must have transferred
the last of his energy to him.
Oh well, it matters not.
Just more time to practice
my favorite techniques.
Though... I still love
the idea of killing
you with your own attack.
Now...  come out!
Yusuke... you will
have to breathe soon.
[YUSUKE] Funny thing
about swamps.
They're just always
connected to another one!
Don't talk Yusuke!
Just shoot him!
And as for my
Spirit Gun technique.
You're doing it all wrong!
Does he have enough strength?
Oh?!
You hold too much back.
[YUSUKE]
Spirit Gun!
Sure you can
use it more than once.
But you lose the
good old stopping power.
Good shot!!!
Do you still
think I'm a fool
for not taking him
out of the fight?
[YUSUKE] Please be dead.
I don't have anything left.
Ten cheers for our
Detective extraordinaire!
-Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
-One! Two! Three! Four!
What's that?
Where? What's what?
[YUSUKE]
Give me a break.
[RANDO]
You have caused me pain.
I do not like that.
Well, this boy's attack
injured me more than I thought.
I barely have the
energy to destroy him.
Even though it looks like
I can't move right now,
I'm very dangerous.
There's no point in
either of us bluffing now.
Both our bodies are exhausted,
and our spirits are weak.
But I'll still succeed.
Because I can reduce your body
and crush your puny bones
like I did with
your ridiculous friend.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
He must've gotten me good.
I can't even tell
if he's talking.
We've already
suffered with Kuwabara.
I can't bare to watch it again.
(Chanting)
Reduction!!
[Rando chuckles]
Soon the world will be
a much bigger place for you.
And you will be afraid.
I will make certain of that,
even if it means ripping
apart your fingers one by one.
It's not right...
[RANDO] How have I been
the one to shrink?
You're the slave
of your own technique.
Yes but how?
It is physical law that
the imbalance of matter
created by that
technique must be relieved.
If there's no victim,
then the user goes boom.
Are you blind?!
That boy was cleary my victim!
[GENKAI] Yes. But his
body must know that.
As with any spoken chant,
the victim is affected
only by hearing it.
In this way it enters the brain
and reprograms the cells.
All a reasonably
intelligent fighter has to do,
is cover his ears.
But if I didn't know
it then how could he?
Are you okay?
Why is everything
so freaking quiet?
[YUSUKE] Swamp algae
in my ears, gross.
Swamp algae?
You know the mechanics
of your stolen techniques.
But without training you'll
never know how to use them.
Shut up hag! All I have
to do is reverse the chant--
[Yusuke laughs]
Come on now. You really
think I'm gonna let you do that?
Even at that size I don't
have the energy to punch you.
But I guess at this point
we can let gravity take over.
And that, boys and girls,
is my Super Elbow Drop.
[BOTAN]
Yusuke!
You really did it!!
I know, but can we
wait until tomorrow
before we jump around
all excited-like?
Winner of the Genkai
Tournament: Yusuke Urameshi!
[BOTAN]
Yay!
[KOENMA]
Well done, Yusuke.
In addition to defeating
a notorious crook
and earning some
training for yourself,
you have also shown
that I was completely correct
in choosing you as Spirit
Detective, because I am perfect.
Hey, uh Koenma sir?
Speaking.
Remember how you said
not to bother you
while you watched the fight?
Well it's caused a
little bit of a back-up.
Oh, have mercy.
[BOTAN] I should take
Rando back to Spirit World
before he wakes up.
Oh darn, I was really hoping
I could keep him as a pet.
You should take Kuwabara.
Now that I've
finished working on him.
What do you mean?
Take him to Spirit World?
[GENKAI] No dim-wit,
to his house.
I've helped him
make a complete recovery.
Whoa, that Spirit Wave
technique sounds pretty cool.
[GENKAI]
I'm glad you approve,
since you'll be training for the
next six months to learn it.
Nah! I'll have to get
back to you on that old lady!
First how 'bout my real prize.
A first-class
ticket to Tokyo Dome!
What? You still remember?
Well of course! You think all
this was community service!
Sorry Yusuke, but
you're not allowed to go.
The entire purpose
of that tournament
was to choose my student.
Do you really think
after all that mess
that I'd let you have
a choice about it?
But my ticket.
Yes you'll need to have
someone go in your place.
But, the Battle Match...
[BOTAN]
Yusuke.
[GENKAI] This is going to
be a long six months.
[BOTAN]
Hello everyone.
Six months will
pass in a blink
as we see Yusuke return from
his training with Genkai.
And you can bet he'll need
those amazing new powers,
as the Earth becomes infested
with terrifying monsters!
Maybe I'll even
step in to fight!
While Koenma learns
of the massive invasion,
Yusuke and Kuwabara travel
to the haunted city
of Ghosts and Apparitions
to combat the heart of the
threat Four Cryptic Beasts
within the walls
of Maze Castle!
It's the next big assignment,
and they won't
be fighting alone.
Next time on Yu Yu Hackusho!
♪