♪
[NARRATOR] As Yusuke's second
detective case rolls on,
the psychic Genkai
announces her last test
will be a tournament
between the final eight.
Kazemaru, Shorin, and Kuwabara
have won their rounds.
Now it's Yusuke
versus Kibano,
and Yusuke has a problem.
The fights are in darkness.
But Kibano's special mask
allows him to track
a person's energy.
And Yusuke is fighting
completely blind.
Can he survive?
[body hits ground
and Yusuke cries out]
Has Yusuke been beaten?
What a shame.
If you say you give up.
I'll let you live.
[KOENMA] You don't seem
to have a chance Yusuke.
But that's not the point.
Just get up and attack
him! It's your job!
Oh well, guess
you'll just have to kill me.
Ooo... Acting with the
reckless arrogance
that only a kid could have.
You probably
think you're invincible.
[KIBANO] You've lost
a lot of energy.
I know because it's harder
to see you in my mask.
Yusuke can't go on like this.
You better not die! Darn it!
Kibano is wrong
about him.
Even with the mask.
Kibano's Awareness is
limited by what he expects.
In a normal person, sure,
power would have gone
down from such an attack,
so that's what Kibano sees.
But this brat's Spirit Energy
has a very unique wavelength.
It responds to desperation
by getting stronger.
He could win if he could see.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Hey, now there's an idea.
If only I could
get him closer I'd--
I'll try to make this quick!
Now it's over!
What?
See, this is all
apart of my plan.
Next I'm going
to break your arm.
Yeah! Do it!
Then stomp on his face!
Not such a bad idea...
If I wasn't a master in
every style of martial art.
Including grappling.
Here's my favorite throwing
technique! The Bonzai Missile!
[Yusuke cries out]
When he's far
away he can't see,
and when he's up close that
guy does Judo moves on him!
What's he supposed to do?!
The only way I see
Yusuke pulling this off
is with the Spirit Gun.
But that's still impossible.
He'd never be able
to make an exact hit.
Who cares, stop
dwelling on what-ifs.
The reality is that he can't see
and he's about to get canned.
[KUWABARA]
You better get up Urameshi!
I'm not gonna let
you run out on me again!
[KIBANO] I must admit...
I'd feel guilty killing an
amateur like you.
Please, tell me you give up and
you can go back to your mother.
I'll even open my ear plate
so I can hear
you're actual voice.
I could just feel
out your vocal vibrations.
But surrender
has such a nice sound.
Then say it yourself
I'm winning this fight.
Next time you attack me
I'm gonna knock
that helmet off your head.
Then I'll slap you around a bit.
If you can still move.
Don't you think it's a
little too late in the fight
for you to bluff?
We all know that you're blind.
Maybe, but my mom
told me not to make excuses.
Fine.
Then I'll give
you no more warning.
Farewell, boy!
I will admit I am surprised
by how long you've
lived but now it's all over.
I can feel you trembling!!
Your body's shaking with fear!
Watch out!!
Yusuke!
Fair well!!
Not trembling dummy!
I'm powering up!
Spirit Gun!
Oh, yeah!
[YUSUKE]
Whoa.
I--don't understand
what happened.
You can't see in here.
How did you hit me?
Why don't you look at your belt
before your eyes roll back.
[KIBANO] What is that thing?
You tracked me down with that?
That's right. It's the cigarette
Genkai was smoking.
Moron!
Hey!
Remember? She threw it at
me at the start of the fight.
I saw it on the ground a few
minutes ago... still glowing.
And while you were busy teaching
me your stupid kung-fu moves,
I slipped it under your belt.
And after that...
well Hell, you know the rest.
You... tricked me.
Yeah well of course I did!
And with that mask
you couldn't see it.
Winner: The Dimwit.
That was close.
Hey... where did you learn
to be so tricky anyway?
It's probably from being a kid,
trying to think up reasons
why he didn't come to class.
Maybe.
Wait... What was that
glow-ball you fired at him?
That's my Spirit Gun.
See, it's like this big
explosion of my Spirit Energy.
So you're using a
gun and I've got a sword.
Don't you think
we're cheating?!!
Oh don't worry, Kuwabara.
Just think of these weapons
as extensions of yourselves.
[GENKAI]
All right kiddies!
Let's start the semi-finals.
The first match.
Kazemaru and Yusuke.
I've waited for this.
Whoa old lady!
Pick somebody who's had
a chance to breath, okay!
If you want to get mad then get
mad at the one who drew the lot.
And that's you.
You're not a very lucky
person at drawing lots,
are you Urameshi?
Well can you at least
throw another cigarette?
No... We won't be fighting
the semifinals in here.
[GENKAI]
Follow me.
Great, now I have to fight
a dude who can shoot a
giant energy blast out
of his whole stinking palm
and my little Spirit Gun
is all used up.
And don't forget
that one of those fighters
might be Rando in disguise.
Oh yeah that's true!
If Rando's hiding as a human
there's only two guys
he could be now.
And there's something not
right about that Kazemaru guy.
Call it a bad hunch.
[GENKAI] This will be your
new fighting ground.
[KUWABARA]
What is it?!
The site of an ancient battle.
An entire army
was overcome by madness.
[GENKAI] Thousands of soldiers
attacked their own men.
Restless souls fill this place.
I'm seeing things here
I never wanted to see!.
Oh please, please
someone take me home!
On this hillside, Spirit Energy
begins to overtake the body.
It's perhaps the best place
on Earth to use Spirit Power.
And so the best
place for your fight.
Excellent, their energy
is circulating through me now.
I feel stronger already.
What about you?
No use, I'm feeling some
of my power coming back.
But there's no way it's
enough to use my Spirit Gun.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Damn it,
I can see his freaking power!
Please don't let him be a demon.
And the first match
of the semifinals, begin!
What a shame for you.
Fighting two battles
in a row, both mismatched.
What?!
Everyone knows Kibano
would have defeated you
if not for your little trick.
And as for my own advantage,
well, you'll soon find out.
[KOENMA] This battle is looking
far from pleasant for Yusuke.
And if Yusuke gets beaten
and blows this case
I'm gonna get reamed for
making him Spirit Detective.
[GREEN OGRE]
Excuse me, Koenma sir!
What is it!
Phone call.
Can't you see I'm busy!
Hello, you've reached
the desk of Koenma,
mighty ruler
of the Spirit World.
I'm not here right now,
but would love
to talk to you later
if you're of any importance.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
Beep.
[KING YAMA] This is your father!
Where the hell are you?
You're in trouble, boy!
Wait! Dad! I was
just using the bathroom.
[KOENMA]
He hung up on me.
Sorry sir! It's not my fault!
Quiet!
It's always your fault, okay?
Could you be quiet sir?
The fight started.
Do you want me to hurt you?
[KAZEMARU] I'm surprised to find
someone else in this contest
who can use the Spirit
firing technique.
Yeah, I'm pretty awesome huh?
[KAZEMARU] Of course,
it's nothing compared to mine.
Yeah good point.
Maybe we should agree not to use
them and just play fair.
Oh don't worry
I'd rather use... my fist!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Okay, brace yourself!
What?
You can't even fight back.
Do something!
He's to tired to block a punch!
Don't give up Urameshi! Put
everything you got into one hit!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Here's everything!
Oh perfect!
What the...?
Damn!
That would have finished
me if I hadn't dodged it.
I can't get that close.
Guess I'll have to,
fight long-distance!
You're, joking!
Shuriken Throwing
Knives, my favorite.
Oh, give me a break ninja boy!
I'm not too weak to dodge!
Hello! I was expecting
a more shocked reaction!
Did you not just see
me dodge your toys!
Not quite.
What?
Yusuke!
Those things
are behind you!!
Uh, oh!
Okay, they're like Boomerang
knives. That's a decent trick!
Actually they lock on
a person's Spirit's Energy.
And they can stay
up in the air for days
until hitting
their appropriate target.
Okay Yusuke.
Think of something!
All right.
Come on!!
[Yusuke cries out]
Oh perhaps I
neglected to mention
the gunpowder stored
in the tip of every blade.
They blow up on impact.
Even if you dodge the blades,
you can't avoid the explosion.
It's a done deal.
Yusuke!
How's he supposed
to get outta this?
It might be a good
time to tell him good bye.
I've already
done that once, okay!
[KOENMA] Kazemaru has
very strange powers.
Not unlike what a
demon would possess.
If he shows himself as Rando,
I'm afraid Yusuke is lost.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Getting blown to pieces is
really going to piss me off.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Not to mention letting
Rando win Genkai's power.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Guess
there's only one thing to do.
Make this explosion
worth something.
I'm a good guy Urameshi!
You have to listen
to me Kuwabara!
You have to win
the tournament now!
See ya!!
Well that's funny.
What do you think he meant?
I figured he wanted to win.
Oh dear!
I see, he knows he can't escape,
so he's decided to
kill two birds with one bomb.
He what? Urameshi!
Don't do it! Can't you think
this out a little more?!
Yusuke.
[KAZEMARU] Prepared for the
ultimate sacrifice, huh?
Well, he's forgotten my power.
You try whatever
you want, Ninja!
But I'm taking you with me.
Sorry, I have other plans.
[KAZEMARU]
What the...?!
He, disappeared!
You see that? He's gone!
Yusuke! Hello?
[KUWABARA] Hey, Urameshi!
Are you playing around?!
I'm gonna be mad if he can turn
invisible and nobody told me!
Only the dead can do that.
Then maybe he
jumped really high
and hasn't come
down yet or something.
[bubbling sound]
I found him.
Pretty clever,
hiding in the mud like that.
I wasn't hiding. I slipped.
You weren't hiding?!
Are you trying to tell me the
whole thing was an accident!
What whole thing?
You mean I actually
won the match?
[GENKAI] Kazemaru's power-up
emitted so much Spirit Energy
that it diverted the knives
toward him when you fell.
Your victory's a total fluke.
But then as I've said before.
Anything goes as long
as you can win the fight.
It isn't fair.
He's got a good point.
Guess this makes
up for the unluckiness
you had drawing lots.
Works for me.
[GENKAI]
Winner: Yusuke Urameshi!
Only three fighters are left.
I hope you're excited.
Well we've narrowed it down.
Kazemaru must not be Rando.
If he was, he would have
shown his true form
after being beaten.
Then, we've figured it out.
Shorin is Rando.
Let's move to the
second match of the semifinals.
It's not hard to guess.
Kuwabara versus Shorin.
[NARRATOR] And so the
numbers have thinned.
Chinpoh, Kuroda, Musashi,
Kibano, and Kazemaru
have all been left
on the tournament floor.
Now Kuwabara must
face the young Shorin,
who by elimination must
be the demon Rando in disguise.
Can Kuwabara possibly be ready
for his first real fight,
against a creature of evil?
[YUSUKE] Hey
everybody, it's Yusuke.
Who would've thought Kuwabara
would be the one to
go up against Rando?
I mean he's strong,
but I'm the hero, right?!
Well at least he's
got that Spirit Sword,
because Shorin's
throwing fireballs,
and it looks like
he'll play a little ball.
The deadly,
fiery kind, that is.
But when things get really ugly,
you can bet I'll tag in.
And I guarantee one thing--
I'm not in the
mood to play nice.
You won't want
to miss this next battle,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪