♪
[NARRATOR] As the final fight of
the Dark Tournament rages on,
Yusuke cannot hold up
against the demon Toguro.
Searching for the
ultimate challenge,
Toguro chose to
kill Yusuke's friend
to draw out his hidden power.
Kuwabara ran
boldly into battle,
but was abruptly struck down.
His life quickly draining,
he gave Yusuke a last message.
I did what I could.
Now beat him for all of us.
Make my death count, Yusuke!
That's oddly
anticlimactic.
You knew him for so long
and now he's dead.
Do you think that was
sufficient for you?
Or do I need to take
another one of your friends
for you to get the point?
[TOGURO 2 THINKS]
So I guess that was enough.
I've been pathetic.
But I won't let you take
away any more of my friends.
Look at it.
I'd say the wind is
something not the same!
For all those still listening
to this broadcast,
Yusuke is emitting
a strange energy
unlike anything we've
seen from him before!
His feelings, I can practically
taste them all in the air.
The energy within Yusuke's
body is changing dramatically.
[KOENMA] The loss of his
friend is too great a shock.
The walls are
coming down.
[KUWABARA] Urameshi, I'm gonna
mess your face up so bad
that kittens won't
even look at ya!
[KUWABARA]
Yukina!
That's it!
My head as a trampoline
is where I draw the line!
Cause I'm Kuwabara and
in case you guys forgot,
I've got a sword!
Beat him for all
of us, Urameshi.
[YUSUKE] Now let's do this.
I already said
I'll never forgive you.
Now I'll never be
able to forgive myself,
so let's just do this.
[TOGURO 2 THINKS]
Anxiety, and fear...
It's been fifty years
since I've felt those.
At last I enter a fight for
which I don't know the outcome.
The tension is
mounting in my neck.
An ultimate fight
with you, Yusuke.
Genkai is dead,
but one part remains.
Now I fight her progeny
and all things can
be brought to a close.
I need to thank you Yusuke, for
finally realizing your power,
You see I couldn't finish this
story with satisfaction,
until you had
become like me.
Now your power's
reached the level of mine.
You know that's
a load of crap Toguro.
Is that so?!
Yusuke,
Toguro makes a
solid right hook,
and Yusuke does nothing
to defend himself!
He ground-slides all
the way to the wall!
[crowd reacts]
[TOGURO 2]
You see?
I can tell that didn't
actually hurt you.
Earlier that punch would
have left you unconscious.
But now you can take it
without even blocking
and still get
up to fight.
If that's not a sign of
equal power, what is?
You're were right
about one thing Toguro,
that punch didn't hurt me.
Yusuke's truly done it.
He's learned how to battle on a
level playing field with Toguro!
Level, and yet at the same
time it's completely different.
[CHU] Both their powers
are mixing together.
It's the real
dinki-di, mates!
It's got the
strength of a ute,
but for some reason it
doesn't feel harmful.
Yeah, it's weird!
All a sudden I feel
a whole lot better!
Kinda' like I'm being
protected or something!
It's such of a melancholy
wind he be firin'.
Like I can feel all the sad
on his inner sides pouring out
into a big black empty.
Yusuke is locked in a struggle
with his own emotions.
A sense of guilt is
reversing his power.
[TOUYA]
His defense goes outward,
guarding all of us
in the stadium,
while his attack is aimed
solely on himself.
[TOGURO 2] Are you hurting,
Yusuke? Feeling guilty?
[TOGURO 2] Don't worry.
It's like the chicken pox.
Once you get over it the first
time, it never comes back.
Think Yusuke.
What do you owe these people?
Why do you let their
weakness drag you down?
Throw off the
bags of guilt
and you can become
as powerful as me!
Give yourself control!
Believe in nothing
but your own strength
and it can never let you down!
[YUSUKE] Shut up,
Toguro. I'm not like you.
I won't just
throw people away.
Can't let go?
[YUSUKE] I never
would have gotten this far
without those guys' help.
And whenever I was
getting my head rearranged,
it's always cause I cared
about them that I could win.
And that's precisely the reason
you've been limited up 'til now!
You're far too soft! You don't
need anyone but yourself!
Don't you understand that!
[Toguro 2 chuckles]
Guess I need to kill another
one of your friends.
Let go.
[YUSUKE] I, somewhere inside I,
I respected you, you know that?
Let's just say I haven't had
many older guys to look up to,
and what you seemed to have
goin', it didn't look so bad.
Genkai told me over and
over again how stupid I was.
But I saw your strength,
and how no one could boss
you around, no matter what!
And I wanted that.
Then you should
take my advice.
Idiot! I'm not done!
That's what I did want,
until Genkai told me the rest.
He asked the committee
to turn him from a human
into a demon of
the highest class.
He left us so he could keep his
youth and his precious strength.
Every one has
to fight with time,
to find their place before
their inevitable death.
Toguro, he ran
away from that fight.
Don't you ever do the same.
No human is ever a one man show.
Every decision that
you make will affect
the countless people
who care about you.
[GENKAI] Do you understand?
You can't just be
a cocky kid anymore!
You have to...
Since I started
this whole tournament,
I've learned the value
of what you gave away.
And I won't let it go, even
if I have to give up my life!
[KOENMA]
Pinch me.
So he understands now.
I can see you're a disciple
of Genkai in every way.
A slave to your softer emotions.
You shouldn't even be
allowed to say her name!
Today you die Toguro!
You go ahead and try.
He's Super-Yusuke!
Even his strategies
have improved.
Wow! Unreal!
Yusuke delivers a
ruthless one-two punch,
knocking Toguro down
with a hard right cross,
then launching a
Spirit Gun blast
before the fallen
beast could react!
It's the first time I've
ever seen Toguro on the ground!
Incredible.
Yeah, you can
say that again!
I think we can
really start hoping...
[YUSUKE] Get on your feet.
I'm firing one last
shot with all I got,
and it's gonna end this
fight one way or another.
So no more stupid
surprises or fakes...
You show me everything
you got right now.
If I win this time I don't
ever want to see you back up.
[evil chuckle]
Oh my, Toguro is back up,
realigning his head with the
sturdiness of an action figure!
A crazy one!!
Don't tell me Toguro
is completely unharmed
after that attack!
I'll tell ya'
he's a total freak!
[SAKYO THINKS] This is the fight
you asked me for, Toguro.
Now let's see you deliver.
[TOGURO 2] The eyes
of determination.
I've encountered them many
times on glory-seeking fools,
and I always give their
owners what they ask for.
Nearly always it's
a fight with me,
and when I see
they truly want it,
I'm obliged to kill.
But you've actually asked me
to give it all I have, so be it.
Wait a sec.
I thought we'd covered this,
but Toguro seems to be
making another increase!
[TOGURO 2] I admit I
haven't been truthful.
What I said was a hundred
was more like eighty-five.
Aw man!
To fully become a
master of a trade,
you must commit your all to it
and throw everything else away.
If you don't have
the guts to do that,
you will never be
more than a groundling.
Damn, you're stupid.
You didn't throw it away.
[YUSUKE] You just
ran away from it.
Like a frightened little child.
[YUSUKE] I won't run,
and I won't let go.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I'm doing just
what you said, Genkai.
I'm caring about
you jerks all the way.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I don't care
I never fire a blast again.
I don't care if I die.
The only thing I want to
do now is make this shot
with all the power I have.
Look at that!
Our cobber is
makin' a last stand.
They'll put their full
powers against each other.
I guess all we
can do now is pray
and let the man
upstairs decide!
Um, can I go home yet?
Whichever way
this turns out...
...it's definitely the end.
Right Yusuke!
Give him all you got!
Their energies are
both pushed to the max!
And not just Rinku! Righty
up ta' the max and beyond!
They're putting their
lives on this one final attack!
Good luck.
[YUSUKE]
Spirit Gun!!!
[Toguro 2 struggles]
[muscles crackling]
Toguro's barely
holding it back!
Yes, it is unusual
seeing him on the defensive.
Come on Urameshi!
We know you can do it!
Don't let Toguro take
all of our lives!!!
He's fading!
Toguro has not released
himself from the Spirit Gun yet.
But if this blast isn't
enough to make him fall,
Yusuke will have no more
power left to fight him.
Toguro will triumph.
Come on Yusuke,
make the thing work!
He's losin' it!
It's over.
Urameshi couldn't do it.
We're screwed!
That means Toguro is
gonna eat us all, man!
I killed Genkai
but one remained.
And now that surviving piece
can at last be put to rest.
This is not good.
[TOGURO 2] Thank you again,
Yusuke Urameshi.
[TOGURO 2 THINKS]
This was the first time
I could use my
absolute strength,
and you answered.
It was the only
way it could end.
That's hard to call.
They're both out?
Yusuke.
Juri, behind you!
He did it!!
We are free.
We can go home
now Shizuru!
Winner of the Tournament!
Team Urameshi!
[crowd erupts in cheers]
[KOENMA] Lovers of suspense
better close your eyes!
We've got a spoiler coming
in 3.. 2.. 1, and now!
Okay, not everything
is quite as it seems!
And we've got a little
more conflict to handle
before we can wrap this up,
like escaping from
a collapsing stadium!
Toguro may have left us,
but what about
Sakyo and his plan
to flood the living
world with demons?
Not to mention
his budding romance
with that otherwise
stone-faced Shizuru??
No one turns off a
movie in its final scene,
so don't miss the
next Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪