♪
[NARRATOR] Somewhere in
Mushiyori City, a psychic is
forging a tunnel between the
Demon and Human worlds.
Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
must stop the unknown enemy,
but the opening tunnel
has given awesome powers
to normal humans,
and it's hard to know
who is friend or foe.
Yusuke has recruited Murota,
a mind-reading human.
But while trying to weed out
the enemies by their thoughts,
Murota was shot,
and the criminal mastermind
made his introduction.
The heroes have taken
Murota to the hospital,
where new danger awaits.
Listen crybaby, we don't
have time to freak out.
They could be
coming for us.
But how can I
help you?
I'm not used to this
kind of thing, I'm scared.
I don't know how
to save the planet!
Give us those names again.
Uh, okay. There's Game Master,
Black Angel, Gate Keeper,
Sea Man, Doctor,
Sniper, and Gourmet.
A guy named Sniper.
Guess he's the one
who shot him, huh?
That's one.
Leaving six more psychics whose
powers we can only guess about.
[GENKAI] Seven enemies
with extraordinary talents.
And besides the man
who approached us,
we have no clue
what they look like.
Right, so even smiling
grannies are suspects.
I wish I had more to
give you, but I don't.
Like I said, all
that's on the guy's mind
is this huge urge to kill.
He wants every
human being dead!
With this plan, he'll succeed.
I can't take this!
Why didn't you tell me
it would be this bad!
[YUSUKE] Careful, slugger.
You're crying again.
[GENKAI] Listen. I want
us all on full alert.
You feel that?
Someone opened up
their Territory.
So, there's another psychic
like us in the hospital.
That Doctor one!
We're inside a hospital.
Of course he'd be here!
He's coming to finish me off!
Make a circle, facing outward.
We won't let this one
sneak up on us this time.
The doctor's coming.
Have a seat.
Hey!
[MUROTA] Bug!
What?
It put somethin' in me!
What the hell happened!
My whole body is aching.
He's burning up!
What were those, and why
are they getting sick?
Those weren't the same
parasites we saw in town.
It's a virus,
I heard his thoughts.
He's going to infect everybody
inside his Territory.
There's more coming!
Kill as many as you can!
[NURSE 2]
Is something wrong?
Why are your friends
on the ground?
They'll make
a meal out of her!
Get them off of you!
This is a busy
place, boys.
I don't have time
to play pretend.
Ordinary people
still can't see them.
And these stupid bugs seem to
know we're the main course.
Lets do something
damn it!
Our only hope to save them is
to find the psychic who did it.
Let's move out!
Hey, candy striper, those
two guys need medical attention!
[GENKAI] Yes. See to it.
No running inside
the hospital!
You realize how many
doctors are in here?
Okay, then we'll
knock them all out.
Just don't hit too hard.
I hate crippling civilians.
Got it.
[KIDO THINKS] Are they serious?
Kido, if you've got
any doubts in your mind,
this is the time to bail.
It's life or death.
Both those choices sound better
than demons on my streets.
You don't have
to worry about me.
This doctor might
not work here.
Maybe a nurse could
spot an imposter.
Clever.
I'll take care of
that, you guys.
And I'll check the upstairs.
If anybody finds him,
make a noise we'll all hear.
Either scream or
blow something up.
Nurse.
[NURSE 2] Please sir.
I'll scream.
Listen to me.
There's a criminal here
posing as a doctor.
You need to help me find him.
A doctor maybe
you don't recognize.
[DOCTOR] What's going on!
Why are you
harassing my staff?
[NURSE 2] Dr. Kamiya! I don't
know what he's talking about!
Leave, before I call
the police on you.
You don't get it!
Call the police, go ahead.
There's someone
in this hospital
pretending to be a doctor,
everyone here
is at risk.
Believe me.
He's already shot up
two of my friends
with some kind of infection.
If we don't find him
they are going to die,
and lots of others will too!
I take all threats
seriously, young man.
You can let the nurse go now.
Come on. I know every
doctor in this hospital.
If there is a fake,
I'll find him.
You might want to
call up 9-1-1, nurse.
[NURSE 2]
Yes.
But, why are you here, sir?
You're not supposed to work
until the late night shift.
Shut up!!
I told her she
needed to call 9-1-1.
What is it, can't move?
Well, that's because I've
severed your spinal cord.
Medical school perk.
I know exactly where to
cut you with my psychic
scalpel to cause pain.
How tragic...
In my own office--
a strange boy kills a nurse,
and then slits his own wrist.
[KIDO THINKS]
Urameshi. Be careful.
Nobody will stand in the way of
our goals. Especially not you.
[door opens]
Help!
That's my cue.
[NURSE 4] Doctor, I,
what's happened?
[THE DOCTOR THINKS]
Change of diagnosis...
Don't just stand there
nurse, call the cops!
That man, do you think
you could describe him?
Pull it together, someone
is impersonating a doctor!
Now call the police!
[NURSE 4]
Right!
[GENKAI THINKS] His Territory
reaches all the way up here?
His power is great,
we have to be on guard.
No...
[DR. 1] So you
knew this boy?
What do you mean knew?
[DR. 1] Apparently a crazy
man with a scalpel
came in and attacked
your friend and a nurse.
We've taken the
girl to the O.R.,
but this one can't
even blink for us.
We think it's
the shock.
[YUSUKE THINKS] A room
full of stupid white coats.
How do I tell who did it,
or if he's even here?
[DR. 3]
Get me a nerve specialist.
And put out an alert for a man
pretending to practice here.
[NURSE 5]
Yes, sir.
So he's not a doctor
from this hospital.
[KIDO THINKS] No, Urameshi.
You're wrong. He's here.
Kido, don't be lazy.
Tell me who he is!
He's pretty shaken up. He won't
be able to speak for a while.
[THE DOCTOR THINKS] Idiots. It's
not shock that keeps him quiet.
I paralyzed him.
Fine, take your time.
This was too dangerous for you
anyway, I'll find him myself.
[KIDO THINKS] No!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Kido's
Territory. He's got my shadow.
I can't move!
Why? Why don't you
want me to go yet?
Unless he knows...
[KIDO THINKS] That's right.
He's here.
But how do I tell
you which one?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Kido must mean the
killer Doc is in here. But who?
Keep going!
That'll have to
wait, son.
We've decided to
move him to X-Ray.
[KIDO THINKS] No you
don't, not yet.
I have to tell him somehow.
But that doesn't
make any sense!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Apparently it does, old man.
When you want to say
something bad enough.
He's writing a name!
Ka... mi...
Ya...
[YUSUKE]
Kamiya!
I'll take it that's you.
[THE DOCTOR] I get so tired of
operating on eggshells.
Hey, not to be bitchy, Kido...
...but could you get
off my shadow now!
Now that was cutting it close...
He's blacked out. Guess that's
why his power stopped.
I was instructed to play
the friendly Doctor Kamiya
for a little longer.
But now that you have come
along, Yusuke Urameshi,
the plan will just
have to quicken.
So, Yusuke's a household name.
Yes it is, at least in the
house that I hang around.
Black Angel says
you've come to wake us
from our sweetest dreams.
[KOENMA] As much as I'm rooting
for humanity's survival...
You've gotta respect
a good villain.
Psychic scalpel, virus
bugs. He's stacked!
I'm a purist...
heroes all the way!
[AYAME]
Koenma, sir.
[KOENMA]
Villians, right?
Yes, as you say, sir. I have
the report you asked for.
We've done a depth
analysis around
the manifesting
tunnel's center-point.
[KOENMA]
And?
The tunnel is indeed placed
several hundred
meters below surface.
There's an intricate cave
system underneath the city.
It will take some more time
to pinpoint its exact location.
[KOENMA] Well done,
Ayame. Keep me posted.
Yes sir.
Do you like her
more than me?
My ogre puppy, have you
done one useful thing
since this threat began?
Well uh...
Exactly. You're for comic
relief and drink-serving.
Ayame and Botan are the pros.
I'm sure it's gotten
worse since we came.
I need one of those
zapper porch lights.
What are you talking about?
What's worse??
The insects of Demon World.
You can't see them.
We just have to say my
powers are gone every hour!!!
Botan's right. They've
doubled from yesterday.
[KURAMA] It's the tunnel.
It is expanding at an
extraordinarily fast rate.
I'm probably teasing you
because I'm jealous, Kuwabara.
Being blind sounds
perfect right now.
Hey buddy, is that bad
guy still on our trail?
No, whoever it was,
he left us a few blocks back.
Why would they
suddenly stop?
Perhaps they've chosen
to focus all their power
on Yusuke's group.
Urameshi?
Strategically, you would
never close an option
unless you've made
a decisive strike.
If they've left us, Yusuke
is probably under attack.
Relax! Genkai's with them!
They won't get into trouble.
That was bad timing.
Hey, we better stop
wasting minutes.
Let's find Urameshi!
[SEA MAN] I pulled
back like you said.
Splendid work, Sea Man.
They all seem so
simple, don't they?
Should I take one out?
Not yet. I've staged
an interesting test
at the Doctor's expense.
I want to see what happens when
Yusuke's group has to battle
a fellow human to the death.
[Laughing]
[NURSE 4]
Yes, officer.
I called before. But listen,
something else is happening.
[FEMALE OFFICER]
Hey, are you still there?
So cold...
[NURSE 6]
I'm freezing.
All these sick people,
but where are the doctors?
I feel it. We've walked
into something.
Even the medical
staff is unconscious.
What's wrong
with her skin?
I don't know, but it's
definitely not good.
I'm not so sure we need to be
hanging around here, Keiko.
But Puu must think
Yusuke's here.
[PUU]
Puu!
What is it now, Puu?
The insects, I saw them
outside but I didn't tell you,
but these are attacking.
But how come I
can't see anything?
[SHIZURU]
Just run.
Maybe this is why I
hate doctor visits.
[THE DOCTOR] This is
definitely my favorite power.
I can infect everyone within
my Territory with a disease
of my own psychic creation.
I changed these demon
insects to be my carriers.
The weaker the victim's energy,
the faster the
disease can spread.
Your friends will
last thirty minutes,
and then I'll get
to watch them die.
You're gonna regret
saying that one.
[YUSUKE] I'm writing an
advice book for bad guys.
It's called
"Don't Piss Me Off!"
I learned from Kido
about you psychics.
Your powers fade when
you're asleep, so go to bed.
No time to sleep.
[The Doctor laughs]
[THE DOCTOR] I'm
working a double shift!
Hey!
Let's see if you can catch me.
Damn it!
Pronounced dead!
Enough!!!
You can't win.
Super strength
and endurance.
You're not built like
a normal human, Doc.
Yet another one of
my medical talents.
I can manipulate my
body's chemistry
to tweak my performance.
Pumping adrenaline
makes me stronger.
And cutting off my analeptic
chemicals makes me
incapable of feeling pain.
[The Doctor laughs wickedly]
I wish you would have
told me that earlier, M.D.
Here I've been
going easy on you
because I thought
you were a human.
But now I can bring
out something special
and not feel so bad.
Go ahead, I'll bring
out mine as well!
[The Doctor screams]
Urameshi's Spirit Gun!
Well Kaitou, you were correct.
Yusuke's team is
definitely in a fight.
What do you say we check
ourselves into the hospital.
The famous Spirit Gun.
That was a warning shot
for the human inside you.
Next time I won't miss.
You're as dangerous as
Black Angel said.
But I have one more
talent to show you.
It's simple, as a doctor.
Anything I can cut,
I can stitch back in place.
I think it's time
for a dissection.
[NARRATOR]
A demented human psychic
fighting for the Demon World.
To save his friends,
will Yusuke have to kill?
[YUSUKE] One downside
to making friends...
...you've got more
people to protect.
I mean, when does
a hero say,
'No! Don't hurt
that total stranger!'
I'll give up my own life!
Keiko, Shizuru, Yana, Murota,
they're all locked up
in this doomsday hospital,
not mention Kido who
may never walk again!
And to save 'em, I may
have to kill another human
with more powers than you
could throw a medical book at.
Don't miss the ass-kicking
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho!
Next time.
♪