♪
[NARRATOR] In the last match
against Team Uraotogi,
Genkai overwhelmed Suzuki,
an old demon with many
tricks and specialties,
but little strength.
Meanwhile, Yusuke recovers
from the torturous absorption
of Genkai's Spirit Wave Orb,
which promises to give
him unfathomable power.
Yusuke's team has claimed
their spot in the
Dark Tournament's final round.
Now Team Toguro
must try to do the same.
[JURI] Welcome back from
intermission, everyone.
Let's bring out
the next competitors.
On my left,
Team Gorenja!
And on my right...
The awesome Team Toguro!
[CROWD CHANTS]
Toguro! Toguro! Toguro!
Team Toguro are the
reigning champions.
And from the
screams of the crowd--
And by the betting pools up top,
they have clearly
been the favorites
in this tournament so far,
and here's three reasons why!
Karasu! Bui! And the eldest
of the Toguro Brothers!
Human or demon, you've
got to love what's next!
Hey, there's
only three of them.
It looks like the
younger Toguro Brother
isn't even
going to fight!
What is it about Team Captains
skipping their semifinals?
Hey, do you think he's in
the bathroom or something?
I bet he's going
number two!
[KOTO] Well, we're just
seconds from game time
and the younger Toguro
is still a no show.
This is highly unusual
for him to miss.
Better explain what's going on.
I don't like surprises.
My brother has much
more important business.
The three of us will be happy
to fight you instead.
Unless that doesn't satisfy.
I can fight you
alone, if preferred.
Do not mock me!
Calm yourself, Aka.
This only gives us a better
chance to destroy them.
This is quite unreal!
With Toguro's absence,
his already-short crew will
start just like Team Urameshi!
We're looking at three to five!
The finals are two days away.
What if he gets his sleep
schedule all screwy?
He should take a shower or
have a walk or something.
[GENKAI]
Don't bother him.
He'll wake up in time,
even if he doesn't want to.
There's something
new inside him now,
and it won't let
him miss that fight.
[GENKAI]
I guess I better be off.
[KUWABARA] Wait a second--
where are you going now?
Tell Yusuke not to follow me.
Are you in trouble?
Kuwabara.
[KUWABARA]
Ma'am?
You have a gentle heart. Use it.
What the heck?
Hope this isn't a sign
people are gonna start
actin' weird on me.
Now, let's get
this second battle
for the final round underway!
Karasu versus Mido Renja!
Finally, I've been
waiting a long time
to fight one of you guys.
[MIDO RENJA] We've been taking
smack in this tournament,
like we weren't on par.
But we kept fighting.
And now I'll prove
it's no coincidence
that we came this far.
Mido Renja has just created
some sort of pasty green object.
And oh my goodness,
it smells really really,
really really bad!
Awe! It's like
hot rotten eggs!
It's melting
my nose hairs!
[KOTO] What a surprise
for section seven!
The acidic blast melted
them with excruciating pain!
Make sure to get the home
release for that one, people!
Everybody's always
underestimating me.
Right until the point that
their bones start melting.
Tell all my other
victims I said hello!
Fool.
You took my arm!!
[KARASU] Now what part
should I dispose of next?
The shoulder? The leg?
Or maybe your head...
Please! I give up!
[KARASU]
How disgraceful.
The fight is over! The
winner by death is Karasu!
[KURAMA THINKS]
It's a deadly attack.
He must send his energy directly
into his opponent's body,
then ignite it from inside.
Too much for me.
I fear everyone on
that team will be so,
at least while I'm still
part human. Part Suichi.
Kurama, Hiei, watch Team
Toguro's fights closely.
We'll need a win
from each of you.
[KURAMA] Perhaps Hiei
was wiser to disobey.
[HIEI THINKS] Watch their
fights. Sorry old woman.
I have much more important
ways to spend my time.
[Hiei cries out]
[young Genkai laughs]
Hey.
[Toguro 2 chuckles]
[young Genkai laughs]
[BOTAN]
Master Genkai!
[BOTAN] What are
you doing here?
Shouldn't you be inside,
trying to recover yourself?
That was such a
giant battle you fought.
Yes, of course. I was just
getting some fresh air first.
So tell me, is our
die-hard spirit squad
ready to cheer for the boys?
Tip top and ready to scream.
Don't have to worry 'bout that!
Though just boys wouldn't
be exactly right, would it?
We all know you're the real
muscle behind the operation.
So you're Keiko.
Yes?
Take care of Yusuke.
He loves you.
I'll be seeing
you around.
Something's wrong here.
Oh, don't worry
about her!
She's a classic
joker, you know!
Let's head back
to the room now.
I'm feeling dead
tired, really!
[JURI] And quickly
on to match two!
Bui versus Ki Renja!
Take your stances, please!
Oh, now this could have promise!
Ki Renja has unsheathed a
humongous sword from his back!
[KI RENJA LAUGHING]
This is my little secret weapon.
And of course by
little I mean gigantic.
Look at this baby.
I had planned
on saving this
for the final
round of the tournament
but you look way too deserving
of an extra-large size defeat.
Oh, damn.
And Bui retorts by creating
a axe out of thin air!
You radio listeners really
need to find a TV screen--
I didn't know they
made 'em this big!
That's very impressive, but we
all know size isn't everything!
[KI RENJA THINKS] That axe will
take forever to swing.
At close range
he'll be helpless!
Alright fighters!
You may begin!
This is ridiculous!
Bui's axe must weigh
twice as much as he does!
He's letting Ki get too close!
He'll never swing it now!
[KI RENJA THINKS]
Too late, Bui.
Oh my goodness it
was so beautiful!
Bones flying everywhere
as if from a busted piñata!
Bui finishes Ki Renja
with one single blow!
I don't believe it!
Did you see how fast that was?
Like it was a pocket knife!
I don't understand.
If these fighters are so strong,
why are they obeying
that little man?
It's simple, underling.
Because even the strongest
man knows when to be afraid.
[TOGURO 1] Let me take
the rest of you at once.
If I lose, we'll
forfeit the match to you.
Fine, we'll take it!
You'll pay for your pride,
you sickly little creature!
Well now, this promises
to be an exciting end!
Toguro offers to face
the remaining three
in a winner-takes-all match!
[DEMON 1] The older
one's gonna fight!
[DEMON 2] Alone?
I thought he was
helpless without his brother!
Begin!
You know what to do!
Keep your heads and
use the strobing effect!
Our teamwork has never
been overpowered!
Here we go!
We all saw Team Gorenja
employing this move
earlier on in the tournament.
And it's nearly impossible
to defend against!
With the onslaught of
convincing false images,
twenty fighters seem
to be going at once!
The opponent doesn't
know who to hit!
Gorenja Batallion!
[Toguro 1 chuckles]
Unfortunately for you...
I'm well equipped for
fighting the larger groups.
[DEMON 3] Did you see that!
[DEMON 4]
I love these guys!
Well, both still
alive after all that.
You really did earn your
place in the semi finals.
As a reward for your
impressive endurance,
I promise to spare
one of your lives.
So which one of
you wants it more?
Don't be a fool.
You have no
choice but to kill us.
If not we'll get just stronger.
Until one day we'll
kill you instead!
He's only speaking
for himself!
Spare my life, I'll
do anything that you ask!
[Toguro 1 chuckles]
The decision is made.
In the demon world there
is no place for grovelers.
Bui and Karasu said
the same thing as you
when they challenged
us and were beaten down.
They were much prettier then.
[KARASU] Kill me now.
That's your only warning.
I'm sorry,
but your time of death is no
longer your decision, Karasu.
You belong to
the Toguros now.
And until you can argue
you will do as we require.
Brother's come to quite
prefer people like you
to fight on our side now.
No loyalties to confuse.
Also, their desire to kill us
keeps them motivated to improve.
Brother would find
you perfect for us.
That's why I
swore to spare you.
[Toguro 1 cackles]
However brother's
not here at the moment,
and we have one most
important difference.
I always hate
keeping my promises.
[Toguro 1 laughs insanely]
We've both been
waiting for this.
[JURI] That's it
for the semi-finals!
Please join us two
days from now at noon!
[DEMON 5]
That fight was so short!
[PURPLE MOHAWK DEMON]
Yeah. I never know if
Team Toguro's good,
or the others just suck.
Hey--check it out.
[GREEN MOHAWK DEMON] How'd you
like the competition, Kurama?
Look at him!
It's a dead man walking!
[KURAMA THINKS]
I must find the secret
to causing that transformation.
[KARASU] You're the only
one who watched?
Your team must
be very confident.
Either that,
or in denial.
Yes. Accepting the
truth would be easier.
The finals will come and
the four of you will die.
Just four?
[KARASU] Yes of course.
One of you dies today.
[KURAMA THINKS] I only
let him go for a second,
and he's completely vanished.
I can't sense him at all.
[KARASU] Your hair is a
bit damaged, Kurama.
Human bodies
are so frail.
I know you fear what
my touch could do to you.
And yet, maybe you
also want to know it.
[KURAMA] Get away!
[KARASU] No need to get
upset. It's just a game.
[KARASU] As a fighter,
I like you best, Kurama.
And when I like something,
I like to take it away.
It gives me a certain feeling,
like pondering
unanswerable questions.
You don't reach
the result you want,
and you're swept
with an empty despair,
that makes you feel alive.
[KARASU]
Save your fight for me, okay?
[KURAMA THINKS]
I cannot win this way.
You've gotten old. It's bizarre.
You haven't
changed a single bit.
[GENKAI] Fifty years
I lived in solitude.
Hoping I could
avoid this situation,
and never have
to see you again,
and do you realize
how close I was?
But in my twilight years
you have to get tangled
up with my apprentice,
and pull me along.
Why did you bring him here?
My association with
Yusuke is separate.
It just so happened that
you had to be involved-
though I confess seeing
you was a bonus to my plan.
[TOGURO 2] You used
to be so beautiful.
I remember. There are faces a
person looks at to feel at ease.
For a while you were mine.
So why did you put that mask on?
Did you not want me to see you
in your younger
appearance again?
Cut the sentimental crap!
I wore that mask
because I didn't
want to be stalked
by one of the hundreds of demons
who wants my head on their wall.
Due almost entirely
to your behavior.
And thank you so much for that.
You're considerably
weaker now.
You've given away
your orb, am I correct?
Yes, all my power
is with Yusuke now.
Well then, it's time
for us to end our chapter.
Hey, you're up
in time after all!
[KUWABARA] Uh, you okay
Urameshi? You have a nightmare?
Genkai, where did she go to?
Oh, I don't really know that.
She did say for you
not to follow her, though.
You idiot!
Hey, Urameshi!
Tell me what's going on!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Come on!
Eternal youth and power.
I see the committee did
a great job on your request.
A decision you
should have made too.
You could still have your youth.
It's most disturbing.
Looking at your face.
This hag you've become.
The man that I had
so much respect for
has lowered himself
to an ordinary thug.
You think I like seeing you?!
Honestly I can't stand it!
Fair enough.
That is precisely
why one of us has to go.
Goodbye, friend!
You sold your soul
for a crappy fantasy.
I should have killed
you when I had the chance!
[NARRATOR] Yusuke and Toguro's
teams have earned their spots
in the Dark
Tournament's final round.
But the first of its battles
will take place
outside the ring,
as former allies move
to settle a very old score.
[YUSUKE] Genkai, do you
realize what's going on?
She gave all her power to me,
when she knew Toguro was
gonna face her at the end.
This whole time
my stupid self
thought this was
all about me and him,
but there's a fifty
year story behind it,
and now she wants it closed.
Am I giving it a way?
Well I don't give a damn.
My teacher's walkin' into
a fight she can't win.
And nothin' is ever
gonna be the same.
♪