♪
[NARRATOR]
At last,
Yusuke defeated Toguro and
won the Dark Tournament,
while Sakyo made
good on his life-bet
by exploding the
stadium around him,
burying his plan to flood
the earth with demons
in the smoldering rubble.
But for the winners,
it is a somber end,
as they leave their
friend Genkai behind.
[waves crashing]
[YUSUKE] That's all the
quiet staring I can handle.
Let's get out
of here, okay.
Right!
After all this time,
it's gonna feel weird
not fearing for my life.
Don't sweat it Urameshi,
I can beat you up at school
every day if that
makes you feel better.
Yusuke is right...
Normal life for us all
will seem pale for a while.
Puu!
Hey!
There you are.
You're all right, Puu.
I didn't think
you'd come back
after Genkai started
talking through you.
You're kind of like a telephone
to the other side, aren't you?
Well, what are you
waiting for, operator?
Patch me in to
Grandma! Come on!
Which side's
your receiver?
What, what you'll do it
for her but not for me?!
You're my Spirit
Animal, you know!
Stop it.
--Yusuke.
--[YUSUKE] Come on.
It's not possible
anymore.
What do you mean?
The Spirit World
Genkai spoke from
is land between the
living and the dead.
[KUWABARA] But,
I thought that humans went
to Spirit World
when they die?
Yes, for a short time.
But it's merely a junction
from which their
real journey begins.
In truth, Spirit World's
a complex system
of many separate worlds.
And with the lands of the
dead there is no communication.
Genkai's was
a priority case.
Her placement should
have been quick.
Listen to me, Yusuke.
It's time we said our
goodbyes to her for real.
[YUSUKE]
It's so dumb.
We just got to let her go.
Are you ready
to go in?
I think so.
[KEIKO] Goodbye, Genkai.
Fine! You heard fox boy!
Nothing we can do for that
hag if she's already limp.
Just got to keep
truckin', yes sir!
I'm gonna go outside,
make myself a nice big
shiny first place medal,
sit in the sun,
and have a stupendous
stupid day, DAMN IT!!
Well, all right Urameshi!
Would you make me a medal too?
He's so neck-deep in repression
even I feel sorry for him.
Puu!
[BLUE OGRE] I'm so glad to have
you back in toddler form, sir.
[KOENMA] Yes, well, you carrying
a teenage stud in your arms
would have looked
a bit curious.
[doorbell ring]
[GREEN OGRE]
Yeah, who is it?
[KOENMA] It's me! And don't
answer the door with a yeah!
[GREEN OGRE]
What?
[RED OGRE]
Who's yelling at you?
[GREEN OGRE] I don't know.
Come back later. We're busy.
They've forgotten us, sir.
We're dust in the wind.
It's Koenma! Now open
up before I kick your...!!!
[KOENMA] Been so long,
I even miss the office.
Don't tell me this
is paperwork.
Yeah. About that, sir...
I told you guys to do the
stamping while I was gone!
I-I even gave you my seal!
And my favorite ink pad with
the ponies on the top!
Yes, sir. And everything
was going perfectly
until King Yama came around.
My dad?!
Yeah, and when he found out
you left your paperwork,
those veins on
his neck popped out,
and he said you had to do
it all when you got back.
You should probably
get stamping, sir,
so he doesn't
give you spankings.
There's no time!
I've got some ultra-
important business to do
and I've have
to look cool!
Now get some brooms and
clean this place up!
Right!
We don't have
time for naps!
I forgot how comfy
this chair is.
[BLUE OGRE] He's here, sir!
[KOENMA]
Fine. Let him in.
[KOENMA] Time to
find your place, Toguro.
I've arranged a thorough
evaluation of the facts.
I don't think that's necessary.
[KOENMA] Oh, no no no no,
quite to the contrary.
In fact, yours is a
very intricate case.
[TOGURO 2]
I've already decided.
I would like you to
sentence me to Limbo.
To Limbo?!
You're asking me
to send you there?
Do you even know what Limbo is?
Obviously you don't!
Of all the destinations
of parted spirits,
it's by far the most horrific.
Absolute misery. Every
part of you sliced away
except your ability
to experience pain.
Ten thousand years of wishing
you would just cease to exist.
And yet knowing that you won't.
Good.
[KOENMA] I've weighed
your demon crimes
against your human achievements.
And considering that
Sakyo's plan ended
in part because of you,
a slight punishment
will be sufficient.
Please. You do have
time to reconsider this.
I've had far too much time.
My choice is made.
[KOENMA]
Very well.
I can't convince a
man with a deathwish.
[KOENMA] Ten thousand
years in Limbo. Godspeed.
Take him away, Ogre.
[BLUE OGRE]
Yes, sir.
[RECORDS GIRL]
Mister Koenma, sir.
I tracked down the information
you desired from Records.
[KOENMA]
Really? And?
And you were right about
the date of the Dark Tournament.
It was exactly fifty years
ago when Toguro became a demon.
But that's not
the interesting part.
Three months before that
Dark Tournament began,
every single one of Toguro's
young apprentices were massacred
by the Tournament's
reigning champion.
The demon Kairen.
[RECORDS GIRL]
Exactly, sir.
[RECORDS GIRL] Kairen was
the highest class of demon,
a hateful,
black-hearted giant.
A virtual immortal from
a forgotten age.
By that time Toguro had earned
a powerful reputation
as a demon killer.
He'd built a dojo to
train young fighters
who hoped to
protect their towns.
When Toguro was away,
Kairen burst into the dojo
and slew his relatively
defenseless students.
The Dark Tournament
was nearing,
and Kairen wanted
all the participants
to fear him
before it began.
It was a sort
of invitation.
No!!
[RECORDS GIRL] At the
sight of his fallen students,
Toguro flew into
a maddening rage.
[KOENMA] Yes, Toguro
had believed himself to be
the most powerful fighter,
had he not?
It was the first time
he'd been proven vulnerable.
The records do
support that, sir.
Toguro did not face
Kairen that day,
but disappeared into the
wilderness for three months.
The morning before
the tournament,
he reappeared in front of his
team, Genkai and the others.
He seemed changed.
Detached. Possessed.
[RECORDS GIRL] He killed
Kairen... in the final round.
As his prize, Toguro was made
into a demon, like Kairen.
I don't understand the
man's way of thinking, sir.
Why would he choose to become
like the creature
he most despised?
Well, that's the
million dollar question.
Perhaps it was guilt,
for not protecting his students.
Even though he'd avenged them,
it wasn't enough.
The only way to atone was
to never be vulnerable again.
Perhaps he
wanted to become
the monster he already
felt himself to be.
Perhaps he was just afraid
of loving someone.
Perhaps he just
afraid of growing old.
Toguro is a complex case.
He's like an ant hill.
The deeper you dig,
the more tunnels appear,
and inside each is a
creature ready to bite.
Layer upon layer
of bravado facades,
contradicting desires and
intensely-wrought obsessions.
But, beneath it all,
I suspect you would
find just a normal man
with a wounded heart...
...and a broken dream.
[TOGURO 2] You were good
in there, Genkai.
Our teamwork is
even more in tune now.
It isn't going to
take us much longer.
Soon every fighter
will know of our names.
And then what?
[TOGURO 2]
We go further.
You're a
beautiful girl, Genkai.
Thank you.
I can't help but
think our human lives
are nothing but a cruel joke.
Here just long enough
to know what we want,
and then it erodes.
Don't tell me you're surprised.
You knew I would
choose to go this way.
You're right, I did know.
After that day on the river,
I knew how everything would end.
And yet I couldn't stop it.
You're a hopeless dimwit.
You realize that?
You just love to wallow in
your own ridiculous suffering.
Kairen is the one who
killed those kids, not you.
Don't you think you've
blamed yourself enough already
for not being perfect?
Haven't you
blamed me enough, too?
You trapped yourself in a body
you hated, hiding in the pain.
And now you want to torture
yourself again for eternity.
Why? Haven't we
both paid enough??
[TOGURO 2] You're wrong.
All that business delighted me.
Murdering Kairen, knowing
that I was the most powerful.
It was through
my fear of Kairen
that I pushed forward to
meet my ultimate potential.
I understood my power and
was freed from human baggage,
and in the larger scheme I
knew the part I had to play.
[TOURO 2] I'm actually thankful
for what Kairen did.
Liar!
[TOGURO 2]
Don't mourn me, Genkai.
Like you said. This is
the way I wanted it to end.
[TOGURO 2] Don't stay here
trying to figure me out.
You have a job to do.
Your apprentice, Urameshi,
he can still be stronger.
But he could go the
wrong way, too. Like me.
Maybe he'll actually listen
to you, the way I could not.
[GENKAI] You really
care about Yusuke.
In your own screwed-up way,
you've been teaching him, too.
He's like a son to me.
Maybe you think the same.
Don't ever feel regret
for the things between us.
No, Genkai. But it would
have been a beautiful life.
[GENKAI THINKS] You really
are a big-hearted fool.
[GENKAI] Okay, open up.
Remarkable.
What is, sir?
The age difference?
No, you dolt. I'm just realizing
the extent of Toguro's planning.
He had everything covered
before the finals even started!
If Urameshi wins
this tournament,
it's clear what
his wish will be.
But I'm afraid the
Tournament Committee
may not be in perfect
health this year.
The responsibility,
Koenma, might fall on you.
Take good care of
Genkai's body.
Just a friendly
piece of advice.
[KOENMA] On the surface, it
seemed that Sakyo was the one
pulling the strings
in the tournament.
But hindsight tells
us another story.
Toguro was the
real puppeteer.
[MANAGER] Ladies and gentlemen,
the final boat back to the
mainland will board
within the hour.
Please complete your check-out
and proceed to the
dock for departure.
I repeat, this is the
final trip off the island.
We hope you enjoyed your stay.
[KUWABARA] Geeze, what's
takin' those girls so long?
We're gonna get left!
Not everyone packed
just one set of clothes.
It's just like family vacation.
My dumb sister's
always making us late.
Prob'ly plucking her mustache.
Should I tell them about
your Fluffy Doll?
[KUWABARA]
Oh, uh, uh!
Hi, sis.
Enough family stories.
I was just tellin' 'em
how pretty you are.
You're a moron.
[ALL] Sorry we're late!
[YUSUKE] Oh look,
the tone-deaf sirens.
Catch.
Hey! Why do I gotta
carry all your stuff?
Of course you don't have to...
...but Yukina's drawn to guys
who are nice to their sisters.
Oh, okay! I am!
Thank you, Kazuma,
that's very sweet.
This too!
No way, Botan.
You're not my sister.
Yes, but Yukina's
socks are in here.
Puu!
[YUSUKE] You don't mind
having Puu duty, right?
[YUSUKE] Thanks. No one's
gonna take the champ serious
if he's holding a blue
teddy bear with a beak.
Puu!!
[KEIKO] Oh, we know you're cute,
Puu. He's just being a jerk.
[YUSUKE] You know I'm actually
gonna miss this stupid place.
Feels like we've
been here for years.
Losing someone
can do that.
Ix-nay on the enkai-Gay.
It took us all morning just to
get Urameshi out of his room!
[BOTAN]
Okay, okay!
[foghorn blows]
Oh, looky here!
Our ship's arrived!
Isn't that happy!
Back to skipping detentions.
And video games!
My human mother.
Various crimes.
Alright let's go home!
[ALL] Yeah!
[VOICE] Well, excuse me
if I'm a little insulted.
Hold on a sec...
[foghorn blows]
You just gonna leave
the old fossil behind?
[BOTAN] Genkai!!!
I don't believe it!
[KUWABARA] You're...
she's really alive!
Must've rubbed off on me,
dimwit. I died like you.
Half-assed.
Genkai!
[YUSUKE] Genkai!
Come here you beautiful hag!
[KUWABARA]
I knew she'd come back!
Ooh, Yukina!
I bet you've never been on a
cruise with a boy before, right?
[NARRATOR]
And so it goes.
Finally, the champion
Urameshi Team sails away
from Hanging Neck Island
with all its members intact.
But unbeknownst to them,
a new plot is unfolding.
For in the rubble of the
stadium lurks a new figure,
determined to keep
Sakyo's plan alive.
[KUWABARA] Okay!
Back to Sarayashki Junior High
for adventures in learning!
But while Urameshi and me were
off saving everybody's hides,
some new street punks
have taken over our turf!
Nobody gives us credit.
Of course, after fighting
demons with giant axes
and swords that unleash
the screaming undead,
a few latch-key kids with
big egos shouldn't be problem.
But, like everything
with the Spirit Detective,
things are not what they seem!
Don't miss out,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪