[APPARITION 1]
Did you hear?
Hina gave birth to twins!
[APPARITION 2]
And one of them is a boy!
[ELDER WOMAN]
He is a curse upon all of us.
My baby!
I beg you! Give him back to me!
Never.
The Imiko must be destroyed!
[ELDER WOMAN]
Rui!
Do not pity the beast.
[HINA]
I beg you, Rui! Don't!
No!
[HIEI]
That dream again.
[NARRATOR]
The three rulers of Demon World,
Mukuro, Yomi, and Raizen,
each summoned a warrior
from Living World...
Hiei...
Kurama...
...and Yusuke.
The recently fired
Spirit Detective
confronted his
dying ancestral father,
who tested Yusuke's strength,
only to tell him
it wasn't enough.
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Now, Yusuke's
Demon-style training has begun.
I suggest you do not push
yourself so hard, Yusuke.
I suggest you shut up!
Don't you go
serious on me, Hokushin,
'cause if you are,
training with you is
a waste of my time!
[distant rumbling]
I'm not giving up
until I'm strong enough
to shred that
old bastard into pieces!
So what are you
punching bags waiting for?
Attack me, damn it!
I'm starting to think
he may be a bit stubborn.
[MUKURO] Like clockwork,
the sound of that mule's
ridiculous hunger strike.
Tell me, Kirin.
How is he holding up?
[KIRIN]
"He?"
Oh. You mean the one named Hiei,
who you called here
six months ago.
As we speak, he's being
attacked by hordes of our men
in the dungeon Training Hall.
[MUKURO] And how many of
our men comprise these hordes?
[KIRIN]
As my liege requested,
I unleashed five hundred
A-Class Demons,
which, if you'll
forgive me for saying,
sounded excessive, but he's
no doubt been killed by now.
[MUKURO]
Kirin.
How long have you been
my second-in-command?
[KIRIN] It's been two
hundred fifty glorious years.
[MUKURO]
I see...
Then you should know by now
that when I say five hundred
A-Class Demons,
I mean a thousand.
[KIRIN]
Pardon my insolence,
but why is Lord Mukuro
so interested
in this particular low-life?
He's shown nothing more
than A-Class levels
since he's been here.
[yelling]
[DEMON 1] I think we might
be the only ones left.
[DEMON 2]
Let's go! We can get him!
[DEMON 3] Hold on!
He'll fall asleep soon enough.
[DEMON 1] Fine, we'll attack
as soon as he's out.
[DEMON 2]
Now!
[DEMON laughing]
[DEMON choking]
[thud]
What a waste of time.
[RUI] Ice Apparitions
cloister themselves
on an island in the sky,
avoiding all contact
with the outside world.
[APPARITION 1]
Did you hear?
Hina gave birth to twins!
[APPARITION 2]
And one of them is a boy!
[APPARITION 3]
A boy? But that's impossible!
[ELDER WOMAN]
He is a curse upon all of us.
[APPARITION 2]
There's only one explanation.
Hina must have
snuck away from Ice World
and met a man.
[APPARITION 3]
How could that harlot do
such a disgraceful thing,
endangering us all like that?
[RUI] The Ice Apparitions
live in a world devoid of men.
Every one hundred years,
to each woman,
a daughter is born,
through immaculate means.
[crying]
[RUI]
The baby is always female,
unless the mother has violated
the laws of our society
and conceived
the child with a man.
[APPARITION 1]
Twins. One girl and one boy.
We've never seen
such an abomination.
[APPARITION 2]
What should we do?
[HIEI] I could see and hear,
even before I was born.
If I'd had the power then,
I would've set every one
of those cold women ablaze.
I wanted to.
My baby!
I beg you! Give him back to me!
Hina...
You have shamefully broken
our most sacred covenant.
You are too young to understand
how you have tainted us,
but I have seen the horrors
that men are capable of.
[HINA] This is my sin, please
don't punish my son for it.
The baby girl is yours to keep.
But the boy...
The boy is a curse,
and he will certainly
be our undoing.
Then I'll leave here
forever and take my children,
and I'll promise
never to return again.
But please,
please give him back!
Never.
The Imiko must be destroyed.
[HINA crying]
[RUI] Our rules may be strict,
but not without reason.
Long ago, the ancients came here
to escape the harmful
influences of men.
We have been free
of vanity, abuse and war.
However, this security
comes at a high cost:
Total isolation.
The elders say there have,
in the past,
been boys born
through impure means.
In each case, the boy grew up
to be violent and cruel,
and the mother always
met a gruesome fate.
[ELDER WOMAN]
Rui...
I know that you
and Hina are close friends
and this is difficult for you,
but you must do this
for her own good.
And yours, and ours.
This Imiko--this boy of fire--
will slaughter us all.
But--
Do not pity the beast.
[HINA gasps]
You killed my son!
[HIEI] As I fell,
I willed myself to survive,
now that my nascent life
had a purpose.
I would live,
if only to see the day
that I would return
to that place
and kill every
last Ice Apparition.
[HIEI]
That dream again.
[MUKURO] You've made
quite a mess down here.
I'm running out of
A-Class Demons to sic on you.
Perhaps it's time we moved on
to a more powerful opponent.
[MUKURO] You've surpassed
even my expectations, Hiei.
But you still can go further.
You lack motivation.
Go figure--After six
months of this training,
I still don't know
what you want from me,
you odd mummy.
I don't know what
kind of Demon you are,
or for that matter, what you
even look like under there.
[MUKURO]
You want to see, don't you?
Don't worry.
There's no big revelation,
shocking or trite like
"I am your father."
But maybe it's time you
saw my face for what it is.
[MUKURO] A challenge:
I'll bring you one more warrior.
If you reclaim your potential,
you might even be in his class.
If you beat him,
I'll show myself,
hiding nothing from you.
And he just... has to die?
[MUKURO]
That's it.
[MUKURO] In addition to the
hundreds of expendable soldiers
you've already met
and done away with,
I always maintain a group of
seventy-seven elite warriors
as my select guard.
I'll bring one of them
here for you to fight.
If you defeat him,
I'll unmask myself.
And I'll give you
the distinct honor
of taking his place
on my select guard.
I have no use
for honors or distinctions.
They're nothing
but meaningless tokens.
[MUKURO] I think you
might change your mind.
You'll find this particular
"meaningless token"
opens many other doors.
You'll have a much easier time
finding what you seek.
[MUKURO] I'll return in five
minutes with your challenger.
[HIEI]
Eerie beast...
The way he spoke...
I wonder how much he really
knows about my quest.
[YUKINA] Mr. Hiei,
may I ask you something?
If you happen to come across
someone in Demon World
who carries a stone like mine,
would you please
give this to him?
It's sacred.
It belonged to our mother.
[YUKINA]
An Ice Apparition sheds a tear,
only one, at the moment
she gives birth to her baby.
When that tear crystallizes,
it appears different from
the ordinary Hiruseki Stone,
and is given to the child.
But I was told that
when my mother had twins,
she shed two tears.
[YUKINA]
I wear one around my neck,
and the other stone is
supposedly held by my brother...
Wherever he is.
[HIEI] I'm surprised
you managed to keep it
from the greedy human swine.
[TARUKANE laughing evilly]
[YUKINA] I hid it where
he could never find it:
My stomach.
[HIEI] So if it's
that important to you,
why are you giving it to me?
[YUKINA] Even as a baby,
my brother was surrounded
by an intense flame.
It was so intense that they
wrapped him up in sacred cloth,
and tucked his stone inside.
That's what Miss Rui told me.
Rui?
Oh... She was my
mother's closest friend.
[HIEI]
The woman who left me for dead.
[YUKINA]
Mr. Hiei?
So... as I was saying,
if his Demon Energy
was so radiant even then,
then he shouldn't
be so hard to find
with your gifted eye.
So if you see someone
with the same stone,
would you please
give that to him,
and tell him his sister
is looking for him
in Living World?
He's been missing
for years, correct?
What makes you think your
brother isn't just dead?
I believe he's alive.
[HIEI]
Yes.
But why?
Uh...
It's something that
Miss Rui had said to me.
[RUI]
I could tell that he understood
every word we were saying.
And he will come back
for his revenge.
She was confident and so am I.
[RUI]
When you come back,
seeking the revenge
that you, and we, deserve,
please kill me first.
It's the least I can offer to
atone for what I'm about to do.
[ELDER WOMAN]
This Imiko--this boy of fire--
will slaughter us all.
[ELDER WOMAN]
Do not pity the beast.
[YUKINA] If the only way
our Ice World can survive
is for our people
to freeze their hearts...
Well then...
They don't
deserve to survive.
That's how I feel.
[HIEI] So that's the
real reason why you left?
And all that crap
about you being "allowed"
to stay in Living World
to look for your brother
was just a lie.
[YUKINA]
Uh...
Never depend on others.
If you want them dead,
then do it yourself.
Quit waiting for a phantom twin
who for all you know is dead.
I guess you're right.
Thank you... Hiei.
I think...
that's the sort of advice
a girl might get
from her brother.
[HIEI]
My stone should be emitting
a powerful Demon Energy,
but I still haven't been
able to track it down,
even with my Jagan Eye.
I suppose there's the
chance that whoever has it
is hiding it as Yukina did--
in their stomach.
[MUKURO]
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
[gasps]
It's you.
[HIEI]
Shigure, surgeon of the damned.
So how long have you been
working for old bandage face?
[SHIGURE] Since shortly after
you left my services, Hiei.
[MUKURO]
You two know each other?
Well, strictly on
a doctor and patient level.
At the time, I did show him
how to swing a sword correctly.
Though...
From what I've seen,
he's made a few
improvements since then.
[MUKURO]
Fascinating.
But I must admit,
your recovery astounds me.
Can you really be the same
Demon I gave the Jagan Eye?
Performing a transplant's
like giving new life.
The process is a rebirth,
so to speak.
Afterwards,
the patient's power is reduced
to that of an infant.
As I recall,
you were no different.
When you left me,
your Demon Energy
had dropped to almost nothing.
Yet here you stand before me
only a few years later,
your power even greater
than it was before the implant.
Truly astonishing.
What can I say--
I've never really been one
for lots of bed rest
or homemade chicken soup.
[SHIGURE] I see you finally
found your mother's tear.
This isn't mine.
[SHIGURE] Oh...
then it must be your sister's.
Which means, at least,
you've found one of the
things you were looking for.
[MUKURO]
Interesting...
Tell me more.
[SHIGURE] Hiei came to me,
and asked for the Jagan Eye.
It was in order to help
him locate two things.
[MUKURO]
And they were...?
[SHIGURE] Number one: The Ice
World where his people lived.
And two: The stone
his mother had given him.
Now you see, I consider
the surgeries I perform
to be unique works of art,
poetry, really, if anything.
[SHIGURE] So all I ask
in return for my services,
as a modest fee, is an
ironic twist to finish it off.
In Hiei's case,
even if he found his sister,
he could never
confess who he was.
[MUKURO]
An ironic price, indeed.
But I will refund my fee
this one time
if you can defeat me.
That's very generous of you,
but I told you before...
I never had any intention of
telling her I was her brother.
Yes, but that
was before you met her.
[MUKURO]
Enough reminiscing.
This is a battle, and I
determine the stakes.
You will each be
fighting for your life.
[MUKURO]
Hiei.
You have the ability
to survive this.
But only if you reach
the strength you did
when fighting for
the pain of your friend.
Now you must
fight for your pain.
Bear yourself to me, and I will
help you find your answer.
[MUKURO]
Prepare yourselves!
[NARRATOR] Amidst haunting
memories of Hiei's dark origins,
a face from his past has
unexpectedly returned.
Is it coincidence, or the
mysterious workings of Mukuro?
In eerie telepathy,
Mukuro beckons Hiei
to dig deeper into
his subconscious.
But what are Mukuro's
true intentions?
[YUSUKE] I gotta say that this
has all been very educational,
and who said learning
couldn't be fun?
We're getting all kinds
of deeply personal things
about old short stack
that I'd never get from...
You know... talkin' to him.
And as much as I love watching
Hiei get his butt kicked,
I think I'm looking
forward to finding out
all about his past even more!
Oh, and Hiei's not
the only one wondering
what's underneath
Mukuro's bandages.
But we'll have to wait
'til the next episode
of Yu Yu Hakusho
to unravel that.