♪
[NARRATOR] In his last case,
Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
and his friend Kuwabara
stormed the stronghold
of Gonzou Tarukane,
and battled a horde
of demon mercenaries.
The greatest were the
strange Toguro Brothers,
whom Kuwabara narrowly
beat with a final boost
from Yusuke's Spirit Gun.
They have rescued the
Ice Apparition Yukina,
Hiei's sister.
Now the adventure continues.
[KUWABARA]
Yukina. Yukina wait!
I just don't get it.
Do you have to?
Yes, I must.
Clearly Ice Apparitions
are meant to live
in the World of Ice.
Thank you for everything
you've done. You're so brave.
[OKUBO] Something's
really come over him.
I bet he's changing his image!
I bet he saw a movie
and now he's acting it out.
No way. I say Kuwabara
got rejected by a girl!
Bull's-eye, Miyamoto!
Now wait! Kuwabara
was not rejected!
Well what else do you call
Yukina dumping out on him
and running back
to the Ice World?
It's a long distance
relationship! It's romantic!
[gang calls out to Kuwabara]
He really is down.
[BOTAN]
Yes.
Not every closed case
comes with a happy ending.
Guess that goes for Hiei, too.
Yes, I know.
I've heard he still
refuses to tell Yukina
that he is her brother.
That's right.
[strong winds]
There goes your
last chance, Hiei.
You really gonna let her
just walk off like this
without knowing the truth?
It's not important.
She and I have
different mothers.
We're only half-siblings.
There's really no
point in telling her.
Yeah but weren't
you looking for her?
I am a rogue and
a convicted criminal.
Even you have had
to come and capture me.
Do you think
she'd be happy to know
that her long-lost
brother is a felon?
[HIEI] It's best to
watch her from a distance.
So is that why you got that
fake eye put in? To see her?
Nonsense.
[BOTAN] Well, there's
plenty of good news, too!
You boys did kill the Toguro
Brothers and save Yukina!
And Hiei was kept
from killing Tarukane.
I would have hated
ordering you to arrest him.
Give me a break!
That would've sucked!
And that is precisely
why there was so much ado
in Spirit World about
letting Hiei find out.
He's considered a
very valuable asset now.
Now you see why we sent
Hiei with the videotape!
Just to keep him distracted!
Are all you people in charge
of Spirit World just stupid?
What if he'd looked at the
tape--ever think about that?
Maybe! But the fact of
the matter is, he didn't!
So HA!
[Botan laughs]
Enjoy your shopping!
[YUSUKE]
What?
[KEIKO] Yusuke!
Yeah, hey!
You're late!
[BOTAN] Here I am!
With another successful
case from my best project!
[KOENMA] Thank you,
Botan. You're priceless.
I must admit, I was about to
give you a couple of black eyes.
Seems like you're always putting
Yusuke up against people
he shouldn't be able to beat,
just to see what will happen!
[KOENMA] That's just a result of
your inexperience, Botan.
You underestimate
his true potential.
Why, I'd never
put him in a fight
I didn't know he could win!
That's incredible sir!
You knew all along??
You betcha!
Uh Koenma sir.
What should we do with
the black suit and eulogy
I wrote for Yusuke's funeral?
Well you know,
a good leader's always got
to take a few precautions!
Big liar!
Hey come on now,
everything turned out
good in the end, didn't it?!
Sir! About the Toguro
Brothers! It's unbelievable!!
What?
[RED OGRE]
Sorry sir,
we accidentally left the
tape running after the battle.
[KOENMA] So, what's your point?
[RED OGRE] Just watch!!
What?! What is this?!
They're supposed to be dead!!!
Be quiet, sir.
Excellent performance, Toguros.
You almost had me fooled.
We have excellent hearing.
Once we overheard the boy's plan
it was simple to play along.
Though I was afraid I
was going to kill them both
before I could fake
a believable loss.
I hope you don't mind
me letting the girl go.
I didn't see any good
reason for making her die.
[TOGURO 1]
Who knows,
maybe you'll want to profit
off her tears yourself some day.
That's fine, the girl is
of no consequence to me now,
not when I think
of all the money
our great plan
will be affording me.
We're so glad that
our client is pleased.
Now my brother and I, we have a
little favor to ask in return.
Please give us an opportunity
to fight with those boys again.
This time seriously.
But of course Toguro!
They will be two of the
most anticipated guests
the in the Dark
Martial Arts Competition.
I should have known all along.
Extorting Tarukane's fortune
was only half your plan.
You wanted to
see the competition.
You're very keen.
So tell me what you
thought of their powers.
That Yusuke Urameshi
boy is very intriguing.
He lacks the
fighting experience,
but could be a dangerous weapon.
The competition will
be held in two months,
so you'd better
make sure you're ready.
Oh... And take care of the mess
upstairs before you leave.
[Tarukane laughs insanely]
A street bum!
I'm a street bum!
What are we going to do Koenma?!
They're after Yusuke!!
Yes, and they will no doubt
entice him to fight
in this competition.
But you know how
those fights will be!!
Are you done yet? That clerk
thinks I'm stealing stuff.
One second! I've found
the perfect outfit!
Now we can grab a
bite to eat somewhere
and then go on to the park!
What?! Do we really
have to go there, too??
[KEIKO]
Uh-huh!
This is the part where
Yusuke makes his escape.
You going somewhere?
Who? Me?
Surely you wouldn't have
the nerve to run out on me
two dates in a row,
would you Yusuke?
No-uh-of course not!
Well, the park it is!
[CLERK] Have a
nice day, you two!
[POLICEMAN] Look, this is the
last warning! Please stand back!
That looked dangerous.
Yeah, better check it out.
Hey! Yusuke!
This area is now closed!
Disperse immediately!
That's weird.
What causes that?
Who are you?
[TOGURO 2]
Already forgotten?
Guess I don't make much
of an impression on people.
No freaking way!
Is something the matter, Yusuke?
You have the strangest
look of surprise on your face.
I'm sorry, when I kill people
I'm used to them staying dead.
I suggest you come
with me for a talk.
After all, you wouldn't want
something some thing bad
to happen to your
precious girlfriend.
What's goin' on?
Hey Keiko!
[TOGURO 2] Surely
you didn't think you had
actually beaten me.
Money decided that fight long
before you entered the ring.
But don't be angry.
You might soon have a chance
to fight me on fair terms
and not get so easily crushed.
Why don't you get
to the point, muscles.
I've got better things
to do with my time
then waste it with you.
You're afraid of me.
What? Amused is more like it!
There's no one
here to impress Yusuke,
and I can see your
entire body shaking.
The ability to fear your enemies
is one of your strengths.
It forces you to
reach your potential.
But you haven't
been scared enough.
You need some motivation,
and that's why I've come here,
to show you my true power!!
I only used twenty
percent of my strength
when I fought with
you and your friend.
So why don't I now show you-
[TOGURO 2] There.
That's sixty percent.
Understand this is the last
time I will save your life.
Two months from now,
a martial arts competition
will be taking place.
Oh, sounds like fun.
[TOGURO 2]
It's a dark tournament,
organized by greedy
human crime lords,
and drawing on the most
vile demons of the Spirit World.
Each criminal gathers
a team of five fighters,
and the teams
battle to the death.
Humans enter for
gambling and entertainment.
Demons fight for blood,
and the chance to win the prize.
You and Kuwabara are special
guests to this competition.
If you refuse,
I will immediately kill
you and everyone you know.
If you want to
survive these fights,
I suggest you get stronger.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Stupid, Yusuke!
You got so scared around him you
couldn't even friggin' move!
You idiot!
He's going to
kick your stupid ass!
What's going on?
[KUWABARA] We beat him!
I assume from your dismal faces
that you've been invited
to the competition as well.
On Urameshi's team, no doubt.
Demons who side with
humans will get no sympathy.
Sympathy has never been
a part of those fights.
As you know the
teams are made of five,
so you'll have to
recruit another fighter.
[TOGURO 2] For your sake I
hope you find someone useful.
What is our chance?
[HIEI]
Don't ask.
It's about time
you came back.
Please tell me you've
gotten a little better.
At this rate
you'll never survive.
This time I
won't go easy.
Do you realize the
danger you'll be in?
Yeah.
[KURAMA] Hiei
can't prepare you for the
viciousness of the fights.
Your weakness and his honor
make him go easy on you.
I will not.
Okay, come on! Toughen me up!
As you wish. Here goes!
Dammit!
Does it hurt, slacker?
Did you come all the way here
just to give me more
of your crap?!
It's different this time.
I promise I'll
push as hard as I can.
[NARRATOR] In this way, two
months of training passed.
[demon voices and laughter]
It's about time this
tournament day arrived!
Now we can kill without getting
those pursuers after us!
And imagine our power once
we've gotten that prize!
We're the ones who are
going to get the power!
Go home if you
don't want to die!
Obviously you haven't
seen us fight yet!
I think I smell
a human over there.
Maybe he's come
here to be our dinner!
Urameshi still
hasn't shown up yet!
What could that
dummy be doing now?
Hopefully he's finding
us a fifth fighter.
Why don't you worry
about yourself, Kuwabara.
Have you gotten any
better since our last fight?
You'll see for
yourself, shrimp-boy!
[KUWABARA THINKS] ]
If we win this competition,
I'm gonna get super famous.
Yeah. That way Yukina and
I can be together forever!
The ship is here, maties.
Now lets try to get on
board without any violence.
Uh, hey wait a minute sir!
Our team still
has some stragglers!
Then we'll have to
put a mark on their heads
and send out a hit man.
Standard rule of the tournament!
[YUSUKE] Now, now!
That's not necessary!
Sorry to keep you waiting guys.
You nearly gave me a
heart attack, Urameshi!
These forest hikes
really wipe me out!
[KUWABARA] Yeah, you look awful!
Oh wait, that's just you!
[HIEI]
Yusuke.
[DEMON 10] What is this?
I thought that they
were on the same team!
Gosh they're fast! I can
barely keep up with my eyes!
Damn Hiei, is this how you
say hello to people now?
I don't know where
you've been all this time,
but it seems you improved
your skills a little bit.
Improved a little bit!
Oh man! I'd say he
improved a lot of bits!!!
Don't be discouraged.
The fact that you
could follow their moves
shows you have
improved as well.
[HIEI] So, Yusuke.
I assume the
little one over there
is going to be the
fifth member of our team.
[KUWABARA] You mean
this little guy here?
He's even smaller than Hiei!
And, what's wrong with his face?
He looks like a
mummy or somethin!
Trust me. That one's gonna
be a lot of help to us.
I don't know--he barely
comes to my waist!
Forget him. Yusuke and I
are all that we'll require.
Enough of pesky distractions!
Let's all get on board!
[ship horn sounds]
[NARRATOR] And so,
the next adventure begins
for Spirit Detective Yusuke
Urameshi and his friends.
On a ship filled
with bizarre demons,
who all have a
craving for blood.
What is this strange new world
where the dark
tournament will begin,
and can Yusuke
even get there alive?
[YUSUKE] Hey guys, it's me,
and I'm about to get
some much needed shut-eye
while my teammates take care
of a little problem on deck!
Turns out that from
the whole shipload of fighters,
only one team is really
eligible for the tournament!
And that means an all out war
between everyone on board!
And in case you didn't know,
demons tend to
fight pretty dirty,
so it's going to be intense.
You don't want to miss
the next whip-lashing,
fist-flying madness,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪