[NARRATOR]
At the stronghold of Lord Yomi,
Kurama has been faced
with his dark past.
One thousand years ago,
he lived as a pitiless bandit,
with Yomi his second in command.
But when Yomi's reckless actions
threatened their success,
Kurama betrayed him,
hiring an assassin who
robbed Yomi of his sight.
Yomi has discovered the truth,
and now forces Kurama
to serve as his advisor.
Because if he doesn't, Yomi
will destroy his human family.
[thunder crashing]
They're still at it.
Any leads?
No. They seem
to talk of nothing.
It's how they speak--
between the lines.
Hardly the warrior's way.
I know one thing--
Lord Yomi certainly
values his opinions.
Apparently they
were friends ages ago.
He treats his words like gold...
And mine like copper.
A shame.
For your sake,
I hope you're thinking
during that silence.
I have devised a plan
to make you stronger, Yomi.
Oh?
There are six powerful Demons
that I encountered in
a previous tournament.
I'd like time to go recruit
and train them for you.
On the surface,
it seems you've acquired
the ability to make friends now.
But they're just tools
to further your goals.
You don't care about them.
Your care for
your family is tougher.
What do they give you?
[laughing]
Allow me to return home
and tend to family affairs,
and in exchange I will
bring you these fighters.
I'm sure you'll be
watching me, anyway.
Of course...
I have to protect...
...my investment.
All right, Suichi,
give me your test.
It's time for me to brag.
Hmm... So many mistakes.
Your equations
are off-balance...
I smell metaphor.
Could be.
So tell me,
what's the scoop?
Are you guys in another
struggle to save the world?
Which world?
Come on, you know what I mean.
Who's the bad guy
you're up against?
Each other.
Yusuke and Hiei are
already on opposing sides.
Say what?!
And which side are you on?
Neither.
Well obviously,
I'm not clear on the facts.
But if you need help,
I'll be right here.
[KURAMA] A noble offer,
but one I could not accept.
This is a Demon war,
where humans should not tread...
A fact that leads me down a
spiral of troubling thoughts.
[KURAMA] For years,
I have lived two lives:
Suichi Minamono,
the normal human teenager.
And Kurama, a fighter helping
to protect what is good.
But in recent times, a third
identity has reemerged...
Yoko, the bearer
of my dark past,
a figure who survives
on bloodthirst
and brutal instinct.
I cannot juggle them all.
But which one will I lose?
Hey, Suichi...
Where did you go?
[KURAMA]
Kokoda. Don't stray too far.
Oh hey, there you are.
You left. Is something wrong?
No, I'm just
staring at the moon.
[KURAMA]
My new step-brother, Kokoda,
the son of the man
my mother married...
In a short time,
he's come to depend on me.
[pager beeping]
Let me guess...
It's your girlfriend.
No, it's just my stepbrother.
Odd though, he should
be in school now.
Pranking from the
lunchroom payphone, no doubt.
Understood.
I'll be right there.
Hey bro, thanks for meeting me.
Come on, why are you
looking so serious?
I figured you'd
be happy to see me.
Not only should
you be in school now,
you've never
called me "bro" before.
Ah, relax, let's just
go somewhere private
where we can talk.
Trade some advice.
I mean, that is your specialty.
[KOKODA] Your friend
Hiei keeps getting stronger.
Mukuro's officially made
him second in command.
I was aware.
Urameshi is training
like a dog, too.
He'll be sure to take over
once Raizen dies.
Now do you really want
to fight your friends?
Say what you will,
but I won't let you
spoil this boy's lungs.
Now come, I want to see
who I'm talking to.
Now before you
try getting violent,
you should know the
nature of my power.
As long as I'm still
connected to my host's body,
if I die, then so will they.
A Parasite Demon...
Did Yomi put you up
to this cowardly act?
Is this his way
of watching over me,
so I'll be certain
to fulfill my duties?
[chuckling]
Actually, Chief Shachi
is who I'm working for.
He wants to make sure you
stay home and never come back.
And you think you
have control over me...
Since as you said, if I kill
you now, my brother dies.
But I have methods to make your
life so utterly meaningless
you'll crawl out on your own...
And then beg me for your death.
Okay, yes, I believe you!
Now don't do anything rash--
No need to kill me.
Forget Shachi!
[PARASITE DEMON]
Let's face it, I'm a parasite!
Jumping from one master's back
to another is what I do.
Truth is, I lied.
I'm playing two sides!
Yomi sent me here. You wouldn't
kill his aide, right?
And he wants to know about
those six fighters.
Yes... It's all in the works,
and though I don't
exactly trust Yomi,
I'll bring them to his side.
Oh? Is that wise?
Not that I'm
calling you unwise!
Look, yes!
Let's work something out!
I can do lots of things!
You need intelligence?
Protection?
You're lucky, Demon.
I do have a use for you.
Sure... They're here.
Has all of the
training been going well?
Yes, but I don't
think it's enough...
Hell, I doubt Yusuke's
strength is enough.
[KOENMA]
Yo.
[KURAMA]
Koenma? You're--
[KOENMA]
Back in my robes, yeah.
My dad decided this
Demon World business
was more important than
his grudge against me.
[KOENMA] Sometimes I think
he planned it all--
That even my disobedience
was part of it.
[KOENMA]
So what's your plan?
This could turn
into a war, you know.
If what you mean to ask
is why am I involved...
I want to make sure the result
isn't bad for Living World.
[KOENMA]
I believe that's part of it,
but I doubt you plan
to come out of this
as Demon World's new king.
And I know the
threat on your family,
but you could get around that.
There's more.
When Raizen dies,
the power balance
will fly out of control,
and the outcome
will be crucial.
[KOENMA]
Kurama.
I need you to tell me that your
motivations aren't personal.
I can't do that.
Ask Hiei or Yusuke
if it's personal.
I don't have to.
I know you're all fighting
for some inner need.
But the stakes
are too high for that.
If Mukuro takes over, we'll have
more chaos than ever before...
[KURAMA]
And if it's Yomi,
there could be a unity
that's just as dangerous.
[KOENMA]
Whatever does happen there,
how it's resolved will affect
all three worlds for centuries.
When you're making
your decisions,
just try to
keep that in mind.
'Bout time, piker.
Chu. In high spirits as always.
[CHU laughing]
Very funny, mate.
Why don't you
take a real hard look
at these muscles
I been working up.
Urameshi and I will have
one rage of blue this time...
I guarantee it.
Yeah. It'd be pretty awesome
to throw down with Yusuke.
We've fought against
all sorts of baddie biggies
being Shinobi and all,
so I see it as nothing new...
But it's to chance
the run with Yusuke
that brings me back 'round.
Well said, Jin.
Not only do we
believe in this cause,
we're anxious for good battle.
Since my embarrassing loss
against the old witch,
I have been craving a
reason to start fighting
and feel beautiful again.
Good.
Maybe you'll stop asking
me to call you pretty.
Not all of us have groupies
to pad our self-esteem, Shishi.
[SHISHI chuckles]
So true.
[KURAMA]
A slew of motivations,
but the result
should be the same.
We'll fight hard to protect
the balance of all three worlds.
[ALL]
Yeah!
Just six months left...
Easy now...
No goin' home...
...till I can toe
the line on the terp.
[CHU]
All right...
What's that you say?
Eighty creeps at once?
Yeah, that does sound tough.
[laughing]
Guess I'll have
to use these, then!
I'll start with
something simple...
[yelling]
What's that? Not enough?
Then how 'bout the kicker?
[RINKU]
Serpent Yo-Yo... Kick!
Yeah, I'll be signing
autographs after the show.
[GENKAI] That'd be great if you
were just fighting rocks, Rinku,
but you're going
into a warzone.
You all have to get tougher
if you plan to live.
[ALL]
Right!
Yes, Shachi?
My lord,
I feel obligated to speak.
I have dependable information
that Kurama doesn't
plan to return.
I know you
trust him, my lord,
but we have to ask ourselves--
What's best for this country?
Can we postpone
our plans any longer
in lieu of six fighters
that may not even exist?
[growls]
Military prudence, my lord.
Steady acquisitions--
That's how you've
carved out your power,
so why change that now?
We have to stay the course--
Continue what's
worked for centuries!
Not gamble it all on
the whims of an outsider!
Shachi...
Your devotion to our
nation's army is unrivaled.
There's no question about that.
The best compliment a
warrior can hope to receive.
But I need you to put
your devotion on hold.
Your army is of
no more interest to me.
[SHACHI]
Kurama...
You better pray
you don't come back.
Well, one hundred
and twenty thousand.
[gasps]
I never would
have believed it...
Six fighters for us,
all with energy levels
of a hundred and twenty
thousand or higher!
That can't be!
[YOUDA] You've said you
spent some time on them.
But these levels
are rare feats--
How did you get them
all so strong?
Just good nutrition
and the proper exercise.
Nothing special.
Funny.
Why don't you say the real
trainin' she put us through!
Yeah, like the four
weeks locked in that cave!
Or balancing on spikes.
Or bein' buried alive
with the snakes and things!
Hmph! Hag didn't let me
shower for months.
Excellent work.
You've done as promised.
And so...
In return, I'd like to make
you my new second in command,
if you'll accept it.
Sure.
But...
Lord Yomi,
should you be so rash?
We don't know if we
can trust these six.
Where their loyalties lie...
That is enough from you.
What have you done these
past five hundred years
to further my power, Shachi?
But... our army!
It is true, Shachi,
by the numbers
you are the second strongest
fighter we have on our side.
But in brains and leadership,
you are weak.
[SHACHI]
What do you know?!
You speak of the
army you've maintained,
but what good's it done?
Can you name one soldier
with energy levels
even close to a
hundred thousand?
[YOUDA] There is a
dark time ahead of us.
A great war for power,
where any edge we get
could mean the difference
between order and bowing
to Mukuro's chaos.
In his short time here,
Kurama has brought six fighters
stronger than your
entire army combined,
yet you can't even
give him praise?
Youda, your point is heard.
Now please, draw up the papers
to make this change
of power official.
What matters here is that
our path to unification
can live another day.
[growling]
[SHACHI]
You worm!
You scrawny, conniving worm!
[SHACHI] Let's see your
real qualifications.
[SHACHI]
Eight thousand?
That's it?
And Yomi wants to put this
piddling maggot in charge?
I have to save this country
from falling apart!
Shachi... No more hiding.
Let's settle this.
[KURAMA]
Be wise...
A blade can't undo
what has passed.
And that's what
your kind never gets...
Blades can undo anything.
What Youda said is correct.
Dark times approach.
I cannot waste effort
on your personal feelings.
I have acted solely
on what I think is right.
And my moves have been precise.
The only thing you can influence
now is the time of your death.
You're wrong again.
It's Shachi--
Are you getting this?
Of course, sir.
I hear you loud and clear.
[laughs]
Excellent.
I want you to kill that boy
you've commandeered.
[PARASITE DEMON] Sorry, sir,
but that I do not hear.
I do not serve you any longer.
[SHACHI]
What?!
[PARASITE DEMON]
Truth is, I haven't for months.
The information I've relayed
were lies to keep you busy.
Kurama is my master now.
You sniveling traitor!
After all those years
I protected you!
You should've known not to trust
a Parasite Demon's loyalty.
We've both played our cards
and my hand was stronger.
Now leave and let me
do what must be done.
Excellent work...
My new second in command.
I'll put your
head on a stick!
[SHACHI yelling]
[SHACHI]
Your power's nothing to mine!
You don't stand a chance
with that human stink on you!
[growling]
What's this?
[yelling]
Time to find a
new dummy to leech on.
[PARASITE DEMON laughing]
What a dream...
Your power... how?
Fool! You should
have known your enemy.
Welcome, Yoko.
It's high time you took
control of him... for good.
[NARRATOR]
In the stronghold of Lord Yomi,
Kurama has cemented
his rank as second in command.
But is his old ally correct?
In Kurama's war of identities,
will Yoko be the one
to take control?
[YUSUKE] Well, I hope
you enjoyed Kurama hour,
cause it's time to swing
that spotlight back on me.
You know I always thought it
sucked not having a dad around,
but maybe I was better off.
I never had frothing
teeth lunging at my throat.
Of course, Raizen's
not my dad, exactly.
He's my ancestor,
which has to make me wonder...
Who was my ancestral mom?
And why the hell
would she have a kid
with someone who
looked like that?
The answers are coming,
with the origin of me,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!