♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke
Urameshi used to be dead.
Thanks to his own selfless acts
and the love of his friends,
he's been given a second chance.
Returning to life
with special powers,
Yusuke becomes
a Spirit Detective,
and must track down three
supernatural criminals
who have each stolen
a powerful artifact.
His first target Gouki,
who can transform
into a Kyukonki,
a powerful,
soul-eating creature.
Can Yusuke survive this fight?
[YUSUKE] Come on, Yusuke, you
better think of something quick.
That soul you let go was my
dinner. And I'm very hungry.
[GOUKI] I'll just have
to eat you instead.
Oh, I've forgotten
how fragile humans are.
Don't let me hit
you too hard, now.
I mean I'd hate
to bruise the meat.
Suffer, but don't die.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I can't move.
He's going to eat me alive.
[BOTAN] Come on, everyone!
I've found a clearing!
We'll camp here for the night!
[BOTAN DISGUISING VOICE]
Let's not sleep.
I want to find that monster!
My pack of big dogs are hungry.
What? I hate big dogs.
[BOTAN DISGUISING VOICE]
No, let's rest.
I'm tired of carrying
all these weapons!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
That voice.
Sorry kid, you're not worth a
run-in with the local villagers,
so I'll have to let you live.
Now be smart and
stay away from me!
[BOTAN] Hurry up everybody!
I think I see someone!
[BOTAN]
He's right up there!
What happened to the forest?
I'm in my room. Don't tell me
that was all just crazy a dream.
Yusuke you're up.
Are you alright?
I think.
Mother!
You don't just wallop
an injured person!
You look like you've been
fighting with a wrestler!
You're going to
get yourself killed!
[Atsuko cries]
Don't do that mother, it's okay.
At least I think it is.
Who was that voice?
Oh come on, you know!
He-llo!
Wow Botan. You saved me?
Yes she did. Brought you back
home asleep in her arms.
She's very strong.
She-! But--! Can other
people see you now?
I told Koenma I'd
make a much better
assistant to the
Spirit Detective
if I had a human form,
and he agreed.
Makes sense, I guess.
[ATSUKO]
Yusuke--
You'll have to introduce me
to this lady properly soon!
And how am I supposed to that?
So how'd you find me? I didn't
even think I know where I was.
[Botan laughs]
Nothing too special--I just
used this compass to find Gouki.
[NARRATOR]
Demon Compass detective item
number two of seven.
Indicates the distance
and direction of an
already-identified demon.
This'll make finding
them a lot easier,
but I think my real problem
comes once they're in my face.
Gouki was stronger
than I thought.
The next two thieves
will be even stronger,
and there's another catch.
Koenma didn't tell you this,
but you only have one week.
Why does that not surprise me.
I should be
encouraging you, but--
I know. The odds aren't good.
Yo! Yusuke! We don't
have time for a pity-party!
If we don't have those three
artifacts back when
my father returns.
Well I'm not sure I can put
words to the devastation!
My dad's big on
acceptable losses.
He'll destroy whole cities!
Not to mention my
precious backside!
[MALE ANCHOR]
And now, continued coverage
on the spreading
epidemic in Grey Corner.
Grey Corner? That's not
very far from here at all.
Four children from
this quiet foresting town
have fallen comatose
in the last three hours.
Doctors are hesitant to pin
a cause to their conditions,
but say it is unlike any disease
they have encountered before.
Town officials are advising
families to stay inside.
Sounds like Gouki's
having his lunch.
In the past he's taken
souls much more slowly.
With the Orb of
Baast it's easier.
He can take all he wants.
You see children,
it's not so bad.
You can all play with
each other in my stomach!
[YUSUKE] The souls he eats. How
long until they're digested?
It's hard to say.
One day at the most.
[YUSUKE]
Fine.
What are going to do?
What can you do?
[YUSUKE] Simple. I'll just
rip open his stomach.
You're not even recovered yet!
There's a lotta' things that
I don't understand Botan,
but isn't it better for a person
to lose their life
than their soul?
They can't even become a ghost,
and I'll give up my body
before I let that happen!
Yusuke.
I haven't used my
Spirit Gun today.
This time I won't let him win.
[NARRATOR] Concentration Ring,
detective item three of seven.
Multiplies the wearer's
Spirit Energy severalfold.
I was supposed to save this item
for when your Spirit
Energy got much stronger.
It will give your Spirit
Gun a huge punch,
but afterwards you'll
be completely exhausted.
Only use it as a last resort.
You got it!
Yusuke, I made tea for
you and your friend!
Hello, Yusuke?
You dropped your ball-ball!
You're a sweet girl. You'll be
even sweeter in my stomach.
[Gouki laughs]
I'm starting
a little collection.
[YUSUKE]
Gouki!
I came all this way to see you.
Idiot! Didn't you listen
to what I told you yesterday.
Yeah, of course
I heard you! I'm just stupid.
[GOUKI]
You're becoming a pest.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Okay,
I just need to go for it.
[GOUKI] For a detective,
you don't know much.
A Kyukonki's skin is solid
as rock. You can't hurt me.
How about a big wooden stake?!
Don't you see it's pointless?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
All out of choices.
I have to use the Spirit Gun.
Trust me Yusuke,
use it as a last resort.
Even with the Concentration
Ring, your Spirit Gun
may not be strong
enough to pierce his skin.
And then you'll be
left without energy.
[YUSUKE] Okay, what if
I shoot him in the eye?
Then he'll be blind, right?
Wait, he's got two eyes!
[GOUKI]
You give me a bigger appetite.
There's something about
those screams of pain!
Hey! Who the hell is she?
Forget about her! She's nobody!
Yes. This way
I can eat you both.
Starting with my top offender.
It's about time.
I was waiting for you to
open up your big fat mouth.
The skin on you whatever--
monsters may be hard as a rock.
But I bet your insides aren't!
Monster, meet Spirit Gun!
Man.
Yusuke!
One, two, three, four, five.
You saved them all, Yusuke!
[VILLAGE MAN 1] Little girl!
Little girl!
Look! She's waking up!
[LITTLE GIRL]
Momma!
Nearly lost my head to
get that one artifact back.
I'm scared to think what
two more of 'em will take.
Hey Yusuke, can't you just admit
it'd be easier to
lean on my shoulder?
Right, can't you admit it'd
be embarrassing?
What's up?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
One of them is here.
If they try to fight me,
I'll be meat on a stick.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
There! It's Kurama!
[KURAMA THINKS] Don't worry.
I have no intention of fighting
you, nor do I intend to flee.
In fact I need
to ask you a favor.
Are you crazy?
Give me three days.
After that I'll gladly return
to you the Forlorn Hope.
[YUSUKE]
Ouch!! Okay!!
Gee, more alcohol and
I'd need a designated driver!
You know this could
be a trap, Yusuke.
It seems a little too easy.
It's no coincidence that he
asked for three more days.
By then, the moon
will be completely full,
and the powers of the Forlorn
Hope will reach their maximum.
When that happens,
the mirror will reflect
the strongest desire
of whoever looks into it,
and it is said that the
desire will be granted,
though the user must
give something in return.
Only a few people know
what that something is.
Getting our mirror
may be pointless
if his wish destroys the earth!
But it sounds like he can do
all that by himself, right?
Why would he go out
of his way to meet me?
That's a tough one.
I don't know. Something tells
me I should trust him, Botan.
What in the world
are you saying?
Let's not forget that
his dear old teammate
tried to rip
you into little bits!
When I was walking up, they were
having some sort of argument.
And I don't have a clue why,
but Kurama told the
other two he was leaving.
Sorry, I must withdraw
from this alliance.
Somethin' in his eyes.
He looked more sad than evil.
I wish I knew
more about this guy.
Yusuke, I've made
us some dinner!
Will you be eating with us
Botan? There's plenty of food!
Oh yes that'd
be lovely! Thank you!
Can't you knock, Mom?
We were in the middle of
an important conversation!
Hey what kind of
conversation can't
be held around your mother?
Well, uh--It's not
what you think, Mom!
What happened to Keiko?! I
thought she was your girlfriend!
I'm gonna see if I can
get more information
on the Forlorn
Hope from Koenma.
You go to your
meeting with Kurama.
And please be careful, okay?
Right, right I'll be
walking on eggshells.
Here we are, the hospital.
Good you came.
Hey there, it's been
such a long time
since you brought
a friend with you.
It's all right Mother.
You don't have to sit up!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Mother?
It's not so bad.
I'm feeling well today.
[KURAMA] Shall I peel
an apple for you?
[KURAMA'S MOM]
No. I'm not hungry.
Please eat, mother.
You'll never get
well without nutrition.
Yes of course.
It's just hard to remember
all these things, Suichi.
[KURAMA] Well try hard. I need
you to get well quickly.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Suichi?
I thought his name was Kurama!
Suichi is the name I've
taken in my human form.
That woman is
my mother, sort of.
My father passed away years ago.
For fifteen years
she has brought me up,
while I have deceived her.
Sorry. I'm not following.
My truest name
is Yoko. I was a fox.
A Spirit Fox, gaining
the powers of a demon
over the hundreds
of years that I lived.
In time I became bored,
and passed my hours learning the
art of breaking codes and seals.
Ancient treasures
were my favorite sport.
But fifteen years ago
I made a careless mistake,
and was badly injured
by a strong pursuer.
With the last energy I had,
I escaped to the living world
and became the child
of a proud human family,
knowing that if I could
withstand humanity
for ten years,
my spirit energy would
have time to safely recover.
Then, I would escape
without a trace.
I take it something went wrong.
My mother fell ill.
I know it might sound foolish
but I couldn't leave her.
Considering what
she had done for me.
That's when they appeared.
Hiei had somehow tracked
me down, needing my expertise.
And I remembered the
powers of the Forlorn Hope.
Did you know in some species
a child eats its mother?
Let me use the Forlorn Hope
to save the woman's life.
Then I'll accept my punishment.
But why would a monster
do that for a human?
I don't know.
Maybe because I'm guilty.
Maybe I feel like
I am one of those
mother-devouring creatures.
I've caused her great pains.
It's hard raising a child
who thinks you're inferior.
I feel I broke her spirit.
Like maybe,
in some way,
I caused her disease.
Why are you telling me all this?
Maybe I just needed
someone to know.
Besides I could tell that
you would trust me.
Suichi! It's your mother!
[DOCTOR] She's fallen into
what we call the critical stage.
To be perfectly honest,
your mother is about to die.
How long?
Probably tonight. We'll do
what we can. Suichi, I'm sorry.
I have no choice.
You'll use it tonight?
Is that what you mean?
I heard you had to
dish out something
to the Forlorn Hope
in order to make it work.
So do you know
what that something is?
Yes... life.
Life? What does that mean?
Just like it sounds.
The one who makes the wish at
the same time loses their life.
That's why it's called
the Forlorn Hope.
You should get a dictionary.
Don't you think Yusuke
needs to know that?!
Well it's not
like he's using it.
Forlorn Hope,
I ask you to wake from
your sleep and hear my plea.
Reflect my greatest desire,
so that you can make it true.
[FORLORN HOPE]
The happiness of this woman.
Is that what you desire?
It is.
Hey! Can't you hold on a second
so we can work things out?
I mean there's gotta be
some other way to do this!
[KURAMA]
No. There is not.
[FORLORN HOPE] To grant this
wish, you must give your life.
Is that what you desire?
If that will save my
mother's life, then yes, I do.
[FORLORN HOPE] Than
your desire shall be fulfilled.
[KURAMA THINKS]
For you, Mother.
[YUSUKE]
No!
[KURAMA]
What are you doing?
Hey mirror-guy, can you hear me?
I want you to take
my life instead!
That way Kurama can live
and he can still get
his wish, isn't that right?
This doesn't make
sense! It's my wish!
Yeah? Well it doesn't make
sense rescuing your mom
so she can spend her whole life
mourning the death of her son!
I've seen that once before, and
I don't want to see it again!
[FORLORN HOPE]
Your desire shall be fulfilled.
Hold on, Yusuke!!
I'm still alive! But what
about my mother?!
Yusuke?
Yusuke, please!!
Hey! Awesome! I'm still alive!
You know, come to think of it,
that didn't make a whole
lotta' sense what I just did.
The point was to stop
the whole sad mom thing,
but my mom would have been sad.
Stupid.
But hey, I did get the
Forlorn Hope back!
[FORLORN HOPE]
In honor of your noble deed,
I fulfilled the desire
without taking life.
Suichi it's just a miracle!
Not only is she out
of the critical stage,
it seems she'll make
a full recovery.
Her will to survive
is an amazing thing.
That's all I can say!
[KURAMA's MOM]
Suichi.
Yes Mother.
The Spirit Detective
strikes again!
That's right! I've only got
one more artifact to go!
To think I doubted the Great
Yusuke. What was I thinking?
Nah-- Great Urameshi
sounds better!
Oh. My mistake!
I don't really see why
they're celebrating.
The last artifact will be
ten times harder to get back.
Hiei has the Shadow Sword,
and he's no ordinary demon.
Such children.
[YUSUKE]
Hey guys, it's me!
I'm about to go face
to face against Hiei,
or should I say eye to eye
to-eye? Whoa, that's weird.
This demon's got serious powers,
and if I don't act quick he'll
turn Keiko into a monster.
But how do I stop a guy
who's as fast as lightning
and can look in
three directions!
I do have a strong
new ally though,
so all hope's not lost.
You'll be dying to see me
wiggle my way out of this one!
On the next Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪