♪
[NARRATOR] In the
opening moments of the
Dark Tournament's final fight,
Yusuke and Toguro
each held back,
testing one another's strength.
After Toguro destroyed the ring
in favor of a larger battle,
Yusuke made the first
significant strike,
unveiling the power
Genkai had bequeathed to him
with a super-
charged Spirit Gun.
Toguro was sent flying
out of the stadium,
and it was hoped
the fight was over
until he returned, unscathed!
Is that all you've got for me?
I expected more from Genkai.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Great.
He can dice me up with nothing
but the force
of his energy.
And I couldn't even lay
so much as a scratch on him
with my Spirit Gun!
And I thought that you might
actually be the one, Urameshi.
If you had passed my test,
I was ready to go
to full power for you.
But there is absolutely
no need for you
to worry about that now.
My total power would
be wasted on you.
[crowd yelling]
He's not at his
full power?
I wasn't aware that anybody
could get any fuller than that.
Do you think there's
hope left for him?
Not really.
If he's that much
mightier than our boy,
what's that say about
us nongs who lost a bout
with Urameshi earlier on?
Face it guys. You're just a
bunch of lame wad losers.
Nice one Rinku.
And you? You lost to Kurama
and Kurama lost to a dead guy.
How's that for being lame?
[KOTO]
Right about now,
Urameshi's gotta be
thinking to himself:
I don't stand the
tiniest little chance!
I mean face it, if his
enhanced Spirit Gun
can't take Toguro down,
what else has he got?
Hey! Whose side are you supposed
to be on these days anyway?
I just call it
as I see it.
But you're not
seeing the big picture!
Look outside of the box
and inside yourself to see
not what is but what
might possibly be!
For all you know Yusuke
has some giant master plan!
A big plan?!
You know that for a fact?!
Er, um, no, but...
he could have one.
If you don't have anything
smart to say, zip it.
[BLUE OGRE]
Why do I always get myself
into these abusive
relationships?
Guess play-period's over?
Oh well, it was fun.
What?
Well, for some
inexplicable reason,
Yusuke has ripped off his left
wrist band to reveal a...
Uh, it's a glowing,
gold, bracelet!
And might I say, it takes
a pretty tough man
to wear jewelry in public.
Especially at a martial
arts tournament.
Uh, Botan? Do you have
any idea what that is,
and is it normal?
I should have expected,
Spirit Cuffs from Genkai.
I gotta say, that's a
pretty sissy fashion statement.
Even for Urameshi, man.
Why would he fight Toguro
using such a handicap?
I hardly understand.
Easy. It's because
he is a cocky fool.
[KOENMA] Yes he must have
inherited it from Genkai.
The Spirit Cuffs that is.
Uh, will somebody please tell
me what the heck is going on?
[YUSUKE]
Genkai, is it time yet?
[GENKAI] One more thing
before I give you your test.
Give me your hands.
I have to prepare your body.
[YUSUKE] This isn't
another trick, is it?
Hold still
and try not to cry.
[GENKAI]
Non omnia moriar.
Perfer et obdura dolor
hic tibi proderit olim!
I don't know what
you're tryin' to pull,
but I'm not into
this kinky stuff!
And you're
way too old!
In your dreams,
you big baby.
I'm doing this for
your own damn good.
These are Spirit Cuffs
and they'll save your life.
Once again, you can
thank me later.
Gee, why wait?
Thanks for being
a cruel, heartless,
domineering old bitch!
All your muscles won't
break you free of this.
[GENKAI] Your physical strength
tops out at only so much,
but your Spirit Power can
reach limitless heights
with proper training.
Ah, not this
speech again!
[GENKAI] Shut up. You must
jointly use the energy of
the spirit and the body,
with each feeding the other,
to overcome this obstacle
and move your little rear.
Alright, already.
You had me at shut up.
Okay.
I passed that test
with flying colors,
now get this crap off me!
You will keep that
crap on you at all times!
That means you are to
remain at full Spirit Power
and full physical strength
twenty-four hours a day,
seven days a week if you
want to so much as take a step
or even pick your nose.
[GENKAI] Think of it
as strapping weights
to your Spirit Energy,
the longer they stay on you,
the stronger you will grow.
Now, I'm gonna give
you a safety word.
[GENKAI] It'll unlock the spell
and release you from the cuffs,
I trust you'll know when
it's time to use it, Yusuke.
Now's a pretty good
time, right Genkai?
Avitus!
Just feel that!
His energy's outta control!
There's no way Urameshi
can lose this now!
Oh my goodness!
Urameshi's strength is
making me feel faint!
Who knew he had a surprise
like this planned
in the back of his head??
I knew it, yes,
I knew it all along!
His power
is phenomenal.
Agreed so I'd say!
When your wind
looks like a phoenix
you know that you
got something big!
He keeps
getting' stronger!
I can't imagine what it'd be
like fightin' the bloke now!
It'd probably be a
lot like last time,
just twenty times
more painful!
I've never felt such intense
Spirit Energy in all my life.
Genkai truly came
through for us this time.
This match is Yusuke's
for the taking!
Really you think?
Yeah as long as Toguro doesn't
ditch any chains of his own.
Are you really so
arrogant Urameshi
that you thought you
could actually beat me
while wearing
those Spirit Cuffs?
Well, yeah, sorta.
In hindsight I may
have been a bit cocky.
[TOGURO 2] You've
wasted enough of my
time by underestimating me.
Fortunately this
will be the last time
you ever make that mistake.
Now we see...
Where did he go?
Toguro's knocked down!
He's gotta be
feeling that one!
This is a very
different fighter.
I've never seen Yusuke
fight so intensely before.
You said it!
He's like a machine!
But why?
Don't stop now!
Just when we were
starting to get
into some hardcore pummeling,
Yusuke got spooked
and backed off
like he was afraid of
Toguro's unresponsive body!
[YUSUKE THINKS] It's that
damn look in his eyes.
Like he was still
the one in control.
What's with Toguro's
muscles all of a sudden?
They've deflated like a
beach ball on the rocks.
Lots a crazy things I seen
but this one takes the prize.
Urameshi's attack
was powerful.
Perhaps this is what happens
when Toguro is injured.
I am afraid that
a ferocious wolf
is laying in wait underneath
that placid sheep's façade.
I know.
It's written on his face.
At last Yusuke,
you've done as I've asked.
I've waited a long
time for this moment.
Now destiny has
rewarded my patience.
Wow! The Earth is quaking!
Now this is shaping up
to be the kind of fight
where some legends are made
and others are painfully broken!
Toguro's power up is
like a solar eclipse,
you should not
stare directly at it,
no matter how beautiful it is.
Oh no! I hope Poo's
barrier can hold!
It's hard to tell if Toguro's
lost control of his power,
or if he's attacking
the crowd on purpose.
Hey! What the?
Who the heck is
turning off the lights?
Be careful, Yusuke.
This is it.
[KOENMA] Not lookin'
forward to this.
[KUWABARA] I can't even
see myself think!!
[Toguro 2 grunts]
[Toguro 2 grunts and
cries out as he powers up]
[KURAMA THINKS] The structure
of those muscles, genius.
[HIEI THINKS] I can't believe
that body was really once human.
[muscles crackling]
Urameshi! This is your chance!
Finish him off.
Do it while you can, before
he reaches full power!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I, I can't move.
It's not fear that's holding
me back though, it's curiosity.
I just need to
know what he's got.
So that's full power.
It's more than I hoped.
Are we certain he
doesn't get stronger?
Poor Yusuke. He doesn't
stand a chance.
Watch it Shizuru!
How can you say something like
that? Yusuke will win this one!
You'll see. He'll win it,
just like all the other times.
[KOTO] Well, after much
anticipation and buildup
Toguro has finally
revealed his full power.
And may I just be the first to
say that I'm not the least bit
disappointed in the
grand unveiling.
You have got to see this muscle-
bound man to believe him.
Where did
everybody go?
[KUWABARA] You know, I was
kickin' myself pretty hard
before for not bein' able
to feel this guy's power.
But now I realize that if
I actually had felt it
my head would've exploded
all over the darn place!
[KOENMA THINKS] Well,
you win some and you lose some.
I guess that's what
makes it gambling.
It's too bad, really, that
Yusuke didn't have enough time
with Genkai before she
gave him her power.
Just a few more years...
I... missed somethin'.
It looks like Urameshi had
a couple too many.
[YUSUKE THINKS] What the hell?
One second I'm standing,
and the next...
His thumb! He made a bullet and
shot it at me with his thumb!
Did you like that one?
Unlike your Spirit Gun I
have an infinite supply.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Man, this is rough,
I hope he gets bored soon.
[KOTO] It looks to
me like Toguro's
done with target practice,
and Urameshi's just plain done.
[Yusuke cries out]
Take this!
[TOGURO 2] I have more power
in my thumb than you have
in your entire body.
We'll see. I've got a
strong finger myself.
Now hit me with
everything that you have.
You have no idea which
shot will be your last.
Spirit Gun!
[Toguro 2 laughs]
Whoa! Not a
dent on him.
He is a true monster.
I consider myself a
good judge of human kind.
Having formerly
been one I can say
there's something
missing in your eyes.
And that
something is fear.
It used to be one
of your strengths.
Without fear, you'll never
grow stronger as a fighter.
I know I've told
you that before.
[NARRATOR] Toguro's full power
is even more astounding
than anyone had imagined.
Even without his Spirit Cuffs
restricting his abilities,
Yusuke's attacks have
no impact on his opponent.
With the end drawing closer,
does he have any hope
of stepping out
from Toguro's shadow?
[BOTAN] Well hello everyone.
It's been quite an
intense fight out there,
and from now on it's only
going to get heavier!
It appears that even more lives
will be sacrificed when Toguro
goes on a soul-sucking rampage.
And if you think that you've
seen Yusuke get angry before,
just wait til you
see how he responds
when Toguro takes the
life of one of his friends!
Oh, wait. Pardon.
What was that?
I hope it doesn't mean me!
I guess we'll all have
to find out together
on the next Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪