♪
[NARRATOR] Thanks to
corruption at the highest levels
of the tournament's
organization,
Team Urameshi's one chance
of defeating Team Masho
lay with
the injured Kuwabara.
Drained of his spirit energy,
only the sight of his
one true love, Yukina,
could bring back his spirit
sword in time to defeat Risho
and send his team
to the next round.
But even now as they take a
break from the tournament,
the boys can't resist looking
for a little more action.
Hello, after an intense
round of verbal attacks
between Keiko and Yusuke,
there seems to be a
brief moment of peace.
[BOTAN] Let's see how this
exciting battle will resolve.
I know you need to fight.
But...
If you die I swear
I'll kill you. Bang!
[YUSUKE]
Deal.
That.. was.. close!
I swear, I won't get beat.
Though, she should
fight for our team.
Hey!
[YUSUKE] Don't think I didn't
hear that, nosey girl.
If it's huggy-kissy
stuff you want,
go home and
watch your soaps.
Meow, meow.
Have any idea what curiosity
does for cats, Botan?
Oh hello Yusuke,
I had absolutely no earthly
clue I might find you here.
Right, right. You were
looking for a place to pee.
Actually Yusuke I've got news!
You're about to
have a hatched egg!
A hatched egg?
Now wait a second,
since when did you
start raising chickens.
Oh my good...
Don't tell me you've
forgotten about it again!
Okay, I won't?
Koenma just finished telling
you about the golden egg
that's got your
Spirit Beast inside!
Do you really need
a recap twice a day
to remind you of
what's going on?!
Oh yeah I remember
pacifier-breath
saying something like that
about something like that.
Watch what you say Yusuke
because Koenma should
be arriving any minute
with your golden egg.
[KOENMA] Arriving where? I
can't be in two places at once.
[YUSUKE] Damn it,
don't do that!!
We're still not used to
you being at eye level.
[KOENMA] And this
pacifier-breath
is still not used
to you getting dumber
every single time he sees you.
Hold on, are you sure that's
the egg I had last time?
Yes, grown quite a bit over
the year. It's ready to pop.
So, how do we know the monster
in here's gonna be friendly?
[KOENMA] We don't know
anything, not until it opens.
[KOENMA] That's all
you in there.
From the moment
we first met,
your Spirit Beast
has been feeding off
the energy of your soul.
Everything you've done
since that day, good or bad,
has shaped the
nature of that beast.
And what if I haven't
always been completely nice?
[KOENMA] It's
the overall picture.
The beast will reflect
who you really are inside,
not the brat routine
you put on to be cool.
And if your true heart
has been selfish and evil,
so will be the
beast, and well,
you remember the part
about head-devouring.
So I'll be a ghost again like
when this whole thing started?
No Yusuke, when a
Spirit Beast consumes you,
it takes the whole
package, body and soul.
You won't be a ghost, and
you won't go to Spirit World.
You will be absolutely
nothing at all.
Where's the egg?
It's not here!
It could
be anywhere!
[Botan laughs]
Poo!
Oh Look! Koenma,
It's Yusuke's innerself!
[KOENMA] Oh no, I'm
ever so terribly frightened!
Please don't hurt
me mean Mr. Monster!
When I picture Yusuke's
disposition, I see scales,
and beady eyes, but cute
and furry's another way to go.
You jerk! Just because
your egg hatched
doesn't mean you
can be a punk again.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Stupid Spirit Beast.
They probably rigged
this whole thing
just to hold
something over my head.
Anyway, it can't look as funny
as these two dumbasses think.
[laughing]
I never knew how
adorable you were inside!
You're as pure as a little girl.
How adorable was that?
Oh Yukina won't you please heal
Kuwabara's itty-bitty boo-boo
and make it feel all better?
Give it a rest for
one minute lover boy.
[KEIKO] There you are,
cutie. Come to Keiko.
As if he couldn't
get any more girly!
So did you hear
that the semi-finals
aren't until the
day after tomorrow?
Yeah, I heard all right.
The committee made us
fight two rounds in a row
just cause they
wanted us wiped out.
They're just like
everyone else in charge.
[POO]
Poo!
You know what,
when you're next to each other
you two kind of look alike.
He's even got
your hair.
I'll say the little
booger's got my hair.
He's got it right
between his retarded claws
and he ain't letting go.
He better not leave
me any Spirit surprises.
[POO]
Poo!
Ooo. How'd it get so late?
Time flies when you're
mocking Yusuke mercilessly.
[ALL]
Let's go.
That's right.
Get lost for all I care!
[BOTAN]
Goodnight, Yusuke.
Oh and don't forget there's
an early match tomorrow
that determines
the next team we fight
and we want a sneak preview
of what we're up against.
So try not to sleep
for a week this time.
[KUWABARA]
Later, Urameshi.
[POO]
Pooooo!
I can kill you all
with my finger you know!
Don't run! I'll show
you cute and friendly.
I'll show you cute and friendly
'till you're black
and blue all over.
[KOTO] Good morning blood
lusters and blood lusterettes!
The battle between Team Uraotogi
and Team Gokkai Six starts now!
Here comes the Ax Fist!
That was amazing!
If you blinked you
missed quite a match!
In less than two minutes,
Team Uraotogi crushed
Team Gokkai Six,
shutting them out completely!
That's gotta be embarrassing!
What a show!
I'd hate to be on the team
that has to fight them next!
[old man laugh]
[ONJI] Even though I think we're
officially wrapped up here,
how would you boys
like a friendly chance
to play with us just for kicks?
Nah, I think
we're good thanks.
Yeah, you guys
probably want your rest.
If your team wants to win
the semi-finals and all.
Semi-finals?
We are going to be
the grand champions!
'Till then, everyone
else is just practice.
Everyone else.
Just wait for your turn.
What an arrogant fool.
[KUWABARA] Well, well,
well. Look who it is!
Hello.
Guess you guys have
the same idea we do
about scoping out our
competition for the semi-finals.
Had the same idea.
The fight's over.
What?!
[KOTO] And so, the first
match of the semi-finals
will see Team Urameshi facing
off against the unbeatable,
indefeatable, beyond
believable Team Uraotogi!
That is unbelievable.
I mean I can't believe
we missed the entire fight
just because I took a
couple of extra minutes
to brush my teeth.
It was an impressive
sight to behold.
Though I'm sure your
minty fresh breath
was well worth the delay.
What is that
ridiculous appendage
growing out of
your head all about?
It's just a puberty thing okay?
So Kurama. How's the
wound treatin' you?
It will be fine. I will
be fighting again tomorrow.
Seems it's not as bad
as you made us think.
Compared with your energy
loss, no it seems it's not.
Hey! I've got an idea, you guys!
Ask Yukina to use
her healing power!
She's amazing! As
soon as she touches you,
you'll feel better than
you ever have before!
She's pretty, too!
She's actually partly here
to look for her
long-lost estranged brother...
I'm gonna help her look for him
just as soon as we
win this tournament.
Yukina's brother. Yes,
sounds like a noble cause.
We should assist
her too, Hiei.
Yeah you could
even lend an eye!
Will you shut up?
Wait, huh? What's
going on here?
Am I missing something, what
aren't you guys telling me,
uh, what do you keep
laughing about anyway?
Just what Hiei said
about this ridiculous
thing on my head--right?
I heard him say that.
It wasn't that funny.
Hello! What's your problem?
[CROWD] It's Team Toguro!
[CROWD CHANTS]
Toguro! Toguro!...
I think he pointed at the human!
Just can't wait
to kill him, can he?
[TOGORO 2 THINKS] You and me...
A fight to the death.
Soon enough, Urameshi.
[MASKED FIGHTER]
At least your act is tough.
Hey! I work
hard at it!
No! This can't be.
How could I have
missed it for so long?
They must've shielded their
energy from detection.
I feel so, light-headed.
We can't compete
with these guys, Urameshi.
What are we gonna do?
[KOTO] Sorry for
the delay folks.
We weren't prepared for the
last fight to end so-- abruptly.
But now, get ready to watch as
Team Gorenja takes on Team Kido.
We can only hope
it'll be half as brutal
and twice as long
as the last match.
[KOTO] Momorenja's a lot
tougher than she looks,
if you can even
keep an eye on her.
Oh! That's the most blood
I've seen in quite some time!
I hope you didn't miss that
one, people! It was crucial!
I'm just saying it's not
that big a deal, Kuwabara,
and us bitching about
it isn't gonna help.
You probably feel
their powers now
'cause your
senses got better.
Come on, Toguro's the guy
who made us come to
this stupid tournament.
None of us thought it
was gonna to be a joy ride,
but we can beat him okay!
[SHISHIWAKAMARU]
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Don't you think you all are
forgetting about somebody?
No one of real importance.
Huh? Who's that?
My guess would be
freak show rejects.
I am Kuro Momotaro.
Makintaro.
Uraurashima.
Shishiwakamaru.
And you can just call me Onji.
If you guys are looking
for us to go easy on you,
you're wasting your, and more
importantly, our, precious time.
No, it's the exact opposite.
We want a good fight.
We will be famous,
but we're going to need more
than two minutes of exposure
for us to get that way.
Arrogant little prick,
don't you think?
You can say that again!
If you want to be famous why
don't you start a boy band--
you got the look down.
We'll get ugly soon enough,
Urameshi! Just you wait!
[laughing]
Those guys aren't
even worth two minutes.
Their powers are nothing
compared to what
Toguro was giving off!
We could always
wear blindfolds.
At least that way
would be amusing.
[MASKED FIGHTER] Pride is
for the weak, Yusuke!
[YUSUKE]
Leave me alone!
Stop looking at me like
that, you masked freak!
If you've got something
to say, say it!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
It's quite simple, really.
If the leader of
Team Toguro is...
Toguro.
Then the leader of Team Urameshi
should be Yusuke Urameshi.
The question I'm posing is,
do you have what it takes to
beat Toguro all by yourself.
Yusuke Urameshi?
[KUWABARA] Guys, guys. Break it
up. Let's just try to get along.
Kuwabara's right can we please
talk this through peacefully?
[YUSUKE] You think you should
lead this team instead of me?
[MASKED FIGHTER]
If necessary. Follow me.
[YUSUKE] Yeah, let's
take this outside!
Yusuke don't be stupid!
[HIEI]
Let them be.
They will have to
settle this themselves.
Yeah. That's what
we're afraid might happen.
Those two are so
strong and so mad
they'll probably settle
this all the way to the death,
and that's no good.
It's a shame but there's
nothing we can do.
And even if there were
anything that could be done.
It's hardly our place to
interfere with their affairs.
How can you possibly
say those things?
Can't you see they could
tear this team apart?!
And none of you can even
be bothered enough to care!
Where the hell
are you going?
So that's it?
Listen, I understand
if you're getting second
thoughts about punching me,
but that doesn't mean we have
to go on a stupid nature walk.
[MASKED FIGHTER] I'm not going
to fight you, Yusuke Urameshi.
Then why are we hiking?
Just shut up
and follow me!
Dimwit!
Okay, now I'm interested.
[KOTO] Team Gorenja
are proving themselves
a force to be reckoned with,
as Akarenja refuses to stay
on the ground long enough
for her opponent
to take a healthy shot!
[KOENMA]
I'm bored, Ogre.
I just don't have the
attention span for this.
She just keeps jumping.
Koenma we've got problems!
Yusuke and The Masked Fighter
are about to face off and
tear each other limb from limb!
[KOENMA] Yusuke and The
Masked Fighter you say?
It seems the time has come
for the Spirit
Detective's final test.
Final test?
What's all of
that about, sir?
[SAKYO] Is something wrong?
You're missing the match.
Neither one of those teams
is worthy of me fighting them.
Let alone watching.
[SAKYO] I admire
your elitism.
Word has it
that there's been quite a
bit of unpleasant commotion
over at camp
Team Urameshi.
Then the Masked Fighter
has set into motion
the final stage of
her plan for Urameshi.
It is about time.
An absolutely lovely
beheading, Kirenja!
That means your team is
moving on to the semi-finals!
[MASKED FIGHTER] I know, I know.
Don't start with me, slacker.
I should have told
you from the start,
but I had my reasons for keeping
my true identity a secret
at the tournament
for as long as possible.
But now is the moment
I've been waiting for.
Then it really was you,
Genkai! I knew it! But wait.
Who was that beautiful young--
[GENKAI] Watch it, kid.
I can still destroy you.
But seriously,
where's your stand in?
You're looking
at her, boy.
Okay I don't understand.
How's that work?
There's no way you
are gonna get this
without a visual demonstration.
See that over there!
[YUSUKE] A big rock? Yeah,
that explains everything.
[GENKAI] Just shoot it with
your Spirit Gun at full power.
But you still haven't
answered my question yet.
Don't make me slap
you upside the head!
Just shoot the damn thing.
Oh all right.
Hag.
I still don't see
how this matters.
Spirit Gun!
Totaled! Are you
happy now, grandma?
I can never tell what's worse.
Your aim or your pride in it.
Give me a break! That was
the perfectest shot there is!
Why don't you show this
young whippersnapper
how it was done
in the olden days?
Gladly, you
patronizing jackass.
What are you doing?
That boulder is just a little
bit bigger than the one I shot.
Pay attention, slacker.
You've been brought to this
Tournament for one reason.
Toguro knows what
you're capable of.
It's time that you
understood it too.
That was incredible!
My Spirit Gun can't
even compare to yours.
[GENKAI] When you channel your
Spirit Power to its maximum,
the body's cells shift and
you take on the form you had
at the moment you were
most powerful in your life.
In my case, I was a
swinging twenty-something.
Yours is right now,
you just don't know it yet.
That's why
we've come here.
It's time for you
to take the final test
and reach your graduation.
Why do I get the idea that
this isn't gonna be easy?
[NARRATOR] Unmasked at last,
the psychic Genkai
prepares to mentor Yusuke
in one final lesson,
more difficult
than any he has faced.
What is this test,
and can Yusuke pass it in time
to defeat the dreaded Toguro?
[YUSUKE] Hey guys. So Genkai
was The Masked Fighter
--anybody see that coming?
I'm not gonna be the one
that says I told you so,
but I will say I
knew it all along.
Now, you'd think nearly a year
of training would be enough,
but oh no, this last test
is supposed be unlike
anything I've had before,
and with a slave
driving fossil like Genkai,
that says a lot.
Rainy caves, buried in blood,
screaming in pain,
blacking out--
and that's just the start!
You'll want to see
where this one goes, guys,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪