♪
[NARRATOR] Earlier today,
Yusuke Urameshi was killed in
a car accident after
saving a boy's life.
Now he's become a ghost,
and was greeted by
the sprightly Botan,
who identified herself
as the Grim Reaper!
In life Yusuke was a
hopeless delinquent,
and told Botan he
was glad to be dead.
But after going
to his wake
and seeing the despair
of his loved ones,
Yusuke agreed to
undergo an ordeal
that will perhaps
restore his life.
So can you explain to me again
about this place we're going to?
The Spirit World!
Right, but what is that?
It's the realm where people
outside of the
living world exist,
including the person who
will explain your ordeal.
And who is this
stupid mystery man?
If someone wants
to say something,
they should come to me!
His name is King Yama.
What?! Are we dealing
with royalty now?
That's right Yusuke and you
had better not be foul-mouthed
or impolite around him
like you usually are.
He calls the shots
and he can send you to oblivion
forever if he wants to!
Whoa! Now wait a second!
I think we should discuss this!
[YUSUKE] Wow, everything's so
big! Is that the River Styx?
[BOTAN]
Well of course!
And just up ahead is the
Gateway of Decision.
[Yusuke cries out]
Oh man! What a pad!
Botan here. I've got
a new arrival with me.
[doors creak open]
[YUSUKE] This place
looks like a giant throat!
Are you sure it's safe?
Don't whine.
Hey!
[YUSUKE THINKS] I wonder what
this King Yama looks like?
If he's running an
operation this big,
he must be gigantic,
and ugly, too.
Now how can I fight
a guy like that?
Ah, of course, I'll punch
him square in the nose.
And then while he's stunned,
go for his eyeballs.
I'll squeeze him till
he's begging for mercy!
See how he likes taking orders!
What in the world
are you muttering about?
[YUSUKE]
Me? Oh, nothing.
Botan again.
Will you let him know I've
got Yusuke Urameshi here?
[INTERCOM VOICE]
We're opening the gate.
I need information on
Mr. Gen in two minutes!
Mr. Pitts is ahead of schedule!
[busy voices]
Just give me the names of
the people in the accident
in alphabetical order.
What, is this like the dead
people stock exchange?
Sir, I've brought you the
boy you requested to see.
[TUSUKE THINKS] Where is he?
Is he invisible?!
[KOENMA] I'm right here.
Look down.
Yes, there you go.
This is the guy
that's in charge?!
Welcome, how do
you like my castle?
This is Yusuke Urameshi and
he's honored to meet you.
Hey! Are you trying
to make me look stupid?
Tell him how honored you are!
That's a good one Botan,
but let's be serious okay?
Why would I lie about
something like this, you moron!
Why would the Spirit World
by run by a toddler?
Don't point your finger at him!
[Yusuke laughs]
[YUSUKE] And to think I was
scared of the mighty King Yama!
[KOENMA] Well to be more
exact I am the mighty Koenma
and I'm the son of King Yama.
Even though
I appear to be a child
I've been around over 50
times longer than you have.
So watch your mouth
when you speak to me.
So it takes hundreds of
years to move past a diaper?
Can't you show
an ounce of decency!
Actually I'm proud to say
that in addition to knowing
the greatest secrets
of the Universe
I'm also quite potty-trained.
Now let's skip to the
business, shall we?
Yusuke Urameshi, I present you,
your ordeal!
My ordeal is a
golden chicken egg?
Your ordeal will be
what is inside of it,
and I assure you it
won't be a chicken.
Hatch this egg,
and face what comes out.
So what's the trick?
Do I do something to hatch it?
No, no. Not at all. You only
have to keep it with you.
This is a Spirit Beast,
and it feeds off the energy
emitted from your soul.
This will be a true and constant
test of your character.
The things you do and feel will
change the monster inside,
for better or for worse.
If, as would be expected
from your files,
your spirit is wicked and cruel,
then the beast that hatches
will be the same way.
It will devour you,
and you'll be lost forever.
[KOENMA]
This, as you might imagine,
is a very painful experience.
[KOENMA] However, if the energy
you emit is good and true,
then so will
be the Spirit Beast.
It will take care of you,
and guide you back
into your living body.
[KOENMA]
Of course if it sounds too risky
you can opt out
and remain as a ghost.
The choice,
Yusuke Urameshi, is yours.
[YUSUKE] I can't
believe I did that.
Yusuke I'm afraid you
don't have time for reflection.
Koenma said that
until the ordeal's finished
he'd keep a pulse in your body,
but that won't help if
it's cremated at the funeral.
I forgot!
Can't very well be alive
if you don't have a
body to live in, now can you?
Oh give me a break!
Then what are we waiting for!
Thought we weren't stopping.
How do we tell
them to keep my body
twenty feet from
the nearest oven?
Is there any way for ghosts to
communicate with living people?
[BOTAN]
Yes.
So are you going to tell me?
You can just
stand at their bedside.
[YUSUKE]
What do you mean?
Human beings are more
attuned to the supernatural
when they're asleep,
and so ghosts can talk
to people in their dreams.
Well I'll be darned.
[ATSUKO]
You fool!
[glass breaks]
Why? What were
you thinking Yusuke?
[Atsuko sobs]
No one gave you
permission to die!
You got hit by a car--
Strong people live through that!
Were you mad at me Yusuke?
Were you mad, didn't
I raise you good enough?!
It's so very sad.
The only thing sad now
is she's got one more
excuse to act that way.
She won't listen.
Let's move on. I think
I know someone who will.
[dog barking]
[YUSUKE]
Look at that.
Her room's become a lot
more girly since we were kids.
Hey, what's up Keiko?
She's crying.
What's wrong?
[KEIKO]
Yusuke!
Yusuke wait.
[KEIKO]
Wait.
Yusuke wait.
Listen to me Keiko! I need
you to pull yourself together!
I'm coming back!
It's hard to explain,
but I'm a ghost right now,
and I have to take
care of this egg, and then--
Yusuke.
Hey are you hearing me?
This is important!
You're heavy.
I need you to take care
of my body until I come back.
You've gotta tell
them not to cremate me!
And tell my Mom not
to waste her life away
'cause we're going to be fine!
Well I guess that's it Keiko.
I'm coming back I don't
want to see you cry anymore.
Oh Yusuke!
But he was, I thought,
was all that really
just a dream?!
No I'm sure I felt him.
Atsuko?
Hey are you in there?
Hi Keiko.
Hello, Atsuko.
Did I wake you?
I just had the strangest
dream about Yusuke.
Yusuke was living in some
other world full of Ogres
and he kept knocking them down
until he became their leader.
That sounds
like him, doesn't it?
I dreamed too.
[ATSUKO]
Oh? Was it like mine?
Then maybe it was true.
Yes, maybe.
[BOTAN] This dream your mother
had seems to give her comfort.
And Keiko doesn't
want to take that from her.
Well while she's being comforted
I'm gonna be a barbecue!
Botan! Is there
any other way
to communicate
with living people!
This dream business
isn't going to cut it!
I wonder.
Geez! You're killing me!
I mean call me crazy
but I'd think that as
the messenger of death
you'd know how to do this!
Well if the dream
communication isn't working
there's always the final method!
You always this vague?
Under the final method
you talk to Keiko
by taking control of
someone else's body.
Oh right, I've seen
that in movies and stuff.
You mean like a possession?
Yeah, sort of.
Can I do it with anybody?
Well no, there are some rules.
First, you have to know them,
and second they have
to be unusually
aware of the supernatural.
In that case I'm screwed.
There's no one like that.
Something the matter, Kuwabara?
Do you think
we're being followed?
I'm feeling a chill.
Gee, maybe it's the flu.
I doubt it.
It's just the tickle
feeling kicking in.
The tickle?
That's what we call it when
Kuwabara starts detecting
the presence
of ghosts around us.
[KUWABARA] Yeah... It's true.
I've had the tickle ever
since Kindergarten.
Voices chase me home at night.
Scary old women whisper
things to me in my dreams.
Sometimes they're nice.
Usually they're not!
I think it's 'cause they know
I'm kind of a natural leader.
What a surprise.
That goof actually
has a purpose.
The ghost-monster is behind
me man, it made a noise.
Are you sure?
Is it the scary old
lady with the axe again?
No it sounds more like
a puny low-level ghost,
like a haunted
raccoon or something.
I'll show you puny, you- !!
You can forget it Botan!
There's no way I'm taking
control of that lame-brain!
Here's my
impression of Yusuke...
..."look at me I'm burning!"
Ready?
Good.
What's wrong, man?
You look a little pale.
Earth to Kuwabara!
All right, he's ready
for the taking!
Okay.
But I've only given you one
hour before the effect wears off
and you're
thrown to the outside.
[BOTAN] A human body
like Kuwabara's
couldn't stand
any longer than that.
If you miss this chance there
probably won't be another one,
so do the best that you can.
I will.
Hey, check me out! I'm inside
Kuwabara! Feeling smooth!
Looks like he's back to normal.
Out of my way punks! Now!
So much, for normal.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
One hour. That's not enough.
Daughter! I need to speak
to your daughter Keiko!
Who do you
think you are, cowboy?
I don't have time to
explain! Where is Keiko?!
[WOMAN] Why
should we tell you?
Because it's me you
guys! I'm Yusuke!
Yusuke was never ugly like you!
And for your information he was
killed in an accident this week!
How could you be so cruel?
We were close family
friends with that boy
and your joke's not appreciated!
Coming here to
harass our daughter
on the day of her
best friend's funeral?
I tolerate a lot
of crud in my life
but bad manners
is not on the list!
Allow me to show you the door!
I might look different
on the outside,
but inside I'm really--!
Have some respect!
[YUSUKE THINKS] That
could have been better!
We should have special
passwords for times like this!
Man! Only forty five minutes!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Dammit! Where could she be?!
Well if it isn't Kuwabara from
the Sarayashki Junior High.
Get off me!
I know what it looks like
but I'm tellin' you
I'm not Kuwabara!
No I remember that face
and I owe it some bruises!
Fine just wait
'til after sunset!
You can hit me all you like!
Sorry, but I don't
take requests.
Oh? Then take this.
Try that with me!
Okay, now I'm pissed!
Man that hurt!
I didn't think anyone
could throw punches
that hard core besides
Yusuke Urameshi!
Darn, I'm giving
Kuwabara a good name.
Kuwabara, it's time for
me to even the score.
Yeah, me too!
And me!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Unbelievable!
Does Kuwabara pick a fight
with everyone he meets?!
Attack!
Can't you understand?
I don't, have time,
for this!!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Well that was fun.
But probably not so good
on the time situation.
Here we go! I think those are
Keiko's friends! What a save.
I hope Keiko will be okay soon.
For our sake as well as hers.
People are starting
to say things!
Hey, girls!
Why are you running?!
Please wait!
That's weird.
[YUSUKE] Ahh! Only ten minutes
'till I'm booted out!
I'm never gonna' find Keiko now!
Sorry about that.
Keiko!
Where'd they go?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Pull it together, Yusuke.
You've found her,
but now you've got
to convince her, quick,
that you're not just
some ugly weird guy
with bruises on his face!
No time, no time.
Okay, I've known
her all my life.
There's gotta be something
between us that only I would do.
Yeah.
Keiko! Nice uniform!
They're so squishy!
Yusuke you jerk!
Oh! Who the heck are you?
I'm exactly who you thought
I was Keiko. I'm Yusuke.
I don't care what
any tough guy says,
your punches hurt the most.
[laughing]
Don't tease me Yusuke.
Is it really you?
It's too strange.
Why do you look like that?
I borrowed somebody's body,
but only for an hour!
I know this is weird,
but you have to believe!
Whether or not I believe
isn't the question!
I knew it was you from
the first time you spoke!
I know.
[KEIKO] And it's not just your
stupid gags, or how you laugh--
There's ways you move
and speak that in a hundred
years I wouldn't forget.
Whoa now.
Don't cry. We'll save the
mushy stuff for another day.
Then tell me what's
going on. What's next?
Next I'm going
to give you my message
before this dummy
gets his body back.
Which, by the way,
happens in about a minute!
I guess you can think
of this as a rental car
and I'm about to
lose my license!
I'll say this as
straight as I can.
I'm taking this
test to get back,
and I'm trying hard not to fail!
So just trust me and take
care of my body until then.
And tell my Mom she's
got to stop the funeral!
I know I've been a bum to you
at times but please wait for me.
I will, I'd wait forever Yusuke.
[YUSUKE]
Okay, Botan I'm ready.
Uh that's funny, I thought
I was with the guys.
Apparently not!
Wow! This girl must really
have the hots for me!
Sorry about that.
Nah, it's okay.
I prob'ly deserved it.
[banging on the door]
[KEIKO] Atsuko! Please open
the door! Atsuko!
I have to tell you! About
Yusuke! He might be coming back!
He already has!
I opened up his coffin
again because well,
I was going to smack him one
more time for leaving me,
but then I saw.
Yusuke's cheeks have some color!
His skin is slightly warm!
His heart is beating.
It's slow, but.
My boy's alive!
All things considered,
I think I'd call this quite
a successful day, Yusuke.
Yeah.
Hey I think it's feeding now.
I only did good-natured things
today, don't you think so?
I don't know Yusuke,
you did beat up a
lot of kids as I recall.
[YUSUKE] Okay, listen up!
I've got to answer
a tough question:
What happens when your
rival shows some backbone
and takes a beating
for his friends?
I mean I'm all for surprises--
But who would have thought
Kuwabara had a code of honor?
See, Mr. Akashi is
threatening to kick him
and his friends out of school
if he doesn't clean up his act.
So what do I do now?
Help my rival?
If it's between him
and that no-good teacher,
I think I might.
I just hope that Spirit Beast
doesn't hatch and eat me first!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪