[NARRATOR]
Yusuke now fights the deepest
of Sensui's seven personalities:
Shinobu himself,
fracturing mankind's hope for
survival, as not even Yusuke
had the strength to win.
Out of options, Koenma
had released the power
of his Mafuuken,
a defensive spell designed
to trap Demon World's
greatest threats. But with
Sensui's control over
the elusive third type
of energy--Sacred Energy--
he miraculously deflected Human
World's last line of defense.
[sighs]
[KOENMA]
I'm ready to pay for this.
The rest of the world
shouldn't have to.
[gasps]
You're not ready to die.
You just stopped teething.
Don't...! You can't win!
It's my mess to
answer for, not yours.
Oh, right. I'm killing you.
Forgive me, I got distracted.
No!
Urameshi's not gonna
leave it to us!
It's not his style
to trust anybody.
He wouldn't give his life unless
he was savin' us for sure.
Perhaps that's just it.
[KUWABARA]
Hm?
Think, Kuwabara...
What you did wasn't
a real gamble.
You knew what Yusuke
had just been through.
They were sayin' he was
s'posed to be stronger.
[KURAMA]
That's right.
You knew Yusuke wasn't
living up to his potential.
A mulberry's a tree.
Kuwabara's a man.
And I'll prove it.
We all have to die
when our time comes,
but if we do our duty,
we don't got regrets!
So taste a little piece
of my sword, Toguro!
Stay right there, Kuwabara!
[yells]
[KUWABARA groans]
No!
Okay, Urameshi...
[KUWABARA]
It's all you...
I did what I could...
Now beat him for... all of us...
Make my death count, okay?
Genkai's Spirit Orb.
Yes. He possessed the power,
but he didn't know
how to tap into it.
Well then, maybe we
should kill Kuwabara again.
No, Yusuke's maxed-out.
We're the untapped ones...
We have the power, but not the
strength of mind to reach it.
Not without the pain of loss.
So, could we save him?
[KUWABARA]
Wait, Urameshi!
You don't have to die!
If you really think I have
the strength, I'll find it!
Please, just give
me time! I swear!
[KOENMA]
This won't accomplish anything.
Please... Yusuke.
You're half right.
I've got a feeling what I'm
about to do isn't gonna seal up
any tunnels, or keep Demons
from having Earth
to play with...
Whole world's probably screwed.
Who cares?
But I'll get one
thing accomplished...
I'll know the loser
of this fight.
[grunts]
[KOENMA groans]
You are asking me to
take your life, Yusuke?
Yeah, that's right.
And do it with some style.
I don't want some
piss-poor, half-assed try.
I know you can do
it real quickly.
Urameshi!
You can't go this way! Think!
What I did against Toguro
in that fight, I did for you.
The breaking point.
[KUWABARA]
I did it for you!
But you can't ever die
and have it be for me!
You can't...! You can't!
Urameshi!
Following for a reason?
Kuwabara...? Nope,
never heard of ya.
[KUWABARA]
Is that so?
Well lemme just jog
your memory, punk!
Nobody forgets fightin' me!
[KUWABARA groans]
--[groans]
--Hey! I think you're right!
The sound of your ribs
breaking does ring a bell!
[KUWABARA chuckles]
I won't ever forgive you...
Not if you go out like this!
There's nothin' wrong with
guys needin' each other!
For me, you're...
Well you're my...
[KUWABARA groans]
You got lucky!
Next time, you're
kissin' pavement!
[YUSUKE]
Yeah, yeah.
You ever beat me,
and I'll become a nun.
[YUSUKE] Hmph, you really got
a pain fetish, Kuwabara.
[KUWABARA]
Finally! He remembers my name!
Well, let's make
this a quick one...
My mom's makin' TV dinners.
[KUWABARA]
The only way you're goin' home
is on crutches!
That's zero wins,
and 46 losses.
[KOMADA]
You should take it easy.
He's stronger than the devil.
[KUWABARA]
I know how strong he is!
I know better than anybody.
But men don't give up on dreams.
[KUWABARA]
These fellas won't ever get it.
Winning's never been the
real reason I fight him.
[OKUBO] So you're gonna
challenge him again?
I'm a real man, aren't I?
You've...
...always gotta be
there, Urameshi!
Can't you get it?
If you're not, then who am I?
[KAYKO]
What's wrong, Shizuru?
[SHIZURU] My brother's heart...
I can sense it breaking.
I have to admit it, Kayko.
I'm really scared.
Is it wrong to be?
Hey...
What are you waiting
for, head case?
[SENSUI] Why can't I
bring myself to strike?
I know he can't stop me.
This is what I've
been waiting for.
It's judgment.
[SENSUI]
Why do I hesitate?
[ITSUKI]
Finish him, Shinobu.
Show what you're capable of.
[HIEI]
Lover-boy.
Release us now and you can
keep your ability to breed.
If we're going to die,
let us die in war.
Against Sensui.
But how?
I mean, we tried everything.
[KURAMA] Kuwabara, Hiei,
and myself will join
Yusuke in four-on-one combat,
using every tactic we have.
We've gone far past the stage
of fighting for our honor.
I'm ready.
[KURAMA] We just need Itsuki
to let us out of this creature.
Perhaps torture would suffice.
You'd still fail.
[gasps]
What? It's four on one!
[ITSUKI] Four times zero
power is still zero power.
I'll show you zero--
If you really think
we can't help,
what was the purpose
of trapping us?
Well...
While you were never a
threat for defeating Sensui,
you could perhaps,
with teamwork, run away.
Carrying Yusuke on a shoulder
as you escape the cave,
deflecting Sensui's attacks.
No... We don't run.
Maybe you don't.
But you should ask your
more strategic friends...
Hiei... Kurama...
I sense that neither one
of you is terribly far
from becoming an A-Class Demon.
In fact, Spirit Fox,
I believe you once were.
Maybe you plan to escape
with your lives now and brace
for the first wave
of demon intruders.
Then, make yourself strong,
defeat Sensui as a team,
and proceed to damage control.
[HIEI]
He's read our minds.
You're clever, Itsuki...
But you've guessed wrong.
Don't try your
bluffs on me, Hiei.
I know your kind too well.
Just stand here and do
the only thing you can:
watch Yusuke die.
You're a soul-less freak!
Uh, Mr. Kuwabara,
I've been thinking
about something.
Sorry, pal, but if it's
not about a way out,
I don't wanna hear it.
It is.
Remember our fight, when
you and your friends
were trapped inside
my water monster...?
That Territory was a dimension.
You shouldn't have escaped!
[OKUBO gurgles]
[MIYAMOTO screams]
[SEA MAN laughs]
[SEA MAN] But you did, by
realizing your new power.
If you got out of that
dimensional beast,
then you can get us
out of this one.
Uh... You think?
Mr. Sensui kidnapped you
because he saw what you could
do... It wasn't a fluke.
Just tap into it.
[chuckles] You should have
brought this up to
me earlier, kid.
[KUWABARA yells]
[KUWABARA groans]
Idiot.
He still hasn't
learned how to hone
his new power.
I know you're
in there somewhere!
[yells]
Why do you think
we prevented Gourmet
from eating you earlier?
Because you're still useless.
You can't yet summon
the Jigen-Tou at will.
[KUWABARA]
Come on, power! Come out!
Sensui, finish Yusuke, now.
Well, then... You just
heard Mr. Itsuki.
I'm no longer
allowed to hesitate.
One of us detectives has to die.
[yells]
Wait!
[growls]
[yells, groans]
Are you okay?
Hope you're studying, boys.
If you couldn't sense that, then
get yourself some wind chimes.
Then, that force was
Urameshi's energy.
Yeah. It's Yusuke's, Sensui's,
and Kuwabara's,
all mixed into one.
[grunts] And someone's
about to pop.
What are you waiting for?
Your balls to drop?
No. It's not fear...
I just want to savor your fall.
Yeah?
Well then, I'll make
sure I'm tasty for you.
[yells]
Stop!
[YUSUKE grunts]
[grunts]
[growls]
[YUSUKE yells]
[SENSUI groans]
[growls]
[yells]
[YUSUKE groans]
[panting]
Now I know I've
made the right call.
[growls]
You're done, pal. It's just
a matter of heart beats.
[YUSUKE groaning]
[groans]
Yusuke!
[gasps]
[KURAMA growls]
[KUWABARA groans]
Why now...? Why?
It doesn't fit the rules!
I get this power right
when we need it...
But then I can't reach it--
how can that be right?
[groans]
[KUWABARA panting]
I'm supposed to get strong
from seein' him hurt--
hit new levels!
It's the part where I
power up and save the day!
No...
We've survived too much--
learned too much
to end this way.
Darn you...!
You're supposed to be here.
For me...!
But how am I supposed
to turn it off?
Go ahead and die with your tail
between your legs.
Maybe they'll make
me a Spirit Detective
since I'm not such a wimp!
[KUWABARA] What in the world
do you think I was doin'
for the last six months
while you were off
training with Genkai?
Letting you get
better than me?
Nuh-uh!
Spirit Sword!
Me and Urameshi
jumped into this
deal together...
And we're both gonna
come out alive,
or we're not coming
out at all! Okay?!
[yells]
[TOGURO 1]
Hm. They want to die with honor.
Kuwabara! Here it comes!
[yells]
[KUWABARA]
Hey...! Urameshi!
[KAYKO]
Is he okay?
[yells]
[YUSUKE grunts]
What the hell?
I thought that we were a team,
but I guess I'm just one big
joke to you all, aren't I?
Well this joke's got feelings!
You punk.
KUWABARA]
Now beat him for...
all of us... Make my
death count, okay?
Don't you get it?
There's been a scheme.
A bigger reason for
it all. We've learned!
[YUSUKE groans]
No! What the hell could
be the reason for this?
[yelling, sobbing]
[YUSUKE groans]
Well, Yusuke...
Hope you've found peace.
[KUWABARA]
Come on!
[grunting, yelling]
I've done all I can!
Finish him, Sensui!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[URA-OTOKO screeches]
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi! Get out of the way!
[gasping]
Hey, Puu...
[gasps]
I think something's
wrong with him.
He just... He just went cold.
Yusuke...
[gasping]
He can't be... He can't.
[SENSUI] Trial of humanity.
The defense rests.
No...
What now, Master Genkai?
I felt that wind.
Please... Is this
why I came back?
More pain?
[YANAGISAWA, KAITOU gasp]
Creepy...
[yelping]
That was awfully
bizarre turbulence...
Something's been shaken up.
[gasps] I've...
felt that before...
The first time.
[KUWABARA]
Come on, stop clownin' around.
Ha, ha... Prankster.
I get it, it's payback
for me trickin' you
with Toguro. Good one.
Too bad I'm not as gullible
as you, big lame-o.
I mean, hey, I'll just
cover up your mouth and nose!
You can't complain, right?
I mean, dead guys
don't gotta breathe!
Look...
Your plan to motivate
us worked. I broke us out.
Now let's beat Sensui
together and go home.
Come on, I'm not dumb!
See...! Ya can't hide
your heart bea--
[KUWABARA gasps]
Urameshi...
[growling, panting]
For some reason,
I thought taking his life
would bring catharsis...
I even timed the video's
climactic final scene
as a requiem for his death.
Instead, I just feel
a deeper sadness.
Another soul lost,
fighting for the wrong side.
[KUWABARA gasping]
[DEMONS growling]
[SENSUI] But in truth,
there's little point
in mourning his passing...
As humans, we will all
join him soon enough.
[SENSUI] If you insist on
getting your swings in,
you should hurry.
The tunnel is complete.
No!
[KOENMA]
Yusuke is dead.
And now my father is
sending his own army
from Spirit World
with mysterious orders.
Sensui's madness
is growing deeper,
and the tunnel between
worlds is finally opened
for the demon invasion.
But as Yusuke intended,
his sacrifice calls forth
unbelievable powers
in his friends.
Now, a desperate fight
for humanity's fate,
staged not in caves,
but on the battle field
of Demon World itself.
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho.