♪
[NARRATOR]
At long last,
the warriors in
the Genkai Tournament
have narrowed to three.
Kuwabara won his match
by acquiring a Spirit Sword,
while Yusuke barely clenched
a victory with a single,
clever shot.
And then immediately
faced the ninja Kazemaru.
With an explosive streak
of luck Yusuke survived,
and now must crack
his detective case--
is Shorin a demon in disguise?
Since he doesn't
seem to be moving
you'll just have
to fight around him.
Come on, you two. Let's
close up the semifinals.
[KUWABARA THINKS]
An easy win.
It's ironic that
out of all the fighters,
Shorin was last on
my list as a suspect.
Yeah, if you're gonna disguise
yourself. Why not look cooler?
[KOENMA] The answer's
simple Yusuke.
Not everyone, believe it or not,
is interested in
how groovy they look.
[KOENMA]
Rando hunts in stealth.
He's not concerned
with fame, or recognition.
Only with increasing his powers.
After stealing the techniques
of ninety-nine psychics,
no one has ever
seen Rando's true face.
At least, no one who lived
long enough to brag.
Yusuke should be happy Rando
hasn't revealed his true self.
Maybe now he won't have
to remove everyone's throat.
If Shorin is in fact Rando,
I'm afraid Kuwabara
is out of his league.
Hey Kuwabara! Wait up!
Don't try to give me your
coaching advice, Urameshi.
Listen, you gotta
pull out of this fight.
You remember that
demon I was talking about?
Well I think Shorin
is him dressed up.
I don't care who he is!
First of all,
I'm gonna beat this guy
and then I'm gonna
grind you into the dirt!
So don't try to get out
of it by making me scared!
And second, you beat
that last guy by luck!
[YUSUKE] So, what's that
got to do with this fight?
I'm not exactly sure!
But I'm gonna fight this guy.
Monster or not!
What's the point, you know
I'd beat you next anyway.
Oh yeah? Well that'd be true
if it was opposite day! Stupid!
Hey! Would you boys please
behave! This isn't Junior High!
[KUWABARA AND YUSUKE]
Shut up!
Please sir, may we start?
Yeah.
Begin!!
I'll take you down in one hit!
What the...?
I see this fighter will take
more strength than I thought.
Gee buddy, are you all right?
That was just a warm-up shot.
You needn't worry
about my health, sir.
Our difference in
strength is pretty big, huh?
So, what are the chances
of a demon being a total wuss?
Maybe Rando's been hiding here
somewhere but not as a fighter.
Yeah.
Or maybe he was
one of the fighters
and he already got beat.
What, is that all
we're gonna fight?
No, let me try a
few techniques first.
The structure of Shorin's
Spirit Energy is changing.
What is that?
It couldn't be.
Circles of Inferno!
You're okay Kuwabara!
Stop giving
yourself a pat-down
and get ready
for his next attack!
Would you shut up?!
Fine, if you want to use your
fireworks, then I'll use mine!
All right you little
shrimp-baby, batter's up!
Whoa, I guess that's a home run.
Those pitches were pretty nasty,
but nothin' compared to the
old batting cages back home.
Kuwabara's like
a whole new fighter
when he starts using
that Spirit Sword of his.
I think he can beat
this little punk,
Rando or no Rando.
Anything's possible, I suppose.
[SHORIN]
Very surprising.
Twice now you've managed
to evade my attack
and make it your own offensive.
Don't try and make
it sound so high-tech.
I'm just trying to cream you.
This requires a new approach.
(Chanting)
What in the heck are you
muttering about over there?
You might as well speak up.
(Chanting)
Yes, I thought I recognized
where that fireball
attack was from.
Ages ago,
two renowned masters spent
the last half of their lives
perfecting the Circles of
Inferno and this chant.
What's this do?
[GENKAI]
That isn't the point.
What matters is that
the only ones who could
have taught this boy have
been dead for centuries.
Old lady, you just
proved something
for me once and for all.
That chanter's
definitely no boy.
(Chanting)
I'm shuttin' you up, boy.
You're freakin' me out.
Reduction!
Hey, hey, how did
that kid get so big?
Hey, the grass got big too!
Wait a minute.
That's a-a caterpillar. Oh,
I've turned into an insect!
What the hell?!
Don't be worried,
you're still a human.
Just a very small
and fragile one.
So, does this hurt?
There's no way he
can pull outta this.
Kuwabara! Tell him you're
backing out of the fight!
Oh, but that just
cannot be allowed.
I have to make use of
this power a little first.
I'm curious about the strength
of bones after they've shrunk.
I'll start with the right arm.
Kuwabara!
Please! No more!
[Kuwabara cries out in pain]
[Shorin laughs]
Well that was a fun experiment.
Now let's see about
the rib cage, shall we?
I can't stand this lady!
I'm going in there!
No I'll call the fight.
That's enough, Shorin!
All-right.
[Shorin laughs]
You bastard!
This punk's not gonna listen
to you anymore, old lady!
Kuwabara.
You wanted me to
let him go, right?
And now...
[YUSUKE]
Kuwabara!
Just say something!
I can't sense him.
(Chanting)
Restore!
Oh my God, Kuwabara!
[YUSUKE]
His body, it's twisted.
[BOTAN]
Both arms are in pieces.
His ribs too, I don't know
if these wounds will heal.
I won't die, even if all
the bones in my body are broke.
[KUWABARA]
Remember, Urameshi?
We still must fight each other.
Yeah buddy, that's right.
I cannot tell you how long
I've wanted to use that
technique on someone,
but it takes so much
time to complete the chant.
It's very bothersome.
The move is so complex,
imagine concentrating on that
while fighting fifteen people.
What with the word
order, the intonation.
But with your
Spirit Wave technique
you could destroy
a hundred people
with one simple
motion of energy.
That is right,
isn't it master?
Yes, if it's misused.
Of course I wouldn't
ever use it that way,
but it's great to
know the potential.
[YUSUKE]
Not so fast, you freak.
You have to beat me first.
And in case you didn't know...
I happen to be
a Spirit Detective.
Let the final match begin.
Shorin versus Yusuke.
[KOENMA] Their power
charts are well matched.
You better win Yusuke!
Well, I see your
Spirit Energy
is recovering
nicely on this hill.
Ready?
The first one is for Kuwabara!
And I've still
got ninety-nine more.
One for every psychic
who's life you stole.
[SHORIN]
My knees!
His Spirit Power scored a 155,
but it must've
increased to over 200
to make that kind of impact.
You better stand...
I'll feel bad hitting you
if you're glued to the ground.
Sickle and Tornado!
What the...?
What the hell is this?
I see.
Of all my techniques
I enjoy this the most.
Congratulations.
I once knew of a fighter
who made quite a name for
himself with this attack.
It creates a vacuum
around the opponent,
and causes air
to escape violently
from their body through
cuts in the skin.
And with as many battle
wounds as you have,
Yusuke, it
should be very painful.
Ouch.
Now that's surprising.
Most would pass out from the
pain, shall we try it again?!
It appears your
friend is a fool.
No. Just mad.
I dare you.
[Yusuke cries out]
I don't know
where he got the will
to endure that kind of pain,
but he's making it
into the eye of the tornado!
[KOENMA] Uh hold the phone,
people. I think I'm delusional.
Did Yusuke just win?
[YUSUKE]
I got him.
And he wasn't
joking about the pain.
You got him good Yusuke! He'll
probably be out for a week!
Well, that's what happens
when you piss me off.
It's a shame Kuwabara
couldn't be here to see it.
Hey, I'm not dead yet,
I've still got
to kick Urameshi's...
Yusuke, maybe you shouldn't
try walking for a while.
[YUSUKE]
Nah--I'm fine.
[YUSUKE] Well? How'd you
like that, Gramdma?
You shouldn't have wasted
your energy walking here.
Your fight isn't over yet.
Did you actually think Rando
could be defeated so easily?
What?
[Rando laughs]
Yes, Mr. Urameshi, you
should listen to the old hag.
They tend to know things.
For example, that I am a demon
who will not be destroyed.
Most likely, she also knows
that I must kill you all,
as you are about
to see my true form.
The only real mystery is this:
How will I choose
to torture you?
What is that thing?
I'm the one you've
been looking for, Rando.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I can
feel his power from here.
That's not a good sign.
[Rando laughs maniacally]
[NARRATOR]
And so it is.
The human-hunter Rando
has revealed his true,
monstrous identity.
Now, can Yusuke succeed
where ninety nine
before him have failed?
[KUWABARA]
Hey guys, it's Kuwabara.
I know I normally
don't do this,
but it's getting crazy.
Yusuke's fightin'
a century-old monster
on a hill full of ghosts
that turn up
everyone's strength!
Meanwhile, I'm blacked
out with broken arms,
trying to tell Yusuke
not to get killed!
But how's he fight a guy with
ninety-nine super powers?
Sure he's got
that Spirit Gun thing,
but I'll give you a hint,
that alone won't do squat!
It's gonna be a giant finale--
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪