♪
[NARRATOR] One day,
Yusuke Urameshi was
killed in a car accident.
He awoke as a ghost,
and was given the
chance to regain his life
by hatching a
dangerous Spirit Beast
that fed off his own energy.
The Spirit Beast probably
would have eaten him alive.
But Yusuke used the power of the
egg to save Keiko's life,
and sacrificed his
one hope for coming back.
Koenma, ruler
of the Spirit World,
has seen Yusuke's selfless act
and will give
him a second chance.
[YUSUKE] There are two things I
hate. Waiting, and being rushed.
And what do you know--that's
all I've been doing lately!
Well Yusuke,
important people like Koenma
are always quite busy.
Those guys just like
to keep you waiting
to make you think
that they're important.
Besides, how
busy can a toddler be?
[KOENMA] I thought we agreed
you'd stop calling me that.
Koenma!
Yo!
Don't sneak up on me!
It makes me really pisses me-
Hey Koenma sir,
Yusuke was just wondering
when would be a good time
to bring him back to life.
Ahhh yes, about that matter.
It seems we're
going to have to rush.
[KOENMA]
Come with me.
[YUSUKE] Nice pad, my mom
must've had good fire insurance.
So are you going to
put me back in my body now?
[KOENMA]
Not just yet.
Energy of the body
and energy of the soul
have their own wavelengths.
Unless the two are perfectly
aligned, they cannot join,
which won't happen until--
Tomorrow.
Wow! Starting tomorrow
I'll be a human
with real fists and everything!
Well that's the
best-case scenario.
There's a small problem.
The frequencies
of your wavelengths,
interestingly enough,
are lower than most people.
If you miss this
chance tomorrow,
you'll have to wait
a while to realign.
What are we talking about?
Like weeks, or months?
Fifty-two years.
Fifty-two years?!
[KOENMA] Yes, but I think
it'd be wise if you
tried to do it tomorrow instead.
And in order for that to happen
you'll need someone in the
living world who cares about you
at least a little bit to
donate their life energy.
You mean like a human sacrifice?
[KOENMA] Are you kidding?
I'm not evil!
They must give it to you,
through the lips.
[KOENMA] I don't see what's
surprising about that.
Haven't you heard of
mouth-to-mouth resuscitation?
I guess so.
[KOENMA]
It's time now.
Hey! Why are
you making me glow?!
[KOENMA]
Standard procedure.
I'm opening the road between
your body and the Spirit World,
so the transfer can be made.
In the morning,
your body will shine in gold.
Tonight, while
your body prepares,
you must enter the
dreams of the three people
who want you back the most.
Tell them each what to do,
and if one of them understands
the message and kisses you
before tomorrow at midnight,
then you will
return to the living world.
Three people, huh?
Poo... empty already?
Must be a sign that somebody's
thinking about me at the bar.
Hey there Yusuke.
Watch over the house
for me while I'm gone.
[KOENMA]
The first is your mother,
who seems
to be leaving now.
Oh yeah,
we better rule her out.
She'll be on
this streak for days.
Who are the other
two people I've got?
[KOENMA] You should know. It's
the ones who are closest to you.
Okay, okay,
I'm sure Keiko is one.
And the other one must be--
It's terrifying! I didn't know
nightmares could be so bad!
[Kuwabara cries out]
[KEIKO]
Yusuke?
[KEIKO THINKS] He
certainly doesn't look golden,
but was it...?
Should I try?
Don't be silly.
It was just a dream.
Hey! Didn't she see me glowing?
[KOENMA]
I forgot to tell you.
The connection starts from the
feet and gradually moves up.
You won't be completely
gold until noon.
Guess she should have
checked the sheets.
Kuwabara and my
mother are hopeless.
I'll just have to wait until
Keiko gets out of school.
I hate waiting.
[SCIENCE TEACHER] Who wants
to learn about Photosynthesis?!
Anyone? Okay, well
it's very interesting...
...see the chlorophyll
and the plant cell...
[KEIKO THINKS] Kuwabara's
not in school today.
I wanted to ask
him about the dream.
Ukimura! Keiko Ukimura!
[KEIKO]
Yes sir?
Would you come with me?
There's something
wrong with your mother.
[DOCTOR] I'm afraid
she's overworked herself
in this hot weather,
Mr. Ukimura.
But with a day's rest,
we think she'll be fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you very much.
Keiko, they say she'll be fine.
Now let's give her
a chance to sleep now.
No. I'm staying right here.
[BOTAN]
Oh, how unlucky this is.
She'll stand at her
mother's bedside all night,
but you're the one
that needs attention.
You know, between
my house burning down
that energy wavelength
problem and now this,
it really feels like
someone's out to get me.
[KOENMA]
Yo!
Your link-up to the Spirit
World is fully loaded Yusuke.
The only thing left
now is the life energy.
Go! Go! Faster you wimp!
Get out of my way,
stupid blue car guy!
There! There he is!
Come on Kuwabara!
Get your head out of that
stupid game and listen to me!
I don't want you to think
I'm weird or anything,
but please please
please just kiss me!
Hey! Get off of my
tail, road trash!
Idiot!!
This arcade just got chilly.
[YUSUKE] Did you see that?!
He can sense me!
Now put it together moron!
Oh no! Not the tickle feeling!
He could take a while.
Which I don't have!!
Hey! Are you listening to me?!
How you can go partying
with these weirdos
when my life is hanging
by a stupid thread?
Get off your butt!
You sure can
hold your liquor.
That much always
gives me gas.
Another round for the ladies!
Oh Atsuko,
you're such a friend.
[ATSUKO]
Drink some more!
[YUSUKE]
Just pull the plug.
I suppose the only thing
we can do at this point
is try to contact Keiko again.
What's the use?
She's practically
handcuffed to her mom.
[KOENMA] What will you do then?
It's about to be
eleven-forty five.
Time flies, doesn't it?
[BOTAN] I can't let
Yusuke give up now.
There's got to be a way to--
If this won't do it
I don't know what will!
Wait! Botan!
Just hang tight! I have an idea
that could still make this work!
Doesn't she know when to quit?
[KEIKO THINKS]
It's gotten so late.
[KEIKO'S MOM]
Yu-ske.
Yusuke.
You must save him.
His time runs out at twelve.
Remember what you dreamed.
It was more, than that.
Keiko, you must not be afraid.
Believe.
[KOENMA]
Five more minutes.
What will you do if
she doesn't make it in time?
The only thing I can do.
Wait around another fifty years.
Then I'll go see Keiko
when she's an old hag.
The mother was asleep so she
was tuned to the Spirit World
I relayed the
message through her.
Will she make it?
[KOENMA] It is now
eleven fifty-seven.
She's only got three minutes!
[KOENMA] Actually,
make that two minutes.
Eleven fifty-nine!
It's, too late!
Got it!
[bell tolls]
[KEIKO]
He's fading!
Yusuke!!
Keiko!!
Please come back, I need you.
Yusuke please, Yusuke.
No don't go. No.
[KEIKO]
Yusuke!!
[KOENMA]
She didn't make it.
Hey, nice kiss.
Yusuke!
[BOTAN]
She barely made it.
I was holding my
breath and everything.
Well I guess this case is over.
KOENMA]
Don't be crazy Botan.
This boy's case is only
beginning, didn't you know?
The real ordeal
will be much harder.
Let's see how our
little Yusuke fares
when he's not
floating in the sky.
My feet are so heavy
they're stuck to the ground!
Man I love gravity!
Pardon us sir, could
we borrow a little cash?
See we've lost our wallets
and we need to call our moms.
You remember how the Golden
Rule works, don't you?
Just give us all the money
you've got on, okay?
Are you guys talking to me?
I mean you see me?
Who else would we be
threatening, buddy?
I can talk trash to
people and even touch them!
To be alive is
a wonderful thing!
How dare you!
You can't touch me!
Leave him alone. It isn't
right to mess with crazies.
[Yusuke laughs]
[BOTAN]
This way.
Yes, over here.
Do you have a minute?
Who, me?
Indeed.
Alright.
[BOTAN] You are born under the
influence of an unusual star.
Your life energy is somehow
different from other people.
You don't say.
[YUSUKE] Maybe I
should tell her I've been
dead for a couple weeks.
That would throw her.
[BOTAN]
No it wouldn't.
You have a mission
to accomplish, young man.
[BOTAN] Where are you
going? I'm not finished!
Sorry, but no missions for me.
All I'm doin' now is
some good old R and R.
[door opens and rattles bell]
[STUDENT 1] All those guys are
from Rugafuchi Junior High.
[STUDENT 2] Yeah, they
come here all the time now.
[STUDENT 1]
I hear they're trying to take
over the turf from Kuwabara.
[STUDENT 2] No way! Man,
we better get out of here.
[STUDENT 1] If only Yusuke
Urameshi was still alive.
[YUSUKE THINKS] These are
definitely kids from Rugafuchi.
I see they've been taking
advantage of things
while I've been gone.
Nice of them.
[WAITRESS] Here you go.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
From the way they're sitting,
I'd say four-eyes
there is the ringleader.
What the--
that guy's got horns!
That's not normal.
Oh well. Not gonna ruin my day.
Aye, Kuwabara's
later than usual.
Yeah, maybe he's
not gonna come after all.
So what makes you so sure he'll
follow your orders, Sakamoto?
[SAKAMOTO] Simple, my boys.
I'm playing with a loaded deck.
And as evidence of
his great loyalty,
I'm having him steal a
comic book from
the most guarded store in town
and bring it to me.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Oh,
give me a break, horn-boy.
Everyone knows
Kuwabara doesn't steal things.
It goes against his honor code.
[KUWABARA] Eikichi! Eikichi!
Where are you?!
She's safe here with me.
Now let's see what
you've got there.
[KUWABARA]
There!
I got you several kinds!
I didn't know what you liked.
Well, isn't that very
interesting, Kuwabara?
Didn't know they gave
receipts for stealing.
[KUWABARA] What
difference does it make?
I got you the comic books,
now give me Eikichi!
Fool. You've missed
the point entirely.
I was trying to teach you
the thrill of stealing things.
This is not
what we agreed upon.
[SAKAMOTO]
Now apologize.
You heard me. Get on your knees
and apologize for being wrong.
--What?!
--Never!
Don't push it, Sakamoto!
[KUWABARA]
Quiet!
Kuwabara, don't.
I'm, sorry Sakamoto.
I was wrong.
[SAKAMOTO] What's that?
You were mumbling.
I'm sorry I was wrong!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Whoa.
This Eikichi girl must be
somethin' special to
make him sink that low.
You're pathetic.
Ya' might as well give
us your backbone too.
I just can't believe
you're doing all that
for a retarded fuzz-ball.
Eikichi!!!!
Please don't hurt her! I'll
do anything you want me to do!
How did such a pathetic loser
become boss on this turf?
Hey who you
callin' a pathetic loser!
Kuwabara would knock
your teeth out
if you'd just fight
him like a man!
It's wrong. Playing off
Kuwabara's love for kittens!
You want her?
You mad? Then why don't
you do something terrible?
I think you'll find it fun
if you do it once or twice.
It gives you a
thrill like no other.
Boss sure has gotten
weird in the last couple weeks,
but you gotta admit
he's getting the job done.
At this rate we'll
rule the whole city soon!
[SAKAMOTO'S BOY 1]
Yeah, Kuwabara's a sinch.
I'm just glad that
other guy got hit by a car.
[thugs laugh]
Well let's not
dwell on dead people.
Terrorizing the living
is much more entertaining.
[KUWABARA] Just tell me
what you want, Sakamoto!
I don't care what, as long
as you give me Eikichi.
Good, this will be your last
order. Hit your three friends.
What?
[EIKICHI] They've been staring
at me ever since we met,
I think it's very rude.
So hit them until I say stop.
Now. Hit them.
[KUWABARA] No. I could
never do that to them.
Fine, do it!
[Sakamoto's boy 3 laughs]
Eikichi!!
Hit them! Or else say
goodbye to your cat!
Hit us Kuwabara! We can take it!
We'll just act like
it's Sakamoto hitting us,
and we'll get him back!
That's right. We owe you anyway.
No. That goes against my code.
You heard him! Kill the cat!
Where'd he come from?!
Who the hell is he?
Hi!
[gasps]
It's, that guy!
It's Yusuke Urameshi!
Y-You've really come
back from the dead!
That's right. And I'm in the
mood for a relaxing throw-down!
Let's fight!
You want to tell me I don't
have a spine now? Huh?!
[YUSUKE] Here.
Hold this guy, would ya'?
Hey! It's a she!
Hey! He's going
to miss the best part!
[YUSUKE]
Don't you want to talk?
You know, I think you're right.
I didn't want to
talk to you either.
You're an embarrassment.
And what's with
the little horns, huh?
Whoa. What the
hell is that thing?
What?!
Get your filthy
hands off of me!
Don't you know living
humans can't see me!
And they certainly can't
pick me out of the air!
You're breaking the rules!
You're too big to be a
tapeworm. And you talk.
He even speaks my language!
[BOTAN]
His name is Jyaki.
He is a ruthless criminal.
Wanted for five previous
convictions in the Spirit World.
He burrows into the evil
portions of a human's soul,
and makes them do his bidding.
Hey you're that fortune-teller
from the alley!
[BOTAN] Yes, and you've proven
to be the one we're looking for.
Jyaki is very hard to find
once he's entered a human.
We've been tracking
him for weeks.
But your instincts helped
you catch the criminal,
before you even
knew the crime.
[YUSUKE]
My instincts?
You have all that's required
to be Detective
of the Spirit World.
That's a fancy title.
What do they do?
You'll learn soon
enough, Yusuke.
The appointment is mandatory.
Whoa, slow down! How the
hell do you know my name?
Don't get fussy!
I hope you know mine, too!
Botan! It's you!
There you see,
I knew you'd remember me!
It's only been one day!
Am I in trouble?
[KOENMA]
Yusuke Urameshi!
[KOENMA] Once again
you have surprised me...
...beginners luck I'm sure.
But alas,
you've passed your test,
and since the situation is
rather desperate right now
I'm going to commission you.
You are for the moment the
Spirit Detective of Earth.
And no, it's not
just a fancy title.
You'll get cool powers.
I've come up with them myself.
As the need arises
Botan will supply
you with information
on your cases.
They won't be easy.
I hope you're ready.
[YUSIKE]
Wait!
I'll take this little
guy back to the Spirit World.
You better get a good night's
rest for tomorrow Yusuke!
You just gonna
leave me like this?!
[BOTAN] I promise this will
all make sense very soon!
We'll have so much
fun working together!
[YUSUKE] Well, so much for
the good old R and R.
[BOTAN] Hey everybody!
Trouble awaits on the
next Yu Yu Hakusho.
Yusuke gets his first big
case as Spirit Detective,
and I'm afraid it's
gonna be a doozy.
Three master criminals have
escaped into the living world,
and they've each stolen
an enchanted artifact.
We're talking three monsters
with magical powers
and superhuman strength,
lugging around weapons that
can steal human souls!
Not exactly a case
for a rookie, right?
Can our Yusuke
survive a crook
who transforms into
a demon juggernaut?
I hope you're as
worried as I am!
♪