[NARRATOR]
Yusuke Urameshi is dead,
a loss that has spurred his
friends to new levels of power
as they chased Sensui
through the completed tunnel.
In Spirit World, King Yama
declared a state of emergency
and dispatched the elite
Special Defense Force to Earth.
While Kuwabara used
his powerful new sword
to destroy the Kekkai Barrier
and propel himself,
Kurama, and Hiei
into Demon World.
But with Sensui's Sacred Armor,
victory seems unreachable.
[grunts]
[KUWABARA grunts]
So... Anyone got an idea?
I'm sorry you feel
so much dedication
to your misguided cause.
It pains me, for your
hearts are noble.
[SENSUI] I used to be
a pawn, like all of you.
It's not too late
to save yourself.
You know, I gave up
worrying about dying
a long time ago, Sensui...
And I care even
less about the pain
it's gonna involve
getting there,
as long as I take your hide
along with me when I go!
So you better be ready
to meet your doom!
[yells]
[KURAMA grunts]
[KUWABARA yells]
[KUWABARA groans]
[KURAMA grunts]
[gasps]
[yells]
Damn it!
[grunts]
[groans]
[KAYKO]
Puu...! Puu!
Oh, what's the matter with him?
And why won't he wake up?
Uh...
[KAYKO]
He's cold.
But... if that's really true...
...then, Yusuke is...!
That's not what that means.
I-I'm sure he's just fine.
[KAYKO]
What's happening?
[BOTH gasp]
[KAYKO grunting]
He's moving on his own...
I-I... can't...
...hold on to him much longer!
Don't go away, Puu!
I can't... lose you, too!
No!
How tough can it
be to trail him?
Yeah.
I don't get it...
He's too young to be dead.
[KOENMA] No, what I mean
is that even though
his heart's stopped, his ghost
has yet to rise out of him.
[SEA MAN]
And that's not... normal?
It usually emerges immediately,
and the last time Yusuke died,
his ghost popped
right out of him.
Wait!
If he's come back before,
maybe he's not really dead.
No, trust me kid.
He's dead as a doornail.
His soul is just MIA.
Huh?
Do you think that could be
Mr. Urameshi's ghost?
Who are these people?
Are they on our side?
They're called the
Spirit World Special
Defense Force.
They're the best of the best,
and Spirit World's
last line of defense.
My father only calls upon them
in the most desperate
of situations,
and I guess this hole qualifies.
He depends on
them, unequivocally,
to get the job done.
Which means, my father
has given up faith
in my ability to do so.
I need three of you
to start on sealing up
this hole right now.
Saitou, Sourai, Oohou!
How long will that take you?
Sir, with the three
of us working together,
it should take at
least ten days, sir.
You've got a week.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir!
[OOTAKE]
That's what I like to hear.
Now, get on with it!
As long as that hole's
open, anybody can get out.
Ryuuhi, Rinbai, Shunjun.
Kill anything that
passes through.
Sir, of course, sir.
[OOTAKE]
Koenma, sir. Are you all right?
[KOENMA]
Well, I did bite my tongue...
Return to Spirit World at once,
where you can recuperate.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is my mess, and I'm
gonna clean it up.
Forgive me, Your
Highness, but I'm afraid
that I must insist,
for King Yama has declared
this a state of martial law.
Meaning, for now, my
jurisdiction supercedes yours.
I'm sorry about this, sir.
I know what martial law is,
Captain, I'm no idiot.
But you are if you think for
a second I'm gonna back off
without a fight.
If you refuse to vacate,
you'll have to witness
something very painful.
Are you... threatening
me now, Captain?
[OOTAKE]
Hm...
[gasps] Your High Majesty
King Yama, sir...
I'm not certain I
understand your orders.
[KING YAMA]
I'm authorizing all acts done
by necessity in defense
of the commonwealth
of the Living World.
Your prime objective is to
terminate Yusuke Urameshi.
[OOTAKE]
Pardon my impudence, sir,
but doesn't Detective Urameshi
fight for our side? And win?
In fact, his track record
is most impressive--
for a human, that is.
Oh, but that's where
you are wrong...
He has the half-breed's blood
coursing through his veins.
A real half-breed? No...
Hey, goldilocks...
get outta the way.
[groans]
Stop! He's just a kid!
No one will stand in
the way of our mission...
...to kill Urameshi.
What?
[OOTAKE] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi...
...a direct descendant
of the Mazoku.
You're out of your mind!
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
[SHIZURU]
He's finally come to a stop.
But, why would he stop here?
[BOTH yelp]
Now that's somethin'
you don't see everyday.
And Yusuke...?
[KOENMA]
That is a vile accusation.
And to level it in front of
his corpse? It's ridiculous!
His mother may act
like a monster,
but his parents are human!
I had an ogre do
a background check.
[OOTAKE]
True.
As were his grandparents
and great grandparents.
But if you continue
back much further...
[gasps]
The Atavism... of the Mazoku.
That's afirmative, sir...
It's through that rare
phenomenon that we think
Urameshi inherited
his demon blood.
And if we're right,
which by all signs we are,
he's a genetic time bomb
just waiting to trigger.
[NARRATOR]
DNA: The blueprint for life,
passed from parent to child.
An atavism is when a trait
recurs in a descendant
after skipping generations.
This can even result in a
reversion to the primitive
characteristics of
a remote ancestor.
The Atavism of the
Mazoku, or half-breed,
is an extreme example.
The Mazoku can deliberately
transmit its DNA
recessively until it reaches
an heir strong enough
to succeed it,
creating a Demon sleeper.
[OOTAKE] The first time he died,
he wasn't strong enough
to awaken the beast within him,
which is why he
came back as a human
when you revived him.
Inadvertently, though,
through his training
as a Spirit Detective, we've...
...amended that deficiency.
Now, there's nothing to
stop that Mazoku gene
from rearing it's ugly
head, except for us.
And if your father,
King Yama, hadn't detected
trace amounts of the same
Demon energy shooting out
from Urameshi and the tunnel...
Well...
We could've defeated
one rogue Spirit Detective
only to give rise to
another, more powerful one.
Thank goodness we arrived
in time to prevent it.
And my father is certain
about all of this?
[OOTAKE]
Yes.
Forty-four generations ago,
before the Kekkai separated
the Living and Demon Worlds...
That's when the Mazoku planted
the seed of evil that's now
ready to bloom within him.
Which is why we must
destroy his corpse!
You'll have to do it
over my dead body!
[KOENMA]
Huh?
You all should be
ashamed of yourselves.
Insinuating that he's
a monster, or a traitor,
or anything other than
what he really is: a hero.
Who do you think he's
been fighting for?
Who do you think he
selflessly gave his life for?
And this is how you reward him?!
It doesn't matter
what's in your blood!
All that matters is
what's inside your heart!
Yeah, like we're gonna trust you
as a good judge of character.
We know all about the
last Spirit Detective
you got involved with,
and as far as I'm concerned,
you're still an enemy
of this mission.
Get your men in check, Captain.
I know the severity
of this situation.
That's why cooler
heads must prevail,
and regardless of
your thug's opinion...
Mr. Mitarai has proven himself
an honorable ally of my
Spirit Detective outfit.
And as for Yusuke...
If what you're saying is true,
it's my fault for missing it.
I won't let him suffer for that.
We will find another
solution, Captain,
because that is
what civilized--!
[OOTAKE]
Forgive me, sir.
[groans]
This is treason.
As a leader, I'm sure
you appreciate
the difficult choices
I have to make.
But this is in the best
interest of Living World.
[SOLDIER B]
Captain!
Look at Urameshi! He's glowing!
No, it's time!
That's not Spirit Energy he's
emitting--it's Demon Energy!
The transformation has begun!
[gasps]
Fire!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
We're gonna die!
Stop pissin' your
pants and fire!
Keep on firing!
Stop it!
[YUSUKE]
Man, you people sure know
how to make a guy feel welcome.
We're... too late...
The Mazoku is alive!
Puu! Puu!
Hey there, little buddy.
I see you've been drinking your
milk while I've been away.
Ya know, even though I was dead,
I could still heard some of
what you guys were sayin'.
So then... I'm...
some kind of evil,
vicious monster...
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[YUSUKE] My teachers have
been sayin' that for years.
I just thought it was
a figure of speech.
[SOLDIERS yelp]
[OOTAKE]
You see, Koenma, sir,
how strong his Demon Energy is?
No... Not Yusuke.
Your... Supreme Evilness...
I'm your humble servant!
Please allow me to do
whatever it is you desire.
[YUSUKE] Thanks, weakling,
but for what I desire,
I don't need any help.
For, what I desire...
...is ending the world
and everyone in it.
For I am the mighty
Mazoku, lord of evil!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[YUSUKE] And now, after
hibernating for more
than 1,000 years, I will
finally reveal my true form.
[laughs]
[SOLDIERS yelping]
[YUSUKE]
Psyche! Jeeze, you're gullible!
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?!
Hey, Koenma...
You didn't really think
I'd turned bad, right?
Well d-- Well, no...
Anyway, I better push
off to Demon World...
Sensui gave me a death
sentence as a gift,
and I'd be a jerk if I
didn't return the favor.
But, you can't go anywhere!
You have to be quarantined.
You even think
about stopping me,
and I'll bite off your
head, mustache and all!
[yelps] I knew you couldn't
hide your true character.
You've transformed
into a demon menace.
Look, jerk.
Gimme a break, it's
called a running joke.
I'm the same.
"Yusuke Urameshi, fearless
protector of the good stuff,
with a healthy kick of nastiness
and a general hate
for authority."
And nothing as trivial
as a violent death
or a few drops of Demon's
blood mixed in with mine
is gonna keep me from
helping out my friends
in savin' the world and
kickin' the bad guy's ass!
[sighs, laughs]
Hold on! I'm comin' with you!
Huh? But, sir!
You would be disobeying a
direct order from King Yama!
Besides this hostile beast--
Pass this to King Yama for me.
[groans]
Sir!
Captain?
Are you all right?
[KOENMA]
You really should wash your feet
more often, Yusuke.
Koenma, I've tried to save you!
You can tell King Daddy that...
And that he can
disown me or fire me
or put me up for adoption!
Mitarai, we'll come
back for you soon.
Let's go to Demon World, Puu!
[PUU screeches]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Now, Yusuke...
You do understand
there's a good chance
we won't be able to go back...
Yeah, shut up.
I can't worry about that now.
Remind me after
we've beaten Sensui.
[chuckles] You are as
irrational as ever!
Ha! Like I'm gonna
give that up.
It's the only thing that
makes this job any fun!
Come on, Puu! Faster!
[PUU screeches]
[YUSUKE]
I'm coming for you, Sensui.
[RINBAI] This baby-sitting
detail is the dullest yet.
There's nothing coming out.
[SHUNJUN]
Of course not.
They may be dumb,
but they're not suicidal.
I'll bet those Demons got one
whiff of us and turned tail
faster than you can say chicken.
Even A-Class Ghosts tell
stories about the SDF.
We're their boogiemen.
[RINBAI]
Ha!
They're prob'ly even sicker
of hearing about the time
you cornered the
Spirit Fox than we are!
[SHUNJUN]
Shut up!
[gasps]
Something with immense
Demon Energy's
approaching the perimeter.
Where?
[RINBAI] Hm... It's
coming from Living World!
Impossible...
There are no Demons that
powerful in Living World.
[YUSUKE]
Hey, tool brigade!
Get outta the way!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[YUSUKE] And get some cooler
uniforms while you're at it!
That's one big Spirit Animal.
I think that was Prince Koenma.
And that Mazoku,
Urameshi, was with him!
[RYUUHI] That's where the
Demon Energy was coming from.
[SHUNJUN]
We're all doomed.
[SENSUI chuckles]
I apologize if I
happened to have
caused you any harm.
Kill us if you're going to.
Just spare us the
sound of your voice.
[KURAMA grunts]
Physical strength is greater
than ours, at the
moment. That's all.
Unfortunately...
...that's the only thing that
matters here in Demon World.
[KUWABARA]
I'm sorry, Urameshi.
I failed you.
[SENSUI]
I am merciful.
I want to relieve
you of your misery.
Huh?
What's that?
A great Demon Energy...
And it's coming
from the other side.
[SENSUI]
It can't be...
Huh?
I'm sorry I got delayed.
Traffic was a bitch.
But I'm back! And I'm
ready to finish this!
[PUU screeches]
[NARRATOR] One is a human
who fights to liberate
Demons and destroy his own kind.
The other is part Demon
who fights on behalf
of the Living World.
The final battle between
Sensui and Yusuke
is about to begin.
[YUSUKE]
I'm back from the dead... again.
But did you ever doubt it--
I mean, it's my freakin' story!
Well, death's the closest
thing you get to vacation
in the Spirit Detective racket,
so no sooner am I back
than I'm raising my fists.
But don't relax yet.
Even though I'm
coming fully loaded
with these new Demon powers,
it may not be enough
against Sensui's Sacred Energy.
But something feels wrong,
and a voice in my head
isn't making it any better.
It's a battle inside me
and a war without,
next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!