♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi,
Kuwabara, and
the Masked Fighter
are locked in a battle royale
with three human
killing machines.
After learning his opponents
were pure-hearted men
tricked into mind-control
by the evil Dr. Ichigaki,
Kuwabara refused to fight,
and instead pleaded for
their humanity to return.
But the influence
of the Verrucae
pumping control into their
blood was far too great,
and despite their true
selves crying in agony,
they have seriously
wounded Kuwabara.
Now, as the men beg to die,
Yusuke is faced with
doing the unthinkable.
Kill us.
It really is cruel,
to be controlled by
an ugly troll like him.
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
His power keeps rising.
Maybe this heart-wrench
is exactly what he needs.
It would better if I
could kill you Ichigaki!
Last chance!
Grizzly Claw!
[YUSUKE THINKS] It's just
like an energy bomb
in his hand!
Angel Blades!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Only
two of the blades are real.
The others must be tricks
to confuse us.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
And jerk number three...
...looks like we're featuring
the old energy javelin.
Invisible Slash!
Absolutely amazing!
Suddenly wonder boy
Yusuke's taking on the
whole team by himself!
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS] Yusuke's
power is reaching a plateau.
He's learned about as
much as he can from this.
It's time.
[ALL] Kill us.
It's been real fun,
but I'll see you in Hell!
Remind me to
apologize to you then!
[MASKED FIGHTER] Wait!
It's alright.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I-I
can't move my arm!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Let me take over from here.
Heads up!
The mysterious fighter's
mask is back on her face
and she's stopped Yusuke's new
attempt to fire his Spirit Gun!
She's squaring up!
Could she just want
some action for herself?
What do you think
the Masked Fighter
is planning
to do now, sir?
They were perfectly innocent
until that doctor tricked them!
Killing them wouldn't be fair!
[KOENMA] Obviously, but then
the completely fair choice
may not be an available one.
Death seems to
be the only option.
But if that's true then
why did she stop Yusuke!
Nothing makes sense!
[KOENMA]
Don't be hysterical.
I assure you the Masked Fighter
is someone we can trust.
Take it easy.
[KUWABARA]
Don't let them...
They're going to do
whatever they can, Kuwabara.
The doctor.
Don't let him leave!
Don't worry, I'll stop
him myself if I have to!
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs]
Neither of you have the stomach!
You can't kill these humans!
You know it'd be wrong!
The only choice is
to accept your defeat!
[Dr. Ichigaki laughs]
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Okay mystery lady...
What ever your
gonna do, do it fast!
Mei In Metsu Jyu--
Retsai Ko--
Ki Ki Kyou Chou Chim--
Com Mei, Ei Kyaku!
The Masked Fighter's
chanting something now!
Let's hope it's a final prayer
for the men she's about to kill!
Damn... And here I was
thinking I was impressive!
Ogre! What's going on here?!
Lots of energy, sir.
It's a hoax!
Don't let it frighten you!
I've gauged this
fighter's strength!
She doesn't have enough power
to create an attack that big!
It's just for intimidation!
Attack her!!!
While the Masked
Fighter's hands are tied up
the Dr. Ichigaki
Team is charging!
Looks like another slaughter!
[ALL]
Kill!!
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Kou!
Jyou!
Sai!
What the hell was that?
You wiped 'em out in one shot!
All their Spirit Energy's gone!
There's nothing left of them.
Yes, an immense attack.
What the--?
My perfect inventions!
How can you destroy scientific
achievements with chanting?
Hey! What did
you do to those guys?!
Why'd you hold me back if
you were just gonna kill 'em!
[MASKED FIGHTER] I did what
I had to. Nothing more.
[KOTO] Wow! I have
no idea what happened,
but I definitely love it!
Let's see, there
was a blast of light,
some heart-piercing,
exploding Verrucae,
and now just one
thing to do! One!
Two!
[KOENMA] I told you the Masked
Fighter would handle it.
You told me we could trust her!
She just killed innocent people!
No offense, Koenma sir,
but I don't think I want
to root for your team anymore!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten! And the Urameshi
Team wins the match!
[KOTO] Hate
'em all you want,
but you better buy some
water for those throats!
'Cause you'll be
screaming for a while
if they keep getting
victories like that!
Oh shut up Fox-Girl!
That was no victory!
No, it's all a sham.
We're supposed to be the good
guys. We should have saved them!
Stupid doc pushin' this on us!
Stupid Dark Tournament!
Hey! Asshole!
You know you're not walking
away from this, don't you?
Don't embarrass yourself.
Acknowledge your cruelty and
your punishment will be swift.
Hold on!
What if I told you that their
Master Mitamura was still alive?
But I am the only
person in the world
who knows where he's hidden
and how to reverse his disease!
Sorry, moot point.
You, evil man!
What? But how did he get here?
Your assistant was
in the mood to talk.
[M-5 cries out at each punch]
Yes, that's very good!
Now tell us where Mitamura is!
Your tail is next.
I don't remember exactly!
It's some cave!
[HIEI] His memory
improved very quickly.
We only had to walk
two miles to find him.
After seeing
Mitamura's symptoms
Kurama was easily
able to make an antidote.
I acquired a few poisonous
herbs as well on this island.
Care to try one doctor?
No need for that Kurama.
You ready to die?!
You're pathetic little minds.
Did you really think
I would experiment
with body manipulation--
And not save some for myself?
Yet another
brilliant development
from the incredible
mind of Dr. Ichiga--!
[DR. ICHIGAKI]
Instant gene therapy!
It's a Dr. Ichigaki
metamorphosis!
Now he's some kind of
giant green killer monster
with incredibly
sharp fingernails!
Did you mindless, puny creatures
actually think you could
stop the progress of science!
Let me show you
my modifications!
Amazing!
Ichigaki's stretching out
his arm like it's warm putty!
Yusuke!
[YUSUKE] Hiei, wait.
I've got dibs on this jerk.
Yusuke's back up!
Despite the delicious outpouring
of blood from his arm!
And what's more, he's
asking Hiei to withdraw!
Does he really want to take
this beast on by himself?
Just don't get killed.
Go ahead then. Defy all logic!
What's this?
That was for the three
innocent lives you stole!
[YUSUKE] And this one's for
screwing with their master!
Nicely put.
And this is for my friend
who felt sorry for them
and got his ass kicked
into the ground!
Thanks for the
shout out Urameshi.
And the last one's for me!
Just for pissing me off!
[Dr. Ichigaki cries out]
Now you go think about
what you've done Dr. Ichigaki.
[KOTO] Wow,
can I just say--wow?
Doctor Ichigaki has
been totally demolished
by Yusuke's powerful assault!
The crowd is speechless!
He, he did it!
Finally! Now that's
what I call just deserts!
It doesn't matter.
Taking Dr. Ichigaki's life away
is never going them bring back.
Yen. Ryo. Kai.
It's all my fault. How
can I ever forgive myself?
[MASKED FIGHTER] Save your
tears, Mitamura.
Your boys
aren't dead.
Are you kidding?
I-I can move!
Now this is stupid weird!
Kai, Yen!
Hey! Fill me in! I can't
see up there, you know!
We're really alive!
And in complete control!
But, I don't understand.
A few minutes ago their Spirit
Energy was completely AWOL!
[MASKED FIGHTER] Yes,
I guess it worked.
It's been twenty years since
I've used that technique.
I never thought I'd see you.
[M-3]
Master!
[MITAMURA]
Wait! Why do you turn?
We've committed
horrible sins, master.
I can't even remember
all the people that I've--
The lessons that you
taught us didn't mean anything!
We're a disgrace to your dojo!
Please, just leave us Master.
We can't bear
to look at you now!
Damn it! Why couldn't she
have just killed us!
How can you say such things?
[MASKED FIGHTER] Your master is
right. Your guilt is misplaced.
The technique I used
is called the Spirit Wave.
It is one of the five
great attacks by trial,
and is powered by
your own Spirit Energy.
If your souls are corrupt,
then the wickedness
will take your life.
But if you are pure of heart,
then that purity consumes you,
destroying any
outside impediments.
It was your soul that
destroyed the Verruca
and freed you, not me.
That proves you
have nothing to hide.
Yen, Ryo, Kai. She says
what I've known all along.
If there was anything
you could have done
to prevent those
kills, you would have.
[MITAMURA] Your
bodies were taken over.
But who you really are--
your souls--are still clean.
I see you in the same
way now as I always have.
As my three most noble students.
Let's put this behind us!
[ALL]
Master!
[M-1]
We missed you so much!
Master, is it true? Are you
really going to be okay again?
Yes, I think so.
Well mystery lady
that was some attack.
You have done us well, Fighter.
They're so happy!
How come you never
talk to me like that, Ogre?!
They're all okay.
I think letting those
guys beat the snot out of me
is the best
thing I've ever done.
[KOTO] And so, in a
dramatic explosion of emotion
fit to make any demon wretch,
the Urameshi Team
is set to advance!
But the price of victory
hasn't been cheap!
Kuwabara's injuries look severe!
So how's he doing?
Not too great.
It's nothing life threatening
but he's clearly going
to need time to recover.
Time, huh?
Yusuke!
Maybe I could
be of some help!
I'd like to repay
you if it's possible.
We're the ones
who hurt Kuwabara!
Let me fight in his place.
I'll join as your substitute!
Well thanks for the offer.
But this dufus would have
a fit if I gave his spot away.
You understand?
Plus, we're only
allowed one substitute.
And only after one
of our guys is dead.
Urameshi, I'm not dead yet.
Well folks, it's official!
Come on. Let's get
Lazarus off the grass.
You're a good man, but
we got to go this alone.
[M-3]
I understand.
Take care of your master.
I'd say he's the one
that needs you most now.
Right?
Of course, well good luck.
Maybe we'll see
you again someday!
[angry crowd]
Oh shove it where it hurts!
[bells ring]
[SPEAKER] May I have
your attention please.
The third round of
the Dark Tournament
will begin immediately.
What? Give me a break!
[SPEAKER] Furthermore,
The Tournament Committee
has unanimously decided
to begin the round in accordance
to the match diagram,
starting from the left.
Team Urameshi and Team Masho,
please report to the ring.
What? Again?
Hey! Why don't you tell
your stupid friends up there
to let one of the
other teams fight!
I'm sorry sir.
If you have a complaint
you'll have to take
it up with the committee.
I'm sure there's a perfectly
good reason for their decision!
Get over there and fight
you ignorant little cry-babys!
This is a demon's tournament!
You're fighting under our rules!
It's perfect! Kill 'em
while they're all worn out!
Rip off their ugly heads!
[MASKED FIGHTER THINKS]
I suspected they'd pull this.
Two of our members are hurt,
and after the
Spirit Wave technique,
I will be of
little help as well.
Yes. Your luck
is very poor, Yusuke.
But think of how
much stronger you'll be
when you meet me in the end.
Okay, if a doubleheader's
the call I might as well enjoy.
I've got plenty of anger left
from the troll doctor, anyway.
[angry crowd]
[KUWABARA]
Botan, help me.
It's about to start. I need
you to help me get there.
[BOTAN] No can do, sport.
You're in no shape to fight!
The best thing you can do
now is focus on your recovery.
But we're all stuck in
this thing together, Botan!
I can't just lie
down in some sickbed
and listen to my teammates
fighting for their lives!
Team Masho! This is your final
call! Enter or be disqualified!
[KOTO] And here
they are, people!
Appearing in the same mysterious
fashion as always! Team Masho!
Why do you I get the feeling.
This is gonna be a tough one?
[NARRATOR] As the powers
residing over the tournament
continue to rule against them,
Yusuke and his haggard team
must begin a new battle while
still exhausted from the last.
The opponent is Team Masho.
What secrets do they hold?
[KOENMA] Koenma here,
and I'm pretty peeved.
My team's match
against the strange
Team Masho is beginning,
and Kurama is
stepping up first.
Everyone in this wicked sect
is a skilled
master of something,
and for Gama, it
happens to be makeup.
Weird and harmless enough,
unless this demon paint
can paralyze any part of a
fighter's body it touches!
See Kurama fight
for his life
while unable to
use his legs or arms!
While outside the ring,
Hiei and the Masked
Fighter succumb to a very,
how do you say,
provocative trap.
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪