♪
[NARRATOR] The Ice Apparition
Yukina, Hiei's sister,
is still imprisoned in
the mountain stronghold
of Gonzou Tarukane.
But Yusuke and Kuwabara
have quickly cut through a
small army of twisted demons,
and have reached the
compound's front gate.
Now they must face opposition
far above what they have seen.
Three demons notorious
in the criminal underworld--
known as the Triad.
Which of you strapping lads
will I have the
pleasure of fighting first?
No way! You are a girl!
We can't fight girls--
it's against my code!
Come on, Urameshi.
Let's just walk past her.
[MIYUKI] Ooh, a gentleman.
A pawn of insecure males
seeking to own their women.
Whoa whoa! I don't know
anything about that, okay!
Guys just don't fight girls!
I'll fight with you.
Urameshi, are you serious??
She's a fighter and she's
trying to get in our way.
I don't care if
she's a girl or a baby
or somebody's grandmother.
I'll still knock her out.
Oh, I love your style.
It's an equal playing
field and anything goes!
Well let me check
first to make sure.
You pervert! What was that?
Now I know.
Hey... I don't get it.
What just happened?
[YUSUKE] Hey lady! You've got
no chance of winning this fight!
Oh, shut up!
You never would have
done that if I were a man!
What did she mean by that?
i don't know...
Oh my gosh! I'm pretty sure he
grabbed Miyuki's... uh...
Well it serves you right to
get choked Urameshi
[MIYUKI] I'm going
to enjoy this.
Maybe he should
try apologizing to her.
Oh... be quiet.
What a broad!
If you wanted
to hang out together,
you should've just asked!
Hello!
[YUSUKE] Hey! Where 'ya goin'?
Let's hang out!
Ah! Urameshi! How can you
keep hitting a girl like that!
I mean you even
hit her in the ta-tas!!!
Give me a break!
You want me just to stand
still while she reams me!
I don't know!!!
All I'm sayin' is that boys
aren't allowed to hit girls!!!
We're both fighters! Why the
hell does it make a difference!
You yell
way too much.
Okay that's it!
You and me gotta
duke it out right now
so I don't get nauseous!
Even if she was attacking you,
you don't have to knock her
head through a wall you bully!
Fine, I wasn't
gonna tell you this
'cause I still don't
think it matters.
But look closely...
It turns out our Mrs. is a Mr.
Oh!
But how did you... know?
Well--uh--I really
couldn't help but notice...
Wait a sec.
[YUSUKE] Okay, I admit.
I was curious.
Things didn't seem right
up-top, and, uh... well...
...you know.
The family jewels
have not been stolen.
So fighting girls actually
does bother you,
but you gave her a check-up
instead of attacking her...
You're kind of weird
person, aren't you?
[MIYUKI] You think I'm
a freak, don't you?
That's why you're
attacking so violently!
What? You're afraid
I'll rub off on you?
Why can't you
treat me as an equal?
Shut up!
If you're going to be
a man, do it all the way!
Not half way!
I'm fighting you because you
won't let us save that girl!
It's got nothing to do
with anything except for
me kicking your ass!
You positive
about this Urameshi?
She looks so--I mean he
looks so--uh--pretty.
I mean... are you
sure that she's uh...
[smash]
You jerk!
Hey look, a camera!
Two more and we're
coming after you!
[laughing]
That must be rather
embarrassing for you!
Now what were
the bids again?
I bet five hundred
million on the demons.
Yes, so did I.
You know if everyone
bet on the demons
Tarukane might make money!
[CLUB MAN 3] Well the four of us
did! That's good for him!
But I bet twenty
billion on the intruders.
[CLUB MAN 1] I'd expect you to
be more pale, Tarukane.
These intruders seem
to be eradicating
all of your
defenses.
And at the
doubled stakes,
you will owe Sakyou
over forty billion in bets.
He's got a good point.
Maybe you should grab
those Hiruiseki stones
and get off the mountain
while you still can!
You've got to be kidding me!
The real game is just beginning!
A sugar-coated
strawberry rice-cake!
My servant must have stood
in line for a week to get this!
You just can't
beat royal treatment!
Aren't you gonna at least take
out your pacifier first, sir?
What's it to you, Blue-boy?
Oh, it's uh nothing sir.
I just think if I got to eat
so much good food like you,
I'd appreciate it more.
Really?
Well then perhaps you'd like
to make a little wager with me.
Who prevails?
Yusuke's team or the Triad?
The winner takes the cake.
Oh thank you sir!
That's so very gracious of you!
Now let me see, I think I'll
bet on Yusuke's team to win!
Nope, can't do that!
I've already decided
that I will bet on Yusuke!
I will!
I will!!
No I will!!
[BOTH] Rock paper scissors!
I've been thinkin' about what
you did back there, Urameshi...
You know... I mean the
way you checked to see
if Miyuki was a boy.
What would you
have done if it'd actually
been a girl you were touching.
Think about it stupid!  Like I
would've have complained!
Keiko's not gonna
like hearing that!
You wouldn't dare tell
Keiko that for real!
Well there is this
new CD I want
and I haven't had enough
money to buy it...
[YUSUKE] And you want
me to buy it for you?
Would you boys knock it off!
We are supposed
to be rescuing Yukina!
That's right! I don't have
time for this! Okay!
Here goes!
By my red pinky string
I'm led to my heart's content!
Another snowstorm is coming.
You'll have to
find someplace warm.
We have to say goodbye
to each other now.
Well, goodbye.
[BOTAN] This way.
[KUWABARA] Move!
Someone's here.
[INMAKI] Demon two of
the Triad, Inmaki.
[INMAKI]
I'm sorry I missed.
You just tore up the Great
Fighting Headband of Love.
You're dead!
That was weird.
Can you sense where
this guy is hiding?
Nuh-uh, he's too fast. It
feels like he's all around us.
You okay?
Let's run!
[Inmaki laughs]
[INMAKI]
Yes, the old cat and mouse.
Botan, take this next corner!
[BOTAN]
Right!
[INMAKI]
There's nothing you can do!
[Inmaki laughs]
Okay! He's here!
Shot gun!!!
Kind of a cheap move when
you don't even have to aim!
What??
[INMAKI]
What?
When there was
only one direction
you could come from it was easy!
I just had to sense your
Spirit Energy round the corner.
And taking my cue
from Kuwabara here,
I just fired a
major Shotgun blast
to cover the whole
stretch of the hallway.
Clever, huh?
One more!
[laughter]
Yeah! Pound 'em Yusuke!
Now Koenma sir,
you do remember that
if Yusuke beats the Triad
I get to eat your sugarcoated
strawberry rice cake, right?
[KOENMA]
I quit this bet.
But sir!
Everyone knows if you quit a bet
you have to swallow
a thousand needles!
Oh I forgot!
[KOENMA] Ogre, I hate you.
Watch out!
[Gokumonki laughs]
The name's Gokumonki,
third demon of the Triad.
I'll write it
on your gravestone!
Are you sure you
won't hit your friend?
Yes, good question!
Ah, dirty trick!
[Gokumonki laughs]
Spirit Sword!!!
Very good!
What the hell was that?
I was afraid of hitting Botan!
I must've held
back too much energy!
Kuwabara!
Hey!!
Can you get up?
You don't have the nerve to
attack me as long as I have her!
Shoot!
Unless you have another plan,
I'm going to start the crushing!
Botan, raise your arms!
Stu-pid!
Oh, yeah!
What a win, sir!
Did you see that?!
[KOENMA] Well of course I did!
Don't ask silly questions--
Obviously I did a good
job selecting Yusuke!
What happened to my sugarcoated
strawberry rice cake??
My goodness! I must have
accidentally eaten it just now!
You see I get so very
excited when Yusuke wins
that my hand just starts
throwing things in my mouth!
You really
think I'm stupid.
Get ready Tarukane!
We're coming to get you!
You!
[TARUKANE THINKS] ] I never
dreamed they'd be this strong!
[CLUB MAN 3] I'd say that wraps
up our bet with the demon Triad!
Yes, and it appears
I've won again.
Perhaps you should
quit now, Tarukane.
That brings my winnings
up to fifty billion.
Speak for yourself, Sakyou.
You may have raked in a fortune,
but the rest of us haven't been
so lucky! We gotta keep playing!
Sakyou seems to have the
inside track on these fights.
I say we all bet on
whatever team he does
and make back all of our money!
Well you better do
it all in one shot,
because there's
only one more bet!
Yes brother, now it's
finally our turn to fight.
Who will win the final
battle, the intruders,
or the Toguro Brothers?
[TARUKANE THINKS] Only I know
the Toguro's true power.
They'll bet a few
billion on the intruders,
and I'll make my money back!
All eyes are on you,
Sakyou. What's the call?
Sixty-six trillion
and two hundred million.
[SAKYO]
Sixty six trillion,
two hundred million on
the intruders' victory.
Sixty six trillion,
two hundred million???
No way!
That's a ridiculous
amount of money!
He couldn't
possibly back that up!
That's unheard of!
It's more than Japan's
Gross National Product!
It's more than
any country's product!
But by my calculations.
That is your Gross Product
if you include the
Hiruiseki Stone creator.
[CLUB MAN 1] Interesting. So
Tarukane really could pay.
[CLUB MAN 2] He'd have to sell
even the fillings in his teeth,
but he could do it!
[CLUB MAN 3] And that
means he has to accept the bet!
The rest of us won't gamble.
We'll just watch as one
of you is permanently ruined.
[TARUKANE THINKS]
What's Sakyou up to?
Is it possible he knows
something I don't about this?
[TARUKANE THINKS] Ah, who
am I kidding! He's just cocky.
I'm the only one
who's knows the truth--
and when I win this bet,
I'll have more money
than anyone ever!!
Fine! I'm takin' your bet!!
Now you better not let me down!!
[TUGURO 2] It's been
ages since I've been
contracted for such a fight!
I might enjoy myself.
Sakashta.
Have Yukina brought to me.
And don't you let the Black
Black Club know she's the one.
We are all going to have to play
our cards very carefully now.
All we gotta do
is stop Tarukane!
And that'll be easy-greasy!
[beeping]
Maybe not!
What now?
Hold on. Yeah I
can definitely feel it.
They're moving Yukina!
How can you tell?
We're attached, remember?
Let's see if I
can get her attention.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Yukina.
Calling all Yukinas.
Can you hear me?
Yukina!
[YUKINA THINKS] Who are you?
It's me! Kuwabara!
[YUKINA THINKS] Kuwabara?
Do I know you?
She said my name!!!
Never fear! I am Kuwabara!
I have come here for you!
And with my sensitive
eye and big shiny sword.
I will save you!
Then we can date, right?
[YUKINA THINKS]
Please! Go away!
Uh--what did you say?
Oh the pain!!
[YUKINA THINKS] No one
must ever come near me.
You'll only be killed!
They've hired terrible guards!
[HUWABARA THINKS] Don't worry!
We've already taken
care of them all!
[YUKINA THINKS]
No. You're wrong.
The worst ones are
standing right next to me!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
There must be a mistake.
I don't even sense
their Spirit Energy!
[KUWABARA THINKS] Look baby,
we'll be there soon!
[Toguro 1 laughs insanely]
I've got a definite
lock on her now!
And I don't care if
she wants us to or not,
we're saving my love!!
Hurry!
[YUSUKE] Ooh! A basement!
So this is her filthy prison.
I, can't believe
they would be here!
[HIEI THINKS] Yukina
hold on, I'm coming.
[YUSKE] What are these things?
[BOTAN]
Disgusting, I'd say.
Come on guys! We don't
have time for that!!
The door's closing.
Hurry!!
I take it we
have one more fight.
Forget it.
Their total Spirit Energy
couldn't hurt a wingless fly!
[KUWABARA] There she is!!
Don't worry. We're
coming for you soon!
Both the brothers are fighting?
I feel sorry for Yusuke.
Are you sorry,
for the rice cake?
Welcome, try not to be
too hard on us--We're fragile.
[NARRATOR]
Everyone seems to know
the Toguro Brothers' reputation.
Except for the two boys
about to fight them.
Can Yusuke and Kuwabara
overcome this strange pair?
And what exactly is the
secret behind their power?
[BOTAN] What a fight!
We've got two demon brothers
versus two human friends,
punching it out over
an ice apparition who,
let's not forget,
is Hiei's sister!
But before Hiei crashes
the party--which he will--
You'll be amazed at how
the Toguro Brothers fight,
giving a whole
new meaning to teamwork!
Our side is clearly outmatched,
but Kuwabara's emotions
will unlock a level of power
he's never reached before!
Don't miss this dynamite
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪