♪
[NARRATOR] Attempting to triumph
where Kuwabara had failed,
Genkai entered the ring
with Shishiwakamaru.
His Banshee Shriek
Sword proved to be lethal,
taking its toll on the crowd.
But Genkai, impaired
without her Spirit Wave,
siphoned off Shishi's energy
and used it to blow him away.
With their front
man defeated,
only one man remained
on Team Uraotogi:
the true brains behind
their operation, Onji,
who is about to
face off with Kuwabara.
Bring it, Onji!
If you've still got it!
And by the
unquestionable authority
of randomly rolled dice,
Kuwabara and Onji will
fight, starting right now!
[KEIKO THINKS]
Get your sleep, Yusuke.
[Demons laughing wickedly]
[GREMLIN]
Isn't that sweet?
PORKEY] Hey there, mon ami.
We've been looking for
something fun to do.
Why don't you drop the
dead weight and come with us?
If it isn't...
[ALL] Urameshi!
[KONG] You know what this
means for us, don't you boys?
It means all those years
of avoiding steady
employment finally paid off.
Once we whack Urameshi
they'll make us into heroes!
We can have anything we want!
Here's to glory!
Who the--?
[PORKY] It's Rinku!
And Chu, as well!
Am I hallucinating, or
is that Jin and Touya too?
Um, excuse us.
Well, I guess I
owe you a big thanks.
Don't get all mushy and stuff,
lady. It was no big deal.
You're just lucky we
happened to walk by.
[KEIKO] Right. Um, didn't
Yusuke's team beat you guys?
Why are you
helping us?
Now love, your boy did alright
by me, and I don't forget.
What's up?
Why, he seems to have
gotten a might stronger!
A might? How
much is a might?
If I went another
round with him,
I might actually have to try.
I would say you tried
pretty hard before.
[CHU]
Shut your clacker!
Look at him passed out.
He looks just like a
sleeping junior high kid.
Ow! Keiko that
hurt, you louse...
Uh, Yusuke?
Stop treating me like
a baby all the time.
I'm not a kid any... more.
He is so whipped!
I see you've domesticated
our mate nice and fine, missy.
We'll leave you two alone so you
can keep on havin' your naughty!
Why's that all
anyone thinks a
boy and girl
can do alone?
[All laugh]
[KUWABARA] I was gonna
give you a senior discount,
but now it's Spirit time!
A weapon like that must
use up a lot of energy.
Don't burn yourself
out too quickly now.
What?
[ONJI] It might help if
you aim for me.
[ONJI}
Oh, too slow!
Missed me!
[KUWABARA THINKS] Why can't
I keep up with this geezer?
His energy feels
weaker than he looks!
I'm glad he left
the girls outside
and Yukina's not
here to see this.
Go Kuwabara! You can do it!
You can't just wait for him
to die from old age, bro!
You don't want to lose and
disappoint Yukina, do you?
But why would I be
disappointed if he lost a fight?
Oh no, sweetie,
it's not true.
That's just what we
call motivation, you see!
[KOENMA]
This isn't good.
I don't know, sir.
Couldn't you put the seven
of spades on the eight of hearts
and move the ace on top?
I'm not playing
solitaire, you moron!
I'm fortune telling to
see who'll win this match,
but I keep drawing the Joker,
and I have no idea
what that could mean!
Maybe you should
enjoy life more, sir.
[KOENMA] I don't
think that's it.
Where'd you run off to,
you slimy weasel?
I can't fight you
if you vanish!
Oh, is that what
you were doing?
You sir, are a coward, running
and hiding behind the innocent!
Why don't you stand in one
place and fight like a man?
[ONJI]
Alright, crybaby.
I'll stand right here
and promise not to budge.
[KUWABARA] Liar!
My body's not so spry these
days. I could use the rest.
Fine. Stay put exactly
where you are old man!
And I'll help you
rest in pieces!
Don't do it, Kuwabara!
Is that supposed
to scare me?
Spirit Sword!
I can't believe he walked
right into that trap on his own.
He is a first
class fool.
Agreed. A fool
and a moron.
An exciting turn!
Onji's led Kuwabara inside a big
ball, and he can't break free.
Who knows what's planned
for this boy in a bubble?
Hey! Let me outta here
you stupid trickster!
[ONJI]
Don't worry.
This is going to
feel something like
Shishiwakamaru's
Cape of No Return.
You do remember what
that was like, don't you?
After all, that
wasn't very long ago,
and it's tough to forget
being transported through
a different dimension.
Shishi required the piece
of cloth I gave him
to perform this technique,
but since I invented it,
I don't need any props.
The other four members
of Team Uraotogi
were merely fillers so I
could enter the tournament,
but they never amounted
to anything without me
and my gifts.
The Steaming Spheres, The
Idunn Box, the Banshee Shriek.
All specially-tailored
by little old me.
[Onji chuckles]
[KUWABARA]
I'm gonna get you, punk!
[Kuwabara cries out]
I know where
this one's going!
Kuwabara's out of the ring
and won't be back in ten!
The winner's Onji!
Not again!
Where am I?
What? Out of all the places, why
do they keep sending me here?
If they don't think
Kuwabara's cut out
for inter-dimensional travel,
they've got another
thing coming!
Let's go geezer!
Let's see who I'll have the
pleasure of humiliating next.
I've got a faint feeling
in my old trick knee
that it's gonna be you.
Now, I know all the
secrets of the Idunn Box,
and I can change you into
whatever form I please.
So sorry, but you'll have to
fight me in your human form.
Presumptive, considering
you haven't yet rolled.
Careful, Grandma, this
guy's got a couple of aces.
You talk pretty clearly
in your sleep Yusuke.
Careful, you might tell me
something you don't want to.
Puu!
'Course I could always
weasel it out of you.
[Onji laughs]
So it's the Unmasked Warrior's
turn to meet her doom.
Isn't this a riot?
The battle of the elderly!
Why don't you drop your tired
act and lose the disguise.
You won't be fooling anyone
else with that crappy mask.
Disguise?
I don't know who you are,
but you're no old man.
And in case you
haven't noticed,
I'm not the
kind of person
who will underestimate
you based on false age.
You've got a pretty
sharp eye there,
for such an ugly,
worn past-its-prime body.
You're the first to notice.
I even masked my own Energy.
You see, disguise is
one of my favorite hobbies.
To be brutally honest,
there are few things I find
more repulsive than old people.
That moth-ball smell
that hovers around them
makes me absolutely retch.
That's why I chose this getup.
I thought wearing the skin
of something I abhorred
would all the more fuel my rage.
Now...
Fallaces sunt rerum species
tamquam alter idem
flamma fumo est!
[Onji laughs wickedly and it
transitions to another voice]
Thank goodness! Free at last!
A few more minutes
smothered under that mask,
and I might've
got real wrinkles!
I plan to die while
I'm still handsome,
before I show any
signs of aging.
It's the price
artists have to pay.
A harsh fate to accept.
My image is my
greatest masterpiece,
and that is how I plan to live
on as a legend eternitus!
I'm relying on all of you,
the fans, that witness my art
to recount it throughout the
generations and keep me alive!
Ladies and gentlemen,
feast your eyes on
the master of a thousand
faces and tricks,
the one, the only, the
Beautiful Suzuki!
Of course I'd hate to
ruin a piece of art, Suzuki,
but I have no
holdups with you.
You're a piece
of trash.
Never refer to
me by my name alone
without placing
"beautiful" in front of it,
or you won't live to
repeat your mistake.
"Beautiful" is a word
made just for me
and we two shall never part!
Fruitcake!
This idiot makes
Kuwabara seem smart.
I admit, I'm embarrassed
listening to him.
[KOENMA] If he's not the Joker,
I don't know who is.
Can you tell me if I
will find true love?
Well, the decrepit Onji
has transformed into Suzuki.
With an odd, better
make that interesting
wardrobe selection on his part.
That was freakin' sweet!
I've already told you to put a
"beautiful" in front of my name.
It's very important.
Why I like the way this
cracked walnut thinks!
But he's nuts, sir.
Oh, who's to say
who's nuts these days?
From now on, you will
only address me as
"Pretty" Koenma,
understand!
I think "pretty" really brings
out the sparkle in my eyes.
And I just finished
telling mother
my job couldn't
get worse.
For somebody who wants
to be known by the world,
you sure hide behind
a lot of masks.
You must be compensating
for something abysmal.
The greatest legends are
all shrouded in ambiguity.
It seems the imagination is
more captivated by the unknown.
People are simply more inclined
to build up in their own minds
that which they cannot see,
or which have
multiple incarnations.
[SUZUKI] Look at how they fear
the Devil and revere God.
With mystery comes
colossal power!
And that power
will be mine.
In a thousand years
they'll worship me,
and each will have a unique
vision and they'll say,
"The Beautiful Suzuki,
he looked like this!"
And another will say,
"No, he looked like this!"
"No, like this!" "Like this!"
And each vision will be]
grander than the last
and I will live in forever!
I don't get
what's so funny.
I thought clowns made
everybody else laugh.
[SUZUKI] Let it be sung
throughout the land
that upon my victory
at this tournament,
I'll first eradicate the
elderly from the world,
in honor of the
soon-to-be-late Genkai.
And then, I shall strike down
all who refuse to worship me,
the Beautiful Suzuki!
And that will be that.
Go back to the circus!
Obey this, asshole!
I'm not a fan
of insubordination.
This wacko's serious
about this domination stuff.
This sucks. Now we can't
root for either of 'em.
For once they're
showing taste.
[SUZUKI] I guess I
fired 'em up!
So, um, you think
you might be ready?
Yes, let's shut
this jerk up!
Right! Let the battle begin!
You're feeling so confident
because you managed
to defeat my front man.
But while I did teach him
everything that he knew,
I didn't teach
him everything that I do.
Don't even think
of using that same
energy-borrowing stunt on me.
For that to work, you have to
lock onto its exact wavelength,
and as you're no
doubt discovering,
I can disguise
that as well.
You're frustrated!
You can sense how I
have so much energy,
but you can't hone in on it!
Marvel at my art as
I unleash my palette!
I call this one Rainbow Cyclone!
Ha!
[Suzuki laughs insanely]
Oh Genkai!
It seems Suzuki,
I mean it seems the
Beautiful Suzuki
has blasted Genkai with his
gorgeous Rainbow Cyclone.
And he didn't just
knock her to the wall.
He knocked her right
smack through it!
[Suzuki laughs]
[SUZUKI] It's truly a
spectacular attack.
Not only is it lethal,
but it's killer to look at!
All those vibrant colors
are so lovely, aren't they?
Though I'm sure
Genkai didn't think so
as they plunged
through her heart
and blasted her
into that wall!
You! What are
you waiting for?
Oh, right, out of the ring.
I'll start the count.
One...
[SUZUKI] What a
tragedy it's over.
I had nine hundred
ninety-nine more faces
and nine hundred ninety-nine
more tricks I wanted to use!
[JURI]
Five...
Genkai's emerged from
the rubble unharmed.
There's not even a scar or a
deep bloody gash on this woman!
Not that that makes
the Beautiful Suzuki's
beautiful attack
any less beautiful.
Forgive me if
I'm not impressed.
I know, you play
by higher standards,
but at least give
me credit for the nose.
If I'd had more time,
I would've taken that big,
ugly grin off your face too.
But when'd
you do that?
Naturally my eyes could follow
every inch of Genkai's movement.
I saw the
whole thing too.
Kuwabara!
And only five hundred
seconds too late to matter.
[KUWABARA] Hey, where's
that guy I was fighting?
I wasn't done yet!
So which is
more humiliating,
losing to an old
man or to a clown?
A clown, definitely
worse to a clown!
Hey!
You lost a nose.
Who cares?
I've ripped off vital
organs that were real!
But I feel so
naked without it!
[GENKAI] Stop your
whining, you joker.
I put my whole body through
hell to make it strong
enough for my Spirit Wave Orb.
And you're crying about
some nasal accessory.
You're not a real fighter.
I sure as hell won't waste what
little Spirit Energy I have left
on your half-assed routine.
Why, it won't take more than
these two bare, wrinkled fists
to knock that
sissy make-up
right off your face
and onto the concrete,
right next to
your rubber nose.
So come on, kiddo.
No matter what you throw,
I promise not to use any weapon
other than my own muscles
to pound the beauty out of you.
I'm not scared of an old lady.
If you're not using your Spirit
Power then neither will I!
Toguro's got nothing on me!
Welcome to the Body of
Steel Muscle Explosion!
Will you just look at these
magnificent washboard abs?
Watch me now as I
rhythmically flex my pecs!
Featherweight.
Let me tell you what
your problem is, Suzuki.
You didn't say
"Beautiful" before my name?
Admittedly you
have talent.
You helped scrounge up a
team of third-rate demons
and found weapons
suiting them well enough
to get them to
the semifinals.
You know more about
arsenals and techniques
than anyone I've met.
But like a true idiot you
forgot all about your strength.
[GENKAI] You're
nothing but surface.
A souped-up car without
an engine to move it.
You're even weaker
than your front man.
Wow! She's amazing!
And the fact that
he's substandard
doesn't help him much.
You see?
[GENKAI] You just don't
have what it takes!
That's enough.
Oh, I forgot to look at that
so called beautiful face of his.
You okay?
It seems Beautiful Suzuki,
who has a remarkably firm tush,
is pretty much incapacitated,
making Genkai the winner!
Genkai's great!
She is cool.
[FAN] Don't look now,
it's the humans.
Can you believe we
made it to the finals?
You guys were all super!
I got a kick out of
watching you fight, Kazuma.
Why, thank you Yukina.
It's nice to see someone
appreciates my strategy.
See there was no one worth
wasting my energy on,
so I had the bad guys
reveal their weaknesses
so Genkai could knock 'em down.
More like you made a big mess
and Genkai cleaned up after you,
like someone always does.
Hey, that stung!
You take that back, sis!
Just the truth, bro.
Well no one cares!
Actually, I'd like to hear it.
Stay out of this, shorty!
Now children,
behave!
[GENKAI]
I'm leaving.
[KURAMA] It took all
of us working as a team
to make it this far.
[HIEI] Not him!
[KUWABARA] I fought just
as many fights as you did!
[HIEI] And lost them both.
[KUWABARA] Oh yeah?
Well you weren't the one
who had to go spinning
through outer space...
[TOGURO 2] Greetings old friend.
I have to talk to you soon.
I know you do.
[NARRATOR] With
Yusuke still recovering,
his team has advanced to the
Dark Tournament's final round.
But what can Toguro and
Genkai have to discuss?
And will the team be prepared
for their final challenge?
[YUSUKE] Last round,
here we come!
Pretty sweet, right!
And once the other, very
quick semi-final's over,
we'll know which team
we're gonna fight,
Team Toguro or Team...
Yeah right.
Anyway, you're not
watching for the outcome.
You're watching to see
the sickly powerful things
those bad guys
can do to people.
Oh, I see I'm not the only
captain playing hooky from--
Hey wait! What the hell are
those two talking about?
I leave my teacher and
rival for one minute
and well you better watch.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪