♪
[NARRATOR] Jin the Wind
Master is locked in battle with
Yusuke Urameshi in the Dark
Tournament's third round.
Yusuke must win,
as he is the only one left
on his team who can fight.
But Jin's powers are enormous,
and not even a point blank
shot from the Spirit Gun
could penetrate
his defensive wall.
With a violent tornado
circling each arm,
Jin is ready for
his final strike,
and Yusuke is
getting desperate.
Doesn't matter
the ending, Urameshi.
Fight we had was nice
and I see you like myself.
Two whirlwinds
doesn't mean I hate you--
only means I have respect.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Alright, Yusuke,
you've tried everything else.
[DEMON] What the hell
is he doing now?
[MASKED FIGHTER] You might
not be needed, after all.
[MASKED FIGHTER] Yusuke's
Spirit Gun channels his
Spirit Energy into one small
point--his index finger.
But this technique will
turn his entire body
into a channeling weapon.
From what I understand,
he never quite
perfected this with Genkai.
Oh, be careful.
[MASKED FIGHTER] The attack
could be very effective.
If the strain
doesn't kill him first.
Sir, Yusuke's
body is churning out
unbelievable amounts of energy!
He seems a little unstable.
Do you suppose this is safe?
[sucking sounds]
Honestly sir,
it's hard for me to think
with your sucking noises.
You realize you've been
going like a vacuum cleaner
since Yusuke
started this fight?!
What's with this
pacifier, anyway?
You're too old
for teething!
I really don't
think you need it.
What the...?
[KOENMA] Actually this baby's
got a great amount
of significance for me Ogre,
and yes I thought you'd
pull something like that.
[BLUE OGRE THINKS]
I hate this job.
Now we're
talking Urameshi.
Your wind's
running like a typhoon.
If my ears were any pointier
I'd poke out a person's eye!
Let's have some fun, Jin.
[JIN]
Love to!
Yusuke!
[laughs]
It's all in the bag.
Come Yusuke, let's see
if you're truly capable.
[YUSUKE]
Tornado Fist!!
What you be doing now Yusuke?
Tornado in the hand no one does!
Yusuke hammers
Jin's right fist away,
disabling his first attack!
But there's still another
Tornado Fist in his arsenal!
It's goodbye!
Blocking it again?
[YUSUKE]
Spirit Wave!!!
Rocket Ship. Spectacular!!!
Sorry guys,
but at a punch party like that
a girl can't help but dance!
What a hit!
And here I was thinking
I'd have to go in myself!
[Togoro 2 laughs]
So you really learned her move.
Did you know he could do that?
No way-- He
never tells me nothin'.
I think he likes
surprisin' people.
After that massive
uppercut by Yusuke.
Jin has yet to
return from the sky!
Could he be using
his wind powers again?
Is this marathon
still not over??
What just happened??
I think we better
stand somewhere else.
[SHIZURU]
Now.
Okay.
I wonder where they're going.
Keiko!!
Don't worry,
Shizuru sensed it.
I don't understand--
How can Yusuke do all that?
Jin seems to be out cold,
unable to use his wind
powers to even break his fall!
Gee--I better count!
Impressive, I'd like to
fight this Genkai someday.
[MASKED FIGHTER]
Yusuke did well for a first try.
The Spirit Wave
is a flexible move.
Similar to Yusuke's Shot-gun,
it can make a large spread
if fired from a distance-
Harder for an opponent to dodge,
but not as damaging
as the Spirit Gun.
The true advantage
of the Spirit Wave
comes when it's shot point
blank through a punch or kick.
Genkai believes
Yusuke has much to learn,
but at least he did that right.
[KOTO]
Three!
Four!
[KOTO]
Five!
Six!
Seven!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Please,
please stay down!
[KOTO]
Eight!
Nine!
Hold it right there Urameshi.
I'll, be coming
in just a second.
[KOTO]
Ten!!!
And with a knockout by ring out.
Team Urameshi takes
their fourth win!
Well, that was a
damn good fight Jin.
Nice to know I'm not
the only freak around.
Maybe we'll hang
out if you ever wake up.
And he's even made a friend.
[DEMON]
Lousy cheaters!!!
I swear!
Can we not have one eency moment
of positivity around here!
It's just so weird, you know?
Talking to your
imaginary friend?
Uh, don't you want to watch?
I'm not leaving the country.
I just didn't think
it'd be festive to pee
in my pants
during the next fight.
Wait up!
Team Masho is pathetic!
There's only one of 'em left!
And they started
out five against two!
[BUTAJIRI]
Hey! Risho!
You better be sure
you can handle this!
Between the bets
and paying people off
I spent my whole
entire fortune on you!
[RISHO] It will be taken care
of. The boy is exhausted.
Convince me!
If you don't trust me,
why don't you just use your
influence one more time?
What? What do you mean?
[KOTO] Team Urameshi
and Team Masho
each have one remaining
person in condition to fight!
By default,
the winner of this match
will advance to the semifinals!
Hey Keek, look
what we got here.
What's your
name, princess?
I am Yukina, of the Ice World.
It's very nice to meet you.
Do you know where I could find a
ticket booth for the tournament?
Oh sure sister, like it hasn't
been sold out for a week!
Even the scalpers
went home!
Damn it! I'd pay
fifty G for a ticket!
I see. Then I came all
of this way for nothing.
Will the last member of Team
Masho please enter the ring!
[DEMON FAN] You better not blow
this like your buddies did!
Yeah! Give us a kill!
Give us his head!
Slap on your game hats, boys!
This fight decides the round!
Let's see what
this meanie looks like.
Sorry to say, Yusuke Urameshi,
but you're going to die without
ever laying a finger on me.
What?
Begin!!
Alright, I'm kickin' your
ass out of principal!
[SPEAKER]
Stop this fight immediately.
Stop the fight? What for?
They're up to something.
Tournament Committee,
please clarify.
Why have you
interrupted this fight?
Yeah, more importantly why'd
you make me look like a fool?
Upon reviewing the
film of the last fight,
it has been discovered that
Koto delayed her ten count
significantly during
Yusuke's first ring out.
Since when do we
pay attention to that?
Therefore, by complete
and unanimous decision.
They tell me to delay.
The fight between Yusuke and Jin
has been ruled a double loss,
and therefore Yusuke
is ineligible to fight
for the duration of the round.
Well that's just the
biggest crap job
I've ever heard in my life!
Yusuke landed
right in front of us.
Do you remember him being
out for more than ten counts!
No!
They always take
their time on the counts!
Yes it was no
longer than usual.
[KURAMA THINKS]
Kuwabara is badly injured
and I've lost a fight.
Hiei and the Masked
Fighter are ineligible.
If Yusuke is ruled out as well.
Our team is out
of the tournament.
[DEMON 3] Who cares!
Urameshi is out!
How can this be over?
I didn't even get to start.
[YUSUKE THINKS] We're dead
if we lose this match now.
[Risho chuckles]
My condolences.
Why are you
waiting, Koto.
Bestow our team
with the victory.
As an experienced officiator.
And as a lover of this
tournament, I must object!
[SPEAKER] There will
be no more deliberation.
Ah come one!
Get on with it!
[Butajiri laughs]
Who needs ninjas, I beat this
whole damn team myself...
The only hard part now
is figuring out which
of my tricks I liked the best...
The medical tent
capture or those
rulings against
Yusuke and Kurama!
[crash]
I don't like the
way you play, Butajiri.
Risho!
This deceit has
gone too far.
Don't you see we'll make a
mockery of their sacrifices.
Gama willfully gave his
life so that we could win.
Not cheat our way out!
Spare me your
romantic drivel, Touya.
He fought for the light.
Now we're going to enjoy it.
But honor.
Nonsense!
We must always keep our
eye on the final goal, Touya.
That's why I am the leader.
And you are the grunt.
And now, as for you Koto,
do you really think it's wise
to be on the human's
side in this stadium?
Keep the resistance,
and I have a feeling you won't
be officiating much longer.
What? But this is my show!
You know you seem really anxious
to intimidate everyone but me.
What do you think that means?
Come on.
Detective.
Don't waste your time
trying to change their minds.
Fight by their
meaningless rules
and you'll be
pulled down with them.
There's only one real
law of the Dark Tournament.
The strongest man prevails!
I've retrieved enough
energy to rip my way out.
Let's show this entire stadium
a new definition for victory.
[YUSUKE] They're gonna
kill us anyway,
so we take on every
freak 'til no one's left.
That sounds good to me.
I'm already about to go off.
I can't hold him off any longer.
The enchantress chords
holding my power--
His energy's tearing
them apart...
A couple more minutes
like this and there
won't be any of them left!
Uh, I don't want to sound
like a traitor or anything,
but maybe we
should cheer for Hiei.
Uh-huh.
That a way Hiei!
Don't stop now!
Keep your energy exploding!
Tear those evil chords apart!!
I'll assume
you're saying that
because you want
him to escape, sir.
Look at it this way.
If demons did have toilets,
would you really
want to sit on them?
That's a very
good point.
Hey.
What's up, Shizuru?
You sense something?
Go in the stadium
and find Botan for me.
Bring her right back here
with you as quick as you can.
Just tell her I
said it's important.
Sure!
Before I start blabbering,
your name is Yukina, right?
Yes, I'm sorry, do I know you?
Not yet, but I've got a brother
who won't shut up about you.
So then, are you
Kuzuma's older sister?
Yeah, nice to meet you.
I absolutely hate to
see such a good competitor
go out of the games
without the chance to
inflict pain on someone! But...
Due to Yusuke's ineligibility,
and as there are
no other members
on his team available to fight,
and as Team Masho
still a has a competitor.
By forfeit, the
winner of the round is--!!!
[KUWABARA]
Wait right there!
We still got one
more fighter on our team.
What the hell's he means?
Where? Where is he?
Where's the other fighter?
Who could he be
talking about sir?
Where? Where'd he go?
Where is he? Is he over here?
[KOENMA THINKS] What's running
through that brain, Kuwabara?
You better not
be talking about me.
Would you shut up!!!
Let's go!!
You're kidding me.
The boy can't even walk
without doubling over!
As the team trainer I must
say this is a ridiculous idea!
Interesting.
Pointless.
Well at least it's not me.
Now that that's established,
what the heck
is Kuwabara thinking?
[BLUE OGRE]
Koenma sir!!
Now Botan is
running off somewhere!!
[KOENMA] Ogre! Who gives a
hissy-fit about her right now!!
Let's just keep our cool and
watch Kuwabara get massacred.
I can handle this you guys!
Remember, that lady
from the medical tent
took Hiei and the Masked Fighter
off, and said I was okay!
[YUSUKE] Stupid! Cause
she's not a nurse!!
Don't confuse the issue!
The point here is that
I'm still eligible to fight!
And I'm the only one!
Yes. But eligible and
able are two different words.
You shut up, shrimp!
See you're in no shape!
I'm going Urameshi! Unless
you want to kill me yourself!
I know these
guys are cheating us.
I know you're angry, and heck,
I know what happens if we lose.
But if you and Hiei
go on some tirade
destroying people
'till you get your way,
you'll be just like them.
Let's win this
thing clean. Like...
Like men.
How touching.
Bite my ankles, shorty!
I swear I'll make
you cry to your mom!
If you have a
mom that is.
[KURAMA THINKS] To think they
could one day be in-laws.
[KEIKO]
Hey! Over here!
[BOTAN] I hope this
is important!
I was in the middle
of a great speech!
Botan?
[BOTAN]
Oh, Yukina!!
Nice to see you!
[BOTAN] All the way from
the Ice World, huh?
That's one doozy of boat ride!
Can I assume you came
here to cheer on Kuwabara?
Yes, and Yusuke
too of course.
I still feel so grateful
to them for helping me.
I've been studying
in healing powers too--
I hoped I could
help them some.
Why, aren't you
the sweetest thing!!
But, there is
another reason I came.
Oh? Well
spill the beans!
The truth is I--
Have an older brother.
[BOTAN THINKS] Oh dear!
She didn't find out about
Hiei already, did she??
[YUKINA] But I don't
know who he is.
All I know is that he's
a skilled martial artist.
I thought that
this tournament
would be the best chance
I had of finding him,
and so I've been allowed
to stay in the human world
for a while to look.
Is that right?
Well I'm sure we're all more
than happy to help you search.
Isn't that right Botan?
[BOTAN THINKS] Oh! I thought
Shizuru knew from the video!
Don't worry.
Just play along.
[KEIKO] It can't be that hard.
Do you have any clues?
Maybe a picture
of him or a letter?
No, nothing at all.
But, I have this strong feeling
that he's very close to me now.
[BOTAN THINKS] Alright, so
the only people who know
are Shizuru and me.
Oh and Koenma and Kurama.
Oh and Yusuke.
And Hiei obviously.
That's a lot of people-- But
Keiko deserves to know, right?
[HIEI] You talk, you die.
[BOTAN THINKS] It doesn't help
that I'm a blabbermouth
and he's a telepath!
Oh, no! It's Kuzuma!
He's not in the ring is he?
Oh, I forgot to tell you!
A crummy ruling's put
Yusuke out of the picture
and Kuwabara's gone in
so we wouldn't forfeit!
Now it's just Risho and
him and he's all injured
and I don't know
how he's gonna survive!
I can barely see!
Is there anything we
can do to get closer?
Excuse me, boys.
Back off! We were here first!
Step aside, or I'll turn
your balls into jelly.
[KOTO]
What fantastic will!
The visibly hammered fighter
has limped into the ring,
preventing his
team's elimination!
But can this haggard boy
possibly hope to compete
against Team Masho's leader?
We men go down with honor!
Fighters, please
report to the center!
Right.
It's dismal,
but at least it will buy us
time to consider our options.
He's killing himself!
Well, now here's the type
of fight I don't mind
keeping my hands out of.
[KUWABARA THINKS] It's not often
a guy gets a chance like this.
Maybe they'll name
a city block after me.
Your heroics
are quite misplaced.
All you'll win is a grave.
Just keep talkin', cheater!
I'll just make
it more tough on you!
Final fight and for the win!
Kuwabara versus Risho! Begin!
[NARRATOR] The fate of the
team lies in the hands
of the hopelessly
injured Kuwabara.
Will Yusuke and the
others be able to watch,
as their chance for
survival dwindles away?
[KUWABARA] Okay, so maybe
I've got a lot on my hands,
and not much
strength in my spine.
But there's more than just
my teammates counting on me,
and I'll be darned
if we're gonna endanger
them all by losing,
while I just sit on the side!
There's decisions that kids
make and decisions for men,
and somewhere down in me
I'll find the reason
to draw that line.
So when Risho unveils
his super big powers,
I'm gonna be right
there to take it.
It's the next
big Yu Yu Hakusho,
and missing it just
wouldn't be right.
♪