[TOGURO 2] To become a
master of a trade,
you must commit your all to it
and throw everything else away.
Damn, you're stupid,
you didn't throw it away.
You just ran away from it like
a frightened little child.
I won't run,
and I won't let go.
Spirit Gun!!!
I killed Genkai
but one remained.
And now that surviving piece
can at last be put to rest.
[TOGURO 2] Thank you again,
Yusuke Urameshi.
[crackling]
[TOGURO 2] This was
the first time I could
use my absolute strength,
and you answered.
It was the only
way it could end.
That's hard to call.
[crowd erupts in cheers]
He did it!!
We are free.
We can go home
now Shizuru!
Winner of the Tournament!
Team Urameshi!
[KOTO] That's right people,
don't kick your radios.
The human verifiably
clinched an upset!
Now we just have to
accept our losses.
We should go now.
Keiko, are you all right?
Finally the Toguros fall.
It's been quite
a long run.
All I can think about is how
much our little sapling
has improved in
this tournament.
That and the whole
saving-my-life thing.
[KURAMA]
Yusuke!
Easy does it.
No sleeping just yet.
Yusuke, snap out of it!
You have your victory.
[YUSUKE]
Am I...am I alive?
[KOENMA] Of course!
Do you see any halos on us??
Everything is a-okay now!
[YUSUKE]
No it's not.
[YUSUKE] Damn it!!!
[YUSUKE] If I hadn't been
such an irresponsible kid,
if I didn't have concrete walls
between my own stupid emotions.
Okay Urameshi.
It's all you.
I did what I could.
Now beat him for all of us.
Make my death count, Yusuke?
I had all the
strength to save him.
I was just too dumb to
know how to reach it.
What the hell do
I say to that, huh??
You say you learned.
[YUSUKE] Shut up!
What good does that do?
He's already dead!
I can't say anything to him now!
Is that so hard to get??
I'm just like everybody
else with power!
I don't do anything to help!
[YUSUKE]
I'm sorry, Kuwabara!!
It's all my fault.
Okay, I think you've done enough
groveling for one day!
Though it is pretty
entertaining!!
Reporting for duty!
Captain Faker! That's me!
Hey, why's the dead
guy walkin' around???
Yes. Well, I tried
to inform you,
but you were too
engrossed in your speech.
The heart! The finger poking!
You're a moving public
speaker, by the way.
Look, he never died.
Just stay with us, Kuwabara!
Just stay with us.
Hold on. Your pulse
is still strong!
Yeah that's right, don't worry.
Toguro missed my vitals.
But keep looking at
me like you're sad.
Urameshi could use some
good shock treatment.
And that's basically
how it went!
How's it feel to be
outta the loopty-loop?!
All you guys
were in on this?
[KOENMA] Naturally. I know
I'm not supposed to lie,
but well, whatever.
And you guys let me
cry like a baby??
You said it yourself.
It was your fault.
[KOENMA] I agree with Hiei.
Mostly so I don't feel guilty.
If you could've reached
your power on your own
the fake death wouldn't
have been needed,
and you wouldn't
look like a child.
I doubt he heard you.
[YUSUKE] We're in front of
about a million people,
including Keiko and my boss
and hardcore demon fighters,
and you make me say
all that sissy crap??
I really thought you
were dead you stupid ass!!!
Oh, I'm so very relieved
to see Kazuma's okay!
He should really try the
Junior High theater department!
Yes, he could at
least play the fool.
[YUSUKE] Stupid! I'll teach you
to act like you're dead!
Yusuke, teach him anymore
and you'll actually kill him.
That's kind of against
the point, isn't it?
Wait a sec.
That still doesn't explain why
Toguro missed dufus-boy's heart.
Oh yeah, I hadn't thought
about that, Dufus-brain.
What with all the years
Toguro spent as a hired killer.
You'd think he'd know
where the heart was.
He obviously knew Kuwabara.
I'd say your defense level
just rose dramatically
and kept your heart
from being pierced.
Your stubbornness is even
greater than your stupidity.
That sure is a nasty
way to give a compliment!!!
I suggest an alternative,
that Toguro didn't
want Kuwabara to die.
He intended to
miss from the start.
I believe that the ultimate
outcome of this fight
is precisely what Toguro
had been looking for.
So he threw the fight??
No. He wanted to be legitimately
defeated, by someone stronger.
But why?
[KOENMA]
Maybe he felt guilty
for choosing strength
over his friends,
and for ditching the
one he cared about most.
[KURAMA] And who
better to vanquish him
than the apprentice
of the woman he abandoned?
He wanted you
to prove him wrong,
show him that your
choice could prevail.
[KOENMA] Guess we'll
never know for sure.
[SAKYO] May I put in my two
cents? I think Kurama's right.
What the hell?
I only knew him a couple of
years, but thinking back,
the signs were in neon lights.
Toguro's poker
face was famous.
When he saw Yusuke barrel into
Tarakane's stronghold,
it was one of the few times
I saw him lose a grin.
I just thought he was
anxious to kill you.
But that's what I get
projecting my tastes onto his.
In the greatest moment, facing
the greatest opponent,
he was able to face
a great end.
It's the dream of every
true competitor.
[SAKYO]
Speaking of, Koenma,
it's time for us to settle
our own great bet.
I see my weak point
was not knowing the truth
of what Toguro was thinking.
It's been a most enjoyable game.
Bet's off.
You've lost your fortune.
You're no threat to me now.
Such kind words.
But where is the
thrill in gambling
if you know you can
get out of all your bets?
Don't worry,
I'll take care of it myself.
That's kind of a showy
way to cark yourself!
I think we should leave now.
[COMPUTER] Stadium
detonation now commencing.
Fifteen minutes.
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
fourteen minutes...
Stadium detonation...
fourteen minutes.
What the hell are we
standing around for?!
Come on!!!
This stadium will
be turned into ruins.
Taking me and my ambitions
along for the ride.
How can you do this?
[SAKYO] You should concentrate
on your own life, Kuwabara.
[KOENMA] Where are you going?
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
thirteen minutes...
Stadium detonation...
thirteen minutes.
We can't waste time!
Or we'll be foundation!
[YUKINA] Keiko!
What's the matter?
You have to snap
out of it!
Keiko!
[KOENMA] Yusuke.
Can you help the girls?
Yeah, naturally.
What are you gonna do?
I still have a little
business to settle with Sakyo.
Don't get killed.
You heard the man, let's go!
Right!
Perhaps you should
let me help you.
See you around, Toguro.
[crowd crying out in panic]
[DEMON 2] Sakyo already closed
off the entrances!
[DEMON 3] Run through the
hole Urameshi made!
Stop the broadcast, Koto!
I wanna go home!
Never! In all my
years as announcer
I've sat through
a lot more danger
than a collapsing stadium.
I'll finish this broadcast!
It's my duty!!
No! I don't want to
die as a virgin!
Oh people! Juri's
just revealed a shocker
that I never would've guessed
with her popular stint
at the committee
cocktail lounge!
Well as dutiful
as I am to the awards,
I think this cause
is a little more noble!
[KOTO]
Let's find you a man!
[KOENMA] I want assurances.
This voluntary-death
bit is a little fishy
coming from a man like you.
[SAKYO]
Such a careful ruler.
But motives aren't suspect just
because you don't understand.
[KOENMA]
Then explain.
I've been playing
my cards for longer
than you will ever realize,
and today Yusuke and Toguro
both had better hands.
It was all or
nothing from the start,
now I simply know
which one I receive.
How do I know the
plan ends with you?
Yes, you've been keeping
your informants busy.
And somewhere along the line,
you learned of
my humble aspiration
to dissolve the
barrier between worlds,
let demons of every size
cross to the human side.
Annul the careful order
your kind has enforced.
I find life would
be better that way,
and I know one
day it will be so.
But fortunately for
you I'm an egomaniac,
and won't let my
work go on without me.
This bomb is
linked to my lab
and will destroy all
the progress I've made.
[KOENMA]
Shizuru.
No, Sakyo, wait!
[SHIZURU] No!
Damn it...
Sakyo, don't leave!
[SHIZURU] Get off of me!
[crowd in panic]
What's up with these
demons going the wrong way?
It's like wading through
a pool of giant trout!
[KUWABARA]
Yukina's in trouble!
Hold on!!
[KUWABARA] Your loyal samurai
in shining armor is coming,
my loving sweet pea!
Hey, get out of my way!!!
Come on, you got
a death wish?!
Why'd Toguro miss?
Well, we might as well
follow his path.
She isn't responding
to anything.
Keiko? Keiko, honey?
We kind of have
an emergency here.
The girl's gone
absolutely catatonic.
I don't know what to do.
Keiko? Come on!
[YUKINA] Nothing.
[KUWABARA] Hey, Yukina!
I'm here to rescue you!
We can go whenever you want!
Kazuma! Something's
really wrong with Keiko!
She's not responding
to anything!
We can't get her to move!
[KUWABARA]
Yukina!!!
You're of no use.
Thank you very much, Hiei.
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
five minutes...
Stadium detonation...
[YUSUKE] This isn't a good
place for a party, guys.
Yusuke! Keiko's not well!
What?
Post-traumatic stress,
and like everything else,
she excels at it!
Hey, Keiko.
Did you hear me?
I said hey it's Yusuke!
We can go home now.
Well so much for that. Listen!
I'm sorry! But we don't have
any more time to talk!
Come on Keiko! Wake up!
Snap out of it will you?
A thousand tons of rock
is about to fall on our heads!
And I'm sure you
already know this,
but that's kind of a lot!
[KEIKO]
Yusuke!! How dare you, jerk!
What's going on here?
Where am...
I think he's dead.
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
three minutes...
Stadium detonation...
three minutes.
Hey, where's my sister?
I'm not sure, really.
We were so busy with Keiko,
I didn't see her slip away.
Sorry.
Hey, don't worry.
She'll take care of herself.
What's the hold up?
[KUWABARA] Clear a path, fans!
Kuwabara coming through!!
Uh-oh. I don't like this!
What now?
Get outta the way.
I'll bust through.
Yusuke, you know you don't
have strength left.
Well neither do you,
so what's our choice?
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
two minutes...
What can we do? We don't have
time to find a new exit!
Damn it!
How goes it, mate!
A lot better now, I guess.
Then don't just stand
there like a bludger!
Let's go! We can't let our
champion team get hurt now!
Right he is! When the tourney
next around comes flying
we'll have to
face you ourselves,
and we'll have new
muscles on us and WHEW-WEE!
You'll go zipping and we'll
be the champions that one!
Right, whatever he said.
[POO]
Puu!
[KEIKO]
Hey, there you are!
You're gonna come
live with me, aren't you?
Puu.
Uh Keiko, the stadium?
Right!
Koenma, sir.
Please, don't leave
this place without me.
[KOENMA] So,
the prodigal moron returns.
[BLUE OGRE] Oh thank you sir!
I love you! I love you!
[KOENMA] Get off
me you big blue looney!
I didn't give
you a rock!
I just pulled you
out from under one!
[COMPUTER] Stadium detonation...
thirty seconds...
[KOENMA]
See ya!
[COMPUTER]
Five...four...three...
two...one...
[blast]
Yeah! With the action hero exit!
So it's over now.
Yeah. It finally is.
What's the matter, Botan?
The prizes for
winning the tournament!
You were each supposed to
get whatever you wanted!
We didn't even
get a souvenir mug!
Aw, I was gonna get famous!
What a crock!
[YUSUKE] It doesn't matter.
Those bastards up in the
Tournament Committee.
They couldn't haven given
us what we wanted anyway.
And uh, what
did we want again?
It's done!
We finished it Genkai!
[YUSUKE] That's it guys.
Well, all most.
The pain we lovingly
called the Dark Tournament
is now thankfully over,
now we can all go back home
and not have to look at
each other for a while.
Well give our last regards
to Hanging Neck island
and remember what
we lost and learned.
And just because Genkai
and Toguro took
their one-way passes,
doesn't mean they
won't be seen again.
They've still got a few
more words for each other
in Spirit World.
Look forward to that and more,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪