♪
[NARRATOR] As the Dark
Tournament continues,
the alluring enchantress Ruka
has trapped Hiei
and the Masked Fighter
in a powerful force field.
With Kuwabara already injured,
Yusuke and Kurama
must face the five members
of Team Masho alone.
Paralyzed by
Gama's demon make up,
Kurama narrowly
won the first match
by controlling his Rose
Whip with Spirit Energy.
But the victory
was not complete.
As the mutilated Gama
made his final swings,
he has splattered
Kurama with a chilling curse.
The death is yours.
What?
You never asked me what
gave my makeup its power,
what made it any different from
the makeup of those human fools.
The difference is
the main ingredient, Kurama.
It's made of my blood.
I have given you
The Makeup of the Seal.
It's what I should
I've done from the start.
I've sealed your Spirit Energy.
Your entire power
trapped inside your body.
I've secured victory
for my Shinobi sect.
And so I die,
knowing it is not in vain.
[KOTO] Will the next fighters
please approach the ring!
You fought bravely, Gama.
I assure you that your
death will be honored.
Kurama will pay.
[KURAMA THINKS] My arms and
legs are still anchored down
by Gama's first curse.
That I can live with. My
energy trapped inside. I cannot.
[KOTO] Alright
people, time's up!
By the rules I must consider
those now in the ring
as the next opponents!
That means it's
Kurama vs. Touya!
Prepare yourself.
I'll make this quick.
Damn. This is wrong!
How can they make him fight?
Darn it, if I was
stronger I could help out!
I'm letting down my
team and now he's gonna die!
Try to relax Kuwabara.
You'll get them
back when you're healed.
[BUTAJIRI]
There you are Sakyo!
I've been looking
all over for you!
You do have a
VIP ticket, you know.
Why are you sharing
ass space with these animals?
Apparitions don't pretend
to know what's going to happen.
It's more exciting that way.
Interesting opinion...
Of course you don't
have to pretend,
if you play the way I do.
How do you like that medical
tent scheme I came up with?
Sure didn't take much to
get the committee going along.
They just want
that Yusuke kid dead.
Personally I think
it's that mess with Tarukane--
we all suspect Yusuke
was responsible for his death.
And even Spirit World's
detectives should know
not to screw around with the
rich and powerful, right Sakyo?
He'll die alright. Even if
this plan doesn't work,
I've got a hundred
more to pull out.
It's hopeless.
[MASKED FIGHTER] Kurama still
has one weapon he can use.
Time. The first
curse should wear off soon,
and Kurama will be able to move.
If he can stall
Touya long enough,
perhaps he can
regain his energy, too.
That's nice, but I'd
rather stay realistic.
Please. Answer
me one thing first.
Why? The Shinobi
have always dealt
with their affairs
in secret.
Why expose yourselves now?
For light.
Explain.
It's simple.
Even the strongest tree,
will die if left in the dark.
I find that to be the
best way to describe us.
A giant oak crashing
through a dark soil,
bringing order to an
otherwise chaotic land.
The Shinobi have done their job
for centuries, and done it well.
[TOUYA]
But in recent years
we have caught glimpses of
the outside world, and asked:
Why not us?
Have we not earned the
privilege others take for free?
We are entering a new era.
And we will begin
with a land of our own.
This island.
It has already been arranged
that if we win this tournament.
Hanging-Neck Island
will be our prize.
[TOUYA] And once this blinding
light pours over us all,
like branches,
we will cover the world.
The ninjas are revolting.
[MASKED FIGHTER] The Shinobi
have survived for centuries
by each master
passing their knowledge
to one apprentice
before he dies.
The previous masters
must have made poor selections.
These fighters
don't know their place.
I don't give a damn about
their internal disputes.
The only important thing
is how strong they are.
[HIEI] I've fought my
share of ice warriors.
Seiryu the Blue Dragon
fell to my sword quickly enough,
but he was no master.
He was a fool
who thought he could get
by on half of his lessons.
But if there is
any true ice master,
any one who completed
the full training
that his master intended
and knows the art of ice.
It is Touya.
Let's cease with
the conversation.
I know that you're
simply trying to buy time
for that seal to wear off.
I admit. You've caught
me with my hands red.
You boys are having way
too much fun okay? Begin!!
Gama made the mistake
of giving you too
much time to think. Not me.
What's that?
Oh! Cold-cold-cold!!
Touya's jettisoning his
power in a wave of freezing air,
and this girl's really wishing
she'd worn insulated tights!
Whoa, it's cold.
Your own climate control.
That's very impressive.
In addition to
improving my attacks.
It will serve as a barrier.
Giving you fewer
options for escape.
Even with your energy sealed,
I admit I'm somewhat
hesitant to get near you,
what with your
little Rose Whip maneuver.
You understand, I'd
rather kill long distance.
[TOUYA]
Shards of Winter.
Seems Kurama can finally
move his arms and legs again!
But it may not be in
time to dodge this assault!
Nice try.
[KURAMA THINKS] There must be a
way to reach my Spirit Energy.
[TOUYA THINKS] You better think
of something quickly Kurama.
You can't dodge these forever.
Despite awesome acrobatics.
Kurama can't avoid these
razor-sharp blades of ice!
Surrender!
And Kurama hits the deck!
Just stay down!
[YUSUKE] I'll handle
it from here!
It's not right!
This might be his time to lose.
[DEMON FAN] What are you waiting
for Touya! Rip out his entrails!
Hurry, Yusuke! What are
you standing around for?
Get in there and
save your friend's life!
Don't bother.
You know it's against
the rules for him to do that.
It's somebody's life...
Who cares about the dumb rules?
Get in there Yusuke!
Punch Touya in the face
if you have to! Come on!
Well, there's a
change of attitude.
Koenma sir, there must
be something he can do!
He needs to win this
fight for the team!
[KOENMA] Don't be a numbskull.
Without access to his energy,
the only thing he
needs to do is quit.
But what about heroism
sir? Determination?
[KOENMA] Save it for
your storybooks.
It's much better to
dump it all on Yusuke.
Running like a baby is perfectly
brave if the odds are too tough.
Yes sir!
Is that so, Koenma?
[KOENMA] Hey! What's with
that tone in your voice?
Oh nothing sir.
Did you just roll
your eyes at me??
I think you rolled your eyes!!
I know you're not disagreeing
with the super almighty Koenma!!
Gee, I'm glad Kurama has more
of a spine than you do, sir.
[KOENMA]
Say something, Ogre?
Uh nothing sir! Nothing!
That hit was not
enough to beat you.
I know that you stayed
down intentionally
in yet another
attempt to buy time.
I don't suggest
you trying it again.
[KURAMA THINKS]
His wits match my own.
Unless I can find a
way to my energy soon,
he'll bleed me to de--
Perhaps.
[KURAMA THINKS] This seal is
powered by Gama's blood.
Perhaps my own
will disengage it.
[TOUYA] Now, now, don't
underestimate Gama's abilities.
It will take much
more than smearing
to get rid of that seal.
Rose whip!
I see, you've noticed
inklings of your energy
inside your blood.
Only one problem.
To release enough to beat me
you'd have to
bleed yourself dry.
[TOUYA] Gama's seal won't
wear off any time soon.
Admit it Kurama, I'm holding the
end of your life in my hands.
I sure know that
facial expression!
Pure, lovely,
excruciating agony!
And yet, he's
still trying to get up!
He's determined
to take some more!
[KURAMA THINKS]
Touya's right again.
These drops won't
get me anywhere.
There must be another
way to reach my power...
I have to win.
He's back on his feet!
The fight continues!
[TOUYA THINKS]
This doesn't make sense.
No one could survive all those
direct hits from my ice attack.
Not unless...
You really are
dangerous, aren't you?
I haven't been
making direct hits.
You've been blocking your
vital points with your own body.
[TOUYA] You must be very old.
Experienced, perhaps, as I am.
More alike than
you know. Now tell me...
This new life
on the outside.
What do you truly
plan to do with it?
The world will know.
Just as soon as we get there.
Don't assume.
[TOUYA THINKS] Could it be?
He still plans to win this.
He's been delaying me after all,
letting me
believe I was winning.
And all the while,
thinking of some clever plan.
I can't allow this to continue.
Wow people!
Touya's created
a sword out of ice!
It's the barbaric finish
we've been waiting for!
Kurama!
Ooh! That head
just nearly flew off!
A rather lucky
move, my friend.
Let's see how long
you can keep that up.
[KURAMA THINKS] The slightest
mistake and I'll be killed.
I can't afford to
postpone any longer.
Tell fox-girl you give up!
I swear I'll take it from here!
Urameshi knows he can't
beat four guys in a row!
If Kurama loses
we're dead meat!
Just tell me when it's over!
[KURAMA THINKS] No more
delaying the inevitable.
It's time I take
my responsibility.
And make my stand.
Son a freakin' bitch, Kurama.
Don't get up!
Let me take him!
Are you trying to
get yourself killed??
Go Touya finish him off!
[KOENMA] Why do I get the
feeling our most intelligent
fighter is going to do
something incredibly stupid?
Strange--almost as if Kurama's
taking this fight. Personally.
Let me do what I must Yusuke.
I'm going to end your life
in one blow. Prepare yourself.
It seems that I've gotten
to know you quite well
in such a short fight,
and I rather like you.
Let's not have this
slaying ruin our friendship.
My thoughts exactly.
Now, you shouldn't have run.
I can't guarantee a
painless kill that way.
Kurama!
Farewell!
But how? Your energy
is locked inside of you.
How could you
manipulate your Death Plant?
Insane, you actually
sowed the Death Plant seed
into your own body??
It was my only option.
My power is locked inside.
By inserting the
seed into my open wound.
The plant could
enter my bloodstream
and take root in
my imprisoned energy.
[TOUYA]
You really are something.
[KOTO] Unbelievable turn around!
I'll take a ten count!
Now it's my turn!
He really did it.
Like the saying:
they can cut your skin, as
long as you break their bones!
Two!
[DEMON FAN 1] Get your
butt off the floor, Touya!
I thought you guys were Shinobi!
Kurama's okay from
doing that, isn't he?
There's a killer plant
growing through his body.
What do you think?
What is this!
I lay everything on a platter
and they still botch it up!
Can't believe I gotta do
everything for these filth.
We won! We won! We won!
You see Koenma sir!
There is something to
be said for not giving up!
Of course there is!
I've been saying
that this whole time
and you've been disagreeing.
Not what I remember.
You know you've been
very unpleasant lately, Ogre.
Maybe after the tournament
I'll have to assign you to the
Lake of Fire cleaning crew!
Ah, ah! Wait sir, I don't
think you have time
to mess with that now!
Look down there! Yeah I
think Touya's getting up!
Why didn't you tell me!!
[KOTO] Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!!!
Kurama wins!
Please update the score board!
You have won
the match I admit.
Please. Kill me!
I will not.
You never answered. What do
you plan to do with this island.
If you get it?
Who cares!
I too have spent years
in shadow. Interesting.
How unexpected,
regret can appear.
That's what this light does.
I only wanted to know if you
could make your life better.
Nobler.
Than mine has been.
Kurama!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] No he can't.
Nobler? Than Kurama?
What did he mean?
Oh Shizuru, is he?
About time they got ridda one
of 'em! Only four more to go!
Oh God.
Wait people! Kurama
still has a faint heartbeat!
It appears he's
slipped into unconsciousness
while still on his feet!
Can anything kill this guy?
So finish him off!
Okay, now we're
getting somewhere!
And hey fox-girl,
just so we're clear.
The rest of the
fights are all mine!
[BAKKEN]
Not so fast.
What??
You forgot something.
He's standing in the ring.
Yes, it looks to me like he's
volunteering to fight again.
Oh give me a break! Kurama's
not even conscious anymore!
I'm taking this fight!
Alright uh, Team Captain
decides! Yusuke versus Bakken!
--It's perfectly fair!
[SPEAKER] Correction: The next
fight will be Kurama vs. Bakken.
What??
[SPEAKER] A fighter
standing in the ring
cannot be removed
against his will.
As will cannot be determined
here, the fighter remains.
[RUKA] Don't think
about it, Hiei.
Unless of course,
you want to try another close
encounter with my force-field.
Looks like you're not
needed anymore, kitten.
Now that the ref
is out of the picture
we can really have some fun.
He's hitting someone who's
completely defenseless!
Clearly not the honor-code type.
You look so peaceful
with your little flowers.
Kurama's definitely
down, Bakken.
Step away so I
can start the count!
You again?
I'm just going
to do my job, okay!
[KOTO] One!
You must think
you're a comedian.
Nobody who humiliates my sect
and gets to slip
away in a ten count.
Six, seven, eight, nine, and...
Say ten!
Oh look, he's
on his feet again.
I guess that means
he wants more!
[YUSUKE] Stop the fight!!
[NARRATOR] Kurama's selfless
acts and corrupt rulings
by the Committee have
pitted the unconscious fighter
in a whole new match.
What will the outcome be?
[YUSUKE] Hey guys,
you know what's coming.
I'm pissed and
I'm gonna get drastic.
Maybe it's against
these dumb rules
to step in during
somebody else's fight,
but with a little
persuasion from my Spirit Gun
I'll at least get that
meat-head to take me on next.
I can't say whether Kurama
will survive or not,
but either way I'm
gonna even the score.
There's three more
members on Team Masho,
and I'm the only one
left who can take 'em.
Chances aren't great,
but I'll promise one thing.
If I go, I'll
go out with a bang.
♪