♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
has been given his next case:
Enter the mountain stronghold
of human crime
lord Gonzou Tarukane,
and rescue the
kidnapped Yukina,
an Ice Apparition who
is in fact Hiei's sister.
Yusuke, Kuwabara, and Botan
started their mountain trek,
quickly butting heads with
the first line of defense--
Demon guards under
the leadership
of the feared Toguro Brothers.
Kind of stupid to
have a mountain trail
that ends halfway up
the mountain, huh?
I guess they don't encourage
much camping around here.
Yes, the stronghold
is very well hidden.
But we should be able
to find it eventually
by following Yukina's energy.
Why are you still
using that compass?
Just follow my way!
The Red Pinky String!
The what?
The moment I saw her.
My love stretched out
and tied us together.
You see?
Let's follow the thread
of destiny tied to my love!!
This is unexpected.
Speak up, boy!
Hirue, who I sent to deal
with the trespassers is dead.
Hey! What kind of people
you sendin' out there!
Bums off the street?!
I assure you my
men are well picked.
Whoever has defeated Hirue.
Must have unusual powers.
Well unusual powers is
what I'm payin' you for!
Don't expect me
to hand out the cash
if you can't handle the job!
You needn't worry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you've said that.
But I'm not the kind a guy who
gets satisfied off cheap talk!
Oh? What do you suggest?
Come with me. You
can prove your stuff!
[TARUKANE]
Triple our security outside!
Of course.
[KOENMA] The Toguro Brothers?
This is going to be messy.
Oh yeah I think
I've heard of them!
Aren't they on
the Most Wanted List?
[KOENMA] This figures, I thought
watching Hiei was bad enough.
But now I can't even find him
and the Toguro's
have shown up too!
Well Tarukane, your
tastes are unique.
Discovering you demons
has been quite a pleasure.
Gives me plenty of new
things to spend my money on.
[TARUKANE]
Light's up!
[TARUKANE] This
beauty's name is Helen.
Believe it or not,
she's a human creation.
Black-market
genetic engineering.
They were trying to
make her into a weapon.
But they could
never control the gal
so I got her at
a pretty good deal.
I want you to kill
her, barehanded.
[TARUKANE THINKS] Surely
he can beat those intruders,
but he won't take on that beast.
Giving me an excuse
to drive down his price!
I don't feel like killing her.
[Tarukane laughs]
[TARUKANE THINKS]
I love a winning gamble.
Especially when I bluff.
Hey!
[TOGURO 2] Of course,
with my job I do many
things I do not enjoy.
What are you doing?!
Are you stinkin' crazy!
Who's gonna make
Yukina cry me more jewels
after Helen rips you apart!
I didn't mean for you
to go in there for real!!
Then you
shouldn't have asked.
Thirty percent
of my strength.
Yes, that should be
more than enough for her.
What??
Am I goin' blind or
is he getting' bigger?!
I'm a very
untalented apparition.
The only thing I can do is
change the size of my muscles.
Hey, don't blame me.
Blame the science that
created you and the human who
--made me kill.
[monster screams in pain]
Not even the
best of contracts
justifies killing as
cruelly as I have just done.
I apologize to this creature.
[Tarukane laughs]
Get a load! I love this guy!!!
Rips him in half and
then he says he's sorry!
Boy who have got to be
my bodyguard! Top pay!
I'll think about it.
Seriously Toguro now
let me get this straight.
You saying you only
used thirty percent
of your whole
strength to do her in?!
Yeah, twenty percent probably
would have done a cleaner job.
But I do tend
to get carried away.
Sakashta, get your
ass to the telephone!
Sir, I've already
notified the black market.
[TARUKANE] That's not
what I mean, dimwit!
Call the boys from the
Black Black Club together!
[SAKASHTA] I see, sir.
You wish to place a wager.
[TARUKANE]
Think about it!
I got the fight of the
century in my own backyard!
The Toguro Brothers' Gang versus
the mysterious intruders!
And since I'm the only one here
who knows Toguro's true powers,
I'll be at a real
hustling advantage!
I'll bet the broad's
jewels against my pals
at the Black Black Club
and double my fortune!
Cheating your friends
isn't exactly honorable.
Hey! When you're rotten
like me there's only
one thing you can do!
Spread your stink!!!
Please go. They're
only going to kill you.
[YUKINA]
Please!
Get away! Get away!
Go!!
[YUKINA]
Please.
[YUKINA] Sweet birds,
you can't come near me.
No one can come
near me anymore.
[KUWABARA] Yukina!!!
[BOTAN] Wait, Kuwabara!
It's this way!
Yeah, but I just got a really
bad feeling. Let's go around.
My compass says
follow the path!
We don't have time for detours.
[Botan cries out]
Botan!
Whoopsie.
A little help?
What a nice catch!
It's a spider this time.
Hey, let her go!
[SPIDER DEMON]
Go?
Now why would I let her go
if I'm planning
to drink her blood?
If you want to save her.
You'll have to come and fight
me in the evil spider's lair!
Sorry to mess up your plan,
but no one's getting
between Yukina and me!
You can't possibly be human!
Yup!
We just happen to be
really, really tough!
Pardon me if I make this quick!
Nice hook!
Thanks, if this Detective
thing doesn't work,
maybe I can try exterminating!
[KOENMA]
Ha ha ha!
[BLUE OGRE]
It's getting dark, sir.
How's it going?
It's going. You locate Hiei yet?
No, I'm afraid
he never came back.
Well it was just
a matter of time
before he found out
about the mission, I guess.
Uh, do you mind if I ask
a question about that, sir?
Well why does Hiei's
sister being kidnapped
have to be a secret from him?
I mean doesn't
he deserve to know?
Moron! Once Hiei knows he'll
barge into the compound
slashing his sword
at everyone in sight!
He'll no doubt feel the
need to execute everyone
including the servants
and the family dog!
[KOENMA] The family dog
will indeed be unfortunate.
But the humans.
Well it's a serious crime
for demons to take human life
no matter what
the circumstances.
You know that.
It's best not to worry.
Even if Hiei is
heading for the compound,
I'm confident he
will work with Yusuke.
I'm surprised
you're so calm, Kurama,
since if Hiei does harm
you'll be punished with him.
[nervous laughter]
[KOENMA] Well, you'd
better come tuck me in.
We'll record the rest on tape.
[BLUE OGRE] Yes sir.
[SURGEON] Are you sure you want
to go through with this?
[SURGEON] The fusion between
you and the Jagan Eye
will be much more
painful than you imagine.
I have to lock
you down to the table
to keep you from
ripping out your own eyes.
I have earplugs for myself.
I won't say a word. Just do it.
Everyone screams. The only
question is, what will you say?
Yukina!
[BOTAN] Did you hear something?
[YUSUKE] No, would
you get up Kuwabara?
[thunder]
All of the members
of the Black Black Club
have been notified
of the meeting, sir.
[NARRATOR] Black Black Club:
a secret society hand-picked
by Gonzou Tarukane,
known for their
wickedness and influence
in the criminal underworld.
How ya doin' boys?
Must admit I'm surprised
to see all five of ya
on such short notice.
I for one would meet
even on my deathbed.
Well said!
This is our only
means of entertainment!
Yeah, world's
gotten too clean
to have fun
anywhere else!
[TARUKANE] Well fun, gentlemen,
is exactly why I
called you today.
Let me cut to the bone here-
As we speak, intruders
are heading toward my house.
So let's start a betting
pool on if they make it.
Or if my security beats them.
Well that would hardly be
a challenging proposition,
Tarukane.
We have no reason to
believe that these intruders
could survive your demons.
Wait--let me give out more
information before you decide.
Hit it!
The situation is
really quite simple, sirs.
There are three intruders.
They are walking through the
forest toward our stronghold.
Twelve from the Apparition
Gang are moving to stop.
Come now, they're children.
I don't know why
you're so anxious
to give away money Tarukane,
offering a gambling pool
where the odds are
so ridiculously stacked.
[CLUB MAN 1] Have you gone mad?
Let's get on with the
bidding. You got two choices.
Pick either the demons
or the intruders to win.
Sakashta will
show you the stakes.
In the event of a win
Mister Tarukane will pay
double of what you bid.
Two Hundred Million
on the demons.
Same here. Two Hundred
Mill on the demons.
[CLUB MAN 3]
Yeah, yeah. Same for me!
[CLUB MAN 4] Three hundred
million on the demons, please.
[Tarukane laughs]
[TOGURO 2] News has been
circulating recently about
two humans boys with
extraordinary spirit energy.
It is said that they have
defeated the Four Saint Beasts
as well as the
human-hunter Rando,
extremely powerful demons.
There is a very good chance
these intruders are those boys.
And if they are...
The first group of fighters
in my Apparition Gang
will suffer most unpleasantly.
[Tarukane laughs]
[TARUKANE THINKS]
I'm going to make a fortune.
You're the only one
who hasn't bet, Sakyou.
Tell me you're not
gettin' cold feet!
I will wager five billion
on the intruders' victory.
That's absurd!
Yes, absurd!
A trio of human misfits can't
take on twelve different demons!
In normal circumstances, no,
but I have a
certain little hunch.
I've heard a rumor
about two boys who have
been hunting down demons.
And I believe it's
a risk worth taking.
[TARUKANE THINKS] Sweet mother!
Where'd he get that
kind of information?!
I'll just have to hustle
him better in the next round!
Huh? What's the matter?
Very strange.
Six of my fighters'
Spirit Energies
have disappeared
all at once.
What?
They're even more
impressive than I thought.
Piece of cake!
Why are they even bothering
with all these wimps?
They're desperate, we're
very close to Yukina.
Yeah.
Let's go!
What in the world are
you tying to your head?
The Great Fighting
Headband of Love!!
Right.
And all those
guys there hate love!
They want to try and
keep me from my Yukina!
[KUWABARA]
Stand aside evil doers!
You're not gonna
be the only hero!
Givin' me the bigger
target? Oh thanks!
Two times five billion
is ten billion, right?
There's the stronghold!
It's the same as the video.
Yukina must be up in that tower.
Hold on my darling!
Your brave man is coming!
Take care of him.
The compass is
getting interference
from three very strong demons.
Don't let him rush in blindly.
I'll go airborne and
try to get a sneak peak.
Don't worry about me!
What do you think?
Botan says it's gonna
be three nasty demons
against little old us.
It sounds good to me.
This mission's felt
different from the very start.
It's like I've
become invincible.
Well, let's go.
Fastest money I've ever lost!
Very impressive.
Obviously the members
of the Apparition Gang
aren't as frightening
as I've been told.
Don't dump your stocks
just yet, old boy.
The next group a' demons
are on a whole different level!
[TOGURO 1] They call
themselves the Triad.
Demon One.. Miyuki.
Demon Two.. Inmaki.
Demon Three.. Gokumonki.
The Triad?
Word is they're the
toughest set of demons
in the whole Apparition Gang!
You must be forkin'
over a lot of money
for those kind
of names!
He'll be in a real bind
if those Hiruiseki
Stones don't come through.
Let's move on!
Your second bet--The
intruders or the demon Triad!
Five hundred
million on the Triad!
Yes, gimme three
hundred mill on them!
[CLUB MAN 3]
Me too!
[CLUB MAN 4]
Yes. Same for me.
Twenty billion on
the intruders this time.
[All] What??
[CLUB MAN 4]
Twenty billion? On those humans?
[CLUB MAN 3] Yeah,
that's Sakyou for 'ya.
Doesn't know when to quit!
Obviously that man is not
thinking with his brain.
No one's askin' for
your opinion, broad!
Just go do your stuff!
We'll take care of them.
[BOTAN] What a waste
of a gorgeous home!
What's going on?
Sounds like a
friggin' war zone!
Don't be alarmed, boys.
Those poor intruders must
have met up with my land mines.
Yusuke! Kuwabara!
Oh please!
Bingo!
Who are these people??
Hello there intruders,
my name is Miyuki.
How'd you like a fight?
[NARRATOR] The boys have barged
into Tarukane's stronghold.
But can they defeat
the demon Triad,
the Toguro Brothers,
Tarukane, and save Yukina??
[YUSUKE] Don't let that glossy,
purple lipstick fool you!
This girl isn't
out for a good time,
unless, of course, it
includes stringing me up
and swinging me around like
I'm a giant Yusuke piñata!
And Kuwabara keeps yelling--
[KUWABARA] Don't hit girls!
[YUSUKE] But even if I do find
a way to take her down,
she's only the first
of the Demon Triad!
We still have two more
powerful demons to face!
It's buy one battle
and get two free,
on the next jam-packed
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪