♪
[NARRATOR] As Team Urameshi
moves into the semi-finals
of the Dark Tournament,
Yusuke and his friends
got a first glimpse at the
ominous Toguro Brother's team,
who await at the
end of their path.
In lieu of the danger,
the mysterious Masked
Fighter led Yusuke
to the forested
outskirts of the island,
and revealed herself to
be the elderly Genkai,
able to revert to her
younger appearance
when harnessing
her Spirit Energy.
Her motivation for
disguise still unclear,
she has challenged Yusuke
to complete his training--
with one last test.
Okay, you're a great lawnmower.
Does this have a point
or are you just bragging?
[GENKAI] You're not hard
to read by now, dimwit.
I know your crabby-ass jokes
are your way of admitting
I'm far more powerful than you.
The point is that you can
have this power for yourself.
But to reach it,
you must face the darkest
shadows of your soul.
What do you mean?
"Darkest shadows of my soul?"
[thunder]
I'm old Yusuke.
I can't use my powers
like I once could.
There was a time when that
blast would have gone for miles.
It's a thing we
all have to deal with.
The progression into old age.
You can sharpen your skills.
Learn new strategies
and neat-o techniques.
But as your
mind grows in wisdom.
Your strength disappears.
[GENKAI] And against foes like
Toguro, you have to bow out.
You just blew up a mountain!
And you still say
you can't beat him??
Well of course.
At my age it's impossible.
And why the hell
should that bother me?
I for one never
had the urge to invent
a purpose for my abilities.
No heroics crap.
There was just the sense that
my power should always exist.
As long as I pass it on, I don't
have any ridiculous regrets.
Let the next bonehead
do something noble with it.
Who knows, maybe
that bonehead's you.
Once you start this you can't
back out. Are you ready for it?
Yeah, anything
to beat up Toguro.
Can you stand through
every hardship?
Just give me the damn test.
All right...
In order to gain my power.
You must be willing...
To take away my life.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
It's the only way, slacker.
Are you ready to kill me or not?
I'm going to be waiting
for you in a cave.
Come and find me when
you've made up your mind.
But, Genkai...
[thunder]
This is so stupid.
How can she really
expect me to do that?
You've always quit
any time the answer wasn't
served on a silver plate.
Shut up. Shut... UP!!!
I don't have
to listen to you!
Half-ass!!
Grizzly Claw!!
Got me.
He really saved me.
I never would have gotten
any of this without her.
But I can't go on
without that power!
Come on, Genkai!
What am I supposed to do?!!!
[KUWABARA] So, hey...
Urameshi and the masked lady
sure have been
gone a long time.
Indeed.
Kurama, what do you
think about our chances?
Two more rounds
and we getta go home!
These are the semifinals.
It will definitely be
a challenge to overcome.
We'll be moved to a new stadium
with an even wilder crowd.
And I'm sure the committee
will do anything to thwart us.
That doesn't bother me.
Bring on the guns
and the arrows--
it's nothin' I'm afraid of!
[door opens]
Dat-dit-dit-daaa...
The cavalry has arrived!
Hey there you guys.
You know, you could
have knocked Botan!
We're discussing
important business here!
Oh? And how do you explain
the cards in your hand?
I guess you've never
seen a mobster movie!
Has your back injury
healed yet, Kazuma?
Aw yeah, it was
just a scratch!
You want to play
some cards with us?
[BOTAN THINKS] So much for
Botan getting attention!
Um, have you
seen Yusuke?
He's still out with the Masked
Fighter. We're not sure where.
I see.
I hope he's fine.
Puu's been acting really funny.
He doesn't even want to fly.
Puu.
Whatever he's doing I'm
sure he can handle it Keiko.
Let's just have some fun, okay?
Okay!!!
That's right baby brother,
it might be your
last night in the living.
Enjoy yourself--I won't tell mom
if you drink your first beer.
Gosh darn it Shizuru!
You always gotta' embarrass
me in front of my friends!
I'm gettin' the hang
of this five-card draw!
Who wants to go fish?!
Come join us Hiei. We're
practically a family here.
Kurama!
Do not make me pull out
your precious voice box!
[thunder]
[YUSUKE] Alright Genkai.
Where are you hiding?
Have you made your
decision, Yusuke?
[thunder]
Then let's get this over with.
There's no time to waste.
[YUSUKE]
You're my teacher.
Yeah, so what?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry but, I give up.
Listen, I know you're counting
on me and that's great,
but if it means
I gotta take out
the only person who ever
taught me anything useful.
I'd rather
take my chances...
With us fighting as a team.
I mean I'm sure I can break
his shades or something.
Points for the cave
idea-great atmosphere--
But all in all I think
you're a head-case! See-ya!
You've answered correctly.
Don't look so
startled, moron.
You've qualified for
the test so let's go!
Wait a second you old hag,
did your hearing aid fall out?
I said I wasn't going to do it!
You give quite a speech
when it's important Yusuke,
but do you really think I'd
give my power to a student
who would willingly
take his teacher's life
to gain more strength?
And yet at the same time
I need someone who wouldn't
refuse the idea immediately.
This isn't for
sissies, you know.
I guess you can thank me later
for my astounding cleverness.
Stupid fossil--
I can't believe I said all that
touchy-feely crap for nothin'!
Not for nothing.
You will remember everything
that went through your head.
[GENKAI] I want to ask
you one more time...
Can you handle
the hardship?
I am about to transfer
something to you.
A something that only the
true and deserving successor
of the Spirit Wave can receive.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Her body temperature is
going through the roof!
What is it, brother?
[TOGORO 2]
It's our mutual friend.
This tournament is finally
about to get interesting.
To be brutally honest,
you shouldn't be
ready for this
until another ten
years of my training.
Even if you did come to
me with unusual talent.
It's the secret of my
power, Spirit Wave Orb.
For years I toiled
with this creation.
Energy of the
spirit and the body
concentrated into
the smallest space.
It is both part of
and separate from me,
and it could power
a whole city block.
Your test is to incorporate
this into your own body,
and hope it doesn't
tear you apart.
The agony of this
absorption is beyond words.
It could go on
for hours or days.
If your body cannot handle it
you will be eaten
away from the inside out.
And the only thing you will
pray for is a quicker death.
Well hell, if it's
gonna be that exciting,
I might as well
order two of 'em.
Yusuke, are you ready?
Yeah.
[YUSUKE] So that's it?
Please, I've had measle shots
more agonizing than that!
[labored breathing]
[painfully] Darn you Genkai!
[GENKAI THINKS] I hope you
can endure it, Yusuke.
[Yusuke screams in agony]
Goin' fast! Primo seats on
the second deck! Whatta ya say?!
[JURI] Sorry to
keep you waiting,
all you demons out there!
Hello everybody,
it's so great to meet you!
My name's Juri and
I'll be the referee!
It's my first time!
So be friendly, okay!
[KOTO] That's right,
you pain enthusiasts!
The semi-finals of the Dark
Tournament are poised to begin!
For reasons I can't talk about
I've been moved out of the ring
and into the measly
broadcasting booth.
Not that I'm bitter of course.
[JURI] First let's have
everyone locate their nearest
emergency exit-- just in case
things get rough!
I don't know sir.
The new stadium is
really spooking me out.
I mean your chair looks
like a big tarantula
and you can't even
see the day light!
[KOENMA] Yes, it seems these
weather-proof dome stadiums
are all the rave
these days.
I just wish they would
have included some A/C!
I wish they would've
used pastel paint!
Now it's with great honor that
I get the ceremony started!
The four surviving
semi-final teams!
[JURI]
Team Gorenja!
Of course Team Toguro!
[JURI]
Team Uraotogi!
And Team Urameshi!
Get those dirty
creatures off the screen!
[CROWD CHANTS]
Kill Yusuke! Kill Yusuke!
[JURI] All right!
Let's review how those
four teams will match up
in the semi-final round!
The pairings run top to bottom.
First off- Team Urameshi
vs. Team Uraotogi!
Let's get it started guys!
Hey, what's with Team Urameshi?!
They're short members!
Ha, looks like their own team
captain's too scared to fight!
Koenma sir! Yusuke still
hasn't returned to the team!
[KOENMA]
That's to be expected.
The kid is undergoing
Genkai's ultimate test.
It's not like that was going
to be just an afternoon affair.
But what should they do?
Until Yusuke and Genkai return
they'll be severely outnumbered!
In the
semi-finals, no less!
[KOENMA] Oh blast it Ogre,
they'll just have to deal!
I'm much more concerned
as to whether Yusuke
will come back at all!
I was not exactly
expecting to fight this
round three against five.
Whatever cause is delaying
them must be important.
We'll simply have
to work around it.
I don't know why you're
all stressin', Hiei!
I'll just beat 'em all myself!
Let's go!!!
[Yusuke crying out in agony]
[GENKAI] Yusuke, you
mustn't be afraid.
The energy will
absorb in time,
but only if you have
the will to endure it.
Give in to the pain now,
and I assure you. You will die.
[Yusuke crying out in agony]
[KOTO on radio] Here I am
at ringside, people,
and the first fight
of the semi-finals
is only minutes away!
The energy of the
crowd is breathtaking,
and within the
walls of this giant dome
the excitement seems to fester
like mold in leftover take-out!
Team Urameshi and Team Uraotogi
are now approaching the ring--
I can tell already this is
going to be a joyous bloodbath!
Puu.
What magnificent images
of destruction and misery
must be swimming through
these competitor's heads
as they stare down
their enemies in the ring!
But as the countdown
approaches zero.
Yusuke and the Masked Fighter
have still not
entered the stadium!
Leaving their teammates
mismatched three to five!
Does this mean the
controversial demons
Hiei and Kurama will
each have to fight twice
to keep their team alive?
[KUWABARA] What's
that supposed to mean?!
I said I'm takin'
'em all myself!!
I thought we agreed
on a good fight.
What has happened to
the rest of your team?
Oh, they just said you guys
weren't worth their time!
It is now time to choose
the conditions for your fight!
It doesn't matter.
Let's just see who lives.
You're a hasty one,
aren't you boy?
I take it you're fighting first.
That's right I am.
First, last and only.
[HIEI] I've been under
too much stress lately.
Killing you all should
be a good remedy.
We're all anxious
to fight here.
Why don't we let an outside
party decide the pairings.
[SHISHI WAK.] Each six-sided
die represents a team,
with one member's
name on each side.
The sixth is a free space,
and anyone can fight
when it comes up.
You fight as many times
as your name appears
as long as you're still alive.
Doesn't bother me.
But one thing.
Whenever it's the name
of someone not around..
I will be fighting
in their place.
Okay! Matches will be
chosen by rolling of dice,
multiple turns are allowed,
and as always in the semi-finals
five wins will advance!
Fate makes her choice.
Looks like you
got Makintaro, Hiei.
Your desperate
plan has backfired.
You talk way too
big, little man!
Alright fans,
it's the first match-up
of the semi-finals!
Hiei versus the
big man Makintaro!
Begin!
That's very impressive.
What's wrong? Did we have a
little accident in our trousers?
Your whole nervous system...
It leaves much to be desired.
What are you talking about--
my "nervous system"!
Come on, just give
me your best shot!
Fool, I already have.
Well now, isn't
that a bit disgraceful.
He's even faster
than last time!!
Did you see that?
Nope, not at all.
You're lucky I'm generous.
Hey where are you going?
I'm not done with you!!
I said I'm not
done with you yet!!
Axe-Blade Fist!!!
Die!!!
Got 'ya!!
Your eyes are rather slow.
Too bad.
[crowd grossed out]
Ger-oss!
What about that one?
Did you see him dodge sir?
Well of course!
Aw heck, who
am I kidding.
He's fast!
I need some
eye drops.
And the winner
by death is Hiei!
Hiei wins in under a minute,
getting bonus points in
my book for both skull
piercing and amputation!
And that means it's
time for match two!
Go ahead and roll Shishi.
I have a feeling it's
going to be me once more.
[Yusuke cries out in agony]
[NARRATOR] As Team Urameshi's
crucial battle begins,
their captain is still writhing
under Genkai's brutal test.
Can Yusuke endure the
over-powering energy
that rips away at his body,
and can the others survive
the semi-final
round without him?
[KUWABARA] Hey guys, it's me--
the acting team leader now
that Urameshi's disappeared!
It's fight two of
the big-time semis,
and it turns out that Kuro
guy with the bubble gum
is really some
kind of hairy freak!
Hair and gum seem
dangerous to me,
but anyway--
Hiei insists on
goin' two in a row,
and when his sword suddenly
turns to scrap metal,
a certain super-powerful
Dragon technique
just might be comin' your way!
I'm runnin' for cover,
but you guys can watch--
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪