♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi has been
kidnapped by three human
teens with unusual powers,
and is now trapped in the
House of Four Dimensions.
Kurama has defeated
the first kidnapper,
using his power over
plants and his cunning wit
to outsmart the genius
Kaitou at his own word game.
With Kaitou's soul extracted,
his psychic Territory wore off,
and Hiei, Kuwabara,
and Botan were saved.
But two gifted
psychics still await.
Nap time is over.
Looks like you guys defeated
my old pal Kaitou...
Very impressive.
So far, we have only
been successful in opening
two of the three doors
that will lead us to
the subsequent room.
Don't tell me that's the
reason you guys woke me up.
We woke you up because
we discovered this
posted warning...
...the one that says Yusuke
dies if we open the door
without your approval.
That is a good reason.
If you know what's good for you,
you will give us your approval,
unless you harbor a death wish.
May I remind you that
those kinds of tactics
don't work here Hiei,
so keep your mouth shut and
do exactly what I tell you.
It really chaps my hide
that we have to stand here
and swallow this dweeb's abuse.
[Yanagisawa laughs]
Your friends may have
been able to defeat Kaitou
but I wonder if they'll
make it up here alive?
Why don't you say
something useful
like how long are you
gonna to keep me here!
What? Are you're tired
of standing still?
Nice effort Urameshi.
Now what's going on?
Interesting.
[KUWABARA] Jeeze,
this place is big!
You've got your
own stair museum!
Yusuke is on
the next floor up,
but each one of you's gotta
take a different staircase
to get to him.
What?!
What's your reason
for separating us?
My reason?
It's like the old saying goes,
that's for me to know
and for you to find out.
Listen weasel!!
[KURAMA]
Kuwabara!
I understand your frustration,
but if we wish to help
Yusuke we must comply.
[Yanagisawa laughs]
Oh, I forgot...!!
I knew this stuff would come
in handy, now let me see.
Here it is!
This clever little gadget is
guaranteed to blow you away!
The always-stylish Megiru Seal!!
[doorbell rings]
Oh great, here we go.
But Botan, what
can it do?
Glad you asked!
It's a modified version
of the classic Tattoo Seal
used as an inmate tracking
device in Spirit World jails.
Only the applier
can remove it!
Hey look, it's
stuck like glue!
Let me try,
Ta Da!
Whoa! Awesome!
What else?
If the person who
attached the seal dies,
it will automatically fall off.
[BOTAN] Also, the seal will
change colors to indicate
that person's physical status,
blue if all is well,
yellow if slightly hurt,
and red if seriously injured.
All in one convenient package!
Pretty neat, huh?
[KURAMA] I see. So we
should write our names
on the seals and attach
them to one another.
Then we will know
if someone is hurt.
Hopefully these are allowed.
Whatever, I don't care.
[BOTAN]
Well, they're all blue.
Glad to know we're all okay.
Everyone except you Hiei.
I don't need them.
Sure you do. You want
to know we're okay.
Touch me and I break
your wrist.
Could it be that Hiei
has already forgotten
that his soul was
the first to be lost?
[BOTAN] So there, rebel!
[KUWABARA] He told you!
I'm ready when the
rest of you guys are.
I'm all set here.
Let's begin.
Remember, caution is our ally.
You bet!
Those seals were a good idea,
too bad they won't be any help.
Kido, everything's
going as planned,
they're on their
way up right now.
Ah, perfect!
This is much easier
than I thought,
too bad that poor sap Kaitou
won't be present to witness it.
Yusuke. Good news.
Your friends are coming
up to visit you.
Then clue me in. Why aren't
you running for your life?
[YUSUKE] They're stronger
and faster than you,
and they don't feel bad
breakin' someone's face.
I may suck at' math,
but I know they
have four shadows
and you only have two legs.
And once they free me by
bustin' out that spotlight,
you'll get to know the floor.
Laugh all you want!
But you know if I'd seen what
kind of lame ass power you had,
there'd be no way in hell
you would have
been able to trap me!!
Yes, Yusuke,
you would win,
there's no question
in my mind about that.
But you see...
It doesn't matter what
you would have done,
because the fact
is I did trap you.
[KUWABARA THINKS] This is
ridiculous, dumb stairs.
haven't you people
ever heard of escalators?
W-Wait a minute, the stairs
are goin down now.
Either that or I'm losin' it.
[BOTAN THINKS] I think
I'm going to be ill!
Amateurs.
[KIDO] If I wanted to,
I could kill you right now,
just by covering
your mouth and nose.
Go on then! It'd be
a hell of a lot better
than just standing
here listening to your b.s.
Sorry, Yusuke, too easy.
We have other plans for you.
Welcome.
What's up guys?
[KUWABARA]
Urameshi!
[BOTAN]
Yusuke?
[KUWABARA]
What's going on?
Why are you just
standing there like that?
Just stay where you are,
I'm here because I'm stuck.
If you get close enough for
him to step on your shadow,
you'll be stuck too!
[KIDO]
That's true...
But I'm not the one you
should be worried about...
...one of your friends
is an imposter.
What is that supposed to mean?!
Now, let's begin the
next game shall we?
Like I said,
one of your companions is
not who they appear to be.
What the...?
Your only objective in this game
is to determine the imposter.
In ten minutes, beginning now.
As for the four of you,
you are only allowed to speak
when Yusuke has asked
you a direct question.
I don't know this guy!
How do we know he's
telling us the truth?
I find it hard to believe anyone
could disguise themselves
so perfectly in such a
short amount of time.
I thought I told you not to
speak unless you were spoken to.
Don't you care what
happens to your buddies?
I could easily slit
your throat before
you even think about doing
anything to the detective.
You don't follow me do you?
Whoever is being impersonated
is currently in our prison.
Mr. Urameshi isn't
the only one at risk.
And for those of you
lacking in manners,
that means if anything
should happen to me,
the other person we've captured
will promptly be killed.
It seems your group has
thought of everything.
Let me guess.
If I don't find the
fake one in ten minutes,
you'll kill the
real one.
Uh oh, nine left.
[KIDO]
You're wasting time.
I suggest you get started.
Don't rush me!
Let's see, what's the best
way to weed out a fake?
Kuwabara, what's your blood
type and when were you born?
Figures, you have to
suspect me first off!
Oh, get over yourself
and answer me!
Okay Mr. Crabby-pants,
but do you even
know my birthday
and my blood type
in the first place?
I guess I don't.
This is pathetic.
Kurama, now tell me your mom's
name and how old she is.
Her name is Shiori,
she is forty years old,
and she will be
married in the fall.
That's great! Tell her
congratulations for me!
Hey, am I invited
to the wedding?
Only seven minutes.
All right, Botan!
Prove to me who you are by
telling me your boob size.
Have you lost your
mind completely.
You and I both know I've never
told you anything of the sort!!
You told me when we were on the
roof of the school, remember?
You just made that up!!!
You disgusting pervert!!!
Damn it! And she almost
fell for it too.
This stupidity is
making me nauseous.
Fine, we'll go to you.
What's your little
sister's name?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I bet he's the fake.
You know her well enough.
I refuse to play
this nonsense game.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Nope,
that's definitely Hiei...
bad attitude and all.
Hey that's weird...
I didn't know you had
a little sis, Hiei.
I bet she's a
pint-sized pain
in the you know what
just like you.
Probably ugly, too.
[HIEI]
I will kill you.
I forgot Kuwabara doesn't
know the relation.
Huh?!
So everyone knows
about her except me?!
Well, basically.
Why didn't you punks
clue me in earlier!!!
It's complicated.
Well, what are you
looking at me for?
We don't have time
to talk about this!
Aw have a heart Kurama,
tell me what her name is.
Five minutes left.
I'll talk to you
about her later!
Okay, you better
mean it!!
Any day now, Urameshi!
Get off me, I'm going
as fast as I can!
[YUSUKE]
Um, guys?
What's the deal with the
stupid looking name tags?
If a certain someone
had paid more attention
when I was explaining
their tools to them,
they'd know that these
are your Megiru Seals!
Oh yeah, I forgot,
sorry about that.
Ya know, sometimes I think
you might be the imposter.
Wait, that's the only one
who can remove the seal
is the one who put it on, right?
Yes, because both
humans and demons
have their own
unique energy print.
Hey that's it!!
I see, the imposter
cannot remove the seals.
All right, ready?
[ALL] Ready.
This is rather troubling.
What the hell?!
This smells
fishy, guys.
But this is impossible,
these things are supposed
to be fool proof.
So there was never an
imposter to begin with.
He's been bluffing
the whole time!
Good guess, but I
assure you there's a fake.
Yanagisawa's
power is copy,
and that is why your
seals don't work.
He has the ability to copy
not only someone's appearance,
but their voice, their
mannerisms, their memories,
and yes, even this
so-called energy print.
He could copy
your own mother
and you would never
tell the difference,
not even with your
little magic stickers.
Bastard.
From what my watch says,
your time's run out.
In a few moments,
I'm going to release you.
Then, it will be
decision time.
I want you to approach the
person you think is the imposter
and hit them as hard as you can.
Are you insane!?
Sorry champ, but that's the
only way to disarm Yana's power.
He has to be hit so hard that
it knocks him unconscious.
And of course, if you
choose the wrong person,
I'll have your
captive friend killed.
So try to be smart, okay?
What's your deal, what do you
get out of doing this to us?
I was wondering
when you'd ask that.
You've made a lot of
friends and enemies, Yusuke.
And now, we're doing one
of them a special favor.
Now make your pick.
You only have thirty
seconds to choose.
I could just order the
hostage to be killed
and save you the trouble.
You have fifteen seconds.
[YUSUKE] Enough! I've decided.
Just don't take this personally.
I hope I'm RIGHT!!!
Uh oh!!
Wow, you actually
figured it out.
How did you know that the
imposter was Kuwabara?
I chose him because I
know that he's used to me
pounding his face in,
if nothing else.
Besides, Hiei and Kurama are
too smart and untrusting.
They'd never just walk
right into your trap.
Yes, or scream
the word Hot.
Now that still
left me Botan.
And if you dirt
bags were low enough
to take advantage of
the only non-fighter,
it wouldn't matter if I lost.
Even if you killed me,
I would come back from the
dead and drop kick your ass,
so Kuwabara was the safest bet.
My hero!
I must say, you're
quite impressive.
The game is over!
Now cough up Kuwabara!!
And he better
not be injured!
[KIDO]
Kuwabara is just fine.
And I will return him to
you in the very near future.
But first off,
I'd like to introduce to
you the master of this plan.
I can't believe it.
Why would you do
something like this?
Tell me you crazy old hag!!!
[KIDO]
I'm sorry!
Forgive me,
I failed you master.
Cool it with the
theatrics all right Kido?
If we're being honest here,
I was counting on
you screwing it up.
You never cease to
surprise me Genkai.
I thought you might have
been behind this little ruse.
This doesn't
make any sense!
Why don't you
explain it fox-boy,
'cause I'm
obviously going nuts!!
She was trying to teach
us a very valuable lesson,
a lesson about perception.
Yes, and it's a lesson
you must learn very well.
I guarantee this won't be the
last time you come in contact
with individuals who posses
the power of Territory.
Kurama, when did you
realize it was Genkai?
When we had reached the
top of the stairs.
If they had truly used their
resources, wanted it more,
we most definitely would
have been defeated.
Give me a break!
But there was an
ulterior motive here
and I realized that
whoever orchestrated this
was trying to tell us
something about ourselves,
that would require someone
who knows us well,
and meant no harm.
You still haven't
given us a reason.
You haven't
sufficiently explained
what you're trying
to accomplish
just by rubbing their
powers in our faces.
The four of you are
well trained fighters.
However, as three of
you have found out,
there will be instances
when your physical strength
will not be able to help you,
so you must depend on your mind.
If you had used that lump
three feet above your ass
you might've held
on to your soul.
[GENKAI] Make that
two feet for you.
Are you for real,
you actually let those
jerks steal your soul?
Show some skill!
Oh? And what
about you, dimwit?!
Ah, come on, I wouldn't
have been caught
if I had known about
that shadow thing.
Are you foolish enough to think
that one of your enemies
would just hand over
that information!?!
If an enemy captures you
you're as good as dead,
if you remember anything
then remember that.
Time out, Grandma.
You keep saying enemy,
but these scrubs aren't
actually bad, right?
So who the hell are they?
Go on, inform them Kido.
Yes master.
Kaitou, Yana and I,
we all went to her compound
for advice when we
developed our powers.
That's where we learned about
you, Yusuke, and your team.
The truth of it is,
we've only had these new
abilities for about a month.
Same as all the
other new psychics.
New psychics?
The cause of which is
our greatest threat.
You're making
me nervous.
I assume some of you
have already noticed
the demon insects flying
through the city.
You don't mean...
Someone is carving out a
tunnel to the Demon World.
Sakyo's plan from
the Dark Tournament
was not buried with him.
What, Sakyo plan?
[KUWABARA] Yeah.
Genkai just filled me in.
Apparently Koenma found
out and never told us.
Sakyo wanted money so he could
drill some doomsday tunnel.
But more importantly, we've
answered the question...
Boxers or briefs.
Would you be serious
for second!
It's not my fault that idiot
stole my clothes! Jeeze!
But how could this be?
I thought Sakyo died when
he blew up the stadium.
[GENKAI] He's dead.
We're sure of that.
And now he's rolling
in his grave,
because someone continued
his plan without him.
It just keeps going,
doesn't it?
[NARRATOR]
The truth is out.
Yusuke's kidnapping
was a mere precursor
to their next great trial.
Who has followed in
Sakyo's footsteps,
and what tragedy awaits
if this tunnel is made?
[YUSUKE] Okay. If anyone's ever
had questions about Demons,
or Demon World,
or what happens when a
crazy guy unleashes
shopping-mall sized
beasts on the earth,
you're gonna hate yourself
for the rest of your life
if you miss
this next episode.
Koenma's laying
out all the secrets
he's kept since the first
time I got hit by a car.
Plus, you'll get a glimpse
of the kick ass new villain,
and a certain frightening
head in a fish tank.
Sound exciting?
Well of course it does!
Just watch my friggin' life,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪