♪
[NARRATOR] In the highest
tower of Maze Castle,
a desperate fight continues.
Suzaku, last of
the Saint Beasts,
wants to flood
the Earth with demons,
and used his dark techniques
to bring Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi to his knees.
But remembering Keiko,
and the others who need him,
Yusuke rose again with powers
he never believed he had.
Suzaku however, refuses
to give up his chance
to rule the Earth.
Now is the final attack,
and both sides have
everything to lose.
[MURUGU] I am so exhausted of
looking at this dirty human!
Can't you finish him?
Of course.
I'm sure you
recognize this by now!
This can't be! I've used
too much energy on him!
I can't form the attack!
Well isn't that a heartbreaker.
I've got enough
energy to serve seven!!!
Shotgun!!!
Like I said,
enough for seven...
[YUSUKE] And that's about it.
Hey, this stone
feels comfortable.
We've got to get to an exit!
[IWAMOTO] You can't
run forever, Ukimura!
Oh, Botan! Botan!!
Run away.
I can't leave you!
[Iwamoto laughs]
The community comes together
when it's important, see.
And correcting bad
girls is very important.
[Iwamoto laughs]
Destroying that whistle
is her only chance.
Please... be close by.
It's far away... Typical.
[MURUGU] I'll never
let you reach it!
[YUSUKE]
Really?
Well I was thinking a hot
meal is just what I need.
I bet you taste exactly
like roasted chicken.
[Murugu cries out]
You're just trying to scare me!
I heard you say you
didn't have any energy left!
Yeah, not enough.
To take down
another Saint Beast,
but I've got plenty to
deep fry a smart-assed bird.
But hey, if being lunch meat
is something you've always been
curious about, then go ahead.
Touch that whistle again.
[BLUE OGRE]
Oh, wow.
Yusuke has learned a lot, huh?
Six months ago he would
have dumped all his energy
into one blow without
thinking about his next move.
Now he's planned ahead--
I'm very impressed.
No, actually
Yusuke did use all his
Spirit Energy in
that last attack.
But, he said--
So he's helpless?!
Indeed, this is what we
call a high-stakes bluff.
This blows, by the time we
plow through all these weirdos
we'll be too tired
to help Urameshi!
Tired hands are
better than none.
Do what you like--
I'm not stopping.
Okay guys I'm coming!
Don't leave!!
You're safe, Keiko.
Thanks for stalling him, Murugu.
Of course, his efforts to
scare you away were all lies.
If he could still
use his Spirit Gun
then he would have already
destroyed the whistle.
Of course.
Your final attack.
Its power was very impressive
but I'm afraid it will not
accomplish what you wished.
It wasn't strong
enough to kill me.
And that will
prove fatal for you.
All your precious
energy wasted on me.
Give me a break...
Go look in a mirror.
You're just as injured as I am.
[Suzaku laughs]
What?
You still don't understand the
depths of my power, do you?
Hey, that's their Spirit Energy.
[Suzaku laughs]
He's using the spirits
of those other six
Suzakus to heal himself.
Let me ask you something
of a philosophical question.
If you take the
lives of your selves
in order to save
your self, is it murder?
Freak.
Now, now, don't get emotional.
I'll bring them back
if they mean so much.
[YUSUKE]
What the--? Oh hell.
Black secret technique.
The Prism of Seven Restoration!!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
After all that damage
he's completely back to normal!
The only way to defeat me is to
kill all seven at the same time.
But you're far too
weak to do that now.
Gee, this time he really
should have dumped
all his energy into one attack.
But I guess he did dump it all
and it still didn't work.
Which I guess means the
human race is going extinct!
Be quiet! Be quiet! Be quiet!
Yusuke, I know there's
nothing more you can do
from what we've taught you,
but surely there's
something else! Magic?!
A missile launcher?! Anything?!
I know precisely what my
problem has been with you.
I've been treating
you like a normal human
when obviously you are not.
I'm not sure what you are.
But this time I'll
fire enough Spirit Energy
to send King Yama to his grave!
Prism Storm of Torment!!!
[Suzaku groups power up]
The biggest lightning
eruption by far.
Suzaku is getting desperate.
The attack will almost
surely kill one of them.
Don't say that!
No!
The stairs.
Now what are we gonna do?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
This is embarrassing.
Being blown back
by his stupid energy.
[YUSUKE THINKS] My Spirit
Energy is completely dry.
I can't do a thing!
The lives of you and
your miserable friends
are all coming to a
close at the same time.
I love good endings.
[YUSUKE THINKS] No.
[YUSUKE THINKS] I'm letting
them down. I'm letting them--
Now it's over!
No!!!
The lightning energy
has missed its target.
I don't see how that can--
Oh no, my tentacle!
Spirit Gun!!!
[SUZAZU] His first attack.
He must have damaged
it without my knowing.
These tentacles are the
guiding lights for my attacks.
They've been dipped
in thick armor
and still he made one crumble.
[SUZAZU]
All this time--
I've, halfway missed!
I am so tired of
being electrocuted!
[SUZAKU] You are not human,
Yusuke, but I will kill you.
Even if it takes
me a thousand tries!
My poor tentacle won't
allow me a direct hit,
so I will just have to
tear at you piece by piece!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Darn it, Yusuke!
Think of something!
You can't take another hit!
Needless to say,
hold on tight.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Spirit
Energy is so stupid.
Doesn't give me
enough to do anything,
except just sit up and
watch everything go wrong!
[KEIKO]
Yusuke!!!
Keiko!
Yusuke!
[Keiko cries out]
Yusuke!!!
[YUSUKE]
That's it.
What's this? Where is
his energy coming from?
His life! He's using
life energy from his body!!
He's actually willing to
sacrifice his life for her!
[SUZAKU] What will
he profit from that?
Such power!
Prism Storm of Torment!!
Shotgun!!!
Urameshi!!
[blast]
[MURUGU]
Suzaku!!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] For you, Keiko.
I'm sorry I couldn't
be there too.
[crackling fire]
I was wrong about
you once again, Yusuke.
It wasn't because you
weren't human that I lost.
I lost because you were--
Feelings are your power.
Touche human.
At last I understand.
All right!! Sound the bells!!
Is this really appropriate, sir?
Suzaku may be defeated but
Yusuke gave his life to do it!
What? Oh--Oh yes,
of course-- How sad.
[KUWABARA]
Wake up Urameshi!
Let's go home!!
I'm sorry, he's expended
all of his body energy.
His heart is stopping.
[KUWABARA] Then I'll give
him some of my own!
That wouldn't be very wise.
Your body is still
badly injured from Byakko.
Any more strain
on it could kill you.
Me and Urameshi jumped
into this deal together.
And we're both
gonna come out alive
or we're not coming
out at all! Okay?!
Here goes, Urameshi! Come on!!!
Well I suppose now we'll have
to return to living world
carrying both
of them on our backs.
Like I said, baby sitting.
Here's what I don't understand.
Why would he bother saving
her if he died in the process?
Trust me Hiei,
there are reasons.
Maybe for a person
who's lived there.
But I'd never do it.
The challenge is enough without
taking someone else's slack.
[birds chirping]
Well, about time you woke up.
[YUSUKE]
Where am I?
You're in my room. Which,
by the way, is back on Earth.
You've been sleeping
for three days straight.
Three days, it feels like
I've been out for a while.
School looks like a war zone,
and classes got
cancelled for a week!
I talked to your mom, too,
so don't worry about that!
Okay, and what about Keiko?
What about Keiko and Botan?!
[YUSUKE]
What?
What?! Hey!!
You better start doin' more
than clenching your teeth!
Tell me what happened to her!!
I recognize that yell
anywhere! What's up, Yusuke?
Botan. Keiko.
[KUWABARA] Oh my gosh
that was so great!
[KURAMA] Sorry Yusuke.
He insisted.
You really should have seen
the look on your face!!!
[YUSUKE] Come here you jerk!
I'll show you a look!!!
[KUWABARA]
Hey! Hey!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Oh man. I
really screwed up big this time.
Bet she's still mad at me
for ditching out at the movie,
not to mention pulling
a Houdini for a week
and not telling her anything.
Like well,
about the zombies
that might be coming
after her and--
Guess I should
tell her something.
Usually I just let
her hit me a few times
and then try to explain myself.
[YUSUKE]
Hey uh, Keiko!
Everything's my fault and I'm
a jerk, so just hit me okay?
[YUSUKE THINKS] Here it comes.
I'll forgive you
on one condition.
I got Botan to fill me in
on everything up to this point.
But the next time you go
off on one of these cases,
you have to promise
to tell me about it!
You hear me?
That's all I'm asking for.
You've made me feel like a fool
the way everyone else around you
is in on your little
secret life except for me.
It's like I don't count.
[YUSUKE] I didn't tell my mom.
[KEIKO] Yusuke. You don't
tell your mom anything.
Well I didn't tell you
because I was just trying
to protect you, okay?
Yes. We can all see how
well that plan turned out.
You're right.
And if I'd known
you'd get attacked
by guys controlled
by insects
I'm sure I would've
mentioned it.
Yusuke, you still
haven't promised me yet.
[KEIKO]
Yusuke.
[BOTAN] Strap on
your boots, everyone,
because Spirit Detective
breaks last long!
Why is Hiei playing
delivery boy?
With a strange
encoded videotape
explaining Yusuke's
next big case!
It's a search
and rescue mission,
complete with a beautiful
damsel in distress.
Yukina--an ice apparition--
is being held prisoner
by a group of
black-market thugs,
who plan to profit
off her tears!
It's a mission full
of wicked new demons,
big surprises,
and even some love!
I'll see you there!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪