♪
[NARRATOR]
As Team Urameshi enters
the Dark Tournament's
semi-final round,
two of its members are
nowhere near the new stadium.
Yusuke is undergoing
his final test from Genkai--
absorbing an orb of
her energy so immense
that it has nearly
torn his body apart.
But there's no nearly for
Makintaro of Team Uraotogi,
as Hiei swiftly
won the first match
and has kept his
outnumbered team alive.
[JURI] Um, can we please
get a cleanup crew
to pick up this body?
That isn't part of
the referee job, is it?
[KOTO] Again--
I loved the brutality,
but next time let's
try to drag it out.
We mustn't forget our torturing!
Roll, I told you to hurry.
I'd like a chance
to finish warming up.
Careful, fate may
have a sense of humor.
So any of us versus--
Kuro Momotaro?
This might be my
lucky day after all.
[thunder]
[Yusuke struggling]
[GENKAI THINKS] He looks
so young, lying there.
God... and I've been
too blind to see.
[GENKAI] It'll be all right.
It's too much. Your body
cannot take any more.
I'm removing the Spirit Wave Orb
before you're just
a lump on the floor.
[GENKAI] Come on.
[YUSUKE]
Hey!
Hey! Give that
back, you old bitch!
Don't be an idiot Yusuke,
making you absorb
this energy so early
was a gamble and now we see why.
All my training with you
will be a waste of time
if you're not even alive
to fight against Toguro.
Perhaps there's
still time to put it off.
[YUSUKE SCREAMS]
Shove it up your ass!
You're not my freakin' mother!
So don't try telling
me what's good for me!
[Yusuke screams]
[GENKAI THINKS] He's certainly
got balls; I'll give him that.
[GENKAI THINKS] But it's going
to take a lot more than balls
to defeat Toguro.
I've watched Yusuke's
power increase steadily
throughout this tournament,
but I knew this was
a push from the start.
He may not be the
same immature brat
that first showed
up at my competition,
but he still has much to learn.
[Keiko screams]
What's the matter, Keiko?
Are you all right?
It's Yusuke.
Don't you worry, sweetie,
you just had a nasty dream.
Good heavens, how did the
sun sneak up on us like that?
We never should've
let those boys
talk us into playing
cards all night.
Shizuru, up and at 'em!
Same for you, Yukina!
They've already started!
Yusuke's pain felt so real!
He must be fighting now!
[PUU]
Puu?
If we can choose anybody from
our team to fight in this match.
Then of course
it's going to be me.
[JURI] The second
match of the semi-finals
will be Hiei
versus Kuro Momotaro.
Looks like we'll see an
interesting match-up this time.
Onji, you positive he
won't pull out that attack
he used to wipe out Zeru?
Absolutely
no chance of it!
[ONJI] Even if he were
stupid enough to try,
he couldn't go
through with it.
His arm still hasn't
recovered from the last time
he unleashed the Dragon
of the Darkness Flame.
I don't believe it's true!
He's going to attempt
the Darkness technique!
He and Zeru could
be obliterated at once!
You know it's impossible
to control it completely!
I have the power to
pull you into oblivion.
Resisting it is not
something I would do.
Dragon of the
Darkness Flame!!!
[Onji chuckles]
[ONJI]
If Hiei were smart,
he would've saved a
desperate move like that
for a more worthy
opponent, such as yourself.
Luckily enough for
you he couldn't wait.
His arm is in no condition
to use that move again.
That wouldn't've stopped me.
Don't be so
confident about that, Kuro.
Even with your abilities,
the Dragon of Darkness Flame
could roast you like a
blonde chicken on a spit.
Sorry to interrupt your
talk, but I'd like to fight.
What are you jokers whispering
about over there for so long?
If you've got something
so important to say,
why don't you share it
with the rest of the group!
Yes, if you wouldn't mind,
we'd like to start
the next match soon.
Or not.
We can wait 'til whenever
you think you might be ready.
Never have been the
ladies' man, have you Kuro?
I should give you some pointers.
I was a real
performer, you know.
Hiei puts on a brave
front even though he's hurt.
Sure he's no pushover,
but once your body has
done its little specialty.
We'll be well on our
way to fighting Toguro.
Just be sure
you hold him off
until your body can
memorize his special attacks.
That's how you'll defeat him.
You're wasting your breath.
I'm gonna chew him up,
spit him out, and stick
him under a desk.
Both fighters
please step forward!
[KURO] If I were you little man,
I wouldn't let that
last victory go to my head.
May have been the
biggest on our team,
but he was also the weakest.
Here, let me get
him off your sword.
[Kuro laughs]
Heeey! That's your teammate!
I think you'll find--
I'm just a tad tougher than
that Makintaro was.
Yeah, sweet sword.
Hate to say but
that's hardly hygienic.
You have no idea
how many creatures
that sword has cut through.
Oh, I'm sure.
Let me add one more.
Did he just forfeit the match?!
[KURO] Oh yeah, that's it!
It's hurts so good!
Oh, oh yeah baby!
Now we're talking!
These guys are making it a
little easy for us to beat 'em.
[DEMON FAN] That Kuro guy
must've gone off his rocker!
This is definitely one of the
more unconventional moves!
Sharp, not that it'll
do you any good now.
This here is the Steaming
Sphere that seals your fate!
I don't know what that is,
but he doesn't make
it sound very good.
Huh? Now what the heck
is that crackpot doing?
[Kuro laughs]
Beast Armor:
Armor of the Ape!
What do you think, Hiei?
Those spheres must contain some
sort of animalistic properties
that transform
him once consumed.
Kuro Momotaro's body
is now covered in hair!
So much for those
freshly-waxed washboard abs
I've loved so dearly.
Well, I won't be needing
this scrap metal anymore--
and I can honestly
say, neither will you.
We'll see about that.
And begin!
Let's put this
armor to the test.
Yeah! You've got him!
That's impossible! What the
heck happened to his sword?
I think it broke.
[HIEI] I'd rather destroy you
with own hands anyway.
He's in trouble.
Hiei!!
[KURO] You still there?
Guess you're probably wondering
how I was able to fend
off your attacks so easily.
Simple, really. My body
does this neat trick
where it remembers the pain
of my opponent's attack.
All I have to
do to get immunity
is expose myself to a small
dose of my enemy's offense.
Kind of like a flu shot.
[KURO] Once my body knows
what attack to look for.
Then it's time for a
good old Steaming Sphere.
What does that do?
Think of it as a
catalyst for my Beast Armor,
which makes me invincible
to my opponent's attack
and much more handsome to boot!
But, that's not fair!
There's no way Hiei can
beat someone invincible!
The big stupid one's
right about that.
[KOENMA] By golly!
Never seen that!
[KOENMA] Huh?
What's your trauma?
There... Those Steaming
Spheres he's got!
They're the same ones
used to brutally slaughter
my ancestors long ago.
Oh dear ancestors!
How you suffered so!
[KOENMA] This is no time for
misty water-colored nostalgia.
Hiei is in serious danger!
Sometimes I
really hate you...
Come on, let's go!
The guys need our support!
This way, ladies,
I know a shortcut!
Wait!...
We're forgetting Shizuru.
We don't have time for this!
Your brother could be dying!
Wait a second!
I forgot Puu!
He's still up in the room--
I didn't even leave him water!
Yusuke said that it's
like his other half!
I'll be right back!
Nooo! Oh Puu!
Puu? Where are you? Puu?
[PUU]
Puu!
[KEIKO]
There you are!
I'm so sorry--
is Yusuke all right?
Puu, Puu.
[GENKAI THINKS] I know that
this pain is severe, Yusuke,
but it's only
going to get worse.
You must endure if you're
going to truly succeed me.
Whoa! Hiei?
[CROWD CHANTS]
Kill Hiei! Kill Hiei! Kill Hiei!
Come on! Whatcha waiting for?
Where's your famous
Dark Dragon crap?
You want it?
As soon as my body memorizes
your most powerful attacks
I can squash you
in the palm of my hand!
[KURAMA THINKS]
Don't let your ego
cloud your
judgment, Hiei.
[HIEI] Who am I to turn
down a fan's request?
Just remember...
You brought this upon yourself.
Oh no! It looks
like Hiei's gonna call
on the Dragon of the
Darkness Flame again.
Get ready to duck and cover!
Hey! What's the holdup
here, you too weak to do it?
[HIEI] True pain takes
time, my friend.
Just try to keep
yourself amused.
You show him, Hiei!
His memory's not
so sharp after all.
Obviously he's forgotten what
that attack did to the last guy!
Not just him. The flame
took its toll on Hiei.
What?
[KURAMA THINKS]
To summon the Dragon,
Hiei must use his
own Spirit Energy
as bait to lure it from
the pits of Spirit World.
This technique only works
if he can emit a
tremendous amount of energy
for a prolonged period.
[Onji chuckles]
Yes, you are correct.
Hiei was in peak condition
when he used the
Darkness Flame against Zeru.
And even that wasn't enough
power for him to control it.
The beast nearly took the
hook along with the bait.
[KURAMA] Who knows
how he will fare now,
operating with little
over half of his energy.
That's half?
You're telling me he's making
that much energy at half--
his normal strengh?!
Regardless, he doesn't have
enough energy to unleash it.
With Hiei's
present levels.
The Dragon will devour
our friend in his entirety.
He's right about that.
But the truth of the matter is
that Hiei doesn't
have an option.
Without such a technique,
Kuro won't get a scratch.
Hiei, where is it?
[HIEI]
Here!
Fist of the Mortal Flame!
Hold on--that doesn't
look like a dragon!
It's a related flame,
but of the human world.
[JURI] Hiei seems to have
hit Kuro Momotoro pretty hard
with some sort
of terrible attack!
I decided, why waste
the flame of the underworld
on the likes of you
when the more mundane one
of the humans would suffice?
[Kuro laughs]
I really had you going
there for a second, didn't I?
[KOTO] It's an
unlikely reversal,
Kuro is back
on his feet!
That Fist of the Mortal Flame
would've sent lesser fighters
running for their mommies,
but not this brick wall!
[KURO] And now I've
memorized this pain, too!
[JURI] Kuro is squeezing another
one of those Steaming Spheres.
I wonder what he's
doing that for?
Could he possibly
get any tougher?
[Kuro laughs insanely]
[KURO] Your
little fist technique is
completely useless against me.
Now that I'm protected
by the second Beast...
The Armor of Phoenix!
This competitor just can't
seem to stay in one body
for more than a few minutes!
He's transformed into
some kind of giant bird!
This sequel to his Beast Armor
is even bigger and
badder than the first one!
What a rip-off--
this guy's too
chicken to stick around
and fight in his
own skin for a while!
Nicely put.
[NARRATOR] With Kuro
Momotaro growing invincible
to all of Hiei's attacks,
how can Team Urameshi's
warrior possibly win?
And how much more
of Genkai's torturous final
test can Yusuke take?
[HIEI]
That's me, Hiei...
And don't think for a second
I'm anywhere near giving up--
death will come
long before surrender.
Don't mistake my annoyance
for weakness, either--
I just like to
know who I'm destroying.
And this fool will transform
every time I cause him pain.
But the Jagan Eye
is open and angry,
and no one besides
Yusuke Urameshi
ever survives its wrath!
Go ahead and watch
to see what I mean.
Death will come
to all who dare.
♪