♪
[NARRATOR] The final fight
between Yusuke Urameshi
and Toguro has been incredible.
Toguro increased his demon
muscles to one hundred percent,
and for the first time
the stadium had a glimpse
of the monster's
true and horrific power.
Yusuke fired a super-
charged Spirit Gun,
fueled by the energy his
fallen mentor had given him,
However...
[KOTO] Toguro blew away
Yusuke's giant Spirit Gun
with nothing but the
aura surrounding him!
Now he's batted Yusuke all
the way to the third level!
[TOGURO 2] You're not doing
your job, Yusuke Urameshi.
This is the first time I've
fought at one hundred percent.
Clearly there must
be a reason.
The way you're fighting now,
I could finish you easily
with one punch of
my powered-up arm.
But that's not what I
waited all this time for.
You have a power you
still have not realized.
And this body will bring it out.
The techniques Genkai
mastered over all her years,
combined with the unnatural
talent you were born with,
that's everything needed
for an ultimate power.
For years I've waited for those
ingredients to show themselves,
and now they have.
So I must put my
strength against yours,
and know the
answer it will give.
I can't stand this guy!
He's trying to beat
more power out of Urameshi
just so he can
have a good time!
[KOENMA] It's the nature of the
demon body they gave him.
His instincts tell him to fight.
Don't sell me short.
It's more than that.
I may have the instincts
to act aggressively.
But it's my own choices
to follow them through
that define what I am.
Without my conscious decisions,
my body has only impulses
that will quickly fade away.
Let me show
you what I mean.
[crowd panics]
Toguro's body is
creating a vacuum
for all the souls
in the audience!
He's suckin' 'em all
straight into himself!
What a cowardly rooter!
Remaining at top
strength is demanding,
and my body gets an
impulse to devour souls.
But it's not until I decide
to kill that the feeding begins.
I've chosen evil, and in twenty
minutes everyone will be gone.
Aren't you going to do
something to stop me, Urameshi?
Or will your
friends have to watch
as you let these people die?
Hang on Ryo!
They're not even fighting!
I don't wanna die this way!
No joke son!
Let's get out of here!
[crowd screaming]
Afraid of being sucked
into Toguro's body,
the weaker fans who
can't defend themselves
are stampeding
out of the stadium!
Their faces contorted
by panic!
That muscle-man's
having his way,
I'm not so sure
Yusuke can stop him.
Please don't step
forward Shizuru.
You won't be protected by
Puu's barrier if you do.
[MOHAWK DEMON] Are you out of
your minds? Let us outta here!!!
Oh you can't want to leave us.
Your lives are worth
less than the tickets.
Now. No one but the
winners get out of here alive.
I'm not going down
without a fight!
I'm charging
that bastard!!
All you weaklings had
best remain in your seats.
Yusuke and I have
some disagreeable tempers.
Shut up Toguro!
Don't you ever put me in
the same category as you!
Now we're starting
to get somewhere.
So it's your refusal
to admit how much you
and I are similar that
makes you lash out at me.
Look how much power
Yusuke's creating!
[DEMON 1] I guess he's our
only chance for surviving!
That's right Urameshi!
Kill Toguro!
We're behind you all
the way, brother!
The opinion polls have changed.
What a bunch of posers!
You know that's not good enough.
What's happening?
Maybe you
shouldn't watch.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Yusuke.
We're not really here, are we?
We're in school,
like we were.
I'm a class representative
and you get me
in trouble all the time.
You play stupid pranks on
me and I wish you'd grow up.
At nighttime I worry
about where you are,
and in the mornings
I drag you to school.
Every day someone ask
me why I hang around with you,
and I don't answer.
But even though
you don't realize it,
you're the only
one in the world
who bothers to see
me as I really am.
We're safe with each other.
We're not hundreds
of miles from home,
and you're not
fighting for your life.
When we're together it's
our own little world,
and nothing gets inside.
This tournament full
of demons isn't real.
It's all a bad dream.
Come on Yusuke.
Just wake up, I wanna go home.
Let's go home Yusuke!!
Yusuke!
Kei... ko!
Alright, let's go
home Yusuke.
Go on without me.
I gotta settle some stuff
with those Rugafuchi jerks.
You're not getting expelled
any more this month!
[8 YEAR-OLD YUSUKE]
Last one there's a rotten egg!!
[8 YEAR-OLD KEIKO]
Hey! Wait up!
Oh yeah, who's the
fastest kid in the world!
Take a bite out of this Keiko!
Fine, you've proven you're
the biggest dummy-head I know!
Let's go home!
Hey you wanna be best
friends with me?
Yeah, sure.
[TOGURO 2] Sorry Urameshi.
There's no escaping from me now.
[TOGURO 2] I won't let you avoid
your problems forever.
The only thing waiting does
is cause more people to die.
[NURSE] Doctor, there's nothing
we can do to help them.
[KOTO] There's relatively few
of us left in the audience now
Toguro is too much.
His draining power is taking
its toll on the strong as well
I don't know if you'll hear
this broadcast much longer.
Rage on there sheila,
I got your tail.
You do want to be a bonzer
announcer, don't ya?
Uh, yeah!
You're all rip snorter over
there, aren't ya mate?
Oh yeah!
Yusuke...
Just take it easy...
Come on back to
reality Keiko.
Yusuke can still win this
fight and then we all go home!
We can't afford to think about
what happens if he loses,
or how much we'll
let down Genkai!
We've just got to trust
him and keep our cool, okay!
[GENKAI] This is
such a mess.
Oh that's just perfect!
Now I'm hearing things too!
You see I become something
of a different person
when I take my full demon form,
I'll do anything
to get what I desire.
I wonder if I'll
miss next time.
[Yusuke cries out]
You're an incredible
disappointment,
I went through with so
much in the assumption
you would be the one
person who could fight me.
If I'm proven wrong
you'll pay for it, dearly.
I'll get you.
[YUSUKE THINKS] If I
ever get the chance.
No, don't give up now Urameshi!
I've never known Toguro
to act this viciously.
He's always so businesslike.
[KOENMA THINKS] There is no
choice. I'm sending her in.
Oh no!! It's over!
Not even Yusuke
can slow down Toguro!
Every one of us
is gonna get it!!
So stupid! Why did I run
away to be an announcer?
I should have stayed
home and raised apples!
[SHIZURU] A little past
twenty and it's over.
I should have went
on more dates.
Don't you talk like
that Shizuru! It is not over!
[GENKAI] Yukina. Botan.
Combine your powers to make
a barrier wall while I'm gone.
Everybody did
hear that, right?
It was the voice of Genkai.
But I took her
to Spirit World.
Well, she's possessed
Puu's body.
I would say someone
brought her back.
[GENKAI] You will never
let this old woman have
some peace and quiet,
will you Yusuke?
Genkai's come back to life
and she looks exactly like Puu!!
[GENKAI] Toguro. You want
to see Yusuke's real
power come to the surface?
I'll tell you how.
He's very predictable.
The only thing you have to do
is kill one of his friends,
and make sure he's watching.
[YUSUKE] Genkai! What the
heck's the matter with you??
[GENKAI] Yusuke has a six foot
wall of crap between him
and his actual emotions, and
that's where his power resides.
To break through that wall you
have to do something drastic,
like killing someone
he really cares for.
Dying must have
ruined your heart Genkai.
[GENKAI] Open your
childish eyes, dimwit!
If you don't stop Toguro
everyone in this stadium dies!
And damn it, if the life of
one friend is what it takes
for you to save the
rest of them,
then that sacrifice
is worth it!
No!!!
You're nothing but a
stupid little hypocrite!
You told me to commit
to something all the way
and I chose my friends!
Now you say killing one
as motivation is okay!!!
Sorry Yusuke.
But this is the world
you stuck yourself into,
and it's not pretty.
When you're not
strong enough to lead,
you lose the privilege
of getting what you want.
I had that idea a while back
and I didn't like
the way it felt.
But if nothing else can
bring out your true abilities.
Well, you heard before.
I'll do anything.
All I have to do
is choose which one.
Don't do this!
How about you, Kuwabara?
Urameshi does appear to be
the most protective of you.
Let's see you bring
out his hidden emotions.
I'll make this quick.
Stop it Toguro!!!
Bastard!
If he makes it over here,
the three of us must
fight him together.
With what secret weapon?
You've barely been able stand up
since your flirting with death.
Yes, your Darkness
Flame technique
hasn't left much of you either.
We could run if you want.
Don't be simple, I'll take
Toguro alone if I must.
[KOENMA THINKS] Did you really
have to do that, Genkai?
[KOENMA] Let's just
hope to all it works.
You do know this is
your fault, right?
For living in a constant
state of repression.
Relax Yusuke,
I'll free you up.
Ready?
[KUWABARA] Stay back guys!
I'm the one he wants.
Just stop and think,
Kuwabara.
It's no time for
your showmanship.
Face Toguro alone
now and you'll die
before this
minute is through.
Hey Koenma. You risked your
life on Urameshi's fight
and now I'm gonna do the same.
So make a place for me, and be
sure my wake is as good as his.
Kuwabara.
There's no stoppin' him.
And if I'm gonna go now,
I'm gonna go
charging at full speed!
A mulberry's a tree, Kuwabara's
a man, and I'll prove it.
We all have to die
when our time comes.
But if we do our duty
we don't got regrets!
So taste a little piece
of my sword, Toguro!
Kuwabara no!!!
No!!!
Okay Urameshi.
It's all you.
I did what I could.
Now beat him for all of us.
Make my death count, okay?
Hold on now Kuwabara.
Just stay with us.
Kuwabara!
Stay with us.
[TOGURO 1]
That's anticlimactic.
You knew him for so long
and now he's dead.
Do you think that was
sufficient for you?
Or do I need to take
another of your friends
for you to get the point?
What??
[YOGURO 1 THINKS] So I
guess that was enough.
You took my teacher, and now
I let you take my friend.
What the hell do
you want from me?
His Spirit Energy is undeniably
different than before.
Alright Toguro.
You got what you wished for.
[YUSUKE] Don't you think I
wanted to use my power
and win this thing
and go home?
Of course!
I just didn't know
how to reach it.
And I have to live with that.
Maybe not for long, Yusuke.
[NARRATOR] Yusuke fights to
escape from the Dark Tournament,
knowing that even if he wins,
he will have to
leave Kuwabara behind.
Toguro wants the
ultimate confrontation.
And as Yusuke unseals
all the power he's acquired,
it seems that's
exactly what he'll get.
[YUSUKE] Kuwabara
is really gone.
And if I can't take this
demon in his full form,
everyone else will be, too.
I still don't know
all the reasons
Toguro wants to fight me,
but I do know
there's a giant power
that's ready to put him down.
Part of it's Genkai's training,
and part of it's her
Spirit Wave Orb,
and a whole lot of it's me.
Because I won't let this killer
screw our lives up anymore.
So don't miss the next
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho.
This one decides it all.
♪