[NARRATOR]
Recover three artifacts.
That is Yusuke Urameshi's first
mission as Spirit Detective.
After two desperate battles,
Yusuke defeated the demon Gouki
and won back the Orb of Baast.
But the second
artifact required
much more than strength.
To save his dying mother,
Kurama offered his
life to the Forlorn Hope.
Yusuke asked the mirror
to take his own life instead,
and the mirror let him live.
Two down, one to go.
[HIEI] Their mistakes
were simple ones.
Gouki's was overconfidence,
and Kurama's,
sympathy for his human prey.
Well... I certainly won't
make the same mistakes.
My plan's too good for that.
[NARRATOR]
Shadow Sword.
Transforms any human it cuts
into the lowest level of demon,
a strong but sluggish creature.
Only the sword itself
can reverse the effect.
[HIEI THINKS]
It's better this way.
The other two wouldn't
have the courage
to use the weapons
as they're intended.
I will... but first,
I'll kill Yusuke Urameshi!
[school bells chime]
[excited voices]
[YUSUKE] I'm still having
nightmares about that Gouki guy,
and most times
I don't even dream.
I gotta say, though,
your hand-thing really worked.
Without that trick,
I'd be limping around
for six more months!
They're just basic
healing powers.
All the good detective's
assistants have them!
[YUSUKE]
Really.
Do all the assistants
wear school uniforms, too?
Or do you just like
the little navy girl look?
Thought I'd fit the part
if I'm gonna follow
you around school all day.
Isn't it adorable?
Whatever you say.
[BOTAN]
Oh, I almost forgot!
What?
About Kurama.
His case was reviewed
by the punishment board.
Koenma has decided to
release him on good behavior.
That's great...
...all I gotta do now is
get back the last treasure,
and I've still got three days.
From monster guy--
what's his name?
Hiei. And listen
to me carefully...
He's the toughest one by far.
Both cunning and ruthless.
He'll do anything
to get what he wants.
There you are Yusuke.
Mr. Takenaka's looking for you.
You're the only one in class
who hasn't turned
in his book report!
Gee that makes sense. Cause
I'm the only one fighting evil!
Hard to balance
school and work, huh?
Do you mind?!
No, not really!
Miss Keiko it's so nice
to meet you in my own body!
I just wanted to say how great a
person you are! When I saw you
running through those
flames to save Yusuke
I just about melted in my shoes!
Do I know you?
I hope you don't mind
me speaking through
your mother but with
his Spirit Energy--
What was that for?!!
Keiko doesn't know anything
about you or Spirit World!
Play it cool okay!
Oh, that's right.
But if you ask me.
Things are about get complicated
if you don't tell her soon!
Alright, I'll see
you after school!
Tell me what soon?
Damn! She just had to bring
you in on this didn't she?!
[KEIKO] Yusuke!
Bring me in on what?
Well it's gonna be
a long, long story.
Let's talk about it later, okay?
Oh... Well I just came,
to tell you about the book
report so you
wouldn't get in trouble.
Well hold on Keiko, don't leave
yet, I want to talk to you.
You do?
How'd you like
to do my homework?
Oh, is that the only
thing I'm good for now?
Well me and Botan are
going to be busy today.
Is that a fact!
Hey! It's not what you think!
[KEIKO] How do you know
what I'm thinking?
'Cause I know how it looks!
[DEMON FRIEND]
Keiko Ukimura.
Classmate and childhood
friend of Yusuke Urameshi.
She's appears to
be his closest link.
Perfect, with a
little help from her
I'll be quite entertained.
[HIEI LAUGHS]
She just had to bring
you in on this, didn't she?
[YUSUKE] Well, it's gonna
be a long, long story.
Well me and Botan
are going to be busy today.
[KEIKO]
I hate boys.
You needn't worry, Keiko.
[HIEI]
He likes you well enough!
[YUSUKE]
He's near--
Only one mile away!
Sorry old man!
Mom's calling!
Don't leave Yusuke! At least
provide a better-- Excuse.
I think my compass went stupid!
No matter how far
I run, it says one mile!
Hiei is using his Spirit Energy
to send out a moving signal
for you to follow.
I'd say he's leading
you to his hideout!
That's cute.
No it's not.
He's told me terrible
things through telepathy!
He's kidnapped Keiko
and he won't give her back
unless we bring him
the two other artifacts!
He what?!
[ship blows horn]
Get out here Hiei!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
What the...?
Who the hell are they?
Physically they're
normal humans.
But it looks like Hiei's
controlling their minds.
What?
The Records Department
doesn't know about this.
For him to control
so many humans at once.
He must possess the Jagan.
Jagan?
[HIEI]
Well done.
[HIEI: evil laugh]
I used my power to round
them up this morning.
They won't do
much good against you
but they do make
excellent scenery.
That's some pimple.
It's the Jagan, a third
eye for the Spirit.
A normal human would've
succumbed to its power by now.
But I see the
geniuses in the
Spirit World found a nice pick.
That's why I've
brought insurance.
Keiko! Hey! What do you
plan to do with her?
Nothing more if you've
brought me the weapons.
Ooh, good boy.
Both the Orb of Baast and
that precious Forlorn Hope.
[HIEI]
You may have her.
Keiko!
So maybe my plan
had a few setbacks.
But the end result is the same.
All three ancient weapons
of darkness are in my control.
And those fools in charge
will soon be bowing at my feet.
[YUSUKE]
You should stop bragging.
It'll just make it more
embarrassing for you.
Now that I've got Keiko
I'm gonna rip out your teeth.
Try, I'll give
you a head start.
You know that cocky laugh is
really starting to tick me off!!
[YUSUKE]
He vanished.
I'm still here.
I only stepped gently to the
side. Was that a real hit?
I was under the
impression it was a joke.
Oh but wait, you're not amused.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
He's so fast--
[HIEI]
And as for Keiko.
What?
Do you really think
I'd relinquish my hostage
without the reward?
Look at her closely Yusuke.
You'll see that
she's still mine.
[YUSUKE]
You're lying!
[HIEI]
Am I?
What is that thing?
I don't understand! How?!
[HIEI] You may have her body,
but her future is mine.
See I've struck her
with the Shadow Sword.
And once that Jagan
eye opens completely.
She becomes a demon.
Not a very smart one I'm
afraid, but perfect for a slave.
Move!
I'll try to prevent
it from opening.
You go and punch his brains out!
[HIEI]
Yes.
You better punch
them out quickly
if you care about
your assistant.
I can feel her precious
energy draining fast, pity.
Her poor little body
is giving everything it has.
Soon you'll have a
girlfriend who's a demon
and an assistant who's dead.
Is that true?
[BOTAN] Don't worry
about me, Yusuke.
I'll stop it as long as I can.
Botan.
[HIEI: evil laugh]
Oh, that's IT!!
I'm glad you're so enthused.
The game will be more
exciting this way.
What game?
The hilt of
this sword is hollow.
Contained inside
is the only antidote
to stop the sword's effect.
If you get the sword,
the girl will live.
Fun, right? Think of
it as a little game of tag.
[HIEI THINKS]
Faster than I thought.
[HIEI] What happened
Spirit Detective?
You weren't that fast before.
This isn't a game,
dirt-face. Keiko's my friend.
Now I see.
You're a decent
fighter on your own,
but when your
friend's on the line
your strength increases greatly.
You're a team player.
A save-the-day super hero.
[HIEI]
I hate people like you.
And yes Spirit Detective,
I'll admit you surprised me.
But like a true amateur
you failed to take
advantage of the situation.
You didn't get back the sword.
A mistake that will prove fatal.
Because now that I know it
I won't be dropping my
guard any longer.
The world doesn't
give many chances.
You've just missed yours.
Are you done yapping yet?
Not quite!
Can you keep up?
Human eyes are so slow.
Come now! Where am I?
What's wrong? Do I confuse you?
Do I?
Now--You're dead!
[YUSUKE] See Hiei, that's
what I'm talking about.
Yap, yap, yap like you're
some crappy Pro Wrestler.
And then what happens?
You have to eat up all your
words. It's pretty dumb.
[HIEI]Consider
this a compliment.
I've never
transformed for a human.
What?
[BOTAN THINKS]
The monster inside her
must be feeding off
Hiei's energy!
I don't think I
can fight it much longer.
[BOTAN THINKS]
But I have to, I have to try!
Something's
wrong she's in trouble!
[HIEI LAUGHS]
[HIEI] Don't be alarmed,
Detective. It's just me.
Now that I'm
in my full demon form,
Keiko will join me any minute.
Never!
There's no reason
to be upset though.
I'll take you out of this world
long before you
ever have to see her!
Whoa, let's talk!
[KURAMA] That scent
is unmistakable.
Hiei must be desperate
to take that form.
Well this is new.
But maybe you could
get me green ones.
They'd match a lot better.
A joker to the end, aren't you?
Perhaps my Jagan
Tie Curse needs to be tighter
before you get serious.
I have a great idea.
How about I give you a choice?
What?
[HIEI]
I can end your life now.
Or if you prefer
I'll make you into a demon.
[HIEI] What's that?
You want me to choose?
Fine!!
[impact]
Kurama?
You really have gone insane!
[HIEI]
My eye! My Jagan eye!
Hey! I've come untied!
[KURAMA] The eyes on Hiei's body
are merely for amplification.
Without the Jagan
exposed on his forehead
his powers become useless.
Are you okay?
Fine only a minor
hole in my stomach.
You didn't have to do that!
I'm alive only because of you.
Please let me pay my debt.
You must handle Hiei.
I will use my powers to keep the
girl from transforming.
Kurama.
Kurama, how could you?
Traitor!
Take your problems up with me.
[HIEI THINKS]
What is this?
The more dangerous
the situation becomes,
the faster his
Spirit Energy grows.
I mustn't allow
this to go on any longer!
You see?
It doesn't matter how strong
you are if you can't hit me!
Damn it!
How sad!
After all this,
you actually think
you can run away from me!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Just a little more!
Detective!!
Here goes!
Please don't miss!
Spirit Gun!!!
[Hiei laughs]
[HIEI] My, what
a well-kept secret.
Too bad all of your energy
was wasted on poor aim.
[HIEI CRIES OUT]
What happened?!
Simple... I won.
But you missed--
The Forlorn Hope!
You reflected the shot.
Must have guessed exactly
the way that I would dodge.
I think that's what they
call watching your opponent?
You're pretty clever.
Goodbye Keiko Monster!
She's going to recover.
I hope so. Thanks for all the
help Kurama. How do you feel?
Good I guess, I avoided
the organs at least.
[BOTAN] I still can't
believe what you did, Yusuke.
Why not?
Why didn't you
tell me the Spirit Gun
could bounce off mirrors.
When did you learn that?
Mmm... about ten minutes ago.
What???
Hiei was way too fast.
I knew he'd be able
to dodge the Spirit Gun
unless I could
shoot him from behind.
That's when I spotted the
Forlorn Hope in the corner,
and I thought,
hey I'd give it a try.
You weren't certain?
Well one time in science class
they bounced light off a mirror.
I thought it might be the same!
Might? You risked
our lives on a might?
What exactly would you
have done if the Spirit Gun
hadn't bounced off the mirror?
Get chopped in pieces I guess.
All the while
we've been thinking
you're a brilliant strategist.
Really you're just a lucky fool!
Hey watch it fox-boy!
What's that word mean, anyway!
A strategist is someone
who uses his brain.
Hey!!
Now, now, boys.
Botan, I'm a
pretty incredible guy.
I got all three
artifacts back in one week.
Beat up two demons,
reformed a third
and saved Koenma's rear end.
Well, almost, Koenma
still got found out.
It didn't take his
father long to notice
the Shadow Sword
had bloodstains on it
and the Forlorn Hope
was a big mess of glass.
So what happened to Koenma?
Did he get a cruel punishment?
It wasn't anything too severe.
Just the normal punishment for
when he does something wrong.
What was it?
A hundred spankings.
Koenma got spankings?
[KOENMA]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Now that's something
I'd pay to see!
What a riot!
Can't take you anywhere.
[door opens]
Oh... That's bad timing.
Oh gosh, she was
knocked out all that time
and I haven't explained
who you are yet!
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt!
[YUSUKE] Wait Keiko!
It's not what it looks like!
I mean it's not what
it looks like again Keiko!!
[Botan giggles]
Out of all his opponents,
she's the only one
who beats him every time!
[BOTAN]
Hey there everybody!
A whole new adventure
is about to begin!
The great psychic Genkai
wants to hand down her
abilities before she dies,
and Yusuke has
to go undercover
to make sure
those powers
don't fall in the wrong hands!
But there's a problem.
A whole army of fighters
want the same thing,
and Yusuke has to pass
a list of crazy obstacles
just to prove his stuff!
It's called the
Genkai Tournament,
and it's going to be rough!
You'll see what I mean,
next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪