[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi
now trains with the servants
of his ancestral father, Raizen,
one of the ruling lords
of Demon World.
While in another fortress,
Hiei confronted the pain
of his past to defeat Shigure,
the surgeon who
implanted his Jagan Eye.
With Hiei's victory,
he has won the favor
of the second lord, Mukuro.
But there is a
third ruler, Yomi,
and he's invited an
old friend to join his side
in the battle over Demon World.
That friend's name:
Suichi Minamono.
His Demon name: Yoko Kurama.
[phone ringing]
[SHIORI]
Hello? Suichi? Hello?
[KURAMA]
Yes, Mother, it's me.
I'm here.
Don't worry, everything's fine.
Yes, I'm feeding myself well.
Earthquake?
No, I didn't feel anything.
We must have only gotten
small tremors in town.
I told you, Mother.
You needn't worry about me.
Stay on your trip as long
as you want--honestly.
You deserve it.
And don't worry about
the house, it's in good hands.
Phone call to Demon World,
thanks to a clever patch
I made before leaving.
She still thinks
I'm at the house.
[KURAMA] On a warm day
in July, my mother,
after raising me on her own
for most of my
human life, remarried.
The wedding was small, with only
family and close friends.
She looked happy.
I'm sorry I'm missing it.
Give your mom a toast for me.
Cheers!
[KURAMA] Yusuke left two months
before, but I was glad he cared.
I have far from forgotten
the risk he took
to allow both my mother
and myself to live.
[AIRPORT AGENT
announcing flights]
[KURAMA] My wedding gift to
them was an all-expenses-paid
overseas honeymoon for
the full month of August.
I sort of forced it on them
for my own convenience.
[KURAMA] I love you, too,
Mother. Take care.
[KURAMA] And now, two months
after Yusuke and Hiei,
and on the condition it would
only last through August,
I make my own trip
to Demon World,
to serve as an
advisor to Yomi's army.
I owe Yomi something.
[gasps]
[GUARDS yelling]
[GUARD yelling]
[KURAMA]
Rose Whip!
Yomi... Was all that necessary?
[YOMI]
Hello, Kurama.
It's been far too long
since I've seen you.
I don't appreciate the pun.
And what sort
of welcome is that?
I came all this way to help you,
not to be attacked.
Don't be cross.
I wasn't entirely
sure it was you.
Your energy feels so much
different than it did before.
I have to be sure I'm
not advised by the wrong man.
So you sent them to identify me.
That's playing it
very cautious, Yomi--
A trait you never had
when I knew you.
You're not the only one
who's gone through changes.
I can't afford
to be reckless now.
Mukuro and Raizen
have had centuries
to perfect the keeping of power.
Now that I have an equal share,
they'll take any chance
to dethrone me.
A thousand years
is a long time.
For some things, it's not.
Forgive the attack,
but if you were as strong
as I heard you'd become,
it wouldn't have been a threat.
And it wasn't.
I believe in your power.
Kurama, please
give me your trust.
[YOUDA]
Lord Yomi.
[YOMI]
Yes, Youda?
[YOUDA] It's time for the
Unification Conference, Lord.
The council has gathered.
[YOMI]
Excuse me.
[YOMI] Actually, Youda,
I have a thought.
I want Kurama to
attend today's meeting.
Show him the way, please.
[YOUDA]
That little thing?
Well, I don't pick up
any special Demon energy
coming out of him.
In fact,
he smells half human.
You sure you want him
gracing our table?
[YOMI]
You heard what I said.
[YOUDA] Hmph.
Well, come on, then.
[YOUDA] Look to the screen,
if you would.
We'll start with a simple graph.
I've charted
the military power
of each of the three
territories in Demon World.
Now the numbers are relative.
They don't mean
anything material.
If you don't
understand any of that,
take a math class
on your own time.
Now, we'll chart a
projection of the same powers
one year from today.
That has Raizen's
strength going down to zero.
That's wishful thinking.
And reckless!
Not so.
Because one year from today,
Raizen will be dead.
[thunder crashes]
Raizen's ridiculous
hunger strike
has brought his body
to critical condition.
He cannot last through the year.
This comes from
highly dependable sources.
[YOUDA] With Raizen gone,
his empire will collapse.
Lord Yomi and Mukuro
will be in a dead heat.
Our strategy should be
to incorporate the defectors
from Raizen's army into our own,
to tip the scale in our favor.
Well...
Your tactics are
by the books, Youda.
Kurama, I'd like
to hear your opinion now.
Yes, I think we all would.
[COUNCIL A]
Lord Yomi spoke well of you,
and now brings you
to our elite table.
We want to see how
resourceful you are.
Yes, we'd just hate for you
to be a disappointment to him.
I'm confused.
The power of each territory
simply mirrors its ruler.
I'd like to see individual stats
of the first and second
strongest in each land.
Strength of the leader
is strength of the team.
But if you need proof,
I can show you stats
of every single warrior.
[KURAMA] No. The first
and second will suffice.
[chuckling]
I see, all that
information would be too much
for your brain to handle...
All right, one and two--
Compiled by our covert agents
with the latest
Demon Energy scans.
[chuckles]
First, the rulers...
Lord Raizen, Lord Mukuro...
And of course, last but nothing
even resembling least,
Lord Yomi.
Now I'll pull up the
second highest readings
we recorded in each territory.
For Raizen, the Paranormal
Taoist, Hokushin.
For Mukuro, it's the
Demonic Arts Guru, Kirin.
And not surprisingly for us, our
Chief of the Military, Shachi.
[YOUDA] Happy now,
or shall I graph it for you?
Well... That confirms it for me.
The right hand man
of each of the lords
has not been present long enough
to be collected
into your database.
Let's assume for a moment that
your information is complete,
and Raizen's army will
collapse upon his death,
leaving a two-way fight.
Because Mukuro and
Yomi's powers are identical,
the deciding factor would
normally be the strength
of the number twos...
But in this case they're all too
weak to make any difference.
And if they're the second best,
logic follows that all warriors
besides the lords are useless.
The only thing that
Mr. Youda's intelligence shows
is that we know nothing...
Not until the number twos
are as strong as the lords.
Hmph. So our only
tactic is no tactic?
Sounds like you've been
wasting Lord Yomi's time.
Not at all, because the whole
balance is about to change.
What?
As I've explained,
those second in command
will determine
who prevails here,
and in half a year
they will all be replaced.
You damned fool!
[SHACHI]
Watch your tongue!
These hierarchies of power
have survived here
for five hundred years,
unchallenged by any Demon!
And only a sword
will make them change.
[COUNCIL B]
Shachi, control yourself.
He's a visitor here,
and doesn't understand our ways.
[SHACHI]
He will soon enough.
[YOMI] Now that was the
most stirring conference
we've had in years.
You should have seen the way
Shachi was staring at you
as you spoke.
The expression was undeniable.
He doesn't simply despise you;
he's already
plotting your death.
For a blind man,
you certainly have good eyes.
[YOMI] I heard his
quickened heartbeat.
Felt the heat from his eyes
as the filled blood vessels
turned them red.
Losing my eyesight was in
part what made me stronger.
But now, let me guess what
you foresee in half a year...
[yelling]
[YOMI]
In the land of Raizen,
his part Demon, part human
offspring, Yusuke Urameshi,
trains relentlessly,
and looks to take control
of Raizen's army,
thus preventing its collapse.
[YOMI]
While in Mukuro's fortress,
your friend Hiei has
improved drastically,
and from a few vague reports,
has garnered rare attention
from that soulless tyrant.
Urameshi, Hiei, and yourself
will be the number twos
in just half a year from now.
Isn't that what
you believe, Kurama?
"The second in command is key
in determining who prevails."
That's what you've
always believed.
[YOMI]
So... Friend...
I think now's a
good time to address
the other reason
I invited you.
After all, it seems out of order
to discuss your future here
before you meet him.
[YOMI]
Here we are.
Can you guess
who's behind this door?
The one I've searched
for all these years,
he who took my light.
That's my favorite saying
for what he did to me.
Maybe not.
You said blindness helped
you to gain your throne.
Right.
What's wrong?
Your heart is beating so quickly
and your eyes are pointed down.
Look up.
Yes, get a good view
of him at the way he is today.
[YOMI] His decay has become
much worse the last few days.
He hardly speaks anymore.
It hurts him too much.
It was one thousand years ago
when he fought against me.
Still, I can only
see him as he was.
[YOMI] In that distant epoch,
our world was opposite.
You were the leader,
and I, your right hand man.
I still had my eyes.
[YOMI]
We were greedy, you and I.
We wanted to make
ourselves known,
and carve out our own territory.
But to be a lord
requires power and wealth,
and to gain both,
we became bandits.
We led a legendary horde,
raiding all corners
of Demon World
for its most precious treasures.
I was hotheaded then, obstinate
and thirsty for action.
I often forced us
into confrontation
when you favored stealth.
Soon, I disobeyed
you altogether,
leading our best men into the
most well guarded strongholds,
costing many of their lives.
I didn't care.
I was selfish and reckless.
I just wanted the
quickest way to power.
I could never understand
your patience.
[yelling]
[growling]
[laughing]
You should watch it, Yomi.
Your foul character
will be the death of you.
[YOMI]
Looking back,
I don't know why you
saved me and kept me onboard,
except that we were friends.
We were so opposite.
You were cruelly ambitious,
but in a different way,
calculating, always
plotting three steps ahead.
It must have been difficult for
you to make your careful plans
with such a loose
cannon at your side.
Yet still you trusted me,
and it didn't take me long
to waste that again.
[YOMI]
A few weeks after my mistake,
I heard news of another fortress
that was impossibly defended,
but held unspeakable treasures.
I disobeyed you again.
When I arrived,
the castle was deserted.
That news was a lie!
Tell me what you're after!
I have no qualms with you!
[YOMI] The entire fight,
he never told me who he was,
or why he attacked.
He was strong.
At least,
compared to me at that time.
[GENWAKU KYOUSHU]
Look upon me!
[screaming]
Life's more
important than the reward.
[YOMI groaning in pain]
[YOMI]
Wait!
Who are you?
What does that mean?
[yelling]
[YOMI] "Life is more important
than the reward."
My only consolation from the
creature who took away my light.
I didn't understand anything,
or how I could live blindly.
I could only wait for you
to save me, as always.
But this time, you never came.
[YOMI] And until now,
ten full centuries later,
I did not meet
you again, Kurama,
didn't even know
where you were.
Why is that?
I resolved that the only
way to answer that question
was to find the
creature that blinded me.
And so I searched
these one thousand years,
but now that I have him,
have yet to learn a thing.
[chuckles]
You find something amusing?
You, Kurama.
Your heartbeat
returned to normal
the moment you saw
the awful physical state
this killer was in, as if
he were no longer a threat.
[YOMI]
You. Wake up.
Please, Your great Lordship.
Take my life from me.
I can't take
this pain any longer.
Very well, Demon.
I shall grant you your wish.
You have suffered
more than enough.
But you must
answer my one question
your fear has
kept you from saying.
Who ordered you that day to
ambush us and forfeit my life?
Okay... he had cold eyes...
They were such cold,
terrifying eyes...
And silver hair...
He was Yoko... Kurama.
[growling, yelling]
There it is.
Of course I long suspected it,
but I didn't want to believe.
I should tell you right now
that I bear no grudge
against you, old friend.
In the enterprise of power,
you made a business decision.
Thinking back,
I was a liability.
Rash. Disobedient.
I lost countless men.
I would have tried
to kill me, too.
What do you want from me?
Precisely as my
Spirit of Words told you.
I want you to assist me
any way that you can...
Just as I assisted you
in the past,
despite my mistakes
of immaturity.
I learned much
from you, Kurama.
I've tried to model
myself after you.
I only brought up the past
so we could move beyond it.
And yet... if I say no?
Your human mother is
on a plane right now.
No, Yomi...
At least according
to the schedule
my agents have supplied.
That was nice of you, by the
way, to give them that trip.
[YOMI]
I just hope it doesn't crash.
Middle-aged newlyweds
dying on their honeymoon
is a bland topic for even
your lousy human TV shows.
You bastard...
[YOMI] Quite a life you had
after my hit was botched--
Reverting to your fox form
and venturing into Spirit World
for a solitary life of thieving,
until injuries forced you
to hide in yet another world,
possessing an
unborn human child.
And there, after fourteen
years of softening up,
your human mother fell sick.
To save her,
you teamed with other Demons
to burglarize
Spirit World again.
That led you to
a debt with Urameshi,
which led you to
Demon World fighting Sensui,
which in turn led you to me.
And all because
of mommy dearest.
[YOMI]
Collecting information...
Another lesson you taught me.
It showed me how much
she meant to you.
Earlier today you said
you didn't recognize me...
A smart lie to disguise
how much you knew.
[YOMI chuckling]
I've angered you greatly,
and yet your mind's
already considering
our every encounter calmly,
trying to sniff out
an advantage.
While others would be
overcome with real emotions,
blinded by their rage,
you're methodically planning
how to save your mom.
And no one could say if that's
because you actually love her,
or because you don't want
anything to handicap
your control of the situation.
That's cold,
and very threatening.
Very soon all of Demon
World will fall into chaos.
And that's when I'll
need your calm and cruelty,
your ability to
think without emotion.
Join me, Kurama.
Help me unify them all.
[NARRATOR]
In a brutal power play,
Yomi has forced Kurama
to serve as his advisor.
But the alliance
is hardly stable,
for the seeds of hatred
lie between them.
[YUSUKE] And I thought I was
having fun beating up monks!
Who can tell me
they don't love q. t.
with Kurama and his
thousand-years of darkness?
And yeah, in case you
didn't see that last shot,
it's only gettin' better.
Can Kurama work with Yomi
and save his mom?
And don't think fish-face forgot
those rips at the meeting.
Of course, don't think
Kurama forgot
how to turn into a certain
silver haired fox, either.
It's showdown time,
on the next ass-kickin'
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho.