[motorcycles roaring]
[THUG GUY 1 yells]
[THUG GUY 2 grunts]
[YUSUKE grunts]
[THUGS yelling]
[THUGS grunting]
[THUG GUY 3 grunts]
[THUG GUY 2 grunts]
[THUG GUY 1 groans]
Damn you!
And that's without hands!
Do I have to beat myself up?!
[alarm clock rings]
[YUSUKE gasps]
[ringing continues]
Damn it...
Sandman's playing reruns.
[YUSUKE]
Same dream every night.
And I think I know why.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Ikeda?
[IKEDA]
Yeah.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Inou?
[INOU]
Here.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Ueda?
[UEDA]
Yes, sir.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Urameshi?
He's absent again? Just
watch me faint in shock.
Ukimura?
Where'd your little mut go now?
Sir, for him to be my dog,
he'd have to respond
when I called him.
Yes, well put.
Enomoto?
[ENOMOTO]
Here.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Oohashi.
[OOHASHI]
Here.
That punk. He'll be in middle
school for most of his life.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Kuwabara?
There's another doubtful.
I'm here!
Don't lump me in with him.
What now?
[PEOPLE chattering]
[KOENMA]
Yusuke, what's wrong?
[sighs] Nothing...
So what's your deal? Can you
not get back into Spirit World,
or do you just
enjoy slumming it?
Understand, if I go back,
it'll be for punishment.
Disobeying my father to protect
you was the worst of crimes.
And, I'm afraid if I go
back he will take my life.
Botan sent me a
message, in secret.
She said my father called up
many of the staff
who worked for me and
sent them out from the castle in
several different directions.
Why?
[KOENMA] I know
my father. He has a plan.
Be careful, Yusuke.
Eyes up.
You're sounding paranoid.
[KOENMA] My father ordered
for you to be erased.
He sent his own troops.
Don't think the Great King Yama
is going to give up that
wish just because his son
was unruly and
his men were weak.
He's going to try
it again, Yusuke.
From a different approach.
What, like some
Spirit World assassins?
'Cause if that's the bush
you're beatin' around,
then I say bring 'em on.
What's wrong with you?
You've been foaming
at the mouth for trouble
ever since you beat Sensui.
I didn't.
I didn't beat him.
That bastard took
it away from me.
At least with new people,
I could find out if he'd try
to take me over again.
Do you regret it, Yusuke?
[YUSUKE]
Regret what?
Deciding to leave Demon
World to come back home.
I don't know, I guess I just
feel unsatisfied, that's all.
Cryin' for the moon.
[KOENMA]
What?
[YUSUKE] It's a saying
my mom used to tell me.
See, I don't have anybody
left to fight here.
I'll never be able
to figure out who I am.
But if I went to Demon
World, I'd miss everybody.
[YUSUKE] My mom, Kayko, hell,
even Kuwabara's ugly mug.
Now, where's the moon
come in to this?
That's what the saying means.
No matter what you have, you
always want what's out of reach.
You're crying for the moon.
Like... Like, a stupid
pack of wolves.
[YUSUKE] But, I think it's
more than a lame outlook.
My body's felt off
ever since Sensui.
It's telling me something.
Yusuke,
you've got deep issues
that I can't resolve.
What about an old hermit
who's thought her whole life
about things like this?
Who, Grandma?
Yeah.
You know what she's
gonna say to me.
[GENKAI] What do you
think I am, a shrink?
[videogame beeps]
I've had a life of crap.
Why would I take on yours?
[YUSUKE]
I hate always being right.
[grunting] Ah!
Truth is, you can do
whatever the hell you want.
If you got mad and wanted
to blow up this whole world,
you could do that, and nobody's
strong enough to stop you.
So, I'm not gonna pretend I can
influence you when I can't.
Tch. Easy, Doomsday,
I just wanted advice.
[grunting] Damn!
[grumbles] I hate games.
[GENKAI] Everyone has
something that matters
to them that they can
protect or destroy.
Kids have pets or toys.
An adult has a child.
Your something, Yusuke,
just happens to be
a whole lot bigger.
With your new powers,
you control all our fates.
So, what's next?
That's the question hidden
beneath all your other feelings.
Heh. Will you become the person
who protects or destroys?
Ah, come on!
But don't take it from me.
I'm just an old hag.
What's this, an address?
[GENKAI]
Kuroko Satou lives there.
Well I am happy to hear that.
Who the hell is it?
Maiden name Kuroko Sanada.
She was Living World's
very first Spirit Detective.
Does she have seven
personalities, too?
She took a very different
path than Sensui,
and she's much more
like you than I am,
so maybe she can help.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
Urameshi...? Urameshi?
[MR. IWAMOTO sighs] Honestly.
Why do I even bother?
Can any of you children
tell me what happens
when you take one rotten apple
and put into a bowl
full of good ones?
They all go bad, real quick.
And class?
Urameshi is a
definitely rotten apple.
Keep your distance...
Or else you'll be
contaminated by his rot.
[KUWABARA]
Huh. Bad apple.
He'd sing a different song
if he knew how many times
Urameshi saved his rotten hide.
Wish he'd get over himself
and come to class, though.
Least then we could make
fun of this jerk together.
[MR. IWAMOTO]
But enough ranting,
everyone turn your textbooks
to page sixty five.
We're gonna learn
about the plague.
Man...
Why is it everyone I gotta meet
is in love with friggin' nature?
[YUSUKE]
Dumb sign...
Like anyone who trekked through
the damn boonies to get here is
gonna be scared of a stupid dog.
Okay, that's not human!
[YUSUKE] What kind of
dog does she have?
[YUSUKE]
Something's close...
[YUSUKE gasps]
[YUSUKE grunts]
[BOY]
Uha... aah.
[GIRL]
Uha... huh.
[YUSUKE]
Tch... Children?
When will you ghosts learn?
The last ones couldn't kill our
mother and neither will you.
She could kill you herself,
but we don't want
her waste her time.
I got real issues here, kids.
I don't have time to
play Cops and Monsters.
[BOTH]
We'll send you to your grave!
[GIRL/BOY grunting]
[BOY yells]
[GIRL yells]
[BOY grunting]
[BOY yells]
[GIRL]
Sorry!
[grunts]
[BOY]
No fair!
[YUSUKE laughs]
Hey!
I'm up here, you stupid
little midgets! [laughs]
--[YUSUKE laughs]
--[GIRL] That jerk.
You're pretty good!
It just means one thing:
We'll have to get
a little more serious.
[GIRL]
Haa...ngh.
[GIRL/BOY]
Twin Dragon Blast!
[WOMAN]
Kaisei, Fubuki, drop it!
[BOY gasps]
Why, Mom?
Look! I stopped! I stopped!
Well then, you must be Yusuke.
Not sure how you know that,
but yeah I am. You're Kuroko?
Yeah, Genkai told me she'd
be sending you here soon.
She said I'd relate to you
'cause you're a pain in the ass.
[KURUKO] Sorry about
the welcoming party.
I've trained them to
attack without question
any time they sensed
Demon Energy.
But you don't need
to worry from now on,
they'll remember your face.
So, I take it they're
the dogs, huh?
[KURUKO laughs] Yeah, well,
I had trouble making a
"Beware of Children"
sign look threatening.
Let me get this straight,
those bones on the way up here?
Probably remains of the
apparitions my kids have killed.
Pleased to meet you.
My name's Shougo Satou,
Kuruko's ball and chain.
You may have heard
of him; he's a novelist.
Yusuke. Sorry,
I don't read much.
Your name's pretty funny.
Yusuke Urameshi.
You're not clean,
"you're-a-messy!"
[laughing]
Yeah, you're ready
for the playground.
Well we've got cool
names, don't we Sis?
Yeah!
Now, kids, you should
introduce yourselves properly.
[KAISEI, FUBUKI]
'Kay!
Kaisei Sanada.
Nine years old.
I memorize TV shows!
I'm Fubuki Sanada.
I'm eight years old.
I'm in love with a movie star,
and want to marry him.
Your last name,
I thought it was Satou.
[BOTH]
Satou's our dad's name,
our mom's is cooler!
Soutou's too common,
kinda' boring.
I think it sounds like "satin."
They hate my name. I can feel
my heart [sniffs] breaking.
Look what you've done, kids.
Your dad's going to cry
an ocean and drown us all!
[KOENMA]
You sent him to Kuroko?
[GENKAI]
For advice. Was that a mistake?
[KOENMA]
No, I think we can trust her.
What does that mean?
She's always been loyal.
Yes, to Spirit World.
That's the problem.
Dad's ordered Yusuke's
assasination.
What?!
Yusuke is so strong now
that the best hope
to kill him would
be through ambush.
Poisoning, for example. But
even that would take some skill.
You mean the kind of skill a
former Spirit Detective has?
[KOENMA]
Yeah.
You're sayin' I may have just
sent Yusuke to his death?
[YUSUKE]
That's you?
No way!
[laughs]
A lesson for you,
things change quick when
you're fourteen years old.
Soon after that,
I grew sixteen inches
but stayed the same weight,
on my way to becoming
Spirit Detective.
[DEMONS growling]
[DEMON 1 grunts]
[DEMON 2 yells]
[DEMON 3 grunts]
[KUROKO laughs]
Pretty soon, I'm gonna be Spirit
Detective, the youngest ever!
Dummy, you can't if
Yusuke's still alive!
[KAISEI]
Maybe he won't be!
Quiet, kids.
Yusuke, are you thirsty?
Do you like brandy?
Uh, yeah! It'd be
rude to say no.
Ooh, me! Brandy for me!
Me too! [laughs]
All right.
[KAISEI, FUBUKI cheer]
Look, I'm not trying
to be Mr. Morals,
but should you really
be giving liquor to kids?
Not the drink... Brandy candy.
Of course, good old candy!
But I get the drink, right?
Right. Just the tiniest
drop to flavor your tea.
[YUSUKE sighs]
Of course...
[KAYKO]
A-N-X-...
I-E-T-Y, anxiety.
Japanese word... shinpai.
H-E-S-I-T-A-T-I-O-N,
hesitation...
The Japanese word... tamerai.
[sighs]
P-A-T-I-E-N-C-E, patience.
Japanese... gaman.
[KAISEI laughing]
Woah...
[FUBUKI laughing]
There's nothing in
that candy, you guys.
It's just brandy flavored!
You're such a pair of
lightweights! [laughs]
Oh, shut up, Mom!
Yeah! You can't talk.
You've had half a glass
of beer and you're drunk!
These three must
drive you crazy.
I can't imagine
a better life.
Let's fight, Yusuke!
Gimme all you've got!
--[YUSUKE laughing]
--And I'm gonna beat you up!
You better wait a few years.
Eeh...
Oh, Yusuke you dream-boat. I
can't forget about that night.
[FUBUKI laughs]
Did you teach him
this little routine?
Cute, right?
[KAISEI snores]
So, Kuroko. What made you give
up being a Spirit Detective?
I wanted to get married.
It was time for me to start
making life instead
of hunting it.
And besides the Demons
that show up here
from time to time, out
for some kind of revenge,
I'm done with that
life completely now,
and I'm happy being normal.
I don't need it to
give me purpose anymore.
Don't you get bored?
I know what happened, Yusuke.
I heard about the Sensui case.
[KUROKO]
You know, I met him once,
when he took over my position.
[KUROKO] Of course I
sensed how strong he was,
but he seemed... fragile. Like,
he was always thinking
so hard to stay afloat.
I won't pull that.
I know you won't have the
same problem as Sensui.
In fact, you just
need to get back
to how you were before
you fought with him.
Not really thinking at all.
But they fired me
as Spirit Detective.
[KUROKO]
Things will change.
They need you too much.
[KUROKO] Here, let my
husband read your future.
It's his hobby. He's good.
[SHOUGO]
Sure.
Let's have some fun.
May I see your hand
please, Yusuke?
Now, slowly turn your face
so you're looking at me.
Directly forward.
[SHOUGO]
Good.
I see...
The world around you is nothing
you can complain
about. Peaceful.
Yet, for reason in your heart
that you can't fathom,
you yearn for danger,
then wonder if it's wrong.
Well, well... You are good.
But the more time you
want to spend thinking
and doing nothing,
the less you should think.
And the more want
to do something,
the less you should move.
So is this fun for you?
[SHOUGO] It means whether
or not you want it
doesn't matter now, Yusuke.
The danger will come to you.
[KUROKO sighs]
You expecting anyone
to drop in tonight?
No... My editor is
supposed to come by,
but that's not
until the morning.
[crickets chirping]
[gasps]
Don't hide.
[KUROKO] What business do you
have, coming into my home?
The business is not yours.
We've come for the boy,
now step aside.
Touou...
I do apologize
for my colleague.
It is uncivil for us to come
to you at such a late hour,
but we have little time to act.
I must explain
this all quickly.
His visit was a secret.
How did you know you
would find him here?
We've followed his
Demon Energy.
[YUSUKE]
Get to the point, cue ball.
What do you want from me?
[HOKUSHIN] We have come here
on a mandate from Demon World.
[YUSUKE gasps]
Demon World?
[SHOUGO whimpers]
I have come to tell
you your destiny,
and take you to the place
where you actually belong.
The place where I belong?
Yes. Not through jokes,
nor flight, nor fists...
...will you escape your call.
[NARRATOR] Three cryptic
visitors from Demon World
have tracked Yusuke down.
What is the destiny
they claim to know?
Is it the answer Yusuke needs,
or the start of
something more sinister?
[YUSUKE] Hell, if I
knew all I had to do
when I was feeling crappy
is call up a few
shiny-headed monks,
well I'd be a pretty
well-adjusted person.
In fact, I could start
up an 800 number.
Don't know what
you're doing in life?
Call the bald guy hotline!
They'll fix you right up!
So yeah, these guys are spittin'
out some insane answers
that could change
my whole life,
but that doesn't
mean I can trust 'em.
In fact, I just might
have to kick some ass!
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!