♪
[NARRATOR] Strange reports
from Yusuke's home turf
has Spirit World in a state
of alarm while Yusuke,
feeling empty and bored after
winning the Dark Tournament,
was quickly lured
into a fist fight
with apparently
harmless students.
As Botan warned Kuwabara of
the unexplained outbursts
of Spirit Energy, Poo flew
in with a frantic message.
Somehow, despite
all his strength,
Yusuke has been kidnapped.
Tonight at eleven,
come to the old mansion
in Rokurokubi Estates.
[KUWABARA] You may bring
as many guests as you like.
But Kurama, Hiei, and
Kuwabara must be among them.
If these three
don't show up on time,
Yusuke Urameshi's survival
cannot be guaranteed.
[BOTAN] It still
doesn't make sense.
How could they have
captured him?
Some serious firepower,
that's for sure.
And knowing about Hiei
and Kurama says a lot too.
Yeah, these aren't your normal
punks off the playground.
Somethin' bad is in the works.
[BOTAN]
Well, let's hurry.
We have to track down
our favorite demon pair.
I bet Kurama's
at his school.
He practically
lives there.
Right. Poo, you watch
Yusuke's home for us.
Poo!
[FACULTY] Attention,
remaining students.
The janitors are
locking up for the day.
Please make your way home, and
we'll see you in the morning.
[STUDENT] Come one, Suichi,
you have to! You're a genius!
And with you as captain,
our team could finally win!
As exciting as a biology meet
sounds, my weekends are full.
But you're a prodigy...
Top scores every week, and the
girls love you, don't they?!
You'll turn this
old club around!
We start winning contests,
we get more funding,
then we get girlfriends!
Please!
You've certainly thought
this out, but I can't.
[STUDENT]
Oh, no you don't!
I've waited too long
to get my chance!
You join this team
or face our wrath!
Nerd violence.
[KUWABARA] Kurama!!
Don't tell me...
Hey!! Where are you?
Oh Kurama!
Do you think you could
be a bit more discreet?
Hey don't distract me.
I've having enough
trouble without my energy.
[KUWABARA] And yelling
helps me keep focus!!
[STUDENT]
Sorry, Suichi...
I'm not really mean,
just desperate, please!
Yes, well, you did
have me scared.
So, will you join?
There you are, Kurama!!
You could've just come
into the hall, you know.
Oh dear.
Hey, what did
he call you?
Who's Kurama?
Oh, just a
meaningless nickname.
There's no need to remember it.
Yes, isn't that right?
Please be mindful,
I'm Suichi here.
Oh, oops.
Is there a reason
you've come?
I'll say, take a
look at this.
Any ideas who could
have written it?
Smells human.
Yeah, that's what's weird.
He left with school kids.
We got just four hours
to find Hiei.
Well, he should be
somewhere in the city.
Although his criminal
record has been cleared,
Koenma still confines him here.
I have not seen
him lately, though.
Too bad Hiei's not here.
We could use his Jagan
Eye to find himself.
That's right.
Logic is panic's prey.
[STUDENT]
Can I get some help?
[gong rings]
[KOENMA] Yusuke's kidnapped?
What is this, April Fool's Day?
It's the truth, Koenma sir.
Look at Botan's report.
Very clever, Ogre.
Did you forge that yourself?
Would you listen
to me for once!
Someone's really
kidnapped him.
And we still don't know who
they are, or what they want.
[KOENMA] Fine,
I'll play along. What else?
Uh, Botan says Yusuke was last
seen leaving his junior high
with three apparently
normal humans teens.
What??
Humans, of course!
The strange blips of human
energy popping up on the radar.
It must be linked.
So now what?
[KURAMA] It's hard
finding Hiei when he
doesn't want to be found.
He could be anywhere.
Can't Koenma find him for us?
Now, now. Koenma wouldn't
waste his effort
making Spirit Detectives if he
still had to do all the work.
That's right!
Yusuke's detective items!
What the what now?
Koenma made them for Yusuke
when he first started.
That's when we were tracking
down you and Hiei.
But then he broke the
compass with Rando,
then he lost the mirror, so
I refurbished them all,
but after that I forgot
when I left them
in my pink komono cause we all
know I never wear that anymore!
I think she's
gone crazy.
You're hardly the
standard for wild outbursts.
I'll need a little
time to fetch it all.
[KURAMA] Very well.
We'll reconvene
at the park in an hour.
It's a date!
[BOTAN]
And bingo!
All the gadgets of the
Spirit Detective!
Wow, like a real
secret agent!
So, which device
will find him?
Oh, right. Let's see...
The superbly improved
Demon Compass!
A fresh take on
the classic style
for tracking down any demon!
But can't Hiei simply deceive
it by manipulating his energy?
Not anymore, thanks to this
newly installed Sample Chamber.
By placing his DNA inside,
such as from a strand of hair,
we can find him
regardless of his energy!
It's too bad I don't carry
around a locket of his hair.
Yes, good point.
Ah! How about this
Psychic Spy Glass!
We can see through brick walls,
and search the entire city!
In less than an hour?
Okay, forget seeing
through walls!
We'll use the Concentration
Ring to blow them up!
Let me see this stuff.
Careful!!
I'm accountable for that!
Perhaps it's the wrong approach.
Instead of finding him,
is there an item that
will make him find us?
Get real! Botan would
have mentioned it
if we had something
like that!
We do!
[BOTAN]
The Mystic Whistle!
I never had much of a reason
to show Yusuke this darling,
but it's really quite neat.
Sort of a dog whistle
for apparitions.
It shoots out a sound
wave only they can hear.
The stronger your Spirit Energy,
the louder the sound.
I can make it go for
at least sixty miles.
You better cover your ears.
It's rather annoying.
'kay.
Well, here goes!
[high pitched whistle blow]
[bird wings flapping
and squawks]
It penetrates my brain.
Really? I'm not hearing
anything but the birds.
There, now we wait for Hiei.
Hopefully he shows up.
That was fast.
What repulsive creature
makes my eardrums bleed?
Thanks, Hiei. I thought you
would come if we called.
I didn't know it was you.
I only came to find the source
of that vile noise...
...and kill it.
[KURAMA] Here.
You had better read this.
So, the detective's
been ensnared.
Wish I'd been around to see it.
Must have been too cocky
to realize his own weakness.
Just tell the kidnappers
I turned it down.
I'm finished babysitting.
You must be
curious, Hiei.
Someone strong enough
to overcome Yusuke
must surely provide a challenge.
Nice try...
...but I no longer care.
How can you even of
walking off, Hiei?
If you don't come,
Yusuke could be killed!
Not my responsibility.
You should have
learned by now
this is a kill
or be killed world.
If you're too weak
to help yourself,
you deserve to fall.
[KURAMA] Then what if stopping
these people now protected
your own interests?
The culprits are likely human,
and we both know what
powerful humans like to hunt.
If they're allowed
to kill Yusuke,
perhaps you will be next.
Fighting humans, that
nearly peaks my interest,
but not quite.
I wonder, Hiei...
How have you liked being
stuck on probation,
bolted down to
one human city?
What do you think?
Well, if you help bring
back Yusuke alive,
I'll have Koenma cut your
sentence to time served.
You'll be free.
You sure you
wanna do that?
There's no other choice.
We're almost out of time.
Make your call, Hiei.
Fighting humans
to win my freedom...
Yes, sounds like a deal.
[BOTAN] Then come on!
This is one house party
we can't be late to!
[KUWABARA] I'm gonna
kick so much tail!
[Laughing]
[KUWABARA]
Stop laughing, hamster-legs!
[KUWABARA] Is this the place?
Looks deformed.
[BOTAN] It's the only old
mansion on the block.
Well, stay here Botan.
Whatever this house is,
it's definitely not
safe for non-fighters.
That's sweet I guess,
but I'm going.
With Yusuke out and you missing
your Spirit Energy,
I'm the only one who can
use the detective tools.
She's right. Our strength
lies in numbers.
Give a warning
next time!
The House of Four Dimensions...
Once entered, this do not:
Ever utter the word 'hot.'
Is it some kind of riddle?
No, it is a warning. There's
no way to know if it's real.
[KURAMA] But we might as
well take precaution.
[KUWABARA]
Right. Nobody say hot.
[BOTAN]
Shh!
Damn it.
[Kido chuckles]
Your friends have come
to visit you, Yusuke.
[YUSUKE] What are you
poser bastards up to?
How come I can't move?
And hell, why do your
doors look so stupid?
[KIDO] You've entered
my Territory.
Space and time follow
different rules.
See how I'm stepping
on your shadow?
Here, it's as binding
as a straightjacket.
Now try to relax.
Our night's about to begin.
Well, that's odd.
What is this place?
It looks all twisted up.
And that steam. It's
like an oven it's so ho...
Remember the word
we're not saying.
[HIEI] Kurama...
Did you feel that?
Yes, when we entered the
energy schematic changed.
It feels as though we've
somehow been transported
to a different space.
[VOICE] Or a different
space-time.
Welcome to the house, everyone.
I'm so glad you made it.
Yeah, that's him, one of
the guys Urameshi left with.
[chuckle]
Recognition. I just
love how that feels.
Listen, dork. I don't
know who you think you are,
but we're no
normal school kids.
His name is Kaitou.
Hold on, how on earth
do you know that?
He is a classmate.
All of his test scores
are second only to mine.
Remarkably bright for his age,
I've never spoken
to him personally,
and naturally I never
told him about you.
Kaitou!
Where have you gotten
your information?
And why have you
kidnapped Yusuke?
[Kaitou chuckles]
It's a real grip-your-seat
mystery, isn't it.
I hear your team won something
called the Dark Tournament,
and I hear that's quite a feat.
My congratulations.
[KAITOU] Really, I was most
surprised about you, Suichi.
Try to put yourself
in my shoes.
Learning my school rival
can also do the funniest
things with plants.
[KAITOU] Ooh.
That's a scary look...
I don't remember
you ever making
that face in
the classroom.
Then again, we both keep
things from our peers.
You see, I've learned
that I have a talent, too.
And being such great
champions as you are,
I was hoping I could
test them out on you.
Okay, this is ridiculous!
We've been through stuff you
couldn't even dream about!
[HIEI]
I'll take him.
You'll agree my impatience for
human fools will be an asset.
Now!
[KAITOU]
You'll be sorry.
I doubt that!
[Laughing]
[KAITOU]
Never doubt.
How the heck did
he just do that?
Energy came right out of
nowhere, it looked weird!
As you see, this is
a very special room,
where brute strength
cannot exist.
[KAITOU] Only your
words have power here.
Just make sure you
follow my one posted rule.
What's he saying?
He must mean the
note on the door.
Indeed.
As a child,
playing pretend,
I would make my own
world with my own rules.
But I've learned I
can do it for real.
Growing up as a bookworm,
I guess it was inevitable what
I would decide to rule out...
...violence.
[Growl]
[KAITOU] I see why that
disturbs you, Hiei.
In the world of fighting,
your skills let you
bully anybody you want.
But in my Territory,
you're just a tiny,
swordless man.
Control your temper, Hiei.
He wants you to act
out of anger.
Any buffoon can
make a shield.
How do we know your other
claim isn't just a bluff?
There's only one way.
No three-letter word
can rule my fate.
[HIEI]
Hot!
[KURAMA] Fight it,
Hiei. Try!
[KAITOU] I told
him not to doubt me.
But, that's what happens when
you say the taboo word.
Your soul becomes
part of my Territory.
Wake him up!
He's ice cold!
Oh dear.
[KAITOU]
You lose a point.
Now we've taken
two hostages,
Urameshi's having
his fun upstairs.
So, what's
your next move?
[KAITOU]  Go home? Or play
through the round?
[KAITOU]
It's a kick, your lifestyle.
The secrets. Dueling opponents
with special powers.
I only started last month,
but I've worked hard.
My first challenge was learning
how to control my power.
The guys and I call it
manifesting our Territory.
So far, I've gotten to a
ten meter radius around me.
As long as I concentrate,
everything inside it has to
follow the rules I've set.
Imagination turned
to physical law.
So, by that logic,
if we incapacitate you,
the rules will cease and Hiei's
soul will return to his body.
[KAITOU]
I don't know. Maybe.
No one's beaten me yet
so it hasn't come up.
That's it!
I can't take anymore of this
rookie and his ego trip!
How do you stand these
friends of yours, Suichi?
They can't handle one
smart conversation.
It must get lonely.
Still, you haven't chosen.
Will you challenge me,
or go home?
Wait, you're forgettin'
the third option.
Really? I'm drawing a blank,
what do you mean?
We forget about Hiei
for now and move on.
That's my vote!
I never expected to hear
that from you, Kuwabara!
Hiei's your teammate!
It's his own code!
Right? You had to bribe
him to help Urameshi
'cause he said weak
men deserve to fall.
Then he turns around and says
the wrong thing on purpose,
just to be cool!
Let's save him
after we're through!
That'll teach
him a lesson!
[KAITOU] You have
a brain, after all.
[KAITOU] Of course it's not
a very good one.
That option isn't valid.
Why not? You can't
hold us back!
[KAITOU]
No.
But you can't get
through a doorway
if you don't have
the proper key.
You mean Urameshi's
in there?
[Yanagisawa chuckles]
[KAITOU] Let's just say that
door is your first step.
But Yanagisawa
has the only key.
Now this is I can handle.
All right, Mr. Hairspray,
hand over the key while
I'm askin' ya nicely.
No dice.
Listen, I'll give you
one more shot
just in case you
don't know who I am.
Give me the dumb key!
All right!
Why don't you come knock
me out and take it man?
Come on, or did you lose
your strength, too?
You little...
Shut your hole!
You gotta get a
better memory.
We're still inside
of Kaitou's Territory,
and you know he
doesn't like violence.
We gotta be gentle
with each other, okay?
[KUWABARA] How 'bout I gently
shove my foot down your throat?
So, you finally decide?
I'll play by your rules
Kaitou, whatever they are.
Good.
[NARRATOR] And so,
the trap has been laid.
To get the key and go
deeper within the house,
to rescue Hiei's captured soul,
and to free Yusuke who
is bound by his own shadow,
Kurama must answer
his brilliant
schoolmate's challenge,
and take part in a
mysterious battle of words.
But what exactly
does that mean?
What grand scheme do these
strangely powered teenagers
have in mind,
and what other oddities
await our team
in the House of
Four Dimensions?
[YUUSKE] Yeah, yeah,
what I think
we're trying to
say here is...
...what the hell is going on
in this freaky house!
Freckly four-eyes over there
is definitely got a thing
for turning souls
into bouncy balls,
as Kuwabara gets the
statue-treatment too.
I don't know what game
Kurama's got to play here,
but he better be good at it,
cause his smarts are the
only way to save us all.
Not to mention that
being paralyzed
is really pissing me off.
It's a battle of minds,
next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪