♪
[NARRATOR] Shinobu Sensui,
former Spirit Detective,
witnessed the darker side of
human nature while on a case.
Disgusted by the atrocities
man could inflict,
he has vowed to open a
tunnel to Demon World,
demanding every human's life
as punishment for their sins.
Just as Koenma was
briefing the team,
Sensui and his henchman Sniper
struck at Yusuke's apartment.
Now, the Spirit Detectives
of past and present
prepare to match
wits and fists.
[YUSUKE] Afternoon, Detective
Sensui. Rumor is you snapped.
You could only deal
with the baby stuff.
Far to the contrary, Urameshi,
I came to lead you
along the path of truth.
I'll stop you, freak.
You will fail.
They both just flared up
without even a warning.
[PUU]
Puu.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Like I
told Genkai before,
there's something
fake about his power.
The only way to
know his strength
is to meet him head on!
[BOTAN]
It's begun.
You can't.
You're actually saving me?
But I just tried to murder
you and your best friends,
I almost did, too!
How can you want to help me?
When men do what they're
supposed to do,
it's not always about
what they want.
Safety! Bring him in to safety!
They'll take him!
You have to tell me what
you're talking about!
Who? Who's in danger?
Do you mean Yusuke?
[YUSUKE THINKS] This is it!
I've caught him off guard.
Oh, Yusuke!
Try that again.
Get yourself off
the ground Urameshi!
You won't defeat him lying down!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
What the hell was that?
All my punches were solid,
but he just brushed them aside
like broccoli he didn't order.
Didn't even give me a
chance to kick his ass!
As I thought, the two
detectives are too much alike.
With their similar background,
it's akin to fighting your own
reflection in the mirror...
A futile war that
cannot be won.
Sensui anticipates
Yusuke's every move.
It's what he would do.
Only, he's one step ahead.
You're not wrong.
And it's all thanks
to his Resshuuken Style.
[YUSUKE THINKS] Resshuuken?
[NARRATOR] Resshuuken is a
special brand of martial arts
that relies on fast footwork.
The fighter maintains
his position
while diverting
attacks with his arms,
then retaliates
with powerful kicks.
There are stringent
rules governing the study
of the Resshuuken style.
One may only learn its ways
once they have every other
technique under their belt,
so many consider
it the strongest,
most elegant maneuver
in all of martial arts.
[SEA MAN] No, Kuwabara!
He's in danger!
[SHIZURU] My brother may
be accident-prone,
but with the others
he's safe.
You're not understanding me.
Mr. Sensui desperately wants
to recruit him to his side.
You got the wrong guy.
No one wants Kazuma on their
side, they get stuck with him.
No, I'm sure Kuwabara
is the psychic.
Mr. Sensui needs his power
to cut down the barrier!
We've got to
warn them!
I can't see them,
where did they all go?
Oh great, they've moved on.
Hey!
[SHIZURU]
Botan! Get down!
[BOTAN]
Oh, not this guy again!
Yes, old woman,
you recognize the
Resshuuken art-form,
but this technique...
you have never seen.
My own special blend of
Resshuuken and Spirit Energy.
A vengeful new twist
on an old favorite.
I like to call it the
Reikou-Resshuuken.
Remarkable.
Energy and style as one.
[KOENMA THINKS] Well,
you've been making the most
of your retirement years,
and that's what matters.
[SHIZURU] I have
to do something
or else Kazuma's toast.
I have an idea!
It's time to judge your allies.
Get down now!
[KUWABARA}
NO!
[BOTAN] Shizuru!
What are you doing?
My duty as a sister.
He may piss me off sometimes
but he's my little bro,
and I'm the only one
who gets to pick on him!
[KUWABARA] Guess all
the training in the world
can't make up for bad aim!
Oh no! Isn't that
Yusuke's apartment?
Damn, Sensui...
This muscle flexing was
just a diversion all along.
A diversion?!
That dingbat's diversion
could've killed Botan and...
MY SISTER!!!
[YUSUKE THINKS] But why?
Hold on! Help is
on the way!
Kuwabara!
[YUSUKE]
Heads up!
All right, guys. You go
take care of the girls.
Meanwhile
you'll be...?
Permanently retiring his ass!
For such a dumb kid,
you've got a pretty
smart mouth Urameshi.
What do you like smarts?
Tell me if this
smarts enough for ya!
[SENSUI THINKS] Interesting...
not a bad fake,
...not that it'll do
him much good.
[YUSUKE THINKS] That's right.
Just try and anticipate
my next move!
Urameshi!
Now I'm gettin' pissed!
[SENSUI] It's a
shame Junior couldn't
find a better replacement.
I just can't decide if
I should be insulted,
or flattered.
[BYSTANDER A]
What's causing that?
Well, when there's
smoke there's fire.
[GAME MASTER]
There's the signal.
Yeah, it's a full scale war
now, brat. No turnin' back.
[YUSUKE THINKS] So... he
thinks he's better than me?
[KEIKO] Shizuru?
[KEIKO]
Shizuru, are you all right?
I'm okay, but...
But...?
But unfortunately,
I can't say the same
for my kid brother,
who once again has gotten
himself in serious danger.
Those freaks want
to kidnap him,
which isn't such
a bad deal for me,
but they're going
to use him to open
the plastic wrap to hell,
so you might wanna tell Yusuke
to keep him out of sight.
I'll do whatever I can.
Thanks Keiko, I knew
I could count on you.
I'll be there in a minute.
If I don't bleed to death.
There! Get him!
They just don't make Spirit
Detectives like they used to.
You mean crazy and evil?
No, they sure don't, thank you.
Bite me!
Gee Urameshi,
just stop playing
chicken with his feet
and use your Spirit Gun to
deep-fry his skinny little rear!
Unless Yusuke prevents
those feet from turning,
any attempt at
a counterattack
would be like
tilting at a windmill.
Well now that I've finally
got a leg up on you,
let's see how you play
kick ball with this!
[SENSUI] Lucky for
me I have a spare.
[KUWABARA] Hey you
yellow-bellied bully!
Are you just gonna kick
a man while he's down?
Why not fight me,
the warrior of love,
defender of the defenseless?!
He'll kill you!
For I am Kazuma Kuwabara!
And now prepare to
feel my shiny new sword!
[SENSUI THINKS] At last,
the moment of truth
I've been waiting for.
We'll see if he
really is the one.
Wait a sec.
This is just my plain old,
everyday Spirit Sword.
[KUWABARA] Man, what happened
to the new souped-up one
I used against Sea Man?
Darn, woulda
been cool.
[SENSUI THINKS] That blade could
barely slice through butter,
let alone dimensions.
He must need
stimulus to power up.
Here goes!
That isn't
very wise!
[KURAMA THINKS]
His defense is superb.
Rose Whip.
[KURAMA THINKS] He may be
able to elude direct attacks,
but my Rose
Whip can hit
several points of
contact at once.
That's not normal.
Must be a movie stunt!
So...
Dare you risk that erratic
weapon amongst civilians?
[KURAMA THINKS]
Merciless coward.
No wonder he moved the
fight to the center of town.
[Sensui chuckles]
[SENSUI] I'm hurt, Kurama.
Isn't my death
worth a few lives,
they'll be dead soon enough.
[SENSUI THINKS]
Ah, Sniper... perfect timing.
[SENSUI]
Farewell!
After him!
You can't do that with these
innocents standing around.
Fine, not that I
ever miss my target,
but if it's a change of
venue you want, I'm game.
With all these gawkers waiting
for blood I can't see a thing!
[KURAMA THINKS] Obviously
they're trying to split us up.
But why? To isolate Yusuke?
We should stay together,
yet they leave me no choice.
[KEIKO] Kurama!
It's Kuwabara!
We have to find
Yusuke and warn him!
Stay back!
[KEIKO] Oh, Puu!
Puu please wake up! Please!
[PUU]
Puu.
You're alright!
[KURAMA]
Keiko! Are you injured?
No, but we absolutely have to
get to Kuwabara before they do!
[KURAMA]
Why?
[KUWABARA THINKS]
I mean, seriously.
Why can't we ever have
a chase on an elevator!
Why aren't you inside watching
cartoons like a normal kid?
Anyways there's a lot of
weirdoes out there today,
so go on, run home
to your mom.
When I was a boy we
listened to our elders,
and our video games!
[KUWABARA THINKS] My Spirit
Awareness is working again!
I must be caught up in one
of those mutant's Territories.
But whose?
You little punk!
Is this yours?
No more running
away for you, Sensui.
This is the place where
I end your damn life.
[SENSUI THINKS]
Three...two...one...
[Kuwabara screaming]
[YUSUKE]
Kuwabara!
Uh oh!
Just hang on I'll
be right there!
[SENSUI]
Gotta run!
[YUSUKE] Damn damn!
Oh no we're too late!
[YUSUKE]
Look out below!
Your car's about to be
impounded, Spirit Gun!
Oh crap! I forgot
about Kuwabara!
Really, Yusuke...
How could you shoot
a blast that big
without thinking it would kill
everyone on board including him?
I was mad!
[KUWABARA] Urameshi!
If you kill me,
you are so dead!
[SENSUI]
Resshuu-Koukyuuha!
[YUSUKE THINKS] That jerk
popped my Spirit Gun
like a party balloon at
a stupid kid's birthday!
In case anyone's takin' notes,
that's not a good sign.
Later.
[KURAMA] On the
bright side,
at least Kuwabara
survived.
[KUWABARA] Yeah,
and they got away!
[KEIKO] Yusuke!
What are you doing?!
That's not even yours!
[YUSUKE]
It is now!
Keiko you know I can't
let them hurt Kuwabara!
Stupid bike lock!
And don't tell me
not to save him.
It's what he would do.
Wait, there's something
you need to know!
[Kuwabara crying out]
[NARRATOR] Sensui's
masterful plan to kidnap
Kuwabara has succeeded.
Can Yusuke possibly
catch up to them
in time to prevent the
jaded ex-Spirit Detective
from breaking through the
barrier to Demon World,
and unleashing terror on earth?
[SHIZURU] Kazuma's hogtied in
the back of a pick-up truck
on his way to bring about
the end of the world.
Knock me over with a feather.
Not that I
would ever want
anything to happen
to the big lug,
he's still my baby bro,
and always will be.
Luckily, he's got a
friend like Yusuke
to look after him
when I can't,
'cause I don't
know about you,
but after twenty minutes
on the exer-cycle,
it's time for a smoke break.
Ugh, I am so over
that whole studly rebel
without a helmet thing.
Well... our fate's in
Yusuke's legs.
Let's see how fast he pedals.
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪