♪
[NARRATOR] One day, Yusuke
Urameshi was killed in a car
accident after saving
a boy's life.
He awoke as a ghost,
and traveled with
a guide named Botan
to the mysterious
Spirit World.
There he met Koenma,
a child-sized ruler
who gave him a chance
to win back his life,
if he could hatch a
dangerous Spirit Beast.
Yusuke took the challenge,
then borrowed
his rival's body
to tell his loved
ones to be strong
because he
would soon return.
I think I can feel
this thing kicking!
Maybe it's practicing
to devour you.
No! Not this little guy!
He's growing on nothing
but good vibes from me.
I've been on
my best behavior.
Well, we'll see.
This ordeal is
kinda tough though.
I mean as hard
as I'm trying I can't
think of a damn
good thing to do.
Well I don't think you'll
become a Good Samaritan
just by following the
girl you've got a crush on.
I don't have a crush on
Keiko, we're just friends!
And I just feel something
bad's gonna happen to her.
I agree you
have a bad feeling.
It's called, will Keiko
like another boy?
Hey!
[Keiko screams]
Think of it as
a toll road, missy.
You give us five hundred dollars
and we let you pass by.
Or I'm sure we could find
other ways for you to pay.
Don't you touch me!
Bastards!
Maybe I'll let you see
what's under my mask.
[KEIKO]
That's easy. Bad breath.
[KUWABARA]
Hands off!
Kuwabara.
[KUWABARA] I take it you guys
are from Kazanega Junior High.
Cause that's where
all the idiots go to school.
It's okay.
Just go on home now.
But I don't even--
Let's just call it an
apology for yesterday.
[KEIKO]
Thank you.
You know I really can't stand it
when guys pick on
people weaker than them.
But I guess I'll
do it to you anyway!
You little!
Against normal people
Kuwabara's pretty good.
Go for the kidneys!
As far as causing
trouble's concerned
you boys keep
topping yourselves.
Attacking a trio of older boys
from Kazanega Junior High,
who according to their
mothers were quite harmless.
Unacceptable!
Here at Sarayashki
Junior High we have
a thing called accountability!
[YUSUKE] Oh please.
Not that speech again.
Why doesn't he tell him that
he did it to save Keiko?
Teachers like that
don't care about reasons.
They just want
to keep yapping.
[TEACHER] What's this?
Not listening?
Well, we'll soon fix that.
[AKASHI] Okubo, I understand
you're working in a part
time job with the school's
permission. Is that true?
Uh huh.
Well not anymore.
Come on! Okubo's
job and this fight
don't got nothing
to do with each other!
Please don't do that,
Mr. Akashi!
My mother is the only
grown-up in our house.
My brother and sisters
are all still little.
If I don't have a job
we can't afford to eat.
If you're bent on
punishing somebody today,
leave these guys alone
and punish me why don't you?
I'm the one who caused
the real damage, anyway.
Well if you're going
to be so pathetic about it,
maybe I can overlook this,
if you make me a promise.
You just name it.
Alright, you have
to promise not to
fight anyone for an entire week.
That's totally undoable man!
What are we supposed
to do if those guys
come back and try to jump us?
Can you make it shorter?
How 'bout two hours?
That seems fair, right?
If you want one week,
then you got it.
But can you
do that, Kuwabara?
[THUG] Three hours!
Ask for three!
Then the promise is made.
And you know what happens
to people who break promises.
I think he just signed
a death sentence.
Breaking the Honor Code is
one of the highest violations
at Sarayashki
Junior High, Mr. Iwamoto.
Yes, and from the way that
boy acted at Yusuke's wake,
he's clearly a punk
who can't resist a fight.
This way we can expel
him permanently.
I don't know which boost to the
school's reputation I like best,
kicking out Kuwabara or
having Yusuke die on his own!
[YUSUKE] I always said those
teachers were out to get me.
I'm surprised they didn't
run me over themselves.
Those guys could use
a good kick in the rear.
Man, I'm getting
angry already.
But let's please
keep this promise.
I didn't tell Mr. Akashi this,
but my mom's sick
and can't work either.
I'm not making this up.
My family could really starve.
Wow, and I thought I had
a bad living situation.
There's no reason
to worry Okubo.
I'll stay at home all week and
I won't even lift a finger.
It's a man's promise!
You're a real friend.
I think we should all get
home as quick as we can today
so the guys from
Kazanega don't see us.
Best of luck until tomorrow.
Remember!
No punching!
I never thought I'd
hear Kuwabara say that.
This is gonna
be one crazy week.
Kuwabara's so loyal
to his friends.
I'll have
to make a note.
Oh yes he's so brave!
You just wait Botan.
This little promise of
his won't last for long.
You don't think
that Kuwabara...?
Those boys should
arrive any minute now.
Mr. Akashi? Gee!
Doesn't this guy have a life
besides tormenting kids?
Kuwabara,
we've been waiting.
Now's really not the time.
[THUG] What is this?!
Kuwabara!
Are you actually
running away like a sissy?
Oh no, I'm not
going anywhere.
He does have guts to face
us without his slave boys.
Especially with the ass-kicking
we're about to give him.
Talk all you want.
Let's see what you can do.
See, what'd I tell you?
[Akashi laughs]
It couldn't be more perfect!!
But I'm not going to fight back.
So you just hit me
as much you're gonna
and let me get out of here!
What did he say??
He's so cool!
It's official, you guys.
Kuwabara has turned into a wuss.
[thugs laugh]
Please guys.
[THUG] Look at this
wimp! Fight back!
Man that's ugly!
Is that a tooth?
Why doesn't he hit them?
I've got one favor
to ask you numbskulls.
Take out all your anger on me
and leave my
buddies out of this.
Yeah I think
we can handle that.
Hitting you's
more fun anyhow.
You're pretty tricky Kuwabara,
but I promise this
isn't over yet.
Dude! What's wrong
with your face?
Those brats from Kazanega
got the best of me.
But I never hit
them back Okubo.
You should have fought.
It's nothin I can't take.
[AKASHI]
Kuwabara.
Are those new bruises today?
I got piled on by those guys
you said were harmless
but I didn't touch 'em!
I'm so impressed.
But I talked to some of the
other teachers yesterday
about our arrangement and they
said I was too easy on you.
What??
I was just as surprised as
you are but they were convinced.
So in addition to not
fighting you must all
score fifty percent or higher
on the Physical Science test.
Hey! You can't just
keep adding conditions!
I'm afraid I just did.
And if one of you fails,
Okubo's job goes out the window!
Please, we can pass that
test easy if we study a little.
I got like a forty-five on my
last Physical Science test!
No worries here!
I scored a fifty-seven.
How 'bout you Okubo?
Yeah I got a thirty-nine so if
I try a little
harder I'll be good.
We're gonna be okay, right
Kuwabara? What did you get?
Uh I got uh...
A seven!
Well what do you know.
Kuwabara is stupider than I am!
What did you make
on your last test?
I got a twelve!
[KUWABARA] Don't worry, fellas!
We've got plenty of time!
If I study all night,
there's maybe a chance!
Not a chance in hell.
There are two types of
volcanoes, cone shapes and uh--
Hm. How do
you say that word?
At least it looks like he's
thinking hard
over there, right?
If he thinks too hard with
that bruised head of his,
it might just explode.
Yeah, I'm worried.
Hah! Even if Kuwabara studies
until he's blue in the face,
he still couldn't score more
than thirty points on this.
[KUWABARA] Let's see.
One of these is gotta help.
Are you telling me he's
gonna spend money
on something for school?
And what is the thug of
Sarayashki Junior
High reading?
It's a good thing
we found you.
We can pay
you back for the
incident at
the baseball field.
That's fine!
But I'm not going to fight you
so just beat me up all you
want and go on back
to your own turf!
Trust me,
that's no problem.
Come on, tough guy!
[sounds of fighting
and groaning by Kuwabara]
[MIYAMOTO] Oh, dude!
You're hideous!
[OKUBO] Seriously. Maybe
I can get a different job!
[KOMADA] Tell us who did this!
We'll slaughter them!
Oh don't worry
about it Komada.
I've been missing my daily
beatings with Urameshi
gone anyway!
He's gone mad.
Enough about my dumb old
bruises. Let's get to studying.
If the moon causes gravity,
and gravity causes waves--
[BOTAN] He sticks to
his goals like glue.
I can say he's got
more guts in him
than anyone else I've ever
rammed into the pavement.
It's a good thing I came
over to check on him.
He's fallen asleep
in the final inning.
Hey Kuwabara! Kuwabara!
Wake up and study dufus!
Your test is tomorrow!
Seems he's out for good.
Guess I'll have to
show up in his dream.
Urameshi! You've come
back for a fight, huh?
Well I'm gonna make
cat food out of you!
Hey! Whoa
whoa whoa whoa!
You've got to
pass this test first!
Gimme! I was just studying
this before you showed up.
Why is the
color of blood red?
Because of all
the red blood cells!
They color it!
That's easy!
But what's the pigment?
Hemoglobin! I forgot!
And what causes
your blood to clot?
Uh, platelets.
Yes, good, good.
And sulfur in the
atmosphere makes acid rain.
[THUG 1] Hey look.
There goes Kuwabara.
I heard he doesn't try
to fight back anymore
when people attack him!
I say we go have
some fun with him!
[THUG 1] Buddy, you're speaking
my language! Come on!
Hey you! Kuwabara!
We wanna have
a word with you!
Oh great, there's no way
I'm wasting that whole night
of questions and answers
cause these lame-o's
make him miss the test!
Anyone who touches
him is dead meat!
Hey! Why the
hell are you stopping?
I don't know man,
I got a bad feeling.
Why don't we turn back.
What are you psychic? Let's go!
I warned you!
[YUSUKE]
I keep forgetting!
[girls giggling]
Oh I know!
[THUHG 3]
Out of the way!!
[YUSUKE]
I'll get you jerks!
Misako! Are you okay?
Hey I know her from school!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Botan
said people get closer to the
Spirit World
when they're asleep,
and she just fainted!
Maybe I can--
Misako, you okay?
Where are you going?!
Get him!
Yeah!
Just wait till I catch you!!
You should've listened.
And you should
go to school, girl.
As soon as
I knock you out!!
Don't you know there's
a test today?! Moron!
I feel better! Kuwabara.
[Yusuke laughs]
Somebody help me!
Man I'm positive I studied this.
But I can't remember.
Kuwabara, just try to
remember what you dreamed.
Hey! I got it!
Guys! I just took the test
and I cleared fifty points!
How'd you already
get the results?
I copied down my
answers on scratch paper
so I could check 'em in the
textbook after I was through,
and I've already
looked over it four times!
I scored fifty-three big ones!
Then you saved me!
Wow Kuwabara
you really licked 'em!
Naw, it was nothing.
Just a promise between men.
Don't get modest now Kuwabara.
Tell 'em you're the big cheese!
This can't be right!
[AKASHI THINKS]
That garbage-brain actually
scored more than fifty points!
If that brat had only missed
one more question!
Now he's thrown the
whole plan into the sewer!
Let me show you a
different method of grading.
You see Mr. Akashi, there really
wasn't an answer written there.
You've made a mistake.
[AKASHI]
Yes, I see.
No! That's wrong!
And what's really painful
is that you were so close!
But I'm afraid a promise
is a promise young man.
I'll go notify
Okubo's employers.
But I checked it.
Oh well. I guess there are
many things you can't do right.
[KUWABARA THINKS]
I know this isn't right!
I checked all the
answers myself!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
I-I don't believe it!
That no good teacher
erased my last answer!
Who does
he think he is?!
I'll show you!
Kuwabara, stop!
I don't know if you can hear
me but I'm gonna say this!
Just remember Okubo! All
the poundings you took for him!
Punch this teacher
and all that's erased!
Kuwabara!
It would've been worth getting
hit just to see you expelled.
But either way the test score
is marked down as forty-eight.
I've got the power,
you see?!
[Akashi laughs]
[MR. TAKENAKA] Find
something funny, Mr. Akashi?
[AKASHI] Did you see
that Mr. Takenaka?
That hoodlum
nearly rang my neck!
Yes, and I think if someone
had corrupted my answer sheet
the way you and
Mr. Iwamoto did to that boy,
I would have
wrung your neck too.
But wait! I don't
know what you mean!
I'm sure that you know how
precious the Honor System
is at this Junior High,
so I'd appreciate it greatly
if you didn't lie to my face!
Now, you're going to
correct that score immediately!
Of course!
[OKUBO]
Kuwabara!
They're going to let me
keep my job for good!
Mr. Takenaka said that everyone
scored higher than fifty points!
You're kidding me!
Oh Kuwabara,
I didn't realize it till now
but I was really scared I'd
be living in the streets!
I'm so happy!
Then it was worth it.
I tried to stop him from hitting
that teacher as a reflex.
I didn't think
he'd hear me!
Kuwabara didn't really hear
what you said to him, you know.
Say what?
They can't hear words
unless they're asleep.
But you can communicate
feelings to living people
when you're on the
same emotional wavelength.
See. You reached
Kuwabara with your feelings.
Hey! Give me a break!
Everything's going fine and
then you have to get mushy!
You don't have
to be embarrassed.
Shut up will you! I think he
can hear us talking about him!
Don't worry Yusuke,
he definitely can't
see us or hear us,
though there's a good
chance he can feel you
after what you
went through together.
Thank you, man.
You talking to ghosts
again Kuwabara?
[KUWABARA] Uh?
No, just listening to the wind.
[KOENMA] Greetings,
everybody! It's Koenma.
You know,
ruler of the Spirit World!
Well Yusuke's about
to be in some real trouble!
Imagine a big fire
starting in your
house while you're
barely-alive body
is still sleeping inside, and
then you'll know what I mean!
Will these flames devour
Yusuke's hopes of revival
before his mysterious
Spirit Beast can hatch?
Keiko's running
in to save him,
but when the house caves in
she'll become a victim herself!
It's going to be hot, and
the finale will blow you away!
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪