♪
[NARRATOR] It is the Dark
Tournament's final round,
with Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi's team
facing the evil Team Toguro.
A catch in the rules
forced both sides to
appoint a fifth member.
Sakyo stepped in for his team,
certain the battle will
end before he has to fight.
Koenma entered
for Team Urameshi,
also hoping he won't be needed.
Now the final begins,
with Kurama claiming
the first fight.
[cheering crowd]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
with no further ado,
the first match begins!
And on my right--
fighting for Team Toguro--
Karasu!!
And at left, fighting for
Team Urameshi, is Kurama!!
Folks, I guess you
could say this tournament
has been one heck
of a roller coaster.
And finally...
finally we can get
to the most awesome loop-
de-loop part of the ride!!!
[crowd going crazy]
From the sound of things,
it seems everyone in
the stadium is a big fan
of the tall, dark,
and gruesome Karasu.
[KEIKO] What'd you
just say!?!
You couldn't pay me to root
for that vampire wannabe weirdo!
I don't know. He does
have some beautiful hair.
Don't forget your
stretches, Koenma sir!
This was supposed
to be Koenma's.
Guess I'll just
use it to scare people.
Kurama! Kurama!...
Damn it, if they start
a riot in the stands,
I'm not gonna be
the one that saves them.
[KUWABARA] Hey Kurama, wait!
You think you'll use
that medicine stuff
that Suzuki gave you?
Actually I took some
about two minutes ago.
Could you elaborate?
The bottle, Kurama, contains
the Fruit of the Previous Life,
handpicked from the upper
realms of the Spirit World.
Allow me the pleasure
of a few more words,
and I'll give you a warning.
This fight was the first time
those darling items were used.
I still can't tell
you exactly how they work
or what side effects they
could have upon their user.
I've run a few experiments,
and found it takes a
considerable amount of time
to absorb into my
body and change me.
I don't know if you should
take that multiple times, buddy!
It could be bad!
There is no way I
would have shown up here
without testing it first.
So, what's it
do when you take it!?
Suzuki was right in assuming
it would transform me.
However, there is a time
limit and I can only stay
in that form
for fifteen minutes.
I'm not worried, though.
Fifteen minutes
is more than enough.
If I could have
everyone's attention,
I'll explain the
rules of the match.
[DEMON FAN 1] Come on!
Let's see some blood!
[DEMON FAN 2] We already
know the rules! Come on!!!
You don't look so hot.
Are you feeling okay?
Oh, I'm feeling great!
In fact so great that
all I wanna do is smile!
You know, there should be a
law against feeling this great!
Well that's good to hear.
I'm sad Genkai isn't
feeling better, though.
I think Yusuke gets a
lot of support from her.
She's right, things have
seemed off concerning Genkai
ever since the end
of the semi-finals.
Well, uh, she did say
she was getting older,
and everyone knows that
the elderly need their rest!
Hey! Where are you going now?
The fight's starting.
Just need some
fresh air, that's all.
That girl, she's been acting
like a basket case for days.
I hope she's okay.
Oh hi, Shizuru.
You need to snap
outta this now.
She lived a long life
and was overdue for some rest.
But she can't have fun if
you keep tearing up about her.
You knew she was gone?
[SHIZURU] I could
sense her spirit moving
farther and farther away.
'Course I was sure of it
when I spoke to her yesterday.
She came by before
you took her away.
[SHIZURU]  Genkai
knew she was leaving
when she talked
to us in the woods.
But she made a molehill
out of a mountain,
because she didn't
want us to worry.
She wouldn't want
us to worry now.
She was ready to die.
[BOTAN] Why that way?
She was sad, and
scared, in so much pain.
I will never forgive him
for what he did to her!!
[Botan weeps]
Don't worry, our boys will take
care of Toguro once and for all.
And even if they don't...
You can bet I'll take on
every one of those lousy punks!
[crowd noise]
Both players take your
opening pose, and begin!!
[KARASU] You're either extremely
brave, or extremely foolish.
It's rare for anyone who
has seen my capabilities
to go through with fighting me.
I'm curious as to why you
would subject yourself to this.
Could it be something personal?
Don't flatter yourself, Karasu.
I'm here to defeat you,
and by the way...
I advise you not
to underestimate me.
Oh wow...
Kurama is surrounded by a
huge whirlwind of rose petals,
Karasu must stink!!
[KURAMA THINKS]
There is no doubt that while
I am in my human form
Karasu will dominate this
fight with his power and speed,
but when I transform
into Yoko Kurama,
I may have the strength
needed to beat him.
As for now, it is
imperative that I take my time
and be as careful as possible.
I must avoid
being touched by him
until my transformation
has taken place.
Petals and Thorns!
Karasu obviously doesn't
feel cause for concern
as he walks directly into the
massive cloud of rose petals!
It's incredible;
each of the petals
is as sharp as a razor blade.
[KARASU]
How utterly charming.
[KARASU] I must say Kurama,
they are absolutely beautiful,
however they are also weak
and lacking in substance...
...traits they must've
inherited from you.
[KURAMA THINKS] He's no fool.
Why won't he protect himself?
In a few more steps the
petals will engulf him,
cutting him to shreds.
What the heck? Those things
spontaneously combusted!!!
Be careful Kurama!!
[KURAMA THINKS] He doesn't
even have to touch the petals
to destroy them, he was right!
[Karasu laughs]
[KARASU]
Well, well, well,
perhaps it was I who
was underestimated by you.
My hands are not the
sole source of my power,
they are merely vessels.
Poor Kurama, it seems you've
entirely misunderstood me.
[KURAMA THINKS] Block him out!
[KARASU] You aren't able to see
my power so you feel secure.
But it's everywhere,
even in the air you breathe.
You can't escape it, it's all
around you, inside of you.
Why don't you make
things easier and submit.
What an attack!!
It's just the way I like it,
confidence with
a hint of malice!
Rose Whip!!!
[KARASU]
You know you can't stop me,
but you continue
to try all the same,
that's what's so
appealing about you.
[KARASU] It's a shame
that circumstances
couldn't have
been different for us.
[KARASU]
But it doesn't really matter.
Even things that seem
ideal always turn sour.
I'm just speeding the process!
Besides! I've found
that there's no greater rush
than taking the life
of someone you care for.
[KARASU]
The intimacy that murderer
and victim share
is unparalleled.
Witnessing their spirit separate
itself from their body.
[KURAMA THINKS] His attacks are
becoming more and more brutal.
If I don't transform soon,
I'll be destroyed.
[KARASU] Like I said, it isn't
necessary for me to touch you,
it's just one of the perks.
You okay?!
Darn it! What's the deal?
Why doesn't he change?
If that clown
gave him bad juice,
I'll make him regret
the day he was born!
Listen to yourself.
This is so boring.
If I were in the VIP room,
I could at least have a drink.
Karasu does likes
to hear himself talk,
but things are
about to get better.
[Karasu laughs]
[KARASU] Perhaps I should
explain how my power works.
It's similar to yours in
that we both manipulate things
with our energy, but with
one distinct difference.
You can only control things that
already exist, like your plants,
but I manifest my
thoughts into tangible things.
For example, the object
I'm holding in my hand.
Although you can't see it, it is
still very real and very deadly.
[KARASU] But honestly, I don't
think words can do it justice,
It's just one of those things
you have to feel for yourself.
[KARASU]
After all, like they say,
actions speak
louder than words.
Now make sure that you pay
very close attention, Kurama.
I wouldn't want you
to miss a single beat.
[KARASU]
Deleterious Bomb!
[YUSUKE]
Where is he?!!!
What a great explosion!
Karasu has just pelted Kurama
with several sticks of dynamite!
But tragically, I'm not
able to see the damage!
He got him.
[BOTAN THINKS] I've already
taken one person I love
to Spirit World.
Please don't
make me take another.
Anyone see?!
[KARASU] Very amusing.
[Juri whimpers]
[YUSUKE THINKS] Where's all
this energy coming from??
I've seen all this before!
This battle is in for
a heart-stopping facelift!
[YOKO KURAMA THINKS] Suichi is
fortunate I could come.
He wouldn't have survived
that blast, being what he is.
Well it's no
surprise I was right!
It's the foxy Yoko Kurama!!!
All right!!
This is gonna be sweet!
You telling me that's Kurama?
Basically, as you've heard,
his full name is Yoko Kurama,
but he's known by
several other titles, too.
You go King of Thieves!
You're my man!!
[DEMON FAN] The Spirit
Fox is back again!
Well, he was always a Legendary
Bandit in my generation.
[YOKO KURAMA] Creating a
bomb from nothing takes talent.
That caliber of
power is a sign you belong
to a superior class of demons.
A class I consider
to be fairly worthy.
[YOKO KURAMA] Worthy to fight,
and worthy to die.
[KARASU] You flatter me.
But we're still not equals.
Rest assured Karasu.
I wholly agree.
[YOKO KURAMA]
Now I see. You create monsters
that act as invisible bombs.
How very clever.
That's why I had such
difficulty fighting you
while I was trapped inside.
Lucky for me I found a way to
break free from Suichi Minamono
just long enough to finish you.
[KARASU] That's fascinating.
But nothing more
than a loser's excuse.
[KARASU] You weren't able
to beat me then,
and you won't
be able now.
[KARASU]
But you're welcome to try!
[Karasu chuckles]
[KARASU] When you come from the
Quest Class of demons you find
that you can create all
sorts of interesting things.
These little jewels are
what I like to call Trace-Eyes.
Once these bombs
set their sights on you
they will follow you forever.
Ever heard of Ojigi?
It's a rare plant found only
on Earth's South America.
The Ojigi is extremely
sensitive to movement,
and when it senses
any kind of vibration
it will quickly close
its leaves around its prey.
[KARASU] I have no
interest in gardening.
[KARASU] My, my, it looks
like you're surrounded.
What's a boy to do?
I thought you'd know better
than to corner an animal
like a fox, Karasu.
We have a tendency
to show our teeth.
[YOKO KURAMA] An Ojigi plant is
quite dangerous regularly.
And it is several times more
lethal and more sensitive
when grown under
a Demon's Energy.
You, unless you want to
be plant food, don't move.
'Kay!
It looks like
it's zeroed in on you.
I guess all your trembling
must've caught its attention.
Um, okay. The table's 180-ed,
and now Karasu's running around
like a cockroach in the middle
of a tap-dancing convention!
How does it feel
to be the one pursued?
[KOENMA] Oh yeah, this
one's in the bag.
Who cares if he's a part of
the whatever-you-call-it Class!
Yoko still kick his butt!
It's called the Quest Class.
I bet you don't remember
your own name half the time.
Get off me!!
Anyway, that Super Fox
Kurama's gonnna beat that idiot,
I just know!
[HIEI THINKS] I hope so.
That's what I
call entertainment.
You still want to watch from
the VIP room with your friends?
[NARRATOR] The match
between Kurama and Karasu
is fully under way.
Kurama's transformation
into his demon form
has given him the upper hand,
but Karasu will
not give in easily.
Will Kurama find
a way to triumph?
[KOENMA] Hello! It's the
mighty Koenma speaking!
It's been one heck of a
match between Kurama and Karasu.
Demon transformations,
invisible bombs,
and plants that make Venus
Fly Traps look like daffodils!
And that's just the start!
But don't get too relaxed,
because just when
you think Kurama's won,
Karasu comes
back with a vengeance,
pushing Kurama
back to his human form
and showing he can
change hair color, too!
Will the compassionate
side of Kurama
give his life for the team?
It's the next Yu Yu Hakusho,
and you won't wanna miss it!
♪