♪
[NARRATOR] In the first round
of the Dark Tournament,
the Urameshi Team is leading
Team Rokuyukai two to one,
and now it's up
to Yusuke to win.
But the drunken master Chu
is proving to be more
than a formidable match.
Threatened with a forceful
energy blast from his opponent,
Yusuke had no choice but to
resort to his Spirit Gun.
With both competitors drained
of their Spirit Energy
but not their desires to win,
there's just one way
to settle this fight.
[crowd cheers]
[KOTO] Ladies and Gentlemen!
That was incredible!
That was amazing!
That was... That was...
I honestly don't know
what that was, but wow!
You just blew all your Spirit
Power there, didn't ya mate?
Now you're as weak
as any other human!
I'm right!
Maybe...
But so are you.
That's probably true, drongo.
Then we'll have
to settle this fight
like a couple of Mallee Bulls.
I've got the balls...
Let's do this with a
Knife Edge Deathmatch!
A Knife Edge... Deathmatch?
Did he say Knife
Edge Deathmatch?
This should be bloody.
[KOENMA] I don't like
the sound of that.
A Knife Edge Deathmatch, huh?
What is that, per se?
I may have gotten into
more than my fair share
of street fights in my time
but I've never even heard
of anything like that before.
[KUWABARA] But if
I had to guess, I'd say...
It involves a match to
the death with those knives.
Shizuru...
What on Earth is happening now?
Well, they're gonna keep on
going at it until it's all over.
But they'll kill
each other, Shizuru,
why can't they just stop
fighting and call it a draw?
Haven't they shed enough
of each other's blood yet?!
Haven't they?!
[SHIZURU] Look, Keiko?
They're men.
So they'll never be satisfied
until they know which
one wields a bigger knife.
[KOTO] Let me take this
opportunity to remind everyone
that no weapon is off limits.
That includes swords,
axes, small rodents.
But what is Chu planning
to do with those two knives?
How odd that Chu
has stabbed his knife
into the ground
instead of into Yusuke!
I say it's odd because
the last time that I checked,
the ground doesn't bleed
nearly as much as a person!
Take off your shoes and put
your foot in front of the knife.
Oh, now what is
he making Yusuke do?
The edge of that knife is
the edge of your world.
That's the only rule of
a Knife Edge Deathmatch.
You don't step
outside that line.
If you do, it's sudden
death... and I mean death.
And we fight using
our bodies--no weapons.
The winner is the
last bloke standing...
Do you think that
you can handle that?
No sweat.
Excuse me sirs,
but it's really not up to you
to make the rules around here.
We have a reputable
tournament committee
that gets paid to do that.
Shut up, lady!
[KEIKO THINKS] They really
want to see him dead.
Man I sure hope
they let 'em do it!
Chu kicks ass at the Deathmatch!
He's never lost one
of those before!
Hey, hold it.
Does no weapons mean
that Urameshi ain't
allowed to use his Spirit Gun?
It wouldn't matter.
His Spirit Power's all gone.
Oh, yeah. That sucks.
Take solace. Chu has also
exhausted his Spirit Power.
Now that the fight has been
reduced to hand-to-hand
it will be the one with the
strongest head that prevails.
There's no chance.
Urameshi, show that lush
what you've got left in ya!
[crowd getting restless]
[KOTO THINKS] C'mon guys,
make a decision already...
But not that one.
The tournament committee
must be out of its mind.
What should I do?
Oh. Nothing. Is your gang...
Have your esteemed colleagues
arrived at their
destination yet, Toguro?
[TOGURO 2] I have no
idea, Mr. Sakyo
[KOTO] Everybody
please remain calm!
I promise, you'll see people
torn limb from limb soon enough,
if you just keep the peace!
Wow! It looks
like the committee
is repealing
their initial decision
and is now considering
letting the Knife Edge
Deathmatch into play!
This latest development
is quite ominous!
The storm clouds are clashing,
just as these fierce
opponents are destined to do!
And when their
awesome bodies collide,
there's no telling
who'll be struck down first!
[restless crowd]
Please remain calm people,
just a moment longer!
I promise--just another minute,
I'm sure the committee
will make a decision!
Just another minute!
Wait for it!
[KOTO] Just a little longer!
Yes! Ladies and Gentlemen!
Get ready for supreme brutality!
[KOENMA] I can't say
that I'm a big fan
of this sort of fighting.
I almost don't even
want to watch it.
We're ahead by one. So even
if Yusuke loses this match
our team still
has one more chance
to win the round with
that mystery fighter.
[KOENMA] Don't succumb to
foolish optimism, Ogre.
It doesn't suit you.
I would prefer not to entrust
my entire team's fate
in that fifth man's hands.
There's just something
about him physically
that doesn't quite measure up.
This is extremely impressive.
Both men are
giving it their all
without taking a
single step backwards.
It's taking a step
forward that'll be hard.
Hit him, Chu!
Hold it!
There's absolutely
nobody beyond this point
without a security pass.
[GUARD 2] Don't take
another step!
Please Karasu...
You've got a long while
until it's your time to fight.
[KARASU] I heard
there was a fighter
that might actually
be worth my time.
[TOGURO 2]
You mean Urameshi?
[KARASU] I wanted to see
what all the fuss was about.
That's him fighting
down there now.
So I've been
watching.
And? What do
you think?
Chu! Chu! Chu! Chu!
Could the battle possibly
get any more brutal than this?
Let's just hope
that it can people!
Whoa. Are you watchin' this?
I've never seen anything
so impressive in my life!
To them, it's like
nothing else exists.
Such focus and such pain!
I wish that were me in there!
This is no longer just
a fight between two guys.
This is the stuff
legends are made of.
I could watch them
fight for hours.
I can't watch
them fight anymore.
Keiko...
If Yusuke goes on like
this he'll wind up dead.
Not like he hasn't
been there done that.
What was that?!
Nothing at all!
[KEIKO]
I need to be alone!
[SHIZURU]
Keiko, come back!
Keiko, I'm sorry!
[SHIZURU]
Where are you running to?
Great.
[SHIZURU] If you
would have just kept that
cigarette in your mouth...
Then you wouldn't have
to put your foot in it.
[DEMON]
It's a human!
Excuse me Miss this
is no place for a lady.
[PURPLE DEMON]
After her!
[PURPLE DEMON] Come on, lady!
We just want to serenade you!
[SAKYO]
Hurry.
[SHIZURU]
Where are you taking me?
[SAKYO]
Come on!
Let me guess... human?
Yes, but remember
that down here,
we're in the minority,
so be careful.
[CHU] How's that for ya?
Hey Keiko!
Kuwabara... You have to
make Yusuke stop fighting.
No way, why would I
want to do that? Hey!
[KEIKO] Because if
you don't stop him,
Yusuke's going to die... again!
Sorry Keiko, but
it's not an option.
Why... not?
[KUWABARA] Because
Urameshi made a promise...
And now everything he lives for
is hanging on
his ability to fight.
Not too long ago,
we faced off against
a very strong fighter.
His attacks still haunt me, and
I think they haunt Urameshi too.
This guy was insanely muscular
and completely unstoppable!
[KEIKO] And that's
who he's fighting now?
[KUWABARA] No. Chu's tough,
but not that tough.
He's nothin' compared
to that other guy.
[KEIKO] So... then
we shouldn't worry?
[KUWABARA] I wouldn't say that.
Urameshi could definitely
still get killed by Chu.
Besides, winning this fight
is only his first step
in taking on that guy again.
[KEIKO] What?!
I'm not really supposed
to talk about this stuff,
but an honest to
goodness rematch
with Toguro is the only
reason we came here to fight.
Oh, but, but why?
It sounds like you don't even
have a chance at beating him!
[KUWABARA]
Well, Keiko, let's just say,
we don't have a choice.
So, who won in the first fight?
Well, Urameshi
and I worked together
and knocked Toguro down--
put a sword through his stomach.
We left him for dead,
but it turns out he
faked getting beat
for some kind of payoff.
Then the guy shows up again
and forces us to
fight him here for real.
Urameshi has to
fight Toguro again.
And more than that, he wants to.
You see Keiko it's our
only chance to settle this.
Then and only then, we'll
know who's stronger than who.
And that is why I
owe it to Urameshi
not to step in there
now and save his life!
Really.
They're so evenly matched.
It must end in a stalemate,
or it might never end at all!
No, I am certain they are both
standing on their last legs.
It is almost all over.
The weaker one
will crumble soon.
[RINKU THINKS] Boy, I wish
everybody on that team
put up this much of a fight.
I might've actually gotten to
give my yo-yos a real workout.
[CHU THINKS] This one's gonna
be bloody rotten on my hangover!
Yeah! No one stands up to
Chu's trademark head butt!
[KOTO]
One!
Two!
Three!
Yeah! That was the most
exciting finish I've ever seen!
I told you the one
with the strongest head
would triumph, Hiei!
And, I had faith
in Urameshi all along!
[KOTO]
Seven!
I guess you're better
suited for tapping kegs
than tapping heads, mate.
Nine...
Ten!
The winner of this match...
and the winner of the
battle is Team Urameshi,
led by Yusuke Urameshi!
[crowd goes wild]
[KUWABARA] That was incredible,
Urameshi! Hey man!
How are you holding up?
Eh.
[KUWABARA] Yes!
We can't be beat!
[KOENMA]
That was awful!
But sir, our team won
the match in the end.
Whether we win or lose,
I get tired just watching.
I think I need to lie
down and take a nap.
I don't believe it.
If I'd bet on that gutter trash
I'd be eating my
shirt right about now.
[SAKYO] I'm tired of your lies.
I expect you
gone upon my return.
[RINKU]
Chu!
Oh boy... Look what
Yusuke did to you!
Your skull cracked the
cement! But he's so small.
He should try to teach that
big blue oaf how to fight.
[CHU]
Urameshi.
We agreed to fight a death
match, mate... Finish me off.
Nah, we'll fight
again when your better.
You're ripper.
[CHU] It's been a dead
set honor, Urameshi
Likewise, pal.
[crowd boos]
Demon fans are so stupid.
A while ago, they were
cheering for them to win.
Hey! If you want a piece of us,
why don't you come
down here and take it?
Finish him off Urameshi!
We want some blood!
Shut up!
[crowd quietens]
[YUSUKE] If you idiots got
something to say...
Say it! But say it to my face!
Or else say it to my fist!
Yusuke Urameshi.
[CHU THINKS] Good on ya.
Urameshi's blood is
worth bottling.
[TOGURO 2] You never answered
my question, Karasu.
Is he worth your time?
We'll be facing off
against him soon.
[KARASU] Only if he
keeps on winning.
Toguro!
[NARRATOR] Yusuke may
be flippant now,
but things are about
to get very serious
for his team with the
Toguro Brothers looming over.
And who is the mysterious
Karasu by their side?
[YUSUKE] Well, I made
it through that fight
more or less intact, but,
I have a feeling things are
about to start getting tough.
We seriously gotta find
some new powers quick,
cause some of us aren't
blessed with a brother
who can morph into
an entire arsenal.
That's right, Toguro.
You're not so tough
without your sibling armory.
Crap.
Okay, so maybe you are.
Anyway, you won't want to miss
the next bone-shattering
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho.
Because it's Toguro's
turn to step into the ring,
and it's gonna be
a real gut-buster!
♪