♪
[NARRATOR] Yusuke Urameshi's
Spirit Detective team
has entered a notorious
demon competition--
the Dark Tournament.
Kuwabara took the first
fight against Rinku,
child member of
the Rokuyukai Team.
And though Kuwabara
brandished new moves,
he has been overwhelmed
by the boy's strange attack.
The Serpent Yo-Yo.
Can he survive?
How do you like this one?
It's my take on
Around the World!
Now take your
time with him, Rinku!
No, hit him Harder!
Give us breaking bones!
[KOTO]
What a glorious fight!
The opponent is helpless!
It's hard to counter-attack when
you can't even move!
I love it!
You see,
I told you that Kuwabara's
training wouldn't be enough.
We'd best assume him dead
and plan for the next fight.
No, there are still some
techniques he hasn't tried.
I'm gonna get you!
You'll be screaming mommy!
You're like fighting a brick--
How many times do I
have to throw you around?
Hey! I know exactly what to do!
And I won't even have to work!
Wait! Uh, what are you doing?!
[KUWABARA]
I'm gonna get you!!!
Well, at least
baby brother
is getting a good view
of the stadium, right?
How can you joke right now?
Don't you know what'll
happen if he falls?
That's easy.
He'll die.
Shizuru! You should
be ashamed of yourself
provoking her like that!
Keiko is worried because
your brother's life
happens to be hanging
by a literal thread!
And us getting upset will
make a heck of a difference,
won't it?
[KUWABARA]
Stop it you brat!!
Just enjoy yourself! You'll
be coming on down soon enough!
I don't like what I
think he means by that!!
Yusuke!!
[KEIKO] Yusuke!
Yusuke?! How can
you keep sleeping
when your friend is in trouble
with these nasty demons!
Help him Yusuke! Get off
your lazy butt and help him!
[KOENMA] Whew! That girl
has some real guts
to be screaming for
the human underdog
in a crowd
chock-full of demons!
Yeah, kind of like
sitting on the wrong side
at an Ogre's
Football game.
She's liable to get hurt.
Yo! Ogre! Go help them!
Me? Are you crazy?
I'm just a scrawny little guy.
You're the boss!
You should help!
Me? Don't make me laugh!
Yes, well true progress
is achieved through
adversity, after all.
They'll be just fine.
I would of course like to help,
but when is Botan going to
learn to handle things herself?
Don't get any closer, Keiko!
We're not on safe grounds!
Maybe Shizuru's
right and worrying
won't make a difference...
But I still have to try!
[demon thug laughs]
What's the matter,
little girl? You lost?
Go on to your filthy home...
This here tournament
is for apparitions only.
You can't scare
me with that talk!
I know Yusuke's beaten creatures
a lot bigger than you!
Your boy's asleep.  Too bad you
can't protect yourself.
Thanks a lot!
So, I see where
Kuwabara got the need
to defend himself growing up.
Yeah.
You know it's really
hard to take this serious!
When a little kid,
with yo-yos is the
one who's gonna finish me!
[KEIKO] What's the matter
with you, Yusuke!
Your friend needs you
now! Think about that!!
Hang tight, Kuwabara! I don't
suppose you can fly, can you?
[KUWABARA] Uh?
Oh, hey Botan! Oh--Sis?
I didn't know you were here!
I'd give a better greeting,
but I'm kinda busy right now!
[KOTO] Rinku seems
to be hesitating!
Why don't we ask
the fans what they want!!
[DEMON FAN 3] Finish him, kid!
We've seen enough!!
[DEMON FAN 4]
Make him splatter!!
[DEMON FAN 5] Let him drop!
We'll watch him fall!
[CROWD] Yeah! Let him drop!
[RINKU] Say,
guess that settles it.
Gotta' give my fans what they
want. And they want a drop!!!
This is it, people!
Get ready for a boom!!
You just made
your big mistake, Rinku!
You should have never
let me use my hands!!!
Spirit Sword get long!!
Kuwabara makes a
sensational recovery!
It's time for the nitty-gritty!!
So the sword absorbs your fall
like a backwards
bungee cord, huh?
That's a pretty neat-o
idea from a blockhead!
There's one
little problem, though!
You flying straight at me
just makes it easier for all
my yo-yos to hit you at once!
And you can't handle that!
My only chance for a hit!!
Not that dummy sword
again! I dodge that easy!
[RINKU] Say what?!
His sword can bend now?
Clever.
Get the hell out of
the way Rinku!
[KUWABARA] We're going
together, you freak!
He really hit--
That's right. I hit you.
So who's
the winner?
Beats me.
Right, well both fighters
have been extraordinarily
knocked outside the ring!
At the very same time!!
Was that the focus
of your training?
Well, more
or less.
The main focus
of our training
was to teach him precise
control of his Spirit Sword.
[KOTO] By the rules,
you're only allowed to stay
out of the ring for ten seconds.
So, um, I'm just
going to start counting.
I'd be surprised
if either of them
got back on their feet in time.
It's true. Both the yo-yo
and the sword made solid hits.
I guess we'll know soon enough.
Get up!
You're late,
Kuwabara!
And Five!
[DEMON FAN 6] Look!
Rinku's back!
[DEMON FAN 7] Of course!
The human can't win!
Damn it! I didn't think
he could throw such a blow!
I'll have to use a lot of
my energy just to recover!
Rinku has entered the
ring after five counts,
but it's not over yet!
That's okay. He's down for good.
I'll have my time to heal.
Get up there Kuwabara!
I'm serious! I know you're
used to losing, but not now!
Six!
What'd you say?!
Six, Kuwabara! You have four
counts to get in the ring!
Not you--Urameshi!
Out of my way! Little bum, you
want to say that to my face?!
Come on!
Oh! You're pretending to
sleep now? You scaredy cat!!
[KOTO]
Seven!
And an eight!
Hey! Hold your
horses! I'm coming!
Oh man, I can't take
any more of him right now!
Hey! HEY!!!
Nine counts!!
Let go of me, stupid yo-yo
strings! That's cheating!!!
[KOTO]
Ten!!
Come on.
And Rinku's the winner! The
Rokuyukai Team gets a point!
[KUWABARA] No, no,
no, no, no!
Hold it, jerks!
That wasn't a
fair move! Let's go!
Whoa-you run on
batteries or something?
I beat you--just please go away!
That was fairly innocent.
It's rare to see both
fighters still standing.
I assure you it
won't happen with me.
This isn't over, kid!
Meet me behind the hotel
when the tournament's done!
[RINKU]
Go away!
What is he talking about?
Junior High
boy stuff.
[RINKU]
'Scuse me!
Used so much power and
didn't even get the kill.
[ROTO] He forgets what makes
this tournament dark.
[KOTO] Ooh! The next competitor
has already stepped up!
Please, I'll handle this one.
[ROTO THINKS] I can
tell this will be exciting.
Kurama.
Considering the stakes we can't
afford to take any chances.
Don't leave the ring
with him still alive.
Naturally.
[YUSUKE] I don't know
if you want to fight him.
Be careful Kurama.
What is he talking about?
Yes, it's simply
time I stepped in!
Um, are you sure
you can do that?
We will deal with the rest
of their team. You relax.
Hey, I'm not out of this yet!
If Yusuke doesn't wake up,
I'll take the last guy.
We'll pray that
that doesn't happen.
[BOTAN] Alright boys
I'm here!
Now let's whip
this team into shape!
Hey--How'd you get here?
[HIEI] Leave, before
you hurt yourself.
Well that's a
jolly thing to say
to someone who's
going to help you win,
don't you think?
You mean you're like
the replacement fighter
for Urameshi?
No, silly.
Tada!!!
In addition to
Detective's Assistant
and Pilot of the River Styx,
I'm also a licensed trainer!
I'll be looking
after you all
and making sure you stay
in tip-top shape for fighting!
Oh great! Then
maybe you can help me
nurse this wound here see I--
[BOTAN] Spirit World to Yusuke!
Wake up! Come on, now!
None of that will work.
The boy is determined.
[BOTAN] Well--at least I'll
get him out of the way!
You know, that Rose Whip
he's got must be ten feet long!
Where's he stash it?
All the ways I can think
of sound kinda painful.
Kurama simply
carries a normal rose.
By manipulating it
with his Spirit Energy
it's transformed
into a whip.
Even weeds can turn into
a deadly weapon for Kurama.
Second fight--Roto
versus Kurama--begin!
I know you've been spending
years in the Human World.
We all do what he must.
I only hope you didn't--say--
get attached to one of them.
This red-haired boy. I don't
think he's really human.
That's funny--
why'd you say that?
For example, be
mournful of their death.
What is your point?
He's clearly no
match for Kurama.
What a joke of a round.
It's a pity you
couldn't have taken him
and let Kurama deal
with the little child
and his yo-yos.
Hey you watch it, shrimpy!
I just got cheated is all!
He can't even
hit the bastard!
But Gondawara.
I thought with the
support of those dirty fans
a team could beat anyone.
Maybe even
upset my Toguro.
I hope you didn't wager too
much of your money on that.
Your skills weren't
enough for this tournament.
Say your last words.
I have your human mother,
Kurama. Or should I say--Suichi!
What happened?
He's bleeding--
you said no match!
Stupid cheater.
I hate him.
Little Stupid.
You sure you're asleep?
Allow me to introduce
my little button.
When I press it, a signal will
be sent to my demon brother.
He's been tracking your
mother for some time, you see.
And he's very anxious
to bite her head off.
So you understand.
[ROTO] No fighting back!
Oh honestly,
do you think throwing
a pebble at my face
is the best thing to
do in this situation?
You've been warned!
With a push of this button
your mother will meet her death
in a very unsightly manner!
Now fold your
arms behind your back
and let me hit you as I please!
Oh yes! That's much better!
I love the posture
of forced submission.
Why train hard to be the best
when you can hold one of these?
Mysterious!
Kurama has become totally
obedient to his opponent!
What's wrong Kurama?!
Let him have it!!
Quiet.
Yeah, that's beautiful! Roto
has somehow hypnotized him!
Who gives a damn! When do we get
to hear the bones break!
Gee, that's so lame! Roto always
uses that dirty trick of his!
Yes, and he always wins.
That's the goal, remember?
I guess so.
You want to try. I can
see it in your pretty eyes!!
I know what you're thinking-
what if I can quickly
cut off that left arm of his?
But what if his severed finger
still presses the button?!
What is that crude doing now?
Just finish the fight!
This is not for
his personal amusement.
Fortunes are on the line!
A loss would make
it two to zero!
Yes Ogre, I know.
Kurama remains
absolutely motionless!
What is the cause? Has he
lost his willingness to fight?
Why don't
you answer her?
Tell the crowd the truth.
Tell them you refuse to fight
for the sake of a human tramp!
It's brutal! It's violent!
It's wonderful!
Roto is punching him
like a side of meat
and there's no retaliation!
Dammit!
I hate that look!
Despite all I've done
you still have that look
like you're superior to me!
[ROTO]
Stop... that... look!
It doesn't matter anyway.
Because I am the
one with power now.
I would like you to lick
the scum off of my boot.
I just can't seem
to keep it clean.
And after you've wiped
the whole thing clean.
I will decapitate you and
spare your nasty mother's life.
And since you
care about her, Suichi,
it's really your only choice!
I will not.
What??
Go ahead, press
it now if you wish.
In the end your
true character emerges.
You're nothing special!
Nothing high class!
Just a selfish demon
like all the rest of us here!
[ROTO] Look at me like I'm dirt!
But in the end it's a lie!
You think only of yourself!
[KURAMA]
Push it!
I will!
I can't move!
Fighting on the strength of one
threat is a very risky gamble.
What if I truly didn't care?
Or what if I could
just make you immobile?
[KOTO] It's hard to tell
what's happening now!
But it's clear
Kurama has control!
[KURAMA] I've sown the seed of
the Death Plant in your body.
And it's had plenty
of time to take root.
[ROTO THINKS]
The pebble!
It was a distraction,
so I wouldn't notice the seed!
I feed it with my energy.
I have but to will it,
and it will instantly bloom.
I'm afraid there
won't be anything left
of your evil life after that.
Wait Kurama!
You don't have to do this!
I never would've actually
pushed the button! I swear it!
[ROTO] I'm just a low-class!
I don't know any better!
Come on! You believe
in mercy, don't you?
No.
What irony.
Such beauty, sprung
from such an ugly soil.
[KOTO] Well, that one's
definitely over!
The score is tied at one!
[HIEI]
What a fool.
So intent on proving himself
he couldn't notice your moves.
Don't worry
about his demon friend.
He vanished the
moment Roto died.
Then you knew.
What a relief.
Yes.
Okay, enough secret-glancing
stuff! What just happened!
Yes! Do tell!
It's passed.
Agreed.
That isn't very
friendly of them!
Those demons think
they're so darn cool!
[NARRATOR] And so
concludes the first two matches
of the Rokuyukai
and Urameshi Team battle.
The score is even at one.
What will happen next?
[YUSUKE]
I swear!
Doesn't anyone appreciate
that a guy's gotta sleep!
The next fight is coming,
and it's gonna
be an ego contest
fit for a high
school locker room!
Zeru, the team leader,
gets angry with waiting and
steps into the ring himself.
And that means
fire balls to the roof!
But Hiei's ready
with the Jagan eye open,
and he's drawing on a dark,
dragon energy
never unleashed before!
Explosions are
pretty much guaranteed!
So don't miss the next exciting
episode of Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪