♪
[NARRATOR] Kurama is now
in the throes of battle
with Team Toguro's Karasu.
With this being
the first match
in the Dark
Tournament's finals,
Kurama is determined to win
by whatever means necessary.
The mystical potion he received
has taken effect
just in time,
barely saving him
from Karasu's deadly bomb
and transforming
him into Yoko Kurama.
Will this be enough,
or will the legendary demon
have to give up his life?
[crowd gasps]
The Ojigi is truly
gifted species of plant.
It can sense the smallest
amount of movement.
Even something as
insignificant as a muscle spasm.
So you see, it's useless to run,
it would only make you
easier to catch.
Oh wow, folks! Things are
really starting to heat up.
It's dinner time and
Karasu's the catch of the day!
This is it!!
He's plant food!
Kick his ass, Kurama!!
It must be hard for
you to lose control.
The Ojigi also
responds to aggression,
so it will be all the
more vicious once you attack.
You're going
to have to come up
with a smart way to
kill it, or else, bang.
I thought it was going to
last much longer than that.
I would've liked to have
toyed with him a little
before he died.
That was the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
Kurama's plant
just grabbed Karasu
and juiced him
like a fresh orange,
I never would've thought botany
could be so
deliciously gruesome!
Kurama sure showed
that punk what was up!
And he closed the deal
in a measly five minutes!
Eat that, Toguro!
Yes! Two more
wins and it's done.
Holy Toledo, I didn't
know Kurama could do that.
Remind me never
to make that guy mad.
Oh Koenma, sir!
Koenma, sir, look up!
[KOENMA]
What?!
I'm sorry sir, but
your face is leaking!
[KOENMA] Crap...
This is always so embarrassing.
I can't believe it,
Kurama won.
Don't get me wrong,
I love my bro,
but it's nice to see
someone not embarrass himself.
Hey Juri, get the lead out!
It's time to
tell us who's won!
Oh, right!!
Um, it looks like Karasu's
been soundly defeated
and the winner of the first
match is Team Urameshi's Kurama!
Hey,
stay back!
[KARASU] I wouldn't
count me out just yet.
Oh I'm so, so sorry,
that was entirely my fault.
Everyone, forget
what I just said!
The fight will
now continue, okay!
This is insane!
I don't know how much
more of this I can take.
You look surprised Yoko.
Did you think that was
the last you'd see of me?
Karasu has lost
his dear old mask.
Indeed he did.
Take a few steps back Sakyo.
Things are about
to get hazardous.
Brace yourself people,
Karasu's back
and he's not too happy!
His hair has also changed from
jet black to hyper-glow blonde.
To follow the stereotype,
that means he's popular
and more aggressive!
Can someone fill me in here,
what's going on with his hair?
It's an explicit sign that
he's internalizing his power,
which means the bombs he
creates are now inside of him,
virtually making
him one giant explosive.
Are you serious!
Of course I am.
If my assumptions are correct,
he's about to detonate.
If you're wise
you'll take cover now.
I think you should know
Karasu has no loyalties,
he'll kill everyone in this
stadium if he thinks it'll help.
[Karasu laughs insanely]
Hey, is everyone alright?!
[KOENMA] That idiot
almost killed me.
I should have him arrested.
You guys
hear singing?
Where's Kurama?!
Now that's devastation!
A significant
portion of the ring
has been completely wiped out,
there are corpses everywhere,
and Kurama's
nowhere to be seen!!
[Karasu chuckles]
Oh wow! That Kurama
is like a nasty virus!
You just can't get rid of him!
However, it does look like
this last explosion
has taken its toll,
because now he's back
in his original human form!
Ah, crap!
The potion wore off.
Now he's really
gonna have to wing it!
I don't get it!
He said that stuff's supposed
to last fifteen minutes!
That's it, the next
time I see Suzuki,
I'm moppin' the
floor with his face!
[KURAMA THINKS]
I don't understand,
I was sure that the
potion lasted longer.
For some reason it's
effects are weakening
every time I use it!
Forgive me for disturbing
your train of thought, but,
shouldn't you take
this time to pray?
After all, you are
about to meet your creator.
[KARASU] You can ask him
why he flawed with you.
[Karasu laughs]
You're too weak Kurama,
you can't even control the
most basic of your attacks.
Make this easier on
both of us and give in.
I promise it
won't hurt too much.
Kurama!!
[KOTO] Wow fight fans,
the suspense is in the air
here at the Dark Tournament,
because everybody knows that
one more solid attack by Karasu
means curtains
for you-know-who!
If you think about it, death
really isn't so frightening.
Who knows, you might
actually enjoy it.
Aw man! Kurama's launching a
full blown assault on Karasu,
but so far it's
completely useless!
Blondie's dodging each punch.
I can't take it anymore,
I need to see some blood!!!
He has a plan. It's obvious
in the way that he moves.
I think you've
finally lost your mind.
If you come any closer,
you are a dead man.
I will not be afraid of
something that I cannot see!
[KARASU] You're just
full of surprises,
but I thought
you'd be more original.
You really thought
this would work?
[KARASU]
It's called tact, Kurama,
you should consider using some.
That stupid jerk is really
starting to piss me off!
He knows what Kurama's
gonna do before he does it!
[KOENMA] Guys, I don't
think he's gonna make it.
I must congratulate
you though.
You've injured
me more than once
and that is
practically unheard of.
Time to say bombs away!!
That's what I
call, my mad bomb.
Out of luck,
now your...
No Kurama!
[Karasu chuckles]
Don't move another inch Kurama!
You're surrounded by bombs!
Didn't you say you chose
not to be afraid of things
you could not see?
Well here's a
better look.
You know that
this entire battle
has been an
exercise in futility.
[KARASU]
You're weak,
you're tired,
you're powerless,
you're pathetic.
Yet it seems you
have a masochistic streak
that wants indulging.
So, here goes.
I can't watch
him suffer like this!
Karasu is such a bastard.
He's clearly playing
with him now.
I wish he would
just get this over with.
I don't ever want to hear
you talk like that again.
Kurama will beat him!
Kurama can't die,
he just can't!
I've lost one person
I love to Toguro's Team,
I won't lose another!
Is he done yet?
Probably not, he deeply
enjoys the suffering of others.
Well, I suppose the two of us
have more in
common than I thought.
Your red hair is perfect for
that fiery spirit that I admire.
You know that's
why I've decided
to leave your
beautiful face unharmed.
I may not be able to keep you,
but I'll always have the memory
of your face to give comfort.
[[KURAMA THINKS] You couldn't
have been more wrong
about my so-called
lack of tact, Karasu.
Just as wrong as
believing that mark on your
chest is only a
harmless scratch.
[KURAMA THINKS] The smell of
the wound so close to your heart
will be more than enough
for a bloodthirsty plant.
[[KURAMA THINKS]
You may not think I posses
the ability to summon a plant.
But you will soon find out that
you are wrong there as well.
I can summon once more,
in exchange for my life!
Alright, let's end this.
No!!!
Yes!! Let 'em
have it, Karasu!!
Do it already!
Finish him, finish him!
The crowd is going
wild here and rightly so!
Kurama's down and I don't
think he's getting back up!
Just do it.
We don't have all day!
Gimme that you big oaf!
Juri, count!!
Please for the love
of good hygiene, count!!
Okay!!!
He has until
the count of ten!
If he stays down,
Karasu wins.
One!
[JURI]
Two, Three, Four,
Five, Six, Seven!
[KURAMA THINKS] I cannot
hesitate. I barely have
enough Life Energy left.
I must destroy him now!
You should have stayed down, but
I guess that's not your style.
Now.
[KURAMA THINKS]
I may die, but at least
it will end in a draw!!!
It can't be...
Where did he find
the strength to do this?
[crowd gasps]
His life!
It's fading!!
Oh Kurama
please get up!
He isn't moving,
do you think he's dead?
Of course he's not!
He can't be!
Accept it Botan. He sacrificed
himself to kill Karasu.
Please wake up!!
[KURAMA THINKS] I'm alive.
[KURAMA THINKS] I don't
understand, how did I make it?
I gave all of
my Life Energy.
Of course!
Each time I take the potion,
the duration of
its effects shorten.
They shorten because every time
I transform into Yoko Kurama,
I retain some of his power.
That's how I survived.
And that's how
we win this, yeah!
He's a little jacked up,
but I'd say he won!
Um, hold on.
[NARRATOR] Kurama's willingness
to sacrifice himself for his
team has allowed him to
escape with his life.
After the first
fight of the final round,
Kurama is standing and
Karasu is laid to waste.
But what important message
is Juri waiting to tell?
[KUWABARA] Kuwabara's
got the mike!
And match two of the
finals is about to start,
once Juri says her
thing and shocks us all.
Hiei's gonna face off against
the freaky quiet man Bui.
I think it's a bad idea
since he's like half the size
of that axe, but when's
tiny-boy ever listened to me??
It's gonna be brute
strength mixed with surprises.
We'll hear Bui's voice
for the very first time,
and see what he looks
like under that armor!
But of course,
Hiei's got a little
surprise removal of his own!
♪