♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi has made the
last step towards defeating
the Four Saint Beasts:
with the help of his team,
he has climbed to the
highest tower of Maze Castle,
and faces Suzaku,
the mastermind behind the plan
to flood the Earth with demons.
But Yusuke's time is short.
Using the Makai Whistle,
Suzaku has
sent an army of
insect-infected
humans after Keiko.
Their orders: to kill.
[YUSUKE] Out of this whole plan,
you made one big mistake.
[YUSUKE] You went
and pissed me off.
Take this!!
His power's increasing!
The whistle!!
It's mine!!
Almost.
You really want this
whistle badly, don't you?
She must mean a lot to you.
[YUSUKE] That's none
of your business!!
I'm sorry,
were you saying something?
You seemed to trail off
when you saw her in danger.
You humans are so transparent
with your feelings.
Meet a female,
and then you love her.
Take her away,
and you get mad.
[SUZAKU]
Though I must admit,
your desire to save her
is making it very difficult
for me to fight with one hand.
Let me hold the whistle now.
Then you can use both hands.
Have wisdom Murugu.
If you hold the whistle
he'll take it from you.
Yusuke here will be requiring a
somewhat more drastic approach.
[SUZAKU] I have two
favorite techniques.
You've already met
my Storm of Torment.
[SUZAKU] Allow me
to introduce the other.
Nice posture.
[Keiko screams]
Take my hand!
[BOTAN]
Now run!!
[IWAMOTO] There's
no way to escape.
We're coming to get you Ukimura.
You have been a very bad girl.
Do you know what happens
when you hit a teacher?
Well, we better think quickly.
Yusuke.
[Suzaku laughs]
Man, I've really got to
get my eyes checked out.
This is the most advanced
ability I have learned
while waiting in this castle.
So can you guess-
Which one of--
These seven forms here--
Is the actual Suzaku?
Bet you can't.
Bet you can't..
Bet you can't...
We all are.
Black secret technique--
The Prism of Seven!!
What a technique!!
[BLUE OGRE] Yusuke's had enough
trouble with one Suzaku!
How's he gonna fight seven?
Hiei, Kurama, Kuwabara.
Yusuke needs your help.
We gotta find some
way to get to Urameshi!!
Yes Kuwabara, I have a strong
sense that he needs our help.
[KUWABARA] I hope you
guys are behind me!!
[SUZAKU] It's really a
magnificent technique.
You see, these aren't
just copies, or shadows.
Each one of us has
our own freedom of will.
Which makes for a
very destructive
combination
of attacks.
[Suzakus laugh]
Prism Storm of Torment!!
[Yusuke screams]
Genuinely, Yusuke,
I applaud your ability to dodge
five out of my six attacks.
But I only need one
hit so I could finish you
and take care of your friends.
[SUZAKU] As you
die, don't be sad.
Ever since you
stepped into my tower
you've been living
on borrowed time.
[Yusuke laughs]
[YUSUKE] That shows, you
don't know me very well.
My whole life has
been borrowed time.
[YUSUKE] Now give
me the stupid whistle.
Get down!
[SUZAKU] Is it possible you care
that much for this girl?
Well, then I'll just have
to stay and watch her die.
[MURUGU] Yes! She's going
to die! She's going to die!
[Murugu laughs]
[SUZAKU]
Pick him up.
[Suzaku laughs]
Can't you drop these
human feelings, Yusuke?
I will make you a king of demons
if you promise
to eat Keiko's heart.
Go,,, to Hell!
[SUZAKU]
I don't like that answer.
What do you think,
my dear Suzakus?
Can we reform this boy's
rebellious attitude?
[Yusuke cries out]
We'll give you just
enough so you won't pass out.
Floating in a constant
state of pain.
Then you can watch every
last minute of Keiko's life.
[SUZAKU] And look Yusuke.
It's getting very exciting.
The final scene, I believe.
Can't you hear the
dramatic music swelling?
♪ Bam-bam,bam-bam-bam-bam ♪
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Kind of sends of a shock
of terror down your spine.
Yours is a unique position.
Don't you agree?
On the one hand
you're the audience
watching a distant
tragedy on the screen.
But on the other hand
you are its very cause.
Yusuke.
[SUZAKU] The door has been
opened, the killer comes in.
The heroine crawls
into the corner
and screams her last breath.
Life is a drag, isn't it?
Keiko!! Botan!!
[IWAMOTO] Ukimura, I always
knew you weren't as smart
as you made us think.
[IWAMOTO]
Hid yourself well, didn't you?
Except for one thing.
Your scarf.
[Iwamoto laughs]
[IWAMOTO] I warned you
to stay away from Urameshi.
But it's too late.
You're damaged.
And now we throw you out!
KEIKO!!!
[Suzaku laughs]
Your girlfriend has
become a pincushion!
[SUZAKU] Well, there's no point
in being sentimental.
Come now Yusuke.
It's time for you to join her.
I know, Suzaku! Have him
die with one giant zap!
That's fine.
But let's make it slow.
[Yusuke screams in pain]
[KOENMA] Yusuke is dying.
The boy may be the Spirit
Detective of all the Earth,
but he's still a human.
Guess it was pretty wrong of us
to think he could
fight a Saint Beast.
We're going to
have to move on sir,
and think about the larger
problem back on Earth,
now that the Makai
Insects won't be stopped.
[BLUE OGRE]
With the whistle still intact,
the numbers of infected
will keep growing.
Soon, cities will start falling.
There's no point rubbing
in what I already know, okay!
I'm just waiting for
a solution to hit me.
It's just, well Koenma sir.
We just might have to give
in to Suzaku's demands.
Are you nuts?!
Well if we remove the barrier
wall from around the city.
Maybe the demons there will make
some kind of treaty with us.
My dad's gonna kill me!
We'll never get up there.
Hold on! I'm comin' Urameshi!
Sword get longer!!!
Here I go!!!
I nearly made it.
[KURAMA] Kuwabara.
What are you doing?
[HIEI] We've cleared
a path to the entrance.
Quit fooling around.
[mindless groans]
They never end!
Let's, not waste
more time.
[Yusuke screaming]
[SUZAKU] Your friends
are drawing closer.
I'll have to speed up your
torturing to deal with them.
[GENKAI VO] Hello! Moron!
You can't give up like this!!
[YUSUKE THINKS]
But, Keiko.
[GENKAI VO] Oh give the girl
some credit. She's not dead.
Dammit?!
[SUZAKU] Must I
do everything myself?!
That girl will die, no matter
how long I have to wait!
[Yusuke laughs]
You! You think this is funny?!
Then let me teach
you some manners.
[SUZAKU] It's rude for
the dying to laugh!
[Yusuke screams]
[GENKAI VO] Don't you remember
one speck of your training!
[YUSUKE THINKS] Get out
of my head you old bitch!!
I can't think right now!!
[GENKAI VO] That's your whole
problem you idiot!! Remember!!
Focus your mind on
the business at hand!
You give up on everything
because you can't
commit to anything.
Let me guess,
did you pick up that cute
saying from a fortune cookie?
I am trying okay! But you're
working me to death here!!
Approaching death is
the key to your training.
What?!
It is called training
under critical condition.
You must push your body all
the way to its breaking point.
Only then will you reach
beyond your physical limits.
[GENKAI VO] Power like this
must be earned, slacker.
I know that's a
new concept for you.
All your life you've
gone the easy way.
So you were born with a talent
for fighting. Who cares.
You never worked for it.
It was easy.
You've always quit any time
the answer wasn't served
on a silver plate.
Shut up, shut, UP!!!
I don't have to listen to you!!
Look at all the
energy you still have!
Shows you're doing your
training like everything else.
Half-assed!!
You people are all alike!
Tryin' to take control
of me and tell me how I am!
You're wrong!!
Yes, kill me to
avoid your problem.
It's time you bit the bullet
and started caring
about something
with all your heart and energy.
But you can't care about it
if you're always
holding yourself back
in case it doesn't work out!
Concentrate on what's
important, Yusuke.
Then commit to it all the way.
Okay... but what's important?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I've come all this way,
but what's the big deal?
Goodbye, Yusuke.
[YUSUKE THINKS]
I mean, what's it gotten me?
Why do I care?
[YUSUKE THINKS]
Because, they need me.
[SUZAKU] Be sure to
hold him tightly.
[MURUGU] Wait, wait, Suzaku!
Let me get a better view!
This is for my
friends you jerk!!
[Yusuke cries out]
Did I miss something
or did you just get
five times more powerful?
Life is a drag, isn't it?
[NARRATOR] His friends.
His mother. Keiko.
Remembering all the
people who count on him,
Yusuke has risen again with
powers never before seen.
As the tower battle
races to its end,
the Spirit Detective will give
every ounce of strength he has.
But will that be enough?
[YUSUKE] That's right.
I'm back on my feet and ready
to bury this Saint Beast
in what's ever left of
his own stupid castle.
But even though I've got
bigger, badder powers
and a whole new
reason to fight,
it's still seven against one!
And that's not easy!
Kuwabara and the others
are cutting their way through
veggie-heads to get to me,
while Keiko's got to do
all the zombie running
when Botan gets knocked out!
It's the grand finale of our
mission against the Beasts,
and I'm giving it my all!
Next time, on Yu Yu Hakusho!
♪