♪
[NARRATOR] Spirit Detective
Yusuke Urameshi
has been kidnapped, forcing
his friends to look for him
in the House of
Four Dimensions.
Hiei scoffed at the human
kidnapper's weakness,
but soon learned
the bizarre truth.
They have entered a world of
the kidnapper's own creation,
where violence is not allowed,
and speaking the wrong
word costs you your soul.
To survive the house,
they must play by the rules.
[KOENMA] They can't
say the word hot.
You better believe it, Ogre.
[KOENMA] There aren't any prizes
for being stubborn
or skeptical today.
Because of the
house, sir?
[KOENMA] Because
of the Territories those
weirdo teens can make.
Unless the rest of our
gang wants to end up
with a captured
soul like Hiei,
they better follow every
strange rule to a T.
I don't know where these
kidnappers got their powers...
But they're pretty smart
to have pushed us this far.
We should watch
them closely, sir.
[KIDO] I heard you
were headstrong.
The nicer way to
say you're stupid.
Shut up.
Well, why you've been
fighting here for no reason,
one of your friends has
decided to stay with us.
You're full of crap.
[Kido chuckles]
No, you'll see what
I mean soon enough.
I'm tired of this. We're
still allowed to talk, right?
We just can't say the
h-you-know-what word.
That's nothin' tough.
So, Kurama...
You said you had
school with this dork.
What other stuff do
you know about him?
Yuu Kaitou, my classmate,
as we've said.
He has garnered much
attention at my school
in light of his I.Q. results.
His intellect is ranked
at the genius level,
with some of his
scores the highest
since the school's inception.
Well that's a roundabout way
of bragging, isn't it Suichi?
If I'm such a prince,
you must be the king,
since you always
beat me on tests.
Cumulatively, yes,
my grades are superior.
But in certain subjects, such
as language and literature,
you far surpass me.
You've even published essays
on literary theory.
So, he's a young
genius writer, huh?
I bet we're cooler than anything
you've read in a book!
[KAITOU]
Not really.
It's so obvious
what you're trying!
Making us sweat
out in this room
so we'll say
your magic word,
I mean, it must be
a hundred degrees!
[KAITOU] Eighty, actually,
with eighty percent humidity.
I keep my room like this so I
can raise my tropical plants.
My tribute to Suichi.
But if the conditions
are making you thirsty,
I have plenty of drinks in the
fridge, I even have glasses.
[Laughing]
What are you chuckling
at, book worm?
Did you poison 'em
or something?
Maybe you should
drink one first.
Waste all my talent
to poison you?
That's brilliant.
You know, you're a
very intelligent guy!
And you bark a lot
for a weenie dog.
Hold up, Kuwabara.
Why don't you let me get that.
I, uh, want to keep
my hands full.
Okay, looks harmless enough,
and quite a selection.
Let's see...
O. J.? It's better
for you than a soda.
That's fine, just
pour it over ice.
And we can share
with each other,
as long as we
use two straws.
Your confidence in my
health is charming.
That can't be!
Good, victim two.
[Kaito laughs]
But why?
You're cheating, Kaito!
He never came close
to saying hot!
I goofed!
That's three.
[KAITOU] I can't believe
that was so easy.
[KOENMA] Well, we obviously
didn't assemble this team
for brain puzzles and academic
decathlons, but what went wrong?
Botan blew it, but
what about Kuwabara??
Ogre, did you hear him say hot??
No.
Let's check the replay.
Here we go.
O. J.? It's better
for you than a soda.
That's fine, just
pour it over ice.
And we can share
with each other,
as long as we
use two straws.
Your confidence in my
health is charming.
I don't get it.
Where's hot?
That's fine, just
pour it over ice.
And we can share
with each other, as...
Share with each other...
Each other. H, O, T...
E-a-c, h-o-t.
It spells hot!
I think my brain just broke.
Forgive me for not
explaining the specifics.
I didn't think your
friends could handle it.
In my Territory, you can't say
the letters h, o and t in a row,
even if they are parts
of different words.
It's no simple child's game.
It's a puzzle of diction,
and I can't bend the rules.
That's fair enough.
Souls are so pretty,
I like the girl's best.
Souls are the only thing you
can't make stronger by training.
[KAITOU] You can only
make them darker.
What do you say, Suichi?
Should I darken mine right now,
by breaking these?
It feels so strange having
this power over people.
[KAITOU] You must
feel it all the time.
Yes. Maybe I'll just
make a little scratch.
I'm warning you.
You so much as bruise
what's in your hand
and I'll show you pain.
The hue of your soul will
cease to matter because you
will not be judged
when you die.
You will no longer exist.
Interesting, you'll
have to show me
to talk like that
once I beat you.
How long can you afford
this brazen façade?
What the? How did
you get that key?
Yana!
He's bluffing you, man.
I got it here in my pocket.
It's gone!
But he never even
came in the hall!
I was not stopped since
I refrained from violence.
With gentle discreetness
I merely borrowed the key
from your coat pocket.
Seems we can use our
powers in your Territory,
as long as we follow the rules.
So you picked my pockets
with some greenery?
You are a first class freak!
Keep those souls in
perfect condition, Kaitou,
you've found yourself
in over your head.
[thunder]
[KAITOU] You can't intimidate
me. I still have the upper hand.
You have to beat
me at my game.
[KURAMA] Tell me, is it possible
to change your taboo?
Naturally, neither one
of us will say the word.
Thus we're locked
in a stalemate.
And I was hoping we could
increase the challenge.
Of course, Suichi, I've been
planning that all along.
I don't want to beat
my great adversary
with a simple word gag!
I want a true battle of wits!
I can change the rules
whenever I please!
Then let me
determine the rules
of the word game
and I assure you,
I will force you to speak the
taboo within forty-five minutes
and thereby free
my friend's souls.
Oh? You're that confident
you can outwit me?
All right, and what
if you cannot get me
to break the rules in
forty-five minutes?
Then you may have
my soul as well.
Oh my...
So, you in?
Or will you cower from a game
in which you clearly
have the advantage?
[KAITOU THINKS] Brilliant,
arrogant Suichi,
I have more advantage
than you think.
Since I found my power,
I've obsessed over every
word puzzle in print.
You can't beat me.
Yet here you are,
strolling into my trap
like it's your idea.
[KAITOU]
I accept your challenge.
So, let's hear the taboo
that ended Suichi's life.
It starts as one letter.
But as time moves forward,
we eliminate more.
There are twenty-six
letters in the alphabet
and forty-five minutes to play.
Thus, every one hundred
and four seconds,
we will lose another
letter we can say,
starting from the end,
at Z, and moving backwards.
[KAITOU] Yes, and
at the end of the game,
every letter will be taboo!
[Kaitou chuckles]
Fascinating imagination,
this game will be fun.
Let's see...
It's fifty minutes
after midnight.
Why don't we start
it neatly at one.
Sounds perfect.
[KAITOU] Follow the rule,
both host and guest.
Don't utter a letter
crossed off from the list.
Each hundred and four
seconds, note too...
Another letter becomes taboo.
We begin.
Better get any z words out
of you before they're taboo.
Zealous zebras, and
crazy zinc Zippers.
The next will be
more a challenge.
We'll forfeit the letter y...
Why, oh why, do we
lose the letter y?
What if we need to cry?
I find this game very
enjoyable, don't you?
Be careful, Kaito. You'll tire
yourself and make a mistake.
At last a challenge.
It's rather remarkable...
So much I use
those last letters.
Losing s t and u should
be a greater obstacle.
When people say I
can't do something,
it makes me want to do it
even more... It's like walking
by a fire alarm and
not being able to pull it!
Sir, calm down...
[KOENMA]
I CAN'T TAKE IT!!!
Zi, za, zoxy wax!
Double-u!
Vittle tips vee wy
wowy voodoo!!!
Is this one of your
baby talk days, sir?
A challenging mindgame,
Minamono.
Ready for conceding?
[KURAMA]
No.
Inform me...
A plan cooking here?
Running clock...
Forbidding more of freedom.
Going off?
Need a john.
No lip...
I'll be back.
[YANAGISAWA THINKS] Right.
I'm in his Territory, too.
I shouldn't even risk a laugh.
[toilet flush]
[KAITOU THINKS] What is
that genius brain up to?
He knows I won't slip on my own.
But he sits,
letting the clock run,
knowing if neither
us speaks, he'll lose!
He must be
waiting for the end,
when no one can speak,
to commit some heinous trick.
I'll watch him carefully.
[body hitting floor]
[KAITOU THINKS] But, no
violence is allowed.
The plants. Maybe they lifted
him gently to the ceiling,
then gently let go.
Has he moved
on alone?
No, he couldn't have.
The layout of the house
wouldn't have allowed it.
There are three doors
between here and the next room.
I have the second key,
and we hid the third.
Besides, Suichi told
me how protective
he was of his friend's souls.
He wouldn't have
left them behind.
Unless, unless
he found a way
to take them with him!
[KAITOU THINKS] Bastard!
How could he do
this so quickly?
[KAITOU THINKS] What?
Everything's still here.
He wouldn't have abandoned them.
Which means he's still
somewhere in the room.
Yes, waiting to
finish the game.
This is how it
should be, adversary.
Your world against mine.
[Noises]
[KAITOU THINKS]
Where the hell is he?
It's one thirty.
Two thirds of the letters
are restricted now.
That doesn't leave
many combinations.
The vast majority of words or
sounds will break the rules.
I just have to
keep from speaking.
Yes. I'll just stand
here and not say a word.
I know that's your
plan, Suichi.
You want to scare me
into screaming a taboo.
But, as long as I
stand in the center,
you can't sneak up on me.
I'll hear you in the brush.
[KAITOU THINKS]
A few more minutes.
Only a, b
and c are left.
You can't sneak up on me.
You won't make me scream.
Only a and b now.
Just don't say a word!
[KAITOU THINKS] I'm really going
to beat him. Once and for all!
Baaa!!!
[KAITOU THINKS]
No. Don't scream.
If you scream you could
make the wrong sound!
Control it!
Control! YEAH!!
Time's almost up!
[KAITOU THINKS] I did it! I beat
you, Suichi Minamono!!!
Ha ha ha!
Oh, he he he!
[KAITOU] No!!!!
All right!
I'm back in the flesh!
Kaito's Territory is no more.
[KUWABARA] Yeah. Out-tricked at
his own crazy game of pretend.
He got it in the end.
But man, we'd be toasted
without you, Kurama.
And no thanks to you, Hiei!
Getting us in trouble
with your I'm so tough act.
It's true he nearly had us...
Ironic after all
his grave intentions,
the one thing to
unravel him was a laugh.
Kurama! That face!
What is going on down there?
You invited three jerks
into your living room
who don't know how to lose.
What did you expect,
they'd obey you politely?
They're coming up here,
and they're gonna bust me out.
And then I'm gonna
kick your ass.
[NARRATOR] The kidnappers have
suffered a serious blow,
as Kurama's wit has
disembodied Kaitou's soul,
and evaporated his Territory.
But the House of Four
Dimensions has many rooms,
and two strangely powered
teens remain eager to strike.
[YUSUKE] Damn it! Just when
I'm getting nice and cocky,
these puzzle-pushers have to
throw another curve,
complete with twisted
staircases, floor traps,
and doors that go nowhere.
I'll finally get free
of Kido's hold on me,
but there's another challenge.
One of my teammates
is an imposter,
and I've got one killer
punch to figure it out.
But that's not all.
Want to know who the evil
mastermind is behind all this?
The truth will make you sick...
Next time on Yu Yu Hakusho.
♪