[NARRATOR]
It's been nearly a year since
Yusuke, Hiei, and Kurama
arrived in Demon World.
And they have each
become firmly enmeshed
in its tense power struggle.
Hiei impressed Mukuro with
his fighting rage so much
that he's become her
second-in-command.
Kurama rejoined his former
partner in crime, Yomi,
who likewise, asked Kurama to
join his cause as top advisor.
Meanwhile, Yusuke has
continued to train to
fulfill his vow to kill
his ancestral father,
the third ruler of
Demon World, Raizen.
Now, the three former teammates
are in high positions
on conflicting sides,
as they head towards
an inevitable clash.
[RAIZEN groaning]
[knuckles crack]
[groaning continues]
[RAIZEN groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
[YUSUKE]
Hm.
[grunts]
[ALL grunt]
[growls]
[NANKAI yells]
[yells]
[gasp, groans]
[gasps, groans]
[gasps, growls]
[yells]
[NANKAI groans]
[TOUOU groans]
[SEITE groans]
[HOKUSHIN groans]
[HOKUSHIN gasps]
Bang!
That was quite a surprise
move you pulled there, master.
[TOUOU]
It's difficult to fathom
you're the same boy
who showed up a year ago.
[SEITEI]
In another year...
[NANKAI]
...twice as strong.
Hokushin, you gotta stop
going all rubbery-necked
every time someone
throws a punch at ya, man.
I mean, with your head
so far from your body,
you leave everything from
the neck down open to attack.
You are one of the few
who has discovered that
vulnerability of mine, heh.
Even you never discovered
that about me, Seitei.
[YUSUKE]
Sorry to kick ass and run, guys,
but it's time for me to
beat the old bastard!
[SEITEI]
But... don't you recall?
He nearly killed you when
you fought a month ago.
[YUSUKE]
Yeah, but that was last month!
[HOKUSHIN]
That boy is relentless.
Like his father.
That's odd...
What is?
The king's... stomach
growl is off schedule.
Oh, no.
I'm back!
Hm?
[RAIZEN groaning]
Bad timing, huh?
[growls]
[gasps]
[growls, yells]
[yelling]
[yells]
[GROUP gasp]
What... was that energy?
[HOKUSHIN]
King Raizen...
[RAIZEN]
I can't take it anymore!
I must feed!
[yells]
[RAIZEN growling]
[YUSUKE] Man, this
hunger thing's starting to
move from his stomach,
and take a toll on his brain.
[RAIZEN growling]
[bones cracking]
--[RAIZEN growling]
--[YUSUKE grunting]
[BOTH growling]
[YUSUKE] I can't believe
we're this evenly matched,
even when he's running on empty.
He must be using every last
ounce of energy he has.
Where did you go?
[RAIZEN growling]
[YUSUKE screams]
[YUSUKE grunts]
[RAIZEN panting]
Man...
You're pathetic.
[YUSUKE]
If this is you at your weakest,
I can't imagine
you at your peak.
You know, I think you've
proved your point by now.
Whatever...
...it was.
If you need to eat humans
to survive, so be it.
I'll bring some for you--
some real evil ones.
The world is mixed up.
Things I was clear on
just confuse me now...
But if what you do is wrong,
then why were you made that way?
[YUSUKE] I don't want
another hollow victory.
I don't want another
star in my "win" column
like I had with Sensui!
Well, if you won't
feed yourself,
will you at least tell me why
the hell you're doing this,
so I can start telling you why
what you're doing
is totally wrong?!
I can see a lot of her in you.
[RAIZEN]
She was much wiser, of course.
But...
It was with her fiery temper
that I fell in love.
[RAIZEN] It's been nearly
seven hundred years now.
The Living World was a
very different place.
Chaos and disorder reigned,
and people everywhere
lived in constant fear.
This was before
the first barrier
between the Demon
and Living Worlds,
and our two kinds
lived side by side.
It was a grand time
to be a Demon,
though I imagine it was a
bit rougher for the humans.
We terrorized them, and yet
their feudal lords were not
above calling upon us
to defend their lands
from the invading horde
of their own enemies.
[RAIZEN] I didn't care
which side a person was on.
They were all food to me.
They didn't like that very much.
[RAIZEN]
But all that changed one night
when I met a woman
of the Living World.
[RAIZEN]
From a distance,
she was just like the rest
of them--pale and weak.
Yet there was something
different about her, special.
Her eyes and the way
they looked at me...
I could see my downfall in
those eyes, but I didn't care.
I was in love.
[WOMAN]
Who are you?
[gasps]
A Demon...
That answers that.
Then I'll just ask...
why you've come here tonight.
[growls]
You look pathetic.
[RAIZEN growls]
You're injured...
Show me where it
hurts, so I can help.
[gasps]
[RAIZEN]
She was a gifted healer.
A medicine woman.
[YUSUKE]
You mean, like a doctor?
[yells]
[RAIZEN]
Not exactly.
This was before modern medicine.
They would ingest deadly
poisons and contagions,
turning their own
blood into vaccines.
Their primitive techniques
were quite effective,
and my wounds healed quickly.
[WOMAN]
What do you want?
Are you hungry?
[gasps]
[RAIZEN]
So naive, I thought.
She had left herself
totally vulnerable.
And I could have killed
her at any moment.
I was contemplating how I
could devour her, when...
[WOMAN] Well, are you
going to eat me or not?
Allow me...
I have toxins coursing
through my veins.
One bite, and your insides
will be corroded by dawn.
Just act now, whatever you
decide; I don't like to wait.
[WOMAN]
Even a savage beast like you
can't handle what's
inside this body of mine.
But if you don't believe me,
come on, try, at your own peril.
[RAIZEN]
I couldn't move.
I was mesmerized by this defiant
woman standing before me.
[chuckles] I guess
you're not monster enough.
[WOMAN] You could...
always just kill me.
Come on...
You can at least do
that much, can't you?
Of course, once my
blood's been spilt,
do you honestly believe you can
resist taking one
taste of my poison?
So, what'd you do?
We made love.
Huh?
[laughs]
I had no other choice.
What could I do?
I told you before;
it was her eyes.
Not to mention, she was
the most beautiful creature
I'd ever laid mine on.
Then a few dozen
generations later,
I just rolled down the tube?
Yes, it was something like that.
How I loved her...
It was one magnificent night.
I can still feel the touch
of her skin against mine,
as our bodies melded
in perfect harmony.
Or how her fingers felt,
stroking through my hair.
Or the warm feeling of being
held in her tight embrace
through the night...
But in the morning, I realized
I wasn't worthy of her.
She had devoted her
life to saving people,
while mine had been
spent destroying them.
So I left, and I vowed never
to eat another human being
until I saw her again.
[RAIZEN] But I was
never to see her again.
[RAIZEN] She died soon
after, in childbirth.
We, the Mazoku,
lead very long lives.
I'd hoped that the time
would allow me to find her
in some reincarnated form.
That hope was the only
thing that kept me going.
But I should've known better.
She was far too enlightened
to return to this world.
[RAIZEN] And so, I haven't
eaten a human since that day.
In fact it has brought
me closer to her,
if only in that it has brought
me closer to mortality.
And who knows, maybe when
my time has come to an end,
the two of us can
finally be together...
...in the next world.
[RAIZEN]
Yusuke, my son...
Have you ever been in love?
Yeah, I guess.
Really?
Then you understand why
I made my sacrifice.
[RAIZEN] There's more
that you need to know
about the situation
here in Demon World
that I haven't told you yet.
[RAIZEN]
The relationships are complex.
In the past,
I fought with Mukuro and Yomi
merely for the sake of fighting.
But things have changed.
You could get along with Mukuro.
He's a traditionalist,
an isolationist who
likes Demon World just
as it is--divided.
Mukuro won't bother with
the Living or Spirit Worlds.
But beware of Yomi.
He speaks of unification,
but it's a front
for moving his army.
He'll take over
Living and Spirit World.
Side with Mukuro.
I don't get it. Why are you
telling me all this now?
Because this is
your inheritance...
...and your duty.
Shut up! You can't die yet.
It's not your time to go!
[RAIZEN sighs]
Lead them well, son.
[gasps]
Urameshi?!
[SEITEI]
Where's our king?
[TOUOU] What was that
explosion all about?
[HOKUSHIN] Master Urameshi,
where is King Raizen?
He's dead.
[gasps]
[GUARDS murmuring]
[GUARD 1]
The king is dead!
[GUARD 2]
Long live the king!
[YUSUKE] Hokushin, I need
you to take me somewhere.
Where, Your Majesty?
The house of Yomi.
[GUARDS gasping]
[YOMI] Raizen's stomach has
ceased its incessant rumbling.
What do you make of it, Kurama?
[KURAMA]
Two possibilities.
First, he couldn't bear
it anymore and gave in,
satiating his hunger
by eating a human.
Or second, he suffers no longer.
Meaning...
Meaning he's... dead.
[KURAMA] But so much earlier
than we anticipated?
I think it's far too soon for us
to come to that
conclusion just yet.
We'll wait.
Whatever you suggest, Kurama.
That's why I made
you my top advisor.
I am positive...
Raizen is dead.
[MUKURO] Through no one's
fault but his own.
A fool, he died a fool's death.
What will you do now?
[MUKURO] As promised, we'll
strike Yomi with our full force.
The edge of Gandara,
the land of Yomi.
Thanks for the escort.
Be careful on your
way back home.
What?! I can't go back.
By now, Yomi is surely
aware of our king's death.
And as his offspring,
you'll be in danger as soon
as you set foot in Gandara.
Well, duh! Why do you think
I wanna go in there alone?
As the heir to the throne,
you no longer
represent only yourself.
And I've sworn to protect
my land's new king.
Fine, you can tag along...
But let me talk, okay?
We wanna be as diplomatic
as we can on this.
Perfect time to
say that, my king.
And why's that?
We should be careful with
what we say from here on.
When Yomi lost his sight, he
strengthened his other senses.
It has been said many times that
Lord Yomi is capable of hearing
every word uttered
within his domain.
Really, is that so?
[inhales]
Yomi! You son of a bitch!
[YUSUKE]
You hear me?!
I'm comin', so boil
up a kettle of tea!
Think he heard that?
Quite diplomatic, sir.
[HOKUSHIN] By the way, Your
Highness, what is in your bag?
In this?
[HOKUSHIN]
Yes.
Somehow, I have a
bad feeling about it.
[YUSUKE]
You worry too much!
[HOKUSHIN]
Wait! Sir!
[YOMI laughing]
Kurama,
this friend of yours
seems rather... silly.
Can he really be the
descendant of Raizen?
Yusuke has wasted no time.
He's gone to meet Yomi.
[MUKURO] And what do you
think the boy has in mind?
Knowing Yusuke, not very much.
He rarely thinks before he acts,
and yet, he always seems
to get the result he wants.
Most of the time, I don't
understand the things he does.
But I've seen the humiliation
of those who underestimate him
far too often for
me to doubt him.
[MUKURO]
Hmm...
You speak more fondly of him.
What's that mean?
[MUKURO] Sounds to me like you
might even call him a friend.
[HIEI]
Hmph.
[MUKURO] If the time comes,
will you fight against him?
[HIEI] I have never backed
down from any fight in my life,
including any brawl with Yusuke.
I may have let him go
the last time we fought,
but I have no reason
to do that this time,
and I eagerly await the
opportunity to beat him.
[MUKURO] I don't find
your words convincing.
Your insecurity is annoying me.
[MUKURO] And if it comes to your
old ally versus your new one,
which side will you choose?
The same side I'm always on...
the only side that
matters to me--my own.
If it's you versus him,
I'll let you two fight,
and battle whoever survives.
[MUKURO]
Interesting.
I can feel it in your voice.
Something about what
you've just said is a lie.
I just can't tell what.
[MUKURO] I have to admit,
he makes me a little jealous.
I'm sure you never pegged
me for the jealous type.
But we'll see soon enough
where your loyalties truly lie.
[MUKURO]
Change the course!
We're heading to Gandara!
Warriors, prepare for battle!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR] Raizen's death has
upset the balance of powers
in Demon World.
Now, it is up to Yusuke
to prevent total upheaval.
But what does he have
planned for his meeting?
Yomi and Kurama...
Mukuro and Hiei...
they will all once
again cross paths,
in the battle for
control of Demon World.
[thunder claps]
[YUSUKE] Yeah, it sucks that
the old man kicked the bucket,
but it sucks even more that
he stuck me with all
this responsibility.
I mean, now I've gotta
single-handedly
save Demon World!
Of course, the funny thing
about the this place is,
you never know when you're gonna
run into some old friends...
or some oddly creepy ones.
Or every once in a while,
a beautiful new friend...
with an oddly creepy one.
So, how am I gonna
get outta this mess?
Well, you'll just have to watch
the next episode of
Yu Yu Hakusho to find out!