♪
[NARRATOR] Toguro, a powerful
fighter believed to be dead,
has appeared
with a firm command
for the Spirit Detective.
Yusuke must fight in an
upcoming tournament of demons,
or else risk the lives
of everyone he cares for.
Knowing the road will be tough,
Yusuke has spent
months training
with the psychic Genkai.
Now the competition
day has arrived,
and Yusuke's team
awaits the unknown.
[NARRATOR]
The Dark Tournament.
It is the fiercest
fighting competition
on either side of reality.
Organized by human businessmen
who make their fortune
in the underbelly
of the black market,
and muscled by the most
notoriously cutthroat demons
Spirit World has to offer.
[NARRATOR] Each
millionaire assembles a
team of five fighters, and the
teams fight to the death.
[NARRATOR]
Sometimes, a special team
is invited to the
tournament as guests,
made of fighters who
have earned a reputation
for causing trouble.
Participation is
not a choice for them.
This year,
one such team exists.
Yusuke, Kuwabara,
Kurama, Hiei,
and the mysterious
masked fighter
are this year's
special guests.
[NARRATOR] And so it begins.
[demon laughs and murmurs]
Shoot, nothin'
here but ugly monsters.
I thought cruises were
supposed to have pretty girls.
[KUWABARA THINKS]
Urameshi said this fighter guy's
supposed to be tough.
But he's bite-sized!
[KUWABARA THINKS] I bet
he'll jump overboard
once he sees my
new sword power!
I sure hope the island
isn't as boring as this.
We're not on
vacation, you know.
I know, but
couldn't they at least
just give us a place to eat?
With pretty waitresses?
[CAPTAIN] Alrighty maties.
Turn your eyes to
the captain's deck.
It's still going
to be quite a time
before the ship finds
her way to the harbor.
So we'll be having
some entertainment
to keep you from getting rowdy.
Ooh!! I knew it!
Some dinner and dancing!
The preliminary battles
of the tournament
will be fought here
on me trusty ship!
Say what?
A preliminary
for the competition.
Now that we can't go anywhere.
Earthquake!
Fool. There can't be
earthquakes on the water.
Look!
Whoa! That thing's huge!!
[CAPTAIN] She's a real
beauty, ain't she?
[DEMON 1] Perfect!
[DEMON 2] Yes--I've been waiting
for a fight all day!
Now I'll tell
it to you straight.
Fifteen teams have already been
chosen for the Dark Tournament.
They're awaiting your arrival.
That means, out
of all you on my ship
only one team will
compete on dry land.
Hold on, I thought that
we were the special guests!
This is the way they operate.
[CAPTAIN] All teams pick
out your strongest man
and bring him to
the arena's portside.
There they'll fight
in a Battle Royale,
and whoever comes out alive
gets their team a ticket
to fight on Hanging-Neck Island.
So, one big beat-down, huh?
Guess I'll have to show them the
brand new Kuwabara super attack!
Yes I do prefer
larger battles.
One-on-one always
makes me bored.
An excellent chance
to sharpen my claws.
Now I can kill me as many
apparitions as I want to,
after I turn that human boy
Urameshi inside out, of course.
Uh--what did he
say about the human?
You know those
guys are pretty big
when you see 'em standing right
next to you and everything.
Hey! That's right! You're the
one who wants to fight them!
Well I guess as
the group leader
it is your responsibility.
Hey! Wake up Urameshi!
I said it's the group
leader's responsibility!!!
Why do I feel like
I'm screaming at myself!!!
[KURAMA]
Stop.
The training Yusuke went
through was apparently immense.
You must give him
time to recuperate.
Then who's gonna fight
with all the big monsters?!
It seems we have a volunteer.
[HIEI] Good. I'm anxious
to see what he can do.
Are you serious? We don't know
jack squat about that guy!
What if he loses and we get
booted from the tournament!
If that happens
all we have to do
kill everyone else on the
boat before we reach the island.
We'll say we're the right
team and no one will complain.
You didn't have too many
friends growing up, did you?
Alright Koenma sir,
who's this new fighter
they've got on their team now?
Beats me.
You can tell me sir!
I keep good secrets!
I honestly don't know.
But I thought you were the
official owner of team Urameshi!
Well yes, technically speaking.
And you don't know its members?
Nuh-uh, no one's even
bothered to tell me yet.
Wow, it's like no
one cares about you.
Like you don't even matter.
Oh shut up!
I'm the chief administrator
for all of Spirit World!
Of course I matter!
Why do they treat
me like such a baby!
Calm down sir.
We'll find out.
That's it! Where is Botan!
Why hasn't she given
me a report by now?
That girl is getting spankings!!
[BOTAN]
Easy now!
No need to get.. violent.
We know that you know Botan!
Tell us where Yusuke is!
And my baby brother, too.
He hasn't come home for days!
And neither of 'em
even gave us a phone call!
Yes, I-I understand
you're worried.
But boys will be boys!
Mine won't.
Now I want you to tell me
exactly where
Kuzuma and Yusuke are.
Please--for our friendship!
It's just, uh--
Now!
Yes, but--
Botan!
[BOTAN THINKS] Koenma's
gonna kill me, but so be it.
Okay, but promise not to faint.
Here goes.
So, they're fighting
in something called
a Dark Tournament?
Against teams of monsters from
an entirely different world?
That's right.
Okay.
Oh dear. Keiko!
That could've gone better.
I can't believe
they'd be so reckless.
But they had to.
Those in charge
won't let them refuse.
The only way for
them to live is to fight.
Now listen.
What?
You have to take me there.
Yes, I'm going too.
[BOTAN THINKS]
Koenma's gonna kill me.
Let's attack the one
from the human team first.
Then we'll start on each other.
Good idea.
Hey! We gotta do
something to warn him!
They're all gonna
gang up on him
and he's trapped
himself in a corner!
Patience.
Attack!!!
I get to keep his head!!!
Only if you get there first!
Holy crap!
He got everyone up
there with one blow!
I guess that explains why
Yusuke can sleep so peacefully
on a boat full of demons.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Whoever
that little guy is,
Yusuke must've
taught him the Shotgun!
I'm sorry to say
that the sixteenth team
will have to be a human one!
Yusuke Urameshi's team!
Good job little man!
So how bout you let us see
under those bandages now!
Hey! What's this?
You really think we care
about fighting by the rules!
There's only one way to find
the best team on this boat.
Wouldn't you know.
I think they stole my idea.
We'll have to make them
pay very dearly for that.
Of course.
Hey!
Now I'm mad!
What kind of wimp
do you take me for!
Rose Whip. Thorn-Wheel!
This kill will make me famous!
Urameshi!!
Now die!!
Come on! You can't
scare me, Grandma!
I'll knock you
back to your grave!
That's a relief.
He's finally awake.
[HIEI]
No, fool.
He's sleeping.
Right now?
Quit you stupid old lady!
Even in his slumber Yusuke
is reliving his training.
His preparations
should make us all jealous.
[KUWABARA THINKS] Hmm,
Urameshi said Grandma
in his sleep right there.
That's what he calls Genkai.
Hey! Maybe that guy's Genkai!
They are about the same size.
But she wouldn't fight unless
she had her own reasons.
What are you mumbling?
He's trying to talk in
his sleep when he's awake.
Oh hey, what happened to
the fight we were just in?
[KURAMA] Everyone's dead.
[CAPTAIN] Blast these
scurvy-ridden pests!
Old Sakyou was right!
They were far too
strong for these wimps!
I'll just have to
wait for the Tournament
to see them struck down!
So I take it that's
Hanging-Neck Island.
This is going to
be wild you guys!
Everybody make sure
not to leave me!
[KUWABARA] Are we
really staying here?
[music playing]
[KUWABARA]
Wow!
Well it's definitely
better than the pirate ship!
The best of the
evening, gentlemen.
The hotel has
been expecting you.
Please, follow me.
I got a bad feeling
'bout the people in here.
I never trust grown-ups
dressed that fancy.
For some reason, I thought
they'd be bigger.
Be nice to them Caroline,
they're about to be dead.
This is going to be a very
intriguing year.
I can't sit here
anymore! I'm going!
Forget this moronic paper work!
Where you
planning to go sir?
Where do you think?!
The tournament of course!
But you have to keep stamping
sir! It's very important work!
A trained monkey
could do this job.
Koenma sir!
You're irresponsible!
It's really a pity
you feel that way.
I was just about
to take you with me.
Ciao, Ogre.
Guess I'm going alone.
Wait Koenma sir!!!
[TOGURO 2] Urameshi's
team has checked in.
[SAKYOU] I've spoken with
the ship's captain.
The other apparitions onboard
were no match for them.
Were you really expecting
it any other way, Sakyou?
[SAKYOU] Their first true test
will come soon enough.
I've arranged for Urameshi's
team to fight Team Rokuyukai
in the very first
match tomorrow.
[TOGURO 2] Rokuyukai...
Well, that should
be interesting.
[KUWABARA]
I gotta hand it to them.
They sure know how to
make things pretty!
I haven't seen this much
rich stuff in my whole life!
[door opens]
[BELLHOP] Your evening
coffee, gentlemen.
Compliments of the hotel.
Careful, those fancy guys
might be trying to poison us.
Does that really
make sense Kuwabara?
Why would they bring us
all the way here to poison us?
The organizers
want to see us fight.
They'll save their murder
attempts for tomorrow.
You guys can talk
your logic all you want.
I'm sticking with
the trusty old aluminum.
[KURAMA] Why is there only one
coffee cup on the table?
[KUWABARA] That's the one I'm
not drinking, remember?
Duh, we had this conversation.
Yes, so there should be two.
One for you and one for Yusuke.
Wow, you think Urameshi
can drink in his sleep, too?
How did you get in here?
He--He must have been hiding in
the room before we even got in!
Fibber fibber! I came through
the door after you got here!
Isn't that what good
boys are supposed to do?
Oops, I guess I did
forgot to knock though!
So you guys are the guests
aren't you? You're so lucky!
Oh, my name's Rinku by the way.
I'm on the Rokuyukai team that
you're fighting tomorrow!
Is that so?
[RINKU]
I wish I was a guest.
They don't have to go to all
the boring opening ceremonies
or meetings about the rules!
You just show
up here and fight!
Guess you don't have to
learn about all the prizes
and final round stuff when
you're gonna be dead soon!
[KUWABARA THINKS]
What is this kid?
He talks about death
like it's a toy!
Somebody told me the guests
would be special
so I got excited.
But you don't
look special at all!
Maybe I'll even
beat you no-hands!
[ZERU] Don't you think
you're talking too much?
What? Who is he?
Somethin's wrong.
I didn't sense
either of 'em coming!
Hey there Zeru!
I was just saying
how-dee-do to our enemies!
[ZERU] Enjoy your last
night with the living.
Let's just say that tomorrow
will see you strongly
resembling your coffee cup.
What?
[ZERU] Did you see their fifth
man sleeping on the couch?
He never moved.
[RINKU]
So?
I can't figure out if it's
because he knew we
wouldn't attack him tonight,
or if he simply--
wasn't afraid of us.
I think he's
just an idiot!
There must be something
different about that boy.
We will see.
[ANNOUNCER] Welcome,
humans and demons alike,
to the glorious
Hanging-Neck Island!
Now let the Dark
Tournament Begin!!
[crowd cheers]
[NARRATOR] The day of the dark
tournament has arrived.
Yusuke Urameshi's team will
battle the Rokuyukai team
in the opening match,
with Yusuke still
locked in a deep slumber!
How will this
ten-man battle be fought,
and what will the outcome be?
[BOTAN] Hello everyone,
Botan here.
While I'm delivering
Shizuru and Keiko
to Hanging-Neck Island,
the first fight of the Dark
Tournament is getting underway!
And with Yusuke still asleep,
Kuwabara has to
take the first match
against that
strange little boy.
He's got some exciting new
tricks with his Spirit Sword,
but it may not be enough!
Especially when defending
against eight deadly-Yo-Yo's?
It's guaranteed to be a fight
of a whole different color,
when Yu Yu Hakusho continues!
♪