[GUARD B]
Area B, status?
Everything's normal.
[GUARD B]
Good. Carry on, then.
[GUARD A sighs]
Talk about cautious.
Even with all these
patrol robots,
they still felt the need
to call in a private
security service like us?
What kind of bigshot do they
have coming to this thing?
[GUARD A grunts]
[GUARD A]
What happened?
Did it malfunction?
Hey, who are you?
That's my tablet!
If Gensei Kihara is here,
then he's probably
in the VIP room.
And judging from the map,
cutting through here
is my best bet.
It's a little reckless.
But that's a sacrifice
I'm willing to make
to get ahead of Shokuho.
[footsteps]
[explosion]
Is she trying to let them
know she's here?
What a brute.
Would it kill her
to have some grace,
or, I don't know, discretion?
[GUARD C]
Hurry! That came from Area B!
Huh? Hold on!
There's someone here, too!
Young lady!
I don't know how
you got in here,
but we have orders to
detain anyone suspicious.
Stop or we'll shoot.
Fine, then. Fire.
Huh? Hey, what's wrong
with you guys?
Didn't you hear me?
Yes, why don't you fire?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
--[gunshots]
--[GUARD grunts]
[GUARD D]
We've been expecting you.
And you did a great job.
Now hold tight for
a second while I erase
this guy's memories.
There we go.
Why don't the rest
of you take a knee?
Do me a favor and seal off
all entrances and exits.
I don't want an ant
escaping this place.
And make sure to capture Gensei
Kihara for me, all right?
[GUARDS]
Yes, ma'am!
"Metal that can turn liquid,"
that's relevant.
Did you find something?
What does it say?
[SATEN]
Well, a little while ago,
the stuff was really popular;
a lot of different companies
were manufacturing it,
but now only two
of those companies
are still in business.
Yes, that's what
I've found as well,
but neither company
has any record of loss
or theft of liquid metal.
Although we can't dismiss
the possibility of it being
an inside job.
Hey, Shirai.
I narrowed down that
Bank list and sent it to you.
Thanks. I'll take a look now.
[SATEN]
Huh...
One of those old liquid
metal factories
is in School District 7.
[KUROKO]
There she is! I found her!
Her name is Mitori Kozaku.
She's a third year at Kirigaoka.
Age 15. Dropped out?
Huh? Non-public information?
What's that supposed to mean?
I cross-referenced
Antiskill's database.
Listen to this.
From what I can tell,
she should have been
admitted to the reform school
for attempted terrorist
activities 14 months ago.
Huh?
Hold on, she couldn't be
locked up, she attacked you.
Does that mean she
broke out or something?
No way.
If she did, Judgement would
have been notified about it.
Are you positive this
is the right person?
Well, she did have a hood on,
covering her eyes.
So I can't be 100% certain.
But the deep-seated darkness
I see in her eyes
makes me think this
is the same person.
Okay, then.
Why don't we head over
to the Bank Control Center
and double-check?
Finding a second
source couldn't hurt.
[KUROKO]
All right.
[UIHARU]
Then let's-- Oh.
But what do we do
about Ms. Misuzu?
[KUROKO] I explained
the situation to Konori.
I don't think it'll be an
issue if we leave her here.
What are you gonna do
while the two of us are gone?
[SATEN]
Huh?
Sorry, you have to be
a member of Judgment
to be allowed inside, so we
can't bring you along this time.
[SATEN]
Oh, no big deal.
Guess I'll just hang out
until you get back.
I'll find some way
to pass the time.
[CROWD cheering]
[SATEN] Oh, yeah, it's still the
middle of the Daihasei Festival.
So much has been going on,
I almost forgot.
[KAMIJO]
Excuse me!
I'm doing a scavenger hunt!
Does anyone have
a good luck charm?
Anyone?
Really? Not a single one of you?
Gimme a break.
I can't believe they're making
me look for something
so superstitious in
science-loving Academy City.
My rotten luck!
[SATEN]
A good luck charm?
I have the one I got
from Mama when I came
to Academy City,
but it's important to me.
I can't just hand it over
to a complete stranger,
even if I feel
sorta bad for him.
Sorry I can't help,
spiky-haired guy.
[KAMIJO]
This sucks!
[TAKOYAKI VENDOR]
There you go.
[KAMIJO] Um, you wouldn't happen
to have a good luck charm,
would you?
No. I'd help you out
if I did, sorry.
No. I'm sorry
I put you on the spot.
[SATEN]
He's still at it.
We've walked pretty far, too.
As late as it is,
he has to be in last place.
Then again,
I think you get zero
points if you drop out
of the scavenger hunt,
but if you manage to finish,
even in last, you get some.
He's really not giving up.
He seems nice enough.
He wouldn't like, throw it away.
[KAMIJO]
...a good luck charm!
[SATEN]
Uh... You over there.
I have one.
Huh? Are you serious?
Would it be okay if
I borrowed it for a bit?
Sure. Let me just
find it in here.
[KAMIJO laughs]
You're a lifesaver!
Careful, can't go
erasing its luck.
Mmm... Uh, anyway...
It may look pretty beaten up,
but it's still important to me,
so try and be
careful with it, okay?
Huh?
Of course, you got it.
I'll give it back
the second I finish.
But it'd be a jerk move
of me to expect you
to stand around here until then.
All right, then how about this?
An hour from now,
we'll meet up right over there.
Sounds like a good idea to me.
And if for some reason
we don't see each other,
could you drop it off at
Judgment Branch 177?
[KAMIJO]
Uh... Will do.
Thanks, uh...
Oh. My name is Saten.
I'm Toma Kamijo.
Thanks again for the help!
I'll be back in an hour!
See ya!
Oh, come to think of it,
that closed-down factory
is around here, isn't it?
[KUROKO]
Huh? That can't be right.
This says Mitori Kozaku
is deceased!
[UIHARU]
Um, excuse me...
Do you know if this
data is accurate?
It is.
Or at least, it's true the
person you're reading about
was filed under "deceased."
[KUROKO]
It's right here.
Two months ago
at the reform school.
Cause of death: heart failure.
Perhaps I was mistaken
about this after all,
and she just has a look-alike.
But don't you think some
of the data is a little strange?
[KUROKO]
Huh?
I mean, look at the timestamps.
If they're accurate, then that
means they cremated her
practically right after
they discovered her body.
[KUROKO]
You're right.
There would have been no
time to perform an autopsy.
[CLERK A]
Perhaps they didn't do one.
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't they?
You know, maybe there
was something fishy
about her passing
and they wanted to hide it,
so they had to get rid
of the evidence before
the cause of death
could be determined.
For that matter,
maybe your person
isn't even dead!
Uh, I don't mean to be rude,
but do you have any
real basis for that claim?
[CLERK A]
Oh, no, of course not.
But I do love a good
conspiracy theory.
I bet you'd get along pretty
well with our friend Saten.
Yeah.
[CLERK A]
I've heard this rumor.
It says that once in a while,
for whatever reason,
the students who are taken
in by Academy City's
reform school end up
disappearing out of the blue.
The guards report it
to their superiors,
but it ends up getting
swept under the rug
without much of
an investigation.
And it's always
the high-level espers
and outstanding students.
They're the only
ones who vanish.
[CLERK A] So the story goes that
there's some deal being struck
between Academy City
and the offenders,
one that allows them
to be secretly discharged
from the facility.
To hide it, the released
are declared dead.
I bet it's easier that way. Heh.
But to be fair,
at the end of the day,
it's just a rumor.
[UIHARU]
That was a bust.
We didn't prove our theory,
and we're leaving here
with even more questions.
Even so,
if we assume we're
correct for a moment,
and it really was Mitori
Kozaku who abducted you,
it means there's someone
with a lot of influence
behind all this.
Someone who could even
fake a death if they wanted.
[UIHARU]
Okay, but if that's true,
what would someone
that powerful want
with Ms. Misuzu and me?
[KUROKO]
When I think back on it now,
it seems obvious that
Mitori Kozaku's target
was that Misaka girl.
However...
I can't even begin to
imagine what their goal
in luring her out was.
It's a mystery.
Wow, you're really
concerned, aren't you?
About Misaka?
What do you mean?!
Not more than I should be!
I was simply speaking
as a member of Judgment!
I am by no means
interested in that girl!
I mean, sure, she was
quite caring and thankful
for our efforts,
but even so, that--
[gunshots]
[GUARD E grunts]
[panting]
Damn it!
What the hell's going on?
I'm so confused!
Why are our own men
suddenly ambushing us?
[GUARD F]
Hey!
Glad I found
someone still alive.
--Any idea what's going on here?
--[GUARD E] Stay back!
--[gunshot]
--[GUARD F] Whoa!
What the hell, man?
Are you the mole then?
Did you do this?
[GUARD E]
No, I bet you did, traitor!
[GUARD F]
You just shot at me!
[MIKOTO] Her ability has
them all screwed up.
They can't tell friend
from foe anymore.
They can't communicate,
let alone cooperate.
The entire organization's
broken down.
[MIKOTO]
This floor has the VIP room.
Which means
Gensei Kihara should be...
[GUARD G]
What are you doing there?
You're with Q Squad?
You know you're in
D Squad's section, right?
Oh, yeah, but...
It sounded like you guys
had some sort of emergency
going on, so I came to help.
All right, well we've already
had our guest take shelter.
I'll have you stick
with me for now.
Come on.
Right.
[MIKOTO] I could knock
him out right here,
but if Gensei is hiding,
I should probably wait
until he takes me to him.
[GUARD G]
This one is sketchy.
Q Squad shouldn't even
be on duty right now,
but she hasn't mentioned that.
More importantly, she didn't
respond to the signal.
As soon as I pass
this next corner...
...[GUARD, SHOKUHO] I'll turn
around and put a bullet in her.
That's what he's thinking.
Yeah, I know, I don't
need you to tell me.
My radar picked
it up immediately.
[GUARD G yells]
[SHOKUHO chuckles]
That's certainly
an interesting look.
[MIKOTO]
Oh, shut up.
Unlike you, I can't afford
to let everyone here
see my face and
school gym clothes.
Anyway, you haven't
found Gensei?
[SHOKUHO] My men are
investigating as we speak.
Are you sure he hasn't
just gotten away?
I've seized control of
every single escape route.
From the underground passages
to the heliport on the roof.
Oh...
[SHOKUHO]
Speak of the devil.
Looks like Gensei
has been found,
and he's in our custody.
[SATEN]
Huh...
It's pretty empty,
but no surprise there.
Give it another couple years,
and this place might collapse.
Realistically, any materials
that were left over
were probably already looted.
Or at least I haven't seen any.
[clatter]
[SATEN]
Someone's here!
[WORKER A]
Man,
I swear, that cosplay girl's
gonna work us to death.
[WORKER B]
You're not wrong, but hey...
[SATEN] Why are they
in an abandoned factory?
[beeping]
[SATEN]
The electricity is on?
[gasps]
[SATEN]
Uh... It's closing!
[SATEN whimpers]
[SATEN] Whew...
I can't believe I made it.
Whew.
What am I thinking?!
I've got no reason
to be in here!
[grunts]
Oh, it won't open!
I need a special
card or something.
What do I do?
I could call Uiharu for help.
[WORKER A]
...cosplaying as, anyway?
[WORKER B] I dunno.
Some weird nurse?
[SATEN panting]
[SATEN] Whoa.
Don't tell me this place is--
[SATEN gasps]
Don't turn around.
Wouldn't dream of it.
[XÓCHITL]
What are you doing in here?
Oh, I'm just...
You see, I got... kinda lost?
[XÓCHITL]
Forget what you've seen,
and get out of here
without a word.
You know what?
That sounds like a great idea!
I'll be leaving right now.
[SATEN whimpers]
[SATEN]
I called it!
Why do I always have
to be right at the worst
possible times?
Wait, I don't know how to
get out of here by myself.
[XÓCHITL] I just told you
not to turn around!
[clatter]
[SATEN]
Huh? What was--
[yells]
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Whoopsie.
Hmm? What are you doing?
You're just letting
her get away.
[XÓCHITL] Yeah, well the plan's
already in its final stages.
What's the problem?
Does it even matter
what happens here?
It's not like it would
change anything.
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Huh?
Maybe, but you have no reason
to let her live either, do you?
[WORKER A]
Hey, everything okay over here?
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
We have an intruder.
Go catch the girl
who ran that way.
[WORKER A]
Uh, right!
[XÓCHITL]
Idiot.
Why'd you have to stick
your nose in this?
[phone buzzes]
What is it, Doctor?
[MEMBER DOCTOR]
Xóchitl,
listen closely,
this is important.
I was finally able to
speak with the members of
Academy City's Governing
Board and ask them directly.
It turns out my suspicions
were correct.
[XÓCHITL]
What?
[SATEN gasps]
Stop it! Come on!
Put me down! Let me go!
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Well, well, well.
We've found ourselves
a lively little rat.
So what do you want
us to do with this kid?
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Hmm...
Once you get her to tell
you why she snuck in,
dispose of her in
whatever way you want.
[SATEN gasps]
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
I've got places to be.
[WORKERS grunt]
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Hm?
What's this?
Are you a traitor
now or something?
Or could it be that you have
some kind of soft spot
for the rat behind you?
[XÓCHITL] I don't really care
what happens to this idiot.
But it's funny you would
accuse me of being a traitor.
Isn't it, Kozaku?
I'm part of the
organization MEMBER.
But you know that.
After all, you're the one
who delivers our orders
from Academy City's
Governing Board.
So when you came
to us with new orders,
we naturally assumed
they came from the Board,
like they're supposed to.
However,
the Doctor had doubts
and did some snooping.
And what he found
was that this job
you've assigned us
has nothing to do
with the Governing Board.
You conspired with
an outside client.
You used your position
as our go-between,
and then tricked Baba and
me into working for them.
Didn't you?
To be clear...
I really couldn't
care less who it is
you're working for now.
But you've betrayed us.
And that deserves punishment.
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
My, my.
If we fight here and now,
you'll end up in
pieces on the floor.
You realize that, right?
[XÓCHITL]
Try me.
You may think you can sit
back and watch from afar,
but somehow I doubt you're
aware of the full extent
of my techniques.
[KOZAKU]
Hmm.
I'm about 90% sure
that's a bluff.
But it's true,
her unusual powers
are unlike anything
I've seen in this city.
Maybe she can conjure
up some phenomenon
I can't even imagine.
I can't exactly afford any
setbacks at this point, either.
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Sheesh! Okay, fine.
I'm out of here.
But a word of warning
before I go.
If you've got a home
you can return to,
now would be a good time
to get out of Academy City.
Unless you'd rather die young.
I have no place like that.
And besides.
There's someone here
I have to hunt down
if it costs me my life.
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
You can be so dramatic.
[SATEN]
Uh...
I, uh...
I think you saved my life;
thank you so much!
Hold on.
You're that girl I met
yesterday, right?
Is this your way of thanking
me for showing you
how to use your cell phone--?
[SATEN grunts]
If you're gonna go
wandering into the city's
underground business,
you need to be able
to defend yourself
or be prepared to die.
If not, stay away.
Follow me.
I'll take you to the exit.
[SHOKUHO]
So, where did you guys find him?
[GUARD F]
The safe room.
He was hiding there on his own.
[SHOKUHO]
Hmm...
[MIKOTO]
So this is Gensei Kihara?
[GUARD F]
Should I pull his tape off?
No.
He doesn't need to be
able to talk for this.
I'll just consult with
his brain directly.
[beep]
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
Whoa, what are you doing?!
[RESEARCHER A grunts]
[MIKOTO]
A disguise?
Wait, Shokuho!
What's going on?
Shokuho!
[RESEARCHER A]
Huh?
You want me to be your stand-in
using special makeup?
[GENSEI chuckles]
Yes, I've got business that
I just couldn't get out of.
[RESEARCHER A]
But sir...
[GENSEI]
All you have to do at the forum
is nod and say "mm-hmm."
[RESEARCHER A]
Okay.
[GENSEI]
Now then.
If you're reading
these memories,
I'm sure you understand
what's happening.
[RESEARCHER A]
Sir?
[GENSEI] The fact that you're
there, with him right now,
means that you can't possibly
be you-know-where.
[RESEARCHER A]
Um...
[GENSEI] And I wonder
if Exterior will be safe
without you there
to watch over it.
Misaki Shokuho.
[SHOKUHO]
Why?
Why would Gensei do that?
[MIKOTO]
Wait up! Shokuho!
At least explain
what's going on!
Floor it!
Get me there now!
[MIKOTO, SHOKUHO groan]
[MISAKA 10032 grunts]
[KEITZ]
Coming around, are you?
This is in School District 2.
You can rest easy.
"Then does that mean
you're the one
who found me and
brought me here?"
asks Misaka, attempting
to express her gratitude.
Please, all of this
is just part of the job.
You really don't
need to thank me.
[MISAKA 10032 grunts]
[KEITZ]
Back to sleep again, huh?
[alarm blaring]
Oh, great.
And here I was,
convinced I'd finally found
some respectable work again.
But it looks like things
have taken an ugly turn.
[MIKOTO]
So what exactly is "Exterior"?
[SHOKUHO]
What?
Oh, you know,
it's that legendary sword.
[MIKOTO]
That's "Excalibur."
--[SHOKUHO] They kill bugs?
--[MIKOTO] "Exterminator."
--[SHOKUHO] Fires?
--[MIKOTO] "Extinguisher!"
[SHOKUHO] Those clip-ins people
use to make their hair longer?
[MIKOTO]
Those are extensions-- Hey!
Will you stop messing
around and tell me?