[KUROKO] Previously on
A Certain Scientific Railgun T .
My name is Kuroko Shirai.
I am a member of Judgment,
which works to keep the
peace in Academy City.
The city is in the middle
of a large-scale event
known as the Daihasei Festival.
During this festival, I was
walking along with my friends
Uiharu and Saten, when
suddenly, we were stopped.
It was none other
than Academy City's
third-ranked Level 5, Railgun,
otherwise known
as Mikoto Misaka.
We both attend Tokiwadai,
but we're not even acquainted.
Yet she felt comfortable
shouting my name out
for all the world to hear!
Who does she think she is?
A little later on, Saten
proposed something peculiar.
She suggested that
perhaps we were actually
friends of Misaka's,
and close ones at that.
And that another Level 5
at Tokiwadai Middle School--
Mental Out, or Misaki Shokuho--
was actually manipulating
our memories.
But that's absurd.
Could she have come up with
a more ridiculous hypothesis?
However, there wasn't
much time to discuss.
At that very moment,
disaster struck
and Uiharu and Misaka's
mother were taken hostage.
And then, Mikoto Misaka
flashed me a smile.
One that suggested she
had complete trust in me.
The image is burned
into my eyes.
Just thinking about it
makes my chest grow warmer.
Uh--! But whatever,
that doesn't matter!
Misaka told us she was
going after Misaki Shokuho,
who apparently knows something
about what was happening,
and went on her way.
After she left, Uiharu and I
began an investigation
into Mitori Kozaku,
the hostage-taker.
While we were gathering intel,
Saten came bursting in
with some new information.
She had gone off on her own
and snuck into a factory,
and said she was attacked
by a metal puppet
controlled by Mitori Kozaku.
Continuing her streak
of reckless behavior!
Fortunately for her,
one of Kozaku's associates,
a girl by the name of Xóchitl,
came to her rescue
for some reason.
From what that girl said,
the true target
in the plan that Mitori Kozaku
was a part of was Mikoto Misaka.
But what did it mean?
Just then, the
skies clouded over
and lightning struck
a certain building.
On my way to
investigate, I found
Kozaku's metal puppet attacking
Misaki Shokuho on a rooftop.
I took the man who was there,
along with a girl who resembled
Misaka, to a safe place.
I also rescued Shokuho.
But when I tried to ask
her what was going on,
and in what way she and
Mikoto Misaka were involved
in the increasingly
complex situation,
she forwent regular speech,
and instead used her ability
to transmit the information
directly into my brain.
According to it, the
ringleader behind the plan
was a mad scientist
named Gensei Kihara.
He had taken control of a
giant facility that housed
what is known as "Exterior,"
which allowed him to use the
same ability that Shokuho
has, and was apparently
using its power to propel
Misaka to Level 6.
To use Shokuho's words,
Mitori Kozaku is an inductor
that will help lead
Misaka to Level 6.
So if I take those
words as truth,
an important element in stopping
Misaka is to neutralize her.
Incidentally, as Shokuho
is the only person
who knows Exterior's
limiter unlock code,
she anticipated Gensei Kihara
tracking her down to learn it,
and laid all kinds
of traps for him.
I really hope that
works out for her.
Beyond that, there are
a couple of boys outside
causing a commotion
themselves.
Perhaps they're trying
to stop the runaway Misaka.
But I can't be certain.
Though, I am certain
they must be playing
some important role
in all this.
In any event, I must
locate Mitori Kozaku
and take her into custody.
Even if all that's waiting
for me is danger,
as a member of Judgment,
I will save Academy City!
[GENSEI] Someone who's
pretending to run away
but still has some plan
shows telltale signs
of what they're after.
I don't let those hints
that they're about to turn
the tables go unnoticed.
I'm experienced.
Which is why I can
tell something else
by looking at you now.
[SHOKUHO grunting]
[GENSEI]
You're out.
You have nothing
left up your sleeve
to reverse the
situation, do you?
[SHOKUHO gasps]
And now the limiter
unlock code is mine.
[grunts]
C'mon!
[SOGIITA yells]
[SOGIITA chuckles]
[GENSEI]
Phew, I can't wait to see this.
What do you think will
happen to Academy City
at that fateful moment?
Oh, I'm sorry.
That was rude of me.
I don't suppose you'll be alive
long enough to find out.
[KUROKO]
Not here.
[KUROKO grunts]
[KUROKO]
Or here.
[KUROKO] Not here, either.
Where is this Kozaku girl?
I destroyed her puppet's
camera immediately,
and rendered her echolocation
completely unusable.
I've successfully taken out
her puppet's eyes and ears.
And yet, it still knew
my general location
and could land a hit on me.
[KUROKO]
Judging from those actions,
I assumed that Kozaku herself
was watching me from
the upper floors.
[KUROKO]
But if I've looked this much
and still haven't found her,
there must be something
that I overlooked.
[SATEN] Hey. Do you think she'll
be okay with those injuries?
[UIHARU sighs] Considering she
just got out of the hospital,
she may not be.
That's what I thought.
And we can't even
tell what's going on
without being able
to see inside.
[gasps]
[UIHARU] Is that a relay
camera from the festival?
Another one.
There aren't any
events around here.
[SATEN] Yeah, they flew
in a little while ago.
You were so focused
on the building,
you didn't notice them.
Antiskill probably sent them
in search of any civilians,
just in case they
hadn't evacuated yet.
Looks like the E-M
waves at the heart
of the electrical phenomenon are
too strong for them to get near.
[gasps] I just had a great idea!
Why don't we borrow
those cameras?
Then we'd be able to tell what's
going on inside of the building,
which means we can
give Shirai some backup!
[gasps] Wow, that is a
great idea, coming from you!
--Uh...
--[UIHARU] I'll start hacking--
I-I mean, accessing
them right away,
and then transfer
command over to me.
[gasps]
Wait a second, when did you
say those cameras got there?
Uh... Not too long ago.
Like, when Shirai first
entered the building.
[UIHARU] Shirai! This
is only a possibility,
but there's something
I think you should know.
[KOZAKU] Not only did she dig up
who I am in this short a time,
but she also had
countermeasures on hand
to shut down my echolocation.
I'm impressed.
But not intimidated.
Luck is still on my side.
I hacked a festival relay camera
that was directing
the evacuation,
and I've taken control of it.
With it at my disposal,
I've gained the means to control
my Liquid Shadow once again.
Even without echolocation,
I still have a set of
eyes on the situation.
[KOZAKU] Oh-ho. Still at it?
Go ahead, search all you like.
[KUROKO]
The last spot.
That was all of the places
where she could hide herself.
Even supposing we
passed each other,
the motion sensor sheets
I placed in key locations
would have picked her up.
Was it all for nothing?
[KUROKO] Assuming what
Shokuho said is true,
then if we're to return
Misaka to normal,
we must neutralize Kozaku
as soon as possible.
[KUROKO]
And yet, I...
[KUROKO] No. If I were searching
for her in the wrong place,
she wouldn't have been so
relentless in fending me off.
Or...
[KUROKO] Is that exactly
what she wants me to think,
and she isn't here?
I need to review the facts.
Calmly. If she
isn't hiding here,
then where else could she be?
The surveillance
cameras caught Kozaku
going onto the street
in front of the building.
However, there has
been no sight of her
on any cameras since.
[KUROKO]
This is the only building
in which she could be hiding.
[gasps]
[KUROKO]
The only building .
--[rustling]
--[KUROKO gasps]
[KOZAKU]
That won't work!
I can still tell
exactly where you are!
[KOZAKU] I'll corner her so she
has no choice but to teleport!
[KOZAKU] It is possible that she
could jump to another floor,
but as long as she doesn't
know exactly where I am yet,
she's gonna want to jump to
a space that she can confirm
is safe with her own eyes.
When she uses her ability
consecutively like this,
I've noticed that it
creates a brief lag.
If I can predict
where she's going,
and catch her in that instant...
There!
Uh.
[KOZAKU gasps]
[KOZAKU laughs]
[KOZAKU] Sorry about that, but
if you hadn't gotten in my way,
I wouldn't have had to kill you.
Then again, if Academy City
is about to be destroyed,
you would have met the
same fate sooner or later.
You're just gone
before the rest of us.
[gasps] It's time!
[gasps]
Sogiita!
[KOZAKU] It's working!
She'll destroy it this time!
Ah. So we're already at
the "unlock" stage, are we?
She's progressing a lot
quicker than I expected,
which means I don't
have a moment to spare.
I'll just go ahead and enter
the limiter unlock code
that you so generously
provided me with.
[beeping]
Code input complete.
[KOZAKU giggles]
Yeah. I know the whole
city's about to blow up,
and you'll be wiped out in
a matter of minutes anyway.
But I wanna make sure
you're annihilated
while I'm still
around to enjoy it!
You can apologize to her
in the next life!
I hope this hurts!
[thud]
[gasps]
[panting]
[KUROKO]
I found you!
[KUROKO] So, you were
in the sewers after all.
You were spotted on the street
in front of the building,
but you weren't hiding
anywhere inside.
So what other option did you
have, besides coming here?
But... I swear
I just killed you!
No way!
You're still showing up
on the camera feed!
[gasps]
[KOZAKU]
A composite image? Since then?
Impossible! There are tens
of thousands of cameras!
Are you saying you were able
to single out the only one
under my control and take it
over without me ever noticing?
That's exactly right.
'Cause I have the perfect
partner for that kind of job.
Good work, girl.
And now there's nowhere
left for you to run.
[KOZAKU]
My Liquid Shadow is aboveground.
There's not enough time
to call it here.
But...!
[KUROKO]
It's dark.
I have to get closer to
precisely judge the distance!
[KOZAKU] Hiding myself
wasn't the only reason
that I fled into the sewer.
It was to be ready
on the off-chance that
you caught up with me!
Above ground, you can jump
around just about anywhere,
but down here, your
movements are limited
to this single, thin line!
When you teleport away
to avoid my first knife,
my second knife will get
you wherever you are!
Forward? To the side? Up?
No matter where you run,
I'll take you down that instant!
[KOZAKU gasps]
She didn't teleport?
Oh, no, I'm too slow--!
[KOZAKU yells]
[groans]
[yells]
[KOZAKU groans]
[KOZAKU]
Dolly...
[pants]
[GENSEI gasping]
[gasping]
[GENSEI] I see. So making
me think that you had
no further plan remaining
was itself your plan, then.
[GENSEI]
I guess...
...you win this round.
[grunts]
Huh?
[SHOKUHO]
Hm...
[SHOKUHO] Graviton panels.
I could probably use these
to create a pitfall
trap of some sort.
Or maybe I could physically
capture Gensei between them.
Mm... But would either
of those solutions
really be enough against him?
No. Out-scheming that geezer
is gonna be a lot
harder than that.
Especially now that he's gotten
his hands on Exterior.
[SHOKUHO] Ugh, speaking of.
Do I even need it anymore?
I mean, I've thought
about it before.
I have to keep
this place hidden,
pay the cost of its upkeep,
and stress about it
being taken over, just for
a boost in my ability.
The pros are starting to be
outweighed by the cons.
Not to mention, with the size
of the mess it's caused today,
other organizations will
find out about it for sure.
[SHOKUHO]
But, how would I even go about
getting rid of
something like this?
It's designed to withstand
five times the seismic force
of the largest earthquake
ever recorded.
And, more immediately
problematic, if it did take
damage like that, the giant
brain would reflect it
to the Mental Out user,
and leave them incapacitated.
The only way to
circumvent that damage
is to input the
self-destruct code.
[SHOKUHO] But the only one
with access privileges
at the moment is Gensei.
If I'm going to steal
those privileges back,
I'll have to undo his
Level Upper first.
But if I could do that,
I wouldn't be in this mess.
I could try to manipulate
Gensei into entering
the self-destruct code himself.
But I'm getting ahead
of myself again.
[gasps]
[SHOKUHO]
No. I can do it!
[SHOKUHO] Though, it would
be incredibly risky.
If he sees through it,
it's game over.
And even if it does work,
he might still choose
to kill me before actually
putting in the code.
I really don't care
what ends up happening
to Misaka, but the
research facilities may not
be able to cure the virus
injected into the sisters
on their own.
And in order to understand
the virus's configuration,
I'd have to do a
little snooping around
inside old man Gensei's head.
What's more, if I miss
this chance to catch him,
I probably won't get another.
[inhales]
[sighs]
It's a big gamble, huh?
[SHOKUHO] Not only do I have
to push myself to the limit
and earnestly try to win,
I have to bet that, despite
those efforts, I'll still lose.
Great.
After I swap my own
recognition of the limiter
unlock code and the
self-destruct code,
I have to erase all
memory of doing so.
[beep]
[SHOKUHO] So, it looks like
you wound up entering
Exterior's self-destruct
code when you wanted
the limiter unlock code, huh?
Somehow I get the feeling
that was my brilliant idea.
Not that I remember it.
[KAMIJO] It changed.
There's more lightning.
Did that girl,
whatever her name was,
shut off the power
at the source?
[gasps] What was I doing?
[gasps] What is that?
What's going on?
Stop it! No!
I can't unleash that thing!
Why can't I control it?
What's happening?
Huh?
[MIKOTO] What is this?
I can't hold it back!
[KAMIJO] Well, whatever's
happened, this isn't over yet.
[KAMIJO] Somehow things with
Zapper have gotten even crazier.
But I don't know what
I can do to help her!
Next time, "Dragon Strike."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.
[SOGIITA] Man, you're doing
your preview bit on this show?
You got guts!
[KAMIJO]
Huh? Should I not?