[KOZAKU] If you want to make
your way in Academy City,
the most effective
method is to suck up
to the researchers here.
It looks like your
rating has gone up
since last time.
Wow, are you serious?
That's awesome!
I'm so glad.
I couldn't have done
it without all of you!
"Effort pays off" is a lie.
Just like going to a
good school will get you
a good job.
The research facility
you're with makes
or breaks your future.
Thank you very much!
I had gotten really good
at putting on a fake smile
to make people like me.
I'm looking forward to working
with you again tomorrow!
All this acting friendly
is more exhausting
than the experiments.
However...
I wasn't counting on having
that girl forced on me
as a result."
[RESEARCHER B]
Oh, Kozaku?
[KOZAKU]
Huh? Y-Yeah?
Hey. Do you think you could
do something for me?
This girl could use a playmate
when you have the time.
Dolly has lived her whole
life at the facility.
We think her stress
levels are affecting
her observational data.
So I figured if she had
someone to play with,
it should help alleviate
that stress, right?
Sure. If you think
I can be of help.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[KOZAKU]
U-Um...
[chuckles]
Are you all right?
Hey, what's your name?
Mitori Kozaku.
Okay, then I'll call
you "Mi" for short!
[KOZAKU]
She's simple.
[DOLLY laughs]
[KOZAKU] From then on, once my
experiments were over...
That felt like it took forever.
[KOZAKU]
Dolly?
[KOZAKU] Without fail, I would
end up being hounded like this.
[DOLLY]
Okay, my turn!
Here we go!
Six!
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Look at that,
I already have two kids!
I'll take my congrats.
So I was wondering, Dolly.
What's with you not
being able to go outside?
They said it's something
about my treatment.
Treatment?
At an ability
development facility?
[DOLLY] They say it'll
help my little sister.
[KOZAKU]
You have a sister?
Apparently, but we've never met.
They say if the
treatment goes well,
I'll have lots
of little sisters.
[KOZAKU]
What does that mean?
[DOLLY]
It's your turn, Mi.
[DOLLY laughs]
Mi, this is amazing!
It's really pretty, too!
I dunno.
It's not like it's a work
of art or anything.
If you want to see what it's
really like, go to the ocean.
[DOLLY]
Ocean?
Oh, yeah, I read about
that in a book!
The place with lots of water!
[KOZAKU]
At first,
I couldn't help but wonder
why I was stuck
with this simpleminded girl,
and just dealt with it.
--[KOZAKU] Dolly, you--
--[DOLLY] Mi! [laughs]
Easy!
[DOLLY laughing]
So cute!
Do we have to hug
over every little thing?
At least warn me.
And quit smelling me
all the time!
[DOLLY]
But I like the smell of people.
And you have such
a warm smell, Mi.
[KOZAKU] Meanwhile,
you smell like chemicals.
[DOLLY grunts]
Why're you doing that?
'Cause you won't listen,
let alone do what I tell you.
Oh, yeah?!
[KOZAKU] Somehow,
whenever I was with her,
I didn't have to
force myself to put on
a fake smile.
It was genuine.
[KOZAKU]
Thanks for everything!
I'm glad we finished early.
I wonder what we
should play today!
Dolly!
[DOLLY gasps]
What... is that stuff?
[DOLLY]
No!
[RESEARCHER A]
Kozaku, come with me please.
I imagine by now
someone has told you
she's here to be treated.
In the simplest terms possible,
she requires
some life support
equipment in order
to stay alive.
Now why don't you head on home?
[KOZAKU]
Life support equipment? Really?
If anyone finds out,
they'll be more than just angry.
"Parameter List." No.
"Planned Exterior
construction site." No.
If you want to make your
way in Academy City,
the most effective
method is to suck up
to the researchers here.
Messing with their work
is out of the question.
Please, stop medicating Dolly!
Ah.
There was a break-in
reported at the data center,
and I was wondering
who could've been
sneaking around. I see.
Well.
Then it's safe to assume
you know what she really is.
I know that she's a clo--
A clone.
And that you're using her
as a guinea pig
so you can make
mass-produced clones,
and you want them
to all live longer.
But you're giving her
all kinds of drugs!
You don't care about her health;
you just want to collect
your stupid data!
Her lifespan is already short.
And recklessly giving
her those meds
is making it even shorter!
[CHIEF RESEARCHER A sighs]
She may be a clone.
But she's just like us!
Clones are alive!
Please, stop doing this!
And what if I told you we can't?
Then I'll go public.
I'll tell everyone what
I found in your research data!
Who would believe
the wild stories of a child?
Someone would.
And if not, I'll go
to the governing board.
They can inspect this--
[CHIEF RESEARCHER A laughs]
That won't happen.
The very governing
board you speak of
is who's running
this experiment.
You think clones are
"just like you," huh?
Well, you're right.
Clones and you espers are
basically the same here.
As far as the
Academy's concerned,
you're nothing more
than lab rats.
[KOZAKU gasps]
Why, you--!
[grunts]
[RESEARCHER B]
You're going to leave her alive?
[CHIEF RESEARCHER A]
For better or worse,
the girl has extremely
high potential.
Once Exterior is complete,
she's likely to come in handy.
Dolly.
I was held in
confinement for months.
No. It might have been
even longer than that.
Suddenly one day,
the guard disappeared.
And when I went outside,
the research facility
was completely deserted.
Go ahead, look down
on us from up there.
But know that someday soon
I'll show you that even
lab rats have fangs
that can make you bleed.
But even after that moment,
no matter how hard I tried,
I was still powerless.
I failed my meticulously
planned assassination.
But I did learn something.
Even if there were 10,000 of me,
I could never lay
so much as a finger
on the governing board.
Do me a favor and remove
the mask, will you?
[KOZAKU]
Where am I?
And who's this old geezer?
My, my.
You have a keen
look in your eyes.
They're smoldering.
Like a glowing ember that
spews the smoke of hatred.
[GENSEI]
Oh!
I supposed I should just
get down to business.
If I told you there was
a way to blow Academy City
off the face of the planet,
would you be interested?
What'd you say?
Huh.
Honestly, it sounds
way too good to be true.
But why are you telling me?
[GENSEI]
Hmm.
Dogma, perhaps?
When a person's capacity
to tolerate stress
is exceeded,
both lofty ideals and
greedy ambitions crumble,
destroying all motivation.
And for that reason,
whether it's by
nature or nurture,
I simply can't put
my trust in the concept
of "resolve."
After all, if it doesn't kick
in when it's crunch time,
what use is it?
However, I find
tremendous hatred's
unwillingness to waver
profoundly beautiful.
People don't think
twice about giving
their life for the sake
of vengeance.
To answer your question,
I'm banking on
the dogma of hatred.
[KOZAKU]
That Judgment girl isn't here.
Handcuffs?
I can get out of these
with my ability, no sweat.
But why bother?
If I'm still alive, then it
means that the plan
must have failed.
Guess I could just stay here.
and be food for the rats.
[KOZAKU]
Misaki Shokuho?
[SHOKUHO] I decided to take
a quick peek inside Gensei's
memories just in case.
And sure enough,
they took me right to you.
You were "Mi," weren't you?
I've always wanted
to know why I had
to play the part of the girl
who abandoned Dolly,
but I brushed it off.
maybe I should've looked
into it a long time ago.
I'll have you turn yourself in,
because it wouldn't be
fair to Shirai if I didn't.
But first, I need you
to come with me for a bit.
Understand?
You see, I learned
something else when I read
Gensei's memories.
[SHOKUHO]
As it turns out,
Dolly had a sister
that was created
around the same time as her.
They wanted to perfect
their cloning technology,
but that wasn't the only
reason they created Dolly.
They were trying
to use her to establish
a network, too.
One that could transfer
data and information
between the clones.
All of Dolly's memories
and experiences
were transferred into
another individual
and are still there now.
That's her "little sister."
And she's asleep in
a research facility.
While she shares her
memories and experiences,
make no mistake,
she's not Dolly.
Still, we can't just
leave her there, right?
You can never have enough backup
when on a mission like this.
--So come with me.
--[KOZAKU] Why?
You didn't have to
explain all that to me.
You could have just used
your ability to control me.
You're not wrong.
Are you saying I should?
[KOZAKU]
No. I'll come.
[SATEN]
All right.
A toast to our dear friend
Shirai's complete recovery!
[GROUP]
Cheers!
[KUROKO] Oh, please,
you're making too much of it.
Not to mention,
it's a little late.
It's been a whole
week since I got out
of the hospital.
Yeah, we know, but with the
Daihasei Festival going on,
we never got the opportunity
to properly celebrate.
And if you really need
another reason to party,
today's the day you
stopped needing
your wheelchair, right?
Now eat.
I suppose I'll set
my hesitations aside.
Whatever the occasion,
I'm happy to eat
anything you prepare, Sissy.
Mmm!
Okay, but why are
we doing this here
of all places?
Come on, it's not
like anything else
is going on.
Oh! Let me just refill
your drink real quick.
One sec, Konori!
Guess it's okay this once.
Thank you for being so generous!
Come to think of it, Misaka,
how is your mother holding up
since the incident
the other day?
Huh? Mama?
Oh, uh...
Good, I think,
all things considered.
Is that right?
I'm glad to hear it.
I think we all are.
But Uiharu was
especially concerned.
Hostage situations
can be very traumatic.
[MIKOTO] Wait, so that
incident wasn't completely
wiped from their memories?
Then, how do they
remember me acting?
I should probably know.
I'm sure Shokuho must
have made some revisions.
Of course she was concerned.
I mean, she got caught up
in all the chaos herself.
The bad guy knocked
you out, right?
That's a big deal.
[UIHARU]
Uh-huh.
Believe me, I haven't
forgotten how little
I did to help.
But luckily Shirai came
along and ended things
without much trouble,
so don't worry about it.
I just wish you
had contacted me.
I could have provided
some support, too.
That would've been helpful.
I can't believe I didn't
reach out to you.
That's not like me.
I'm terribly sorry
for that, Konori.
[MIKOTO] It sounds like
she just erased the fact
that I was there at all.
Which, I guess makes sense,
considering she said I was stuck
in the bathroom with
an upset stomach.
Unless you're ready to
kill me right here and now.
[SATEN]
Welp.
That's okay, why don't
we use this party
as a way to wipe
the slate clean?
Whaddya say?
I say that's a poorly
disguised attempt
to avoid responsibility
for your Shadow Metal
exploits, Saten.
You sure caused a lot
of trouble, huh?
[KONORI]
What are you talking about?
One day, Saten just started--
[SATEN]
Here, Uiharu! Ahh!
'Scuse me!
I'll have you know Sissy
made that especially for me!
Is something the matter, Sissy?
Not at all.
I was just thinking how
nice it is to have friends.
[UIHARU]
Are you sure? Okay.
[MIKOTO]
I'm really glad I'm here.
Being outside of their
circle was tough.
This just feels right.
By the way, you can have this.
You need some
sort of liquid metal
to make your ability
work, don't you?
[SHOKUHO]
That's what she wanted to see.
So basically,
Dolly would be with you,
but she would see
and hear me instead?
Yeah.
At the time, I hadn't
developed the power
to alter people's memories yet.
But to tell you the truth,
I'm fairly certain
she figured out that
I wasn't really you
at some point.
I see.
She had some surprisingly
keen instincts.
Thanks.
If everything you
told me is true,
then Dolly wasn't
alone at the end,
thanks to you.
And that was really
my biggest regret.
[KOZAKU]
Dolly.
[DOLLY'S SISTER]
Mi.
Is that you?
It is, right, Mi?
[DOLLY'S SISTER]
We've missed you.
We were afraid you didn't
like us anymore.
That you thought we
were disgusting. And--
Dummy.
None of that's true at all.
We remember this smell.
It's been so long.
We love it.
Wait!
You're Misaki, aren't you?
[SHOKUHO]
Hm?
I have no idea who
you're talking about.
We know it's you, Misaki.
Because in our dreams,
we were always with both of you.
The times we spent with you two
are the only memories we have.
[SHOKUHO]
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for tricking
you for so long!
I'm sorry I didn't catch
on to their lies!
I'm sorry for butting
into your memories,
and without asking you.
And I'm sorry for taking
the easy way out
and just believing that lie.
If only I'd bothered
to look into
who "Mi" was back then.
I could have reunited
her with Dolly.
I'd have learned
what the experiment
was really about,
and I could have saved Dolly
from such an early death.
Everything that happened
to you two is my fault
for forcing my way
into your friendship!
I'll do anything
to make up for it.
Okay, then take us to the ocean.
After that, we want
to ride a roller coaster
at an amusement park,
and see a hippo at the zoo.
Oh, and going on
a plane would be nice.
We want to see
the auroras in Finland,
and play with the
dolphins in Hawaii,
and the llamas in Machu Pichu.
Hey, you're asking
for way too much.
Are you trying
to travel the world?
Yeah, actually, you're right.
If the three of us are together,
anywhere's fine.
Is that okay?
[SHOKUHO]
Honestly.
You always did ignore
whatever was being
said to you,
but made sure we knew
what you wanted.
You've got a
real selfish streak.
Really.
I just don't know
what to do with you.
[MIKOTO]
Good.
It looks like your temperature's
back to normal.
We're officially out
of the woods now.
"However, while Misaka
was lying in bed,
drifting in and out
of consciousness,
the Daihasei Festival
concluded," says Misaka,
lamenting her
unfortunate circumstances.
Oh, don't pout.
I'll take you out somewhere
to make up for it, okay?
Where do you wanna go?
Ocean.
The ocean?
We're so not in beach
season anymore.
"For some reason,
unknown to her,
Misaka suddenly feels
the desire to make
an exciting promise
with someone dear to her,"
says Misaka, having a
strange sense of déjà vu,
and feeling sentimental.
[SATEN] Hey, if you could have
any dream you wanted,
what kind of dream
would it be, Uiharu?
[UIHARU]
Hmm.
I'd dream of eating lots
of delicious food
whenever I want!
[SATEN] You do that
all the time already.
You, Shirai?
[KUROKO]
I would of course dream of--
[SATEN] Ah, on second
thought, never mind!