[keyboard clicking]
[door opens]
[MIKOTO]
I'm back!
I brought your uniform
over to the cleaners.
Oh, and they had
your winter uniform,
so I grabbed that, too.
[KUROKO]
I really appreciate it, Sissy.
Apologies if I put you
out at all.
[MIKOTO]
It's no problem!
And you deserve it
for saving that girl's life.
Pretty impressive.
[KUROKO]
Yes, well...
Hm? What's the matter?
Did something happen?
Kind of. Um, let me explain.
[MIKOTO]
Wow. A precognitive app, huh?
Yes.
We don't quite understand all
of the specifics yet, though.
So starting tomorrow,
my work is likely to get
a bit more hectic.
I can see why.
Is there anything I can do
to help you out?
Oh, Sissy, you care!
Just knowing you're
concerned for my wellbeing
is more than enough for me.
But whatever you do,
please do not stick your nose
in without asking first.
Reminder:
You're just a civilian.
I'm fully aware of that.
[KUROKO]
Incidentally, Sissy, question.
Are you planning to use
one of those cards
when you turn in for the night?
By cards you mean Indian Poker?
No, I think I've had enough
of that for a while.
Today was kind of a nightmare.
Well, I'm sorry you
had a bad day.
But then, yes, I agree.
I think that would be
for the best.
[MIKOTO]
Why?
Did you have a bad experience
with those cards too,
or something?
[KUROKO]
Yes, you could say that.
[SATEN]
Huh?
Hold on, didn't you say
you had the day off today?
Originally, I was scheduled to.
But remember yesterday
how you told me
about that app that shows
the times of accidents,
and some of them
haven't happened yet?
Well, now I have to be on patrol
so we can investigate it.
Oh, man, really?
[phone buzzing]
[UIHARU]
Oh, it's from Shirai.
Wow, she's really rushing me!
Sorry we couldn't hang out
like we planned to.
[SATEN]
It's fine, I get it! Good luck!
[UIHARU]
Thanks. See ya!
Hello? Yeah, I'm on my way now!
[SATEN] It feels like forever
since we got some food together.
I was looking forward to it.
[SATEN humming]
[SATEN]
Oh, there it is!
[EMPLOYEE A]
That'll be 1,088 yen.
[SATEN]
Okay, out of 1,100 please.
[FRENDA screams]
Here too...
They're completely out!
[EMPLOYEE B]
I am so sorry about that.
We just sold our last one.
Stockroom and all.
This is so unfair.
I've been all over
the city today,
how is it that every store
is completely sold out?
Heh... It was featured
on a show last night.
They kept talking
about how good it is
for your looks.
That's why I picked some up.
[FRENDA screams]
Hey! What are you doing?
Give me...
[SATEN]
Huh?!
[FRENDA]
Give me that mackerel!
[EMPLOYEE B]
Ladies!
So, um...
How long are you
gonna follow me for?
That depends.
How much longer are you
going to try to keep
that mackerel away from me?
[SATEN]
Huh?
Just to be clear,
I'll pay you for it!
I'll buy them for ten times
the regular price.
All I have is plastic.
[FRENDA]
Okay then. Forget money!
How about you trade me
for this shockingly
adorable doll?
[SATEN] I personally find
that kind of creepy.
[FRENDA]
Okay.
Then how about this
"Dangerous Cracker"
that you can shoot at your
enemies to blow off steam?
[SATEN]
A party popper?
My walls are thin, so...
Come on!
What do I have to offer
to convince you to trade?
[SATEN]
I never said there was anything.
Do you really like
mackerel that much?
[FRENDA]
"Like" doesn't even come close.
If I go too long
without eating it,
I get awful palpitations,
my extremities shake,
and I hallucinate.
[SATEN] If that's true, maybe
you should stop eating it.
For your health.
You know, I've been eating
it every single day,
supporting the canned
mackerel industry,
but then one TV feature
comes along and everyone
and their mother rushes
out to buy it all up!
Do you understand
how unfair that is?
You owe me that fish!
[SATEN]
Huh?! That's absurd!
[SATEN groans]
All right already.
I really don't want you
hounding me anymore.
I guess you can have one
of the two cans I bought.
Really?
You know, I pegged you
for a gullible sucker
the second I saw you,
so I knew if I kept pushing you,
you'd cave eventually!
And it looks like I was right
on the money!
[FRENDA]
Okay, let's get to it!
You're gonna eat it here?
[FRENDA yells]
What the--? What happened?
[FRENDA] I used the one
with too much firepower!
[FRENDA]
Hey, wait!
That was, all told,
just an unfortunate accident!
[SATEN] Sorry, I need what's
left for my own cooking.
Plus, I have no patience,
let alone pity,
for people who waste food.
[FRENDA]
Huh?
The people of this country
are much cold-hearted.
I just wanted taste of my
homeland to ease homesickness.
It has been so long time.
[whines] I'm so sad.
You know, it's rude to
ignore a crying lady!
Oh, all right!
You can come over to my
place for dinner tonight.
Is that enough for you?
Okay! Okay!
Japan people is so nice!
Such kind!
[SATEN] What country are
you supposed to be from?
C-Curry?
What do you think you're doing,
putting the treasure that is
mackerel into curry?
Curry is way too
strong a flavor!
All the other ingredients
get completely
overpowered by it!
You're basically
murdering all the flavor
the mackerel would've had!
There's no way this
could taste any good!
So good!
The spiciness pairs nicely with
the rich taste of mackerel.
Rather than competing,
they synergize
and enhance one another!
The flavors are dancing
deliciously atop my tongue!
I'd appreciate it if you
didn't eat and talk
at the same time.
Mmm! Deilig!
[SATEN]
"Die lee"?
It means "delicious."
Oh, okay, it's another language.
Well, anyhow,
I'm glad that you like it.
I'll take seconds!
[SATEN]
At least she's honest.
[FRENDA]
Man.
You're a better cook
than I gave you credit for.
Next time we meet,
it'll be my turn to treat you
to a yummy meal.
Mackerel in miso,
or soy sauce or something!
[SATEN]
Always with the mackerel.
[FRENDA]
Oh, that reminds me.
Are you on FUKIDASHI?
[SATEN]
You mean the messaging app?
Yeah, I use it with
some of my friends.
Great, here's my ID.
Let's add each other.
[SATEN]
Uh, sure.
[FRENDA]
I'll get out of your hair.
Well, "Ha det bra!"
"Haday..." Okay.
You're gonna have to translate.
It means see ya later.
[giggles]
Bye!
[door closes]
That girl plays by no one's
rules but her own.
Well, it's fine.
I definitely had
some fun, at least.
[SATEN]
Really?
Then I guess it was
a good thing I told you
about that app, wasn't it?
If you were already able
to prevent an accident
from happening, that's great.
Yeah. I can't tell you
all the details,
but just take my word for it,
knowing about that
app has helped.
"Helped" is an understatement.
You're kicking butt!
Oh, Shirai took care of it.
I was mostly just support.
But either way,
thanks for telling me
about the app.
Hey. It's fine.
As for thanking me,
you already did,
with those adorable little pugs.
[gasps]
Wait, I don't remember you
flipping my skirt yet today!
When did you see?
Ho-ho.
You still have much
left to learn, Kazari.
[UIHARU]
Oh, whatever.
I'll see you later!
[SATEN] Good luck with
your Judgment work!
See ya!
[phone chimes]
[SATEN]
That girl from yesterday.
And before I knew it,
we became friends.
[FRENDA] She's so weird, what's
the point in learning that?
Hello there!
Have you had any good
cards come in lately?
[TRADER A] One that you
would like? Let's see.
There's this one
from a clacker champion.
This one from a
coin-stacking record holder,
and then this!
It's from an incredibly skillful
chopstick handler.
Whoa. Chopstick handling, huh?
[YOBOU]
Indian Poker?
[HEART MEASURE]
Yeah.
You can learn just about
anything with them.
One's skill or experience
can be passed on
to another.
[YOBOU]
So, what made you bring that up?
[HEART MEASURE] There's been
a trend in Academy City lately.
Scientists are starting
to use it.
They've begun recording
their findings
within their dreams
and leaving behind cards
as a form of insurance.
[YOBOU]
Oh, yeah?
[HEART MEASURE] Of course,
the cards aren't guaranteed
to capture the data they
want to leave behind.
But rumor has it, there
are quite a few of them
who are attempting
it regardless.
I guess there must be
a fundamental part
of a scientist's mind
that can't be codified.
That makes sense, and I see
where you're going
with this.
[HEART MEASURE]
Yes.
I'm talking about none other
than the nanoparticle
object interference
adsorption manipulator,
better known as the tweezers.
Apparently, knowledge
of it has been leaked
in the form of a card.
And is your information
about this reliable at all?
[HEART MEASURE]
Who knows?
But if there's even
the slightest possibility,
we have to investigate.
I'll leave the method
up to you, so get on it.
[YOBOU sighs]
[YOBOU]
Time to work.
Between security
ranks A through D,
extract any conversation
presumed to be related
to Indian Poker
and the tweezers.
[SYSTEM VOICE A]
Thirteen items returned.
As many as 13?
Most of them seem to be
just idle conversation,
but even if there's only
a one-in-a-thousand,
or one-in-a-billion
chance it leads us to it...
...that's a chance
I'll have to take.
[FRENDA]
Hmm.
This one? No, maybe that one.
[FRENDA]
Those guys.
They're no amateurs.
But they might as well be,
compared to me.
A rival organization? Or...
[MAN A]
F Team here.
Yeah, we're getting
very close to the source.
[SATEN hums, giggles]
I can't wait to use this.
Ooh. I should tell
Uiharu about it.
[SATEN]
Huh?
[FRENDA]
Ah, jeez.
What am I even doing?
I'm not usually one
to work for free.
But...
I guess I do owe her one
for treating me to dinner.
Hey, Hamazura? Bring the car.
[MAN A]
So this is an Indian Poker card.
And get rid of her cell phone.
[MAN B]
Right.
What should we do
with the girl herself?
[MAN A] They said she
might have more info,
so we have to bring her with us.
[MAN B]
Torture? That's awful.
[MAN A] Oh, yeah.
I forgot you're a newbie.
There's supposedly
someone above us who has
the ability to make a person
spill their secrets
without breaking a sweat.
Which means if you or I
think anything out of line,
we won't be able to hide it.
So watch what you say,
especially around her.
[MAN B] I... I've got
nothing to hide, I swear.
[FRENDA]
Come on, get the lead out!
Hurry up!
All told, they're so far ahead
because you took too long.
It's literally been less than
five minutes
since you called me.
Find someone faster, I dare you.
[FRENDA] If you ever hope
to actually be useful,
you gotta get here in two.
[HAMAZURA]
Yeah, yeah.
[FRENDA] There, we're just
about caught up to them.
Now we just gotta make
a quick left turn.
Hey! They're below us!
What are you doing, Hamazura?
[HAMAZURA] I'm just driving
where you tell me to!
Ugh. Fine. I'll have to make do.
[HAMAZURA]
Whoa! Watch it!
Hey! Stop!
[yells]
[FRENDA] Grab my legs
and help support me!
Also, don't jerk the wheel,
it'll throw off my aim.
Who made you king?!
Okay.
There's a wind speed of two,
and they're at a range
of roughly 80.
So why don't I aim for
something besides the car?
[HAMAZURA whimpers]
What was that? What happened?
I dunno, but the road's
blocked now!
Again?
[MAN A]
The back, too?
[FRENDA]
Yes! Bullseye!
Did you see that? Easy stuff!
Okay Hamazura, you can go now.
How'd I end up like this?
Is this real? Am I dreaming?
Couldn't be.
I mean, if I was, there'd
be bunny girls all over me.
[FRENDA]
You're gross, you know that?
So, how's your work
coming along, my friend?
Can't get the prototype
done in time.
My presentation'll be nothing
but the promo video.
You did that last time.
Is everything okay?
I've had a few setbacks lately.
[RESEARCHER A]
Huh? What's wrong?
I thought... I saw something.
I really need to get some sleep.
[YOBOU]
Remove all ambient sounds.
In here, huh?
No surprise,
the security's rock solid.
Cracking it is
gonna be difficult.
Ignoring the alarms and brute
forcing my way through
would be easier, but I'd
rather not leave behind
any trace that I'm after
the tweezers if I can help it.
Nothing's been written
to this yet,
but it's a genuine
Indian Poker card.
Skimming the data on
the card inside the safe.
Not rock solid enough, huh?
I guess they didn't
anticipate an esper
who can duplicate
scent components
to come sneaking in.
[beeping]
What is it?
[MAN A]
Stuffed animals.
The stuffed animals exploded!
Stuffed animals?
We're completely
surrounded by the smoke.
I can't get a read
on what's happening!
We need you to send in backup!
[FRENDA chuckles]
[YOBOU] F team was sent
after a card with a low
probability of being
related to the tweezers.
If someone's attacking
them over it,
we've probably hit
an unlikely jackpot.
No choice. I gotta send her in.
I won't flip your
skirt anymore, okay?
[FRENDA]
Hey, wake up.
Hey!
[SATEN]
Huh? Where am I?
And why am I handcuffed?
I'll melt those off you,
so lie down
on your stomach for me.
You might lose
a wrist if you move,
so hold still, okay?
[SATEN]
Huh?
[STUDENT A]
Hey, Yumiya!
Yumiya? Hello?
Oh. Uh... Yes? What is it?
We were thinking, maybe,
today we'd venture outside
of the Garden of Learning
for a change of pace.
Would you like to
tag along with us?
[STUDENT B]
Um...
Wait.
Just to be totally certain,
you two are talking to me?
[STUDENTS]
Yes.
Um... I'd be delighted to come.
[phone rings]
[RAKKO]
I'm sorry for the interruption.
Excuse me for just a moment.
Ah, Mr. Yobou?
Yes. Huh?
You mean right now?
I was gonna go out with
some friends, but...
No. Yes. Yes. I understand.
[RAKKO]
Um...
I'm terribly sorry about this,
but something just came up.
Aww. That's unlucky timing.
[STUDENT B] All right,
some other time, then.
[RAKKO] Judging by the
state of the battlefield,
there are two targets.
One of them was
the captured girl,
which means the other
was the attacker.
Loafers and high heels.
They're both female.
They're 150 and 153
centimeters tall.
Also, considering the
communication log and debris,
the weapons they used were bombs
disguised as creepy dolls.
It's been a year and a half
since my classmates
last spoke to me.
I was this close to
escaping isolation,
and I would've become the
most popular girl in class!
Eventually, I'd have become
the school's idol!
My promising future was
destroyed just for this.
At the very least,
please let this hunt be
somewhat entertaining
for me.
[SATEN] Aww.
I must've lost my cell phone.
[FRENDA]
Well, all told,
you're pretty lucky
that's the worst thing
that happened to you.
[SATEN]
Huh?
I mean, those guys weren't
just a couple of punks
out pulling a prank.
Do you have any idea why
they might've been after you?
No! I got nothing going
on worth all that!
But either way, shouldn't
we contact Antiskill?
[FRENDA] Uh, yeah,
I already took care of that.
Wait, really? You did?
[FRENDA]
Yup yup.
Aww.
I must've lost that card
I just bought, too.
[FRENDA]
That, I doubt you'll get back.
Aww.
So anyway...
I did kinda save your life,
so if you wanted to thank me
somehow, I'd understand.
Uh... Okay.
[FRENDA]
On that note,
why don't we head on over
to the supermarket
and buy us a whole bunch
of canned mackerel!
It's always mackerel with you.
[RAKKO] That little blonde
girl still has it on her.
The scent of blood
from the capture team.
It's like a guide, leading
me straight to my prey.
Would you look at that?
I had to turn down a fun day
with my school friends
because of you, and you're
out here living it up!
How ironic.
That really pisses me off.
My orders are to capture the
black-haired one alive, but...
I'm free to hunt
the other one, right?
I wonder what I should
have you make for me.
Curry is, all told,
the obvious choice.
But as far as other dishes
that are good with mackerel,
we've got options.
[RAKKO chuckles]
[SATEN] Canned mackerel curry,
ten-second cooking!
Empty the can into
a pot, water and all.
Add grated ginger
and whatever else.
Add a reasonable
amount of water.
Bring to a boil.
Dissolve in a good
amount of roux.
And that's it!
[FRENDA] For being so thrown
together, this is delicious!