[SATEN grunts]
[MIKOTO]
Ah!
Pretty sweet, right?
I'm a kendama pro.
Yeah, you're not kidding.
And you said you mastered
all that in one night?
[SATEN] Yep.
Anyone can with the right card.
All they gotta do
is choose and snooze.
It's crazy you can
learn while you sleep.
I had no idea you
could use Indian Poker
for something like that.
One person learned
a foreign language.
They just used a dream
of someone fluent.
And then there's
that one bowler.
They're a powerhouse
because of the skills
they learned from the
dream of a professional.
So next, I'm learning
pen-spinning tech.
[MIKOTO] Clearly she has a
preference for parlor tricks.
So what does that mean?
You know people who are
expert kendama players
and pen spinners?
[SATEN] Nah. I get them
through a Trader.
[MIKOTO]
A Trader?
In the early days,
all people could do
was trade cards
amongst their friends.
But that inevitably got
pretty boring after a while.
So lately, some
people have decided
to become Traders.
They'll have loads of cards
that are separated
into different ranks.
Which is good news for
your average consumer,
'cause you can generally
get the most popular
S and A-Rank cards
from a Trader now.
They usually accept trades of
a bunch of lower rank cards.
Or you can just pay
for them outright.
I ended up trading
for this one myself.
[MIKOTO]
Sounds familiar. Ugh.
[BOYS]
Blau! Blau! Blau! Blau!
[MIKOTO] I really hope those
kinds of cards haven't been
going around too much.
[MUGINO] Ah!
I can finally take a shower.
You can wipe blood away,
but the smell always
lingers in your hair.
[KINUHATA] Maybe if you
used your ability instead of
ultra-pummeling them.
[MUGINO] Yeah well, that target
today was kind of a pain
in the ass, right?
A quick Meltdowner blast
wouldn't have let me
vent my frustrations.
I'd probably still be pent up.
Takitsubo!
Would you mind grabbing me
the Cybele number 5?
[TAKITSUBO]
Hm?
The one with the orange label?
[MUGINO]
That's the one.
[TAKITSUBO]
Here.
[MUGINO]
Thanks!
[KINUHATA] Mugino and
Takitsubo are both sporting
some prime quality goods.
But taking my age and
height into consideration,
my figure is ideal!
Some may even venture to call it
the ultra-perfect body-type!
Besides, I'm not at the bottom.
That'd be Frenda.
[KINUHATA] Frenda, has your body
ultra-developed recently?
Huh? Uh, yeah,
I guess a little bit.
Maybe it's 'cause my little
sister's been rubbing them.
My bras have been
feeling tighter,
and I keep having to buy
new ones lately.
There are so many other
things I'd rather
be spending my money on,
but nope!
It's seriously becoming
a big problem!
Hey, I'm back.
Took you long enough.
[HAMAZURA] Ugh. Why do I
have to be an errand boy?
[MUGINO] Quit your griping
and hand it over already.
[HAMAZURA]
Here. Banana tea.
Awesome, thank you.
[HAMAZURA]
Black bean cider.
[FRENDA]
Thank you!
Oh. You weren't here to
tell me what you wanted,
so I grabbed you
a bunch, Kinuhata.
Pomegranate cola, guarana green
juice, and Musashino milk.
[COW moos]
Interesting choices.
Was there a particular reason
you picked out milk?
[HAMAZURA] Well, drinking
milk is supposed to be good
for growing kids.
[HAMAZURA yells]
Whoa! The hell was that for?
[KINUHATA] Hey! I didn't say
you were allowed to dodge me!
[MUGINO]
Don't kill him please.
Re-staffing our subsidiary
organizations is a real pain.
[HAMAZURA yells]
[KINUHATA]
This is ultra-aggravating.
Hey there.
Care to take a look?
I guess. Indian Poker, huh?
I am in a sour mood.
Maybe it'll help me alleviate
some of my stress.
[KINUHATA]
I don't know what to choose.
[GIRL A] I'll take this one,
that one, and that one.
[M TRADER A]
Okay, three C-Ranks.
Thank you!
[GIRL A]
Thank you, too!
[MIKOTO]
Oh.
That must be one of
those Traders Saten was
telling me about.
[M TRADER A]
So, nothing catch your eye?
I dunno. I'm ultra-lost here.
[M TRADER A]
I recommend this one.
It was created by
a Portuguese teacher.
Use this and you'll be
conversational by morning.
No thanks.
I'm not really interested in
the knowledge or skill types.
I'm looking for one where
I can experience
an ultra-good story.
And not an A-Rank one
made for amateurs, either.
I want an ultra-clever one.
Like a C-Rank or below,
with lots of personality.
Huh.
Well, different strokes for
different folks and all.
How 'bout you?
[MIKOTO]
Oh. I think I'll pass.
I've had an ultra-bad time
with these things.
Uh, hi.
Can I help you with something?
You're fine.
Railgun.
If Mugino were here, there'd be
an ultra-bloodbath,
but I have the day off.
Everything's fine.
Ho! Sounds like you got
unlucky and drew
a dud of a card, huh?
That's rough.
But don't give up on your
dreams 'cause of one failure!
You don't want to live a boring,
aimless life, right?
[MIKOTO]
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I noticed you don't have
any S-Rank cards on display.
Nah. Gotta keep
those close to me.
Plus, all I have right
now is this one.
It's not anything
perverted, is it?
You really think
I could deal those out
in the open like this?
If that's what
you're lookin' for,
head to the back alley.
Did it sound like
I was looking for one?
[M TRADER A]
Well, there's always this, then.
There's an interesting story
behind it, let me tell you.
The dream on this card
is of a brilliant scientist
who suddenly vanished.
Apparently he was
quite the whack job,
even by this city's standards.
And his final research
theme was aptly titled
the "Bust Upper."
There's a chance that the
essence of it is infused
within the very card
I hold in my hand.
Now, whether you
actually believe it or not
is up to--
[HAMAZURA] Well, drinking
milk is supposed to be good
for growing kids.
Growing kids. Growing kids.
[KINUHATA] It's ultra-easy to
beat a whipped subordinate
into shutting up.
But in this case, resorting
to violence feels like
admitting he's right.
If I'm going to knock
that stupid jerk
down a peg and
get him to respect me...
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but I had my
hand on this card first.
Don't give me that; my hands
were ultra-quick to grab it.
[MIKOTO] Unless my ears
were deceiving me,
I seem to recall you saying
you weren't interested
in knowledge and skill types.
For someone who had
an ultra-bad time
with a card and was
acting above it all,
you sure are changing your
tune all of a sudden, huh?
How strange.
Get your mitts off
this card already,
you dirty little runt.
Keep dreaming,
you ultra-hypocritical
washboard witch!
[MIKOTO] She's got spirit,
I'll give her that.
[KINUHATA] She doesn't know me,
and at this range,
I've got the upper hand.
This'll be ultra-easy.
Whoa! Hold on a sec!
If the film gets peeled off,
it'll become unstable!
And then nobody will
be able to use it!
[M TRADER A]
Ow...
Huh? Wha--
My cards! No!
No, no, no, no...
They're all mixed up!
I don't know which one
is which anymore!
I think the S-Rank
was silver-colored.
Well first off, there's a bunch
of other silver ones.
[M TRADER A]
Ugh! Now what do I do?
How about this?
I'll take your whole stock.
Uh, I guess that's fine,
if you're really okay with it.
[KINUHATA]
No. I'll pay for half of it.
[M TRADER A]
Huh?
Thank you.
[MIKOTO] After thinking
it through logically,
we both want the same thing.
The research within the card,
not the card itself.
And whichever one
of us hits the jackpot
can easily just share what
they learn with the other,
so there's no reason
for us to fight.
[KINUHATA] Yeah, butting heads
would be ultra-stupid.
Besides, we've got a lot
of cards to go through,
so if we both work on it...
[MIKOTO]
...we'll cut the time...
[KINUHATA]
...in half.
Us kindred spirits have
got to work together.
Let's hope for some
ultra-good luck.
[MIKOTO (YOSHIKAWA)] According
to the monthly measurements
of "my" body,
there was no change
in chest size at all
in the latter teen years!
And yet my classmate's
development has been
so extreme, her chest
might as well be
her true form!
No. Let's look
at this differently.
If there's no change
in my measurements,
all it means is that I'm
successfully holding on
to my youth.
There's still plenty
of time for a growth spurt.
My waist grew three centimeters?
[MIKOTO gasps]
No!
I can't keep hoping
I'll grow eventually.
Once I hit that age,
it's game over.
I gotta keep trying.
[KINUHATA]
Hm? What's this? A maid?
But this is an ultra-plain
looking room.
Why would they hire a maid?
Looks like a dorm room--
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Bam!
A pervert!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] My super-rare
petite-sized Leviathan Bra
Maid top has finally
arrived from London!
With this on,
you'll look just like
a fallen angel maid!
Even if you don't have
an hourglass figure.
If you don't get
that disgusting thing
out of my sight now,
you're ultra-dead.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Whoa-ho-ho!
Your refusal today is even
more extreme than usual!
However...
From the bottom of my heart,
I truly believe no one
in Academy City
would look more beautiful
in this crude outfit
than you.
If nothing else, I want
you to understand that.
[KINUHATA] This guy's
crazy, and not to mention dumb,
but his heart is sincere.
And deep down,
the owner of this dream
isn't against that.
It doesn't matter
what the world thinks.
As long as the man
I adore accepts me.
Then it doesn't matter
what my body is like.
That's what this
dream is saying.
And if you don't like that one,
I also have this maid swim--
Too bad my patience
is ultra-short
with perverts like this.
[MIKOTO]
He's late.
How dare someone like Yobou
keep me waiting for so long?
I'll have to punish him
for this later.
I'm being watched.
Is she hostile?
No, her body language is
that of a normal person.
She's got on a high-class suit,
and shoes well-worn
from walking.
There's a business
card in her pocket.
W-Wait! Is she about
to do what I think?
[F SCOUT A] Hello there! I'm a
producer for a talent agency.
How would you like
to be an idol?
[MIKOTO] The innocent young lady
from the Garden of Learning
in her brilliant debut!
I would be an instant sensation!
But no, if that were
to really happen,
I'd become alienated from
my classmates and friends!
I have to turn her down.
Excuse me.
Could I have a
moment of your time?
[MIKOTO]
H-H-Huh?
[F SCOUT A] Pardon my
abruptness, but would you like
to be an idol?
[KONGO laughs]
You are a woman of
discerning taste, I see!
However, I am still a student.
In order for me to
properly play that part,
I am afraid I must decline
your generous offer.
[MIKOTO] But our looks are
practically neck-and-neck.
And I was standing
in front of her,
she had to have seen me!
Why?
Of course!
I hate how much society
cares about bust sizes!
If mine were just five
centimeters larger, I'd be fine.
Imagine, being hurt by a friend
in a dream that someone
you don't even know had.
Though I gotta say, that outfit
emphasized the chest nicely.
I wonder if I can buy
that somewhere.
[KINUHATA]
First a maid, now a kunoichi .
Huh? A temptress scroll?
It must be a technique for
capturing male enemies.
[M NARRATOR A] "Use your
feminine form to the utmost.
The bigger your
breasts, the better."
"If you can control
his gaze in combat,
you can create an
opening to attack.
Your charms can be
useful in overcoming
even the most
insurmountable foe."
What a surprise!
Men really are nothing
but sentient trash.
[M NARRATOR A] "On those
occasions, forsake all sense
of shame.
However, feigning
bashfulness is permissible."
Ha! What's that
supposed to mean?
Girls who are well-endowed
don't have any shame
to begin with!
"My shoulders are stiff."
"Ooh, I don't have
any cute bras."
All they do is humblebrag!
[M NARRATOR A] "But there are
also shinobi who are not blessed
in the chest."
[KINUHATA]
Nobody asked you!
[M NARRATOR A] "For you,
there is always your legs!
Men can also be charmed
with the lower body.
Go ahead and show
off your inner thighs
to incite their lust."
I'm shocked!
This scroll actually
has some useful info.
[M NARRATOR A] "Though boobs
are in far greater demand.
You'll never beat them. Sorry."
[KINUHATA]
Oh, just shut up!
All I need to make
a man fall in line
are my two fists!
If you like big lumps
of fat that much,
you can eat fatty foods
for the rest of your life
and slowly die from gout,
you ultra dumbasses!
Excuse me, you're bothering
the other guests here.
Could you keep it down?
[KINUHATA]
I'm ultra-sorry.
[MIKOTO] I just so happen
to be a telekinetic as well.
It seems I'm significantly
more skilled at it--
I wish I could stop
thinking about that.
I was acting all smug
and ate my words.
So embarrassing.
[KOBAYASHI]
Are you still feeling down?
[MIKOTO]
Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI] The Daihasei
Festival is all in the past.
Try to cheer up.
I messed up big-time too,
but it doesn't bother
me anymore.
[MIKOTO]
But...
[KOBAYASHI] Our Queen told me
something that struck a chord
with me.
That feeling down is a waste
of our brain's resources.
So, come on,
shoulders back, chest out!
[MIKOTO] Yeah, well,
that might be good advice
for someone like you, Kobayashi,
but with my chest like this,
there's no point
in sticking it out.
Okay, that's enough!
If you think you can't be
confident at your size,
then what about all
the other smaller girls?
Have you ever thought
how those of us
who barely have a chest feel?
Get over yourself!
[M EMPLOYEE A]
Could you two leave now?
[KINUHATA]
Yeah.
Ugh. There're still some cards
we haven't gotten to check.
What do you want
to do about them?
Hmm. We could try this hotel
I know that's around the corner.
I really do apologize,
but unfortunately,
because of renovations,
our regular rooms
are closed for about a week.
[MIKOTO]
Well, there's the dorm,
but I'd need to jump
through hoops to get them
to allow a visitor
anywhere near it.
[KINUHATA] It's not like I can
realistically bring her back
to our hideout.
Plus, if Mugino saw me
hanging around Railgun,
things would get ultra-messy.
There's the outdoor lounge,
if it's still open.
[MIKOTO]
It is nice and warm out today.
Yeah, I think this'll
work ultra-fine.
Huh?
Okay, now this is different.
I usually turn into
somebody else.
Recall the moments you've
dreamt of a brighter future.
Wouldn't you say these
are also the times
when you're filled
with the most hope?
I guess?
Take, for example,
a woman's chest size.
Any girl would want
to grow into a body type
that people admire.
That much goes without saying,
but the rate of growth
and the pure excitement
you feel as you gradually
transform into
your ideal figure.
That period of optimism
and anticipation
is the sweetest moment
of your whole life.
However, we're faced
with numerous obstacles
over the course of our lives.
They throw a wet blanket
over our hopes
for the future.
For instance, a threat
you cannot ignore.
But then, by removing
such a threat,
one may inadvertently
bring out yet another,
even greater threat.
If that happened,
what would you do?
[MIKOTO]
That was a weird dream.
[SPHINX meows]
We went through
every single one,
and the Bust Upper was
nowhere to be found.
That trader.
The next time I see him,
I'll ultra-kill him!
[MIKOTO] I should have trusted
my gut from the get-go.
A card like that is way
too specific to really exist.
[KINUHATA] It's nothing
but an urban legend.
And a baseless one, too.
[MIKOTO] And the researcher
mysteriously vanished?
Not suspicious at all!
[KINUHATA]
Even for a made-up story,
the guy clearly didn't
put much effort into it.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
How was I supposed to know
you hated milk so much?
I just figured it's the go-to
when you wanna get taller.
Get taller?
Uh, yeah.
Don't you remember?
That time I made you
a fake student ID?
We wanted to get you into
that R-rated movie.
The lady behind the counter
was totally onto us,
but she let us through.
I wish I was taller.
Life would be so much easier.
Y'get me?
So when I saw some milk,
I thought you might want it.
[HAMAZURA yells]
[HAMAZURA] Hey! Wh--
What did you do that for?
[KINUHATA]
That was ultra-misleading!
[MIKOTO] So anyway, there
was this girl who kept going
"ultra" this and "ultra" that.
We kinda got off on
the wrong foot at first,
but after we talked for a bit,
I realized she was a
surprisingly good person.
Very interesting,
but don't you think it's time
we went to bed?
I slept pretty
much the entire day,
so I'm wide awake.
Oh, speaking of...
Let me tell you about
this one dream.
There was this street
performer girl,
and we spoke for a bit.
Her figure was like mine,
but she was wearing
this revealing outfit.
And she was so confident in it.
[KUROKO]
I'm so tired.
Sissy.
I know I'm always saying
how I'd love for you
and I to spend
the night together,
but I must confess, this is
not the way I meant it.
Check it. Pretty impressive,
don't ya think?
[UIHARU] Wow, you really
got that good overnight?
Sure did! This just
gets better by the day!
For my next one, I'm lookin'
for a card master.
I wanna build the
best house of cards!
A house of cards this time, huh?
That'll fit right in with all
the other useless skills
you've learned.
But hey, do what
makes you happy.
Aww...
I wish nighttime would
get here already.
Did you see that? Look at her!
Her boobs are gigantic!
[UIHARU] Hey! You can't
just say that, Saten!
[SATEN]
Oh, what's the harm?
[KINUHATA]
Well that was, overall,
an ultra-awful experience.
So, what are you up to, Frenda?
[FRENDA] Just texting
with someone. A friend.
[MUGINO]
Let's see.
"I got pounded on
by my associate.
She has gorilla power."
Now who might that be about?
[FRENDA]
Uh, definitely not anyone here!