[MIKOTO]
Uh... Kuroko.
This is a joke.
You're all just trying
to pull my leg, right?
No idea what you're
talking about.
[MIKOTO]
Right, Uiharu? Saten?
That's weird, why would
she know our names?
[UIHARU] I imagine Shirai
must have told her.
I didn't.
We aren't even acquainted.
I couldn't have.
Listen, I don't know
where you heard about
the three of us, or who told
you all of our names.
But if you need help,
or you're in trouble,
I'll hear you out.
I am a member of Judgment.
No. That's okay.
[MIKOTO] You've really
done it now, Shokuho!
You've decided to mess
with my friends' heads?
How dare you!
This goes way beyond
just screwing around!
If I show them Kuroko's
and my dorm room,
or some photo albums,
I should be able to convince
them that their memories
are being manipulated.
But... Would they even
cooperate with me
long enough for that?
They see me as a total stranger.
I don't want to drag
them into it like this.
[F STUDENT 04D]
Misaka?
It's time for the next event;
we need to start getting ready.
[MIKOTO]
What is Shokuho's goal here?
And now that she has
me under surveillance,
can I even do anything about it?
[AWATSUKI] You're really
in top form today, Kongo.
Yeah.
Even the announcers were
complimenting your performance.
[KONGO laughs]
Well, they must know
exemplary achievement
when they see it.
[KUROKO]
What was that all about?
Honestly? I wanted to
talk to her a little longer.
Did you actually?
Or were you just star struck
from meeting someone famous?
That was so weird.
It felt like she had something
she wanted to tell us.
[KONGO]
Is that Shirai?
Saten and Uiharu, too?
[SATEN]
Oh, Kongo. Hey, there!
[KONGO] It's good to see you
out of the hospital, Shirai.
As your replacement
in the festival games,
I've made sure to take first
place as often as possible.
[laughs]
Um, why in such a dour mood?
You must know there's
a girl they call "Railgun"
who goes to our school, right?
Well, we were
just strolling along,
and out of nowhere,
she decided to shout at us.
Then she accused us
of playing a joke on her,
even though she came up to us!
Oh.
Anyway, thanks for taking
my place in the festival,
and best of luck.
[KONGO]
Of course.
Uiharu!
[UIHARU]
See you around.
--[AWATSUKI] Yeah.
--Take care.
[AWATSUKI]
I'm guessing that she and Misaka
are having a fight or something?
[WANNAI] They usually get
along so well with each other.
[UIHARU]
Wow, Shirai.
I didn't realize you were signed
up for this many events.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
And they're all
pair events, too.
They are?
[RADIO DJ A] Our next paired
event is the Balloon Sandwich!
Each team holds
a balloon between them
without using their hands,
and races it
to the finish line!
But if the balloon breaks,
that team is disqualified!
[MIKOTO] Now really isn't
the time for playing games.
I have to get out of here
somehow and go looking for her.
[KONGO]
Misaka? It's time.
We need to blow up this
balloon soon, so may I?
Oh! Mm-hmm.
[KUROKO]
All right, Sissy, go ahead!
Embrace me!
Hold your partner Kuroko in
those beautiful arms!
[MIKOTO]
Hey! Stop it!
If the balloon breaks,
we're out, you know!
[MIKOTO] She couldn't control
herself, so we didn't get
any actual practice in.
[KUROKO] Don't you think
it's kind of inappropriate
to shout my name
out to the world?
[KONGO] I forgot to mention,
I had no idea
that you had a twin sister!
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
Yesterday,
during Balloon Hunter,
that was your sister
who entered, was it not?
Are you serious?
You could tell that wasn't me?
Yes, of course!
I have quite the discerning eye,
if I do say so myself.
Plus, there is a subtle
difference in the air
you both carry about you.
I need to ask you for a favor!
It's really important.
[CROWD clapping]
[M CROWD A] That's another
win for Tokiwadai!
[M CROWD B] They are one
of the top five schools.
[F STAFF A]
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
[KONGO]
Ugh!
What a despicable,
cruel thing Misaki Shokuho
has done to you!
Whoa, Kongo!
Turn it down a notch.
She kidnapped your sister.
And that's to say nothing
of manipulating
your close friends' memories.
She is not fit to be
a student at Tokiwadai.
I know how serious this is,
and I want to help you.
I can go look into your sister.
Can I count on you
to keep the attention
of Shokuho's clique off of me?
I'll try.
Sorry for getting you
caught up in all this.
Listen.
Whatever you do,
don't get in over your head.
The scary thing about this
is that we don't know
what she's thinking.
If you can find me
a strong enough lead,
I can handle the rest by myself.
Hold on.
You shouldn't trust
any info given to you.
Even if it's coming from me.
Wait, why not?
[KONGO] Because Misaki Shokuho
could have already
brainwashed me by the time
I report back to you.
Any information I give you
could be leading you
straight into a trap.
You must plan around
that very real possibility.
Really?
[KONGO]
Yes.
I'm sorry, I know I'm planting a
crushing seed of distrust.
But don't worry, Misaka.
I will bring you
not information,
but your sister herself.
I hate to do this after
telling you not to trust me,
but please believe me,
and wait for my return.
Kongo.
[F STUDENT 04D]
Way to win first place.
Impressive as always.
Oh. Thank you.
[KONGO] She could have easily
turned Shirai and the others
directly against Misaka,
but didn't.
Which means she must
not have seen a need to.
If her goal revolves
around the sister,
then this was likely just
to buy her some time.
She only hopes to keep
Misaka away from her
until she fulfills her plan.
I don't have any time to lose.
[MISAKA 10032 panting]
[MIKOTO]
Don't do anything crazy, Kongo.
This isn't your problem.
So please don't get
hurt for my sake.
[HOKAZE]
Misaka?
Your cell phone.
[MIKOTO]
Oh, no. Is she onto me?
That's the "Lovely Mitten
Gekota" model,
if I'm not mistaken.
[MIKOTO]
Huh? Yeah, it is.
[gasps]
It so happens I have one, too.
[MIKOTO]
Pyonko?!
[HOKAZE] I saw the Gekota
strap you have on your bag,
and I have been wondering
if you were into them since.
[MIKOTO]
So that's why.
My, isn't this nice?
I've always wanted to sit
down and have a nice,
long chat with you.
I wish they weren't labeled
as being for children.
It makes things so awkward.
I get funny looks around
town from mothers
with their children.
[MIKOTO]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
My dorm rules keep me
from lining up early
on the day new merch
comes out, too.
[HOKAZE]
Speaking of new releases,
you know the regional series
that just went on sale?
Total slap in the face
for us Gekoers, right?
[MIKOTO]
Thank you!
They completely ignored
established canon!
[KOBAYASHI] This is all
going way over my head.
[MIKOTO] Aw, I still haven't
gotten my hands on one.
I keep checking online
auction sites, but no luck.
[HOKAZE] Well as it turns out,
I have two of them.
One to play with,
and one that I keep safe
for my collection.
--You have two?!
--Sure do.
Tell you what, if you try your
hardest in your events today,
I'll give you the
one I'm saving.
What? Really?
[MIKOTO]
Talk about an elaborate trap!
[BABA]
I'm telling you.
Mikoto Misaka has
definitely been neutralized.
I injected her with
the nanodevice;
there's no way she can move.
Besides, securing her
is your job, isn't it?
Are you absolutely sure she
wasn't just taken to a hospital?
[KOZAKU] Well, I won't
worry about that for now.
Baba, I have another job
that I'd like you to do.
[BABA]
Another?
[KOZAKU] Your target will be
Mikoto Misaka's clones.
The Sisters.
[KONGO] According to what
Misaka told me,
this is the location
where she and her sister
last saw each other.
So it's likely she came
into contact with Shokuho
somewhere nearby.
But there's something
off about this.
Misaka's sister isn't
as powerful as she is,
so she shouldn't be able
to avoid Mental Out.
Shokuho could have just
used her ability to order
her target to go wherever
she wanted her to.
So why did she go
through the extra effort
of capturing and relocating her?
What if it wasn't her ability,
but something else that caused
Misaka's sister to faint?
Perhaps Shokuho had
nothing to do with that.
If that is true, then there
may be a clue around here.
Is that... the character
Misaka likes so much?
Kerozo?
--[BIRD squawks]
--[CAT A meows]
[KONGO]
That kitten.
[CAT A meows]
[KONGO]
Hey, you!
Why don't you pick on
somebody your own size?
[CAT A meows]
Don't worry, little one,
you're all right now.
[CAT A meows]
[KONGO]
I'm sorry.
I know you must
still be frightened,
but right now I don't have
another moment to spare.
I'm in a rush!
[CAT A meows]
[KONGO] I really do not
have the time for this.
For now, I'll take
you to Judgment.
Hey, Kongo!
You seem to be in a hurry.
What's goin'--
[KONGO]
Perfect timing!
I hate to do this to you, but
would you mind hanging on to--
[WANNAI]
Hey.
By any chance, does this kitty
cat belong to Misaka?
[KONGO]
Huh? Does it?
Well, I'm not 100% sure,
but yeah, I think so.
It looks just like the cat
I took care of for her
during the Balloon
Hunter competition.
Wait, Balloon Hunter?
Then wouldn't that mean
the cat is Misaka's sister's?
Did you just say
Misaka has a sister?
First I'm hearing of it.
I'm sorry.
I really don't have the time
to go into much detail
at the moment,
but Misaka asked me to help
look for her missing sister.
I'm trying to assist
however I can.
She's missing?
[KONGO]
Yes.
I was checking the area
she was last seen,
and I stumbled upon this cat.
[WANNAI]
Well...
I'm still a little lost here,
but I know a psychometrer
on the swim team
who can mediate with animals.
It's possible that we could
get her to make contact
with the cat.
[KONGO]
That's great!
Check it out, Mom!
A robot dog!
[MOTHER A]
Wow, you're right.
Well, that's Academy
City for you.
[CROWD chattering]
[KONGO] We'll find Misaka's
sister in no time
if this works out. All we need
is a little bit of luck!
[BABA]
A Tokiwadai student.
Misaka's sister? Interesting.
[WANNAI] I left my phone
in a storage locker
by the school garden.
I'll go call her; stay here!
All right, hurry back!
To think this little kitty
could be a lead.
That girl possessing psychometry
is probably far enough
removed from Misaka that Shokuho
won't have done anything to her.
I brought your darling
sister back to you,
just as promised!
[MIKOTO]
Wow, Kongo, thank you!
You saved the day!
Oh, I was just doing
the right thing!
[BABA]
Excuse me.
Hello. What is it?
I was actually hoping I could
have a word with you.
[KONGO] Um, I am afraid
I have little time right--
[BABA] It concerns
Mikoto Misaka's sister,
if that changes anything.
There are so many
people around here.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
[SATEN]
Whoa.
A Daihasei Festival
limited edition, huh?
I'm sure she already knows
about it, but just in case.
I'd better ask.
[SATEN]
Wait, who?
Kongo? And...
Who is that?
[BABA]
So when you say "sister,"
I have to imagine that comes
from the "Sisters" nickname.
Right?
Unless she was
introduced to you as
an actual biological sister.
Well, I guess it doesn't matter.
See, I was asked to protect
this "sister" of hers myself,
so you're not the only
one looking out for her.
If you wouldn't mind,
I think it'd be smart
to pool our
information together.
[KONGO] While I appreciate
your offer, the fact is
I don't know who you
are or your motives
for seeking Misaka's sister.
And without those,
I can't trust you.
Explain yourself first,
then we'll talk.
[BABA] Yeah, that's about
what I expected. But...
I'd suggest we skip that
and jump straight to the part
where you tell me all about
that lead you've found.
Because if you don't...
[KONGO gasps]
[KONGO]
A robot?!
I'll just end up using
my special drugs
to force it out of you anyway.
I would advise you
to keep your distance!
I was extremely suspicious
from the start,
so naturally I assumed he
was working with Shokuho.
But if he doesn't know
where Misaka's sister is,
then perhaps not.
I tagged along,
thinking maybe I could get
some information out of him.
But regardless,
it does not change the fact...
...that he is Misaka's enemy.
[GIRL B laughs]
Aww! It's so cute!
[MIKOTO] I need to find a way
to get out of here, and soon.
[GIRL B]
No! My balloon!
[MIKOTO]
That'll work!
[MIKOTO gasps]
[GIRL B]
Whoa.
--Thank you so much, miss!
--Misaka, look out!
[MIKOTO]
Uh-oh!
I accidentally jumped aboard!
And now I can't get down!
[MIKOTO] There! That was just
an unfortunate accident,
so they can't blame me!
[KOBAYASHI] Misaka, please
wait for us at the next stop;
we'll come get you.
[MIKOTO] I'm outside of
her telepathic range.
Perfect!
[thumping]
You aren't hurt, are you?
You look fine.
Yes.
We just caught up
with her and she's safe.
We'll get off at
the next station.
[MIKOTO] Good to know
I'm dealing with people
who can catch up
to a speeding train
without breaking a sweat.
I'm really sorry about this.
[KONGO gasps]
You're not getting away.
I made sure to look
into your ability
after one of your events.
I know you can create
air jets on objects
and propel them forward.
But then, there's nothing
here for you to use
that ability on.
Which is exactly why
I led you to this spot.
If you just give up and tell
me what I want to know,
you'll save yourself
a lot of pain.
And if you don't...
[BABA]
What?!
[KONGO] I regret to inform
you that you've made
two miscalculations regarding
my ability, Aero Hand.
First of all, you assumed
I had limitations
on where I can place my jets.
[BABA] You can just put
them on the ground?
And your second mistake...
[BABA]
The parabolic antenna?!
[KONGO] ...is that you failed to
realize I can gather my jets
for a massive output that
can launch heavy equipment
into the stratosphere!
With my power, I can send
absolutely anything flying!
[KONGO] And I can just pay
for whatever I destroy!
Frankly, I don't see
any other option
but for you to give up.
I had no idea her ability
could be this powerful.
The Great Dane Types
aren't gonna cut it.
If I can just create
a brief opening...
[CAT A meows]
[BABA chuckles]
[AWATSUKI] Hmm.
I don't see Kongo anywhere.
Are you sure this
is where you left her?
Yes. I'm certain.
I told her I had
to go grab my phone
but to wait right here.
Sorry for making you
come all the way out here
for nothing.
It's cool! Don't worry about it.
And if you find her,
feel free to hit me up again.
See ya!
[AWATSUKI] I wonder where
she could have gone.
[WANNAI]
Hey, Saten.
Hey!
We keep running into each other.
[AWATSUKI] Did you happen
to see Kongo around here?
[KONGO grunts]
[CAT A meows]
[KONGO]
I... suddenly feel faint.
[BABA]
Look at that.
I went for the cat, and you
actually leapt in to defend it.
Don't bother trying to move.
I just injected you with a
nanodevice that deprives you
of control over your body.
I was hoping I wouldn't
have to use it
since they're so expensive.
[KONGO]
At least let this little cat...
...find its way back to Misaka.
Let me guess.
You're doing this because
Misaka asked you to?
For nothing in return?
All for someone else?
It's pretty funny that
you've put yourself
in this situation for no reason.
And that Misaka's a
real piece of work, too.
I mean, convincing you,
who has nothing to do with this,
to do the dirty work for her?
I swear, those Level 5s are
all the same on the inside.
[KONGO]
You take that back.
Hear me?
Misaka is not someone
who would take advantage
of other people like that.
This is something I decided
to do all on my own.
Perhaps someone
like you isn't capable
of understanding that.
[KONGO grunts]
Oh, shut up!
You think you're better than me?
Is that it?
Even though you couldn't
do a thing to stop me?
Huh?!
You're a complete
waste of space!
You understand?!
That Misaka's a disaster.
If you're the best cannon
fodder she could rummage up...
She should've sent someone bet--
Whoa, that was a close one.
Can't have her dying before
I get that info out of her.
Ah, man.
For a piece of trash, you're
pretty good at pissing me off.
All right, Great Dane Types,
carry this girl away--
[SATEN]
Kongo?!
How awful. What happened?
Did you do this to her?
What are you gonna
do about it if I did?
I was just taking
out the garbage.
Does it even matter?
[SATEN]
What?
[BABA]
It's funny.
That girl said she's here
on behalf of Mikoto Misaka.
And the fact that she's
doing this for no gain
makes her second-rate.
But since she couldn't
even get the job done,
I'd say in reality,
she's lower than third-rate.
Truly human trash.
Shut your mouth!
[WANNAI] Saten, I'm sorry
to ask this of you,
but could you take
Kongo and that cat
and move them to
someplace safe for us?
But...
[AWATSUKI]
If we don't keep that cat safe,
everything Kongo's done
will have been for nothing.
[WANNAI]
Besides...
...I know you're angry.
[AWATSUKI] But you're
not the only one here...
...who's utterly
furious right now.
[WANNAI]
Awatsuki.
This is the first time I've ever
felt such a strong instinct
--to fight!
--[AWATSUKI] Me too, Wannai.
I think we need to have
a word with that boy
who disrespected Kongo!
[WANNAI]
Let's go!
[BOTH] For a high-schooler,
you have the vocabulary
of a middle-schooler!