[WANNAI]
Besides...
I know you're angry.
[AWATSUKI] But you're
not the only one here...
...who's utterly
furious right now.
[BABA] You're mad because
I beat up your friend?
What good does that do you?
You're so codependent.
[CAT meows]
Go ahead, pretend to be
heroes all you want.
But I guarantee,
when you're lying on
the ground in pieces,
you're just going to blame
the weakling you were
trying to help.
Since you girls obviously have
no sense of imagination,
you'll have to experience
it for yourself
to see what I mean.
[SATEN gasps]
Water?
[SATEN] I've always heard that
unconscious people were heavy,
but...
Wait, she's lighter.
Hey, did you use your
ability, Awatsuki?
I'm afraid it won't
last very long.
Please, take her away
while you can.
[BABA]
Whoa, there!
Do you really think I'm
just going to let you
walk away from this?
[SATEN gasps]
Is that all?
My Great Dane Types
can jump over that easily!
[BABA]
There goes my only lead!
Just kidding.
The Mosquito Type may
have ejected its nanodevice,
but it can still be used
as a GPS transmitter.
Now there's no need to rush.
I'll track her down later.
And in the meantime...
...I'll take care of these two.
[SATEN panting]
[CAT meows]
Okay, now I gotta call
an ambulance and Antiskill.
I hope Wannai and Awatsuki
are gonna be okay
on their own.
[phone buzzes]
Yeah?
[KOZAKU]
Well, Baba?
Is everything going smoothly?
Yup. Without a hitch.
[BABA grunts]
What are you mutts doing?!
Y'gotta dodge that!
[KOZAKU]
What was that?
Don't tell me you're
in a fight right now.
[BABA]
It just sort of happened.
This might take a little more
time than I thought.
You think you're gonna be okay?
Want some backup?
[BABA]
I'm fine. No need.
Are you sure?
I'm so worried about you,
I can't concentrate
on anything else.
[BABA]
Such a liar.
[KOZAKU] Okay, how about
I go after your lead for you?
I still haven't learned
anything that would help
get that info out of her.
But I'm sure they've
contacted Antiskill,
so I'd appreciate it if you
could delay their arrival.
Idiot.
You really think I'd just let
you steal all of my credit?
Anyway.
Those two didn't compete in
the Balloon Hunter competition,
so I haven't checked
out their abilities.
But the one with the chestnut
hair must have Hydro Hand.
That's dangerous for
the Great Dane Types
if they get drawn
into the water.
Though she doesn't seem
strong enough to land
a fatal blow while
fighting on land.
As for the one with the braids,
maybe telekinesis?
Regardless, seeing as
how she can't pin down
any of my robotic canines,
she clearly doesn't have
all that much power.
Their abilities put them
both around Level 3.
I doubt they've had much
combat experience,
but they seem to be
getting by pretty well
by attacking in sync.
They're taking my pawns
out slowly but surely.
[clapping]
Not bad, not bad at all.
I'm looking for Mikoto
Misaka's "Sister,"
or rather, her younger twin.
Hey, chestnut hair.
Your friend.
You called her
Mitsuko Kongo, right?
I believe you two
were discussing a way
that you could
locate this sister?
Would you mind telling me
how you planned on doing that?
I'm not asking for it
for free, of course.
In this capsule,
I have a nanodevice.
A powerful machine that can
immobilize anyone I want.
And one's inside
Mitsuko Kongo right now.
Crazy, I know.
All it takes is a mosquito bite,
and you're down.
I touched Kongo before.
It felt like she had
a pretty high fever.
So I think there's probably
some truth to what
he's telling us.
It's quite tricky to
remove a nanodevice
once it's been
successfully injected.
But maybe if you had this,
you could analyze it
and find some sort
of shutdown command.
Would you like to exchange
your information for it?
I mean, you want to help
your friend, don't you?
We're not telling you anything.
No matter what you offer.
However, we will be
taking that nanodevice.
Even if it means using force!
Well, so much for
civil negotiations.
Guess that's okay.
One of these two boxes
has already been used,
and is empty.
The other one has a fresh
nanodevice inside of it.
Want to guess
which one is which?
Awatsuki!
On it!
[BABA] They know it's a trap,
and they still split up.
These girls are a joke.
[WANNAI grunts]
Where are you going?
Stop right there!
What's the matter?
You're gonna have to start
chasing me or I'll get away!
Oh, interesting.
Looks like Kongo and
Misaka competed together
in the Balloon Sandwich event.
Didn't expect that.
I wonder if those two
are close friends.
[KUROKO]
Railgun.
Hmm. I swear, every time
I think about that girl,
it's like my chest feels tight,
and I get all jittery!
I don't even want
to think about her!
She's so conceited and rude.
All she's got going for her
is that pretty face!
Sounds like you've been
thinking about her
a whole lot, huh?
That must have been
one fateful encounter
between you two.
You never know,
maybe you guys would make
a good pair if you got
to know each other.
[KUROKO] Huh?!
Who, you mean me and that girl?
That's ridiculous!
You must be joking;
that could never happen.
Okay.
[KUROKO grunts]
Hold on, where are you going?
[KUROKO]
I should be fine on my own now!
Let's start
patrolling separately.
We'll cover more ground.
[F STUDENT C] I can't believe
how long the line
to get a taxi was.
The entire area's packed
with spectators.
Hopefully there'll be
room on the bus.
[MIKOTO] I can't let Kongo
do all of the legwork.
I have to get away from them.
[siren wailing]
[F STUDENT C] Oh, no.
I wonder what that's about.
[F STUDENT B] I heard a lot of
people have been getting
heatstroke lately. Maybe that?
We should be careful that
doesn't happen to one of us.
[F STUDENT B] They say hydration
and electrolytes are key!
[MIKOTO gasps]
Is that...?
--Hey, Saten!
--Misaka!
Oh. It's you.
Hi again, Misaka.
[MIKOTO]
What happened?
Why were you in an ambula--
Get back here!
[WANNAI grunts]
[BABA]
Huh.
Even away from the pond,
she can control
a pretty decent amount of water.
The Great Dane Type
that sucked up
some of the water
she was controlling
was destroyed from the inside.
I guess once the water
is under her command,
she can control it
without even seeing it.
I pretty much have her analyzed.
Espers like her usually have
a limit on the weight
and effective range of
the water they can control,
and both are based
on their level.
If I can get her far enough
away from the pond,
she can't replenish
her water supply.
Then, if I pretend
to leave myself open
within range of her attacks...
[WANNAI grunts]
Aw, sorry.
I knew it.
She can't control
water that's detached.
Then there's the other
limitation that espers
with Hydro Hand have.
The amount of water streams
they can control at once.
[WANNAI grunts]
[BABA] Physical attacks
against water may look futile
at first glance,
but every time she deflects,
her defense is slowly worn away.
It's clear as day
that you only know
how to fight head-on,
you sheltered little brat.
And I love watching
you lose hope.
And when I got there,
Kongo was on the ground.
There was this creepy guy
controlling robot dogs,
and Wannai and Awatsuki
started fighting him.
[MIKOTO]
This is my fault.
I was naive.
I thought this was just
part of the usual rivalry
between us.
That she was just messing
with me because
she doesn't like me.
That we're classmates.
So she'd never really hurt us,
even if she hates me.
We're ready for your friend.
You're welcome to wait
over here if you'd like.
Oh, okay. Huh?
Misaka. Where are you going?
It's obvious you have a
situation on your hands, but--
Move it.
I'm sorry.
But we really should wait
for the other members
of the clique to get here--
I said move.
Unless you're ready to
kill me right here and now,
then move.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[SATEN]
Misaka?
[WANNAI grunts]
[BABA]
Well that's a surprise.
I figured you were gonna
run out of water
with two of my dogs
still standing.
I'm impressed you beat them,
even if you used up your water.
But look.
You've got none left
to protect yourself.
What can you do now?
As part of the curriculum
at Tokiwadai,
we're taught a list of
self-defense techniques.
I don't see any weapons on you,
so I don't need
my ability for this.
Ha! How courageous of you.
But unfortunately,
I'm not a fan of how barbaric
fist fights tend to be.
So I think I'll have
these reserve forces
I've been saving
finish you instead.
I have a plan for everything,
because I know
basic field tactics.
[AWATSUKI] It hasn't gotten
away, but it's also maintaining
a distance from me.
It must be trying
to buy some time
by keeping me
separated from Wannai.
I have to hurry.
That should work.
[AWATSUKI grunts]
Guess it didn't expect me
to take a shortcut.
This is all... debris from
Kongo using her ability.
I did a complete lap
without even noticing it.
Sorry, uh, not to toot
my own horn,
but I'm actually a lot
stronger than I look.
At least, I think.
If you had any water left,
I'd be willing to bet
good money that this line
is your maximum range.
[chuckles]
Being the exceptionally
perceptive young man
that I am,
well, it didn't take much
to figure you out.
We're talking what,
18 meters give or take?
Let's see, what else?
I can tell the max volume you
can control is 300 liters,
and the number of water
streams you can control
at one time is limited to three.
So what'll you do now?
Fight hand to hand
and go out a hero?
Bow down and beg for your life?
Or, under the clear blue sky,
pray to God for a
sudden downpour?
Here, I'll pick for you!
None of the above.
Your only choice
is to curse yourself
for thoughtlessly
sticking your nose
where it didn't belong.
You're going to meet
the same fate as your friend.
Rain, huh?
Huh?
[WANNAI]
Speaking of, have you noticed?
This park has a network of
drains buried underneath it.
So that when it rains, the water
will flow into the pond.
Huh?
[WANNAI] I will admit that
you did an excellent job
analyzing my ability, but...
...you should have considered
what might be happening
outside of your vision.
[BABA yells]
[BABA]
What? Water?
Where'd it come from?
Is that a drain?
Don't tell me she's been
hiding it down there
since we left the pond?!
I can control four water
streams at a time.
Understand?
[BABA]
Four?!
[WANNAI] It looks like you
didn't have a plan for
this situation, did you?
What did you say again?
That this is basic
field tactics?
[BABA]
I can't get it off me!
I'm gonna drown!
I'll die at this rate!
Let's go you stupid mutts!
Do your job!
Suck up this water
before I suffocate!
[BABA coughs]
No... How could I forget?
Is that the last of
your robots, then?
[BABA] Damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it!
I have zero
Great Dane Types left!
No choice!
I can't believe I have
to use the last nanodevice
I got from the Doctor!
Have you decided to give up yet?
I said I didn't like
fistfights before,
but that doesn't mean
I can't hold my own in one.
I was trained in assassination
skills throughout my childhood.
Family situation, you see.
I know many techniques
that we're normally forbidden
from using.
But seeing as how you've
turned out to be so strong,
my hands are tied.
I just need to keep her
attention with these bluffs
long enough for the Mosquito
Type to inject her
with the nanodevice!
Almost there!
A little more!
[gasps]
It dropped?!
Is the battery dead?
No way, I just
activated the thing!
Wait, the way it's moving...
[AWATSUKI]
I'm glad to see you're safe.
[BABA yelps]
[WANNAI]
Awatsuki!
[AWATSUKI] The one I went
after turned out to be empty.
And based on his
behavior so far,
I figured if you got
the upper hand,
this guy would try
to use the nanodevice,
so I lowered the buoyancy
around you to zero.
And it looks like that
was the right decision.
[BABA]
Buoyancy?
You mean her ability
wasn't telekinesis?
It's buoyancy manipulation?
Wait a minute,
let's think this through!
Are you two espers
really planning on striking
an unarmed man?
I'm just a hired hand
in all of this!
And I can't do anything
with the mosquito robot now.
Look, it's dead on the ground!
Sure, maybe I was being
a little too rough
with your friend earlier,
but can't we just
agree to walk awa--
[BABA yells]
I apologize if I'm being
presumptuous here.
But I think the reason
you hate seeing us
stand up for a friend
is because you don't have
anyone who'd do that for you.
But it makes sense.
That happens when
you're condescending.
You've closed yourself off.
Unless you start
letting people in,
and show them that you're
willing to meet them halfway,
no one will want to help you.
[BABA yelling]
I'm not exactly experienced in
the ways of the world, either.
Hey.
You don't have to be
so hard on yourself.
I think that was good advice
and he needed to hear it.
I just hope he takes this
opportunity to rethink his ways.
[BABA panting]
Damn them!
Those girls think
they're better than me!
I'll make them pay
for looking down on me!
[BABA panting]
It's all intel.
If I'd only known
what their powers were
before going into that fight,
there's no way I would
have lost to them!
Mantis Type!
I didn't think I should use
you because you stick out,
but your power is in
a whole other league
from those glorified
tracking dogs.
Now that I know everything
about their abilities,
there's no way
I could possibly lose!
Go get 'em, Mantis Type!
This is payback.
Merely killing them isn't
gonna be enough anymore.
I'll capture and humiliate them!
I'll take some racy photos and
post 'em everywhere online!
I'll crush their dignity and
live stream it to the world!
And not only destroy them
mentally and physically...
I'll destroy their social
lives on top of it!
Then when they cry
and beg me to kill 'em...
[beeping]
That's the GPS signal
from the Mosquito Type
I attached to Mitsuko Kongo.
What's it doing here?
And why's it on a direct
path toward me?
What?! How?!
What is this?
Why is Mikoto Misaka here?
Impossible!
She shouldn't be able to move!
I shot the nanodevice into her!
Oh! That's gotta be it!
She's not the real
Misaka at all, is she?
That's one of the Sisters!
My luck's turning around!
I'll capture her
and redeem myself!
I can deal with those
other girls afterwards!
Mantis Type,
seize that girl! Now!
[BABA laughing]
It's...
...really her?
No. Stay back!
[BABA screaming]
[MIKOTO]
I know you can hear me.
I avoided the
communication system.
And I know where you are
from the comm signal.
[BABA yells]
[BABA]
Why won't it open?!
Don't tell me...
She's already taken over
the entire system?
[BABA yelps]
[MIKOTO] I'll be there shortly
to do to you what I did
to your robot friend.
[BABA yells]
At least, that's what
I'd like to do,
but taking into account
that you might be under
that girl's control...
...I'm gonna let you
go this time. But...
[BABA screams]
[MIKOTO]
Make no mistake.
If I ever see one
of these again,
or if they go near my friends...
...or if you so much as
look in their direction...
Then no matter where you are,
I swear I'll find you.
And crush you.
[KOZAKU]
Uh-oh.
What's the matter?
[KOZAKU]
It's Baba.
Sounds like he's
out of the picture.
[XÓCHITL]
As in what?
[KOZAKU]
He's lost all of his robo-pawns.
And now he's looking
to lay low somewhere.
What's more,
he says he's neutralized Misaka,
but now she's out and about.
I guess this means
I'll have to step in.
She's a tough one.
What do you mean?
Have you met her before?
[XÓCHITL]
Sort of.
Let's just say I've seen
her fight up close.
It'll be fine.
It's not like I have to totally
beat her or anything.
Everything will be okay
as long as we wrap this
up by the end of the day.
[SATEN] The key to this mystery
is "Auribus oculi
fideliores sunt."
[UIHARU]
"Auribus oculi fideliores sunt."
[KUROKO]
[SATEN]
Okay everyone, together now!
"Auribus oculi
fideliores snoot."
[SATEN] Wait, did one of us say
something different?