[KUROKO sighs]
What's up?
What are you sighing about?
Only my crushed dreams.
I'm finally out of
that lonely hospital.
I should be making
up for the nights
I've spent without you, but no,
we can't sleep in our dorms.
No sense sulking.
It's just Tokiwadai's custom
for students to stay
at a hotel with their families
during the Daihasei Festival.
[KUROKO]
Yes. I realize that.
I suppose I'll just
have to suffer
through nocturnal solitude.
On one condition.
As soon as the
festival is over...
...we will share a hot,
passionate night together.
[smooching]
Ugh.
Will you cut it out already?
[F STUDENT A]
Excuse me.
One extra-large, please.
[VENDOR] You got it!
Comin' right up. Just a second.
[MIKOTO]
Oh, yeah. I wonder what she got.
[KUROKO]
Sissy?
Oh, sorry.
Y'know what, Kuroko?
Is there any food you're
in the mood for?
If there is, it's my treat.
We should get something
for Uiharu and Saten
while we're at it.
I'm sure they'd like
a snack to munch on.
[KUROKO]
I can't decide.
But if it's a gift
from you, Sissy,
anything would be amazing.
Then again, if you're truly
offering me anything...
...I'd be a fool to not ask for
your half-eaten scra--
[MIKOTO yells]
Let's get to work!
Man, it almost looks like
a war was fought here.
Hey, Uiharu?
The schedule says this stadium
won't be used again today.
Which means I can
search all I want.
Just waiting on you
for some more info.
I know.
I've already started
looking, don't worry.
[SATEN] I wonder what
Shadow Metal even looks like.
Maybe it's in tiny little
particles, like gold dust.
Have you found any information
on the color or shape?
Hmm. It's the strangest thing.
I'm getting a bizarrely
large number of results,
especially for this topic.
And yet there's nothing
but vague nonsense
written in any of them.
That is weird.
But like they say, where there's
smoke, there's fire, right?
If there's really
that many results,
there's gotta be
some truth to this.
[UIHARU]
How optimistic.
[SATEN]
All right! Here we go!
Let's find some Shadow Metal!
Y'know, these results
really are odd.
[SATEN]
Ugh.
I'm not finding anything
here that's metallic.
Unless this roasted pebble
is somehow a chunk
of Shadow Metal in disguise.
Still nothing new
on my end, either.
And actually, no matter
how much I look,
I can't seem to find that
site you read about it on.
[SATEN]
Really? You sure?
That's weird.
I was just on there
a week ago, I swear.
[gasps]
You understand what this means,
don't you, Kazari?
We're in the midst
of a conspiracy!
And how's that?
[SATEN] They say if you
look for Shadow Metal,
you end up targeted by
a mysterious organization!
What if they shut down
the site because
we're getting too close
to the truth?
Oh. I can see you're working.
I came to drop off Kuroko.
Hey, would it be okay for me
to kill some time here
before my next event starts?
[SATEN] That's gotta be it.
I mean, what else could it be?
We have to get a move
on or the organization
will get to it first!
Makes sense.
But hold on, Saten, if these
people actually exist,
doesn't that mean you're
in considerable danger
right now?
Do my ears deceive me or
is she causing trouble again?
Huh? Danger?
[UIHARU] If an organization
that's willing to manipulate
public data to
monopolize Shadow Metal
found you searching for it,
you'd be in a tight spot.
Don't say that, Uiharu.
You're starting to freak me out.
I know, I'm sorry,
I was just kidding.
But that's what you get for
always flipping up my skirt.
Boo.
Who are you--?
Hey! Wait--!
Are you okay?
Saten, is everything okay?
What happened?
[UIHARU] I don't know,
but it sounded like Saten
was attacked by someone!
Uiharu, where is she?
School District 18,
the Kirigaoka grounds!
Sissy, let's go.
I'm coming--
[KUROKO]
You stay here to back us up.
Depending on what we find there,
we might need you at
the ready to contact Antiskill.
--But I--!
--[MIKOTO] Uiharu.
We've got this.
[SATEN grunts]
All right! All right, already,
just let me go!
[SATEN]
Stop it, that hurts!
Will you get off?
Wait, they look like...
What do you think you're doing?
--Uh, Sissy? Hang on--
--Let her go!
[SATEN, MIKOTO]
We're so sorry!
We're just doing our jobs.
We secure the school
grounds and prep rooms,
and thoroughly clean
them after each use.
You never know, some shady
character might show up
and try to collect samples
of high-level esper DNA.
In fact, we've stopped plenty
of attempts to do just that.
So think about it.
If we find someone suspicious,
we can't just let 'em go.
And I haven't even
mentioned you attacking us.
[SATEN]
You're absolutely right.
[MIKOTO]
We really screwed up!
If you've learned your lesson,
I'll let you off with a warning.
[SATEN]
Excuse me.
Totally unrelated, but have you
ever heard of Shadow Metal?
--[M WORKER A] Huh?
--Saten...
[SATEN] Not even the guys
who clean up after the festival
events have seen it.
[KUROKO] It sounds like the
Shadow Metal rumors started
because people were suspicious
of the tight security
around school grounds
that was meant to prevent
the leaking of DNA maps.
The power of the human
imagination strikes again.
This is precisely the reason
I told you not to get
caught up in wild
hearsay like this.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
[KUROKO]
You, too, Sissy!
Sorry I freaked out.
[KUROKO] See?
Was that so hard? Really?
If you two would just pay
attention to what I tell you
every day, you wouldn't
have these problems!
[UIHARU sighs]
I'm just glad that
everyone's safe and sound.
Sometimes I forget how much
of a troublemaker Saten can be.
Oh, yeah.
These search results really
are abnormal, aren't they?
Is it possible someone spread
all of this dummy data
online in the last week
to keep anyone from finding
what Saten found?
Or maybe to conceal some
embarrassing information
that was on the site?
Yeah right.
I guess Saten's starting
to rub off on me.
Although, if this dummy data
is something that was
automatically generated,
then by analyzing its pattern,
I may be able
to recreate the original site.
That's a tall order, but...
"Boom."
[KEITZ]
Well, well. Curious.
[UIHARU]
Yup.
This is exactly the kind
of site Saten told me about.
But I'm not seeing anything
on here worth hiding.
The information it has
on Shadow Metal
is pretty much what
Saten already told me.
"A very valuable orange."
"Disciplinary Guides."
"A DNA computer that
produces abilities"?
Huh?
Isn't the person
in this picture...?
We're back.
[UIHARU]
Hi everyone!
[SATEN] Ugh. Sorry about
all this, Misaka.
Hey.
I acted without thinking
things through, too.
We're both to blame,
I can't judge.
Sorry I dragged you
into this too, Uiharu.
I'm just happy
everything worked out.
[SATEN] So, have you
found anything new out
--since we last--
--[MIKOTO, KUROKO] Stop it!
[KUROKO] How have you
not learned your lesson?
[SATEN]
I, uh...
Well...
I did look into it on my own
after everything calmed down,
though I didn't find
anything worth mentioning.
But I did find some good
intel that's totally unrelated.
It turns out there's a secret
spot where we can get
an up close and personal view
of the night parade fireworks!
[SATEN]
Whoa. Really?
[KUROKO] Is this location
somewhere we can legally get to?
[UIHARU]
Yup! It's just not well known.
I made sure to double check.
[MIKOTO]
Oh, yeah? That sounds nice.
Let's check it out!
[KUROKO]
They're so pretty.
[SATEN] They do this every night
during the Daihasei Festival,
right?
[UIHARU]
Mm-hmm. That's right.
Then... Let's all
do this again, okay?
--[SATEN, UIHARU] Yeah!
--[KUROKO] Okay!
[MIKOTO yawns]
I just can't get a good
night's sleep without
my own pillow.
[F TOKIWADAI B]
So, where's the Queen?
[KOBAYASHI] No one has
seen her since last night.
Oh. Misaka, good morning.
Yeah, right back at you.
[F TOKIWADAI 02B]
What does that mean, then?
[MIKOTO] I think they're
a part of Shokuho's clique.
[WANNAI]
Misaka.
[MIKOTO]
Hey, Wannai. Morning.
Good morning to you, too.
So, um...
I don't mean to sound like
I'm rushing you or anything,
but when can I expect
my gym clothes back?
Gym clothes?
Huh?! She hasn't come
to return them yet?
[WANNAI]
Pardon?
I'm sorry! I mean...
Uh... Coffee!
I spilled coffee on them!
And even if I had them cleaned,
there would still be a stain,
so let me buy you new ones.
I'll order another set
for you right now!
Oh, please!
You really don't need
to go to all that trouble!
[MISUZU]
Oh, Tabikake.
[MIKOTO] A whole night has
passed and she hasn't returned
them yet?
What, is she pretending
to be me so she can goof off?
No. She wouldn't do that.
I've got... a bad feeling
about this.
[MIKOTO]
Okay.
I found the surveillance
cameras near where we
split up yesterday.
If I look through
the recordings,
I should be able
to follow her trail.
Nothing here. Next.
Good thing I have
some free time today.
Maybe I'm getting
worried over nothing.
But then again,
those girls' bodies do need
regular maintenance
to keep healthy.
So if something
happened to her...
An ambulance?
[MIKOTO]
There she is. That's her!
She's passed out.
Is she hurt, or sick?
This is not the time
to get emotional.
Which jurisdiction is this?
[MIKOTO]
Found it.
This should be the
ambulance from the footage.
[MIKOTO]
Excuse me!
--Huh?
I've got a question.
Who was driving this yesterday?
Yesterday?
That would be the two of us.
'Kay, then a follow-up.
Did you transport a girl
with shoulder-length
brownish hair a
little before noon?
Oh, that girl.
Yeah, come to think
of it, we did.
Really? That girl is
a friend of mine.
Could you please
tell me which hospital
you took her to so
I can go check on her?
It's that one there.
It's not far. See it?
[MIKOTO] Wait, that's where the
real-life Gekota doctor works.
He knows about the
situation with the Sisters.
[MIKOTO]
Thank you very much!
[MIKOTO] If they took her there,
I'm sure she's fine.
[MIKOTO] Huh? You mean
she wasn't brought here?
No. We have no records
of any emergency cases
around that time.
But the EMTs said this is
where they dropped her off!
[F STAFF A] Perhaps they
confused us with
another hospital.
[M WORKER C] No. I'm pretty
certain that's the place.
[M WORKER B] Yeah. We definitely
took her to that hospital.
But they said they don't
have any record of--
[MIKOTO]
Wait, something's wrong.
She was wearing gym
clothes from Tokiwadai.
If these guys are
telling the truth,
then no matter
what hospital it was,
they would have
contacted the school.
But it's the next day and I
haven't heard from anyone,
let alone the school.
Excuse me,
but is that the truth?
[M WORKER C]
Yeah?
Then can you tell me the
name of the hospital staff
you turned her over to,
or anything else
that may have happened?
Of course we can.
We, uh... Huh?
[M WORKER B]
What are you, senile?
Remember, we... huh?
[M WORKER C]
Hey!
[MIKOTO] I'll just check the
ambulance's route history.
[MIKOTO]
I knew it.
They didn't go to the hospital.
They went to an underground
parking garage and back!
[M WORKER B]
Hey, get out of there!
[MIKOTO] She was taken there
in this ambulance.
Did they move her to
a different vehicle then?
So, where is she now--?
What's going on?
Why did you lie?
From what it's showing here
in your route history,
you never even went
to the hospital!
I get the feeling you won't
be able to explain that one.
Well that can't be right.
You're lying to me
and I have proof!
You can't talk your way
out of this!
Huh? You're the girl
from yesterday.
What's the big idea?
We bring you to the hospital
and now that you've recovered
you show up and
start calling us liars?
What? No way!
I'm just--!
[M WORKER B]
Hold on.
I thought I'd seen you before,
and now I know where.
You're that Level 5, right?
The one that controls
electricity or whatever.
How do we know you
didn't use your ability
to tamper with the route
history yourself?
What are you--?
There's no way I'd
do something like that!
I'm sorry for keeping
my identity a secret.
But stop lying to me!
Tell me what really happened!
[M WORKER B]
But I'm not lying, I swear!
If you're not lying,
then why don't you have any
memory of what happened?
Everything you've told me is--
[MIKOTO]
Memory? Tampering?
Was it...?
[M ANTISKILL A]
You! Take your hands off him!
[SATEN]
She's lookin' pretty dead.
Is everything okay?
Well, she knows she has
five more nights away
from Misaka ahead of her.
She told me before it's
sapping her will to live.
Ah, that explains it.
[KUROKO]
Uiharu?
You realize this street isn't
on our patrol route,
don't you?
Huh? What do you mean?
That's not true.
I remember this was...
[KUROKO]
Look at the map.
[UIHARU]
Whoa. You're right.
Honestly.
If you're going to tell someone
they're wrong about something,
you should at least be
certain about it yourself.
[UIHARU] How could I have
made that mistake?
[SATEN]
Don't beat yourself up.
We can go back easy enough.
[KEITZ]
Sorry to bother you.
I noticed the armband.
Are you with Judgment?
Yes. That's right.
So, I'm not from around here.
I only came to see the festival.
And I just got
robbed over there.
Oh, no! That's awful!
What did they take from you?
[SATEN] Turns out taking the
wrong route was a good thing
after all.
All right, there's
no need to be cheeky.
[SATEN laughs]
[UIHARU]
I can't...
[SATEN]
...move.
[KUROKO]
Or teleport.
What was taken? Let's see.
Your memories of Mikoto Misaka.
How's that?
[WATANABE] I really am
terribly sorry about this!
Come on, let's go.
For goodness sake,
what were you thinking?
Very nearly committing
assault while trying to prank
a public agency?
You realize how lucky you are?
They didn't have to be
so accommodating.
They could have pressed
charges against you.
What brought on
this erratic behavior?
[MIKOTO] While waiting for
Ms. Watanabe to arrive,
I tried asking all kinds
of trick questions,
but they didn't seem
like they were lying.
Which supports my theory.
Wanna know the truth?
I think Misaki Shokuho
is using her ability
to cover up a crime.
If that accusation
has any merit,
this is a serious matter.
Do you have any evidence that
led you to that conclusion?
Well, I...
No.
Any way I explain this, I'll
have to mention the Sisters.
I know this doesn't help,
but I really can't give
you any specifics.
Then that makes it difficult
for me to do anything.
Misaka, the Daihasei Festival
is going on.
The entire world's attention
is on Academy City right now.
As a Level 5, you must
conduct yourself not only
as a representative
of our school,
but of all of Academy City.
I realize that's a tremendous
amount of pressure
to put on you, but we must
be more careful
about your hasty actions
than ever before.
Do you understand?
[MIKOTO]
Yes.
I don't get it.
If Shokuho manipulated the EMTs
to use them as traffickers,
what was her objective?
Ugh. I need more info.
As soon as the events
start up again, I'll slip out.
For now, the underground
parking garage
where the ambulance
went is my only lead.
[WATANABE]
Oh, this works out perfectly.
Ladies, could I ask you
for a favor?
You see, Misaka is
feeling unusually anxious
at the moment,
so I'd like for you
to keep your eyes on her.
[F STUDENT B]
Sure. No problem.
[MIKOTO]
Guards?
And of all people.
Misaki Shokuho's clique?
My... isn't this nice?
Misaka, I've always wanted
to sit down and have
a nice, long chat with you.
I'm looking forward to it.
[MIKOTO]
Uh... Yeah.
You should really try not
to cause so much trouble
for our teachers.
You do have a history
of being mischievous.
[MIKOTO]
Aww, man. This is gonna suck.
[KOBAYASHI]
Misaka?
[MIKOTO]
Was that telepathy?
[KOBAYASHI] Since I'm
going to be watching you,
I've opened a direct
line between us.
While this line is connected,
I will be able to track
your general location.
I think it's only fair
I tell you now.
If you run away,
I regret to inform you
that we will do everything
in our power to stop you.
You may start driving.
[M DRIVER A]
Yes, ma'am.
[WATANABE]
I am sorry, Misaka.
It wasn't my intent to put
a damper on things.
Especially not during the
long-awaited Daihasei Festival.
However, Misaki Shokuho's
"Optimization" is absolute.
[MIKOTO] I know I could shake
them off if I really tried.
Or, at least I think so.
But gathering more
information while on the run
will be really difficult.
[MIKOTO] I don't sense any
open hostility from the girls
in the clique.
Does that mean that Shokuho
hasn't told them anything?
[MIKOTO]
Is that...
Kuroko! Uiharu and Saten, too!
Uh, would it be okay
if I talked to my friends
really quick?
I won't run, promise.
[F STUDENT D]
Huh? Okay.
[MIKOTO]
I can't say too much.
I'll try to get them to help
without being obvious.
[MIKOTO] Hey, Kuroko!
I need a little favor from you.
[KUROKO]
Excuse me.
Don't you think it's kind of
inappropriate to shout my name
out to the world?
It's a little overfamiliar.
Hey, Shirai, is this a friend
of yours or something?
Not at all.
This is Mikoto Misaka, she's an
upperclassman at my school.
Oh. Yeah, you're famous!
What do they call you again?
"Railgun" or something?
Uh, Kuroko. This is a joke.
You're all just trying
to pull my leg, right?
No idea what you're
talking about.
[MIKOTO]
Right, Uiharu? Saten?
That's weird, why would
she know our names?
[UIHARU] I imagine Shirai
must have told her.
I didn't.
We aren't even acquainted.
I couldn't have.
Listen, I don't know
where you heard about
the three of us, or who
told you all of our names.
But if you need help,
or you're in trouble,
I'll hear you out.
I am a member of Judgment.
No. That's okay.
[MIKOTO] You've really
done it now, Shokuho!
You've decided to mess
with my friends' heads?
How dare you?
This goes way beyond
just screwing around!
[MIKOTO] Shokuho, what do
you think you're doing,
tampering with my
friends' memories?
Not to mention having
your clique stand guard
over me and keeping me
from finding that sister!
I gotta do something.
[KONGO] Misaka, allow me,
Mitsuko Kongo,
--to deal with this!
--[MIKOTO] Huh?