[RADIO DJ] And our next
competition is Balloon Hunter!
In this contest, 30 students
chosen from each school
will compete to pop
the paper balloons
attached to their
opponents' heads using
the designated beanbags!
Contestants whose balloons
are popped are disqualified,
and the team with the
most students remaining
at the end wins.
The game area is pretty wide,
but going indoors or onto
any roads still open
to the public is
strictly prohibited.
It's time we get going, Misaka.
Uh...
[F TOKIWADAI 03A]
Kongo, we're about to begin!
[RADIO DJ] Now, are all of
the teams ready to start?
[KONGO] You didn't tuck
your tail and run away.
I'll give you points for that.
Heh. Yeah, yeah,
let's see if you're still
talking smack when this is over.
[RADIO DJ]
Ready... Set...
[gun fires]
Huh?
[M STUDENT 03A] That's it!
Keep running as far as you can!
If we all make it through this,
we'll force them into a tie!
Wow. They're not
very direct, are they?
Let's go after them!
"Pursuing individually
is dangerous.
We should divide
into three-man teams,"
Says Misaka, proposing a...
Oh, well, then.
[MIKOTO] I want to say,
"how did this end up happening?"
But it's really not
that hard to imagine.
I guess the fact that
no one could tell us apart
is lucky in a way.
But it's also
pretty disheartening,
when I think about it.
Well, no use worrying
about what's already done.
Since you're filling
in for me anyway,
make me look good
out there, will you?
[SATEN] Are you sure you don't
have to go out on patrol?
[UIHARU] I do have to go
on patrol, just not "out."
I can do it all online.
Since we're dealing with
such a large-scale event,
they're anticipating a
number of cyberattacks,
so they need extra
help on the net.
Ahh, and that's right
up your alley, isn't it?
[RADIO DJ] Three minutes
have passed since the start
of the balloon hunter game,
and there's still no one
out from either team.
Who will be the one
to break this tie?
Hey, isn't that the event
that Misaka said
she was competing in next?
Yeah, that must be the one.
I wonder if she changed
her clothes in time.
Well, it is Misaka
we're talking about.
I bet she made it.
Look, Kongo!
Everyone, let's try
splitting up!
[GROUP]
Right!
[SATEN] So they're just
supposed to pop the balloons
on each other's heads?
Tokiwadai has more
than just Misaka.
There's tons of strong
espers that go there.
I can't imagine they'd lose.
[UIHARU]
Hmm...
I'm not so certain.
Why don't you just
give up already?
A telekinetic, huh?
Let me guess, you lured me here?
[OMOSHI chuckles]
Feels cheap doin'
this to a girl.
But don't worry,
I'm not trying to
hit you in your face!
That the best you got?
I take it you're not even
a Level 3 then, are you?
I just so happen to be
a telekinetic as well.
Luckily, it seems I'm
significantly more skilled
at it than you.
[OMOSHI]
Damn!
Do you really expect
to dodge them all?
[RADIO DJ]
Contestant Omoshi is out!
[KIRIFU]
Too easy.
At this rate, I could take
all of you on myself
and not even break a sweat.
It won't be long before
the rest of you are elimi--
[RADIO DJ]
Contestant Kirifu is out!
Huh?!
But that attack happened
after he was disqualified!
That's a completely
illegal move!
[OMOSHI chuckles]
It would be, if I had done it.
[rustling]
Um, hey there.
She's the one who
actually used her power
to throw that at you.
You dropped your guard,
thinking it was over.
Level 4, telekinetic
Megumi Kirifu.
[gasps] Why do you
know my full name?
Because we know we're
weaker than your school.
We found out everything
there is to know about you
and came up with
some strategies.
[KOBAYASHI]
All right, girls.
Is everyone in position?
Moments ago,
I saw at least five members
of the other team nearby.
They were entering
this very alleyway.
Thankfully, we are in
control of all three exits
leading out of the area.
I'll send the signal to move
out in a few seconds,
with my telepathy.
[KOBAYASHI]
Okay, three, two...
...one?
[KOBAYASHI screams]
Take it easy, Kobayashi!
I feel like my head's
gonna explode!
[M STUDENT 03A] Screams that
are delivered telepathically
echo directly within the brain.
It amounts to a sonic weapon
that can't be blocked out.
Oh, and that's a fake spider.
So you can chill.
[F TOKIWADAI 02B]
They just keep running away.
Why won't they quit?
[F TOKIWADAI 02B gasps]
Mud? That's gross.
Do we have to go through here?
Our shoes are going
to get filthy.
I'm sure there's some
other way through.
Yeah. I mean, there's gotta be.
[M STUDENT 03C]
There they go.
With no idea we're
leading them around.
Incredible!
We're playing Tokiwadai
like a fiddle!
It's just like you said, Baba.
Good call.
Hey. I just collected some data
and made some suggestions.
No big.
Maybe, but how'd you get
such detailed information?
Like personalities
and weaknesses?
It's 'cause I have a friend over
at the Garden of Learning.
Connections, man.
[M STUDENT 03C]
Hey, what do we do next?
Oh. Gimme a sec.
[BABA] Sure enough,
wars are won with detailed
intelligence and leaders who
can make effective use of it.
Know thy enemy and know thyself,
and even these idiots
will make good pawns.
Oh, that's right.
'Kay, let's head out. Baba?
[BABA]
Hm? Okay, let's go.
[M STUDENT 03D] Things are
going pretty smoothly so far.
We've got a healthy lead.
Let's not get too cocky.
They do have Mikoto
Misaka on their team.
She can sense we're coming,
so we can't sneak attack.
She's like a fortress.
[M STUDENT 03D] Well, we don't
have to eliminate everyone.
[M STUDENT 03C] Yeah. No reason
to take that kinda risk.
We should tell everyone
not to go near her.
[BABA]
Great, just what I needed.
If we were at a
big disadvantage,
I wouldn't be able to
go forward with the plan,
so I had to tilt the scales.
But now that we're dominating,
we're gonna end up
ignoring my target.
What a pain.
Well, let's see what shakes out.
[F STUDENT 03B panting]
Gimme a break,
this is so unfair!
Out of every single
kid at my school,
why did I have to run
into a level 5?
Is... Is she gone?
[F STUDENT 03B yells]
Not long ago,
there was an experiment
that took place in this alley.
So the general layout,
good places to hide,
and where to attack
from are all familiar.
[M STUDENT 03E] Damn it,
I knew that wouldn't work!
Ah, it's dangerous
to go that way.
"I told you so."
Misaka says with a smug sigh.
[RADIO DJ] Contestant Misaka
defeats her second opponent!
Can Tokiwadai make a comeback
in the remaining time?
[WANNAI]
Did you see that, kitty?
[meows]
Misaka's quite
impressive, isn't she?
[CAT meows]
I just can't get over how
cute this little cat is.
It looks as though this is the
end of the line for me.
Ecaterina, limit yourself
to only one rat per day.
[RADIO DJ]
Yeah, anyway.
Can you get up and make
your way to the sidelines now?
[KONGO] Huh?
Sorry, was that too much?
You put up a good fight.
Especially against seven of us.
One should expect nothing
less from the great
and powerful Mitsuko Kongo!
She apparently
just transferred in,
so there was hardly any
data on her to study.
She just transferred in
and she's that pompous?
[M STUDENT 03D] Bad news!
Nomura's group was wiped out!
[M STUDENT 03I]
For real?
[M STUDENT 03C]
Not good.
If they're out, that means
we've lost most of our lead.
As well as our precious Level 3.
[BABA]
Nice.
Here's an idea.
Do you think we should
go after Mikoto Misaka?
[M STUDENT 03D]
What?
For the time being,
the opposing team is scattered,
but with the game's
end approaching
and no time to spare, they
might start working together.
If that happens, it's not
gonna be easy for us
to keep the slim
lead we do have.
But if we take out
their head right now,
we should be able
to shake 'em up
and cripple their leadership.
That's easier said than done.
Yeah, there's no
way to beat her.
Don't you guys worry.
There's a way to bring her down.
And a simple one, at that.
Ha, ha! That guy didn't
even follow me!
I'm with Judgment,
that's far enough.
You're under
arrest for stealing.
What the--?
You'd be better off
not making this harder
for both of us.
I'm in an especially
poor mood right now!
'Cause so far, all day...
...I've been without my
necessary, daily dose of Sissy.
[sighs] Speaking of, she must
be competing right about now.
Where was the closest
street monitor again?
It better be big.
[F STUDENT 03C panting]
[MISAKA 10032]
"Strange," Misaka thinks,
as she watches her opponent.
This girl does not appear
to have any desire to fight.
But she also does not
seem to be running away
in a random direction.
Perhaps she led me
to this wide-open area
to make better
use of her ability.
Or perhaps... it's a trap.
[BABA] If you can't hit your
opponents by throwing,
then don't throw.
[M STUDENT 03D]
Huh?
[BABA]
You remember the rules?
They say you have
to pop the balloon
using the designated beanbags.
And that's all.
Get it?
So you can pop it with the
beanbag still in your hand.
And if Misaka uses her
electricity on the beanbags
while we're holding them,
it'll count as attacking an
opponent with her ability,
and she'll be disqualified.
All we have to do is
keep our weapons on us
and we lock down her shocks.
[M STUDENT 03D]
If she can't use her ability,
then we've levelled
the playing field!
[M STUDENT 03D grunts]
[M STUDENT 03C]
You're mine!
[STUDENTS grunt]
"Misaka has fought in
over 10,000 battles
against someone who could take
her life with a single touch.
Catching her...
...will not be a simple matter.
Will it?" says Misaka, snidely.
[M STUDENT 03I] Don't let up!
Everyone charge her together!
[RADIO DJ]
Ooh!
Contestant Misaka, faced with
a flurry of attacks...
...dives, dodges,
and ducks out of the way!
This is incredible!
[BABA] Good grief, it took
a lot of work to set up
those conditions.
[BABA] Typically, our target,
Mikoto Misaka,
emits faint E-M
waves around her.
They can serve as
a kind of radar if she
pays attention to them.
And it's practically impossible
for an electronic device,
even a small one,
to get near her undetected.
However, with her focus
on the opponents
closing in, and the
rules of the game
preventing her from
using her ability,
it can be done.
[M STUDENT 03K] Listen!
Let's all rush her toge--
[MISAKA 10032] A hole in
the wall has opened up.
Now is the chance to--
[BOTH gasp]
[RADIO DJ]
Contestant Misaka is eliminated!
[F STUDENT 03F gasps]
No way! We actually did it!
[MISAKA 10032]
Misaka has been defeated.
[BABA]
Mission accomplished.
Man, that was an
unusual one, though.
Seriously, incapacitate
Mikoto Misaka?
[RADIO DJ] The Balloon
Hunter competition has
officially concluded!
Tokiwadai Middle School,
which was favored to win,
has been beaten by
a razor-thin margin!
[WATANABE] That marks their
first loss in this tournament.
Though one could say
having the real possibility
of defeat is the
point of all this.
True.
After all, there's more
to learn from a loss
than from a win.
This'll be a good lesson
for the conceited
and the powerful.
Just what the doctor ordered.
We can't have girls
worrying about dirtying
their clothes so much
that they lose a match.
Yes, I agree.
How about I add
scrubbing toilets
to their dorm chore rotation?
That sounds like an
appropriate idea.
[MISAKA 10032]
"It is unfortunate that Misaka
did not remain vigilant
and fell for their trap.
"Yes?" says Misaka, suspecting
that you feel the same way.
She failed to fulfill her
role as your substitute.
[MIKOTO]
But did you have fun?
[MISAKA 10032]
Hm?
[MIKOTO] I asked if you had
fun competing in the game.
[MISAKA 10032]
Oh. Yes.
[MIKOTO] Then there's
nothing to feel down about.
I wasn't happy about the mix-up,
but when you got mistaken
for me, what could you do?
And it's my own fault for
being late in the first place.
All things considered,
you did pretty well.
Better than I would have done
at the end, that's for sure.
Good job.
[gasps]
[purrs]
[MIKOTO]
It's just about lunchtime.
Have you had anything to eat?
[MISAKA 10032]
No.
Here.
They're street stall vouchers
they gave out to the students.
I'm supposed to grab some
food with my mama,
so you can use them
if you feel like it.
Street stalls, you say?
[MIKOTO]
We're at a festival, remember?
We can't forget
to have some fun.
Oh, and don't forget,
those gym clothes you've
got on are Wannai's.
Get them back to her
as soon as you can.
[MIKOTO] I know it's okay to
bring your own food in here,
but I get the feeling
that doesn't include
your own pot filled
with cheese fondue.
[MISUZU]
Oh, it's fine.
Plus, isn't this nice?
A mother and daughter
having fondue together
during the festival.
[MIKOTO]
I guess.
[MISUZU sighs] But it's gonna
be a while before the cheese
is melted all the way.
Maybe I should have cut
it up into smaller pieces.
[MIKOTO] Then how about I go
buy us something to drink?
Okay. I'd sure like some wine.
They definitely don't have that.
[MIKOTO gasps] Ah, man.
It's just as crowded out here.
[KAMIJO]
Oh! You, too, huh?
Well, look who it is.
This sucks, doesn't it?
There are lines
everywhere you go.
Yeah, I know, I've had
to wait forever.
Ol' Kamijo here very
nearly wet himself.
[MIKOTO gasps]
What are you talking about?
So you weren't talking
about the bathroom lines
being insanely long?
[MIKOTO] No, I'm just trying
to buy some drinks here!
Oh! My bad.
[MIKOTO groans]
You are so crude.
[KAMIJO] Tell you what,
I'll go stand in line
and grab some extra drinks,
so there'll be plenty.
I doubt my mom packed
enough for everyone.
I'll get some for you, too!
[grunts]
[MIKOTO] And you're also
too nice sometimes.
[SHOKUHO]
See? What did I say?
It's just like I told you.
[KEITZ]
Yeah. You're right.
Still, I'm surprised
you could tell
from the video
footage alone.
Ha! Menta l Out can be used
in many different ways,
depending on the situation.
But you don't need
to know specifics.
[KEITZ]
Fair enough.
I should have expected
as much from a level 5.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
All I need from you
are your keen powers
of observation, understand?
[gasps]
Well, well.
Ugh.
Hello, Misaka.
Enjoying a relaxing lunch?
Relaxing? What's that
supposed to mean?
Don't tell me you run to
some corner to train
instead of eating.
Of course not.
I used my ability to cancel
all of my afternoon events.
Huh?
After my busy morning,
I'm exhausted.
Jeez. Listen to you.
[KAMIJO]
Do you think this'll be enough,
or should I go get some more?
They mostly just had tea.
Eh... So, uh,
who's this lady here?
She's a classmate. Sort of.
[KAMIJO]
She's in your grade?
[gasps] Oh! Like your
grade in school!
[MIKOTO]
Real smooth.
I swear his gaze dropped like
30 centimeters just now.
[SHOKUHO chuckles]
It's good to meet you, Kamijo.
[gasps]
If I may introduce myself,
I'm Misaka's very good friend.
You may call me Misaki Shokuho!
And it's a pleasure!
[MIKOTO]
What? Since when are we friends?
[SHOKUHO]
Aww. How scary!
Misaka doesn't seem
to like me very much.
She's always so charged
and tense with me!
[KAMIJO] Uh, yeah.
She's always jolty with me, too.
[SHOKUHO] Oh, yeah?
So she's charged and jolty?
Well that's fitting, isn't it?
[MIKOTO]
You two just met.
Stop bonding over making
bad puns about me!
I'll be seeing you
around then, Misaka!
Compete hard enough
for the both of us!
[MIKOTO grunts]
[SATEN]
Hmm...
[UIHARU]
Is everything okay?
You look like you're lost in
thought, and that's pretty rare.
[SATEN]
Shouldn't you be working?
I have been.
In fact, there were
three significant
server attacks earlier.
But they were barely above
the level of an amateur,
so I dealt with them in no time.
Oh. Cool.
[UIHARU]
What have you been up to, Saten?
I've been thinking.
But I have no idea where
to find some Shadow Metal.
Are you still going
on about that?
[SATEN]
If it's supposed to be created
whenever esper powers
clash with each other,
it'd probably be wherever
the toughest schools
have been competing.
[UIHARU sighs]
Didn't Shirai warn you
about believing those rumors?
Why so desperate?
Are you in financial
trouble or something?
[SATEN]
No.
I mean, I'm not exactly
rolling in dough, either.
I guess I'm just
looking for adventure.
Imagine finding something
most people think is fake,
something you'd never
see in a million years
just going about your life.
It's a little like
being a level 5.
[UIHARU sighs]
[UIHARU]
Eh, what the heck.
If you wouldn't mind a partner,
I could help you look for it.
What was it again?
"Shadow Metal?"
I'll poke around for whatever
information I can find.
Aww. That's my girl, Uiharu!
How come you're wearing
your gym shorts under here?
So I can participate in
an event right away.
Um, please don't tug.
[MISAKA 10032]
Cotton candy. Candy apples.
What must they taste like?
The yakisoba might
have onions in it,
so we can rule that
one out immediately.
[CAT meows]
[MISAKA 10032 gasps] "Cats are
able to eat grilled squid,"
says Misaka.
[CAT meows]
[meows]
[MISAKA 10032]
How... unfortunate.
These clothes are borrowed, too.
[MISAKA 10032]
Now they're dirty.
[KUROKO] Sissy, at least the
two of us are alone together!
[MIKOTO]
It's no big deal.
[KUROKO]
It is!
It's been 23 episodes
since the two of us
did a preview together!
Feel free to plant
one of your usual,
passionate kisses on--
[KUROKO yelps]
At least let me finish the gag!