[KEITZ]
Is this... the Misaka Network?
No.
[MIKOTO growls]
What happened here?
Did you hurt her?!
[GENSEI]
Yes, Aleister's favorite,
kept hidden within the
shadows of the main plan.
What if I were to use this
opportunity and trigger
the awakening of your
dormant powers?
I wonder.
[MIKOTO gasps]
[GENSEI]
Now, let the experiment begin.
Let's find out.
Can Misaka reach
the divine world...
...of Level 6?
[XÓCHITL] I think their true
objective is Mikoto Misaka.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
[KAMIJO]
Hey. Fill me in, too.
[KUROKO]
Really?
So she thinks Misaka
is their true goal, then?
[SATEN] Yeah. I don't know
any other details about it,
but that's definitely
what she said.
I think Saten's on to something.
There's an electrical
discharge phenomenon
occurring in School District 2.
Electrical discharge?
[MIKOTO]
Huh? Wait.
What was I just doing?
My head feels so groggy
for some reason.
For that matter, who even am I?
Hey, you.
Answer me this,
how is it that you can be
so apathetic about the kind
of things that happen
in this city?
[MIKOTO]
"This city?"
You mean in Academy City?
What's going on?
[KOZAKU]
You've seen it, right?
You know.
How they treat clones
as less than human--
No, it's even worse.
Even when dealing
with normal people,
they still treat them as
nothing more than lab rats.
The true face of this city
that tramples on human life
all in the name of science.
[MIKOTO]
Yeah, that's right.
I remember.
They'll pay.
No matter what reasons
they may have had,
they've done horrible,
unforgiveable things.
Never again.
I have to stop them.
I have to. I have to.
But how?
[KOZAKU]
Right over there. That building.
The control tower thingy
at the city's center.
So long as it exists,
those psychos will do this
over and over.
Another innocent soul
will be hurt again.
Another will be brought
to tears again.
So what do you say?
Let's destroy it. Okay?
[MIKOTO]
Sounds good.
[KOZAKU] Whoa... That was even
crazier than I imagined.
It almost made me wet myself.
But at least it's done now.
It's fine?
How is that thing
still even standing?
It doesn't look like there's
been any damage at all!
[GENSEI]
Goodness.
That may have been a dozen
times more firepower
than Misaka can
normally put out,
but she won't leave
a scratch on that building
without getting close and
landing a physical blow.
That's not what you said--
[GENSEI] You young people
today are so impatient,
it's incredible.
You can't expect her
to develop fully
in a matter of minutes.
After seeing that,
I'd say she's about 2%
of the way to Level 6
at the moment.
Don't be so hasty, Kozaku.
If you want to
achieve your goal,
then you need to perform
your duties properly.
Understand?
Yeah.
[GENSEI]
Oh. Right.
There's one other thing
I wanted to ask of you.
Huh?
[ANTISKILL A] It's the board
chairman's building.
It was struck by record-
breaking lightning.
Meanwhile in School District 2,
there was a massive electrical
discharge phenomenon.
[CHIEF A]
Hmm...
Then let's send rescue
teams and investigators
to both sites at once.
[phone rings]
Yes? Yes. Right, understood.
All right. I'll--
[CHIEF A]
No.
On second thought,
we can't afford to have
outsider casualties
during the tournament.
Our priority is the
evacuation of tourists
and local residents.
[ANTISKILL A] But sir,
that's a different issue--
We'll be closing off both sites.
Not a single soul is
allowed to go inside.
Not even Antiskill.
[ANTISKILL A]
Yes sir.
Well, even if Antiskill
did head here to help,
realistically, they'd just be
adding to the body count.
Although, it sure would
be nice to have someone
who could hold
her back a little.
Oh, my, what do we have here?
Out of nowhere,
right when I'm looking for help.
You're coming on
a little strong.
If I weren't a part
of this mess,
that'd be a major red flag.
Okay, I'm in the right area.
[SHOKUHO] But since I am
front and center in all of this,
you look more like
a prince to me.
A woman's heart
is a funny thing.
Okay. If I go from the top,
I should be able
to get the right angle.
[KAMIJO panting]
[KAMIJO]
Is that...? Huh?
[SHOKUHO]
Hi!
Whoa! What is that?
It's like it's coming from
the inside of my head!
[SHOKUHO] Let me just
say this up front.
If you touch your head with
that right hand of yours,
you'll erase everything
I'm about to tell you.
--So no touching, okay?
--[KAMIJO] Wha--?
Also, unlike a telepath,
I'm pretty much just
writing everything
into your brain at once, so
don't bother complaining.
[KAMIJO]
You what?!
[SHOKUHO] I'll try to summarize
this as best as I can.
My ability and
the Misaka Network
are being used for evil,
and Misaka is in big trouble.
[KAMIJO]
So that really is her?
--[SHOKUHO] However...
--Will you listen?!
[SHOKUHO] ...if you were
to stick around her
and keep countering
her with your powers
of interference,
you might be able to
delay her transformation.
At least... I think. Maybe.
Oh, that's reassuring!
[SHOKUHO]
Anyway, I've been thinking.
Since brainwashing
shouldn't have any effect
on her in her current state,
I wonder if they're using
the Network to manipulate
her deep psyche instead.
What do you think?
[KAMIJO] You couldn't hear
my response anyway.
[SHOKUHO] Well, if you
can touch her directly,
maybe that will turn
her back to normal.
Think of it as a challenge!
I really wish I knew
who you were.
A challenge, she says.
Seriously?
Hey! Where's Shirai?
Already on her way.
Do you think there's
anything I can do
to help out?
Thank you for offering.
I'll look.
[SHOKUHO]
There they are.
But I don't see Gensei.
Is he planning to keep
out of sight and watch
from a safe distance?
[SHOKUHO]
Just one second.
For all I know, you could
have been ordered
to attack me as soon
as you're freed,
so I'll be taking
some precautions.
Let's go with "do me no harm."
Would you mind taking
this girl somewhere?
Preferably safe?
Assuming such
a place even exists.
And you?
[SHOKUHO]
I'm going after Gensei.
I mean, if I sent anyone else,
they'd just get brainwashed.
The only one who stands
a chance against
Mental Out is someone
who can use
Mental Out themselves.
[SHOKUHO]
Hey!
[KOZAKU PUPPET] Uh-oh,
that doesn't work on something
being remotely
controlled, does it?
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
That won't help.
I hate to ask, but could
you hang out with me
for a bit?
Do me a favor and don't fight.
Just behave.
Ow.
[KUROKO]
I'm with Judgment!
It seems the situation
is escalating,
and it was already
a public safety concern.
I'll need each of you
to explain to me
exactly what's going on.
And Mitori Kozaku,
I have even more
to discuss with you.
Starting with the
falsification of Bank data.
[SHOKUHO]
Oh, Shirai.
That was very heroic,
but you must realize
you're not questioning
anyone right now.
I hate to impose,
but do you think you could
prioritize teleporting
the two of them
out of here first?
[KUROKO]
Is that Misaka? No.
[SHOKUHO gasps]
Do you want to go with them?
No, but if I could get you
to warp both of us
inside the building,
that'd be great.
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Ugh. I gotta admit.
Finding my data in
the Bank in such
a short amount of time
is impressive.
Not bad.
[SHOKUHO]
Thank you very much, Shirai.
You saved me.
[KUROKO] Yes, so you can
explain what's going on here.
It's only fair to warn you.
I don't trust you
even a tiny bit.
You're also under
suspicion for the attack
on the 177th Branch Office.
We can discuss that
at a later time.
But for now,
teaming up would be in both
our best interests,
don't you think?
There's no need
to be so frightened.
I'm just going to send
you my observations
about the situation we've
found ourselves in. 'Kay?
It'll save me the trouble of
having to say it out loud.
[KUROKO groans]
[SHOKUHO]
And there you have it.
Thank you.
[KUROKO]
All right.
You're going to explain
all of this later, got it?
Good luck out there!
Now then.
[STEERING COMMITTEE A]
As you may have noticed,
there are massive
cumulonimbus clouds
now passing over Academy City.
All outdoor competitions
are being suspended.
Further, some competitions
will now be held
at the Dome.
To ensure the safety of
all of our visitors today,
please follow the instructions
of your nearest attendants...
[SOGIITA]
Huh...
Whatever's causin' that
has got some real guts.
There's lighting coming
out of the ground.
Yeah, think I'll go
take a closer look.
[MIKOTO]
Still not enough.
To destroy that thing,
I'll need something more.
But it's okay. Pretty soon...
Noise?
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO]
I just gotta time this right!
[MIKOTO]
What's that?
[KOZAKU] It's just a gross
little bug that's trying
to interfere.
You know what we do
with those, right?
Squish them!
That figures.
I shouldn't have expected
this to be easy.
[KUROKO]
That's where Misaka is.
[SHOKUHO] They're obviously
looking to control her
barbaric strength.
And it's safe to
assume that Mental Out
is an essential
component in that.
As for Kozaku...
My ability has no effect
on her puppets,
much to my dismay.
So under normal circumstances,
I'd have to assume she's acting
as Gensei's bodyguard.
But that's a bit hard
to accept at this stage.
I mean, one of the
few pawns he has left
should be pushing
his plan forward,
not just protecting him, right?
Knowing the crafty old man,
I'd bet he'll be making
use of Level Upper
to share Exterior's powers
with her as well.
If I had to take a guess,
I'd say that her role
is that of an "inductor."
I'm not even familiar
with that word.
But somehow I more
or less understand.
It's an unsettling feeling.
[SHOKUHO] Based on the precise
movements of her puppets,
she can't be too far from here.
And if she's controlling Misaka,
she can't be far
from her either.
That should help
narrow down the search.
Please find the puppet master
so we can stop Misaka.
[KUROKO growls]
The nerve!
Everyone is trying
to order me around today.
Judgment is not your
personal handyman!
[KOZAKU PUPPET]
Sure enough, she's on the hunt.
Hey, so, I kinda failed to
capture Misaki Shokuho.
I hate to do this,
but I think I'm gonna
have to focus on
protecting myself now.
Think you can you
handle the rest there
on your own?
[GENSEI]
Oh, well.
If I have to.
[KAMIJO panting]
[KAMIJO yells]
She's strong,
but I can stop her attacks.
If I'm careful, I can do this!
No, no, no, no!
That is so not fair!
Come on Hyper Eccentric Ultra
Great Giga Extreme!
Throw in another Hyper!
Amazing Punch!
You okay over there?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks for that,
you saved my neck.
Whoever-that-is is crazy, huh?
Gotta say, it takes guts
to grow horns like that.
All right.
It's probably best
to leave this to me.
But I know her,
and this isn't normal.
Thanks, but I just can't
leave her like this.
Listen man, I'm not sure
you can handle her.
Just get to safety, will ya?
I wasn't trying to fight her.
From what I've been told,
she's pretty much being
manipulated somehow.
What, so she's not in control?
Guess she's lacking
in guts then, huh?
I'll just have to knock
some into her!
I kinda doubt that's
a factor here.
[SOGIITA]
Why?
She probably lost her way
and is acting out
or something. No big deal.
If she had more guts,
she'd be fine.
[KAMIJO]
Will you listen to me?!
Wait, he punched
the lightning away?
[SOGIITA]
He canceled out the lightning?
[BOTH]
Who is this guy?
[SOGIITA]
Heh.
I'm Gunha Sogiita. You?
[KAMIJO]
Toma Kamijo.
[SOGIITA]
All right!
Make sure not to get
in my way, Kamijo!
Right back at ya.
[KUROKO] If what Misaki
Shokuho told me is true,
then Mitori Kozaku
must be hiding inside
a building that's
somewhere near Misaka.
That being said,
this area is packed
with research facilities.
Finding a single person
in all this will be hard.
I guess I have little choice.
Uiharu!
Check the cameras near
the Judgment Building
in School District 2.
An 800-meter radius
should suffice.
I need you to tell me
if Kozaku shows up
on any of them.
Also, I'd like for you to
calculate the blind spots
of those cameras
and send them to me.
I'll go check those myself.
You will? All by yourself?
Is that a good idea?
You need backup--
[KUROKO]
There is no time for that.
Besides...
[MIKOTO]
I just had faith in you.
I knew I could trust
you to save her.
So that's why.
[KUROKO] I'm doing this
as a member of Judgment,
but also because she trusts me.
That doesn't feel half bad,
for some reason.
[SOGIITA grunts]
Those are some
cool moves you got there.
But they're getting old!
Hey! Sogii--
[KAMIJO]
Is that a barrier of iron sand?
That's what that is?
What's with her?
Still playin' in
the sandbox like a kid?
That's not gutsy at all.
[KAMIJO]
Wha--? Not again.
[SOGIITA]
Stand back, Kamijo.
[SOGIITA grunts]
[SOGIITA yells]
[KAMIJO grunts]
That right hand of yours
does some awesome stuff,
doesn't it?
Yeah. I'm thinking if
I touch her with it,
I might be able to
turn her back to normal.
[gasps]
But I can't find any way
to get close to her
like this.
You don't say.
We can fix that.
[SOGIITA]
'Kay. Leave it to me.
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
[SOGIITA]
Super Amazing... Punch!
[KAMIJO]
Awesome!
Now's your chance, bud!
No, no, no, no!
Hold on, hold on, wait! Stop!
Good luck!
[KAMIJO yells]
I'm here, might as well try!
[KAMIJO]
Wait, how do I land?
What do I do?!
Huh?
[footsteps]
[SHOKUHO]
Found you, Gensei Kihara.
[KUROKO] Well, things certainly
have taken a strange turn.
I'd like to get some real
answers out of Shokuho,
but at the moment,
Mitori Kozaku comes first.
[SHOKUHO] My, how resolute
you are, Shirai.
That's a good look on you!
[KUROKO] Do you think you
could refrain from speaking
directly into my mind?