Watch your five!
That one's probably
the main unit!
Hold on! Your line of fire's--
[DOPPEL]
Why?
Why did you miss me?
[MIKOTO]
So that is her real goal.
Thought so.
[DOPPEL]
What's the matter?
Are you trying to set
Academy City ablaze?
[MIKOTO]
Those bluffs won't work anymore.
I don't think you would do that.
Can't you just live
like you are now?
What's wrong with that?
What a cruel thing to ask of me.
If you suddenly learned one day
that you were
just a counterfeit,
a lie covered with
a layer of skin,
would you have the confidence
to maintain your identity?
If you think simply continuing
to operate is enough
to bring happiness to a machine,
your human ego betrays you.
Okay, fair enough.
But I mean, there--
[DOPPEL] To be in this body
is to be reminded
every waking moment
that I have no soul.
Continuing to exist within
a form that does not
allow any reprieve
from that is torture.
Please.
If this is what you want...
[MIKOTO panting]
[DOPPEL]
Good work, Railgun.
I thank you.
You've got to be kidding me!
You're thanking me for this?
If you are troubled
by something this trivial,
you are too soft
for your own good.
Be reasonable.
This is no different than
disposing of a broken appliance.
[MIKOTO]
Your goal was being destroyed.
And being permanently
destroyed meant getting rid
of the airship
with all of your data
and your creator.
Because Kuriba could use
that data to remake you.
But you can't kill yourself
'cause of your safety.
So you used those gas tanks,
hoping to get the city's
interception systems
to do the job for you.
[DOPPEL]
Yes.
While I can,
I'd like to propose something,
if you're okay with it.
Who is that?
[KURIBA]
What happened?
[KURIBA gasps]
Right on cue.
I was about to say
I'd talk with her.
Hopefully convince her
to never make ano--
[DOPPEL]
What a lucky woman she is.
[CHIEF RESEARCHER yells]
Oh, no! Really?
This isn't happening!
It can't be!
Wait, wait, wait,
Kuriba, we can fix her!
Hurry up and collect her parts!
[MIKOTO]
Hold on!
Just let the Doppelganger
pass away peacefully!
That's what the girl
wants for herself!
[CHIEF RESEARCHER]
What are you talking about?!
[KURIBA]
Chief. I can't do this.
I can't take part in this
experiment any longer.
You--?
[KURIBA] Torturing a subject
for profit or fame
isn't what I'd
call medical care.
It's just self-serving cruelty.
Just a second, now.
Do you have any idea
the good this research
will bring about?
[MIKOTO]
What you want
isn't even in the Doppelganger!
There's no soul inside of her.
It's just a fallacy,
caused by wishful thinking,
when you wanted results.
That's all.
[CHIEF RESEARCHER]
You--
You expect me to believe that?
I'm taking her with me,
no matter what!
[MIKOTO]
This is ridiculous.
Oh, shut up!
Turn around!
Do what I tell you to, or else!
[MIKOTO] Their EM waves tell
me roughly where they are.
But if I'm not careful,
my attack could hit Kuriba.
There's a good chance
that masked kid
is watching what's
going on, but the airship
drifted far from where she is.
And there's no telling
how long it would take her
to get here by car.
[CHIEF RESEARCHER] What nonsense
is this about her not having
a soul?
[MIKOTO]
It's true!
The whole "soul
possession" thing
was just an act that she put
on with artificial muscles.
You're lying!
[MIKOTO]
No, I'm not!
All this time, this poor girl
has been suffering
inside a synthetic body
that has no soul.
That's why she wanted
to be deactivated!
I disagree!
It's in there, just deeper!
Beyond even the artificial
muscles, it has to be!
If I take her apart,
I can prove--!
[KURIBA]
Chief, stop it!
We can't trample over
the Doppelganger's dignity
any more than we already have!
Hey! Let go!
If we don't open our eyes now,
we'll just end up making
this mistake all over again!
[CHIEF RESEARCHER]
Let go!
[gunshot]
[KURIBA gasps]
[CHIEF RESEARCHER]
No! No! You grabbed me!
I didn't mean to shoot you!
[CHIEF RESEARCHER yells]
[MIKOTO]
Kuriba!
Stay with me!
[LEADER] I'll contact the
hospital for you right now.
Seike and Naru
are on their way to--
[MIKOTO] Thanks, but I'll take
care of things here myself.
Just let the hospital
know that I'm on my way.
[LEADER]
All right.
[MIKOTO] What a terrible
place to take a bullet!
Kuro--
[DOPPEL] What a lucky
place to take a bullet.
And would you look at that?
Her lucky streak continues.
There's a cyborg designed
exclusively for her,
right here, with those
parts still intact.
With a little miahilin,
a part of me could help.
They really had me learn
such useless things, huh?
Sissy--!
[MIKOTO]
Kuroko.
I hate to ask, but do you
think you could help me
get these two to the hospital?
I'm pretty exhausted.
[CHIEF RESEARCHER]
No soul?
After everything we went
through, that can't be true.
Wait, that's it!
Even without Kuriba,
I could just replicate
the experiment!
Who needs a willing participant?
I can get myself a
Child Error to save time!
[SHOKUHO] So even a man
who dedicated his life
to researching affordable
cyborg treatments
in order to save the lives
of "medical refugees"
can end up like this.
Good to know even a
noble person can't apply
their brakes once
they go astray.
Human avarice is
a truly frightening thing.
I'll help rewind you
to the point where you
remember your
original intentions.
If you really do have the
capacity to redeem yourself,
you can do it by
crawling your way back
from square one.
[KUROKO]
Sissy?
Did you get some
good news or something?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm.
You know that girl I had
you take to the hospital?
Apparently she's
out of intensive care.
It sounds like she's
recovering nicely.
[KUROKO] Well, you couldn't
wish for better news than that.
[MIKOTO]
And it's all because of you.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, no. Think nothing of it.
I simply wanted to see
this expression of joy
return to your face.
However, I certainly
wouldn't stop you
from showing your
gratitude if that's what
you'd like to do.
Yeah, I think I'll
pass on that one.
[SHOKUHO]
My word.
I see you two are
as close as ever.
[MIKOTO]
Shokuho.
How do you do today?
Misaka? Shirai?
What's up?
"How do you do today?"
Oh, yeah, by the way.
If it's about little Miss
Kuriba, I already know.
I'm just as relieved she
pulled through as you are.
You worked hard out there.
Good job, Misaka.
I worked my butt off.
Don't be condescending.
[KUROKO]
What is happening here?
Is this about when you
snuck out the other night?
When you said you
made a "little deal"
did you mean you
were having a tryst
with Misaki Shokuho?
Uh... In a way, but...
While we're on the topic,
Sissy, did you two not used
to have more friction
between you?
When did you get to be so close?
Trust me, we haven't gotten
to be especially anything.
[KUROKO] Then why are
you keeping what you did
that night a secret?
You must be feeling
guilty about something!
[MIKOTO] What could I have
done that I'd feel guilty about?
Your attempts to dodge the
question are not lost on me!
Oh, calm down, you have
nothing to worry about, Shirai.
Promise.
I'm not going to take
your Sissy away from you.
Well. If I have your word.
But you never know.
Someday I may instead get
the urge to come and take you.
Or not!
[SATEN]
Hey, guys!
Look who's here.
[SATEN]
Hi there, Hokaze! What's up?
Uiharu, Saten, it's a
pleasure to see you again.
How do you do today?
Great!
And how do you do today?
Chill, Uiharu.
Oh, wow.
You guys know each other?
Yeah, we actually just
met the other day
at the 177th branch.
Still killin' it here.
Man! You really give off that
"put-together young
lady" energy.
Especially with those ringlets.
That is so kind, thank you.
Oh! Allow me to introduce you.
This is Misaki Shokuho,
otherwise known as our Queen.
Whoa! Did she say "Queen?"
[SATEN]
Uiharu! It's her, in the flesh!
Believe me, I know!
What are we gonna do?
What a response.
It's nice to meet you two.
[SATEN, UIHARU]
Pleased to meet you!
[SHOKUHO]
It's my pleasure.
You're so shameless.
[SHOKUHO]
Oh?
What was that?
I didn't hear you.
I didn't say anything.
Oh, Sissy!
[HOKAZE] Now listen up,
this is very important.
When speaking to the Queen,
there are rules that must
be observed at all times.
Really, there's never a dull
moment in this city, is there?
[MISAKA]
Hey, Shokuho, wait up!
[LEADER] Okay, so now
that we keep running into
these ridiculously
hard missions...
Does anyone have
any ideas as to how
we can improve Scavenger?
[NARU]
Ooh, ooh!
[LEADER]
Does anyone else have any ideas?
[NARU]
Huh?!
How come I'm not
good enough to pick?
[LEADER]
Agh, fine. Go ahead, Naru.
[NARU] Simply put, we need
ourselves a new member!
Someone who's got
the expertise to make up
for what we're missing!
Wow, Naru's actually
making sense for once.
[LEADER] All right,
so what are we missing?
A Yellow, duh!
--A Yellow?
--What does that mean?
Doesn't "Scavenger"
remind you of something?
Sounds like a superhero team.
Starting with me,
I'm the Pink one.
And Leader, you'd have
to be Red, right?
Seike, I was thinking
maybe you'd be Black,
but nah, you're Blue.
And Yakku, you're so
the White one, I can feel it.
Which means the
only essential color
we're missing is Yellow!
I guess so.
And, building off of that idea,
we could use your ability
to make us all paper outfits,
so we could pose and transform
and do a roll call and stuff.
That's what they do, right?
[LEADER]
Not a chance in hell.
I was just kidding.
That's a great idea--
let's run with that!
[YAKUMARU] I'm gonna say
we should focus on polishing
our skills first.
[LEADER] Yeah, you're
probably right about that.
How can I be an objective judge
if I'm wearing it myself?
It'll just take a second!
[NARU yells]
Why are you doing this?
You've seen me naked
a million times!
It's not like we have
a choice when you
just start stripping!
[NARU] Teammates are supposed
to be open with each other.
Not hide stuff!
[SEIKE] This is a very extreme
interpretation of that!
While we're on the topic
of team improvement,
my chemical stock
is starting to run low.
[SEIKE]
Would you just stop already?
Yeah. I should be able to
take a break soon enough.
'Cause if I recall, you can
only use your ability
for like, three minutes
straight, right?
We should be just about there.
[SEIKE] She was out to run
down the clock from the start?
As dumb as she is?
[SEIKE] Well, Naru can only
pay attention to something
for about 30 minutes anyway.
I just have to kill time
outside until then.
When did she paper the door?
She knew I'd have to
stop my ability to grab
the doorknob and
was waiting for it!
[NARU] Come on now,
Seike, don't be shy.
Let me take a good look!
[SEIKE]
No!
There we go!
Sure enough, Seike,
you're definitely more
of a Blue than a Black!
What was that, some kind
of performance art?
Now our bond as Scavenger
members has increased by--
[LEADER]
Both of you, be quiet.
[SCAVENGER LIASON]
First of all...
I'll start by saying good
work on your mission.
Though it sounds like
it was a bigger deal
than anticipated, huh?
Now, as I'm sure
you've already heard,
the client's business has
recently gone bankrupt.
They've screwed
us out of our pay.
What can you do?
Just consider it a stroke
of bad luck and--
[LEADER]
Wait a second.
What do you expect?
For us to just be
okay with that?
[SCAVENGER LIASON]
What do you want from me?
We no longer have
a client, that money
isn't going to appear
out of thin air.
I don't get my
commission either.
I'm a victim here, too.
[LEADER] The difference is,
we risked our lives out there.
You just had to make
a couple of phone calls.
So don't start
getting cute with us.
That's funny.
You've got bite for being
a little second-string
dark side organization.
[LEADER] This isn't about
being first or second string.
It's not even about the money.
When we take on a mission,
we know the risks.
We may get put on ice, demoted,
or even liquidated,
and we're prepared for that.
So when our contract
is broken, and you try
to dismiss it like
it's no big deal,
do you think we're the
kind who will just submit
and accept that?
No, we're not.
Because we're not stupid.
And we won't accept it
until you at least
show us some good faith.
[SCAVENGER LIASON sighs]
All right.
Since we can't give
you your payment,
I'll restore your group's
rank to its original level.
Normally, you'd have had
to carry out several more
missions for this,
so it's quite the deal.
[LEADER]
Is that all? Really?
How about you throw
in a team name, too?
[SCAVENGER LIASON] Don't press
your luck, you pipsqueak.
Now get to sleep so you're ready
for your next assignment!
[YAKUMARU]
All right!
Way to go, Leader!
This means our pay
will go up next time!
What are they talking about?
[YAKUMARU] Our night-vision
gear is outdated.
And our rations are
past their expiration.
Plus our communicators
are just toys.
[LEADER]
No, we can keep these.
They still work fine.
And besides, I've actually
taken quite a liking
to this character.
[CAT meows]
So, how are you feeling?
Any better?
"Misaka's numbers
are satisfactory.
However, since she
was told to refrain
from leaving the grounds,
she is craving some
out-of-hospital stimulation,"
replies Misaka,
taking the opportunity
to express her dissatisfaction
with her situation.
You gotta prioritize
your recovery.
Here, I bought you that
cake-in-a-jar you like!
You do realize what
is en vogue changes
on a daily basis.
The most popular
item at that shop
is another product now.
That said... Misaka will
still readily take those.
Hmm. What's with the attitude?
You should be more grateful.
Hey! Where are you going?
[KONGO] Am I mistaken,
or are you that cat
from once upon a time?
[MIKOTO]
Kongo?
[KONGO]
Oh, Misaka!
Fancy meeting you here!
Tell me about it.
Why are you here?
Wait you're not still
admitted here, are you?
No, I'm not.
I've returned today
to finish the last
of the remaining paperwork.
But never mind me,
would that happen to be...
You mean...?
This is my sister.
I had a sneaking suspicion.
This young lady is Kongo.
Remember? I told you about her.
About how she helped
me find you?
She really went all out
to bring you back home.
I do.
And I remember that she was
injured for Misaka's sake.
Thank you very much
for your help.
It was no big deal.
Please, don't give it
another thought.
I'm honestly just relieved
that you're back
safe and sound.
Oh, but you know what
would be lovely?
If I could get a name.
Name, you say?
Okay, then. "On Hold."
[KONGO]
Miss On Hold?
That's uh, quite a unique name!
And he seems to have
taken a liking to you.
Oh! I understand,
that's the cat's name!
All right then.
What is your name?
"What is this Misaka's name?
This Misaka is Misaka 10032,"
answers Misaka succinctly.
"One" what? I'm sorry.
Why don't I go ahead
and call you Ichi instead?
--Oh, wow.
--Yes.
Misaka doesn't
mind that nickname.
You're kidding! You like it?
[KONGO] Ichi, is that
a Tokiwadai uniform?
Correct.
Think of it as cosplay.
[KONGO]
Cosplay?
[MISAKA 10032] "Since you
have given Misaka a nickname,
what would be an appropriate
nickname for you?"
asks Misaka, brilliantly
changing the subject.
[KONGO]
Wait, you mean me?
Umm...
All right then.
I guess, since I gave you
one so frivolously,
you can call me. M--. "Mi?"
[DOLLY]
Awesome!
So is this the ocean?
[SHOKUHO] Uh...
Yeah, close enough.
I know you're just
messing around,
but can you not lie to her?
You'll confuse the poor girl.
I told you.
This is an aquarium, remember?
[DOLLY]
Ah!
So it's like a bigger
version of what you used
to make inside that bottle!
I wouldn't say that.
[SHOKUHO] I can't help
but wonder if this is really
the best place we can take her.
I'm well aware
of all the trouble
you have to go through
to leave Academy City,
but if I use my ability
on the right people,
I'm sure I can swing something.
You're right.
But if we went too
far away so soon,
I'd worry about treating her
if her health declined.
Why don't we take it slow?
If you think that's
for the best,
it's certainly good
enough for me.
[DOLLY laughs]
Mi! Misaki, look at that!
That one over there,
is it a dolphin?
[SHOKUHO]
Umm... I don't think so.
Probably a tuna.
[DOLLY]
Oh, I know that one!
I read about them in a book!
They're yummy fish that
dissolve on your tongue!
Are you sure you weren't
reading a cookbook?
[KURIBA]
H-Hey.
It's you.
The Doppelganger.
Is this a dream?
Or a hallucination brought on
by my guilty conscience
as I cross the Acheron river--?
[DOPPEL]
It's a dream.
Are you giving me an
opportunity to apologize?
[DOPPEL]
Apologize?
Why would you expect that?
I didn't try to kill you out of
resentment or anything.
It was but a requisite
condition, that's all.
Then again,
maybe me readily accepting
sacrifices for the sake of
accomplishing my mission
was a pattern of thought
I got from you
during our year together.
You knew that Indian Poker
would bring chaos
to society.
But you didn't mind that.
As long as it gave you
the opportunity to save
your mother from her early fate.
That was all that
mattered to you.
You couldn't even
separate your own life
from your objective.
By your very nature,
you can't accomplish
anything unless you dedicate
your entire being to it.
But with that being said,
there's no need
to fight against who you are.
You can't let yourself
become someone
who's afraid to create
just because it might
end up hurting someone.
Because if you were to do that,
it would be very dull
to coexist with you.
To coexist?
[DOPPEL]
So for starters...
I took the liberty of looking
over the cybernetic
components that you
developed for your mother,
and found three things
you'll need to correct.
Your design will start well,
but will develop some
problems in about ten years.
I'm far better at
running simulations
than you are, you know.
So first of all...
[MIKOTO]
Okay.
So then, the Doppelganger
basically came to you
in your dream?
[KURIBA]
Yeah.
It's the strangest thing.
I only swapped out
a portion of my organs.
That kind of phenomenon really
shouldn't be happening.
That is strange.
[KURIBA] At first I thought it
was it was my own guilt
causing me to hallucinate
or have the same dream
night after night, but...
Yeah that pretty much
sounds exactly like
what she could do
when I fought against her.
[KURIBA] Uh-huh. And what's
more, she went on and on
finding fault with a lot
of the past research
I've done.
So, how can we help you cross
over to the other side?
[DOPPEL] I have no soul,
so I can't cross over.
Now that I've explained
your errors in detail,
next we'll go over
your dark past.
--There's quite a lot to unpack.
--[KURIBA] No, no, no!
To be honest,
I'm afraid to go to sleep.
Well, even so.
[MIKOTO]
That's kind of a relief.
[KURIBA]
I'm sorry.
I sort of ended up dumping
all of my responsibilities
onto you, huh?
And, maybe, it's not really
my place to relay
this to you, but I'm going to.
Throughout all of the
time that Doppelganger
was operational,
she only seemed truly fulfilled
during her battle
with you.
[MIKOTO] Well, if you
happen to run into her
in another one of
your dreams soon,
tell her she wasn't
so bad herself.
Oh, there you are, Sissy.
You kept us waiting.
So I was thinking.
Since we're all around,
why don't we go out
and get something good to eat?
Oh! I know a place.
There's a café around here
from an urban legend
that I've been dying
to check out!
Excuse me, Saten?
[UIHARU]
Man, you never learn, do you?
[SATEN]
What? I was just kidding.
[KUROKO]
No you weren't!
You're always like this.
[MIKOTO] Anywhere's fine,
as long as we're all together.
[MIKOTO]
Okay, let's go!