[SOGIITA]
Super Amazing...
...Punch!
[KAMIJO]
Awesome!
Now's your chance, bud!
No, no, no, no!
Hold on, hold on, wait! Stop!
Good luck!
[KAMIJO yells]
I'm here, might as well try!
Wait, how do I land?
What do I do?
[KAMIJO grunts]
That works.
Uh, thank you.
Even though you're
the reason I was in danger
in the first place.
[SOGIITA]
Well?
No dice.
There's some sort of
power flowing into her
from the outside,
and I can't cancel it.
It worked for a second
on the area I touched.
But it didn't last long.
Okay, so now what?
[KAMIJO] Well, apparently
there's someone aside from us
trying to turn her
back to normal.
Though, I have no idea
who they are.
But until they can
shut down this power
at the source, all we
can do is slow her down.
And from what this
person was telling me,
as long as I stick around,
I should be able to delay
her transformation a little.
'Kay. But she's clearly
still changin' over there.
[KAMIJO] Well, they said slow
down, not completely stop.
[KAMIJO]
S-Sogiita!
[SOGIITA grunts]
Man. I let my guard down.
Pathetic.
[KAMIJO]
Are you actually okay?
How could that
not have hurt you?
You're insane, man.
Looks like I'm gonna
have to put some more
guts into this.
[SHOKUHO] Gensei is after
something, and that puppet
wasn't trying to kill me.
It was trying to
capture me alive.
So he probably thinks
he can get information
out of me.
And I'd be willing to bet
he wants Exterior's
limiter release code.
[KUROKO]
The camera. There it is!
[KUROKO] If the data in
the Bank is correct,
Kozaku's puppets don't
see like humans do.
She senses her surroundings
the way a bat does
using echolocation.
And it's sensitive enough
to pick up the sound
of a heartbeat within
a few dozen meters.
The camera's supplementary.
This calls for...
...the anti-listening devices
I have for security.
For the moment,
I've effectively deprived
Kozaku of her eyes and ears.
Now let's find her.
[GENSEI] Good heavens,
that Shokuho girl really is
the overly cautious one,
isn't she.
I can't find a trace of
how to remove the limiter
on Exterior, and I'm
sure that's exactly
what she's hoping for.
What a wild goose chase this is.
[SHOKUHO]
I knew it. He is after that.
To be able to accurately
control Misaka in that state,
he must need more
power than Exterior
can currently provide.
That's why he has
to unlock the limiter.
All of the major function
codes for Exterior
have been erased
from external memory.
But they're still
inside my head
with picture perfect clarity.
The key to Exterior's
defense is its covertness.
Ideally, no one should ever
know that it even exists.
But, in case word got out,
I have other measures in place.
[GENSEI]
Hm?
[SHOKUHO] This building
and those surrounding it
have a security system
unlike any other.
Naturally this includes
several traps.
Ones that only I can activate.
It'd sure be nice if this
sleeping gas worked.
[GENSEI]
My Multiskill.
While I may not have
nearly as many abilities
at my disposal as Kiyama,
I do have a small, curated
selection of kidnapped--
I mean, secured people,
whose powers I've borrowed.
But of course, you must
have anticipated me
taking such measures.
[SHOKUHO] Ugh. That is
one despicable old man.
But this isn't over
just because he got
through that trap.
If gassing him won't work,
then let's try this.
[GENSEI]
No luck.
[SHOKUHO growls]
Mind if I ask you something
while we're doing this?
[GENSEI]
What is it?
[SHOKUHO]
As I recall,
you concluded only one esper had
a chance of reaching Level 6.
And unsurprisingly,
that was the first-ranked
Level 5, wasn't it?
Mmm. Correct.
I believe he's the only
one who can achieve
a stable Level 6,
at least currently.
Stable?
[GENSEI] So at the moment,
we're letting Misaka's powers
run wild in an attempt
to forcefully push her
towards Level 6.
If she keeps growing
as she has been,
then theoretically,
when she reaches 53% completion,
her mind will transform into
an other-dimensional entity.
And, once she has
reached that point
in her evolution,
we'll require the limiter
unlock code
to even keep her
enmeshed in our world.
Finally, when she reaches 100%,
the moment she becomes Level 6,
both her body and mind
will reach their limit,
and I theorize that she'll
come apart as an individual.
To put it in simplest terms,
Misaka is incapable
of attaining a stable
Level 6 form.
However, in exchange
for losing everything...
For a moment,
one that will
no doubt be shorter
than the blink of an eye,
she will be able to catch
a fleeting glimpse
at the realm of gods.
And as a result,
she will either wither away,
like a white dwarf
star slowly fading
into a black one,
or she will explode
like a supernova,
with enough force to break open
and shatter the doorway
to a new world.
Whichever way she goes,
one thing is for certain--
we'll all witness
something big enough
to blow this city off
the face of the planet.
[SHOKUHO]
If Academy City gets destroyed,
you do realize
you'll be caught up
in the middle of it
too, don't you?
I know that you're a monster,
but I wouldn't have
guessed you were suicidal.
[GENSEI laughs]
You say that like
it's a bad thing.
I fail to see the problem.
In order to advance science,
you must be willing
to make sacrifices.
Spoken like a madman.
This is exactly the
reason I hate dealing
with people who are
running low on sanity.
[GENSEI] This "clairvoyance"
business is surprisingly
inconvenient once
you start using it, huh?
Even though I can see
through the obstructions
before me, I need
to be very precise
in calculating the
distance and direction
of my target.
Dealing with it has wasted
a lot of my valuable time.
Now, even if I were to
try to use Mental Out
to read your memories,
you could just use
the same ability
to lock me out of
your brain entirely.
However, if I put you in
a state where you can't use it,
such as inflicting an
intolerable level of pain,
or knocking you unconscious,
I could get through
quite easily.
[SHOKUHO]
The air... I can't breathe!
Fortunately for me,
you seem rather weak,
so I imagine you'll
give in quickly
before I have to waste
more of my time.
Misaka must have grown plenty
in the time I've spent with you.
Ha ha!
I had anticipated some
kind of interference
from Kamijo, but never
in my wildest dreams
did I think Sogiita would
join the fight as well!
Now I have the stimulus
of Imagine Breaker,
and the extraordinary power
of the seventh-ranked!
It's a sight to behold
as exceptional
as dividing the
universe by zero!
If those two clashed with Misaka
and multiplied her power,
it'd be extraordinary!
I have to go.
I need to gather all
the analytical espers
and equipment I have
to observe this!
No. No!
[SHOKUHO]
What is he, an idiot? Whatever.
At least I got something
out of listening
to his little speech.
It sounds like as long
as I can keep the limiter
unlock code safe, then
Academy City will be spared,
with Misaka being
the only casualty.
Thanks a lot, Misaka.
You won't be forgotten...
for at least a week.
Yeah. If it happens, it happens.
There's nothing
I can do about it.
Doubt he's gonna quit
chasing me just because
I got away at
the first opportunity.
Sheesh.
If Mental Out
were the only ability
he had access to,
this would be a lot easier.
But what am I supposed
to do against a fossil
who cheats by using
Multiskill like that?
At this point, this special
defense system of mine
isn't gonna do much
more than buy me
some extra time.
[SHOKUHO]
Graviton panels?
[clatter]
I guess she's not
in here either.
No good.
It's going to take too long
to search for her blindly.
I need a lead.
[SATEN]
I found her!
This is totally Kozaku, right?
[UIHARU] Saten just found the
suspect on security footage.
Sending it your way now.
The timestamp is
three minutes ago.
Since she hasn't shown up
on any other camera,
I should be able to figure
out which building she's in.
I'll head there now!
[KOZAKU] That's weird.
She's heading in my direction?
The security cameras!
Are you kidding?
Those guys only covered
their own tracks
and not mine?
[KUROKO] And you're sure
she hasn't shown up
on any other cameras
in the area?
Mm-hmm. I checked,
and she isn't anywhere else.
[KUROKO] If she tries to move
to another building now,
the security cameras
will definitely see it!
[KUROKO]
She's in there.
Uiharu, fix all of the
nearby movable cameras
on the target building!
Okay!
[SATEN] At the rate she's going,
she'll find her in no time.
Maybe, but let's stay focused.
But the computer will detect
anything that moves
and let us know.
It's not like we
can't look away.
[beeping]
[UIHARU]
What the--?
[SATEN] Was that the alert?
Did you find something?
[UIHARU]
Can you be quiet for a second?
[SATEN]
Oh, right.
[UIHARU]
Look!
It's using the sewage pipes?
[UIHARU] Shirai, the puppet
is heading your way, and fast!
[KUROKO]
That must mean that I am close.
[SATEN] Is she sending
her puppet to destroy
the surveillance cameras?
Maybe, and we don't
want her creating
a new blind spot
and using it to escape.
Although, every one of
the directional cameras
in the area are fixed
on this building.
She would need a lot
of time to take out
enough of them to
secure herself a viable
escape route.
I have to find her
before that happens.
[crash]
So she's not after
the network of cameras,
but taking me out?
Well that works for me!
I'll take advantage
of her impatience,
and take out this
puppet of hers!
Now that I know her ability
and how to counter it,
the threat it poses is minimal.
[KUROKO yells]
[KUROKO grunts]
[UIHARU] What's the matter,
Shirai? Did something--?
[KUROKO]
I was just careless.
So I ended up taking
a little counter damage.
[UIHARU] Huh? Are you
sure you're all right?
[KUROKO]
Yes, it's not a big deal.
She only grazed my side,
but the cut on my arm
went a lot deeper.
And after my old wounds
were starting to heal!
I'm supposed to be
saving this body
for when I get married!
Still, now I'm certain.
Kozaku really is here.
Moreover, she's on
the upper floors.
That last attack was
able to hit its target
despite my
anti-listening devices
blocking out the puppet's
senses at the time.
Which means that Kozaku
herself saw me
and directed the strike.
Further, each appendage
took similar paths.
She was trying to
catch me linearly.
Most likely, she was
watching from above,
couldn't tell my precise
location,
and split the attack up
to increase her chances
of hitting me.
If I come at her from below,
she has nowhere to run.
It's only a matter
of time before I catch
her real body.
But, truth be told,
something doesn't
feel quite right.
Like there's something
that I've overlooked.
[GENSEI]
Hm?
Ah, Shokuho!
[chuckles] Hey.
Forgive me for getting
so excited earlier.
I should really try
to act my own age.
It's just that when I see
something I wasn't expecting,
that's it.
I'm practically blind
to everything else
around me until I calm down.
That bad habit
has almost killed me
a number of times.
[SHOKUHO] I wish it had
so I didn't have to deal
with you anymore.
[GENSEI]
But this is unexpected.
For you to be standing there,
in the middle of the hallway,
waiting for me?
I was certain you'd be
keeping your distance.
[SHOKUHO]
Why waste the energy?
I doubt I could get
away from you
with your clairvoyance.
And if you caught me
outside this building,
I wouldn't have access
to my security measures
and I'd be completely
defenseless.
So. I came to make a deal.
[GENSEI]
What kind of deal?
One where I tell you what
the limiter unlock code
for Exterior is,
and you let me go.
Huh?
[SHOKUHO] I thought about
it for a little while,
and decided that
I really don't care
what happens to Misaka.
And if Academy City is
getting blown off the map,
I have to make sure
I get out of here first.
So I've waited for you.
You'll find me anyway,
so why waste
any time running around
when I can use it
to get out of the city?
Hmm. That does make sense.
[SHOKUHO]
Good, almost there.
[GENSEI] But this negotiation
feels a bit one-sided.
What do I get out of the deal?
[SHOKUHO] Well, I can't
exactly use my Mental Out
on you anymore, right?
And this situation
has made me realize
without my ability,
I'm simply an elegant,
captivating young woman
with a knockout figure.
And you don't want
to have beating up
a delicate girl like me weighing
on your conscience, do you?
Unless that's how
you get your kicks,
but I have a feeling it's not.
My ultra-high-power-
oscillator-embedded trap,
the "Hag's Hug."
Once you step on it,
you're finished.
The vibrations will shoot
up through your foot.
They'll reflect and amplify
through your body
as they travel up and
converge in your head.
It'll destroy your ears'
semicircular canals
and give your brain
a good shake!
[GENSEI]
Hmm.
[SHOKUHO]
One more step.
[SHOKUHO gasps]
[GENSEI]
You're right.
As long as I get my hands
on the limiter unlock code,
I don't need you for
any particular reason.
But there is one thing
that concerns me.
I noticed you've been
fixated on this particular
spot for the last few minutes.
Is there perhaps something
waiting there for me?
You knew?
Yeah, just kidding.
[GENSEI gasps]
[SHOKUHO]
That was a decoy!
The actual trap was
right under your feet
the entire time!
Graviton panels.
Normally, they just form
a pathway for me
to use as my own
personal shortcut,
but this time,
I set them up to mimic
the floor before you got here.
Enjoy being trapped down there.
Are his feet exploding?
No, he's compressing
the air underneath them
to make steps.
That's how he was
able to choke me
and change the direction
of those flames
I shot at him earlier.
He has the Aero Shooter ability!
[SHOKUHO grunts]
[GENSEI]
That's enough.
I don't intend to spend
any more time
on you, Princess, okay?
You won't get away this time.
Let's end this now.
[GENSEI yells]
[SHOKUHO]
How do you like that?
Looks like I laid more
traps than you expected
me to.
I was hoping I'd get
to use this.
They take a while to build up,
so this can only work on someone
who's let their guard down.
Who knew graviton
panels were handy
in so many different situations?
The technology was developed
to make temporary
scaffolding for use
at construction sites,
but as you're well aware by now,
they can also be
deployed to crush
the brittle arms of old men.
With all that intense pain,
do you think you'll be able
to defend yourself
against my Mental Out?
[GENSEI]
Huh?
[laughing]
Wow, you're a terrible girl!
To put a helpless,
feeble old man such as myself
through such agony?
Though, I would have
to actually have a wrist
in order for you to crush it.
A... prosthetic?
[GENSEI]
Didn't I tell you?
My experiments have nearly
killed me many times.
My entire body is
basically a showcase
for prosthetic
replacement technology.
And I was pretty much
able to read your true
intentions prior
to this, anyway.
Someone who's
pretending to run away
but still has some plan
shows telltale signs
of what they're after.
I don't let those hints
that they're about
to turn the tables go unnoticed.
I'm experienced.
Which is why I can
tell something else
by looking at you now.
You're out.
You have nothing left
up your sleeve
to reverse the situation,
do you?
[GENSEI chuckles]
And now the limiter
unlock code... is mine.
[KUROKO] I should already be
on top of Mitori Kozaku,
but I'm having trouble
reaching her.
And something feels
out of place.
No matter, I'll still find
her whatever it takes.
Huh? Does Shokuho not
have a line this time?