I wonder what I should
have you make for me.
Curry is, all told,
the obvious choice.
But as far as other dishes
that are good with mackerel,
we've got options.
[SATEN gasps]
[RAKKO chuckles]
[SATEN]
Blood? Wait, what happened?
Wha--? Hey, what's going on?
[FRENDA]
We're being shot at!
But from where?
The bullet went right through.
But I'm okay.
I still have feeling in my arm.
I have to contact Mugino and--
I shouldn't be visible
to the surrounding buildings
at this angle.
It's not a long-range shooter.
Hey, are you all right?
[FRENDA]
We're going inside!
[SATEN]
Hold on!
[RAKKO chuckles]
So she gave up
on calling her friends
as well as this hiding spot.
She knows how much
danger she's in.
After fleeing into
the department store
and pausing for a moment,
they took the elevator
to a higher floor.
[chuckles]
I do hope you'll entertain me.
[SATEN]
Do you think they came after me?
--[FRENDA] Probably.
--[SATEN] Um, okay.
[FRENDA] We're gonna try
to buy some time in here.
All told, with this many people
every way you look,
it should be easy for us
to disguise ourselves,
blend in,
and give them the slip.
[SATEN gasps]
[FRENDA]
They took a shot?
In a crowd like this,
with no hesitation?
[FRENDA]
Run!
Uh, right!
[FRENDA]
Crap.
They're the ones using
the crowd against us!
[RAKKO] If you thought this
situation would help you,
you're sorely mistaken.
My sniper rifle
is under my clothes.
I can assemble it
simply by bending
and stretching my arm.
And I can silently shoot
my rounds with the force
of CO2 gas.
There isn't a single
person here who realizes
I'm a sniper aiming at you.
We should ask some
of these people to help.
That won't do anything for us!
They're more likely to panic,
which would just end up limiting
our movement instead.
We're up against an enemy
hiding in the crowd.
That could be a fatal move!
Then we could try to borrow
someone's phone.
[FRENDA]
And what?
Risk that person getting
their head blown off?
[FRENDA] We're being driven
into an emptier area.
There are two types of hunters--
The type who take joy
in doing a perfect job
without ever letting their
presence be known.
And the type
who like to show off
and enjoy watching
their prey writhe in pain.
This one is definitely
the latter!
And the reason I know that
is that all told,
I'm the latter, too!
[RAKKO chuckles]
[STREET MAN A grunts]
Why is this happening to me?
[CROWD chattering]
[STREET MAN A]
I didn't have any choice!
I didn't double-cross you
because I wanted to!
--You think that blood's real?
--No way!
Anything!
[CROWD gasps, yells]
[RAKKO] Ah, the pleasure of
that last, wretched scream
the prey lets out.
I wonder.
What kind of sound
will you make in the end?
[FRENDA] This person probably
has a personal set
of expectations for their hunt.
So if their prey deviates
in some way
that displeases them,
they'll kill them
on the spot.
On the other hand,
that means they'll prolong this
as long as we play
into their quirks.
In other words, that sadistic
nature is going to
cost them their life.
If they're targeting us
from the crowd.
I've got you!
[FRENDA] You fell for it,
you twisted sicko!
Thought I was over there, huh?
In reality, I was right here,
waiting to ambush you!
What do you mean?
[FRENDA] Don't you dare
play dumb with me!
[SATEN]
Hey, is that necessary?
He shot me twice,
so yeah, it is!
[SATEN] But how can you be
sure he's the one who did it?
[FRENDA] If you're targeting
someone from a crowd,
you're gonna have to
disguise your firearm.
And glancing around the area,
this guy is the only one
carrying something
long enough.
You gotta think critically!
This golf bag is
irrefutable proof!
Okay, but there's nothing but
ordinary golf clubs inside.
[MALL MAN A yells]
[SATEN]
Sorry about that!
[RAKKO]
No good, I'm afraid.
I'm tracking your actions
with perfect clarity.
You're easy to read.
Interesting.
She threw something
on the ground here
before running off.
I'm glad to be able to come
over to your place
for dinner again, Himegami.
It feels like it's been forever.
Get ready!
Today, we're going to flex
those cooking muscles!
Damn it!
Who does that girl think she is?
I was just minding my own
business. What the hell?
[MALL MAN A grunts]
[KOMOE] Um, are you
all right, young man?
[HIMEGAMI]
That was close.
One wrong step, and we
would have ended up
like that.
[RAKKO]
Traps by the merchandise.
I see that she isn't
concerned with involving
any innocent bystanders.
Isn't that nice?
What lovely desperation.
But it's pointless.
[FRENDA gasps]
[FRENDA]
They took off half my ear!
Damn it!
[YOBOU]
What's up? I'm back.
I snagged us three cards,
and I brought a researcher
from the place that
was keeping all of them.
Good work out there.
[YOBOU]
Any word from Yumiya?
No, nothing yet.
Let's just hope she's
not up to her old tricks.
That'd be a mess.
[FRENDA panting]
[FRENDA] Damn it, they're not
falling for any of my traps
or feints.
They've made no mistakes.
They know everything we do.
Did they stick a
transmitter on her?
[FRENDA] No, even if they did,
it still wouldn't explain
how they're avoiding
all my traps.
Hey, hold up!
[FRENDA] How can they know
every move we make?
Not even Takitsubo's AIM
stalker can do that.
It's not telepathy, either.
With all the distance between us
and the constantly changing
sources of cover,
they should have
lost us long ago.
I can't figure out
how to counter this.
[RAKKO]
I suppose it's about time.
Once I shoot through her legs
and she can't move anymore,
she'll start begging
for her life--
Oh, no!
This is terrible timing!
I'm on a mission!
But what if they're like,
"Oh, Yumiya!
What a crazy coincidence,
running into you here like this!
By all means, come and join us!"
If they were to invite me
along like that,
I'd have no choice
but to say yes!
[STUDENTS laugh]
[RAKKO]
What an amazing assassin I am.
My ability to blend in
with my surroundings
is utterly perfect.
And no, it has nothing
to do with me being
a loner who's
practically invisible
to the average person.
Oh, they're gone.
[FRENDA]
It hurts, a lot.
Honestly, without knowing
where they're attacking from,
I basically have no options.
Why is this happening to me?
[SATEN]
Hey!
[FRENDA]
That's right.
I'm not even
the one they're after.
All told,
I only know her
because we shared one
canned mackerel dinner.
I'm under no obligation
to protect her.
If we both run in
opposite directions,
the enemy will follow her.
I hate to do this, but I have
to use her as bait.
I can't just ditch her, because
she'll come chasing after me.
I have to talk her
into it somehow--
[SATEN]
Hey! We should split up!
What?
If we go in
different directions,
it's more likely
they'll come after me.
[SATEN]
Huh? What is it--?
[FRENDA]
I know we should split up!
You don't have to tell me that!
But if you left my side,
could you protect yourself?
You're a Level 0, right?
Do you think they won't kill
you after they catch you?
I don't know what kind
of info you have,
but once you tell them
what they want to know,
they'll just get rid of you!
I know, but if we do nothing,
they're gonna get both
of us at this rate.
And I know I'm just a liability.
I-It's all right.
I can hold my own
in a race, trust me.
[FRENDA]
All told...
I knew you were soft from
the second I saw you.
But I didn't think
you were this dumb.
But...
If you insist, then I guess
we'll do this your way.
Let's turn you into a decoy.
[RAKKO sighs]
This isn't good.
If I take too long,
Yobou will chew me out again.
[YOBOU]
Hm?
[RAKKO]
I have to hurry.
She's coming this way
by herself?
[FRENDA] But, if you insist,
then I guess we'll do this
your way.
Let's turn you into a decoy.
You're nothing but a
level 0 burden right now.
But if you're willing to
put your life on the line,
you can become
the perfect soldier.
[SATEN]
All right.
[FRENDA]
Are you sure about this?
What if I'm tricking you
to save my own skin?
[SATEN] If you hadn't rescued me
when they first caught me,
I'd already be dead.
So even if you do run,
I won't hold a grudge.
Yeah?
[RAKKO] My tracking is
for following targets.
If they come back to me,
I can't tell
what their actions
are on the way.
I doubt she's seen
through my skills--
this is just a coincidence.
But I know what
my prey is trying to do.
Identify me.
The blonde is using
the black-haired one
as a decoy so she
can observe the crowd.
She'll make a note
of whoever reacts
to her friend and attack
them from the shadows.
But it won't work.
As someone who has
mastered the art of lonely--
I mean assassination,
I can blend perfectly
into a crowd and not
look out of place.
My gaze, my expression,
the way I carry myself.
All perfectly natural.
Ah well, there's
always the chance
that she abandoned the
black-haired one to run away,
but that would just make
things more fun for me,
so I wouldn't mind.
Friendship is such
a superficial thing, after all.
[RAKKO gasps]
No, that isn't it.
She didn't abandon her.
The blonde's plan is...
Bombs?
This girl is expendable! Crap!
This plan gets her
everything she wants.
She can waltz
right on out of here,
and every witness
will be caught up
in the explosion!
Not to mention, it'll kill me!
It's three birds with one stone!
But if she commits
indiscriminate mass murder,
her whole organization
is done for.
Does she really think
the cornered mouse
can bite the cat?
[RAKKO gasps]
[RAKKO] Oh, no!
Gotta get behind the pillar!
Whoopsie.
[MALL MAN B]
Is everything okay?
--[SATEN] Yeah. Thanks though.
--[RAKKO] Oh, crap--
[FRENDA]
I found you!
[RAKKO grunts]
[FRENDA]
All told,
the only person around
here who realized
my doll was supposed
to be a bomb was you.
You've been tormenting
me with this game
of cat and mouse,
but I'm gonna get you
a hundred times as hard!
You've turned the tables.
[MALL WOMAN D]
What was that?
[CROWD chattering]
[MALL MAN D]
Run! Let's get out of here!
[MALL MAN F]
Don't push!
[CROWD chattering]
[SATEN] Not to be pessimistic,
but do you really think
this'll help us find them?
Basically.
But if they have a way to see
what we're doing right now,
then we're out of luck.
If my prediction
is correct, though,
this should be enough
to force them out of hiding.
Once they're safely identified,
I'll leap in to fight them.
Everyone will panic and leave.
Stick with the crowd
and get out of here.
--I can help!
--[FRENDA] All told...
If you stay, it puts me
at a disadvantage.
If you get taken hostage again,
I won't save you this time.
Besides, we've always been
from two different worlds.
It'll be much easier if you
just forget about this girl
you're probably
never gonna see again.
But... the mackerel!
I figured you might come
over for dinner again,
so I stocked up on
a whole bunch of it
just in case!
I can't eat it all by myself.
If you don't step up
and come eat it with me,
it'll all go to waste!
[RAKKO yells]
[RAKKO grunts]
[RAKKO]
Miniature bombs?!
They may only be
good for shockwaves
with no shrapnel inside,
but to use bombs
in close-quarters
combat is insane!
However...
[RAKKO laughs]
If your arm is so messed up
that you can't throw right,
then you're no longer a threat!
[RAKKO grunts]
Really? With all that boasting,
I was expecting you to be
less pathetic.
Weren't you gonna pay
me back a hundredfold?
Good luck.
How can you
when you can't even stand?
[FRENDA]
I...
I can't keep this up
much longer, huh?
All told,
the reason I'm staying down
is because it's about
to be a whole lot safer
here on the ground.
[RAKKO grunts]
[RAKKO]
A mass detonation?
When did she plant
so many of them?
Was it while the
black-haired one
was acting as a decoy?
She might be trying to
use the smoke as cover,
but it will take a lot more
than this to get away
from my nose.
If anything, I'm the one
with the advantage here.
[RAKKO]
Wait, what?
Low oxygen?
She was using thermobarics?
So that's what you were up to.
Sorry, but you didn't
close the deal!
There's no point unless
it's an airtight space!
And there's plenty
of oxygen streaming in
from the windows you broke!
[RAKKO gasps]
[FRENDA chuckles]
[RAKKO yelping]
[screams]
Ha det bra !
[TEACHER A] So, you can't
think of anything you did
that would have
made you a target?
[SATEN]
No.
[door opens]
[SATEN] Sorry I couldn't
be of more help.
Ugh. That questioning
took forever!
At least it's over now.
[SATEN]
Thanks for waiting, Uiharu.
I've got a rough schedule
mocked up for you.
Considering how little we know,
there's a chance you
may still be in danger.
So for the next few days,
you're going to be staying
at an Antiskill facility.
Once it's been determined
that the threat
has lessened enough,
you can go back
to your dorm.
At that point,
you'll still be guarded
by Judgment until they
decide you're safe without it.
So you're in good hands.
[SATEN]
All that for me, huh?
[UIHARU]
It's no trouble!
So hey, about that mall, uh...
[UIHARU]
Oh, right.
According to the report,
there were signs of
explosives and a struggle,
which lines up with all
of the witness statements.
They also didn't find any
injured people or bodies.
Oh, yeah?
[UIHARU] All right,
let's get you moved in.
If there's anything you need,
I can get it ready for you.
Hmm... Well,
I did lose something.
[phone chimes]
[SATEN gasps]
[KAKINE]
Good work on that lousy job.
Thanks to you guys,
we have more data
on the tweezers.
Even though their
exact whereabouts
are still unknown,
we've confirmed that within
the next few days,
they're gonna be used
at a facility near
Kirigaoka Girls' School.
And there's no arguing
with our source this time.
We'll handle this ourselves.
The calculations we'll need--
[RAKKO]
Wait a second!
Before we do that,
give me the chance to hunt
down that damn blonde girl!
[KAKINE]
Hey, now.
It's only thanks to Yobou
slipping onto the scene
at the last second that you
got way with your life.
Don't waste it yet.
Listen.
I can't blame you
for being pissed,
but with the regenerative
treatments in this city,
your face can be restored.
Besides, without that
nose you're so proud of,
do you really think
you can track her?
[RAKKO] I can find her location
by using the black-haired girl's
cell phone.
Besides. I don't feel
the slightest bit angry
at that smug little goldilocks.
She and I had a death match
under extreme circumstances.
She did everything in her
power to get close to me!
That's what friendship
is, isn't it?
You said the two of you
had a similar scent,
didn't you?
Relax.
That means you'll
bump into each other
soon enough.
[RAKKO] I can't afford
to be relaxed about this!
I'm sure she's waiting
for me too.
She must be!
[KAKINE]
Hey.
How many more seconds of my life
am I gonna have to waste on you?
[RAKKO whimpers]
[YOBOU gags]
[HEART MEASURE] Guess he
still hasn't gotten over all
that trauma yet.
[KAKINE]
The tweezers take priority.
Personal grudges come after.
[RAKKO grunts]
[HEART MEASURE]
What do we do?
She might be completely
useless to us now.
It's your call.
We had a backup sniper anyway,
didn't we?
Either way, a lot of people
are gonna die this time.
To hell with whatever
Academy City has in mind.
I've got my own dirty tricks.
And I'm gonna
do whatever I want.
[doorbell rings]
[SATEN gasps]
[groans]
Jeez, you took your sweet time!
Dinner is getting cold!
Hello...
[SATEN]
Oh. Uiharu.
I, uh, brought you
today's security report.
But frankly, there's
really nothing in there
to report.
Well, that's good.
I know you're hurt,
so thanks for still checking
on me.
As long as you're here,
why don't you come in?
[UIHARU]
I could, but...
It turns out I made
way too much dinner.
You're welcome to some,
if you want.
[SHOKUHO] Hey Misaka, you break
into places all the time,
don't you?
By now you must have
done it, what, 100 times?
[MIKOTO]
What do you want from me now?
[SHOKUHO] Since you're
such a professional and all,
there's somewhere
I need you to sneak into.
Congratulations on number 101!
[MIKOTO] You need to learn
how to ask for a favor!