[MIYAMA] Foreseen phenomena
are basically etched in stone.
Actions taken to change
them can only make
a small degree of difference.
The core of the event will
happen no matter what.
So basically there's
no escaping fate.
Is that what you mean?
Something like that.
I don't know if anything
as occult as fate is real,
but there might be some
causative principle at work.
Unfortunately, precognition is
a poorly understood field.
But every prediction has
proved to be unavoidable
until the one you changed today.
We don't know much
about my ability just yet,
but it seems to be
based on calculations
in a three-dimensional
framework.
And ordinarily, that pathway
I predict can't be altered.
[UIHARU gasps] Then there's
Shirai's teleporting.
It's based on 11 dimensions!
Do you think that's why
it's capable of interfering
with an unavoidable
three-dimensional outcome?
Well it's all just theoretical.
[KUROKO]
What is that?
It's only your average penlight.
But I like to carry it around
for times like these.
It makes it easier to
concentrate when using
my second-stage.
I could've been lying to you.
But a demonstration will
prove I'm telling the truth.
So I'm going to use my power
to predict something
that isn't recorded
in the app yet.
[shutter clicks]
Go ahead and scan
that photo with the app.
[UIHARU]
Uh, okay.
Here it is.
Less than a kilometer
south-southwest of here.
[KUROKO] Let me tag along
and confirm this for myself.
[UIHARU] It looks like it
happens in 40 minutes.
[RIVER GIRL A]
This is dangerous.
We should go get a grown-up.
[RIVER GIRL B]
It's totally fine!
I almost got it. See?
No proble--[yells]
[RIVER GIRL A]
Chisa!
[RIVER GIRL B gasping]
Help!
[UIHARU] Good thing
you brought life rings.
It made sense since
the location was a river.
[RIVER GIRL B crying]
[MIYAMA] Was that enough
to verify my ability?
Yes, and what about mine to you?
That's the second time my
teleportation has intervened
with your precognition.
Not a bad deal, right?
As a member of Judgment,
I'm sure you can see
the value in helping victims
before they get hurt.
[KUROKO]
Not a bad deal at all.
[KURO-GYARU screams]
Whoa! Maki?
I knew it!
You are cheating on me, Ta!
No, no, no, hold on a second.
It's not what you think, this
chick came on to me first!
I what?
[MAKI yells]
[KURO-GYARU]
Really?
I understand how you must feel,
but don't do anything
you're going to regret.
You should step in,
or this will end up uglier
than predicted.
[STREET GIRL A hums]
[STREET GIRL A]
Huh?
[STREET WOMAN A]
How did that get out?
But you guys bumped into us--
What's that?
Do you have any idea
who you're talkin' to,
ya little brat?
If you haven't heard, we're--
I'm sure Antiskill would
be very interested
in knowing you who are.
[MIYAMA]
Nice job.
--You're pretty good at this.
--[KUROKO] Thank you.
[NEWSCASTER A] We have some
further information on that mass
unconsciousness incident
the other day.
According to a
release from Antiskill,
the victims are not showing
any discernable aftereffects,
but the cause is still
unknown at the moment.
Well, that's interesting.
It looks as though your
ability missed that one.
I can't say for sure,
but maybe it didn't register
'cause they were only asleep
and didn't really get hurt.
Plus, I don't know
if I've told you,
but it prioritizes incidents
that are close to me.
When I think about it that way,
it's more of a roundabout
way of sensing danger.
But, since nothing I do can
change the outcome anyway,
sensing it doesn't
do me much good.
--Here.
--[KUROKO] Huh?
[MIYAMA]
For your leg.
[KUROKO] Oh. I must've
scraped it at some point.
[MIYAMA] Even if you're
gonna treat it later,
you should still
wipe it down now.
You may come off a bit cold.
But I have to admit, you do
know how to treat a lady.
[MIYAMA] Well, I make an effort
to be considerate toward women
as much as possible.
Even if that woman is
someone like you, Kuroko.
You should have quit
while you were ahead. Jeez.
[MIYAMA]
Hey, why did you join Judgment?
[KUROKO]
Huh?
Well... How can I put this?
I guess I would say it's to
maintain order in the city.
So for the sake of justice?
Sort of.
Though I can't say I was
prepared to put it into words.
[MIYAMA] I don't really
understand things that don't
have a clear reasoning
behind them, myself.
[camera shutter clicks]
[MIYAMA grunts]
[MIYAMA]
I have a new prediction.
[KUROKO] You look somewhat pale.
Are you okay?
[MIYAMA]
I'm just a little anemic.
Is that... the park?
[UIHARU] The time is tomorrow,
in the late afternoon.
Miyama, is something the matter?
Just look.
[KUROKO]
Two of them in the same park?
This is the first time we've
seen that happen.
[MIYAMA] This one is a
prediction I had before I met
you two.
Both predictions are
supposed to happen
at just about the same time.
Could they be related?
Like they're both part of the
same accident somehow?
Maybe. But the two incidents
are separated
by several hundred meters.
The first photo has
already been analyzed.
I used the machine back
at the research lab,
but like I told you,
they always come out blurry.
From what I could make out,
I think there was a lot of fire.
A fire?
Would it be possible for us
to see the analysis
of that photo?
[MIYAMA]
Sorry.
I don't have it, and it's not
very easy to sneak things
out of the lab.
If you're right and the two
predictions are related
to each other,
then that means this fire
would cover an
alarmingly wide area.
So a fire, an explosion,
pyrokinesis.
I can't think of anything else
we might be dealing with here.
And if it stretches
over such a large area,
there's a high chance
that people other than
the two he predicted will be
caught in the middle of it.
In that case,
This is beyond what we can
reasonably deal with alone.
If I promise to keep you out
of this as much as possible,
can I ask for assistance?
[AOMI]
Excuse me!
This month happens to
be Crime Prevention Month.
Would it be all right if we
checked your student IDs
before you entered?
[PARK MAN A]
Sure.
We appreciate it.
[KONORI] He's not in
possession of any explosives
or hazardous materials.
[AOMI]
Great. All set.
Thanks very much
for your cooperation.
[KUROKO] We've got checkpoints
set up at every park entrance.
We'll cross-check esper
abilities with the Bank,
ban any hazardous materials,
and search for any already here.
Including the help provided
from other branches,
Judgment's presence here
is 40 members strong.
I'm relieved,
but also surprised.
We're lucky they agreed to come
with our vague explanation.
[KONORI] Well, to be honest,
it's not that hard
to figure out what's
going on here.
Those girls have been
at every incident lately,
saving people
before they're hurt.
There's gotta be some sort
of precognition involved.
[KONORI] Some Judgment
members were asking why
we didn't shut down
the park entirely,
and I can't help
but wonder myself,
but there must be some
reason why we can't.
I wish we had a better
idea of what stage
your ability interferes
with the future.
If we did, we could
plan this out
much more efficiently.
[KUROKO]
Yes, I agree.
We can't close the park since
that might move the fire,
so for now we just have
to keep an eye out.
Two more hours.
[UIHARU] There. Hey, Shirai.
Put this on for me.
[KUROKO]
What is it?
That's satellite imagery.
It should let you see where
everyone in the park is.
I figured it'd be useful
for the operation.
Wow!
You got permission to--
Wait, did you hack into it?
Lives are more
important than rules.
Also, witnesses
have recently reported
an increase in stray cats
and dogs at the garbage dump.
You okay?
[KUROKO] Yes, it's just...
those cherry blossoms.
It's October--
not exactly their season.
Does that happen?
[UIHARU]
Hmm...
Well, after the temperature
drops considerably
and then gets warm again,
I think cherry blossoms
will sometimes get tricked
into thinking spring has come.
[KUROKO] Have we had that
kind of weather, though?
[UIHARU]
No, we haven't.
[ringing]
[KUROKO]
Is something wrong?
I've made more predictions.
Two this time.
Both of them take place
inside the park, too.
These aren't that close
to the previous two.
They're spread about the park.
Thank you. This is helpful.
If we refocus our search
based on this layout--
[KUROKO]
Miyama!
His red blood cells are damaged?
Hmm. That's right,
and as a result,
they're struggling to
transport oxygen properly.
It's rare, but it's a
phenomenon occasionally seen
when espers overexert
their abilities.
As you can imagine,
I recommend he refrain
from using it
for the time being.
Otherwise, he could be
putting his life in danger.
[KUROKO] Why would you do
something so reckless?
[OKAWACHI]
Hey. Hey!
[MIYAMA]
Okawachi?
Your ability lets you see
when bad things happen
to people, right?
Talk about depressing!
More like gross.
Perro!
Oh, there you are.
My ability is pretty morbid.
It just shows people suffering.
But maybe if I'm lucky,
someday in the future
it can be used to help
people somehow.
Who knows?
Maybe it could protect them.
Yeah, right.
[RESEARCHER A] Here's the
analysis of your photo from
the other day.
[MIYAMA]
Is that...!
No. Okawachi?
[OKAWACHI]
Wait, so you mean that's me?
[MIYAMA]
Probably.
H-Hey...
I'm sorry for all those
mean things I said!
Do something!
I'm trying, that's why I
secretly made a copy for you.
We need to come up with
a plan to change the future.
Get out of here!
[MIYAMA]
Okawachi. I'm...
I'm sorry we couldn't
change the future.
"Change it," huh?
Are you sure this didn't happen
because you foresaw it?
Are you sure you don't bring
misfortune to people?
It's not--
This is your fault!
You're the reason that this
happened to me, aren't you?
I don't ever want to
see your face again,
you big jinx!
[MIYAMA]
It didn't help, Perro.
I tried everything I could
think of, but in the end,
it didn't change
anything at all.
I just have to accept it.
No matter what I do, I can't
protect people after all.
[MIYAMA]
What? Perro?
No... How is this
happening again?
Is it really because
of my ability?
[MIYAMA grunts]
Do you have a headache?
No, it's nothing.
[camera shutter clicks]
[MIYAMA] If I can find that
sensation I felt before...
[camera shutter clicks]
Interfering with a prediction?
Depending on their ability,
it's possible someone
could do that.
[MIYAMA]
Found them.
And they're with Judgment--
People who voluntarily
help others.
But, I'm not sure they
would save a stray dog.
Still...
Where am I?
Oh, no!
[UIHARU]
It's just about time.
[KUROKO]
Yes.
No explosives or
suspicious people so far.
There aren't any gas lines or
shopping areas underground.
It's hard to imagine
that these incidents
are not actually supposed
to be in the park.
[KUROKO]
So what is it, then?
It's starting!
[UIHARU]
Ready, Konori?
[KONORI]
You bet.
Don't forget the plan.
We need to be prepared
to protect any civilians
that Kuroko teleports to us.
[PARK WOMAN B yells]
[KUROKO]
Remain calm.
I'm about to teleport
you out of here.
Once I do, please follow
the nearby Judgment officers
and evacuate.
[KUROKO]
Next up...
[gasps]
It's already this widespread?
I saw a fire way in the distance
and started filming it,
but like a second later
the flames were right up on me!
[KUROKO] The flames
are growing too quickly.
This can't be a regular fire.
The things burning the
worst are the cherry trees.
Cherry blossoms.
They do seem out of place
with them blooming
out of season.
What's causing it?
Did you say that there
are plant ampules?
[KUROKO]
Yes.
Whatever it is that's been
injected into the ground
beneath the trees is
likely highly flammable.
If you're right, then once
this mystery substance
has passed into
the soil and trees,
all the rows of cherry
blossoms would effectively
become one giant fuse!
All right.
Simulating the spread
of the fire based on
that hypothesis now.
You can use the simulation
to decide where to go next.
[MIYAMA]
Perro.
[UIHARU]
Shirai!
[KUROKO]
This girl is the last one.
I looked into those ampules.
We found a bunch of them
at the bases of trees
around here, too.
Sure enough, they don't appear
to be commercially made.
[GROUP gasps]
Well, that's all we needed to
see to prove your hypothesis.
Yes.
But who on earth would
do something like this?
[MIYAMA]
Kuroko?
[KUROKO]
Miyama!
[MIYAMA]
I need your help.
Can you please teleport
me into the middle
of the park grounds?
It might serve as
interference or something.
Slow down.
Take a deep breath and
tell me what's going on.
A stray dog?
That was your first prediction
that was in the park,
wasn't it?
[MIYAMA]
Yeah, but he's my friend, so...
Can you tell me what
this dog looks like?
Uiharu, check the
satellite imagery for me.
The smoke is too thick.
Hold on. If I remove
the unaffected areas,
I'll be able to narrow
it down in a minute.
[KUROKO]
Konori!
Okay.
Let's do it.
[KUROKO]
That kid.
I had a feeling he might
be hiding something from us.
But did he really think
we wouldn't help him
rescue a stray puppy?
[KUROKO] For acting so
adult all the time,
he sure is childish
in some weird ways.
Heads up!
I've narrowed it down!
[KONORI]
Next!
Not here. Or here.
[MIYAMA]
Kuroko!
Come back here and
send me in there instead!
I'm being too selfish.
I have been from the start!
Teleporting can interfere
with my predictions, yes.
But that doesn't mean
it will always change
the future for the better.
It might not!
I shouldn't have gotten
you involved in this mess.
I can't let you become
a victim, too!
This is a much bigger disaster
than any of the others.
You don't have to be
so willing to--
[KUROKO]
Miyama.
If you risking your own health
to rescue a stray dog
is selfish,
then my refusal to back down
now is plenty selfish too.
I found him! He's limping away
from the fire over there!
[KUROKO]
Just watch.
Because what some people
might call selfishness
is the very thing that you
and I would call justice!
[MIYAMA gasps]
Kuroko...
[MIYAMA]
Perro...
Don't tell me that they...
Good work out there.
That was a close call,
but we're in one piece.
It's a good thing I had
those ampules.
I threw them in the
opposite direction the fire
was advancing and was
able to change its course
for a few critical seconds.
Judging by your face, I'm
guessing we got the right dog.
Other than his left hind leg,
I don't see any
obvious injuries,
though he may have
inhaled some smoke.
We can take him
to the vet together
to get him checked out.
Now now, I understand.
But young men such as yourself
aren't supposed
to cry that easily.
Oh, shut up.
And don't look at me.
[crying]
[UIHARU]
That's right.
Reports are saying those
ampules were the cause
of the fire,
just like you thought.
The people who put them
there said they thought
they'd developed
some sort of substance
that would allow the
cherry blossoms to bloom
all year round.
They apparently had
no idea that it essentially
turned those trees into a
nitrogenous powder keg.
I take it these people
specialize in fertilizer
chemistry or something?
Actually, not at all.
According to their statement,
they learned it
via Indian Poker.
[KUROKO]
I heard the news.
You found someone
to take Perro in, huh?
[MIYAMA] Mm-hmm.
One of my classmates from my old
school said she could
keep him at her place.
I'm sure you'll miss him.
Yeah. For sure.
But even if I can't see him
as often as I do now,
since he's alive, I can visit.
He's only alive because
you saved him, you know.
I didn't save him, you did.
Not true, without your
predictions to warn me,
I never would have
known to help Perro
or any of the
people in the park.
You think so? Are you sure?
Absolutely.
But my power,
if I use it too much...
[KUROKO]
That's right.
You have to be careful
not to exceed your limit.
However...
...abilities are things
that can grow.
Stick close to your curriculum,
and someday you
may be able to use it
without taxing your body.
And when that day arrives,
come see me again.
[MIYAMA]
Let's say my ability does grow.
What if I don't bother
using it to help anyone?
Or if I decide to only help
who I care about, like Perro?
[KUROKO]
Oh, no.
I very much doubt
you would do that.
You remind me too
much of myself.
[MIYAMA]
Of you?
[KUROKO]
Yes, as in...
I think I looked up to
the same kind of people
that you do.
You know, the "champion
of justice" type?
[MIYAMA]
Oh, yeah?
But it goes without saying
I was a child at the time!
'Kay.
I'll think about it.
[SATEN]
Step right up!
Today we have the perfect
product for those of you
who want to develop
yourselves in "certain areas."
Indian Poker!
[MIKOTO] Yeah, I think
I'm done with that.
[SATEN] You can also
acquire knowledge or skills
while you sleep!
[MIKOTO] I said I'm not
interested-- "Bust Upper?"