[SATEN, KUROKO gasp]
She restored the erased data!
[gasps]
There it is!
[MIKOTO]
Shokuho!
So "a DNA computer that
generates abilities"?
If she's hiding it, then
Shokuho is probably involved
in this research.
I wouldn't go that far just yet.
But what I am willing to bet is
that she wanted to keep the fact
she was at this place a secret.
Following that logic,
this is likely her hideout.
And I'm sure she's there, too.
--Kuroko.
--Ah!
Take a look at all these photos.
Think you can tell where
this place might be?
Huh? Maybe.
Just stop blurting
my name out like that.
I think I know this one.
It's hard to be sure,
but it looks a lot like
the Judgment branch
in School District 2.
[MIKOTO]
District 2?
I'll check it out.
By the way,
when my mama wakes up--
Yes. First, I'll explain to her
that she collapsed
from heat exhaustion.
And then keep her here
with the excuse that
we need to issue her
a new entrance pass.
I know how to handle
this kind of situation.
Thank you. And Saten?
Thank you for the info.
Oh, sure.
--Um... Misaka?
--[MIKOTO grunts]
You can imagine
the self-doubt that would come
with having your
memories messed with.
Are we really friends with you?
It's a tough situation.
But once this is over,
I'll grab Shokuho by
her pretty little neck
and drag her here.
That way you can be sure.
[gasps]
[SHOKUHO sighs]
Honestly, this is
turning out to be
a real thorn in my side.
[CAT 02A meowing]
[SHOKUHO] What exactly
am I looking at here?
[KEITZ]
It looks like she fell victim
to a military-grade nanodevice.
I'm not sure we can
treat her with
the vaccine software alone...
...since her
electrical abilities
might interfere with it.
[SHOKUHO sighs]
That said, I still think it
would be smart to take her in.
This situation has created
an opportunity for us.
One way or another,
we have the initiative.
If we find out
her life's at risk.
I'll raise the
white flag to Misaka.
[KEITZ]
Are you certain?
It would be annoying, sure,
but at that point,
we'd be out of options.
[SHOKUHO] For now, though,
could you call her an ambulance?
I'll use Mental Out on the crew
and have them drop us off
along the way.
On it.
[CAT 02A meowing]
Is this her cat? Or...?
[yowls]
Guess it's scared.
Well, could be a stray.
I didn't see a collar.
But regardless, we don't have
time to bother with that now--
just leave it be.
[KEITZ]
Yeah, you're right.
Hello?
[SHOKUHO]
Well then?
Can you tell me what's happening
with Auribus oculi
fideliores sunt?
Oh. Right, right,
that urban legends site.
I'm still so annoyed.
I had our security
turned up to 11,
which should have
prevented anyone
from following or seeing me.
But an esper
who can use drops of water
as a camera lens managed
to get a picture.
I can't believe that the admin
of some silly urban legend site
has that kind of an ability.
Espers are the worst.
Always causing trouble.
Now that's rich,
coming from you.
You say something?
Nope. Back to
your original question.
I've got a program running
that's automatically
generating dummy sites.
That website will never
see the light of day again.
[SHOKUHO]
Hmm?
[alarm beeps]
[KEITZ]
Well, well. Curious.
Someone's analyzing
the dummy data generator.
I have to imagine
it's in an effort
to recover the original site.
I'm sorry, what was that?
I seem to recall you saying
there was nothing
to worry about yesterday.
[KEITZ]
Just give me a second, please.
I didn't expect this,
but I did set up a way to trace
any intruders, just in case.
Found them.
[SHOKUHO]
Judgment Branch 177?
I started to realize things
wouldn't go as smoothly
as I planned when
I found out that
Judgement girl was
a friend of yours.
That's not something I expected.
But it's not like
there's anything else
I could have done at the time.
Perhaps a situation like this
was simply unavoidable.
Right...
...Misaka?
Whaddya know?
It's pretty funny
running into you here.
Really? That's the
excuse you're going with?
You realize checking all the
security cameras makes you
easy to track, right?
Where is she?
As I'm sure you're aware,
she's in the building
you saw on that site.
Of all my
favorite hiding places,
that's the most
reliable one I have.
Is she safe?
You make it sound
like I would torture her.
She may look like you,
but that's not my thing.
There. Are we done?
Are you happy now?
Yeah, right. Not even close.
I've got a lot of
questions to ask you.
[SHOKUHO]
Can't have that, can we?
But you see, I'm pretty
pressed for time myself.
So if you want to chat,
come with me.
[SATEN] Man. I wonder
if there's anything
I could be doing.
She certainly seemed
to imply she could handle
all of it on her own.
I don't think you need to
stress yourself out over it.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm still not convinced
we were manipulated.
Though it's hard to say.
Okay, but what
if it is all true?
Having your friends completely
forget you would be miserable.
I doubt you'd be this coolheaded
if Uiharu and I forgot about you
and treated you like
some random stranger.
I guess not.
I know I would hate it.
[KUROKO]
Hmm.
[SATEN]
What are you looking at anyway?
Some people listed in the Bank.
I'm trying to find the girl
who took Uiharu hostage.
I barely saw her face,
and I don't know
what school she goes to...
...but I can take
a guess at what her ability is.
It allowed her to
remotely control a liquid metal,
and create a likeness
of herself out of it.
Plus, if she's
a Level 3 or a Level 4,
that should narrow down
my search considerably.
Good call, then.
If we can find her,
I'm sure it'd help Misaka.
Listen, I'm only acting
as a member of Judgment.
I'm pursuing a criminal
wanted for attempted murder.
I can't just hand
the sensitive details
of my investigation
over to a civilian.
Aww.
[KUROKO] However!
If the situation becomes
far more urgent, and I think
sharing the information
with her could help
the investigation,
then I may be able
to make an exception.
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
Okay! I'll just have
to help you search
so we can find her faster!
Hey, did you hear me?
What was that weird face about?
Wasn't that
the place in the photo?
Why are we going passed it?
I believe I already
told you that I'm short on time.
If you want to talk to me
so badly, don't complain.
Plus, just think about it.
Why would I want anyone
going near that place?
[MIKOTO grunts]
You've got
no reason to look so angry.
Once this is over,
I'll give her straight to you.
It looks like she was injected
with a powerful nanodevice.
Because of that,
I'm a little concerned about
her immune system, but her
life is in no real danger.
And the people who
injected this "nanodevice" thing
in her--they're the ones who
are looking for the Sisters?
What's the story with them?
I thought they were operating
under your orders at first...
...but they've kept on looking,
even after her disappearance.
And they're poking around,
asking about things
you wouldn't have to.
At this point,
I'm guessing you guys
are on opposite sides.
Yep. And, right now,
we're headed straight
to where their boss is gonna be.
If you must know,
it all started
when I heard about
an experiment.
One that you're
quite familiar with.
Project Level 6 Shift.
Some of the
researchers at the facility
I was with were whispering
about it amongst themselves.
Apparently,
the project hit a setback,
and its data had leaked
into the underworld.
[SHOKUHO] I haven't.
But I'd like you to tell me.
[RESEARCHER 08A]
From what I've heard,
they were trying to elevate
the first-ranked, Accelerator,
to Level 6 by having him fight
mass-produced clones
of the third-ranked,
Mikoto Misaka.
[RESEARCHER 08B]
But the project seems to have
stalled midway through.
So then, what happened
to all the clones
they made for it?
[RESEARCHER 08B]
I don't know.
I assume they were disposed of?
[SHOKUHO] So? Have you
discovered what's become
of the Sisters,
since the experiment ended?
Not just yet.
I apologize.
What's the hold up?
You were involved in
the experiment, right?
That's part of the reason
why I hired you to begin with.
I was involved, yes,
as a security advisor.
And when the project
was suspended,
the Sisters were taken in
by some other institution.
But... I'll check with my
contacts and see what I find.
I would prefer it
if you did so
sooner rather than later.
Just know,
one thing concerns me.
[SHOKUHO]
Mm?
[KEITZ] It looks like there's
another organization
trying to track down the
Sisters at the moment.
[SHOKUHO]
Is there? Then you'd better do
a concurrent investigation
on them, too.
And what we found
from that venture.
Were these other guys, right?
The ones you've
encountered so far
have just been hired hands.
It sounds as though their
directive was to get rid of you
and search for the Sisters
at the same time.
Why get rid of me?
Well, you were
the one who threw
the original Sisters
project into disarray
if I'm not mistaken.
So I'm sure you're
on their radar.
And now an innocent
girl is paying the price
in place of me.
[SHOKUHO]
What I'm wondering is why
they only tried to immobilize
you with a nanodevice.
But I think we can
both imagine the reason
they'd need the
Sisters, can't we?
After all, there's only one
thing they could want.
It's the Misaka Network.
Right. The network formed by
the Sister's brainwave link
is quite valuable.
If its incredible
processing power were to fall
into the wrong hands,
then any number of
awful things could happen.
So I took preventative measures.
I took out every pathway
that could carry
an electrical virus
between the sisters.
Using my amazing ability.
That way,
even if another Sister were
to find herself in
the clutches of our enemies,
they won't be able to use her to
mess with the Misaka Network.
So that's what you
meant by having the initiative.
Okay, but do you know what
they're planning to use
the Misaka Network for?
Unfortunately,
all I can say for sure
is that it isn't going
to be anything good.
After all, the man
we're dealing with here...
...was the one pushing
for Project Level 6 Shift...
...Gensei Kihara.
Gensei Kihara...
I've never met him in person,
but I have heard his name
a number of times.
You're saying he was
the primary advocate
for that project?
Regrettably,
not just that one, either.
That man is willing to sacrifice
anything to find the "truth."
He's the grandfather
of Academy City's field of study
focusing on SYSTEM,
and has brought down
countless research institutions.
He's not so short-sighted
that he'd propose
simply "restarting" the project.
So he must have
something up his sleeve.
Now you know who
I'm talking about.
And like I told you before,
we're currently en route
to the man's location.
Is he really that easy to find?
Of course not.
He's adept at making
himself disappear,
so it took a lot of work
to track him down.
He's supposed to be attending
the International Ability
Researchers Conference
about to be held
in School District 9.
I read the mind
of one of his inside men,
so it's a sure thing.
This is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity,
so I'm using it
to settle things with him.
Did you screw
with my friends' memories
to "protect" them?
To, like, keep them out
of the mess this is
all about to become
or something?
Because that feels like what
you're about to tell me.
Well, they like to get
involved just as much as you do,
and they'd almost
certainly die if
they went up against this man.
Even if they didn't,
any way they might intervene
would mess with
my careful plans,
and I can't have that.
Things would have
turned out poorly for everyone.
I was trying to
be smart about it.
[MIKOTO] Okay then. Why didn't
you tell me about this
from the start?
Why go through
the trouble of erasing
their memories to hide it?
I see you
already forgot about
our earlier conversation,
so let me remind you.
You're on their radar, and if
we teamed up, I would be, too.
[MIKOTO] Still, there were
any number of ways
you could have gone about this!
I mean, Kongo got--
[MIKOTO] I guess I was
the one who got her involved.
And if she did run
into them by accident...
...then I'd be
misdirecting my anger
if I blamed you
for it. But still!
You should have
just come to me with this
from the beginning!
Then maybe Kongo wouldn't have
ended up in the hospital!
[SHOKUHO] I honestly do feel bad
about what happened to her.
But...
In the end,
she took out some trash
I'm not very fond of, and I
appreciate the assistance.
So that's a win.
Are you kidding?
I could have taken him out
easily if you had told me!
Explain!
What if you had
set off their alarm bells,
but Gensei Kihara
didn't present himself?
What if you
decided to sell me out
and hand me right over to them?
--I'd never do something like--
--[SHOKUHO] Cooperation? Trust?
I don't know how
you can bring yourself
to believe in such
hollow things.
You've taken people
at their word before,
and look what happened.
Project Radio Noise...
...and Project Level 6 Shift.
[SHOKUHO]
I'm different.
I make sure to peek
around inside the head
of anyone I work with.
I learn their motives
and standards of behavior.
And in some cases, I manipulate
their emotions and actions.
I can't know
what you're thinking,
so partnering with you
was out of the question.
You understand.
[SHOKUHO]
And yet we're together now.
But I'm only allowing you
to chat with me because
I respect your
dedication to your friends.
And because we're
so close to finishing this,
they couldn't possibly
do anything even if
they saw us together.
Surprise, surprise.
You and I are never gonna
get along, are we?
[MIKOTO]
One more question.
Why would someone
as heartless as you are
care about the Sisters?
Sorry. I'm under
no obligation to tell you that.
Plus...
...it looks like
we're just about there.
[UIHARU groans softly]
[UIHARU]
Ms. Misuzu?
This is the 177
Branch's infirmary.
[KUROKO] Okay, so if we
assume you're correct...
...it would mean
that Uiharu has been
manipulated since yesterday.
[SATEN]
Yeah. They did a lot of work
to hide the site,
but she found it anyway.
So I'm sure they'd
track her down
once they figured
out who she was...
...then show up,
and alter her memories
to whatever they
wanted them to be.
I wonder if that's why
she made that mistake
on our patrol route as well.
[SATEN] Hmm... Either way, let's
not tell her about this, okay?
She'd probably find some way
to blame herself for it.
Ah! Uiharu!
Um, sorry to eavesdrop...
...but could you please tell me
what you're talking about?
[SATEN]
Uh...
--If you insist.
--[gasps]
However, before we do,
would you please
make us some tea?
I know you just woke up
and all, but it would help.
Uh, sure!
Hey! Shirai!
[KUROKO] Listen, I completely
understand why you want to keep
your friend from getting hurt,
and I admire that.
But Uiharu is not
so fragile a girl
that this would
break her spirit.
[SATEN]
Mm.
[UIHARU]
Mind control? I see.
[UIHARU] So then, that means I
must've been sabotaging you guys
without even realizing it.
[KUROKO slurps]
Okay. Now that
we've taken a break,
let's continue
our investigation.
Uiharu, please pick out
any suspicious individuals
from the Bank.
Huh? Is that smart?
What if I'm still under the mind
control they placed on me?
I could accidentally lead
you in the wrong direction.
We don't have
the time for you to undergo
a thorough examination,
and we could really use
your expertise at the moment.
If you're concerned,
you can do all your work
in front of us so
we can keep tabs on you.
Unless you haven't
slept enough, of course.
I'm awake! I'll go get set up!
[SATEN]
That went well.
To be fair, both Shirai and I
were under her mind
control, too, but...
...I'll keep that to myself.
[SHOKUHO]
All righty then...
...you're free to go back
to your usual business.
The conference is up ahead.
The security on the way
there has been neutralized.
And that's where
Gensei Kihara is, right?
[SHOKUHO] If you promise
not to interfere at all,
you can stay here
and watch if you'd like.
Are you kidding?
I'm sick of these people
who can't get anything done
without destroying lives.
Someone's gotta
teach them a lesson.
[SHOKUHO]
Hey! Wait up a second!
[MIKOTO] Level 6. A domain
that can't be reached
by existing abilities alone.
Something even
Accelerator would have to
sacrifice 20,000 clones
to get anywhere near.
Whatever Gensei Kihara
is planning,
it'll likely come at a cost
even greater than before.
But if he thinks
it'll be worth the price,
then he'll try. A godly brain.
If that's their goal,
then is this city
really just one big...?
Oh, come on!
I can't be preoccupied with that
when I'm about to charge
into enemy territory.
[gasps]
[MIKOTO]
Shokuho? She's gone.
The way here
was a straight shot.
She couldn't have gotten lost!
She set me up!
She must think she's so smooth.
You got me right where
you wanted me, what next?
You think I'm just gonna
lie down without a fight?
[SHOKUHO wheezes]
Hey. Hold on!
I told you...
...to wait a second.
[wheezing]
Don't just ignore me!
There's no way...
...you didn't hear that.
Don't go...
...getting fired up...
...without me.
I'm the one
who brought you here.
So it's only right...
...that we stick...
...together.
Don't go dashing
off at full speed.
Uh. That was more like jogging,
but sure, whatever.
[SHOKUHO]
Yeah. Well.
You know how it is.
I am heavier in certain
areas than you are...
...so you have less wind
resistance to worry about.
You can imagine how
hard that must be, right?
[MIKOTO]
Yeah...
...you're just really out
of shape, aren't you?
[SHOKUHO]
Huh?! Excuse me?!
I am the pinnacle of health!
Interesting.
Now that I think about it, I
don't remember ever seeing you
do anything in gym class.
Yeah, so?
You think being athletic
makes you a better person?
How old are you, ten?
Ahh. That explains why you have
the figure of a little girl!
Ah! My figure has
nothing to do with this!
What about your sparkly eyes,
straight out of a Shojo manga?
[SHOKUHO]
I was born this way!
Didn't anyone ever teach you
not to make fun
of other's appearances?
[MIKOTO]
What do you think you just did?!
You are such
a hypocritical little brat!
[overlapping yelling]
[BOTH panting]
[SHOKUHO]
Whatever, this is pointless.
Bringing you along wasn't
part of my plan anyway.
Before our little
meeting today,
I had every intention of taking
care of things on my own.
So it's not like
we have to rush there
hand in hand, right?
Yeah. I think
I'd feel a lot better
if I wasn't forcing myself
to work with you.
[SHOKUHO, MIKOTO]
So why don't we just split up?
[SHOKUHO] Don't do anything
to slow me down, okay?
[MIKOTO]
Right back at you!
[KOZAKU]
Let's see...
Why don't I summarize
what I've found?
As far as the identity
of who stole the data
from our villas goes...
...it wasn't Mikoto Misaka.
It turns out it was the
fifth-ranked, Misaki Shokuho.
My guess is she
couldn't cover everything up
by manipulating memories, so
she had to set up a scapegoat.
Also, she apparently knew about
the "do-not-kill" order on
Misaka that MEMBER sent out.
[KIHARA] Did you just now figure
this out, Mitori Kozaku?
Huh? Hold on.
Does that mean
you knew that already?
You could have
told me, you know.
[KIHARA]
What's the problem?
It's not like me telling
you would have changed
your job at all.
Just focus on finishing your
preparations like before.
Understood?
Okay. But are
you sure about this?
I mean, Misaki Shokuho's
objective when she took
that data from the
villas was definitely--
[KIHARA]
Yes, I'm sure.
No need to worry.
Everything is good to go.
In fact...
...I'm almost afraid
things are going too smoothly.
[MIKOTO]
Okay, let's bust in there!
You immobilize any security
guards, and I'll blast my way
through any walls
using my railgun!
[SHOKUHO] My Mental Out
doesn't work on Misaka.
At times like these, I wonder if
it's because of her EM barrier,
or if it's because her brain
is nothing but muscle.