[calls]
[EAGLE 1B calls]
[CROWD screaming]
[roars]
[TOURIST 1A]
It’s a villain!
[TOURIST 1B]
Quick, get off the street!
[VILLAIN 1B cackles]
Ten million dollars
just like that.
I love this job!
[VILLAIN 1A]
Up ahead!
[VILLAIN 1B]
Huh?
[ELECTOPLANT] Your crime spree
ends here. Stand down!
[VILLAINS grunt]
[ELECTOPLANT]
You’re up, Cow Lady.
[VILLAIN 1A roars]
Y’all are finished.
Go ahead and try to stop us.
[VILLAIN 1A growls]
[GIRL 1B]
Daddy!
[VILLAIN 1B]
Don’t stop. Just crush them.
[VILLAIN 1B screams]
[ALL MIGHT] Fear not, citizens.
Everything is fine.
You’re safe, because I am here.
[BOTH gasp]
Really?
And just who the hell
do you think you are?
A hero from Japan.
Who just so happened
to be passing by.
Hah! I’ll send you
back home in a coffin.
If they can find your remains.
[yells]
I’m sorry, what was
that threat... again?
[ALL MIGHT]
Running away already?
You got ahead
of yourself, Toshi.
[ALL MIGHT]
They’re fast. Follow them, Dave.
[DAVID]
You’re impossible.
Your body always moves
before ya think!
[VILLAIN 1A] Hey, some
weird car’s followin’ us.
Damn these heroes!
[CROWD screams]
You’re kidding me!
[VILLAIN 1A growls]
Toshi. We’re gonna be
late for the lecture.
Hurry up and finish this.
That’s the plan, obviously.
You just don’t give up, do you?
Ha! Detroit... Smash!
[groans]
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Now for an ultimate move.
[roars]
[ALL MIGHT] Dave. I named this
one after your home state.
Do it!
[ALL MIGHT]
California...
...Smash!
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[TOURIST 1D]
Uh. Who’s that hero?
[TOURIST 1BB]
I’ve never seen him!
[TOURIST 1E]
That was incredible!
He’s an exchange
student visiting
the states from Japan.
You can call him by his
hero name, All Might.
[TOURISTS, HEROS]
His name’s All Might?
Take him in.
Someday, that name’ll be known
by everyone in the world.
Someday, he will become
our Symbol of Peace.
[ALL MIGHT]
Thanks for the help, Dave.
Because of the suit you
made, that was a cinch,
and we’ll make it back
to class in time.
Well, we’d better.
If we’re late again,
I doubt we’ll be able
to pass the course.
[POLICE RADIO] Alert. SFO
Flight 857 has been hijacked.
‐‐I repeat...
‐‐Did you hear that?
It’s too risky, man.
Ya know, for a good guy,
you are way too reckless.
Does that mean you’ll help me?
Guess so.
Ugh. Who knew that being a
hero would be so much work.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
Don’t worry, I’ll buy you lunch.
[IZUKU]
All Might. Hey, All Might.
Are you asleep?
[grunts]
Somethin’ the matter,
Young Midoriya?
Look. We can see it!
Right there!
The floating city that
can move anywhere.
Home to over 10,000
scientists! I‐Island!
I can’t believe this is where
I get to start summer
vacation. It’s so amazing!
I didn’t realize that
you’d be this excited.
I’m glad I invited you.
Yeah, you’re sure it’s okay
that I came along with you?
It’s not gonna be a problem?
Don’t even think twice about it.
The invitation was clear,
and I’m welcome
to bring whoever
I want as my guest.
But doesn’t that usually
mean a family member or‐‐
I think you’re forgetting
that the two of us
are connected by
something far thicker
than blood, Young Midoriya.
We will forever share
the bond of One For All.
‐‐Right!
‐‐[beep]
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Attention, passengers.
The plane will soon begin
its descent to I‐Island.
[ALL MIGHT] This is gonna
be monumentally exhausting.
Once we’ve landed and
go out in public...
...I must maintain my
muscle form constantly.
Now! It’s about time for
you to change as well.
You did ask UA if you could
bring your hero costume
along with you, right?
[IZUKU]
Yes!
[IZUKU] Our world is
a superhuman society,
with about 80 percent
of the population
possessing some uncanny ability.
When our cities swirled
with chaos and confusion,
heroes began to dominate our
collective consciousness,
and we had new
champions to look up to.
[ALL MIGHT laughing]
Fear not, citizens.
Hope has arrived.
Because I am here.
He’s the coolest
in the universe!
And once I get my Quirk,
I’m gonna be a hero
just like him!
Sorry, kid, it’s
not gonna happen.
[IZUKU]
My name is Izuku Midoriya,
and I was born without
any special power.
I was Quirkless.
Because of that, I almost
gave up on my dream
of becoming a hero.
But my life changed completely
when I met the number‐one pro.
The person I’d admired
my entire life.
All Might.
[IZUKU]
Is it possible to become a hero,
even if I don’t have a Quirk?
I’m a normal kid
without any powers.
Could I ever hope to
be someone like you?
[ALL MIGHT] There are
stories about every hero.
How they became great.
Most have one thing in common.
Their bodies moved before
they had a chance to think.
Kacchan!
What the hell? Why are you here?
I couldn’t just stand there
and watch you die!
You, too, can become a hero.
There’s nothing natural
about my ability.
I wasn’t born with this power.
It’s a sacred torch that was
passed on to me
from someone else.
I can transfer my
Quirk to another.
And that’s just one facet
of my secret abilities.
The true name of my
power is One For All.
One For All.
[ALL MIGHT]
One person improves the power.
Then hands it off
to another person.
It continues to grow
as it’s passed along.
It is this cultivated
power that allows me
to save those who are
in need of a hero.
The truth behind my strength.
Young Midoriya, you’re next.
I can give you my abilities.
[IZUKU] After I received
All Might’s Quirk,
I enrolled in a prestigious
hero course at UA High School.
I began running
toward my dreams.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face
in order to become the
world’s greatest hero.
[VOICE 1A] We will now begin
the immigration process.
Let’s test your
trivia, young man.
Why was this artificial
island created?
I know this.
It was built so the world’s
brightest minds could
gather together
to research Quirks
and develop new
hero support items!
They made the island moveable
in order to protect
the scientists and
their top‐secret research
from villains.
It’s got a security system
on par with the one
at the Tartarus prison,
so basically,
no one has ever
committed a crime here.
Way too many details,
but I should’ve expected that.
[VOICE 1A] The immigration
inspection is complete.
The island is currently holding
the pre‐opening of I‐Expo,
an event that showcases research
and development
projects our teams
have been working on.
Only those with invitations
may attend the preview.
[laughs]
[ALL MIGHT] I can’t believe
so many people are here
before the expo is officially
opened to the public.
[IZUKU]
No way!
The pictures of this place
don’t do it justice!
[ALL MIGHT] Unlike back
in Japan, people are allowed
to use their Quirks however
they wish on this island.
The pavilions are
jam‐packed with attractions
and demonstrations.
Make some time for them later.
[IZUKU]
I will!
Now let’s see, the
hotel should be nearby.
[WOMAN]
Welcome to I‐Expo.
[gasps] S’that you, All Might?
Is he really here?
Wow, the number‐one hero!
We need an interview.
Let’s get closer!
‐‐[ALL MIGHT laughing]
‐‐[CROWD clammoring]
[ALL MIGHT] Thank you so much
for the warm welcome!
Form a line for
autographs, please!
Oh, wow, I didn’t think I’d
get stopped for so long.
I’m afraid at this point
we’re in terrible danger
of being late.
Late to what?
[ALL MIGHT] Ah. I wanted to drop
in on a dear old pal of mine
who I haven’t seen
in quite a while.
Sorry to spring it on you,
but would you mind coming along?
You mean I’d get to meet
one of your friends?
Obviously, of course I’ll go!
[whispering] By the way,
I haven’t told him
about One For All
or how I’ve passed
the Quirk on to you,
so keep everything
under wraps, okay?
[IZUKU] Whoa, not even
your close friend knows?
Only because danger
tends to follow anyone
who knows the truth
about my power.
Oh, yeah, I see. For
their safety, of course.
[IZUKU] I can’t forget
how important it is to keep
One For All a secret.
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya.
Because you have
inherited my power,
you now bear a heavy burden.
Since I failed in the past,
you’ll one day have to face
the great evil of All For One.
[IZUKU]
That’s right.
I have to keep training so
I’m ready when the time comes.
I must learn to master
One For All, as soon as I can!
There you are, Uncle! Finally!
[MELISSA]
Welcome, Uncle Might!
[ALL MIGHT] It’s so good
to see you, Melissa!
Oh, my gosh, it’s been forever.
I can’t believe
you’re actually here!
I’m truly grateful
for the invitation.
I almost didn’t recognize you.
When did you go
and get so grown up?
Well, I am 17 now you know!
Much heavier than the
last time you saw me.
Are you? No.
[ALL MIGHT laughing]
Glad to see you’re looking well,
though I suppose you always are.
[IZUKU] Wait, this is
All Might’s old friend?
They must’ve met when she
was just a kid or something.
Or maybe her Quirk
makes her look young?
And Dave? Where’s he hiding?
[MELISSA giggles]
Oh, he’s in his lab.
He had a breakthrough
on some research
he’s been focusing on for years.
Actually, he has no idea
you’re even here;
this is just a little surprise
to celebrate his work.
So that’s what this is about.
Give me the scoop then.
What is he cooking up this time?
[MELISSA]
He said it’s confidential.
He won’t even tell me
what he’s been doing.
[ALL MIGHT]
Scientists and their secrets.
Oh, right, Young Midoriya.
Allow me to introduce you
to my friend Dave’s daughter.
It’s really nice to meet you.
I’m Melissa Shield.
This makes more sense now.
Huh, what’s that?
Uh‐‐ Nothing! Uh, hi, it’s
really nice to meet you.
I’m a first‐year student
at UA High School.
Izuku Midoriya.
In the hero course?
So that’s how you
know Uncle Might.
Uh‐huh, I’m his student.
He’ll be a great pro one day.
[gasps] I can’t believe
I’m meeting someone
that Uncle Might teaches!
You must have
a promising future.
Well, I hope so, but I
have a lot to learn.
Tons of training!
[MELISSA] So, what kind
of Quirk do you have?
[IZUKU]
It’s a power type!
The costume’s cool.
Though it’s a pretty
simplistic design.
Huh, I don’t see any
support items either.
[IZUKU]
She’s so close to me!
[gasps]
[MELISSA] It looks like
you should think about
upgrading your gear a bit.
[ALL MIGHT clears throat]
Melissa, shall we?
Oh! Sorry, I got
distracted. Heh.
If we hurry, we can
surprise Papa in his lab!
This way, Uncle Might.
It’s right over here.
[phone ringing]
[WOLFRAM] We infiltrated
the expo without a problem.
So? When do the goods arrive?
[VOICE] Three PM. You’ll
find them at Gate 66.
Then we’ll be waiting.
[SAM]
Excuse me. Um, Professor?
[SAM] I’ve finished putting
the equipment away,
just so you know.
[DAVID]
Already? Thanks so much, Sam.
[SAM] Why don’t you get
out of the lab today
and go have some
lunch with Melissa?
She’s busy today
at the Academy.
Oh? I thought they were
on break for I‐Expo.
Yes, but she’s doing
independent research.
You know me, I am
my father’s daughter.
For better and for worse.
Melissa, hey!
Hello, Miss, it’s
so good to see you.
Aw, right back at ya, Sam.
Thanks for always
taking care of Papa,
since he does nothing
but work here constantly.
Come on, I’m not that bad.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
Oh, you’ll see.
Since you completed the first
stage of your research,
I invited someone here
to celebrate with us.
Who would that be?
[MELISSA]
A person you dearly love.
[gasps]
Yes, I am here!
Shaking with emotion for
our heartfelt reunion!
[DAVID]
Toshi‐‐ A‐All Might?
Is it really you?
[laughs] I came all this
way just to see you,
Dave, old buddy.
Well, Papa, are you
totally surprised?
Uh. Yeah. Completely astounded.
We both have Melissa
to thank for that.
Man, how long has it been?
Oh, now, come on.
Don’t make me say it.
I already feel
old enough, ya jerk.
[BOTH laugh]
You do have a point.
Glad to see you
again, my friend.
Agreed. I’ve missed you, too.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya.
Let me introduce you
to someone incredible.
David Shield.
I know him!
Professor David Shield!
A top scientist in
the research world
who received a
Nobel Quirk Prize!
He was All Might’s partner
when he lived in America.
And he’s a genius when
it comes to costumes.
All Might’s Young Age.
Bronze Age.
The Silver Age.
And, of course, the Golden Age.
He’s the inventor who created
each of those iconic looks!
I never thought I’d get
to meet him in real life.
I’m just so moved!
[giggles]
It seems I don’t have
to introduce myself.
[IZUKU]
Uh‐‐ Oh, wow. I’m sorry!
No, don’t apologize.
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[DAVID]
Listen, it’s been a long time.
Can the two of you
give All Might and me
a little time to catch up?
[IZUKU]
Yeah. Of course!
Melissa. Why don’t you
take our new friend
on a tour around the expo?
[MELISSA] Sure thing,
Papa. Sounds like fun.
You’re not busy?
No, I’m honored to
show off our hard work
to a future hero.
Right this way.
Thanks! This is so nice of you!
Sam. You should
take a break, too.
[MELISSA] So, what do you
want me to call you?
By your real name, or do
you have a hero one already?
[IZUKU]
Well, actually...
Why don’t you call me Deku?
Deku? That’s kind of
a strange nickname.
You can stick with
Melissa for me.
See you two soon.
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
Hey. Are you all right, Toshi?
[ALL MIGHT]
Thanks for catching it.
The amount of time I
can keep my muscle form
has gotten even shorter.
You said it was bad
in your email.
But I had no idea
it was this serious.
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[IZUKU] Holy whoa!
This place is amazing.
I can’t believe the
entire island is man‐made.
It’s nuts.
And there’s normal city stuff.
About everything you could need.
The big downside
is we can’t travel.
[IZUKU]
Really? Why not?
[MELISSA] The scientists
and their families
have to keep their
work top secret.
That ensures there
aren’t any leaks.
[gasps] It’s the
Monster Hero, Godzillo!
Wow, I’ve only ever
seen him on TV!
His Quirk is so insane!
[MELISSA]
Nice. I bet a sponsor
flew him out here for the expo.
[MELISSA] They invite heroes
to show off new gear
and sign autographs.
Looks like the events
are in full swing.
[IZUKU]
This place is incredible!
A lot of the pro heroes will
be at the big party tonight.
Ah, but I’m sure you already
knew about that, huh?
I mean, since you came all
this way with Uncle Might.
[IZUKU] Oh, so I guess
that’s why he told me
to bring formal clothes.
Glad I found some.
[MELISSA]
Look! Over here!
You definitely have
to check this place out.
[IZUKU] I’ve never seen so many
new hero items in one place!
Deku, look at this one!
This multipurpose Beagle can
fly like a jet, of course,
but it can also move underwater.
So cool!
[MELISSA] You can wear
this diving suit and drop
up to 7,000 meters in the ocean.
So deep!
This helmet is equipped
with 36 different sensors,
so you can see all the
way around your body.
That’s so much!
[MELISSA] You know, almost
everything here was created
using different inventions
that Papa patented.
Wow. I bet you’re proud of him.
These support items
will help heroes
around the world.
Who knows how many people
will be affected because
of his hard work.
I think it’s great that
your dad is someone
you can look up to like this.
That’s because it’s my dream
to become a scientist
just like him.
[IZUKU]
Oh, yeah?
So does that mean
you’re training
at the school here
on the island?
[MELISSA]
Mm‐hm. I’m a third year.
The I‐Island Academy is
where everyone who dreams
of becoming a scientist
wants to go.
You must be a real genius!
Oh, no, I’ve still
got a lot to learn.
Honestly, I should be
studying much more.
I feel the same.
If I’m gonna be a
hero like All Might,
I’ve gotta train even harder.
Uncle Might really
holds a special place
in your heart, doesn’t he, Deku?
I still can’t get over how much
you were geeking out earlier.
Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
I’m kind of a fanboy.
[giggles]
Looks like you’re
having fun, Deku.
Uh‐‐! Huh, Uraraka?
What are you doing here?
It looks like you’re having fun.
[IZUKU]
You said that.
[YAOYOROZU clears throat]
[IZUKU]
Yaoyorozu?
You appear to be
having a good time.
[JIRO]
Midoriya. I heard everything.
[IZUKU] Jiro’s Earphone Jack!
The ultimate spy tech.
Are these your friends?
Uh, yeah, these
are my classmates.
And I didn’t tell
them I’d be here.
Oh, guys, this is
my friend Melissa.
She was just showing me around
the Expo a little bit.
Nice to meet you.
My dad and Uncle Might
are really good fr‐‐
[IZUKU screams]
[IZUKU whispering] I’m sorry.
Please don’t tell them
I came here as All Might’s
guest. It’s kind of
a big secret, okay?
[whispering] But why is that?
[IZUKU whispering] Because
reasons? I beg you.
[whispering] Your secret’s safe.
How about we all grab
some tea at the café?
[MELISSA] Wow! You really
got to work with pro heroes?
Like, out in the field?
Just normal training
and a few patrols.
I helped out with
a hostage crisis,
but only the evacuation part.
That’s still amazing, though.
Somehow, I ended up
in a TV commercial
for hair products.
Sounds like an
experience. Lucky.
We were thinking about going
to check out the pavilion
where the Academy’s
exhibit is tomorrow.
[OCHACO]
I’m really excited!
[IZUKU] I’m saved. They’re
not questioning anything.
[KAMINARI]
Thanks for waiting.
I know that voice.
Kaminari!
[OCHACO]
Is that... Mineta?
[JIRO]
What’re you two doing here?
They needed extra wait
staff, and since it meant
a free trip to the island,
we applied to work. Right?
We get to explore the
expo on our breaks.
And we make some money.
Plus, there’s the chance
we’ll have passionate
encounters with
some of the cute‐‐
Oh, my god, I think I’m in love.
[whispering] Hey, Midoriya,
who’s that high‐voltage
hottie over there?
Don’t be greedy, introduce us.
Well... That’s, um...
[MELISSA]
Are they also your classmates?
That’s right.
We’re basically pros.
[TENYA]
Why are you two slacking off?
You wanted to make
more money didn’t you?
But you’re not willing
to work hard?
[BOTH scream]
[IZUKU]
Wait, Iida?
You’re here, too?
[TENYA] I come from
a long line of heroes.
It’s to be expected
that we received
an invitation to the Expo.
But my family was busy,
so it’s just me.
I wondered if you’d be here.
I received an invitation because
my father’s a shareholder
in some of the expo’s
sponsor companies.
It’s so fun to get
to go to the preview.
Yeah. And she had
a few extra plus ones,
so we basically gambled for ’em.
[GIRLS]
No hard feelings, whoever wins.
Rock, papers, scissors.
My life is over!
[JIRO] So, after an
impartial game of chance,
the two of us ended up joining
the fun as her guests.
The other girls are here,
they just can’t
visit the preview.
Oh, are they really?
Uh‐huh. We’re all planning
to look around together
once the expo opens up
to the public tomorrow.
Here’s a thought.
Why don’t I show you
girls the sights?
You’re sure you have time?
[MELISSA]
Mm‐hm!
[OCHACO, JIRO, YAOYOROZU]
That’s awesome!
[MINETA, KAMINARI]
Please take us with you!
‐‐[rumbling]
‐‐Whoa, what was that noise?
[MC 1AA]
A clearance time of 33 seconds.
He’s in eighth place!
[IZUKU]
Kirishima?
So I’m guessing he’s
from UA, as well?
Yeah, he’s in the
same class as us.
[MC 1AA] Please welcome
our next challenger!
Kacchan?
[MC 1AA] The Villain Attack
course has been reset.
Ready. Go!
Die!
[IZUKU]
"Die"?
[MC 1AA] Look at that time!
Only 15 seconds!
First place!
[CROWD cheers]
[KIRISHIMA] Hey. Isn’t that
Midoriya in the stands?
[laughs nervously]
[yelps]
Damn it! What are you
doing here, Deku?
Uh, hey there, Kacchan.
‐‐Maybe calm down a litt‐‐
‐‐[KATSUKI] Don’t you dare
tell me what to do!
Bakugo, behave yourself!
[MELISSA]
Why is that boy so angry?
[JIRO]
That’s just who he is.
[OCHACO]
He and Deku are fated rivals.
So, Kirishima, you two got
asked to I‐Expo as well?
Nah, Bakugo was invited
since he won the
UA Sports Festival.
I just tagged along with him.
You guys gonna do this
villain course, or what?
Don’t even try it.
There’s no way you’ll get
a better score than I did.
Yeah. You’re prob’ly right. Yep.
Huh. I’m not so sure. Only one
way to find out, I guess.
Yeah. You’re prob’ly right.
Huh?!
Just hurry and get your
pathetic attempt over,
you damn nerd. Then
you get outta here!
[IZUKU]
Right. I’ll do that.
[MC 1AA]
We’ve got a new challenger
coming in at the last minute!
Will he end up on top, or fail
in front of the entire Expo?
[IZUKU] If I’m doing this,
I’m gonna go for it.
[IZUKU]
One for All... Full Cowling!
The attack course is set.
Ready. Go!
[IZUKU]
To keep from injuring my arm,
I’ll use five percent
of my power!
[MC 1AA]
An incredible run!
He’s in second place
at 16 seconds!
[CROWD cheers]
[MELISSA]
He has such explosive speed.
And that destructive power.
It’s just like Uncle Might’s!
But...
Wow!
That was a good
showing, Midoriya.
I didn’t think I’d be
able to get so close
to Kacchan’s time.
What?! No way, I’ll go again
and blast your score to ash!
‐‐[rumbling]
‐‐[MC 1AA screams]
[MC 1AA] This is insane!
Fourteen seconds!
This gentleman has jumped
to the top of the pack!
Todoroki’s here, too?
Another one from UA?
Yep!
Your class is amazing!
You’re gonna be
such great heroes.
Oh, please, you’re too kind.
Outta the way, Icy Hot bastard!
Bakugo.
You can’t just appear outta
nowhere and show me up!
And I see the others
are here, too.
Don’t ignore me!
What are you even doing
on the island, anyway?
[TODOROKI]
My father was invited,
so I’m representing him.
Um. The next person is waiting.
Shut up! I’m doing it again!
[TENYA]
Everyone, please stop!
You’re gonna make the world
think UA’s full of degenerates!
[laughs]
Oh. Sorry to laugh.
I was just thinking
it looks like you have
a whole lot of fun
at your school.
[YAOYOROZU]
Well, it’s never boring.
I’ll say that much, at least.
[OCHACO, JIRO]
True.
[phone ringing]
[WOLFRAM] I picked up
the goods as planned.
What? All Might’s here now?
It doesn’t matter. We can
handle him, no problem.
[WOLFRAM]
Of course he had to show up.
[gasps]
[DAVID]
I don’t get it, Toshi.
Why are your Quirk levels
going down so dramatically?
I know you were seriously
injured by All For One,
but to suddenly get
these numbers is absurd.
What in the world
happened to you?
[coughs] I suppose if you’re
a hero for a long time,
your body starts to fall apart.
[ALL MIGHT] I wish I could
tell him the truth
about One For All.
But if I did,
I’d risk getting him
and Melissa caught up
in the fight
against All For One.
[DAVID] At this rate, the
Symbol of Peace will disappear.
The only reason
Japan is able to keep
its crime rate at six percent
is because of your presence.
Other countries hover
around 20 percent.
And some are even
worse than that.
Honestly, part of me
wishes you’d never left.
America could use you.
There’s no need for you
to be so pessimistic, Dave.
The world is full of
capable pro heroes.
Not to mention the
good people like you
who support them.
Besides, I can
still be All Might
for a few hours each day,
I’m not dead yet‐‐
[DAVID]
Come on.
What if a monstrous
villain appears,
and you’re not capable
of saving us again?
[ALL MIGHT]
Listen.
[gasps]
Just in case that day comes,
understand that I have no
intention of stepping down.
[ALL MIGHT]
Besides, there’s still hope.
For the future of One For All.
And the Symbol of Peace.
A new generation will
rise to take my place.
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
The I‐Expo preview
will be closing at 6 PM.
Thank you for coming.
Enjoy your night.
[KAMINARI groans]
The Expo isn’t even
open to the public yet.
If we’re this slammed now,
will we ever get to rest?
Shut up. I don’t
wanna think about it.
[IZUKU]
Hey, Mineta! Kaminari!
How did your shift go?
You should be proud of the
work you’ve done today.
What are these things?
Invitations to the big Expo
reception later tonight.
There’s a party?
These are for us?
Melissa took pity on
you for some reason.
She figured you
could use a break!
I had a few extras.
Please, I’d love
for you to have them.
[MINETA]
Kaminari...
[KAMINARI]
Mineta...
[BOTH] A beautiful angel
has rewarded us
for all our hard work!
[TENYA] I heard there’ll
be quite a few pro heroes
attending tonight’s
party as well.
It’s imperative we don’t
tarnish UA’s reputation.
We’ll change into our formal
clothes and go as a group.
Everybody meet in lobby seven
of the central tower
at 6:30 PM sharp.
Don’t you dare be late.
I’ll contact Todoroki and Bakugo
and share this information.
Thank you, you’re dismissed!
There he goes.
Always at full throttle.
[OCHACO]
Meet you in a bit!
[IZUKU]
Bye!
[MELISSA]
Deku. Can I show you something
before you get
ready for tonight?
[KATSUKI]
Why would I wanna go to a party?
It’ll just be a bunch of
old geezers I don’t know
giving speeches. Sounds like
a pretty lame night to me.
[KIRISHIMA] But we can eat as
much gourmet food as we want.
Well, it’s not like I
brought any fancy clothes
with me, anyway.
[KIRISHIMA]
I figured you wouldn’t.
[KATSUKI]
Huh?
So I brought some stuff for ya.
You’ve gotta be kidding,
you spikey‐haired idiot!
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
Right, then. I’ll see you later.
Looking forward to
partying with you!
Same.
Toshi.
Yes, Dave?
No, uh, never mind.
See you tonight.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[STUDENT 1A]
An experiment went wrong.
[STUDENT 1B] There are still
people trapped inside!
[DAVID coughing]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[STUDENTS cheer]
[DAVID]
Thank you.
Uh, my name is David
Shield, by the way.
And you are?
Hi, I’m All Might.
Just a student
trying to be a hero.
[DAVID] I made you this costume
using cutting‐edge materials.
It’ll hold up better
than what ya had on.
This is great.
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[CITIZENS cheering]
[DAVID]
The Symbol of Peace?
[ALL MIGHT] I wanna see
a society where everyone
can smile without worry.
I want to be the
Symbol of Peace
and shine a light on this world.
[thud]
[HENCHMAN 1C]
We found five guards,
but they’re restrained now.
The plan’s a go.
[WOLFRAM] Keep ’em bound,
but don’t kill ’em.
Start workin’ on
the security system.
[HENCHMAN 1C] Yes, sir.
We’ll begin infiltration now.
Now the fun can begin.
[WOLFRAM]
Get ready to move.
[MELISSA]
This is the I‐Academy campus,
where I spend most my time.
And to the left here is my own
personal research laboratory.
[MELISSA]
I’m sorry it’s such a mess.
[IZUKU]
Wow, it looks so professional.
I can’t believe you get to
study in a place like this.
Whoa, so many trophies.
You must be really talented.
[MELISSA]
Well, actually...
Not long ago, I was
getting terrible grades.
That’s why I’ve been
studying so hard lately.
I’ve gotta be a good student
if I wanna be a hero.
Uh, you mean like a pro?
[MELISSA] Oh, no. I gave up
on that dream a while ago.
I mean, I’m Quirkless after all.
You don’t have a Quirk?
[MELISSA]
Nope.
After I turned five and
I still didn’t have one,
I got taken to the doctor.
And they said I was in the
minority of the population
that would never
develop a power.
[IZUKU]
Exactly like I was.
See that, Mom?
There’s always a
smile on his face,
no matter how bad things get.
Do you think I can
be a hero, too?
[IZUKU’S MOM]
I’m sorry, Izuku.
I wish things were different.
Gosh. I’m sorry. I’m
sure it must be hard.
Oh. Uh, what do you mean?
Oh. I... It’s just, to be
told you don’t have something
that comes naturally
to everyone else
must be really painful.
Well, I was definitely
in shock for a while.
Luckily, I had another big goal
that was close to my heart.
[IZUKU]
Huh? What was that?
To be like my father.
Papa didn’t have a Quirk
that would let him be a hero.
But he supports Uncle
Might and other heroes
with the power of science.
He’s still fighting for peace.
Just indirectly.
And you want to be someone
who does that, too.
[MELISSA] Yep. That’s how
I’ll make a real difference.
Or at least, I hope so.
[MELISSA] This is a support
item I made a while ago
after observing Uncle
Might using his power.
[IZUKU]
What is it?
Try pressing the button
here on the back.
[gasps]
A glove?
[MELISSA] As far as names go,
I was thinking "Full Gauntlet."
When we first met,
I saw your scars.
It looked as though
you’d injured yourself.
Then, at the villain attraction,
I noticed you were limiting
yourself on purpose.
So I was thinking, maybe
your Quirk is too strong,
and therefore, your body
can’t handle its full power.
[IZUKU]
She figured it out!
I made the gauntlet strong.
It could withstand Uncle Might’s
punches three times.
So I think it’d be a
perfect fit for you, too.
You should be able
to use your full power
if you have it on.
For real? All of it?
[MELISSA]
Please take that with you.
Uh‐‐ But I can’t.
It’s important to you.
[MELISSA]
That’s why I want you to use it.
Just promise you’ll be
a true hero someday.
And you’ll never stop
helping people in need.
Promise.
[MELISSA chuckles]
[phone rings]
Yeah, hello?
[TENYA]
What are you doing, Midoriya?!
It’s way past when you
were supposed to be here!
Sorry about that, you guys‐‐
Uh, where is everybody?
They’re not here yet.
Does a proper meeting time
mean nothing to you people?
Sorry I’m late.
It took me a while to get ready.
[BOTH]
Best night ever!
Apologies for the tardiness.
Jiro’s feeling shy.
[BOTH]
Jackpot! Yes!
This is fancier than anything
I’ve ever worn before.
It feels like a costume.
I’m just glad you’re
not in a t‐shirt.
Even the jacket can’t ruin it.
[BOTH yelp]
Shut up.
Why would you do that?
It was a compliment.
No, it wasn’t.
This is my first time
in formal wear.
I just borrowed something
from Yaoyorozu.
It looks really good!
Like perfect.
Oh, Deku, stop‐‐
you don’t have to
flatter me so much.
Contain yourself!
[MELISSA] Oh, good, I thought
I was gonna miss you guys.
Let’s get downstairs
to the party!
[MINETA]
The headliner has arrived.
Mineta, I can’t take
this much beauty,
I think I might actually die!
These tickets were a mistake.
[ANNOUNCER 1B]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to I‐Expo’s
opening night reception.
We at I‐Island hope
you enjoy yourselves.
Now, I wonder if we
can get All Might,
the number‐one hero up here.
He’s visiting from Japan.
Wouldn’t you like to hear
him say a few words?
Come on.
Maybe a round of
applause would help.
Please, join us on the stage!
Really, Dave?
Could’ve warned me.
This was bound to happen
once they found out
you were in town.
You owe me one.
[TENYA]
It’s no good.
Neither of them is
picking up their phones.
Knowing those two, they’re
just blowing off the party.
Moron.
You’re absolutely positive we’re
going the right direction?
Yeah, I mean, I’m
pretty sure we are.
You’re "pretty sure"?
Uh, well, I left my
phone back in the room,
so we’re going on instinct here.
[ALL MIGHT]
Thank you for inviting me.
It’s truly a
pleasure to be here.
Formal speeches
aren’t my thing‐‐
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
This is an announcement from
the I‐Island security system.
We have received a report
that an explosive
device was discovered
somewhere on the I‐Expo grounds.
‐‐[SATO] A bomb?
‐‐[SERO] Seriously?
[ANNOUNCER 1AA] I‐Island will
now be in high‐alert mode.
Your safety is our top priority.
Residents and tourists should
return to their lodgings...
[HAGAKURE]
Oh, man.
I hope nobody’s hurt.
We’ll be safe as long
as we follow directions.
Oh, yeah, totally.
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
Anyone remaining on the street
after ten minutes will be
in violation of the law.
[SHOJI]
We should hurry.
Of course.
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
As a precautionary measure,
most of the main
island buildings
will now be sealed off.
I repeat: we have
received a report...
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
[WOLFRAM]
In case you haven’t caught on,
the security system is
under our control now.
I know we’ve got a lot
of heroes in here,
but if you decide
to make a scene...
[WOLFRAM] ...I’ll make sure
the security sentries think
the good people they’ve
got in their sights
are dangerous criminals.
So, I’d play nice.
Because everyone on this
island is my hostage.
Naturally, that
includes all of you.
Do it.
[RESEARCHER 1A] The emergency
restraining devices!
Crap!
[gunshot]
[WOLFRAM]
Don’t move.
If you take so much as a step,
I’ll kill everyone in this room.
Villain.
There’s a good boy.
You’re going to follow
All Might’s lead
and do whatever I say, right?
[DAVID] Toshi. You have no
choice but to listen to them.
[ALL MIGHT]
Dave...
[DAVID] Don’t worry. I’ll make
sure everyone is safe.
Don’t make a move.
[TODOROKI]
I’m not getting any signal.
It looks like my service
is completely blocked.
Are you serious?
The elevator’s not
working either.
What the heck is going on here?
It’s strange that the system
would go on high alert.
That’s not the protocol whenever
explosives are discovered.
Iida. Let’s go to that party.
For what reason.
Because that’s the
place we can find
All Might right now.
Wait, All Might’s in there?
Oh, thank goodness,
we don’t have
anything to worry about, then.
So, Melissa.
Do you know of any way
we can get down there
without the elevator?
[MELISSA] Yeah, sure. We can
use the emergency stairs.
That will at least get us close.
We’ll follow your lead, then.
[TSUYU]
Our phones don’t have a signal.
And the internet’s
not working, either.
[ASHIDO]
Ugh.
What happened to
all the channels?
[HAGAKURE]
We’re roughin’ it, ladies!
But I brought some
games along. Who’s in?
[WOLFRAM]
Don’t worry.
If ya stay quiet, there’s
no reason to hurt anyone.
We plan to release you safely
when the time is right.
What are you criminals after?
‐‐[WOMEN gasp]
‐‐[groans]
[WOLFRAM]
Do you not know how to listen?
Stay down.
[phone ringing]
What’s up? Yeah, I got it.
[WOLFRAM] Hey, Tubby.
You a researcher here?
Yes. I am.
Take this one up.
No, please. Don’t.
Stop it. That man
is my assistant.
What do you plan
on doing to him?
[WOLFRAM]
Hm? Ah. The famous David Shield.
Bring him, too.
[DAVID]
What if I refuse?
Then somewhere on this island,
you’ll hear a pretty little
blonde girl scream.
All right. Lead the way.
[ALL MIGHT]
Dave.
I have to subdue these villains
and get the system back online.
How much power do
I even have left?
[ALL MIGHT]
I have to find a way.
Because I am here.
The Symbol of Peace.
[ALL MIGHT]
What? Young Midoriya?
Okay, he knows that we’re here.
Jiro, is your jack in place?
[JIRO]
Yeah, ready.
[IZUKU whispering] You can talk
to us. We’re listening!
[whispering] Hope you
can you hear me.
Some villains have
taken the tower.
They have control of
the security system,
and everyone on
this island is now
being held as a hostage.
That includes the heroes
who are at this party.
It’s dangerous. Get away from
here as soon as you can.
[JIRO]
This is bad, Midoriya.
[TENYA] We’ve received All
Might’s orders loud and clear.
He’s our teacher.
I suggest we follow
his instructions
and escape this place.
Otherwise, we’d be
going against his will.
I’m afraid I have to agree
with what Iida is saying.
We’re still only students.
We can’t fight these villains
if we don’t have
our hero licenses.
[gasps] Why don’t
we get outta here
and tell the heroes outside?
It’s not going to be
very easy to escape.
The security system here
is on the same level
as that of the Tartarus prison,
which is where they keep
the most dangerous
criminals in the world!
Then, all we can do
is sit and wait
until everything’s
over, I guess.
[JIRO] Are you really okay
with that, Kaminari?
Well, what choice do we have?
Don’t you think we should
at least try and stop them?
Hey, come on, those villains
have even got All Might trapped.
There’s no way we can
stop them ourselves
if the actual pros are stuck!
Aren’t we trying to
be pros ourselves?
[YAOYOROZU]
Well, yes, but we’re not allowed
to work as heroes‐‐
you know that.
Does that mean that
it’s right for us
to do nothing at all?
Well. It’s complicated.
[IZUKU]
I wanna help.
[OCHACO]
Really, Deku?
I want to save them.
You wanna go fight
those villains?
Didn’t you learn anything
from the USJ, Midoriya?!
This is totally different.
We don’t have to fight them.
We just need to think of
a way to rescue All Might
and everyone else at the party
without facing the bad guys.
That’s easy to say,
but you know it won’t
be that simple.
[IZUKU]
I know, but I still wanna try.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] We can figure out
what the best plan of action is
and keep these
criminals from winning.
We can save everyone!
Are you sure?
[MELISSA] I know where
the security system is.
It’s on the top floor
of this tower.
If these criminals managed
to take control of it,
then the authentication
locks and password
have probably been disabled.
We should be able to restart
the system ourselves.
We just have to stay off
the villains’ radar
until we can get to the
top floor. That’s all.
If we do that, the whole
island will be safe again.
Then it’s possible.
Sure, but how do we keep
on the low for that long?
The security system
hasn’t discovered us yet.
That means the villains probably
don’t know how it
works very well.
So we avoid fighting anyone
and try to get the
place back to normal.
It could work.
Not bad. What do ya think?
Let’s do it!
Many of our enemies are likely
gathered there on the top floor.
[IZUKU] If we’re fast,
we won’t have to fight them.
When the security system
goes back to normal,
All Might and the others
will be released.
They’ll immediately
jump into action
and stop the
villains‐‐I know it.
Let’s do this, guys!
[IZUKU]
Uraraka!
I don’t wanna sit around
here being helpless.
Not if there’s something
we can actually try.
What’s important is that
we’re helping people,
even if we’re not real heroes.
That’s exactly the way
I feel about things.
We’ll follow our hearts
and save the island!
Yeah!
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya. I’ll go with you, too.
I’m in.
Todoroki!
Thanks, Kyoka!
[TENYA] The moment I think
we’ve gone too far, it’s over.
If that’s something
you can agree to,
I’ll join you as well.
[IZUKU]
Okay!
All right. If that’s
the case, I’ll go, too.
[KAMINARI]
Obviously I’m in.
[OCHACO]
Yaoyorozu!
[IZUKU]
Kaminari!
Have you all lost your minds?!
All right, I’ll go!
[IZUKU]
Thanks, Mineta!
[KAMINARI] The girls’ll think
we’re so cool for this.
[OCHACO]
Be a hero, Mineta!
Melissa, you can wait
down here for us, okay?
No, I’m going, too.
Uh‐‐ But, without a Quirk,
you’ll be in danger.
I don’t suppose any of
you know how to change
the settings on the
island’s security system?
[KAMINARI]
Uh...
[MELISSA]
I’m a student at the Academy.
I’ll be useful to you.
Hold on.
I know I might just
get in your way.
At least until we get
up to the top floor.
But I want to help.
People are in danger!
[gasps]
[MELISSA]
Please!
Yeah, all right, then.
Let’s do this.
We’ll save everyone.
Yeah!
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Oh, no!
That look in your eyes.
Don’t tell me...
Please. Run away!
[IZUKU]
I know what you’re thinking.
[ALL MIGHT]
It’s too dangerous.
[IZUKU] But I have to do
whatever I can to help.
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya.
[IZUKU]
It’ll be okay. You’ll see.
[ALL MIGHT]
He’s not going to leave.
I know I should be furious
that he’s ignoring
his teacher’s wishes.
But who am I kidding?
If he didn’t act right now,
then he wouldn’t
be my successor.
I’ll just have to
keep this form up.
And have faith that
they can get us
out of this situation
on their own.
We’re counting on you,
fledgling heroes!
Let’s go!
[STUDENTS]
Right!
[SWORDKIL]
Here’s the smart guy.
[HENCHMAN 1C] Good. Hurry up
and unlock the vault.
You’re not the boss here.
Well, you heard him.
I’d move quickly if you
wanna keep your head on.
Sure. I’ll begin.
[SWORDKIL]
Take ’em.
[HENCHMAN 1D]
This way.
[TENYA]
Level 30.
Wait, Melissa.
How high does it go?
[panting]
The 200th floor.
[KAMINARI]
The what?!
[MINETA]
That’s way too many stairs!
But it’s still better than
running into the villains.
[panting]
Hey, Melissa.
Do you want me to use
my Quirk on you?
I’ll be fine.
But thanks anyway!
[MELISSA] Save your power
for when we need it.
I’m right behind you.
[TENYA]
This route’s blocked!
What should we do?
Break through it?
[MELISSA]
If we did that.
I’m sure the security system
would alert the villains
that someone’s in here.
[MINETA] Then why don’t we go
through this door instead?
‐‐Mineta!
‐‐[MELISSA] No, don’t!
[HENCHMAN 1C gasps]
[SWORDKIL]
Somethin’ wrong?
[HENCHMAN 1C] A door on
a high floor just opened.
What the hell?
I thought you scanned each
level and they were all clear.
[WOLFRAM] Use the barriers to
trap them on the 80th floor.
Don’t let those kids escape.
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Roger.
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Be careful, everyone.
Villains can be cunning.
[TODOROKI]
Is there another way to go up?
There should be another
emergency staircase
down at the other
end of the hallway.
Let’s hurry!
[ALL gasp]
[IZUKU]
The gates!
The ones behind us, too!
[gasps] Todoroki!
I’m on it!
Everyone, quick, we can
cross through here!
[IZUKU]
What is this place?
[MELISSA]
It’s a plant factory.
They research the effects that
Quirks have on fauna here.
Hold on! Look. The
elevator’s coming up.
Don’t tell me the
villains found us.
We should hide and
let them pass.
[KAMINARI] I wonder if
we can use that elevator
to get to the top floor
once they’re gone.
[MELISSA]
No. Only authorized people
can use the controls,
unfortunately.
And it’s built like
a bomb shelter,
so we can’t even
break in and try.
Of course we can’t
go the easy way.
[elevator dings]
Look at their clothes.
They’re definitely the
villains from the party.
[HENCHMAN 1B]
He said the kids came in here.
[HENCHMAN 1A]
They just had to pick a place
with so many hiding spots.
[OCHACO]
They’re after us!
Stay quiet.
[MINETA]
Please leave. I don’t wanna die.
[JIRO]
Keep going.
[YAOYOROZU] Don’t stop.
Please don’t notice us.
[HENCHMAN 1A]
Hey, we see you, stupid kids.
[IZUKU]
What should we do?
Are we gonna have to face them?
[KATSUKI]
What’d you say, ya bastard?
[IZUKU]
Kacchan and Kirishima?
[HENCHMAN 1B]
What are you two doin’ here?
[KATSUKI] Ha. That’s what
I wanna know, too.
Hey, man, just leave
this to me. Okay?
Um, we kinda got lost
lookin’ for this party?
Can you maybe point us
in the right direction?
How did they get all the
way up to the 80th floor
looking for the reception?
[HENCHMAN 1A] Don’t lie
to me or you’ll regret it!
Hey, watch out!
Kirishima!
[KATSUKI]
This looks like...
[KIRISHIMA]
Todoroki?
The three of us can keep
them busy down here.
Look for a way
to get to the top.
What’re you doing?
‐‐[TENYA] But, you guys‐‐
‐‐[TODOROKI] I’m fine. Go!
[YAOYOROZU]
Todoroki!
I’ll be right behind you
after I clean up this mess.
Right!
Wait, you guys are here, too?
What the heck’s
goin’ on, Todoroki?
You didn’t hear the
broadcast alert?
Never mind then. Some villains
have taken over the tower.
Wait, that’s what this is about?
[TODOROKI]
I’ll explain more when I can.
No time now.
What’s with this guy’s Quirk?
[TODOROKI]
Stay on your guard.
[KATSUKI]
Shut up! I know that.
So you wanna pick a fight?
Then let’s see how
tough you really are.
[TODOROKI grunts]
[yells]
[KATSUKI]
Die!
[HENCHMAN 1B groans]
[KIRISHIMA]
Bakugo!
Kirishima!
[TODOROKI]
Dodge!
[HENCHMAN 1A] You boys know
how to fight, don’t you?
Hm. Where’d you come from?
Right, like we’d tell a
couple ’a weak‐ass villains.
Why would we tell you anything?
This way’s blocked as well.
[MINETA] Great, so what
are we supposed to do.
We’re like helpless mice
stuck in a fancy cage.
We need a plan.
Hey, Melissa.
Where does that little
vent up at the edge
of the ceiling
lead to? Over there!
I think it runs under
the maintenance room
for the sunlight system.
Ha! There’s probably
an emergency ladder
in the maintenance room, right?
[MELISSA]
Well, yeah, there is.
But it’s a manual release,
so someone would
have to be inside to
let it down for us.
Is this really as far as we go?
No, there’s still a possibility.
[YAOYOROZU] If somebody
climbs through the vent
and to the exterior
wall, they can get
into the maintenance room.
Right!
There must be another
vent leading inside!
They can get in that way!
But who can go through
such a cramped space
and then climb the outer
wall without falling?
You can’t be serious!
No, I can’t!
[OCHACO]
Please, you have to, Mineta.
[JIRO] You’re the only
one of us who can do it!
You idiots.
Do you have any idea
how high up we are?
If you save everyone
and become a celebrity,
they’ll interview you on TV,
and then you’ll be popular
with girls everywhere.
[BOTH]
Come on!
Just imagine the harem.
Oh, man. Okay, fine,
I’ll do it! Whatever!
Harem, harem, harem,
harem, harem!
Harem, harem, harem, harem!
I did it! The chicks
are gonna swoon!
Come on, you guys.
Time to show me some love.
Let’s have some kisses
from the ladies, please.
You were incredible, Mineta!
As I’d expect from
a student hero.
[MINETA] That’s it, let’s
get fired up, everyone!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[SWORDKIL] What’s the deal?
Can’t you find ’em?
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Damn it!
Hey, 80th floor.
You’re lettin’ those
dumb kids get away.
What’s the problem?
We’re workin’ on it.
[KATSUKI yells]
[HENCHMAN 1B grunts]
[HENCHMAN 1B yells]
[HENCHMAN 1A yells]
[TODOROKI] This guy’s not
making matter disappear;
he’s displacing it.
Is that how his Quirk works?
Don’t learn, do you?
I can’t keep messin’
around forever‐‐
it’s time to put an end to this.
[yells]
[KATSUKI]
Howitzer... Impact!
[groans]
Damn you!
Bakugo!
[HENCHMAN 1A]
What the hell?
[KATSUKI]
That’s the sweat from my palms.
It works like nitroglycerine.
[gasps]
[groans]
[KATSUKI]
Kirishima!
[TODOROKI]
Are you okay?
Um. I can’t move.
Can you get me outta here?
Are you that stupid?
Just turn your damn
Quirk off, you idiot.
[KIRISHIMA] Oh. Right. Guess
I shoulda thought of that.
[TODOROKI] I’m just glad
to see you’re not injured.
Yeah. Same to you guys.
[KATSUKI]
Hmph.
Thank you.
Whoa, where’d that come from?
Don’t worry about it.
I’m not worried.
[TODOROKI] Right. Let’s
catch up with the others.
[KATSUKI]
Don’t order me around.
Todoroki. Time to give
us some details.
[TODOROKI] Looks like
they’ve gotten serious.
[HENCHMAN 1C] Boss, those are
no ordinary kids in the tower.
They’re students from
UA High’s hero course.
They’re well trained.
[WOLFRAM] The brats are
probably trying to restore
the security system.
Be on alert.
You sent out the security drones
on the 80th floor, right?
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Yes, sir!
Then raise any barriers
from floors 100 to 130
and let ’em pass freely.
Just do what I say.
[KAMINARI] Seems like we’ve
gotten pretty lucky.
The path’s been clear since
we passed the 100th floor.
Yeah, do you think
we lost them maybe?
I doubt that’s it.
It’s quite possible that
they’re leading us somewhere.
Likely.
Even if that’s the case,
we’ve almost made it
to the top floor! We’re so
close to this being over.
[OCHACO]
So many robot sentries.
[TENYA]
The villains aren’t just trying
to block us in anymore.
It looks like they’re actually
trying capture us now.
If so, then I bet
they realized that
we’re hero course students.
[YAOYOROZU]
If that’s true,
no reason not to show
them what we can do.
You’re right.
We’ll go ahead and
commence with Plan A.
Ready, Kaminari?
You got it. I won’t
let you guys down.
Let’s do this, Iida.
[TENYA]
Right!
[KAMINARI]
Indiscriminate shock.
One point three million volts!
It’s not working!
Fine! How ’bout we
try 2,000,000 volts?!
Don’t! If you do that, then...
[KAMINARI]
Yay.
[JIRO]
...you’ll turn stupid.
[IZUKU]
Well, at least he stopped
the robots for us, right?
[KAMINARI]
Uh‐heh!
‐‐[JIRO] Kaminari!
‐‐They’re just too strong!
Right, then. Quick. Plan B.
On it!
[YAOYOROZU] We can jam their
communications with these.
[OCHACO]
Take that!
And that!
[grunts]
Now, Mineta!
Don’t hurt Kaminari!
He’s got a harem to get home to!
It worked!
Aw, man!
Our turn. C’mon, Midoriya.
Let’s go!
[IZUKU]
One for All... Full Cowling!
And Full Gauntlet!
I think it’d be perfect for you.
You should be able
to use your full power
if you have it on.
[IZUKU]
First, I’ll try it out with just
30 percent of my power.
Smash!
[IZUKU] It didn’t hurt.
My arm is fine. I’ve got this.
[KAMINARI]
Whee!
Jiro! Do they have backup?
Yeah, coming from the left!
[TENYA] Then we’re heading
the opposite way.
[STUDENTS]
Right!
Deku, what’s with that
glove? It’s amazing!
It worked perfectly,
Melissa, thanks.
I’m so glad you brought it.
I didn’t know how to
get it off my arm.
[HENCHMAN 1C] Boss, there’s
something interfering
with the drones’ sensors.
We’ve lost those kids.
[WOLFRAM]
Lose the chatter.
We don’t know if one of
those brats has a Quirk
that’ll let ’em spy on us.
I hear a lot of those
security machines
on the floor below us.
Any sounds from above?
No. It should be clear.
[TENYA]
Let’s go!
[ALL gasp]
[TENYA]
A trap?
Let’s break through, Iida!
Wait a sec.
We can’t damage these servers.
It could affect the
island’s security system!
[MINETA] How many of
these things are there?
We can handle these machines
while protecting the servers.
Midoriya, go.
Take Melissa and see if you
can find a different route.
We’ll leave it to them, come on.
Ochaco, you should
come with us, too.
But, the robots...
Do it. They may need you.
[TENYA]
Torque over, recipro burst!
If you’ll take over
the gun, then
I’ll make us some soft ammo.
Roger that!
I won’t let you hurt my ladies!
[KAMINARI]
Yay.
Fire!
[panting]
[gasps]
[OCHACO]
Deku, you can’t stop! Run!
If we all get caught here,
Iida and the others
did that for nothing!
Everyone... Please be safe!
[TENYA]
Stalled.
[TENYA yelps]
Iida! Yao‐momo, ammo!
Yao‐momo?
That’s my limit with Creation.
My scalp’s telling me that
it’s time to surrender.
[JIRO grunts]
[YAOYOROZU gasps]
[SWORDKIL]
Ha! That’s what you get
for thinking you can take us.
What about the three who ran?
We’re looking for them now.
These kids are so annoying.
[IZUKU]
What is this?
[MELISSA]
The wind power generator.
So what are we doing here?
There are more
robots in the tower.
Probably just waiting there
for a chance to ambush us.
But if we climb to
the top from here,
we’ll avoid them.
There’s an emergency
exit we can enter.
[IZUKU]
All the way up there?
[MELISSA]
But we have Ochaco.
Your Quirk makes anything
you touch weightless, right?
So, this should be easy.
Leave it to me.
[OCHACO]
Melissa. Hang on to Deku.
[MELISSA]
Okay!
Go!
All right!
[gasps] Oh, no!
Uraraka!
Release your Quirk
and get out of there!
[OCHACO]
I can’t!
If I do that, you might not
make it to the top in time.
Ochaco, no!
[IZUKU]
Hurry up! Faster!
Come on. We’re almost there!
[IZUKU]
Kacchan!
[OCHACO]
Todoroki and Kirishima!
[TODOROKI]
That was close, are you okay?
Yeah, fine.
I used my Quirk on
Deku and Melissa.
They should be able
to reach the top.
[TODOROKI]
Good job.
Now you can help us
stop these things!
Who died and made you boss?
Aw, come on, man.
You’re a good team!
[KATSUKI]
Dream on.
Thanks so much, you guys‐‐
[BOTH yell]
Oh, no! They’re blowing away!
Bakugo!
Aim the propeller
at Midoriya, quick!
I told you not to
give me orders!
[yells]
That did it!
Yeah!
[IZUKU] Todoroki. You used
your flames! Thank you!
[MELISSA] Deku! We’re
going to hit the wall!
[MELISSA]
This gauntlet is strong.
It could withstand Uncle
Might’s punches three times,
I would think.
[IZUKU] This is it,
no time to hold back now!
[IZUKU]
Hang on tight!
Okay!
[IZUKU]
One For All... Full Cowling.
Detroit... Smash!
They got in the tower! Release!
[MELISSA, IZUKU yell]
Send Swordkil in and the others.
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Yes, sir!
[WOLFRAM] Defend the control
room until I can get there.
[ALL MIGHT]
Keep it up, All Might.
Just a little while longer.
Your students will prevail.
You know they will!
Ah‐‐ Deku, are you okay?
[IZUKU] I think so. I’m
more worried about you.
I’m fine. Just some scratches.
[SWORDKIL]
You shouldn’t have come here.
Tell me why you criminals
are doing this!
You chose the wrong place
to play hero, kid!
[cackles]
[MELISSA]
Stop it!
[SWORDKIL]
Get out of the way!
Little girls‐‐
[IZUKU]
Melissa!
Don’t worry. Look, it’s
hardly even bleeding.
[IZUKU]
Here. Let me.
I apologize. I
couldn’t protect you.
[MELISSA]
I think you mean "thank you."
Right!
Let’s go, then.
We’re almost to the top!
Yeah!
[HENCHMAN 1G]
They’re here!
[IZUKU] Melissa, where’s
the control room located?
[MELISSA] In front of
the central elevator.
Someone’s in there.
[gasps] Papa!
[IZUKU]
Whoa, it is!
Why is he up on the
top floor, though?
Maybe the villains
brought him here.
They might need
something from him.
We have to help him!
Right.
[gasps] I’ve unlocked
it. Block 1147.
[SAM]
Wonderful.
[DAVID]
It’s opening.
[SAM]
You did it, Professor!
Look, everything is
here. It’s perfect.
[DAVID]
Finally. I’ve gotten it back.
All my research.
And they just took my
device away from me.
But now it’s mine.
[SAM]
Just like we planned.
And it looks like the villains
are holding things down.
[DAVID]
Thank you.
I couldn’t have done any of
this without your help, Sam.
Papa.
[BOTH gasp]
[DAVID]
Melissa? No.
[SAM]
Miss, what are you doing here?
What does he mean that
it’s like you planned it?
Don’t tell me that you’re
the one behind this.
This was all you?
Just to steal something?
No. It can’t be true!
Yes, it is.
Papa. How could you?
[SAM] The professor is
only trying to get back
what was stolen.
The invention inside
this briefcase
can amplify someone’s Quirk.
Wait, is that even possible?
[SAM] Yes. It’s still
being tested, of course.
But, unlike with drugs,
this device can magnify
a person’s Quirk without
doing any damage
to their body or brain.
Yet, despite that,
our sponsors confiscated
this prototype and
our research data.
Then they demanded that
the project be abandoned.
They worried that
something like this would
drastically affect the structure
of superhuman society.
Fearing chaos, governments
from different nations
put pressure on your
father to end it.
That’s why we did this.
I can get my research
back? But how?
[SAM] All we have to do is hire
someone to steal it back for us.
[DAVID]
Ugh. Don’t be ridiculous.
[SAM] Wait, listen.
I’m not talking about
using actual
criminals, Professor.
[DAVID]
Huh?
We can hire people who will
pretend to be villains
and have them "force" us
to break in and take it.
Of course,
we’ll order them
not to harm anyone.
And after it’s done,
we can continue
our research somewhere else.
This is crazy.
I know, but I wanna
get that data back
and keep working.
Don’t you feel the
same way, Professor?
[SAM]
I’ve completed the preparations.
We’ll carry this out on the
day of the I‐Expo preopening
when the tower’s closed.
The plan will begin
alongside the reception
since that’s the only time
when all the people involved
will be together
in the same place.
We’ll pull the strings
in the background
while the actors make
it seem like I‐Island
has been taken over by villains.
[SAM]
Professor?
I don’t understand.
There’s something
I’m missing, right?
You’d never do this!
I’m so sorry.
[gasps]
[MELISSA]
This doesn’t make any sense.
The Papa I know
and love wouldn’t
act like a villain,
no matter what.
So why, then? Why?
I had to for All Might.
[BOTH gasp]
[DAVID] You two probably
aren’t aware of this.
But his Quirk is disappearing.
[gasps]
However, if he uses this device,
he’ll be his old self.
No. His abilities will
be even stronger
than they were!
The number‐one hero...
The Symbol of Peace...
...can get his strength
and light back again.
He can keep saving people.
Just like he always has.
[IZUKU]
The professor’s upset because
his friend’s power is fading.
This is happening,
because All Might passed
One For All onto me.
He doesn’t know.
[DAVID]
Please.
Please just let me hand this
device over to All Might.
There’s no time to remake it.
When he’s better,
I don’t care what kind of
punishment I receive.
[MELISSA]
They risked their lives.
Deku and his classmates
went through so much.
Do you know how
dangerous this was?
How hard we were trying to
save everyone on the island?
No, what do you mean?
The villains are fake.
It’s all supposed to be an act!
Of course it was a performance.
[IZUKU, MELISSA gasp]
But the real act was pretending
we weren’t criminals.
You’re the boss!
[IZUKU grunts]
Oh, no, Deku!
[IZUKU] His Quirk lets
him manipulate metal.
[WOLFRAM]
You’d be smart not to resist.
Sam. Hand it over.
[SAM]
Right. Uh. Here you go!
Sam? This was your plan?
You were going to
hand it over all along?
[SAM] You’re the one who
tricked me, professor.
I’ve been your assistant
for all these years,
and you let them take our work.
We could have had
fame and fortune.
But, no.
I deserve more.
I need to be rewarded.
Otherwise my entire career
was a complete waste of time!
[WOLFRAM] Here’s the
payment I promised you.
[gasps]
Sam!
[SAM] No. Why? This isn’t
part of the plan.
[WOLFRAM]
Is it not? That’s strange.
Because it was always
a part of mine.
[grunt]
[IZUKU gasps]
[gasps]
[SAM]
Professor. Why?
Get outta here.
Papa!
Stay back.
[MELISSA grunts]
[DAVID]
Melissa!
[DAVID grunts]
[WOLFRAM] Trying to play
the hero after all this?
Too late for that.
No matter what
your reasons were,
you’ve dirtied your hands now.
Whether we’re real villains
or actors is irrelevant.
You planned and committed
an actual crime here.
You’re exactly the
same as we are.
You can no longer remain
a respected scientist.
Or continue your
research without shame.
Your life is forever tainted
by the darkness of villainy.
[WOLFRAM cackles]
[WOLFRAM]
And if you want a future at all,
you’ll be a good scientist
and mass produce
this device so I can sell it.
[grunts]
Hey, take him to the roof.
[MELISSA]
No.
Please, no. Give him back!
[WOLFRAM]
That reminds me.
This’ll be much easier
if I get rid of the
professor’s attachments.
[IZUKU]
Don’t you hurt her!
Smash!
[IZUKU]
Melissa!
I’ve got the professor and Sam.
[IZUKU]
You save everyone else.
[gasps]
[WOLFRAM]
Stop her! Don’t let ’er escape.
Right.
[IZUKU]
I won’t let you past me.
Don’t make threats you
can’t live up to, kid!
[IZUKU]
Everyone...
[MELISSA]
[IZUKU]
All Might...
[MELISSA]
Papa...
[IZUKU]
I will save you.
[MELISSA]
I promise.
She got control of
the security system?
[KATSUKI]
What happened?
They just stopped.
Midoriya and Melissa must’ve
made it to the top!
[ANNOUNCER 1AA]
I‐Island’s security system
is now operating in normal mode.
Oh, hey, that’s good.
Yeah, my phone’s working, too!
[HEROS gasping]
[HENCHMAN 1F]
Damn it!
[HENCHMAN 1E]
What’s happening?
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL MIGHT] Did you pull
it off, young heroes?
[WOLFRAM]
Is it here?
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Just landed.
[WOLFRAM]
Then we’re leavin’.
[HENCHMAN 1C]
Yes, sir.
[grunts]
[pants]
[IZUKU]
I have to rescue him.
Otherwise, why am I even here?
[IZUKU] I may not be a pro,
but I’ll do what I can for now.
[phone rings]
[ALL MIGHT]
Melissa, what’s happening?
Oh, thank goodness!
Papa’s been taken by
the villains, Uncle Might!
And Deku’s gone after them.
[ALL MIGHT] Don’t worry.
I’m going to stop them.
[PILOT HENCHMAN]
Boss, what about everyone else?
[WOLFRAM] We’re goin’ before
the security system’s
back online.
[HENCHMEN]
Uh. Yes, sir!
[DAVID]
Kill me. Just do it.
[WOLFRAM] I’ll add a few more
sins to your heart first.
But then I’ll make
your wish come true.
[IZUKU]
Stop!
You give the professor
back right now!
I wonder.
Did you come to
bring this man back
so he can pay for his crimes?
Of course not.
I’m here to rescue David Shield
from the likes of you!
Even though he’s a criminal?
You watch. I’m going
to save everyone.
That includes the professor.
It doesn’t look like that to me.
Shut up! This is what heroes do.
They help people
who are in trouble.
How, exactly?
[gasps]
Save yourself. Run away!
[WOLFRAM] Jeez. Bein’ a hero
seems really inconvenient.
I didn’t even use
much of my power,
yet you’re helpless.
[gasps]
[WOLFRAM]
Doesn’t sound like a very smart
way to live to me.
[WOLFRAM]
Take off.
[PILOT HENCHMAN]
Roger!
[IZUKU] That guy shouldn’t be
able to activate much metal
if all he can touch
is the helicopter!
No. You’re...
[MELISSA]
Deku!
Grab my hand!
Stop it. Let me go, Midoriya.
Melissa is down there.
Your daughter is
waiting for you!
[WOLFRAM] I’ll give you this.
You act like a real hero.
But you’re an idiot, too.
[yelps]
[screams]
[IZUKU]
Don’t give up. Think!
What do I do? What can I do?
[MELISSA]
Deku!
[groans]
[WOLFRAM]
Have a nice nap.
‐‐Come back. You can’t!
‐‐[MELISSA] Are you hurt?
Let him go! Don’t
take the professor!
Damn it!
Don’t you dare lose that smile.
All right, Young Midoriya?
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL MIGHT] It’s fine now.
Do you know why?
Because I am here.
[BOTH gasp]
All Might is free!
I’ll have you return
my friend to me,
you fiend!
[MELISSA]
Papa!
My Melissa.
[ALL MIGHT]
Everything will be okay.
We did it.
I’m so sorry.
It’s my fault.
[IZUKU]
All Might!
[yells]
[MELISSA]
Papa!
[IZUKU]
Professor!
[WOLFRAM]
I heard Sam.
All Might’s Quirk
is failing him.
He doesn’t have the same
unstoppable power he once did.
[IZUKU] He’s using
the professor’s device!
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Damn! Not much time.
You really don’t know
when to give up, do you?
Texas...
...Smash!
‐‐[ALL MIGHT] What?
‐‐All Might!
Is that all you got?
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[WOLFRAM] David Shield’s genius
lives up to its reputation.
I can tell my Quirk’s
growing more powerful.
[WOLFRAM cackles]
It feels amazing!
I’m never taking this off.
Dave, what in the
world have you made?
I had no idea he created
something so powerful.
[WOLFRAM]
Now...
I think I know the best
way to raise the price
of this device.
I can charge whatever
I want if it was used
to kill the world’s
number‐one hero.
[screams]
[IZUKU]
All Might. This isn’t good.
He’s at his limit.
[laughs]
Is Uncle Might okay?
Why won’t you just die already?!
All Might!
[KATSUKI]
Go to hell!
How can you let
yourself get beat
by such a lame final boss.
Hurry and take him down!
Thanks for the help,
Young Bakugo!
We’ll do what we can.
We’ll help you!
Todoroki! Everyone!
Iida, let’s knock
those hunks of metal
out of the sky.
Yaoyorozu, take care
of things down here.
Right!
[ALL MIGHT] With my students
so motivated, there’s no way
I can let myself be
held back by something
so foolish as a limit.
[ALL MIGHT] I need to
push past my boundaries
and go beyond.
[ALL MIGHT]
It’s time to be Plus Ultra.
[ALL MIGHT yells]
Carolina... Smash!
[ALL MIGHT]
Prepare yourself, villain!
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL MIGHT]
Nice trick, but I‐‐
[WOLFRAM] "Prepare" myself?
Take your own advice.
You’ve underestimated me.
[ALL MIGHT] Where did
this strength come from?
[coughs]
[ALL MIGHT screams]
All Might!
Are you all right?
Damn it!
[ALL MIGHT] This new power
seems to enhance his muscles.
He must have multiple Quirks.
No, wait, it couldn’t be.
[WOLFRAM]
Oh, yes.
While we were planning
this little plot,
I received an intriguing phone
call from the man himself.
He said he wanted to
work with me. To help.
When I asked him
why he’d bother,
he was happy to
explain his interest.
[ALL FOR ONE] If All Might’s
friend wants to have a hand
in something evil, I will
assist in his fall from grace
in any way that I can.
I regret only that I
will not be able to see
All Might’s face twist
in pain when he discovers
the truth about the professor.
All For One is behind this?
What’s the matter?
Looks like you’ve
finally stopped smiling.
[ALL MIGHT]
No!
[WOLFRAM cackles]
[ALL]
All Might, no!
Please don’t do this!
[WOLFRAM]
Farewell, Symbol of Peace!
Uncle Might, no!
[IZUKU]
Detroit...
...Smash!
[WOLFRAM]
That damn brat!
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya!
Your body can’t handle this.
It’s too reckless.
[IZUKU]
Yeah, but...
It’s a hero’s job
to save those in need,
no matter what, right?
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
You make a good point.
And it looks like I’m in
quite a bind without you.
Will you lend me your aid
once more, Young Midoriya?
[IZUKU]
Yes, sir!
Let’s go!
[IZUKU]
Yes, sir!
[WOLFRAM]
There’s no way you can stop me.
You’re insignificant pests.
And you don’t know
when to lie down
and be crushed.
You’re the one who
doesn’t know he’s beat!
I won’t let you stop them!
[WOLFRAM]
This is over!
[STUDENTS yelp]
[OCHACO]
What’s happening?
[ALL MIGHT] To overcome
the crisis in front of you.
[IZUKU]
By giving everything you’ve got.
[ALL MIGHT]
And save people.
[IZUKU]
No matter the cost.
[ALL MIGHT]
That’s what makes someone...
[IZUKU]
...a hero!
I’ll bring down
this entire tower!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Double Detroit...
...Smash!
[groans]
Deku!
[BOTH]
Stop him, All Might!
[ALL]
Go, Midoriya!
[BOTH]
Destroy this guy!
Let’s go...
...beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!
[screams]
[WOLFRAM screams]
[TENYA]
They did it.
They stopped him.
They beat up that villain
and saved our lives!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[gasps]
[MELISSA]
Deku!
[IZUKU]
Melissa!
I’m so glad you’re alive!
[ALL MIGHT]
Dave.
Dave!
[DAVID]
All Might.
[ALL MIGHT]
I came to save you, my friend.
[DAVID]
Thank you.
[MELISSA]
Papa!
[IZUKU]
All Might!
[ALL MIGHT]
If you want to thank someone,
you should thank Melissa
and Young Midoriya.
[MELISSA]
He’s okay. I can’t believe it.
I’m so grateful.
And it’s thanks to you guys.
You’re how we saved the island.
[IZUKU]
We did it together.
After all,
the only way I made it
this far was because
I had your Full
Gauntlet on my arm.
Thanks so much for your help.
We’re a good team.
Oh, but I broke it.
Sorry about that.
[laughs] Don’t worry about it.
[OCHACO]
Deku! Melissa!
[STUDENTS shouting]
[IZUKU]
We’re fine up here!
All Might and the
professor are okay, too.
But what about the
rest of you guys?
[OCHACO]
We’re good!
[TENYA]
Alive, anyway!
[ALL MIGHT] I’ve heard most
of what happened from Melissa.
It’s all true.
I was so scared you’d
lose your light.
Scared that the peace
you built as a hero
would fade away with you.
But my ideas and that
device were nothing more
than ways to maintain
the status quo.
To ensure that nothing
would ever change.
[DAVID] Even though the future
was standing right there
in front of me the whole time.
I just didn’t notice it.
Look at those two.
She wants to become my
successor, you know that?
And you have Izuku Midoriya.
He’ll take your place
one day, too, won’t he?
He still has a long road ahead.
But, in him shines
the greatest potential
I’ve ever seen among those
who would become heroes.
I can see it, too,
Toshi. Hope.
A light like yours.
[DAVID] That boy has
the heart of a hero.