[NARRATOR]
The Earth Union Fleet
was suddenly caught
in a desperate battle.
[VULGAR grunts]
[OPERATOR 13A] Three craft
damaged in Vulgar's unit!
Sending for help!
[NARRATOR] They had been
attacked by the People of Metus
who trapped them dangerously
close to the atmosphere.
[MECHANIC 13A]
Let's go people! Sortie time!
[LIGIER]
You ready?
I need you back in four
minutes at the most.
I know you think your
Durandal's awesome,
but even it won't withstand
the atmosphere.
[SUBARU] No you're right,
it's been sucking lately.
And I'm a pretty hot mess, too.
Who cares if we don't come back.
Here! New helmets
make everything better.
[gasps] For real?
Yours was looking
a little tragic.
Plus, I know that you hated that
Shigeko wrote your name on it.
You get me.
And PS...
You shouldn't let the fact
that the Durandal
is down affect how
you perform, ya know?
I hate to say it, but I need
you to help us, Subaru.
You're our only hope right now.
[SUBARU]
Y-Yeah, sounds great.
Okay, awesome. Good talk.
You can pay me back
for the helmet later!
[NARRATOR]
It's really that simple.
Having reawakened his
inner warrior thanks to
a droplet of attention
from a gorgeous female,
Subaru placed a protective
film on his new visor.
Sucks putting these things
on a round surface
when you only get one chance.
And they're so damn expensive.
[PAC2-AR] Subaru, the enemy
is quickly approaching.
We need to focus and be ready!
"Primero use la tela
provista para--"
What?
[PAC2-AR] Or I guess we
could just wait to die.
It's whatever.
[PAC2-AR yelps]
Random acts of nakedness?!
Oh, so because he doesn't want
to get lint on his helmet,
I have to get visually harassed.
This level of obsession
with protective film
can't be considered normal!
[beeping]
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru! Incoming enemy!
[SUBARU B laughing]
[SUBARU gasps]
[gasps]
[SUBARU] Are those bubbles
underneath the film?!
Three of them?!
Oh, come on!
Hey, Soob. This is
called checkmate.
Oh, it's you.
[ISUZU] The Kerukeion
will hold him in place!
But I need you to kill him!
Hmph. Hm...?
[ISUZU] That is not a tear
in my favorite suit!
Okay, I need a minute.
Sorry, Subaru B!
You are not getting out of
this that easily. I will--
[gasps]
[SUBARU] Is that a cockpit mite
in one of the bubbles?!
[screaming]
Huh?
The Durandal can't
decelerate, Sir!
It's about to reenter
the atmosphere!
--[LIGIER gasps]
--[VULGAR] Hm?
Ah! Balls!
Why won't you just stay stiff
long enough to get in the hole?
[OPERATOR 13C]
Update! It's in reentry!
[BOTH gasp]
What are you doing?!
Stop messing around
and come back!
[SUBARU yelling]
[NARRATOR] One pilot trying
to rip off a protective film.
Another fighting against
odds to thread a needle.
Two men bound by fate,
plunging into G force!
We've lost contact!
It doesn't look good.
[ALL gaps]
His dumb mecha can't
handle that atmosphere.
Good one, Pee Pants.
What the--?
When'd I reenter the atmosphere?
Hey Soob, guess what? Overtime.
Neither one of us will
survive at this rate.
I'll use my Griffin Mode.
It'll stabilize our
angle of incidence.
Hurry and launch
your escape pod.
I'll catch you. I promise.
[ISUZU]
Subaru? Hey, can you hear me?
He's unconscious.
So be it.
It is a battlefield.
Farewell.
What a drama queen, going out
in a blaze of glory like that.
[PAC2-AR]
We are running out of time!
If we don't evacuate now,
we could die in here--
Shut up! I know!
But I can't just leave the
Durandal to save myself!
Now, let me finish!
I'm typing as fast as I can.
[NARRATOR] In desperate
situations such as these,
Subaru turns to the internet
for council and guidance.
Done! And I did it
without jokes.
That way they know I'm serious!
Submit!
--[computer pings]
--[PAC2-AR gasps]
[SUBARU]
Yes! So many answers!
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU] "LOL"?! But I
didn't use any smilies!
What's wrong with people?!
Screw them!
How do they not recognize
a man with a crisis?
Ow!
[PAC2-AR] Armor temperature
has reached 2,000 degrees!
The escape lever
is under your seat!
Pull it, Subaru! Hurry! Please!
I feel dizzy. Sleepy.
[SUBARU]
You're so strong!
[DURANDAL]
As are you.
[SUBARU]
My boss sucks, amiright?
[DURANDAL]
Believe me, I know.
[NARRATOR]
While the cockpit was broiling,
Subaru reflected on his
memories with the Durandal--
which were actually disturbing
fantasies that never happened.
[SUBARU]
Is this it?
Are we going to die?
[gasps] I don't wanna!
Not now!
I'm sorry! Forgive me, Durandal!
It's just... I can't die yet.
The Earth still needs me,
but I love you! [growls]
[SUBARU] Come on! Why is this
lever so hard to pull?!
[SUBARU]
The familiar embrace of gravity.
I'm on the ground.
I guess this means
I didn't die up there.
It was you.
You protected me.
Thanks, Durandal.
[SUBARU whimpers]
[SUBARU sobs]