[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Air lock is operational.
Commencing final checklist.
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU] There's nothing more
important to me than my cockpit.
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A] Durandal
attached to launch catapult.
Preparing for takeoff.
[SUBARU]
It makes me feel warm.
Like I'm back inside
my mother's womb.
It's the only place
in the universe
that I can go to be
completely alone.
I wanna stay here, snug in
my cockpit, for all eternity.
Subaru. Five hostiles.
You ready?
What if I say "no," Cody.
Would you fly out here and
shoot them down instead?
Let's not find out.
[SUBARU]
I got this.
Give me five, no,
make it three minutes.
[CODY]
And that's why you're the Ace.
I knew I could rely on you.
We'll launch you in two minutes.
Prepare for immediate contact.
Don't die, Subaru.
Roger that.
[CODY laughs]
[SUBARU]
So, two minutes, huh?
That's plenty of time...
...for some pre-flight pork!
[NARRATOR]
This fried pork cutlet
was more than just a snack
to Subaru Ichinose.
It was a symbol of comfort.
[VULGAR]
Me? Oh yeah, I'd bang her.
If the chick is hot, I'll jump
her and her mecha, enemy or not.
[SUBARU]
Kale... Kidney beans...
[NARRATOR] Subaru was unable
to banter with the other pilots,
who were older and
more experienced.
Instead, he spent his downtime
memorizing the nutrition
labels of space smoothies.
Whatcha doin there, slugger?
Checkin' the label to make sure
you got plenty of boner fuel?
Don't want you dyin' out
there a virgin, amirite.
Get offa me.
You're wrong.
I know I'm gonna
make it home alive.
[NARRATOR] To Subaru,
this meal was best alone.
Alone and... cockpitted?
Cutlet ready to la-- Uh?!
What a fool, I almost
forgot the sauce.
Here in this sacred place,
there's no one to criticize
me for double dipping.
I can do whatever
I please with you.
Wait, no! The breading!
This is the worst thing
that could possibly happen
in Durandal's cockpit.
My sanctuaries interiors
can't be coated in grease.
I've got to get to the napkins!
Only then will I
avoid this tragedy!
C'mon!
[SUBARU]
No, no, no, no!
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Twenty seconds to takeoff.
[screams] Oh c'mon!
The cabbage too?!
Anything but the
reeking cabbage!
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Catapult thrust is normal.
Launch is all clear.
Wait, not yet, do you copy?!
There's a pork crisis!
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Durandal, launch.
I didn't even get a single bite!
Nice work out there, Subaru.
Hostiles eliminated.
Mission accomplished.
Subaru Ichinose,
returning to home base.
[VULGAR] So, guys with pretty
faces have pretty asses, too.
[gasping]
Hey, what the hell, man,
no peeping in the shower!
[VULGAR] So I guess honor
students get to take their time,
even when it wastes hot water.
Do you have something
against privacy?
I don't know why you
bother coverin' up.
We're both men, right?
Unless there's somethin'
you're keeping a secret.
[NARRATOR]
Subaru had always tried to hide
his misaligned nipples--
that pointed in two
different directions.
I think we're done here.
So soon?
[alarm blares]
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Enemy approaching!
Pilots, sortie immediately.
Another attack? Dammit.
[SUBARU]
Crap!
How many fighters did they send?
[SUBARU yelling]
[panting]
[SUBARU]
Something's wrong.
I'm finding it difficult
to breathe normally.
But this is supposed
to be my safe space.
Cody, come in!
I've got a problem!
What is it, Subaru?
Your breathing's increased.
Check my oxygen reserves.
[CODY]
Huh.
Looks like they're
over 80% full.
I don't see an issue.
[SUBARU]
I don't on my end, either.
Wait, no.
[NARRATOR]
In the heat of battle,
Subaru realized he was wearing
his unnecessary
t-shirt backward.
And inside out, as well.
This explains my discomfort!
Incoming!
Life and death hang
in the balance.
But I can't concentrate
with my shirt on my throat.
I had to rush getting dressed,
so I didn't realize...
You're to blame.
This is your fault!
Calm down, Subaru,
you've got this.
This is your sanctuary.
You must protect it.
You're the owner of this
magnificent cockpit,
and you can do anything!
Changing your shirt
while fighting is nothing!
Just get it done, idiot!
Right arm!
Left arm!
And now wait until the
right moment to rip it off,
taking care not to stretch
the fabric as I go.
[SUBARU]
Now!
It's no good!
I can't get it over my helmet.
I... I can't see!
[SUBARU screaming]
[SUBARU growling]
Dammit.
How dare you?!
[NARRATOR]
In this moment,
something deep within
Subaru snapped.
[SUBARU] Die, die, die,
die, die, die, die.
[NARRATOR] Though unwilling
to reveal his body
to anyone in real life,
in his cockpit,
he let it all hang out.
[SUBARU]
...die!
[panting] It's over.
Gotcha. On you go.
Farewell.
[NARRATOR]
In year Space Age 0156,
Subaru Ichinose cast
his favorite shirt
into the vacuum of space.
Will this ace pilot be able
to protect planet Earth
better than he protected
his underwear?