What happened to Subaru?
He's acting like a completely
different pilot!
He's probably out
changin' his diaper.
I tried to get him on the radio,
but he didn't say anything back.
[LIGIER] Maybe the Durandel's
malfunctioning.
Well, whatever this is, I'm sure
Honor Roll can handle it.
For the moment,
let's focus on the fight!
[LIGIER]
Roger that!
[SUBARU grunting]
[NARRATOR] How did Subaru
end up with a girthy mouthful
of ehomaki mid battle?
Let's find out.
[SHIGERUKO]
Hey, Subaru! C'mere a sec.
Uh? Is something
the matter, Shigeko?
Nah, I gotta little somethin'
for ya, that's all.
Whipped up some of my special
ehomaki for Setsubun.
Take it, kid, you could
use a little feedin' up.
Thank you very much ma'am.
[SHIGERUKO]
Oh, there ya are! Here.
[SUBARU]
Ehomaki ...
It wasn't really a thing in
the part of Japan I'm from.
[SUBARU] Why's it smell
like pickled balls?
What is that?
[PAC2-AR] It's a sardine head
impaled by a holly branch!
Did you see who
pulled this prank?
[PAC2-AR] Shigeko's the one
who hung it here.
Curse that woman.
[PAC2-AR] It's a custom
to hang these on Setsubun
to ward off evil spirits.
I'm sure she was just
worried about you, Subaru.
But if this putrid smell gets
infused into my cockpit
it'll be like hell in there.
[SUBARU] She also give me
this weird burrito thing.
[PAC2-AR] Oh, that must
be handmade ehomaki .
Eating it in one go while facing
the year's lucky direction
--brings good fortune!
--[beeping]
It's probably all nonsense.
But since she went
to all the trouble.
[PAC2-AR] My research shows
that it was made up
by convenience stores
to boost sales,
but Subaru doesn't
need to know that.
[SUBARU] I should've waited
until after the battle
to bite in. Now I have to
finish it in silence!
Wait.
I also have to look in
the lucky direction!
[muffled] Hey, which way is
supposed to be lucky?
[PAC2-AR] Sorry, but I
can't understand you.
[PAC2-AR] Wait, given
the circumstances,
the answer to what he's
probably asking is--
[PAC2-AR]
This year's lucky direction
is towards this star, Subaru!
[SUBARU] There are a lot
of stars out here!
[PAC2-AR] Yeah, but this
is the brightest star of
the Ursa Minor,
AKA the North Star!
Which means you should
look south-southeast!
[SUBARU]
So this way. Got it!
[PAC2-AR]
And a bit to the right!
[SUBARU] Wait, how much is a
"bit?" I can't just eyeball it!
[PAC2-AR] Sorry, but
the colloquial instructions
given in Japan are imprecise.
The bearings used in the Chinese
systems are a little
more exact, but--
[SUBARU]
PAC2-R isn't gonna be any help.
I need to figure
this out myself.
C'mon. Which way's lucky?
I'll use my universe sense!
[NARRATOR] Despite the danger
around him, Subaru focused
all his senses on finding
his personal lucky direction.
Okay, again with this?
[SUBARU] I found it!
My lucky direction!
[SUBARU grunting]
[SUBARU] No way. The second
half is pure seafood?
That's right! It's what
makes my ehomaki special!
[SUBARU]
How could she?
Doesn't she know seafood
makes you crave soy sauce?
[SUBARU] I'll just have to
let it sink into the roll.
[SUBARU grunts, gasps]
[SUBARU] Oh, come on!
I freakin' botched the tear!
[PAC2-AR]
Uh oh, now you've done it!
[SUBARU] Why don't they
just make it so you can
tear them anywhere?!
Fine then! You wanna
play rough? Let's go!
[SUBARU]
Oh crap! My beautiful cockpit!
[PAC2-AR] If you don't clean
for the next few months
it could cause minor corrosion!
[SUBARU]
What now?
Don't give up, Subaru.
There has to be
a way out of this!
Hm?
[SUBARU] I could use
the ehomaki as a straw and
suck up the soy sauce!
[SUBARU]
It's not working!
[beeping]
[SUBARU] Gotta finish
eating this somehow.
I'll just stick on as
much soy sauce as I can!
[SUBARU]
One more bite and I'm there!
Mission accomplished.
[beeping]
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru! Enemy craft incoming.
I think it's a new model!
I didn't know Setsubun
Oni's wore loin cloths.
[alarm blares]
What is that smell?
[SUBARU]
Is that burnt soy sauce?
[PAC2-AR] Th-Th-The soy sauce
you spilled everywhere
must've slipped into a crack
in the c-c-control panel.
It would seem that you've
shorted the w-w-weapons system.
Even PAC2-R is down.
Damn it. D Saber!
[SUBARU]
Oh, crap!
[LIGIER]
You okay Subaru?
[VULGAR] Did ya s---
your spacesuit again?
Lay off it Hummer--
that was one time.
[LIGIER] Here, they're
gifts from Shigeko.
What are they?
A bunch of tiny bombs?
They're actually still
in the testing phase,
but we've got tons of 'em.
You boys up for a
little field test?
[SUBARU]
Yes, ma'am!
[VULGAR]
Take that!
[SUBARU] It's just like
we're throwing beans.
Get outta here. Stupid Oni.
[NARRATOR] On the Setsubun
holiday of February 3,
space age 157...
[SUBARU grunts]
[NARRATOR]
...ace pilot Subaru Ichinose
ate a bean for each
year of his life.
[SUBARU]
I like beans.