[SHIGERUKO] Here comes
Mamma to save the day!
Someone needs to
give me a raise.
I went lookin' everywhere
for this thing.
Ya know where I found it?
Subaru's cockpit!
[SUBARU]
You gotta be kidding me!
[PAC2-AR] Wow! I have
no idea how it got there!
But I am so very happy
that you found it.
[SUBARU] Like I want
an arm in my cockpit.
It was all fisted up and shoved
up underneath your seat.
[PAC2-AR] Thank goodness I don't
have to cancel my credit card!
Okay, back up.
I did not take her arm!
You son of a bitch.
So you want to just
cruise back in here
and start stealing appendages?
You're a grown-ass pilot!
Stop being jealous of a machine!
It wasn't me.
[PAC2-AR giggles]
PAC2-AR did this! Watch!
She changes when you
guys aren't looking!
She hid the arm!
[PAC2-AR] You're hurting me!
Beep beep! Please stop!
Beep boop beep!
Get off her, Pee Pants!
No means no, Subaru! Let go!
[PAC2-AR]
Stop choking me. Beep boop!
[SUBARU]
Just a darn minute!
She's got a personality
adjustment switch?
And it's on Maximum Evil!
All I have to do is move
the switch and she'll be nice!
Put the robot down,
you little freak.
It's startin' to get real weird.
[PAC2-AR] I apologize for
upsetting you, Mr. Subaru.
Please tell me what
I did to deserve this!
You need a new attitude!
And I'm gonna give it to you!
And then you're going to tell
the truth about what you did!
Got that?
[SUBARU]
Aw, crap!
The freakin' switch is rusted!
[SUBARU]
Oh come on, move!
Someone needs to return
this crap the manufacturer!
"Bike Mode"? That'll work!
[PAC2-AR]
Now functioning in Bike Mode.
[SUBARU]
Be right back! I need a minute!
[LIGIER]
Where are you going?!
[VULGAR]
Wait. Don't break her!
I'm gonna find your box
then stuff you in it
like a metal pretzel.
[PAC2-AR]
Ouch! Ouch! Okay I get it! Ouch!
[SUBARU]
There's gotta be a return slip.
As soon as I fill
it out, she's gone!
[SUBARU]
Where's the damn box?
[PAC2-AR]
On the top shelf in the closet.
You know, you should
really throw away
some of these old game boxes
before you end up on one
of those hoarding shows
Shut up.
Here it is.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
You're discounted?! Of course!
Why wouldn't you be one
of those shady no manual,
no warranty, dollar store,
"as is" robo-knock offs!
Damn it!
That means I'm not
allowed to return you!
You cheap bastards!
[NARRATOR] Subaru ended up not
needing to send PAC2-AR back,
a security camera later revealed
the truth about her actions.
Shigeruko permanently set the
personality to Maximum Good,
and PAC2-AR finally
became the Assist-a-bot
of everyone's dreams.
[PAC2-AR]
Great work, Subaru!
You've wiped out every
enemy craft in this sector
and in record time!
Aw, thank you, PAC2-AR!
My brother-- I mean,
Cody, would be very pleased
with the job you're doing.
[PAC2-AR] I'm happy I could
be of service, "Mr. Soob."
[SUBARU] Guess this means
Isuzu's not coming.
--Figures.
--[beeping]
[PAC2-AR]
Incoming orders.
The Tiramisu wants us to wait
here for Vulgar's team.
[SUBARU] Well, shoot! Bring up
the next episode, then!
[PAC2-AR]
Copy!
Downloaded and ready, sir!
[moans]
[PAC2-AR] I'm so happy to be
sharing quality bonding time,
let's talk about feelings--
[SUBARU]
Shut it! Zombies are happening.
There's the man! Get it, Dave!
No one else handles a Chinese
broadsword like that,
and he's so European.
[PAC2-AR]
Oh! Almost forgot!
Dave dies in season two!
It comes out of nowhere!
[SUBARU gasps]
Why would you say that?!
[PAC2-AR]
I wanted you to be prepared.
Shocks like those can
take you by surprise!
Uh.
Well, sometimes that's what's
fun about these kind of shows.
[PUBE singing]
[PUBE]
Oh! Hey, amigo!
Long time no see!
It's Pube!
[PUBE]
Yes, it is my triumphant return.
Uh. Wait.
How'd you get out
of the mint case?
[PUBE]
You kept me? How sweet!
And a bit weird, yes?
But you should know that once
we fall, another grows back.
Enough about that.
I want you to meet
someone special.
Mi amore ?
[PUBE'S WIFE]
Hi!
Oh, my husband has told
me so much about you!
Your... what?
[PUBE]
That's right. I got married!
[laughs] Hang on,
if she's from me, too,
then aren't you related?
[PUBE]
Let me explain...
[PAC2-AR] He sure talks
to his pubic hair a lot
when his Universe
Sense is activated.
He's registering 89.95% happier
talking to stray
follicles than to me.
I should work harder
for his attention.
I know!
I'll download full seasons
of the shows he watches!
Then, we can watch
them together!
[PUBE]
Wait! An enemy!
And he's speedy!
Right now?
I wonder. Is it my brother?
PAC2-AR! Uh?!
What's with the ad?!
I can't see where I'm going!
[PAC2-AR]
I'm sorry!
This site forces ad content
while downloading!
[SUBARU] I didn't ask you
to download anything!
[PUBE]
Andele !
We gotta unplug the
back of the monitor!
But this is not an HDMI cable!
[PAC2-AR]
I know!
I have a composite input!
The video plug is
the yellow one.
Can you see it?
[PUBE]
Composite input.
Ok, by the root! Pull!
[PUBE'S WIFE grunting]
I'm pullin'!
[PUBE]
Ready, one...
[PUBE, PUBE'S WIFE]
...two, three!
[PUBE]
It's out! We did...!
[PUBE grunting]
[PUBE'S WIFE gasps]
Sweetheart, no!
[PUBE]
Subaru, remember me.
And never let go.
Pube! No!
[SUBARU gasps]
A black Durandal?
At last we meet.
I am also Subaru.
[laughs]