[NARRATOR]
We begin with a reunion.
Ace Pilot Subaru Ichinose
and his beloved Durandal
were together again.
[SUBARU]
Sweet, sweet sanctuary.
I've missed it here.
[gasps]
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A] Supply
vessel Ashigara is now docked.
All crew members will have
20 minutes to visit her,
beginning with the pilots.
She's here.
[NARRATOR] Supply vessels
are scattered throughout
Earth Union-controlled airspace
spreading joy and snacks
to space crews far and wide.
[SUBARU]
Cockpit, you know I love you.
But it is snack time!
[chiming]
[SUBARU] Who's about to eat
a quarter of his paycheck?
This guy!
Hey, new flavor!
[SUBARU]
Gettin' it!
If this place had disco pants,
they'd have everything.
[VULGAR]
There she is!
You really want to
work on a food baby
right before you sortie?
How I choose to pleasure myself
is none of your concern.
And I have excellent
portion control. Ass.
Sure know how to use
your mouth, doncha?
Virgin School's workin'!
[SUBARU grunts]
Whatever.
[VULGAR sighs]
Douche.
[NARRATOR] As Subaru was showing
space enemies who's boss...
[CODY]
Get it together!
You're all over the place today!
[NARRATOR]
He was fighting even harder
not to wet his space suit.
[SUBARU] I have excellent
portion control.
Control, control, control.
[SUBARU grunts]
[CODY]
Subaru, do you copy?!
[SUBARU screams]
Dammit!
I need you guys to hurry
up and die already!
Why can't I be anyone
else but me right now?!
Don't pee, don't pee, don't pee!
What the hell is wrong with me?
What kind of moron loads up
on soda and ice cream
before a freakin' sortie?
No one should ever pay me!
All I do is eat myself
out of a job!
Subaru, listen! I'm trying
to help you out here!
[SUBARU]
Help your face... shut up...
Get it together, bladder.
We need a plan!
I'm halfway between ships.
It's game over whether I
turn back or keep going.
Uh? A bottle!
Will it fit in there?
Wait! I'm a genius!
The bag!
I'll put this around the bottle!
Crap! Why is there a hole in it?
This is all your fault!
Don't look at me
in that tone of box!
[beeping]
[SUBARU gasps]
Not now!
Don't you move.
Hold out for me, Durandal!
I'll just take a quick leak.
[SUBARU gasps]
Aw, man!
She'll see my lil co-pilot!
I have to breathe it out.
I'm about to unleash the beaver.
I mean the dam.
I'll have to surrender.
No, screw that!
This is Subaru Ichinose,
returning to the Supply Vessel!
Durandal, full purge!
I got it!
Okay, here it goes.
No!
[SUBARU]
It's over.
I'm done for.
[NARRATOR]
When he reached the end,
Subaru was at least able to buy
a change of underpants.
[CODY] Hey Soob. I'm gonna need
you to head out and give Leroy,
Vulgar, and their
crew some backup.
You're about to make contact
with the fleet, okay?
Are you listenin' to me?
Do I have the option
of not listening?
Right.
I'll leave you to it.
[SUBARU] When was the last time
I cleaned these crevices?
[NARRATOR] Subaru's obsession
with his cockpit knew no bounds.
He loved every shiny inch of it,
and he took note of even
the smallest details.
[SUBARU]
Is that a pube on my stick?
[SUBARU gasps]
That's gross. Why would--
[PUBE]
Not so fast, Muchacho!
You must first answer
this question.
[SUBARU]
Did that pube just talk to me?!
This is crazy.
I've been holed up in
a cockpit too long.
Or maybe... I have
Universe Spaceman Powers!
[NARRATOR]
He means "The Universe Sense."
It's a rare sixth sense that
some space immigrants possess.
It's not unreasonable
that with his keen senses
and at times disturbing
concentration, he could have it.
[sighs] Look I just say
what they tell me...
[PUBE]
I must know.
Your favorite baseball team.
I'm going to guess
Giants, because, well...
Actually, I kinda
like the Dragons.
[PUBE]
Ay dios mio !
That was my second guess!
You know they changed their
colors from pink to blue, yes?
Everybody was upset.
But I say, so what!
If they are handling
the balls well,
you don't care if they
are pink or blue.
[SUBARU]
That's it. I can't do this.
[PUBE]
Enough about that.
Where are you from?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
[PUBE]
South of the border!
[SUBARU]
Okay, done.
I don't need comedy from a pube.
[PUBE]
Slow down, Hermano!
Not so fast!
Why must you assume I
have fallen from you?
[gasps] You didn't?
[PUBE]
Perhaps, yes, but perhaps no.
What if I was plucked
from a woman?
For real?
[PUBE]
Maybe. There is a sensual,
bouncy senorita on
the ship with you, yes?
You talkin' about
Lieutenant Leroy?
[PUBE] Why don't you come
closer and smell me?
See how your body reacts!
[laughs] No that's okay.
I doubt you would
be hers anyway.
[PUBE]
Why not? I am very sexy! No?
[NARRATOR]
And just like that,
Subaru was sharing laughter,
feelings, and dreams.
He had made a new friend.
Tell me, ever thought about
trying one of those flat irons?
[PUBE]
You cannot tame this stallion.
[PUBE gasps]
Okay, amigo, vamos !
Back to work!
I am sensing heat coming close.
The enemy...
[SUBARU]
Excuse me!
I'm trying to have a chat
with my new friend here!
[PUBE whistles]
Muy bien !
It's no surprise I am from
your strong, bulbous cojones!
Heh. Ah man, you really were
my pube this whole time.
[PUBE laughs] I gave you a
bit of a thrill, though, eh?
[NARRATOR] Subaru's Universe
Sense eventually went away,
and so did the voice
of his pubic hair.
But he still carries it with him
in a special place to remember.
Hey. You got yourself
a souvenir?
Yeah.
It's just a little memento
of someone special.
Hopefully we'll meet
again someday.