[NARRATOR]
Metus Captain Isuzu,
who also happens to
be Subaru's brother,
has infiltrated the Tiramisu
under the guise of a Durandal
operator named "Cody."
His goal is to get
closer to Subaru
and monitor the awakening
of his Universe Sense.
[ISUZU sighs]
Oh, man. I can't believe
they're still fooled!
See that, through the screen
nobody will ever
know the difference.
Just gotta get the lighting
right and you'll be golden.
That Maybach really makes you
feel like you're in good hands.
Grubby, disgusting hands, but...
[beeping]
How's it goin'? Was I right?
All is well. No sign
of intelligent life
in the Earth Union,
if you know what I mean.
Just remember what
we talked about.
Don't let them find you out
or we're all screwed.
[ISUZU]
Yeah, I know.
[SUBARU] Cody, come in!
I've got a problem!
[ISUZU]
Well, showtime.
What is it, Subaru?
Your breathing's increased.
Check my oxygen reserves.
Huh. Looks like they're
over 80% full.
I don't see an issue.
[ISUZU] Crap! I was looking
at my video game!
Wait, scratch that!
What's wrong?
You okay, Soob?
This can't be...
[ISUZU]
Did he really run out of oxygen?
But the level's fine on this
screen too, what gives?
Something with
the Durandal maybe?
It doesn't make sense,
why would he be--
Don't have a diva fit if
communication cuts off.
That happens all the
time in battle zones.
[ISUZU]
Does it though?
'Cause Subaru's bed wetting
kinda sounded like it's rare.
He should read this book.
Need to calm down a pilot who's
about to piss his spacesuit?
No matter how bad things may be
the magic words are
always "no problem."
Hearing that from a person they
trust can make anybody relax.
[ISUZU]
Oh! I said that!
Maybach's advice is so good,
I followed it without
thinking about it.
[ISUZU]
Heh!
[ISUZU] So, today's
Option A is pork skewers.
Ah. Lookin' good, secret sauce.
[ISUZU] Everything else
here is a space tragedy
but Food Staff is killing it.
Just like Earth food.
Did you really just
double-dip?
What? No, who does that?
Well, I thought only Subaru did,
but it looks like you
proved me wrong.
Bunch of animals.
[ISUZU]
Blood is thicker than sauce!
[NARRATOR] Isuzu was oddly
thrilled that someone had
noticed a similarity between
him and his brother.
[SUBARU] Cody!
Something is very wrong here.
[ISUZU]
What's up?
Is his life in danger?
[SUBARU] It looks like someone
went on a decorating spree.
My cockpit has been violated!
Tell me. Was this
Shigeko's doing?
[ISUZU] Who knew he was
so high-maintenance?
Sorry. I don't know
who's responsible.
But right now you need
to get your s--- together
and focus on that launcher.
[SUBARU]
I can't!
Not when someone reorganized
without my permission.
My name is written on my helmet!
[ISUZU] When did you grow up
to be such a pain in the ass?
[ISUZU]
Uh. Subaru, it's time.
How could you do this to me?
The cockpit is my sanctuary!
Shigeko!
[NARRATOR]
In year Space Age 0156 Subaru
was so emotionally distraught
he missed his target.
[ISUZU]
Run. Now! Get outta there!
[NARRATOR]
As Cody,
Isuzu continued to support
Subaru both on and off the job.
Tending to his
brother's many crises
to gradually gain his trust.
[sighs]
[beeping]
Hey, Maybach. Something wrong?
Woo, sorry to catch
you in your jam jams.
We need you to grab a sample
from your brother, "Ebenezer."
Really? You mean you've
gotten that far?
Uh-huh. We've been plannin'
to do a little somethin'
special for you, Captain Suzie.
Came out even better
than we expected!
Aw, you shouldn't have!
You're doin' well,
don't ef it up.
A sample from Subaru, huh?
I know just what to do.
[SHIGERUKO yawns]
[ISUZU gasps]
It's passed your
bedtime, Subaru.
Why're you still up?
Uh, well, I...
I'm glad you asked!
I had to pee!
But, I'm going back to my
precious cockpit right now!
[SHIGERUKO]
What's with the stupid patch?
Ya got the pink eye?
[ISUZU]
Pink eye? Eww!
N-No there's a normal,
non-sketchy reason.
Just dust in my eye!
[SHIGERUKO]
Bless your heart.
I suggest you put
in some eye drops
and stop rubbin' your eyes
after ya make boom boom.
There's some over on the egg
shelf if you need 'em.
[ISUZU sighs]
[ISUZU] Wait, did she just
say they keep the eyedrops
on the egg shelf?
Is that a thing?
[ISUZU]
When I look at him up close
I can see how big he's grown.
Uh?
[ISUZU] Hey! I lost that
toy when I was little!
He had it all this time?
Oh well, at least you
took good care of him.
I'll let you hold
onto him for a while.
--[music plays]
--[gasps]
[ISUZU]
Thought I silenced this thing!
[music continues]
[ISUZU]
Crap!
[SUBARU]
Help! A space ghost got me!
[NARRATOR] Subaru cried
"ghost" to everyone on the ship,
but no one took him seriously.
This caused him to spend
more and more time
confined to his
beloved cockpit.
This sucks, Cody. They all
think I'm an idiot now.
It's okay, Subaru. I believe
your space ghost story.
[NARRATOR] Having caused
Subaru's humiliation,
Isuzu almost felt a tinge
of guilt. But...
[ISUZU] Maybe you shouldn't
have kidnapped Mr. Robot,
dumb jerk-face.