[NARRATOR] After a number
of hellacious battles
in who-knows-where,
with who-knows-what,
the Durandal was finally showing
signs of exhaustion.
As was its pilot,
Subaru Ichinose.
[SHIGERUKO]
Nope. Doesn't look good!
It gets rollin'
and then just stops.
[PAC2-AR] Do you still think
it's the fusion engine?
Damn straight.
It's so unstable
it needs therapy.
There's nothin' more
I can do for it.
[PAC2-AR] Should we plan
a memorial service?
No, not yet.
I need to chat with
the developer first.
Seriously?
[SUBARU]
That would be my dad.
Heh! There!
[ISUZU] Uh! Who said you
could put my sticker there?!
Dad's so gonna murder you.
Dad's busy researching!
He's not even payin'
attention to us.
He won't notice.
[SOICHIRO]
We can't just stand by
waiting for Grand Mars's wisdom.
We need to find a way
to surpass it somehow.
[SUBARU laughs]
[sighs] Huh? What?!
No way!
Subaru, you're the worst!
You wasted one of the most
rarest stickers possible!
I had to get like a million
packs to find this one!
Oh. I'm sorry.
From now on keep
your peter clamps
off my things unless you ask!
How the hell did those two
get up here this time?
Hey! You two better
cool it up there!
You're doing it wrong.
You're supposed to peel
it from the edge first.
[SOICHIRO screaming]
[SUBARU]
See? You got it!
[ISUZU groans]
It's all floppy.
Put it back on the paper.
[SOICHIRO groaning]
What's your deal?
You're always messing stuff up.
It's like you just want
Dad to get mad at me.
If he kills me because of you,
I'll never speak to you again.
[SUBARU grunts]
[screams]
[SOICHIRO screaming]
[BOTH groan]
[RESEARCHER 12A] What happened?!
Are you okay? Talk to me!
[RESEARCHER 12B]
Isuzu! You need some help...
So that's a cockpit? So cool!
[SUBARU] When the Durandal
and I are together,
we can defeat anyone.
No! Wait!
Durandal, please!
Can't we talk about this?!
Wait, where are you going?!
We have to sortie!
Don't leave!
You're the only one
who understands.
Please don't leave,
just hold me.
[grunts] Durandal, no!
What the heck?!
[PAC2-AR] That dark Durandal
knock-off is attacking!
[SUBARU]
Dammit!
Whaddaya think you're doing?
It's not fixed!
So what?! It still kinda
functions, doesn't it?
I guess.
If you're okay with
the engine cutting out
when you're fightin'!
Don't be an idiot. Come with
me, I'll give you the spare.
A spare? Since when?
[SHIGERUKO]
He's seen better days for sure,
but I kept him around for
exactly these kinds of pickles.
[SUBARU]
You gotta be kidding.
They still have one of these?
Nothing about that thing
says, "space boss"!
[NARRATOR] Subaru's space image
was important to him,
and piloting the reserve
robot was a mini tragedy.
[SHIGERUKO]
You're gonna thank me later!
[SUBARU]
We'll see about that.
How 'bout giving me somethin'
that won't shatter
during an attack?
Quit cryin'!
It's reinforced glass like the
kind they use on helicopters!
She cannot be serious,
ugh, helicopter glass...
[gasps]
[SUBARU] Gross! It smells like
sweat, oil, and rotted beans.
Like the dirty whites I
used to chase Isuzu with!
[SUBARU] It's fine, I'll just
try breathing through my mouth.
What the hell is--?
Is that a dream catcher?
[SUBARU screams]
Then the handle's all sticky.
What kind of animal was
piloting this thing?!
I can't do it!
It's freakin' brutal in there!
Could you go to the Durandal
and get me wet wipes,
air freshener, and a candle?
[VULGAR]
I did not just hear that!
The only thing
getting wiped is you!
This is how it's done
in a man's world.
You don't get to
decorate this one
with all your dainty
knickknacks!
[SUBARU] I can do that
and still be a man.
[VULGAR]
I'll fight the copy robot.
You put your big boy pants on
and back me up... in this!
[SUBARU]
All right, fine.
You wanna see a man?
[screams]
[SUBARU] I love the smell
of sweat and rust!
And this pull starter is
giving me life right now!
Because I am a man!
[SUBARU]
Got it!
[music plays]
[SUBARU gasps] There is no
reason for it to be that loud!
Who blasts yacht rock
during a sortie?
Hey, Princess, are you there?
[VULGAR] I'm out here toying
with the robo-roach.
But I'm getting kinda bored.
I'm gonna lead it to you.
[VULGAR] See if you can handle
the D Photon Launcher.
It's one of those things
that should be easy to do
if you're a man.
So if you fail,
we'll know your secret.
I got it.
[SUBARU]
Except, I can't lift anything,
'cause the genius who built
this gave me drills for hands.
But that's fine--
because I'm a hero!
Where the hell is my scope?
Just great!
I got this. I'm a man.
It's easy.
[SUBARU grunting]
So gross!
Why does everything
in here smell like ass?!
Oh! Is that someone's
half eaten fish snack
on top of a crusty leaf?
[SUBARU gasps]
Ya know what?
Screw you, Previous Pilot!
I hate you so much!
[NARRATOR]
Space Age 0157.
As Vulgar was
struggling to escape,
Lieutenant Leroy heard his cries
and she rushed to
the scene to help.