I'm freaking out.
Are you Isuzu or not?
Come with me, Subaru.
I'm here to take you to a world
that is better suited
to your needs.
[gasps]
[ISUZU]
I know firsthand
just how stressful
it is for you here.
But all of that can end today.
The Metus Germen is
an isolated fortress
far away from
suffering and idiocy.
But how far?
[ISUZU]
Does it really matter?
It's not like you have
any family here.
[gasps]
Watch this!
This is my mecha built with
the wisdom of the Fifth Note.
Kurukeion!
Step into my cockpit and
we'll discuss this further.
Let me just grab the ol'
keys and then we can--
Crap! Where the hell
did I put the keys?
[NARRATOR] We interrupt
this suspenseful moment
to look for something important.
[ISUZU]
Hold on.
[SUBARU]
Uh. You need me to help?
[ISUZU]
Mother of Pearl.
If I can't find it,
we're in trouble!
Maybe you should try
to retrace your steps?
[ISUZU]
I just had it!
Where'd it go?
Who does this?
It's a little black guy.
Have you seen it anywhere?
I didn't even know
you were alive,
much less that you might be
losing your things on my ship.
Ugh! There must be some dirty
thieves running around!
I can't believe this is
happening to me!
Ugh! Why does everyone
want in my cockpit?
This is the worst!
[SUBARU]
Well that seems... dramatic.
Okay, take a breath.
Have you tried looking
in all the pockets?
It might've fallen out
when you put the bag--
Oh, please!
You think I don't know
the anatomy of my own bag?
Look here. Some jealous
bitch stole it! Oh.
Could this be the little black
thing we're looking for?
It was at the bottom
of your bag.
Hey. How 'bout that.
See. I knew we'd
find it eventually.
Team work makes the dream work!
Ya know, you've always
been good at scavenging.
Just like a cute
little squirrel.
[SUBARU]
Yep, it's him.
He hasn't changed.
[ISUZU] Are you still feeling
guilty about what happened?
No.
Okay good. 'Cause they're
just unconscious.
The Tiramisu isn't a threat
to me without you on it.
Well, you and that tiny cockpit.
Great. Good to know.
[SUBARU] It's uncomfortably
clean in here.
There is absolutely
zero clutter.
Nice minimalist vibe.
Sleek. Modern.
Uh? What's that yellow thing?
Feels like a cookie tin.
I'd kill for a snickerdoodle.
[ISUZU] ...that's why I'd
check in with you so often.
[SUBARU]
Oh great. Letters?
"Dear Suzie"? What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Isuzu's nickname is... Suzie?!
--[ISUZU] What are you doing?
--Uh. Nothing!
As I was saying, we are
the chosen ones.
You and I will end this war
together as brothers.
That sounds fun, but,
I still haven't--
[ISUZU]
Stop everything right now!
We have a serious problem!
What's going on?
I can't believe this.
Un-freakin'-real.
I left my eye thingy
on the Tiramisu !
[SUBARU]
Not the eye thingy!
Farts! I can't with this day!
That thing was
ridiculously expensive!
Seriously, it's the
fourth one I've lost!
[NARRATOR] It was a reunion he
never thought would happen,
and now, wished it hadn't.
[RESEARCHER 7A] Synchronization
with pilot complete.
Brainwaves normal.
So, what do you think, Subaru?
That new cockpit sure
looks good on you.
I still don't get it.
I feel like this might
be the third time
I've explained this to you.
You're a Chosen One who's
awakened the Universe Sense
and we need to
update your cockpit
so we can unleash
your full potential.
You're going to update it?
That's right. For now,
I want you to put
all of your energy
into experiencing
this new cockpit's power.
We're going to fill it
with a special liquid.
This will link your brainwaves
directly to your craft.
All you have to do is
think and the Durandal
will move exactly
as you envision it.
Wow. That's awesome.
Damn straight! Your world
is about to change.
This cockpit will
become your sanctuary
both in reality
and in your mind!
Cockpit. I miss it so much.
[gasps]
[ISUZU]
Here it comes.
Breathe the liquid in just
like you breathe in air.
It'll relax your lungs and free
them from the demands of oxygen.
Seriously?
Nope! Can't do it!
I'm freakin' out!
We have to stop!
My lungs aren't having it!
Uh!
I need to at least splash some
on my face first or something!
Are you kidding me?!
We've been at this
for an hour now!
Open your mouth and
suck it down! Suck it!
Like a straw in a milkshake!
Like a kid on a lollipop!
Throw your neck back
and swallow it!
[ISUZU growls]
Lieutenant Maybach!
Yeah?
[ISUZU]
Now watch and learn.
Maybach and the rest of my crew
have mastered this technique.
Everyone here has awakened
the Universe Sense like you.
[MAYBACH]
Hey Suba-Whatever your name is.
[gasps]
[MAYBACH laughs] Looks just
like takin' a bath, huh?
He can he talk when
he's underwater?
So you can hear him?
The liquid acts as a
form of transmitter,
but only for those with
the Universe Sense.
[SUBARU]
That's disgusting.
I do not want to get in
the tank after that guy.
Uh. Can we drain it first
and then fill it up again?
[ISUZU]
Why would I do that?
That's wasteful!
Oh. I guess you're right.
[SUBARU]
Disgusting, it's all cloudy
and full of fat guy floaties.
Nope! Can't do it!
What's your problem?
Are you trying to embarrass me
in front of the crew?
Y'know what? You get in here
with all the skin-fold-lint
and let's see how
well you can breathe!
If you can do it, I'll do it!
Me? But how?
I can't.
Why not?
[ISUZU]
Because...
...I'm not like you, okay?
I'm the only one here
who hasn't awakened!
I've never done it before!
Huh?
[ISUZU] I'm just normal!
I don't have nine senses!
Well, we don't exactly know
that to be true, yet.
Captain Suzie is a special case.
That's true.
It may be that Captain Suzie
just hasn't realized it yet.
I think since he's got family
here for emotional support,
it might be a good time for
us to finally test it out!
[ISUZU] C'mon guys!
I haven't awakened yet!
Let's get these clothes off you!
Hey! Cut that out!
Who's got my eye thingy?
[RESEARCHER 7A]
Look at those abs of steel!
[SUBARU] So this is how my
brother is around his friends.
[NARRATOR] Subaru couldn't
quite put into words
what he was feeling
in that moment.
But he knew something
was, well, strange.
[ISUZU]
...my brother is watching!
Wait, maybe he likes to.