[VENTURI]
As you may be aware,
protests against the military
are happening on Earth.
[VENTURI]
The Earth Union Government
has responded with a media-based
public image strategy.
Therefore, starting
sometime today,
a crew from StrifeTime TV will
be filming aboard our ship.
Welcome to Hollywood.
[VENTURI]
Ichinose!
Sir!
For some bizarre reason,
they want to spend their
time following you.
I'm trusting you'll cooperate
and show them around.
With all due respect, sir.
I think we've all got
more important things
we should be doing.
Like going after that
wanna-be black Durandal.
Hey, why don't you
stop being a pansy?
TV Guys are real panty-droppers
for the ladies.
I mean, I'll go.
I don't have time for you today!
Why don't you go drop
your mom's panties?!
[VULGAR]
Hm...
[SUBARU] Gotta go fix
the Durandal now!
[VULGAR]
Why don't you cry about it?
[SUBARU]
Shut up!
I don't have time for
these stupid PR stunts.
Follow me... For what?
They can film the floor
for all I care.
I'll just have to end the war
before they get here.
Huh?
There's our guy right now!
[PRODUCER SUZUKI] Hey! We
were just checkin' out the ship!
Looks great!
I'm Suzuki.
Producer for the show.
[NARRATOR]
Subaru was a fan of reality TV.
[SUBARU]
True Professionals ?!
[PRODUCER SUZUKI]
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Is this real life?!
It's a pleasure to
meet you, more!
[NARRATOR] And had watched every
episode of this particular show.
I think audiences are
going to love you.
You're nowhere near
as flakey as the captain said.
That's comforting!
All right, let's do it!
I'm gonna roll, but don't
look at the camera.
Oh, and I'll be feeding you
questions, but don't look at me.
Just stay focused on
whatever you're doing
and only answer when
you can, okay sport?
Yeah, got it.
[PAC2-AR]
Poor Subaru looks so nervous.
First off. Um...
This must be kinda like driving
an excavator amiright?
Uh, I wouldn't know.
Somehow, I've gone
my entire life
without ever driving
an excavator.
[PAC2-AR] Oh look,
even his nerve sweat stains
--are soaking through.
--[ALARM 11A] Danger. Danger.
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru!
We've received permission
to proceed to the catapult.
[SUBARU] This whole camera thing
is giving me the shakes.
I can't hold the D Photon
Launcher in place!
And now I can't get
into the catapult!
[CREW laughing]
[SUBARU] They don't have
to laugh so loud.
[PRODUCER SUZUKI] ...harder
with a camera in your face?
[SUBARU]
Huh? Well, yeah kinda.
Plus, I love your show so much,
I've seen each episode twice!
Wow. We didn't know
you were a fan.
[SUBARU]
Oh, yeah!
The one about the space wives
and the robot butler!
Amazing!
[CAMERAMAN 11A]
Heh. Remember,
you're not supposed
to look at the camera.
[gasps] Right. I'm sorry.
Hey, man, just be cool.
We wanna see who the
real you is on camera.
Okay. Got it.
[inhales]
--[exhales]
--[beeping]
Huh?
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru, look!
[SUBARU]
Please don't say we missed it!
[PAC2-AR]
It came from out of radar range
and then closed in unexpectedly!
[SUBARU]
I'd really prefer not to fight
with civilians aboard, but...
[PAC2-AR]
This is strange.
It's not approaching us at all.
[SUBARU]
Some kind of stalker-ship?
Creepy.
Well, I can't just leave
it dangling like that.
Hold on tight.
We're about to go into battle
with an unknown craft.
[CAMERAMAN 11A]
Is it gonna shake the camera?
[SUBARU]
Probably!
[gasps] No freakin' way!
Chibi, you're back!
[PAC2-AR] There is nothing
"bitsy" about that dog!
I never thought
I'd see you again!
I've missed you so much!
[PRODUCER SUZUKI] So, is that
your ginormous space dog?
[SUBARU] His name is Chibi,
and he's grown so much
since I last saw him!
Come to Papa!
Chibi!
[ALL screaming]
[SUBARU]
No, bad doggy! It's me!
Stop chewing the Durandal!
That's fine. He'll know me
when he sees my face.
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru, wait!
Good boy.
You recognize me now, don't ya?
You used to be my
fluffy little copilot.
[SUBARU]
Come here!
[PAC2-AR gasps] His sweat!
He recognizes his stench!
[SUBARU groans]
[laughs] What's that?
Your breath...
...still smells like stale
fish and meat paste.
You want me to stop rolling?
No, stay on them for a bit.
I'm actually thinking
of changing my vision
for this episode.
Let's show that even
on a bloody battlefield,
a miraculous reunion can happen.
[SUBARU]
Come on, Chibi!
Let's go for a spacewalk!
[SUBARU laughs]
[SUBARU] Chibi, no!
N-Never mind, it's fine.
Nice. This is art!
[SUBARU]
Are you serious? Ah. Hold on.
Don't worry, I got ya.
Oh, boy, it's a doozey.
That was close.
[PAC2-AR] I wish everyone
was as responsible
with their space dogs.
[gasps] What's that?
[CHIBI growls]
[SUBARU]
Oh, great!
I don't think Chibi's ever
been around other dogs!
[PAC2-AR]
Just stay calm!
[SUBARU]
And he's pulling.
It's okay, Chibi! Stay back!
Stay, damn it!
I said stay!
Damn it Chibi, hold it!
[growls] Stay and hold it!
[NARRATOR]
The damage from Chibi's
earlier nibble was more
severe than expected.
[CHIBI roars]
Chibi! Come back!
[SPACE RETRIEVER roars]
Um. I guess I should
stop rolling?
No, it's cinema veritas .
I actually think this is gonna
send a stronger message.
That even on the bloodiest
of battlefields,
the seeds of new
life can be sown.
And we should make it a
full-length documentary.
[NARRATOR]
Subaru once again faced
the difficulty of loving
and losing a pet.
[COMMENTATOR 11A] Deuce!
And they are back in the game!
Amazing serve by Clark!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
the women's volleyball season
had begun, and
Subaru's episode
of True Professionals
was delayed... indefinitely.
[SUBARU]
U-Uh...
[SUBARU sighs]