[PILOT 3A]
Man, check it out.
Never seen that mecha before.
Is it new?
[PILOT 3B]
That's Lieutenant Leroy's mecha,
the Primavera Delta.
Right. The new hottie pilot
who just got posted here.
Which explains why it looks
like a giant blowup doll.
You guys might wanna
keep your voices down.
[BOTH gasp]
[PILOTS]
Ten-hut!
[PILOT 3A]
Good day, Lieutenant!
[LIGIER]
Subaru Ichinose, is that right?
[SUBARU gasping]
[SUBARU]
That smell.
What could it be?
[gasps]
[LIGIER] Have you received the
update about your Durandal?
If not, I need you to
get ahold of my Papa.
[SUBARU]
Get a hold of her... "tatas"?
[VENTURI]
Thank you, Lieutenant!
I told you I would get in touch
with him on my own time.
And while we're on the Tiramisu,
I am not your Papa,
I'm your Captain!
Yes, Captain! Roger that!
[gasps] She's his daughter?
[VENTURI]
Subaru Ichinose.
[SUBARU]
Sir!
[VENTURI]
This is not up for discussion.
Effective immediately,
Ligier Leroy will
pilot the Durandal.
You will graciously take her
place aboard the Primavera.
[gasping]
Subaru, can you hear me?
It's not that bad, all right.
She's his daughter.
What's he supposed
to do, tell her "no"?
Come on.
You can't just shut
down on me like this.
Listen. I know it's weird.
You've got a lot of miles
with the Durandal
and it's a little like
sawing off your arm...
[beeping]
[CODY]
Subaru! Incoming!
[SUBARU]
Hostiles?
I look like an easy target
because I'm inside
a woman... robot.
Woman Robot.
They don't know it's me.
Or they do and they're attacking
because I'm an embarrassment
to my gender. Or worse.
Uh. They'll think I'm a freak.
A crossdressing,
pink-loving freak!
They'll all laugh at me
when they get home!
And why wouldn't they?!
I'm frilly!
[SUBARU]
No!
I hate it! Make it stop!
I may as well be
working the streets
or on my way to grandmother's
house to deliver cookies.
I can't take this anymore!
I'm a man! I'm a man!
I'm a man!
[SUBARU] How am I even supposed
to fight in this thing?
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
It smells like... shampoo.
Lieutenant Leroy's lady musk.
[SUBARU]
That's right.
I forgot, I'm inside her pink--
Subaru, I need you
to focus here!
[SUBARU]
I'm in... a girl's room.
[NARRATOR]
Poor young Subaru Ichinose.
Barely 19.
He's spent what should
be the best days
of his formative youth
trapped in outer space.
I'm doin' it!
[SUBARU] Time to grab me
some steel tatas!
[NARRATOR] Which is where
his brain remains today.
Shouldn't be too hard
to find him.
Don't do that!
You idiot!
You can't touch those!
[yelling]
Or they will explode.
Too late. Good news is,
he makes dumb look cute.
[NARRATOR] Miraculously,
Subaru returned to base
with only minor burns
[footsteps]
[VULGAR grunts]
Hey.
Whatcha doin' in there,
Powder Puff?
That mech isn't gonna
fly itself, now is it?
Uh, no, mostly because
I don't have one anymore.
Thanks for bringing it up.
Ha, ha. That's right.
You've been in here ball
scratchin' so you don't know.
The Durandal Full Model
Change just came in.
[SUBARU gasps]
Wait, what?
Did you say I have a new mecha?
A cockpit that
only I will handle?
You'd be a fool to ride it
without a good manual first,
wouldn't ya?
[gasping] Ha, ha! Later!
--[SHIGERUKO laughs]
--[VULGAR] What a douche.
[NARRATOR] Subaru's heart
throbbed with excitement
as he nestled into the warmth
of his very own cockpit.
[sighs]
Oh, c'mon they gave
me volume two!
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Durandal launching!
[SUBARU]
This is nuts.
I figured the basics would be
pretty much the same for both.
But the new Durandal's cockpit
is way more complicated!
Forget battling the enemy.
I can't even make it
back to the Tiramisu.
What kind of jerk-off
doesn't know how to handle
his own damn equipment?
[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
Switching to F Flyer Mode.
[SUBARU]
Uh?
How the hell did it transform?
[SUBARU]
That's really nifty and all,
but I still don't know how
to pilot this thing!
Uh? Asteroids?
Now is not the time to crash!
C'mon Durandal Freakin' F!
Help me out here, man! Uh?!
This is this it.
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
It looks like last year's...
[SUBARU] Why would
I need a split screen?
I can't see!
Of course the support
center is closed!
That's it. It's all over.
I can feel time slowing down.
I must not have
survived the crash
and am falling into
death's arms.
[SUBARU]
Weep not.
This is the way
I would've wanted it.
The cockpit will forever
be my sanctuary.
[gasps]
Hey there, Pee Pants!
Couldn't figure out
split screen, huh?
Yeah, neither could I.
Lieutenant Hummer?
It'll go away if you press
the glowing button
for three seconds.
I'll remember that.
[SUBARU]
I'm still alive.
Now back to the sunken
ship of broken dreams.
Freakin' Tiramisu and
all its A-hole crew.
[gasps]
[SUBARU] What?
They're all in Durandal Fs?
Oh.
So it's a mass production model.
Of course.
Why would they ever trust me
with my own personal
mecha again?
[NARRATOR]
And with that,
Subaru clung even more
tightly to his cockpit.