[RESEARCHERS panting]
[RESEARCHER 10A]
Crap! I think we lost him!
[RESEARCHER 10B] Never seen
anyone move like that!
[RESEARCHER 10C] He was
like a space spider monkey!
[ISUZU]
The copy is complete.
And you finished it
in just two hours.
[FODEN]
Impressive, huh?
We didn't think we'd
have enough paint.
[SUBARU B grunts]
Finding enough to keep
you busy out there?
You know, your timing couldn't
be more perfect, Subaru B.
I've got a little
surprise for you.
[ISUZU]
He appears to be stabilized.
This dark craft is
made to compliment
your insanely high
Universe level.
It's Durandal Zwei
and it's all for you.
We call it the Black Demon.
[SUBARU B]
A mecha that's all mine?
[ISUZU]
That's right.
The better to defeat your
copy with, my dear. Uh?!
[SUBARU B]
My own mecha.
To defeat my copy.
[ISUZU]
Whoa. Where are you going?
Just hold the phone!
That one's mine!
Yours is the shiny black
demon thing over there.
[SUBARU B growls]
No! I hate black things!
Uh, 'kay. Let's start over.
Everyone take a deep
breath, for real.
I used to feel the same way,
because you could see dirt
so much easier.
But it turns out,
white actually
gets way filthier.
And so... [yelps]
Uh! Oh, you like my eye thingy?
If you pilot the black demon,
I'll give it to you. Eh?
[SUBARU B laughing]
[ISUZU] You don't wanna
get too far ahead.
Make sure you're
staying close. Uh--!
[ISUZU] He's like a
mutant clone of Subaru.
Highly unstable,
but his Universe values
are much greater.
[SUBARU B laughing]
[ISUZU] All right Brother Soob,
let's settle this, shall we?
[ISUZU]
Kerukeion: Griffin mode!
[ISUZU] Ah! What the hell
is wrong with you?
[SUBARU B laughing]
[ISUZU]
Stop it!
Hey!
Griffin Mode does not mean ride
me like a mechanical bull!
[SUBARU B growling]
[computer pings]
[SUBARU B] There it is!
The white one! I found you!
[SUBARU B]
I want white one!
Is that a black Durandal?
[PAC2-AR]
It's heading right toward us!
Get ready! You'll have to fight!
[SUBARU yells]
[SUBARU]
It's fast!
[ISUZU]
Do you see this?
This happened when you decided
to start a space rodeo!
The jaw line is all jacked now!
C'mon, we're going back!
[SUBARU]
What the...
Why did Isuzu come out here?
[PAC2-AR] I don't want
it to get weird, but,
that black Durandal
is stronger than yours.
Also. I'm pretty sure it's
enhanced with Metus Technology.
Makes sense as to
why it was so fast.
[PAC2-AR]
But these new HMV parts
will let you fight on a
more level playing field!
Load me up! I'm gonna
destroy that black mecha!
Wait and see!
Just clear me for
launch, PAC2-AR!
[PAC2-AR]
Poor Subaru.
He's seems to blame himself
for the loss of his
poor follicle friend.
[SUBARU] At least the Cockpit
will never leave me!
It's because these
sad battles won't end
that we're all still... sad.
But not today.
Today, I end this war!
[PAC2-AR] Rate of speed is
currently 12 G's!
[beeping]
[SUBARU grunts] There's Isuzu
and the freak copy!
[NARRATOR] Out of a sense of
duty, or a sense of rage...
[COP 10A] Slow down and
pull over immediately.
Yes, you, in the
white mobile unit!
[SUBARU]
Is this some kind of speed trap?
[NARRATOR] ...Subaru broke
the law that day.
[SUBARU]
Great, here he comes.
[COP 10A]
Union Space Police.
I need you to roll down
your window, please.
[SUBARU]
Uh. Hi.
What seems to be the problem?
[COP 10A]
Gotta make boom boom?
Goin' pretty fast there.
Caught ya with
the ol' speed gun.
They got cameras now.
Look at that quality.
I'm gonna need to
see your license.
Right...
[SUBARU]
Gross.
My face looks terrible
under G-force.
[COP 10A] Why don't you
just step out of the mecha
and follow me.
Yes, sir.
[COP 10A] Late for a hot date
or somethin', son?
No, sir. I was actually
on my way to stop a war.
Yeah...
Just need your signature
at the bottom
saying you'll pay the fine.
[SUBARU]
Ugh. Eighteen thousand?
Well there go my fun-time funds.
[sighs]
What's that?
Do I smell a little somethin'?
Huh? I would never drink
before a big sortie.
Plus, I'm underage.
[SUBARU] He better not
mean those stupid
saké pickled veggies in
my catered lunch box!
I ate freakin' all of them!
Here. Take this thing and
breathe into the straw.
[SUBARU]
Fine...
[SUBARU] Great, Subaru.
Way to ruin your life!
[SUBARU gasping]
[SUBARU]
It's the enemy!
Hey, sir?
He must be unconscious.
What now? Do I just
use this thing to fight?
[gasps] Perfect!
[SUBARU]
Now I'm the law.
And I'm going to end this war!
[SUBARU] I need something
that'll block the enemy's saber.
Oh! What's that?
[SUBARU]
A people pusher?
No you don't!
[NARRATOR] The people pusher
is used by space authorities
to apprehend someone
from a safe distance.
Usually, by pinning
them against a wall.
However, in space,
there is no wall.
Space Age 0157.
Not only did Subaru have to pay
a hefty fine for speeding,
he also spent almost 40 minutes
searching for a suitable wall.
[SUBARU] Where the hell
is the damn wall?!