[INTERCOM VOICE 1A]
All units have returned to base.
Shifting to battle
readiness level 5.
That was some good work, Subaru.
[SUBARU] I love the warm
embrace of my cockpit.
I'm safe here.
It's my sanctuary.
But...
[VULGAR]
Hey, slugger.
Here we go...
Quit rushin' the enemy
just to show off
the size of your doinker.
[sniffs] Ah, jeez, kid you smell
like balls and failure.
I get that we're all men here,
but hygiene's still important.
Go sniff somebody else!
Just messin' with ya.
Man, I'm gettin' pretty
ripe over here, too.
I'm going to talk
to the captain now!
[SUBARU]
Shut up!
Oh, how I long for the
solitude of my cockpit.
[VENTURI] Absolutely out
of the question, Ensign.
Don't make me discipline you
for violating the regs.
But please, Captain Venturi--
I said no, and that's final.
I will not allow you to keep
a dog aboard the Tiramisu !
[NARRATOR] Having forgotten
that he was in a war zone,
Subaru adopted a stray dog.
[barks]
[VENTURI] You obviously don't
know that when Space Chihuahuas
are exposed to oxygen
they increase in size.
And don't get me started
on their temperament.
They're vicious curs
with huge appetites.
That creature will eat
through everything.
Sir, Chibi is a gentle soul
who wouldn't harm a fly!
That's enough!
Ace pilot or not, you dare
pull one more stunt like this
and I'll have you up
for a court-martial!
Now put that space dog
back where you found it,
understand me?
Yes. Roger that.
[SUBARU]
Dammit!
I ought to court-martial him !
I hate everything about
life on this stupid ship.
Sweet boy. You don't want
to be stuck here, either.
You need someplace comfort--
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Of course! My cockpit!
That's the answer!
[laughs] Come on, Chibi.
Let's get back to the hangar.
[SUBARU] I will always have--no,
we will always have, my cockpit!
Here we go, boy.
The Durandal will be
your home from now on.
[barks]
[SUBARU grunts]
I gotcha. Don't worry.
It's nice and
air-conditioned inside.
Here, I brought you
one of the yummy rolls
that we had at... lunch.
[SUBARU]
This won't work.
There's no place left
for me to sit.
[SUBARU groans]
How'd you grow so fast?!
Dammit, the captain
was right about him.
Hey, Subaru.
What's going on in there?
I can't see you on the monitor.
What happened?
Be advised: the Durandal's
making an emergency sortie.
[CODY]
Subaru! Answer me!
[SUBARU]
I'm sorry.
[NARRATOR]
With a heavy heart,
Subaru ultimately decided to
follow the captain's orders
and put Chibi back
where he found him.
Don't look at me
like that, Chibi.
I had no choice.
[CHIBI whimpers]
[SUBARU whimpers]
[HANGAR DECK CM 2A]
Look out! Comin' in!
[SUBARU] I didn't realize
he would get that big.
If only I'd known.
[NARRATOR] Sad over losing
his precious "Chibi,"
Subaru endured a lecture
from the mechanic
who installed the
D Photon Launcher,
a new weapon for
his next mission.
You kids are always comin'
home with critters, arent'cha?
I used to find roly-polies
in my little one's pockets
all the time. Drove me nuts.
Bugs, huh?
That's different, though.
Stop right there!
How many times do I
have to tell you?
Don't touch the button on top!
Right, sorry, ma'am.
[NARRATOR]
Her title may be "mechanic,"
but should be "muther."
The Launcher's designed
for long-distance
precision shooting,
so you have to make sure to
set your coordinates before
you fire. Now, give it another
try while I watch, okay?
Of course, ma'am.
Poor baby, you look
so nervous.
Well, the photon beam won't
go off yet, don't you worry.
I haven't hooked
the photon cable
up to the robot yet,
so you're fine.
Now be a man and give it
a nice, firm squeeze, m'kay?
Don't want the enemy
to get the drop on you.
Imagine how sad your poor
mama would be if you died.
I got a kid about your age
back on Earth, you know.
Sorry, your name is
Honda Shigeruko, right?
Call me Shigeko.
Shigeko, I'm afraid my
mother is no longer with us.
Huh?
[SUBARU]
They tell me that it happened
during the Second Earth Attack.
It was a long time ago.
I was too little to remember.
Oh, you poor boy.
How terrible for you.
[SUBARU]
I'm sorry. I should go.
[SHIGERUKO]
Hey, where're you off to?!
[SUBARU] I'll do my best
tomorrow, okay?
[SHIGERUKO]
Wait! You forgot something!
[CODY]
Okay, Subaru, listen up.
You'll only have
one chance at this.
They're building
a field base here.
Take out the control tower,
as soon as you do that,
Vulgar's team will attack.
Get it right.
You're the only one who--
Subaru. Are you listening?
Hey, Subaru!
Failure is not an option.
[SUBARU]
Cody!
Something is very wrong here.
What's up?
[SUBARU] It looks like someone
went on a decorating spree.
My cockpit has been violated!
Tell me.
Was this Shigeko's doing?
Sorry. I don't know
who's responsible.
But right now you need
to get your s--- together
and focus on that launcher.
[SUBARU]
I can't!
Not when someone reorganized
without my permission.
My name is written on my helmet!
Oh, no. She didn't!
[gasps] She did!
She reordered my
hidden DVDs by genre!
I will kill her!
No need to thank me, dear.
[CODY]
Subaru, it's time.
How could you do this to me?
The cockpit is my sanctuary!
Shigeko!
[NARRATOR]
In year Space Age 0156,
Subaru was so
emotionally distraught
he missed his target.
No! How could I?
[CODY] Subaru, retreat!
Get out of there!
[SUBARU]
I missed.
Damn that woman!
[NARRATOR] He returned to the
ship, but it was a long time
before he was willing to
speak to Shigeko again.
[SHIGERUKO]
No need to thank me, dear.
[SUBARU]
C'mon!
[bang]