September 21, 1945...
That was the night I died.
Disgusting!
[Man 1] Hey, watch it!
[Man 2] Sorry.
[Girl 1] Is he dead?
[Girl 2] The Americans will
be arriving any day now.
[Woman 1] These bums
are a disgrace.
[Child 1] Mama!
Tell me what day is it?
Setsuko...
Another one.
What is this stuff?
Oh what does it matter?
Just dump it!
[Worker 1] This one's
a goner too.
You can see it in their eyes.
[can rattling]
[sirens wailing]
Air raid! Get to the
shelters! Quickly!
[Officer] We're in for the
big one this time!
The shelter behind the
firehouse should be safest!
It's hot!
Be a good girl; try to
be patient.
Well I guess, I had better get
over to the shelter.
So be careful Seita, and get
over there as soon as you can.
Setsuko, be a good girl and
listen to your brother.
Mom, never mind us!
Get to the shelter!
Yes, yes.
[Seita] Mom, do you have your
medicine with you?
I have it right here,
don't worry.
[Setsuko] I hate the shelter!
Well, you'll be sorry if you
get blown up by a bomb!
Now, get on.
[Setsuko] My doll! My doll!
[Officer ringing warning bell]
[Officer] Air raid!
Seita!
[war planes approaching]
[incendiary bombs being dropped]
[Setsuko] Get down!
[Both] Aah!
[Setsuko] Seita! Seita!
Seita!
[Man 1] Hurry! Lets go,
lets go, lets go!
Clear the way people!
Get out of my way!
Move the damn cary, will you?
Oh God!
[Woman 3] Help me!
[Man 5] Take whatever
you can carry!
[Man 6] Hurry! Bring all
[baby crying]
Long live the Emperor!
We're safe here,
don't worry. Okay?
Where's Mama? I want Mama.
Why she's in the shelter.
The firehouse shelter can take a
hit from a 250‐kilo bomb, easy.
Don't worry about her.
She'll probably go to Niponmatsu
Station to find us.
When things calm down we'll
meet her there.
Let's just rest a bit.
[Seita] Are you okay, Setsuko?
I lost one of my shoes.
Don't worry, I'll buy you
better ones.
I have some money.
Open this.
Wow, Setsuko you're rich.
It's black rain, from all
of the bombing.
[explosion in the distance]
[Seita] Look, it's all gone.
That was the civic hall.
We ate lunch there once.
Seita, is our house gone too?
Probably.
What'll we do?
Dad will make them pay for this!
[Daughter] Mother, mother!
[sobbing]
Well, it's not like I was the
only one who lost his house.
We're all in the same boat.
[Man 2] Well at least we're
still alive.
There were two direct hits.
The fire's impossible to
put out!
You try to smother them,
it just spreads the oil around.
It's not her. She's not
down here!
Seita, I have to pee.
Okay.
[Officer] Attention all
residents of Ichirizuka
and Kaminishi!
Please report to the elementary
school for first aid services!
What's wrong?
[Setsuko] My eye hurts.
Don't rub it.
We'll get it washed out
at the school.
Where's Mama?
She'll be there.
At school?
Yes, let's go.
Oh, Seita! Come with me.
Have you seen your mother yet?
She's been injured. Go to her.
I'll watch your sister.
My goodness, wasn't that
scary, Setsuko?
Seita has to go somewhere.
We'll wait for him together.
Ah Seita, I'm glad you're here.
Are you okay?
[Seita] My mom?
[Obayashi] This way.
Oh...
This is your mother's,
isn't it?
In here.
She's finally fallen asleep.
Your mother really should
be in a proper hospital.
We can't do much here.
[Obayashi] I don't think
they hit Kaisei hospital
in Nishinomiya.
My mother, my mother has
heart trouble. Can she get
her medicine?
I'll find out.
I'll be around, son.
Mom are you‐?
You saw her?
[Seita] Yes.
I am so sorry.
I'm thirsty.
[Neighbor] If there's anything
I can do, just ask.
Did you get your ration?
Let me. I'll get it for you.
Keep this ring safe
in your purse.
Don't lose it. Okay?
Mom's been hurt, Setsuko.
But‐ But she'll get better soon.
Where is Mama?
In the hospital, in Nishinomiya.
[Seita] We'll stay here at the
school tonight.
Then tomorrow, we'll go stay
at our aunt's house near
the hospital.
Okay? Setsuko?
Understand?
We're all staying on the
second floor. Why don't
you stop by later?
Thank you for all your
kindness, we will.
See you later, then.
Bye now.
Want some?
I want to see Mama.
Maybe tomorrow,
it's too late now.
[Setsuko crying]
[Seita] Setsuko, watch me,
I'm good at this!
[Obayashi] I haven't unbandaged
her. Believe me you don't want
to see the body.
With this heat we're having,
she'll have to go on the
truck today.
[Obayashi] Where's your sister?
[Seita] In Nishinomiya,
we have a distant aunt there.
[Seita] I think she'll take
care of us.
[Obayashi] I see, lucky for you.
I'd better get back to work.
Good luck to you.
Mama!
Where's Mama?
What's the matter?
Is she still sick?
Yeah, yeah she's still sick.
Welcome back.
How is your mother?
Is she at Kaisei?
Yeah.
[Aunt] Lucky your dad's
in the Navy.
You get to have a truck help
move you over here!
I've laid out futons and
mosquito netting in your room.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
Doesn't Mama need her ring?
Did she give it to me
to keep for her?
Just be careful you don't
lose it.
Setsuko...
When Mom's a little better,
I'll take you to see her.
Time for bed, okay?
Dried bonito, herring, some
dried potato, pickled plums.
And I do believe this
is butter!
All of these things are so hard
to come by nowadays.
It's soldier's families who
always get the best.
Anyway, did you stop by the
hospital today?
I'd like to tell your mother
all the things that have
been happening.
And I could take Setsuko
along to visit her.
How bad?
My mom passed away while
she was still at the school.
[Aunt] What?! She's dead?
Then why didn't you tell me?
Why were you hiding it?
Answer me child.
I didn't want Setsuko to know.
So she's dead.
How awful. Well you'd best write
your father and tell him!
[Setsuko giggling]
Hey Seita!
Look! She brought me new shoes!
Good for you, Setsuko.
[Cousin] Hello there!
[Seita] Watch this.
[Aunt] Don't be too long.
[bullfrogs ribbiting]
What's making that noise?
Huh? Bullfrogs, it's nothing
to be scared of.
A firefly!
Ready? Come on, catch it.
Ah, you squashed it!
Ew! It smells!
Don't squeeze so hard next time.
[Setsuko] Wow!
[Seita] Whoa. There are
millions of them!
Hey Setsuko, close your eyes
and say "ah."
Why should I?
Come on, just do it, "ah."
Aah.
Fruit drop! Mmm!
♪Orange and cherry and
lemon and lime♪
♪I'm eating my candy and
taking my time and‐♪
That was close. I almost
swallowed it.
[door opens]
[Seita] We're home.
[Aunt] Where were you two?
[Aunt] Did you thank the lady?
[Seita] Yes, ma'am.
That food looked good.
Seita, why aren't you up?
Shouldn't you be going to
school? Or something?
Yeah, but the steelworks they
had me working in was bombed
the other day.
And my school burned down.
There's no place to go.
Well, I hope you've written
to your father.
I did that. I sent it through
the Naval Office.
When?
Just after we came here.
It was um...
I guess it was about ten
days ago.
That seems strange.
There should have been
a reply by now.
Return the scissors when you've
finished with them, Setsuko.
Any news on the war?
It's begining to look hopeless.
It seems that the more factories
we lose, the harder the others
have to work.
The war effort is eating up
all of our supplies.
You're right. That's why food's
getting so hard to find.
Our soldiers aren't the only
ones who are suffering.
You work for our country's
defense too, young lady.
Eat up and work as hard
as you can!
[Air raid siren]
Not again.
So, you've taken in a couple
of homeless children?
Poor things, losing their
mother when they're so young.
What's wrong? You got an itch?
It's hot. I hate shelters!
Just hang on. We'll be out
of here soon enough.
Hey, you want to go
to the beach?
[Setsuko] Uh huh! Yeah!
Yeah! Let's go! Let's go!
Wow! It's all vegetable
fields now.
What are they doing?
They're making sea salt.
Because all the salt
and soy sauce is rationed.
Alright, hurry up, Setsuko!
Might be a little cold.
[Setsuko] Oh! It is cold!
It feels good, right?
You won't itch now.
Hey!
It's a big bath!
[roars playfully]
[Setsuko laughs]
[Setsuko laughs and screams]
[Seita] I'm gonna get you!
Ah here I come!
♪Snippy, snippy, snippy crab♪
♪Snippy, snippy,
snippy, snip...♪
What's wrong? Is he sleeping?
[Seita] Don't look at that.
When it gets a little warmer,
I'll teach you how to swim.
Let's swim, then we can eat.
[Satsuko] We'll swim, and that
will make us hungry.
[Mother] Seita!
Setsuko!
You're hungry, aren't you?
There's food here for you here.
Come on now. Time to eat.
[air raid sirens]
[Young woman] Mother!
How are you?
Are you all right, my daughter?
I'm fine, really! They're
very nice here.
[Setsuko] I'm hungry.
[Seita] Let's get home before
we're caught in the next
air raid.
I'm tired, please carry me.
[bombers approaching]
[Officer] Air raid!
I'm afraid these are no use.
Your mother won't be needing
kimonos anymore.
Why don't you trade
them for rice?
I've been trading off my
things little by little for
food we need.
[Aunt] You can probably get a
full toh of rice for them.
That much?
You need your nourishment,
you know.
I mean, how can you be a soldier
if you don't grow up healthy?
A whole toh of rice?
Your mother would be glad that
you didn't let them just go
to waste.
Why don't I take them for you?
[Setsuko] No!
[Aunt] Have you been awake
this whole time?
They're Mama's! No!
They're Mama's!
Don't take them!
No! No! No!
[Seita] Setsuko, let them go.
[Setsuko] [crying] No!
[Seita] Setsuko... Setsuko! No.
[Setsuko] No! No! NO!
NOOO! Nooo! Nooo!
[Setsuko crying]
[Setsuko] Mama!
[Setsuko] [crying] Nooooo!
Noo! No!
Such fine rice.
Yes it is.
We'll have a proper rice
dinner tonight, Setsuko.
Here, this is your share.
White rice, Setsuko!
[Setsuko starts crying]
[Aunt] Here you go.
With my daughter and our lodger
working so hard.
I've felt just terrible about
not having rice to give them.
It's great, huh?
Real white rice!
More please!
Sure.
You're just gobbling it down
tonight, aren't you, Setsuko?
Mhm! It's very good!
What's wrong?
I don't want rice porridge.
I don't suppose we have any
more of those pickled plums?
Oh we finished those
off ages ago.
[Aunt] Here's your lunch.
Thanks, I'd better be going.
[Cousin] Bye Mom.
[Aunt] Take care.
[Seita] We'll have rice
balls for lunch.
Just hold on until then.
You stop that! You'll have
porridge for lunch too!
You think a lazy slug like
you deserves
the same as people who are
working so hard for our nation?
Really Seita, you're certainly
old enough to know now that
everyone has got to cooperate.
You keep saying you want rice,
but do you do anything to earn
this rice you want?
No, you don't.
I even give you some rice,
and you still complain!
But it's our rice in the
first place.
Oh, so now I'm cheating
you, am I?
How dare you say that?! After I
take you two into my home!
Fine! Here's a new rule.
From now on we'll make
our OWN dinners.
How do you like that?
Tell me Seita, you have other
relatives in Tokyo, don't you?
Some people on your mother's
side of the family?
Why not write to them?
WE could be bombed any day!
I don't know where to find them.
[Little girl] Let's go
home, mommy.
Uh‐huh, Daddy's waiting for us.
[Mother and little girl] ♪Frogs
are singing, it's time to
go home♪
[both giggle]
[Mother] Come on.
Sorry you had to wait so long.
What's wrong?
I'm really hungry,
and thirsty too.
Okay.
Here. It's a fruit drop.
[Seita] Mom has 7,000 yen
in the bank.
7,000... That's more than enough
for us to live on, so don't you
worry. Okay?
I'm telling Dad to write back
soon, because Setsuko
is waiting.
Now write your name.
[Clerk] You're in luck.
You can't buy a stove like
this easily nowadays.
You know what I mean?
It's almost impossible to find
any hardware to sell.
And of this quality.
I'll take that comb, and...
Do you have an umbrella?
An umbrella... Oh, yes!
[Seita] ♪ It's raining, cats
and dogs♪
[Seit & Setsuko] ♪It's raining,
cats and dogs.♪
♪But I have a rain coat and my
big red rubber clogs♪
♪Drip‐drop, plip‐plop, down
comes the rain!♪
♪It's raining, cats and dogs.
It's raining, cats and dogs.♪
And that should do it.
Be careful with that fire.
Right.
[Lodger] And what are
they up to?
[Aunt] They're doing their
own cooking.
[Lodger] Well good for them!
It's about time. More, please.
[Cousin] Mom, did you ever
scold them again?
Yes, and they refuse
to apologize.
And that boy even bought
a stove. Just to spite me!
Finished!
You can't do that.
That's bad manners.
We can sit any way we want to.
Doesn't matter.
There, rice for two.
[Seita] That's it?
[Clerk] Yup.
Next ration will be in July.
[Setsuko throwing
a fit and crying]
Let me.
[candy hits the can]
Let me!
Ready?
Here.
Do you like it?
It's all different tastes!
Grape, strawberry, mint
melon, all the flaveors are
in there.
Now you drink it all up. Okay?
It's all gone.
[Aunt] Great, they left the
dishes for me to do.
So selfish. Honestly!
Those little brats are two of
the worst children in the world.
[Satsuko starts crying.]
Not again!
Seita please, that man and my
daughter work hard for our
nation all day long!
We can't have her crying
keeping them awake.
We've enough trouble getting
any sleep with all of these
air raids!
[Setsuko whining]
[Seita humming to Setsuko]
[Air raid siren goes off]
[Air raid warden] Attention!
Atterntion! Report from Central
Military Division.
Several waves of enemy bombers
are approaching.
[Aunt] Going to the shelter
again, Seita?
You are old enough to help fight
the fires, aren't you?
[Sirens countine wailing]
[Setsuko] I want to go home.
I hate living with her!
We don't have a house
to go back to.
[Seita] ♪With a great big
streamer shaped like a carp
in the wind...♪ Go!
[Both] ♪With a great big
streamer shaped like a
carp in the wind...♪
♪The big one's papa♪
♪And the little ones the kids♪
[Aunt] Stop it!
Don't you realize that there
is a war going on?!
You two are nothing but
trouble for me!
A couple of pests,
that's what you are!
You're no help during the raids.
Take, take, take!
You could go live in that
shelter for all I care!
That's it.
We can live here.
No one seems to be using it;
it seems sturdy enough.
And we can live just like
we want to!
Can we live here really?!
[both laughing]
We've bothered you long enough.
We should be leaving now.
You're leaving? For where?
Haven't really decided yet.
Oh. Well then you two, bye‐bye.
Take care of yourselves.
[Setsuko giggling]
And this will be the kitchen!
And this will be the front door!
But where's the bathroom, Seita?
That can be anywhere.
You wanna go somewhere with me?
Thanks a lot! Where do you
want the wagon?
Just leave it right there.
Do you think, you can sell
my sister and I a little bit
of food
and maybe a bale of straw?
I guess so, there's not much
left though.
It smells so good!
Let's eat!
Well I guess, we can always
eat frogs if we have to.
[Setsuko] Frogs?
[Seita] Yeah, they taste great.
[Seita] You'd better get under
the mosquito net now.
What's wrong?
I forgot my toothbrush.
[Seita] One night without
it won't matter.
It's getting pretty buggy out
here. You'd better go get
under the net.
It's dark in there. I'm scared.
I have to pee, Setsuko.
How about you?
Look a kamikaze.
Looks like a firefly.
[Seita] Yeah...
Hey, let's catch some.
[Seita] [quietly] Okay, get in.
[Seita] Ready?
I can see you!
[Seita] I can see you too.
Oh, a hair clip!
Hey! Let's get as many
as we can!
Did I ever tell you, I went to a
naval review one time, just
before you were born.
[Setsuko] Naval review?
Yeah, Dad's naval cruiser, was
named the "Maya,"
it was in formation with the
fleet in the harbor.
[crowd cheering]
[Naval band playing]
♪Mighty fortresses floating
on the seas♪
♪Defending our homeland from
invaders near and far♪
Enemy plane! [immiates gun fire]
[immiates gun fire]
I wonder where Dad is fighting
right about now?
[Setsuko] Get off me, Seita!
Whatcha doing?
[Setsuko] Making a grave.
Mama's in a grave too.
Auntie told me about it.
She said that Mama died, and
that she's in a grave now.
We'll go and visit her
grave sometime.
Do you remember the
graveyard, Setsuko?
That really pretty one
out near Nunobiki?
That's where she is now, resting
peacefully under a big
camphor tree.
Why do fireflies have
to die so soon?
[kids laughing]
[Boy 1] Wow. Looks like
somebody's living here.
[Boy 2] They probably
lost their house.
[Boy 3] Maybe it's some
crazy hermit.
[Boy 2] It's a swing.
[Boy 3] Hey a kid lives here.
What's this?
Rest in Peace! Rest in Peace!
Aw I wish it was real food.
[Boy 4] It says "Setsuko."
Who's Setsuko?
Look guys! Dried out frog guts!
Who'd wanna eat that?
Nobody I know would ever
eat this stuff!
Ground soybeans? Yegh!
And I thought the food I got
was bad!
A ghost, a ghost! Aah!
Hey! Wait up!
[Seita] I've traded everything
for rice, even my mom's kimono.
There's nothing left to trade.
Please, I can pay you good
money for the rice.
Sorry, I can't trade or sell
anything to you.
I'm a farmer, but I'm afraid
even I don't have any rice
to share.
Don't you have any other
relatives to help you?
I don't know how to contact
any of them.
Then take my advice and just
go back to the woman in
the village.
Look, everything's rationed now.
You can't survive outside
of the system.
Just swallow your pride
and apologize to her.
Thanks, anyway. I'll just go
and ask someone else.
[Farmer] You're the son of
a navy man, aren't you?
So try to be brave.
[Man] Look out!
Is it good?
Oh no!
[Seita] It doesn't matter if you
like it or not.
You have to eat!
You need to, so you can
grow up strong!
[Setsuko] Seita...
I feel... My insides feel
really funny.
Are you cold?
I've been having diarrhea.
[Farmer] Hey you!
[Seita] Hey sorry!
Sorry! I didn't mean to.
Forgive me!
My sister's sick, I just wanted
to get her some sugar!
I'm sorry!
Yeah, sure! Stealing food's
a serious crime in wartime!
You god damned!
Come back here!
What the hell?! Potatoes too?!
So, YOU'RE the one who's been
stealing my crops!
[Seita] I'm sorry!
[Setsuko] Seita?
I'll never do it again, I swear!
I promise you'll never see
me again!
Tell it to the cops! I'll take
you there myself!
[Farmer] Now walk!
[Seita] Please.
[Farmer] I hope they lock you up
for the rest of the war!
[Seita] Please, she's sick! She
needs me.
[Setsuko] Seita. Seita!
No. Ah... Ah!
[Farmer] MOVE!
[Setsuko] Seita...
Seita!
Seita...Seita...
Based on what you both
told me, the nature of the
crime is very clear.
So I thank you for the
information sir,
and I'll take care of this.
You may go now.
But, officer!
You've knocked this poor
kid around enough.
I'm even tempted to call it...
Assault!
I... w‐ but‐... Thank you, sir!
I suppose you heard about
the latest attack.
Would you like a glass of
water or something, son?
Setsuko...
Seita!
Seita?
Should I get a doctor for you,
Seita? What parts hurts?
can help you.
Setsuko!
I have to go to the bathroom.
Can it wait a little bit?
Hop on.
♪Brother's gone to the mountain
to bring back some firewood...♪
Hurry come on!
[Seita] Setsuko, dinner.
This pumpkin is great.
Tastes like sweet bean jelly.
[Setsuko] But I don't
like that stuff.
Look, if you don't eat,
Dad will blame ME for it.
Come on, ready? I'll even help
you. Okay?
Now come on cheer up and eat!
Once you're better, I'll take
you to the beach again, Setsuko.
I promise.
[air raid siren goes off]
Yeah! Yeah!
Now I'll really get you
something good to eat, Setsuko!
Seita?
Seita...
So you're telling me, these were
your mother's? Oh please.
Trying to pawn your garbage
off on me? Get out of here!
Setsuko!
Setsuko?
Seita... Water...
Yeah.
[Doctor] Breathe in.
And out.
[Seita] She's been having
diarrhea for a while now.
Prickly heat, and rashes all
over her body.
And her skin seems very sensitve
to any salt water.
Weakening from malnutrition,
it's typical. Probably due
to diarrhea.
Next paitent!
Can't you give her medicine?
Or a shot?
[Setsuko] Don't wanna shot.
Please, doctor, you have to help
her! Medicine, please!
Give her some medicine? All this
child needs is some food.
A good meal.
She needs food...
[Doctor] How can I help you?
[Paitent] I‐ I...
[Seita] Where am I suppose
to get food?!
I am so hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Tempura, sashimi, jelly...
Anything else?
Ice cream, and also...
I want fruit drops.
Fruit drops? Okay!
I'll withdraw all the money and
buy you all the food you need.
[Setsuko] I don't want anything.
You can have it.
Don't go! Stay with me!
Don't leave me alone!
I don't want you to
worry, Setsuko.
I'm going to go buy you some
good, nourishing food, okay?
And I will never, I'll never
ever leave you again.
Never, ever.
I promise.
[Bank clerk] 3000 yen.
There's a typhoon coming?
Well that's just typical,
isn't it?
we get our "divine wind" AFTER
we surrender. Figures...
Surrender? Are you saying
we lost the war?!
So you haven't heard
young man?
[Seita] You're telling me
Japan's lost the war?
The Great Japanese Empire?!
Yeah, surrendered
unconditionally.
But what about the fleet?
Are they...
All gone. The whole fleet's been
sent to the bottom of the sea,
not one left afloat.
What?! Was my Dad's ship
sunk too?!
Do you know? Please tell me.
Is that why he hasn't written
me back?!
How the hell should I know?
Crazy kid.
Damn him!
God damn him.
I'm so hungry.
Daddy...
Now Dad's gone too.
He's dead too.
[plane flying overhead]
Dad...
I'm sorry that I'm so late,
Setsuko. I'll go ahead and
start making up some rice.
♪Up they go.♪
♪And down again.♪
Oh, the firefly's stopped.
I bought us some chicken
and I got a few eggs.
And I also have...
Setsuko, what's in your mouth?!
This is a marble.
It isn't a drop!
I brought you something really
special. I know that you're
going to like it.
[Setsuko] Seita, have one.
One what, Setsuko?
Rice ball.
I made them for you.
Here. Here have‐ have one.
You don't want them?
[Seita] Setsuko!
Look here, watermelon.
And I didn't steal it.
Here, eat it.
It's good...
Hold on to this and I'll go make
us some rice gruel with eggs.
I'll leave the melon right
here for you.
Okay?
Seita...
Thank you.
[Seita] She never woke up.
There you go, charcoal for
the cremation.
Now since it's a little child,
you really should do it
at a temple.
About the body, it should be
lightly dressed and use
beanstalks for a good fire.
In spite of it all,
it's a lovely day.
[girls laughing]
[Girl 1] It's good to
be home!
[Girl 2] It hasn't changed
a bit!
[Girl 1] The old phonograph!
[Girl 2] I've missed this view.
[Setsuko] Come back soon!
[Seita] The next morning, I put
some of Setsuko's ashes into
the candy tin, and then
climbed down the hill.
I never went back to
the shelter.
[Setsuko] Seita!
Time for bed, okay?