[FEMALE VOICE]
Shock!
[GINKO screaming]
Ginko!
[laughing]
One bear successfully
eliminated by our trap!
We known what you two really
are, and this is what you get!
[LULU gasps]
[GINKO] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also, we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you,
so we had to cross the wall.
I had to have you all to myself.
Tomorrow's the day.
Oh, Sumika. What was it
you wanted to tell me?
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[sighs] This letter is hard.
I barely even know what to say.
[SUMIKA] I guess, I can
start at the beginning.
The moment I first met Kureha.
I'll never forget that day.
Oh, no. It's gone.
I can't find it.
Grandma gave me that hairpin
especially for today.
I can't believe I lost it.
[KUREHA]
Are you looking for this?
Uh.
[KUREHA]
Here.
[SUMIKA gasps]
It's yours, right?
Yes, thank you.
[SUMIKA] I know you probably
don't remember that, but I do,
and it meant the world to me.
I was so happy you were there,
so happy to have met you.
[SUMIKA]
And then, there was that storm,
and I wanted to protect
what you cared about.
[gasps]
You came out, too.
[SUMIKA]
We got soaked, remember?
Sure, it was scary, but we ended
up having such a good time.
I started feeling
so close to you.
Like it was just you and me.
The only two people
in the whole world.
It was heaven.
I remember everything about
that day, but more importantly,
I will always remember it,
even when I'm old and gray.
[SUMIKA] "The Moon Girl
and the Forest Girl."
Your mother wrote this?
Yep, it was actually
her last book.
Since it was never published,
it's the only copy.
It's so good.
Mind if I read it?
Not at all.
[SUMIKA]
"Once upon a time,
the worlds were divided
into two parts by the sky.
There was the moon world,
and the forest world.
One day, a moon girl
accidentally dropped
her mother's precious pendant.
It fell far down
into the forest.
A forest girl stumbled
upon the pendant
while she was out walking.
Surprised by its sparkling star,
she found herself
looking up at the sky
to see where it came from.
She started to think
what she could see
might not be all
there was, and said,
'There must be an amazing
world beyond that sky.'
Meanwhile, the moon girl
couldn't stop wondering
about the forest world, and
what happened to the pendant.
'Where is Mother's pendant?'
she said. 'I have to go find it.
There must be an amazing world
beyond that sky.'
Day after day, the moon girl
and the forest girl
looked at the sky, each one
gazing from their own world.
At long last, they decided
to appeal to Lady Kumaria,
for she was the
Goddess of the Sky.
The moon girl prayed,
'Please help me, Lady Kumaria.
I want to go beyond the sky,
so I can find
my mother's lost pendant.'
The forest girl prayed,
'Please help me, Lady Kumaria.
I want to go beyond the sky,
so I can deliver this lost star
to the one who dropped it.'
'I am sorry, but you
may not,' said Kumaria,
'For the two worlds
have been severed forever.
Wanting to cross that
severance is pride,
and pride, as you know,
is a grave sin.'
And yet, they prayed again.
'Please help us, we still want
to go beyond the sky.'
Reluctantly,
Kumaria answered them.
'There is one way
to make your wish come true.
In the center of the sky
is a place called
the Door to Friendship.
If your love is true, your
friend will be waiting for you.
You'll find her on the
other side of that door.
When you see her,
give her a Promise Kiss.
Do that, and your wish
shall come true.'
Kumaria asked the
two girls a question.
'Is your love the real thing?'
Then, she laid down
a ladder for them,
connecting the two worlds
together once more.
They climbed the ladder
until finally arriving
at the center of the sky.
There they found a single,
vast mirror standing
like a wall in their path.
Each girl saw her own
reflection in the mirror.
They heard Kumaria's voice say,
'Now, your friend is waiting
just on the other side
of that very door.
If you smash the 'you'
in the mirror to bits,
if you tear yourself apart, she
shall grant you a Promise Kiss.
But beware, this may
cost you your life.
I will ask you one more time.
Is your love the real thing?'
The girls stared at themselves
in the mirror for
a very long time."
Is that the end?
No, the story
doesn't have an ending.
A bear killed Mom. She never
got the chance to finish it.
How sad.
So, what would you do
if it was about you?
[SUMIKA]
Uh?
Y'know, that part in the story?
Would you risk your life
in order to break the mirror?
I'm not really sure.
Lemme think.
[KUREHA]
I would break it.
[SUMIKA]
Wha?
I'd shoot my reflection.
I'd shoot because
I would do anything
to prove my love was true.
[SUMIKA]
In that moment,
I decided I wouldn't
back down on love, either.
No matter what happened...
...I would do anything
to prove my love, too.
Now, ladies, it's time to decide
on the next evil to exclude.
Let's search evil!
[KATYUSHA]
Uh.
Oh, ladies.
I have bad news.
It seems we have a traitor
among our ranks.
Kureha Tsubaki was the one
set up to be the next evil.
Unfortunately,
before we can target her,
we must first
exclude the traitor.
I'm sure she agrees.
Right, Sumika Izumino?
[SUMIKA]
Kureha, I'm sorry.
I jumped into the storm myself,
and I did it willingly.
[SUMIKA] At the time, I thought
if I could prove my love,
I wouldn't mind getting hurt.
Even heartbroken.
But then, I realized
I was wrong.
It wouldn't be me the
Invisible Storm would break.
It would wind up being you.
The one I care about most.
[HARISHIMA]
Good, you wrote the letter.
[SUMIKA]
Uh.
Oh, Kaoru.
Thanks, great work.
I can take it now. That way I'll
be ready to give it to Kureha.
What's the problem?
[SUMIKA]
About the letter.
Would you mind
holding off a bit?
I'd like to wait until we
celebrate Kureha's birthday here
at the garden.
Is that okay?
Fine, whatever.
Just don't forget.
I have to be
Kureha's new friend.
That's the only way we can make
sure the storm will pass her by.
Yeah.
[HARISHIMA]
I can't stop the storm,
but I can protect Kureha
as long as I'm her new friend.
I know it puts you
in a terrible position,
but we have no other choice
if we want to save her.
I still think I should do it.
Deliver the letter, I mean.
[SUMIKA]
No. Let me.
This is the last love
I ever get to give her,
so it has to be done right.
It has to be me.
Okay.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
See ya.
[SUMIKA] Kureha, this will
be my present to you.
Because, I understand now.
[grunts]
I promise to never
back down on love.
[HARISHIMA]
I owe you one.
Thank you for saving my life.
You told me the truth
about Ginko and Lulu.
That they were bears
disguised as humans.
Because of you, I got
to set a trap in advance.
Although...
We know what you are,
and this is what you get!
[chuckles]
[LULU]
Bear Flash!
[HARISHIMA groans, yelps]
I can't believe
that stupid bear.
Who knew she'd have
a trick up her sleeve!
--[footstep]
--Uh.
But it's not a problem.
The plan is still going
off without a hitch.
Yes, Sumika's death was
definitely unexpected,
but your idea of using it
was inspired. Pure genius. Heh.
Tomorrow it'll finally be
Kureha Tsubaki's birthday,
and I think we'll
really enjoy it.
[KUREHA]
Oh, no.
Don't tell me.
Leave me alone,
for your own sake.
[KUREHA] I wonder where
they could've gone.
I was planning
to apologize, too.
[LULU]
Growl. Ginko.
Oh, hang in there!
Growl, sniffle.
Dang it. Stupid Kaoru Harishima.
It doesn't make any sense.
How did she even know
we were bears?
[YURIIKA]
Reia.
I can't help but be reminded of
the day I swore my love to you.
And now, it's your
daughter's turn.
I wonder what she'll get from
her friend on her birthday.
So that it's perfect,
since it's my present to you.
Sumika, I promise
to accept your gift,
and I'll do
what you asked me to.
[HARISHIMA]
Hey, Kureha.
Do you remember the day
of the entrance ceremony?
[KUREHA]
What?
[HARISHIMA]
Pummeled by the cold wind
that scattered
the cherry blossoms,
a girl searched for something,
but she couldn't
seem to find it.
[HARISHIMA]
I felt bad for Sumika.
No one helped her
look for it at all.
Although, why would they?
It was just some cheap hairpin,
nothing to get upset about.
But you, you're not
like the rest of us.
[HARISHIMA] Tell me something.
Why haven't you lost hope, yet?
The world is cruel.
You've lost things,
had them taken from you.
Why don't you become invisible?
[KUREHA] Well... I think it's
because I don't forget love.
I don't understand
what that means.
[KUREHA] It means, as long
as you don't forget love,
you'll never, ever be alone.
And if you don't
give up on love,
even if you if you
lose something,
you won't be invisible.
[HARISHIMA grunts]
What's that?
It's a letter from Sumika.
She gave it to me
not too long ago.
This-This is my
birthday present.
I'm supposed to read it
at the flowerbed.
So, Kureha, it means a lot
that you're giving us a chance
to make amends for
all this. Thank you.
I'm super excited about
your birthday party, aren't you?
Yes, I am, thank you.
Oh, there's no need
to thank me, silly!
[HARISHIMA]
Especially considering your love
is about to be utterly destroyed
by the Invisible Storm.
[FEMALE VOICE]
♪ Yuri ga aku. ♪
Kureha!
[LULU]
Growl! Ginko! You're alive!
Oh, Lulu's so happy, Ginko!
What a relief!
That was terrifying.
Lulu was so worried! She didn't
know what she'd do if you died!
Lulu did everything
she could think of!
She carried you
all the way to here
and stayed up the whole night
taking care of you!
Oh, no! Today is Kureha's
birthday! Growl, growl, growl!
[LULU]
Huh?
I said, today is
Kureha's birthday.
--[phone ringing]
--[BOTH] Uh?
Hello?
[LIFE SEXY]
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from
the Wall of Severance.
Ginko Yurishiro,
if your love is true,
you need to get
to the flowerbed.
The moon girl is there right
now awaiting for your arrival.
Do I know a "moon girl"?
All you have to do is give
yourself over to the flames,
only then will
your love be approved.
Kureha! Are you
trying to tell me
the moon girl is
supposed to be Kureha?
All right.
I wonder if the Promise Kiss
will come to pass, now.
We shall see.
For that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.
Uh.
On your birthday, Kureha,
we wish you well!
[STUDENTS]
Happy birthday!
Thank you, guys.
Don't forget your promise.
You told Sumika you'd read
her letter right here.
Uh. Yeah.
[KUREHA] "Kureha. The girl
standing in front of you is...
...is your new friend."
What does this mean?
[HARISHIMA]
Exactly what it says.
It's pretty obvious
when you think about it.
That's Sumika's
break-up letter to you.
Seems she's trying
to give you a gift, too.
Her final present for you was to
make sure you had a new friend.
One that wasn't her.
But we have no intention
of making friends with you,
Kureha Tsubaki.
I can't imagine
it feels very good
to realize you
were both tricked.
We were tricked?
[HARISHIMA]
That's right! Surprise.
I was the one who had
Sumika write the letter
to you in the first place.
[HARISHIMA] Her death
screwed up the original plan,
yet, fortunately,
we got to use that letter
to punish the real evil anyway.
The girl who refuses
to follow social cues.
In order to wish you
the happiest of birthdays,
Kureha Tsubaki,
this is a little something
special from Us to you.
[KUREHA gasping]
[STUDENTS]
Happy birthday!
The time has come for Us
to exclude the evil!
[STUDENTS]
Exclude!
Tell me, does evil get
to have any friends?
[STUDENTS]
No friends!
Tell me, does evil get crushed?
Crushed by the Invisible
Storm as punishment?
[STUDENTS]
Crushed as punishment!
She's excluded!
Good job, ladies. Kureha Tsubaki
just snapped like a twig!
[STUDENT A]
Yay!
[STUDENT B]
We did it!
[HARISHIMA]
Tragic.
You won't get any new friends.
On top of that,
you'll never be able to accept
Sumika Izumino's final gift.
Oh, what a pity. At least now
you know the emotion of love
is powerless and pointless.
[gasps]
No use for this anymore. Ha!
No! Sumika wrote that!
[SUMIKA]
Such a beautiful smile.
I want you to always
smile like that.
Like a flower. That's my love.
It's funny. Even if I had to
watch you from a distance,
I would be happy
just to see that smile.
Please, it's Sumika's love.
She gave to me!
[GINKO]
Growl!
[KUREHA gasping]
[GINKO groaning]
[KUREHA]
Wha--? Ginko?
Okay, everyone,
looks like the party's over.
Let's get out of here!
[yelping]
I won't. I'll never
back down on love!
[LULU panting]
Ginko!
[GINKO groaning]
Ginko, you dummy!
Lulu would have killed you
if you'd really died this time!
What were you thinking?
Why would you do that, Ginko?
You're a dummy, too! She did it
because she loves you!
She wha--? She loves me?
That's right.
Ginko loves you so much
look at what she's done for you.
Don't waste her love!
Please, don't waste it!
[SUMIKA] "Kureha, the girl
standing in front of you
is your new friend."
[gasps]
[KUREHA] Is this for real?
She's my new friend?
[SUMIKA] I think
I got here a little early.
Still, I'm gonna have
to fix this place fast.
The flowerbed has to be
packed full of flowers again
before Kureha's birthday!
[MITSUKO]
Well, good morning, Sumika.
[SUMIKA gasping]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Shock!
Kuma shock!
[MITSUKO]
Such a lovely morning.
And I'm practically starving!
[SUMIKA]
Mitsuko, is that you?
[SUMIKA gasps]
[thud]
[MITSUKO]
Growl, growl, chomp, chomp.
Growl,growl, chomp, chomp.
Growl-growl...
[GINKO] That day,
I committed a serious crime.
I am a... criminal bear.