It smells good.
You should smell the lily, too!
[GINKO]
Sniff, sniff.
All set, are you girls ready?
Try to smile pretty for me!
Okay, say cheese!
[GINKO] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also, we loved you from
the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you,
so we had to cross the wall.
I had to have you all to myself.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[GINKO]
Delicious smell. Slurp.
Good morning, Kureha.
Growl, growl.
Ginko, good morning.
Growl, growl. Lick!
[giggles]
Kureha, you're close to me.
[KUREHA] Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
[GINKO]
Heh.
Seriously! Why are you
in my house again?
I moved in, growl.
Wha-?
Growl, growl! All done!
We're finished moving in!
Wha--? Huh?
We're your roomies, now.
Bottoms up!
[BOTH]
New roomie noodles!
Come on, Kureha!
Bottoms up!
[LULU, GINKO]
New roomie noodles!
Get... out...
Get out of my house!
You have to leave, and,
by the way, it's not acceptable
to just move into someone's
house without asking!
Growl, growl. But, Kure-pie,
you ate your new roomie noodles!
So? I don't even get
what that means!
[STUDENT A]
Look, it's that one girl.
[STUDENT B]
Wha--? Oh, her.
She's totally bad luck
to her friends.
[STUDENT C]
It's worse than bad luck.
Students are disappearing,
and the missing girls all
happen to be from her class!
[KUREHA]
There, you heard them.
Getting close to me is bad luck.
It's true.
You're gonna get caught
up in the Invisible Storm.
Do you really believe that?
Yes.
If you two make friends with me,
you'll just wind up excluded
because that's
the law of this herd.
Understand now?
Leave me alone,
for your own sake.
Growl, growl! You're the one
who doesn't understand, silly.
Lulu told you, Ginko
and Lulu came here
to make friends with you!
[GINKO] We'll protect Kureha
from the Invisible Storm.
And we promise, we won't
back down on love. Growl, growl.
[KUREHA] I'm not lying! She was
a bear masquerading as a human!
[YURIIKA]
That's impossible.
[KUREHA]
I saw it.
Mitsuko turned into a bear
right in front of me!
She ate Sumika.
She killed my friend!
Mitsuko told me as much herself.
And then... And then, I--
I took my gun and
I aimed it right at her.
[YURIIKA]
Kureha.
That's enough of this story.
But it's true!
You poor darling.
The shock was just too much,
so you've clearly hallucinated.
No, it's real! I swear!
I won't force you to
do anything right away;
however, you will eventually
need to accept the reality
of the situation and let it go.
[YURIIKA]
I just remembered!
Next Sunday is your
birthday. It is, isn't it?
[KUREHA]
Yes.
Reia's little girl about
to be 17. I can't believe it.
Time certainly flies.
So, tell me, what would
you like to do this year?
Go out for dinner? Or did you
want a particular present?
[KUREHA]
No, not this year.
[YURIIKA]
Now that I think about it,
you know your mother's pendant?
She loved it so much.
It was a present for her
when she turned seventeen.
I'm actually the one
who gave it to her.
Really, it was from you?
[YURIIKA] Yes. It was a symbol
of a promise between friends.
We pledged to each other that
we would never forget love.
You pledged to
never forget love?
We sure did.
As long as you
don't forget love,
you'll never, ever
be truly alone.
And, if you don't
give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you'll never be invisible.
Of course, it's
important to know
that love can cause
us pain, as well.
For example, when we
remember time that's been lost.
Remember time that's been lost?
Sumika.
Whenever we feel that pain,
we should try to focus
on something else
and not be too hard
on ourselves.
Kureha, I think what you
probably need right now
more than anything
is a new friend.
A new friend? Seriously?
[YURIIKA]
Yes.
Try allowing yourself to
get close to someone else.
I can't do it.
[YURIIKA]
What?
I don't want to get
close to someone else.
Sumika is my only friend.
I'll never give up on love,
no matter what!
[LULU, GINKO]
Growl, growl, munch, munch.
Growl, growl.
[GINKO]
Munch, munch.
Growl, growl. Kure-pie is eating
one of those rolls again,
but Lulu doesn't think they
smell all that delicious!
Kureha eats what
tastes like love to her.
What tastes like love?
Yes. It's something
which can't be destroyed
by any storm, or bear, or human.
Say what? Are you sure
that's for real?
[GINKO]
It's real. I'm sure.
[gasps]
[KUREHA]
It's okay. I'm your friend.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
[gasps]
I'm here, and I love you.
[GINKO]
Lady Kumaria?
[growling]
[GINKO] I remember
getting love from someone.
That's why I came.
Why I crossed the wall.
Kureha, I want to have you.
I want you all to myself!
[HARISHIMA]
Hey, Kureha.
Got a sec, maybe?
[grunts]
[HARISHIMA] I want you to know
we talked it over this morning.
Everyone agreed
we've been really cruel.
We know we're in the wrong,
and we're beyond sorry
for what we've done.
So, we wanna
make it up to you.
Huh?
Not just you,
to Sumika, too.
[KUREHA gasps]
Gimme a break.
Uh!
You all excluded Sumika!
None of you have the
right to be forgiven!
Why the change of heart now?
If this is some sort of game,
you girls better finish it,
because I won't lose
to people like you.
You're not gonna
make me invisible!
Please, please forgive us.
We've all been so--
We've been so awful!
[cyring] We really are sorry!
[HARISHIMA crying]
[GINKO]
What was that, growl?
Only we get to make
friends with Kureha.
That girl is in
our way, big time!
Only one solution.
Growl, growl.
[LULU]
Growl. Hey! Listen to this!
"Article One:
The Way to a Girl's Heart
is Through Her Stomach."
Challenge accepted! Ginko and
Lulu are going to make Kure-pie
something she loves as
much as those crazy rolls!
And then--
[giggles]
Lulu is so clever! Hm?
Delicious smell. Growl, growl.
No! You can't transform here.
It doesn't matter
how hungry you may be.
We have to follow
court rules on this side.
We're only allowed to eat the
flesh of invisible girls, Ginko!
[GINKO]
Growl!
So, do you know what kinds
of food Kure-pie likes?
[GINKO]
Shiokara and spaghetti.
That sounds like what
an old man would eat.
She's liked them
since she was little.
Hmm. All right, guess we know
what tonight's dinner will be.
Growl, growl!
Welcome home, lady!
[KUREHA]
Um, what're you doing?
[GINKO]
Making dinner. Growl, growl.
[LULU]
Uh-huh.
Ginko and Lulu have decided
to make your love flavor!
Make what? My "love flavor"?
Yep! We're cooking
your two favorite foods!
What? No way!
[GINKO] Yes! We call it
"Shiokara Spaghetti"!
Delicious smell! Growl, growl!
Oh, wow! Incredible.
A flavor pairing made in heaven.
Try one, Ginko!
Cherry tomato! "Ahh"!
[GINKO]
Ahhh!
Here comes, Ginko. Try some
creamy honey flan. "Ahhh"!
[GINKO]
Ahhhhh!
Eat this, Ginko, creamy,
lightly salted salmon! "Ahhh"!
[GINKO]
Ahhhh!
Now it's your turn, growl.
"Ahhh"!
No, thanks. I won't eat that.
What?
[growls]
But why? We thought you were
a fan of shiokara and spaghetti
just like old men are!
Wait, how'd you know that?
We... didn't?
I'm certain I only ever
told Sumika about that.
Two transfer students
shouldn't know anything!
[LULU] Mmm. Good point.
We don't know anything.
I'm serious. I want you
to stay away from me!
[LULU] Growl! But we want to
be your friends, Kure-pie!
Why is that so hard
to understand?
Stop it!
[BOTH]
Uh!
[KUREHA] Enough about being
my friend! I'm sick of it!
Why is everyone trying to
make me give up on my love?
How many times do I
have to repeat myself?
I don't want new friends!
Sumika is my only love!
I don't want anyone else!
What's with you two?
Why are you so damn
desperate to get close to me?
[water dripping]
[LULU]
Growl, growl.
That was super scary for Lulu.
Lulu thought for sure
you were about to tell Kure-pie
the truth about everything.
But you know, Ginko,
if you tell her,
we can't be human girls anymore.
Those are the court's rules.
Sheesh. Lulu hopes
Kure-pie remembers you soon.
This is getting exhausting.
[sighs]
[KUREHA]
Ginko, I'm here!
[gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE]
♪ Yuri amore! ♪
Listen, about earlier.
I'm sorry! I was happy.
I just had a hard
time admitting it.
Growl, growl.
It's okay. I understand.
I was thinking,
if we took some time to
wash each other all over.
It might give us the chance to
really get to know one another.
Gorgeous smell!
What about that, Ginko?
Does it feel good?
Growl. Yeah, it feels good.
And here, Ginko, this spot?
Does it feel good?
Oh, yeah. It does. Really good.
And what about here. How does
this spot feel? Really good?
[GINKO] Oh, yeah.
Really good. It's-It's amazing!
[moaning]
--Uh?
--There you go,
clean as a whistle!
[LULU yelps]
[SUMIKA]
Here, Kureha. For you.
I know it's a little early.
[KUREHA]
What's that?
My birthday isn't for
a while, you know.
[SUMIKA]
Yeah, of course I do.
I can't explain it. I just
had to give you this today.
[KUREHA]
Okay. You are so silly.
[SUMIKA]
Um, wait. Don't open it yet.
What?
On your birthday, I want you
to come to this spot,
then you can read what it says.
Why then?
So that it's perfect,
since it's my present to you.
You got me a gift?
How could I not?
Wait though to open it? Please?
Yeah, sure thing.
[SUMIKA]
Look at you.
[KUREHA]
Uh.
[SUMIKA]
Such a beautiful smile.
I want you to always
smile like that.
Like a flower. That's my love.
It's funny, even if I had
to watch you from a distance,
I would be happy
just to see that smile.
What're you talking about?
There's no distance between us.
I'm always right by your side.
[SUMIKA]
That's true.
You kept your promise, and
didn't back down on love.
I'll never, ever
forget that, either.
Sumika?
[SUMIKA]
They'll bloom soon, won't they?
[KUREHA]
Yeah.
Oh, Sumika.
You're my only friend,
and the only friend I want.
The flowerbed.
[HARISHIMA] We asked the school
to help you grow flowers again.
I'm sorry about what
happened yesterday.
We all really are sorry, Kureha.
[KUREHA grunts]
The Invisible Storm
wrecked this place,
but we want to fix it now.
We'll do whatever it takes.
Our thought was to
refill it with flowers.
We were hoping we
could work together
to make Sumika's
last wish come true.
Last wish? What do
you know about it?
[HARISHIMA] Well, we know it
has to do with your birthday,
which is next week, right?
[KUREHA]
Yeah, that's right.
You see, I heard
that before, uh,
before what happened to Sumika
happened, that she said, um.
What?
She said she wanted a party.
One for you. And she wanted
it in a garden full of flowers.
[gasps]
So that it's perfect,
since it's my present to you.
[gasps]
Sumika.
[HARISHIMA]
We're asking you to allow Us
to celebrate your
birthday this year.
Because that...
That's what Sumika wanted.
[KUREHA gasps]
[HARISHIMA]
Please, for Sumika's sake.
Growl! What's with that?
Ginko and Lulu are her friends,
not those stinky girls!
You agree, yeah?
Uh.
[HARISHIMA] We don't have much
time before Kureha's birthday.
Let's start today, okay, girls?
[STUDENTS]
Okay!
[STUDENTS chatter]
Ladies, thank you for working
so hard these past few days.
Because of everyone here,
Kureha Tsubaki has
started to believe
that we are interested
in being her friends.
We only need to endure
her a little longer.
At this moment, we will
confirm our feelings
and make a final decision.
Who is the evil we must exclude?
Let's search evil!
[HARISHIMA]
Select!
We have chosen Kureha Tsubaki
as the evil to exclude.
[BOTH growling]
Growl, growl.
This is great news!
Turns out she is
an invisible girl.
Meaning we can
eat her, after all!
Guess who'll be judged
this time. Growl, growl.
[LIFE SEXY]
Let the Yuri Trial begin!
I wish to eat her.
That way I can save Kureha
from the Invisible Storm.
Growl, growl!
Not this again.
Excuse me, but doesn't everyone
want to protect
the girl they love?
Sparkle, sparkle!
Meh, I wouldn't be too certain.
Huh?
[LIFE COOL] Defendant bears, so
far you've eaten several humans
affiliated with this
"Invisible Storm,"
all in the name of
"saving Kureha Tsubaki."
Is that correct?
[GINKO, LULU]
Yes.
[LIFE COOL]
They're guilty, Your Honor!
Ginko Yurishiro, answer this
question honestly, please.
What is it that you want?
And don't say to save Kureha.
That's just an excuse.
In fact, isn't it true,
all you really want
is to make sure you are Kureha
Tsubaki's one and only friend?
[LIFE BEAUTY]
Objection! Speculation.
The prosecutor is being
ruled by his personal sadism!
For your information,
Ginko just wants to give back
the love she got from Kure-pie!
She wants a Promise Kiss.
Is that so wrong?
[LIFE SEXY]
Order.
The objection is overruled.
Ginko Yurishiro, please answer
the prosecutor's question.
Okay. The truth is. I want
to have Kureha all to myself.
Ginko?
I want to be friends
with her again,
and I want to have
Kureha's love again.
That's the only
reason I came here.
That's the reason
I crossed the wall
and dragged Lulu
into it with me.
But, Ginko, Lulu wanted
to cross the wall with you.
It doesn't matter, though!
I won't back down on love!
I'll still do whatever
it takes for love!
I'll do anything.
There's no going back now.
I've committed a serious crime.
Uh, Ginko? What "serious
crime" do you mean?
I mean--
Whoa! No need to finish
that sentence, okay? Ha!
This is too much.
Your Honor, the defendant
bear confessed in court.
She just admitted
to committing a crime.
You must find her
guilty at once!
[LIFE SEXY] Ginko Yurishiro,
is your love the real thing?
[GINKO]
You bet it is.
[LIFE SEXY] And what if
it's an egotistical love?
What if that pride
eventually destroys you?
[GINKO grunts]
[GINKO] That's fine,
because I'm a criminal bear.
[LIFE SEXY]
I see.
Defendant bears, I ask you.
Do you want to be invisible?
Or, would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat.
Guh, bring on the humans.
[BOTH]
Growl, growl!
[LIFE SEXY] I am now ready
to declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
What did you wanna
meet me for? It's kinda late.
Growl. This is about Kureha.
Ginko and Lulu are going
to be friends with her!
Huh? What is that
supposed to mean?
It means we won't let
you have your way.
We're on to you.
So now, you disappear!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Shock!
Kuma shock!
[gasps] No! This can't be real!
Are you two what I think?
No. You just can't be!
Growl. But we are.
We're bears, and we'll
eat you up, growl.
[HARISHIMA]
Ah! Help! Someone help me!
[roar]
[HARISHIMA screaming]
[GINKO screaming]
Ginko!
[laughing]
One bear successfully
eliminated by our trap!
We know what you two really
are, and this is what you get!
[LULU gasps]
[HARISHIMA chuckles]
[GINKO groaning]
[GINKO]
Kureha.