[GINKO gasps]
Lulu!
[GINKO cries]
[CHOUKO]
You don't have to be, like, sad.
I mean, you'll get to join
her after I exclude you, too.
[chuckles]
[LULU] From the beginning,
we hated you.
But also, we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you.
So we had to cross the wall.
[LULU]
Ginko, Kure-pie, thank you.
Lulu loves you. She loves
both of you, so much.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[CHOUKO]
Attention, ladies!
Above all things, we must
remain way invisible!
The time has come to begin
the Exclusion Ceremony.
"Friends" are, like, more
important than anything else,
agreed? The friends gathered
here right now are Us.
We are Us.
Those who, like, dare to
contradict Our feelings
are a disgrace, like, totally.
As are those who want to, like,
way stick out from our crowd.
The ones that, like,
refuse to fit in with Us,
are nothing but a nuisance.
People like that,
those who, like, don't follow
social cues, are way evil.
Humans and bears have
been, like, way severed.
Yet still, certain people are,
like, trying to cross that wall.
We're here to decide who that
next evil will be so we can,
like, way exclude them.
Let's, like, search evil!
[CHOUKO chuckles]
Select! We have our evil.
So, is everyone,
like, totally ready?
All right. We will now, like,
totally exclude the evil!
Nega-kuma energy,
replenishing and ready.
[KONOMI-BOT]
Buzz, buzz! Nasty, nasty!
Nasty, nasty, nasty.
Nasty, nasty, nasty,
nasty, nasty, nasty.
[KUREHA gasps]
Shoot her with that, and
she gets way blown to bits.
The bear will be extinct
in, like, no time flat.
Hold on! I'm the evil,
isn't that right?
All you really have
to do is exclude me!
[CHOUKO chuckles]
Of course,
that's exactly
what we plan to do.
[FEMALE VOICE]
♪ Yuri ga aku. ♪
[CHOUKO]
This will be your punishment.
You're gonna get to kill your
friend, so we don't have to.
[gasps]
[CHOUKO] You don't follow
this world's rules,
so you're, like, way evil.
We all stay invisible
because we don't wanna
be anything like you.
But, if you're invisible, how
are you ever going to be found?
[CHOUKO chuckles]
[GINKO]
My friend?
You have to be kidding.
Growl, growl.
Don't be ridiculous, that girl
is hardly a friend of mine.
I came here to eat
Kureha Tsubaki.
From the beginning,
that's all I wanted.
Kureha is my prey,
nothing more.
I've never once thought
of that girl as my friend.
Ginko.
She's not my friend.
Kureha Tsubaki's not my friend.
--[CHOUKO grunts] Lia--
--[KUREHA] That's a lie!
I know you're lying, Ginko.
If you're telling the truth,
then why did you cross
the wall and come over here!
[GINKO] Because I wanted
to eat you. Growl, growl.
[KUREHA] And if that's true,
why did you stay by my side?
Why save me?
You both did what you could
to protect me from
the Invisible Storm.
That's because if you
had become invisible,
you wouldn't have
tasted as good.
Growl, growl.
You can stop this now, Ginko.
From the very beginning,
you were my true friend.
You crossed the wall,
and you found me.
You saved me from the Invisible
Storm, and gave me love.
You're wrong!
Look, I am only your enemy.
All I wanted was to eat you.
Get it now? I'm a bear!
The bear has revealed
her true form to Us!
Like, exclude that thing!
[GIRLS] Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude...
[KUREHA] Oh, yes,
I remember everything, now.
[KUREHA]
Please stop it!
[GIRL A] We have to
exclude all traitors!
[GIRLS] Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude...
[GINKO]
Growl.
I don't understand.
Does she not get to be
approved 'cause she's a bear?
--But why? Is being a bear bad?
--[GINKO sighs] Growl.
If... If she were a human girl,
would we be able to
be together forever?
Would I be able
to protect Ginko?
Please, Lady Kumaria. Tell me!
Yes. I'm the one who
hoped for a Promise Kiss.
This is my fault!
[gasps]
[LIFE SEXY]
Kureha Tsubaki,
this is a challenge from
the Wall of Severance.
Is your love the real thing?
[KUREHA]
Yes, absolutely.
[LULU] If they grant a bear
yuri approval in court,
she can become a girl.
But to do that, you have
to let go of something.
It's usually whatever
you care about the most.
[KUREHA]
What does that mean?
[LULU] Well, and this
is just Lulu's theory,
but Lulu bets in Ginko's trial,
when they made her let go
of something, she had to
let go of your love.
[KUREHA]
Sorry, Lulu, you were wrong.
Ginko didn't choose to let go of
her love in order to get a wish.
--It wasn't her.
--[door opens]
[KUREHA]
It was me.
[LIFE SEXY]
Let the Yuri Trial begin!
Defendant human Kureha Tsubaki,
is there anything you
would like to say?
I want to be with
Ginko forever, please!
So, I was hoping, that, maybe,
you could make Ginko
a human girl like me?
Your Honor, the defendant
has obviously just committed
the crime of pride. Therefore,
the court must find her guilty!
Crime of pride?
What does that mean?
Basically, it's about
you wanting to transform
Ginko Yurishiro from
a bear into a human.
But I have to change
her. Because...
Because bears all get excluded.
[LIFE SEXY]
Hm...
[KUREHA] And I know Ginko
will be much happier
as a human anyway!
[LIFE BEAUTY] Whoa, someone's
confident! Sparkle, sparkle!
[LIFE COOL] And that is exactly
what we're telling you is pride.
Well, I don't care if
it's pride, or a crime!
Please, I want you to
make Ginko a human girl!
[LIFE SEXY] Very well.
However, there is one condition.
[KUREHA]
What's that?
In order for your wish to come
true, you must relinquish love.
You know what that means?
Without love,
you'll forget all about
your precious
friend, Ginko.
[LIFE SEXY]
When you wake up,
understand that you will
most likely reject her.
Reject Ginko?
[KUREHA] That day, I made a wish
that no one should ever make.
I was foolish enough to
believe my selfish love
was actually the real thing.
[LIFE SEXY] You must wait.
One day the time will come.
When the Invisible
Storm arrives,
you will find Ginko
Yurishiro again.
[LIFE COOL] If you can make
friends with her once more,
you must then exchange
Promise Kisses.
[LIFE BEAUTY] After that,
you can be together forever!
Sparkle, sparkle!
[KUREHA]
Really?
And now, defendant human
Kureha Tsubaki, I ask you this,
will you choose to make Ginko
Yurishiro a human girl like you?
Or will you choose
to give up on love?
Sir, I refuse to ever
give up on love!
So, please, make Ginko
a human girl!
[KUREHA]
Lulu, I hate to admit it,
but I'm afraid I wished
for Ginko to be human,
and I did it in exchange
for what was most precious.
[LIFE SEXY]
Let the Yuri Trial begin!
Defendant human Kureha Tsubaki,
are you ready to
admit your crime?
Yes, I am.
I admit that I have previously
committed the crime of pride.
I did so by asking you to turn
Ginko into a human girl.
[LIFE BEAUTY, LIFE COOL gasp]
Now let me ask, when you
searched the Invisible Storm,
did you find what you wanted
to find? What you hoped to find?
Yes. I met a girl there.
[KUREHA]
She taught me so much.
She found me.
I found what I wanted.
I found true love with Sumika!
[KUREHA]
Sumika.
Oh, thank you.
[KUREHA]
I'm not afraid anymore.
As long as I don't forget love,
I'll never, ever be alone.
If I don't give up on love,
even if I lose something,
I'll never be invisible. So...
I'm free, now, and I will
leap into the storm!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[gasps] What does that mean?!
[KUREHA] Lulu, thank you. I'll
take this star, this true love,
and deliver it to Ginko.
[gasps] Stay away!
[gasps]
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty?
Face it, Ginko,
you are my friend.
No! You're wrong! You're no
friend of mine! Growl, growl!
I'm a people-eating bear,
Ginko the Lone Wolfsbane,
and I came here to eat you!
Stop. Stay back!
Hurry up and shoot me!
Otherwise, I'll eat all of you!
I'm a criminal bear!
Growl, growl!
Admit it.
Please, Kureha, stay away.
I can't do that.
I finally found you.
Help me with my wish!
Lady Kumaria!
Whoa! It's Lady Kumaria!
Oh, how wonderful,
she's regaining her form!
Indeed, she hath returneth,
which means we gots to go.
For this is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo!
[LIFE COOL]
This is so cool!
[LIFE BEAUTY]
Sparkle, sparkle!
Kureha Tsubaki, is your
love the real thing?
Is it true?
Absolutely.
I will smash it.
I will smash my image!
Lady Kumaria,
make my wish come true.
I... wanna be... a bear!
Yuri approved!
[STUDENTS sigh]
What? Ew!
Huh? Uh!
Kureha, how could you?
[KUREHA] Ginko, thank you
for refusing to forget love,
and thank you for never,
ever giving up on it, either.
[gasps]
It's for you,
my Promise Kiss.
[KUREHA]
Did you know?
You and me are gonna
be together forever now!
[GINKO]
Together forever. Growl, growl!
[GINKO, KUREHA]
Yuri approved!
[CHOUKO]
That's, like, way unbelievable.
A human, like, became... a bear?
Uh! Like... way... gross!
[UKO gasps]
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty.
We can't do it.
Stop! No shooting!
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty.
Like, hey. What are you,
like, waiting for?
That thing's not human anymore!
It's a bear! It's evil!
[STUDENTS]
Uh...
Like, exclude them!
We have to exclude all evil!
[STUDENTS whimper]
Aim straight!
--Don't think about it!
--[STUDENTS whimper]
Fire!
[CHOUKO]
We worked hard,
we worked together,
and we got the job done.
Congratulations.
Ladies, we successfully
excluded the terrible evil
that had been overrunning
this school for far too long.
[applause]
What's more,
we know we've been right,
and should remain
invisible at all times.
Let's begin the
Exclusion Ceremony!
[CHOUKO]
"Friends" are more important
than anything else, agreed?
The friends gathered here,
right now, are Us. We are Us.
Fire!
[coughing]
[UKO gasps]
[CHOUKO] The ones who
refuse to fit in with Us
are nothing but a nuisance.
People like that,
those who don't follow
social cues, are evil.
Now, let us decide on
the next evil to exclude!
[KONOMI-BOT crying]
Nasty!
[crying continues]
[KONOMI-BOT]
Nasty!
--Nasty? Nasty?
--[footsteps]
I found you.
[LULU] "And so, having
completed their Promise Kiss,
the two began a journey
beyond severance,
guided by the star of love."
Big Sis, Lulu, I wish
this wasn't the end.
Do you know what happened
to them after they left?
That's a very good question.
What do you think
happened, Milne?
[MILNE]
Hmmm. I dunno!
Oh, I think I figured
out something else, though!
[LULU]
What's that?
--[MILNE] Smooch!
--[LULU] Uh!
I should've just done it myself.
I could've given you
the Promise Kiss instead!
Milne.
Right?
[gasps] We'll be
together forever.
[MILNE] Mm-hm! Big Sis,
Lulu. I love you!
[LULU]
I love you, too!
[LADY KUMARIA] And so, no one
knows where the girls have gone.
But, that is as it should be.
In the end,
it is with your own love that
the world awakens and changes.