Throughout history,
every domain in the
world has had to
deal with foolish rulers.
There is nothing suspicious.
Chosen to serve the
lord in bed on that night
was the daughter
of one of his retainers...
Her name was Sato.
Tadanaga Tokugawa...
New lord of Sunpu Castle...
...son of the previous
Shogun Hidetada...
...younger brother of
the current Shogun Iemitsu...
To see this spoiled
man face justice
for his reign of cruelty,
the world would have
to wait until a certain
match held before the
lord in Kan'ei Year 6.
Kan'ei Year 5, June.
Excuse me good sirs...
Could you please wait a moment?
What do you want?
Ah, you gentlemen left
but have not yet paid.
Oh, the bill from the inn...
Right...
We forgot...
Insolent punk.
He got what he deserved.
They say that Suruga
Dainagon-sama is as
ferocious a lord as Nobunaga.
And from what I hear...
If we have the skills
he would not have
any problem employing
swordsmen like us.
Everybody knows that.
Look around you...
This town is full of ronin.
Even he...
cannot employ us all.
Then we will show
him we are the best.
Once we prove to him
that our skill level is much
greater than these other ronin,
his choice will be clear.
Much like Musashi who
defeated Yoshioka in Kyoto.
Yes, that would be
a quick and easy way.
So who...
will be our prey?
There is a dojo nearby,
something called
the Kogan Style.
The Kogan Style...?
What kind of backwoods
swordsmanship is that?
The story goes that the Sensei,
Kogan Iwamoto, is insane...
...and his daughter is
nearly as mad as he is.
People say that of
the two instructors,
Ushimata is the idiot,
but the other, Fujiki,
cannot even speak.
Not so much a "backwoods" dojo
as it is a "brainless" one, huh?
Say that again!
Say what again, boy?
You must be one
of Kogan's pupils.
Show me...
What you've got.
Not just yet.
I am very sorry.
Not only did I use the Kogan
Style for my personal strife...
...but I also
promised to fight them.
My opponents are
seven rogue ronin...
They told me to
bring a witness to
Jinba Pass this evening at dusk.
Please give me your permission.
I will defeat them
with one sword
even if it costs me my life!
Suzu...
Well done.
It was one year ago in the
spring when the new pupil,
Suzunosuke Kondoh, was
approved for Naka-Mokuroku.
We are done.
What...?
one more match, please!
Just one...
One more!!
Nagare is a Kogan Style
secret technique passed on
only to those of Naka-Mokuroku
level and above.
Have patience,
you cannot master it overnight.
Is Fujiki-shihan cold to me...
...because I was approved for
Naka-Moku-roku due to
my "connections?"
He is not the kind of man to be
bothered by such a thing.
I suppose the fight at Jinba
Pass is in full clash by now.
Yes.
How truly heartbreaking.
According to Mosuke-san...
...she still refuses to
eat any of her meals...
...no matter how many
ways they prepare them...
At most she eats only rice
broth every couple of days.
Three years after
his banishment...
And she still cannot
get over Irako.
Do not mention that name.
Sensei, too much of
this sun is not good for you.
We should go inside.
Sensei?
He...
With bare hands...?
With these stray dogs...
I have no need...
...for a sword.
I did not know a dragon
was hiding in Kakegawa.
Shinmusou Hayashizaki Style.
Look at him...
He is good.
Winter, Kan'ei Year 2.
Eleven months after the
punishment of Seigen Irako.
Sensei...
This is no ordinary hole.
I believe, Sensei...
...that this has something to
do with a secret technique.
Too slow!
If you want to take something...
You should first give it.
If you want to
make something weak...
...you should first
make it strong.
If you want to
shrink something...
You should first extend it.
Thus...
If you want to open something...
You should first...
cover it.
Based on his skills, it was
the following day that
Gennosuke Fujiki
was approved for
Dai-Mokuroku in the Kogan Style.
Leave one of them alive.
We give him a new
look and send him back.
Someday...
Someday that will be me.
Suzunosuke...