Irako...!
You will state the
purpose of your visit.
Of course.
Kengyou Shizuhata-sama
sent me...
I have come to deliver
his appreciation to
Kogan Iwamoto-dono
for his swordplay
performance the other day.
Is that a biwa lute?
That is very thoughtful of him.
Then, please...
do come in.
So that is the blind samurai
who desires Sensei's life.
It is laughable that he
came here on his own...
He will find that the
three Tengu of Noubi
will quickly turn
the tables on him.
I smell urine.
He must be in his
state of dementia.
He is certainly not
in his right mind.
There are two men
in front of me.
And one behind.
Iku...
Shall we begin?
That was splendid.
Sensei also seems quite pleased.
Please pass our regards
along to Shizuhata-sama...
We appreciate your performance.
Of course...
Next I will show you
a rare piece of art.
Art?
It is a refined bit of work...
drawn on the skin of Iku-sama...
Kengyou's mistress.
Go on...
Take a good look.
You have done well...
Iku.
Seigen-sama...
Finish it...!
Finish it,
as your heart desires!
I checked the hardness of the
tatami mats when
I was dancing earlier.
We successfully
made him draw his sword.
Things are going
just as I intended.
Sensei!
We will handle him!
Am I...
Dead...?
This place...
This is Hell...
The sounds...
The smell of
blood and entrails...
...It was not enough
to shut my eyes...
Now you wish to shut
my ears and nose as well...
Kogan.
This place...
Do not bow your
head before him...
Remain steady and look
Sensei directly in the eyes.
Do not move even a muscle.
Irako-sama...
...please, do as
your heart desires.
That is it...
He is doing it...
Irako-sama's certain
victory stance.
Nagareboshi, the Kogan Style
secret swordplay technique.
No man has ever been known to
escape this devilish maneuver.
I have beaten it...
I have beaten Nagareboshi.
All that is left is to
hear the sweet sound
of Kogan falling to the ground.
That was not it.
That was the sound
of Iku collapsing.
Not that either...
That is the stone lantern.
What is that...?
What is happening...?
What the hell is there?
Father...
Today...
I have found true happiness...
Mie, it is you...
You have become so beautiful.
Gennosuke Fujiki has arrived
at the Iwamoto residence.
Mie-dono!
Sensei!
Sensei...!
Oh, Sensei...
Fujiki...
Welcome home Fujiki...
Seven days after
he had left town,
Gonzaemon Ushimata returned.
Upon seeing the front gate,
he realized what had
happened in his absence.
Tell me, are you the blind man
who killed the
Tiger in Kakegawa?
Go on, Seigen.
Tell him your name.
I am a steward for
the Shizuhata Family...
My name is Seigen Irako.
What style do you use?
Mumyo...
Sakanagare.
I wish to see...
Show me your technique.