Six days after the party
at the Kengyou residence...
About seventeen miles
away from Kakegawa...
At a post-station town
near Hamamatsu...
We have heard much
about the Kogan Style
skills you have
shown us today...
Having seen them in action
has enlightened my students.
It is not much, I know, for we
are a people of modest means.
But, please...
accept this meager token.
I sincerely appreciate it.
As the day of the full moon
in August draws closer,
they visit every dojo
that has the word
'unrivaled' scrawled
on their signboard.
This action is known widely as
"Tiger's visit
to unrivaled dojos."
It was through this that
Kogan earned his traveling
expenses when he
was a young samurai.
This summer, Gonzaemon
Ushimata has good reason
for completing
this journey alone...
There is no doubt in my mind...
...that Seigen Irako's intention
is to put an end to the
Kogan Style with
Kengyou's support.
Leaving the dojo
during such a crisis
is the last thing
I would like to do...
Please, Sensei...
Please let me stay with you.
No!
This is a task
we must not neglect!!
And now, my hopes must rest...
with Fujiki...
The plan was for Sekiun
to slay Gennosuke Fujiki.
But that old fool stepped
in and saved you...
It seems that he did not
believe you to be strong enough.
And you are supposed to be the
successor to the Kogan Style?
Gennosuke-sama...
There are visitors
here to see you.
I am an Instructor
at Kogan's Noubi Dojo...
Hanshinken Ibuki.
Likewise...
Rokurobee Neoya.
Likewise, I am...
Unryusai Kanaoka.
You heard from Ushimata-shihan?
Correct...
In his letter,
he asked us to
fill in during his absence
from Iwamoto Dojo.
Therefore...
We will protect Sensei.
Is there a problem?
Get up and go tell Sensei
we are here right now.
I am sorry...
...but Sensei is
resting at this time...
In his absence...
I would ask you to
have a match with me.
You are the one called Fujiki...
Are you not?
And you are saying you would
like to witness our skills.
I had heard
Fujiki was a
stubborn and fearless
man, but this...
Kuramashi...
He dodged it!
Clearly I need not
go easy on this one.
That man, Gennosuke Fujiki...
It seems he is
truly not ordinary.
Since we have
revealed our plan to him,
sooner or later we
will have to settle things.
As a baby of no more
than a few months age,
I was abandoned by
my parents and
my eyes pecked out by crows...
Since that time, too far back to
remember, I have not seen light.
Because of my circumstance,
I had to gain the
light on my own...
Through performing arts,
social studies, community
status, even fame.
However...
there was one thing...
One mountain I could never
climb no matter my efforts.
That is martial, arts...
Seigen.
The last frontier...
...that which blind men
have no ability to reach.
But in this frontier
of martial arts,
your body hides
mysteries that would
surpass even
those men with sight.
This last light...
Will you share it with me...
Seigen Irako?
Fujiki...
Know that you are next.
On the night of the full
moon in mid-autumn...
It is a custom for samurai
households to keep their
doors wide open in
admiration of the moon.
Oh, Mie-dono.
Welcome...
Please sit down.
Her body had come
to life once more,
and again gave the appearance
of being dangerously seductive.
But for whom
did this change occur?
The moon is beautiful
hanging in the sky.
Iku...
Tonight...
Tonight, it all ends.
Their punishment and
subsequent exile from the
Kogan Style caused Irako
and Iku tremendous misery.
Iku...
Take cover.
You scum!
It was at this moment,
most unexpectedly,
that a great speed was achieved.
Stupid...
I was in too much of a hurry.
Seigen Irako must
have given this order.
Irako!
Poison?!