Please forgive
my impertinence...
If I force myself on her now,
Mie-sama will take her own life.
If that happens,
your family line ends.
For her sake and that
of the Kogan Style,
allow us to continue
after the wedding.
Irako-sama.
Hello, Mie-dono.
Training has ended for the year,
why do you still practice?
Because, I still
lack experience.
Well, then...
Mariko, do you recall where
Irako said he was from?
If I remember correctly,
he is from Edo...
I heard tale that he is the son
of a rich dye shop owner...
...and that the
man disowned him
because Irako failed to do
anything but practice swordplay.
Hmmm...
That makes the
successor of Kogan Style
the disowned son of
a dye merchant.
I find it peculiar
that no one has seen
Gennosuke since
earlier this evening.
How far could he have gone
in all of this snow?
The incident with
Mie affected him deeply...
He seems to have descended
into very low spirits.
Now that I reflect back on it,
when Sensei chose
Seigen as his successor...
None of us was more
unsettled by it than Fujiki.
Certainly you don't think
he would have run away?
He is not a man of such
petty characteristics.
I believe he has his own
valid reasons for doing this.
There is no need to worry...
He will be back in no time.
Welcome.
Your companion is
waiting for you upstairs.
You know what
is required of you?
Of course.
I know nothing...
You were never here
this night, and certainly
neither was anyone
resembling your companion.
In fact, this night
is absent of visitors.
Thank you.
I like the snow...
When winter comes...
...the children sing
a different song...
instead of
"How Cruel, How Cruel."
♪ Du-ring the cold sea-son. ♪
♪ Down came a crying
boy from the moun-tain. ♪
♪ So many tears;
is there a reason? ♪
♪ From the boy came sim-ply:
"Because it is cold. ♪
Apparently...
I am to be successor
to the Kogan Style.
It is time we stopped
fooling around.
I can't...
Even the thought of another
woman tearing you from me...
I will not stand for it.
I refuse to face this...
I am not your mother in law...
I am neither Tiger's mistress...
...nor am I cursed.
I am a perfectly normal woman...
Somebody told me that one time.
Cuh...
Con...
Conceive!
Fujiki...
A year surely passes quickly.
Irako...
The last day of December,
in the first year of Kan'ei.
Wanna have a good time?
♪ How boring is the world.
Oh, good heavens. ♪
♪ From the dreary days of old,
all the way to this very day ♪
♪ Nothing is harder
than being in love. ♪
♪ "Why," someone asks. ♪
Say...
Say mister.
Looking for a good time?
You should not sneak
up on people like that.
A pregnant whore?!
Hell, no.
What happens if I
go knocking in there,
and something knocks back?
Boy, it sure is cold out here.
It's so cold.
Oh, great.
Now I'm sober.
To think that her baby
is six months overdue.
It sounds creepy,
but I would think the child
has already died
inside her belly.
Then it must...
It must be a demon child.
Looking for a good time?
Gintsuba from Mochiya.
The rice cakes you
said you wanted
to stuff your face with one day.
Those detestable fingers...
They have taken from
me two former lovers...
No...
Not any more...
Irako-sama makes three!
Soon that 300 koku will be mine.
I will not allow it.
This is the last time I come
to this muddy row house.
They will not take him away.
From this moment
forth, my status is...
No one will take Irako-sama.
...samurai!
I dreamt last night...
That I was bitten by a mosquito.
Let me help you change.
You must be cold.
I am not.
Iku?
Yes?
By observing the
patterns on a blade
a swordsman can guess how
many his tool has killed...
...and in what manner.
It is even more apparent
with one's own sword...
I can see clearly who cares
for it while I am asleep...
...and how well he does.
Exceptional work, Fujiki.
Iku, come here.
You, also, are my tool...
And I can see
you clearly as well.
How dare you deceive me...
Irako!
Those are all of
Sensei's instructions.
Each of you, please
take action, immediately.
Ushimata-sama...
Mie-dono, good morning.
If you need something,
please tell us servants.
We are obliged to assist you.
Dried chestnuts, sea tangle,
dried abalone...
Those are for Shihou-Zen--the
warlords meal.
Are you headed
into battle or something?
Ushimata, answer me.
Irako.
Kogan-sensei wishes to see you.
Sensei?
He said it is an urgent matter.
Fujiki...
From now on...
Call me Young Master.
Halfway up Akiba Mountain...
Kontake Shrine...
A hallowed place
to the Kogan Style.
It is where swordsman
Kogan Iwamoto awoke
to the secret swordplay
technique, Nagareboshi.
Seigen Irako...
at your disposal.
Seigen Irako.
Today, at this sacred
place, I will instruct you
on the Kogan Style's
secret technique.
This is it...
Nagareboshi...
Not only is he giving
me his daughter,
but he is finally giving me the
Kogan Style's secret technique!