Sensei.
When a dead body
is discovered within
the Kogan Dojo's premises...
...the first
suspect to consider...
...should not be an outsider.
Pardon me.
Please take your time.
It is not Kogan Sensei
who killed Suzu.
And therefore...
...we need to tell the local
officials about this incident.
The clothing around his neck
is not stained with blood.
Which means his head
was severed from his
body after his heart stopped.
Then that means...
Suzunosuke's life was
taken by the singular
stroke which split his
soft face down the middle.
Ushimata...
Do you have any
suspects in mind?
The other day a
ronin spoke poorly of
Kogan Style and
Suzu executed him.
What a foolish thing to do.
Here at Kakegawa...
there are masses of ronin
who seek to be employed
by Tadanaga-sama.
And the violence these
men bring with them...
...becomes more difficult
to watch by the day...
It may not be easy to get
a good idea of who did it.
Suzunosuke...
Tell me...
Why were you crying then?
The unrivaled Kogan Style
has been disgraced...
We have to take care
of this killer quickly...
If we let this go much longer,
people will scorn us.
Once we become a laughingstock
it will be too late.
We will lose our reputation
and never get it back.
Then our best option
is to invent a killer.
What do you mean by 'invent'?
Are we to choose
a person at random
to take the fall as murderer...?
That would mean the real
killer would walk away free.
It must be known that those
who oppose the Kogan Style
will be dealt with swiftly.
So our suspect cannot
be just anyone...
He must be highly skilled
in the ways of a warrior.
Jingoro Higaki.
He uses the single sword style.
A most suitable candidate.
Where is he?
I heard that after
he lost to Ushimata,
he secluded himself in
Awagatake Mountain and
now spends all of his time
improving his swordsmanship.
Eventually, we will
slay the true killer.
Hold that vexation in your
heart for the time being.
Shinpachirou Munakata...
The twenty-two sword wounds,
on his body of steel are just
like those of a
fierce warrior from the
Period of Warring States.
The wounds on his palms tell
an even more graphic story.
Who is there?
My name is Shinpachirou
Munakata of the Kogan Style.
I...
am glad you came.
I was thinking of going to see
you lovely people very soon.
You will face me in battle.
You should have left
Kakegawa long ago.
I have slain
the chosen killer...
...for the murder of
Suzunosuke Kondou.
Is that a madman I see?
That is no walking stick...
It is him...!
This is Suzunosuke's
true killer!
It may be possible
for the Kogan Style
to save face in this matter.
However...
Where is the honor in it...?
Can this truly settle the score
for Suzunosuke's death?
Well then...
I take my leave now.
Thank you for troubling
yourself to come here.
As before...
It was an upward cut.
This is obviously the work of
the same person who killed Suzu.
Munakata was approved
based on his skills, right?
Yet being split down
the middle like that...
Must have let his guard down.
How unsightly.
Yamazaki...
watch what you say.
Munakata was one of us!
Stop it.
This is no time for fighting
amongst our own brethren.
Remain on your guard...
Our enemy is very skilled.
Right, an imitation sword.
He said when Munakata's
head was put out in
public an imitation
sword was in his mouth.
Why would the
killer take the time to
do something so
stupid like that?
Don't you get it?
He is saying
that the Kogan Style...
...is as dull as
an imitation sword.
Are--Are you
with the Kogan Style?
You say that we are dull?
No...
Not me.
I never said that!
Confine your tongue,
lest it confine you.
I remember on that
day how the cicadas
were as noisy as they are now.
What day was this?
Nevermind.
Fujiki-sama...
She has been like this
for about an hour now.
Mie-sama?
Wha--...?
Was it you...?
Was it you who killed Suzu...?
Was it?!