Mie-sama is eating again...
I wonder...
The Kogan Style
apprentice murders
shocked everyone in Kakegawa.
It came to be known that
the one responsible for
vertically cutting the faces
of the four swordsmen
was their fellow apprentice
Sanjyuurou Okitsu.
Likewise, the one who
came to punish Okitsu
was his fellow apprentice
Gennosuke Fujiki.
What is truly fearful about the
Kogan Style is the members'
way of risking their lives in
swordsmanship competitions.
Many rumors have found their way
to a close through this manner.
Don't play dumb!
You two must have sold out the
Kogan Style for money,
just like Okitsu...!
Out with it!
I swear I would never
do such a thing.
I am not blind...!
You two are dogs!
Both of you are
Kengyou's lapdogs!
When the obsessed old
swordsman snapped out
of 49 days of dementia,
he became frenzied at the
betrayal by one
of his apprentices.
It was at that time a letter
was delivered by this man.
I do not understand...
If Kengyou Shizuhata is the
one behind the scenes,
controlling the
killing of our men,
why does he hide behind
a veil of anonymity?
When one faces this
biwa lute, it is the same as
being before
the Tokugawa Family.
Raise your head...
No need to be formal.
Kogan...
I am glad you came.
Of course...
You should start going
easier on yourself, Kogan...
I hear you are having difficulty
presenting yourself for duty.
Thank you for your concern.
You should also choose
your successor soon
and reassure our lord.
My daughter is
quite ill right now.
I would humbly
ask for more time.
Very well, Kogan.
Kakegawa treasures
the Kogan Style...
I wanted you to hear
those words from my lips.
I asked you to come
today because I wanted to
borrow the eyes of the
first-class Tiger swordsman.
What do you think
of Sekiun's sword?
You are said to be unrivaled,
so I want your expert opinion.
What do you see Kogan?
Is it a Wazamono?
This cannot cut...
It is for show.
For show, you say.
If I am not mistaken, Kogan,
your leading students
are praised as the 'two
dragons.' Is that correct?
One of them,
Gennosuke Fujiki, is here...
...but the other one has been...
Would you be so kind as to allow
Gennosuke to give
my Sekiun a lesson?
Show him some real swordplay?
They are ready, sir, and
awaiting your command.
Today, Gennosuke Fujiki
will use a bokken...
Since Sekiun's sword is nothing
more than a display piece,
this match will be just for fun.
So please...
both of you...
Have as much fun as you like.
The bokken has
not been doctored.
Se--
Sensei...
Kogan...
are you fighting?
Since this is for fun...
Sensei...
Stand down.
Now, boy...
Come at me.
Ridiculous...
He cannot cut with that grip.
Guarding, huh?
That is foolish.
Such a thin sword cannot...
However, Sensei
has only a bokken...
Perhaps, it might...
Spanish swordplay.
In Spanish swordplay, the sword
is not designed for cutting.
It is designed for thrusting.
Sekiun's father was a highly
stipended retainer of a lord.
Though shunned and
abandoned by his parents,
it was not because he lacked
enough hair to tie a topknot.
After wandering many places,
he ended up here.
In the care of Tada-aki Ini, a
user of the Single Sword Style.
This sword is from Spain,
a country in the land
known as Europe.
Hold it lightly, as you
would a feather duster...
and thrust it as if
striking a shuttlecock.
Sekiun...
You must master this thrust.
Sekiun did not know how
this bizarre sword became
separated from
its owner and arrived
from such a far
away foreign country...
...even so,
he saw himself in it.
This foreign sword perforated
top students of the
Single Sword
Style's Ono Faction,
like so much Swiss cheese.
And its certain
victory piercing thrust...
Sekiun-dono...
Is the opponent you
face this evening a tiger?
Not good.
Because Sekiun is retained by
Kengyou-sama, Sensei hesitates.
That man is too strong for
this to be merely for fun...
Damn that Irako.
He entrapped us!
What was that noise?
Sekiun-sama has fallen.
Since this was for fun...
I used my bare hands.
The reason Sekiun's
parents abandoned him
was because he
did not understand--
nor could he employ--
the loyalty that a samurai
feels towards his master.
To think he aimed
his vexation at losing
to you towards me,
his own master...
I suppose it is my fault
for paying a stipend to a
man I always suspected
of being disloyal.
Kogan... You did
well in punishing him...
I thank you for it.
Senior apprentices,
it has been a while.
Remember where we are Fujiki.
This is the residence
of Shizuhata-sama.
If we make waves here, Sensei
will be the one who is punished.
Ushimata-shihan.
Won't you have a drink first?
Forgive me...
As you know, I am blind...
Irako...
Was it you who tried to
kill Sensei by setting him
against that man
with European swordplay?
You accuse me falsely.
The plan was for Sekiun
to slay Gennosuke Fujiki.
But that old fool stepped
in and saved you...
It seems that he did not
believe you to be strong enough.
And you are supposed to be the
successor to the Kogan Style?
You are wrong, Irako.
Shizuhata-sama told
them to "have fun."
That is the only reason Sensei
told Fujiki to stand aside.
What are you trying to say?
Gennosuke Fujiki is
incapable of having fun.
A man who cannot
have fun, you say?
Nonsense.
You are the same
scum who joined in the
"fun" of burning a woman's
breast and who blinded me!
Fujiki...
Know that you are next.