He actually did it.
Yes...
The Hachimaki-Giri is
Ushimata-shihan's
special technique.
The real question is
when did Irako master it?
Natural talent...
What he was born with probably
outweighs our natural
abilities combined.
In just one short
year of being with
our dojo he has accomplished
impressive many things.
By comparison,
Assistant Instructor Fujiki
is hardly taken
notice of lately.
The way things stand, the
successor of the Kogan Style
might not be who we
have anticipated.
Fujiki...
A year surely passes quickly.
Yes...
In just one short year...
I have come so far...
Kogan Iwamoto...
His demented state keeps hidden
numerous secret
swordplay techniques.
Mie Iwamoto...
She is a vessel
that will give birth to
the successor of
the Kogan Style.
The Kogan Style will be mine...
And when it is...
I will bleed it dry.
We humbly thank you for
your loyal patronage.
Certainly...
Put it on the tab for the
Iwamoto household.
Yes, of course...
And thank you, madam.
Please, take care of yourselves.
Neri, huh?
Is it raw enthusiasm
that leads you to
attempt my method of training?
Or is it merely curiosity?
I have a request.
I know.
But you are not allowed a
sparring match with Irako.
Because if you were
to match blades,
it would not be
only for practice.
Fujiki, you are
Naka-Mokuroku in the
Kogan Style--an advanced pupil.
Why do you concern
yourself with practice drills?
That bastard...
He lacks the etiquette
for martial arts...
His behavior...
...sets a bad example
for the others.
Nonsense...
There is something else that
lurks in the corners
of your mind...
A thought that disturbs
your consciousness
and dulls your swordplay.
Did you think I could not see
through to your very core?
Father!
I am not Iku...!
It is Mie!
I am not Iku!
Good, Mie.
The vessel is finally ready.
Bath...
Yes, sir.
At some point between
every fall and winter,
Kogan will awaken from
his demented state.
He is normal for only one
half a day at the longest.
It is during this short
period of time that he
gives instructions for the
dojo while the apprentices
seek to satisfy these
demands to the letter.
This...
is the Kogan Style practice.
Gonza...
Sensei?
Who do you think should be
the Kogan Style successor?
Fujiki or Irako?
Gennosuke Fujiki
would be my choice.
And why is that?
Above all else, because
he respects Mie-dono.
Raise your head.
What did you say?
What was that about Mie?
You can say it...
If only the girl had
been born a boy.
I do not care about respect.
I am asking which of these two
men will give the stronger seed.
And in that...
...you would say they
stand even, correct?
In the town of Nissaka...
I believe Ichidensai
Funaki has twin sons.
Their heads...
Bring me the heads
of Funaki's sons.
This task is for
Fujiki and Irako...
The one of them
who completes this...
...will seed my bloodline.
In Kakegawa Domain,
Ichidensai Funaki has
been called a master swordsman
since the Keichou Era.
In his dojo, a special
swordplay technique
is performed every spring.
Brother!
Got it!
Hyouma and Kazuma Funaki.
They have mastered
the secret of Kabuto-Nage
and are fully proficient
in the Funaki Style.
They are the strongest
swordsmen in Nissaka.
But why Funaki's sons?
Long ago, during a match
before the shogun lord,
Sensei sliced off
Ichidensai's lower jaw.
It was after this
that the lord spoke.
Believing Sensei
had lacked in manners,
he severely punished him.
Perhaps he has not
forgotten such humiliation.
At any rate, the
country is at peace...
Even if the dojos of
the Kogan and Funaki
agree to having a
match with real swords...
...decapitation of
another as if in battle...
They probably will
not even agree to it.
Even so, how could
we approach such a matter--
asking them to have matches
so we can choose our successor.
We would be laughed at.
The order given us by Sensei...
is simply too unreasonable.
However...
Sensei's word is absolute.
It is our duty as apprentices
to follow it to the letter.
Around 6pm.
Nakayama Pass in Sayo.
The name Sayo
comes from the word
'Sai' which means 'obstruct.'
The name Nakayama
means 'boundary.'
Do you know why
the rock before us cries?
The story I have heard,
tells that it used to be
a God of Obstruction,
that protected travelers
by blocking evil spirits.
One day, a pregnant
woman named Oishi
went to Kikukawa
village to work.
She was on her way back home
when her stomach began hurting.
A passing samurai found her, but
could not leave her there...
He tended to her
with the greatest of care.
But...
The woman was
killed by a Kamaitachi...
Now possessed
within this rock...
...her soul forever weeps.
Nissaka...
is a dangerous place.
So, big brother...
Have you given any
thought to getting married?
It would certainly alleviate
some of our father's stress.
I would have to be
careful in my choice.
She would, after all,
serve you as well.
Both body and soul...
have been purified.
Who are you...?
Do you not realize we are Hyouma
and Kazuma of Funaki Dojo?
If you desire a match, the
proper way is to follow the
samurai code and let us know
the time and place beforehand.
We are not samurai.
We are Kamaitachi
from Nakayama Pass.
You look rather small for
a supernatural being!
Our style will teach
you a lesson in humility.
Kabuto Wari...
Fujiki...
I can move
more quickly than him.
I know I can.
But striking
simultaneously will not work...
So what will?
Why do you pause...?
Do you wait for the sun to rise?
Kamaitachi, do not scare...
These men...
are from Kogan.
Fujiki from Kakegawa.
If a man of Kogan Style lifts
his sword above
his head, beware.
With this much
distance between us...
What can he do?
He's too far.
Brother...
Too far.
He's too far.
It is the quickest
slashing attack that is
capable of slaying the
opponent instantly.
This technique is a secret
passed on only to those who
are Naka-Mokuroku and
above in the Kogan Style.
It is expressly
forbidden from being
used in practice at the dojo.
And it is called...
Nagare.
Brother!
Irako.
Rinse your mouth.