Keichou Year 6.
Kogan Iwamoto.
A warrior said to be
unrivaled in the Noubi area.
His right hand
had one more finger
on it than any normal hand.
It was Sadakatsu Matsudaira,
then Lord of Kakegawa,
who said...
The Kogan Style Secret Swordplay
Technique, Nagareboshi...
Its mysteriousness
is unequaled...
...throughout all of history.
Shall I do that for you?
Please...
Do not worry about me.
This is excellent
training for my fingers.
So...
How is Fujiki holding up?
While it was only training...
I cannot say I am surprised...
To lose so badly,
so disgracefully
and to a challenger
of our dojo, no less.
He refused to open up,
even when Mie approached him.
My feeling is that
he will not be up to any
lessons of reading
and writing today.
It may be only my imagination...
But Mie has acted
oddly since the match.
Use care when
choosing your words.
This man Irako,
with his skills and attitude...
He impresses me as dangerous...
I imagine he will be
quite difficult to deal with.
I hope we did not bring
trouble down upon ourselves.
Not to worry.
He is a fool.
That leap...!
I knew it was out
of the ordinary.
He reads the distance
to his opponent.
I have seen through your
moves to your weaknesses...
Knowing this, you should
concede the match...
Show the integrity of a samurai.
Well, Ushimata-dono?
Ootsubo, Yamauchi...
Block all the exits.
It seems Instructor Ushimata
has finished warming up.
Excuse me.
I have not yet
mastered this technique...
...but I will still show
you the Kogan Style.
His smile...
It has vanished.
Killing him would be easy.
Making him into
something else, however...
Finally...
I have come to face what I
know is true swordsmanship.
I now know regret...
...of the days I have
spent as a rogue.
Starting at this very moment...
I would like to become
a pupil at this dojo.
A dojo is no place for
these kinds of theatrics.
He looks to have made
Instructor Ushimata quite angry.
Violating our hallowed
dojo with this charade...
My sword!
Out of my way!
That is mine!
Take your hand off of it!
Challenging swordsmen
of other styles
is simply another
part of training.
It is never a matter
of life and death.
The bastard actually
has some natural talent.
No...
That is not talent you see.
It is cowardice.
Bring me a spear.
How is he?
He said he would not eat until
his request had been granted.
What a stubborn one.
He will be quite a
challenge to deal with.
Ushimata-dono...
I must apologize
for this, my lady...
But I have to ask you to leave.
I am here because
Master asked me to come.
I understand.
However, you will not
be able to see him today.
I am sorry.
The size of this place...
The number of servants...
Exactly what I would
expect from the
famed martial arts instructor
in Kakegawa Domain.
Must be at least 300 koku...
The only daughter
of Kogan Iwamoto.
Mosuke?
Yes.
It is ready for you now.
I prepared it using
thick malt syrup in addition
to the kuzuan sweet sauce.
Please enjoy.
The amount of
stickiness is just right.
If I marry into the family,
I become Kogan's successor...
Gaining also the Kakegawa
retainer worth 300 koku...
Not too bad.
Ah, Ushimata-dono!
Seigen Irako...
Our Sensei would
like to see you now.
That is wonderful news!
I take it to mean he has granted
my request to become his pupil?
Sensei will make that decision.
So, I will finally
meet Kogan Iwamoto...
A rare master swordsman,
who has even faced battle
with Munenori Yagyu...
In another time,
Kogan himself might have
become swordplay instructor
to the Shogun family.
What an unusual grip.
Plus he's fast,
and has a long reach.
Stepping into that
range is foolhardy...
Very well...
Yagyu Shinkage Style...
Juumonji!
Very nice.
Kogan Style, Nagareboshi!
I should not do this...
I should not fight any longer.
Even through the use of my
certain victory technique...
I stand no chance
of defeating this man.
I yield.
The match is a draw.
I have seen your skills
and judged you worthy.
I will recommend you
to the Tokugawa family.
Thank you for this honor.
However...
You wish to work for us...
Why do you hide your finger?
It is displeasing.
An insult.
His Highness Taiko has the exact
same number of fingers as you...
Are you saying that
this is displeasing?
Driven by ambition,
Kogan asked Munenori Yagyu for
his assistance in preparing for
his audience with the official.
Therefore, it was he
who advised Kogan to hide
his extra finger
during this audience...
It was his cunning that
crushed Kogan's ambition.
Bunroku Year 4.
Ushimata-dono...
If you keep me
tied up like this...
I cannot show
Sensei every courtesy.
Do not bow your
head before him...
Remain steady and look
Sensei directly in the eyes.
Do not move even a muscle.
This ritual...
What kind of charm is this?
Sensei will now appear.
Ushimata-dono!
No Sensei, this is not Iku-sama.
This is a man who wants to
join the dojo and be your pupil.
Magnificent.
Magnificent...
Most magnificent...
Do you see?
The Yodare-Azuki Bean Ceremony.
A decorum for the commencement
of training in the Kogan Style.
No one knows when it was
that Kogan Iwamoto began
his descent into such
a demented state.