Kan 'ei Year 10.
December.
Due to conduct unbecoming
the lord of a large domain,
Tadanaga Tokugawa was
ordered to commit seppuku
despite his standing as
Shogun Iemitsu's
younger brother.
Tales of his misconduct
have been passed down
through the generations,
although none have ever
been confirmed as true.
Kan 'ei Year 10.
Sunpu Castle.
My Lord, there
was something I would
like to say to you, if I may.
Something stinks.
My request is something I wish
you to accept at any cost.
It-- It concerns the
match to be held...
September 24th
inside the castle walls.
Please do not force the
swordsmen to use real blades.
I beg of you to stop.
Their swordsmanship
can be represented
fairly using bokken...
To use real katana would be a
waste of these
highly skilled men.
The country is at peace now...
Sunpu Castle is bound
to Tosho-Daigongen-sama.
To violate the Castle's garden
with blood at a time like this
would be seen as defiance
toward the government.
It would bring nothing but
despair to his
lordship's family.
Therefore, on behalf
of those swordsmen,
I will show you the result
of using real blades.
This is what a real sword...
would do to those men...
This is it... my Lord.
Suruga is worth
550 thousand koku.
Are you saying, my Lord,
that you would desire
this match even if it were
to cost you that domain?
You... fool...
September 24th...
The same year.
Indeed it is a pointless
thing to lose such
skilled samurai in a
match using real swords.
However...
Who can stop our Lord?
Who can stop him when
even Torii-dono sacrificed
his life and was still ignored?
We all know, quite well, that a
samurai's life is not his own.
The highest honor
a samurai can achieve
is to die in the
name of his Lord.
Mie-dono.
What is the matter?
I saw you.
I had a vision of you and you
were winning the match.
Gennosuke Fujiki.
It is time for your match.
At the pleasure of our Lord,
the match will now commence.
Yes, sir.
On the west, Gennosuke Fujiki!
One arm?!
If I remember
correctly this is the
man recommended by you, Saegusa.
You are correct.
Have you lost your mind?
The only thing a one-armed
swordsman can do out there is--
Is win.
But Hyuga-dono...
Ah... You use the Kogan style,
which is said to be
unrivaled in the Noubi area.
Gennosuke Fujiki.
You come recommended by
Chief Retainer Saegusa-sama,
the Lord of Izu, correct?
To be safe...
I must now give your
body an inspection.
Please...
Take your time.
A wound of defeat...
Is it acceptable to bring such
a man before our Lord?
It was clear to me
that he had been
diligent in developing
the muscles on his back...
...to compensate
for his missing arm.
On the east...
Seigen Irako!
Iku...
I will be fine.
A cripple?
And that is not all...
He's blind...
Gennosuke Fujiki.
Seigen Irako.
Without hesitation,
please exhibit to the
greatest extent of
your abilities,
your sword skills for our Lord.
A one-armed man
versus a blind cripple.
To stain the garden
with such a show.
It is unworthy of
being called martial arts.
There is no excuse for it.
Enough.
Look at them, Asakura.
To swordsmen of
such indomitable spirit...
...they will take this
cruel fate given them...
...and use it to
stir their souls...
...until finally...
That stance...
I have not seen it before.
There it is...
Irako-sama's certain
victory stance.
Mumyo Sakanagare!
Fujiki-sama...
I want you to slay him.
Please kill Irako.
I detest him so...
...so very much.
You damn monster.
I cannot...
read their swordsmanship.
Their swordplay is...
abnormal.
Gen-na Year 8.
To-otomi Province.
Here it is...
Tsuba-zemari.
A tough move...
He is not even able
to say, "I give up."
I...
That will be enough.
Fujiki...
Could you not have tried and...
How do I put this...?
Gone easier on him?
Ushimata-shihan...
They will never
learn unless it hurts.
Reporting!
A man with another
style is at the entrance.
My name is Seigen Irako...
I am here to
challenge your Master...
Iwamoto-sensei.
Father!
Father, a man with another
style has come to the dojo!
Master...
No...
I beg you, please...
Oh!
Father!
Challenging our dojo?
Very well.
I will let our sensei know.
However, the rules of this dojo
state that you must first
face two of our apprentices
before you can challenge sensei.
That will be fine.
Matching our apprentices
against swordsmen
of other styles is a
vital part of training.
As vital as the rules
governing the match itself.
Yet, regardless of
whom is victorious
at the end of the match...
...no grudge of any
kind should ever be borne.
Treat with courtesy...
Swordsmen of other styles.
Killing them, of course...
Is never allowed.
We give them a new look...
And send them back.
Make the bodies of those
who challenge us a living
message that shows the
strength of the Kogan style.
This will raise the reputation
and fame of the dojo.
Unnecessary.
Unnecessary...!
That bastard's red lips...
They are unnecessary
for swordplay!
It seems the tip of
Fujiki's sword is fired up.
And the young
upstart jumps right in.
Now.
Tsuba-zemari.
I will crush him!
He missed his chance.
What is happening?
Something is wrong with Fujiki.
Interesting...
Yubi Garami.
Enough.
Assistant Instructor!
Shihan-dai!
Fujiki Shihan-dai!
It is nothing.
This is not over.
This...
This is not over yet...
Do you hear me?
I am certain you think that.
I said 'enough'.
This is not... over yet...
This is not over yet.
Fujiki...
Do you hear?
Yes, Fujiki, I know.
I will be the next
person you face.
So it is to be another
sparring match using bokken?
Now, please...
forgive my rudeness.