♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ wicked Lady Iku
comes this way ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ she is Tiger's
mistress, beware! ♪
♪ As the morning
glory vendor gazed ♪
♪ slowly on the face of Iku ♪
♪ A flower of crimson
bloomed that day. ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ Iku called the
name of her fiancé. ♪
♪ The man was a kimono tailor. ♪
♪ A kesa robe of crimson
bloomed that day ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ When a wise man
from the magistrate ♪
♪ came to visit
Iku in her store ♪
♪ An apron of crimson
bloomed that day. ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ Wicked Lady
Iku comes this way ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ she is Tiger's
mistress, beware! ♪
♪ How cruel, how cru-el ♪
♪ wicked Lady Iku
comes this way ♪
You show
much improvement...
You will soon be
ready to write on paper.
Hold it...!
I object...
Hold that last move.
I cannot hear you.
No holding in a
duel with real swords...
A senior apprentice
acting this way
is not fit to look
Fujiki in the face.
A fine job you did in
slaying the Funaki brothers.
Irako did
as much as I.
You killed the older
brother, Hyouma, first...
Irako only took advantage
of that opportunity.
Correct...
From a strategic angle,
you practically
killed them both.
Regardless, I wish
I could have seen it...
Irako must have
been quite astounded,
witnessing the
Kogan Style secret
technique Nagare for
the first time.
The "Number One Ladies
Man" of Kakegawa
has probably lost face.
How cruel...
how cruel...
Do you not place any
value upon your life?
One cannot die by
simply enjoying a hot bath.
The "How cruel,
how cruel" song is not a lie...
Men who come close to
me--well, you know the rest.
He's one of
Master's apprentices...
Seigen Irako...
My lady, there is something
I want to tell you.
Do you always do this?
The sword is a samurai's life...
Are you warm enough?
Please continue...
It is curious...
When I was ten years old,
my father ordered
you to hold metal sticks
thrust into hot coals...
I remember...
Even when the smell of
burning flesh filled the room,
your face never flinched...
Your eyes that day
filled me with fear.
The curse I bear is real...
Two men have
taken me as their wife...
And two men
have ended up dead...
Yet even though
my curse was to blame...
Master continues
to show me kindness.
Are you familiar with the
sword called
"Nana-cho Nenbutsu"?
Nana-cho Nenbutsu...?
If I recall,
it was left in Master's
care by the Shogun Lord.
What I now tell you...
...is the tale of Sensei...
...and how he came to
keep that sword.
This Wazamono,
given me by Lord Yorinobu
is named "Nana-cho Nenbutsu"...
Which means
"The Half-Mile Prayer."
His retainer,
master swordsman
Lord Nagakatsu Tamiya,
used it on a Beggar Monk
in a roadside shrine...
While the monk was
indeed cut, he kept walking,
reciting his
prayer to Buddha,
without shedding
a single drop of blood.
Only after he
walked nearly half a mile...
...did his wound open
and blood gush out.
Tell me, Kogan...
Do you think this story is true?
I shall try it myself.
L-Let's go...
No use fighting.
I suppose it
was merely a rumor...
Or have your skills grown
weak with advancing age?
This sword cannot
be called a Wazamono.
It should be called
an accursed blade.
Entrusting it to one such
as you would surely
bring misfortune to his
lordship's family.
Is that right, Kogan?
My Lord...
Your time is done...
Then my fiancé...
The official who was killed...
Are you saying
Master did it?
I am his apprentice...
I cannot say anything more.
It is ludicrous to think of...
The man I have
been sleeping with...
...is responsible for
killing a man I loved.
The truth remains unclear...
But, what I want
to say to you is this...
You are a perfectly
normal woman...
That children's song...
is a joke.
♪ How cruel,
how cru-el... ♪
So, Ushimata-Shihan...
What is it that you
needed to discuss?
Sensei is thinking
about arranging a
marriage for Mie-dono...
to either you or Fujiki.
And become successor
to the Kogan Style...?
It is far more
than I deserve...
Let me tell you one thing...
You would be wise
to stop your frequent
visits to Lady Iku
in Togiya town.
What--are you talking about?
I followed you...
...from the bathhouse
the other day.
Oh that...
She felt dizzy
after a lengthy bath...
I was merely
escorting the lady home.
She had expressed
a growing fear of
the rats infesting her ceiling
space, and I offered to
stop by occasionally
to rid her of them...
I have done
so several times.
I have done nothing
to be ashamed of.
Do not insult me.
Irako...
...if Sensei were to become
aware of what you are doing...
I understand fully,
Shihan...
I will not
visit lady Iku again...
So he wants to give me
that virgin daughter of his...
If those are
Sensei's orders...
...how can I ignore him?
December,
in the First Year of Kan'ei.
The Kogan Style's
final training for the year...
...the Performance
of Mutou-Dori.
Sensei!
Father, please...!
What do you
want from me...?
What have I done?
Cuh--
Cuh--Conceive!
All due respect,
Mie-dono...
If I understand him...
Sensei wishes...
...for you and I to
have physical relations
right here and now.
Cuh--
Cuh-...
Conceive!
For a samurai family...
...a wedding ceremony
is a solemn act...
...performed to
continue the family name
and give birth to an heir.
There is no
room for the
personal feelings of
the betrothed...
All decisions are
made at the judgment
of the head of the family.
Utterly deplorable...
I take my leave of this farce.
Mie-dono!
It is nothing.
Ignore my father...
He is more deplorable
than usual today.
It is in your best interests
to leave here now as well.
Ushimata...
Out of my way!
Please return to
where you were seated.
Sensei has chosen Seigen
Irako to be your husband.
It is vital to the security
of the Kogan Style.
Fujiki...!
Those eyes...
The same eyes
he had that day...
Puppets...
Men are all puppets...
And I am a tool
for giving birth...
But the fruits
I bear will be rotten.
I'll kill myself...
I'll bite off my own tongue...
and kill myself.
Please forgive
my impertinence...
If I force myself
on her now...
Mie-sama will
take her own life.
If that happens...
your family line ends.
For her sake...
...and that of
the Kogan Style...
Allow us...
...to continue
after the wedding.
My--my heir...
It is born!
Seigen Irako was no puppet...
He was something
far more horrific...
Irako-sama...
What have I done
to warrant this punishment?
Do not worry...
I will not do anything violent.
Irako-sama...!
What is this...?
The Kogan
Style successor...
The Kakegawa Domain
Martial Arts Instructor...
A fief of 300 koku...
The Suruga Domain
Swordplay Instructor,
Tamiya,
the Lord of Tsushima...
800 koku...
The Shogunate Family
Swordplay Instructor,
Munenori Yagyu...
3000 koku...
How far will my
swordplay take me?!
It is a joyous day today...
It is a joyous day...
Sensei has made his choice...
Irako...
I am Iemon Shigaraki
of the Funaki Style...
To avenge Hyouma and Kazuma,
I shall take your head.
It was not you, was it...?
Your hands lack
the skill to have
defeated the Funaki brothers.
Impossible...
So fast...
From his
frozen fingertips,
a new technique
was suddenly born...
And it was good.