Mie-sama...
Fujiki...
You are not eating...?
Is something wrong?
Um...
What does it feel like...
when you cut through a person?
Hmm...
...the sound is not unlike that
of beating on a wet towel.
If you cut well, however,
you do not feel a thing.
Dinner is good tonight.
It was Mie.
Slay her.
Slay her, and bring it back.
It is uncanny.
Mie-sama...
I have no choice.
For the Kogan Family.
Mie-sama.
Mie-sama...
With a sword
over her shoulder...
Hold these for me.
This is dangerous...
Mie-sama's Nagare must be--
It is imperfect...
And that imperfection...
...is precisely what
makes her such a threat.
Fujiki...
Why would Mie-sama
take a cursed sword?
She is only a woman.
Soon...
Soon, he will come for me...
You will have to say that again.
It is my belief that...
the killer is Seigen Irako.
Seigen Irako
committed the murders...?
Why do you say that?
When we punished
him three years ago...
it was Shinpachiro Munakata
who gave him an imitation sword.
And Munakata's body was found
with such a sword in his mouth.
By the same token,
Kurouemon Yamazaki branded
Seigen with a hot iron...
And his body was found
with a burned cheek.
Furthermore, the place
where Suzunosuke's
head was left on display...
...was where we all
cornered Seigen when he
first came knocking
on our dojo's door.
Irako is a blind man.
Another blind swordsman,
named Seigen Toda,
famous during the
Period of Warring States,
once found himself ordered
to a match by his lord.
Once he neared his opponent,
he pummeled the
man with a wooden stick.
Because he could not see, it
was the only way he could fight.
That is what the swordplay
of a blind man is like.
Irako is hiding.
Somewhere here in Kakegawa.
Ah, gentlemen...
Does Iwamoto-sama
require my services?
No massage today.
So, what does bring
you gentlemen here?
Have you heard anything about
a new face among the Zatou?
New face...?
Well, as you can see...
...uh...
...and as you know,
we Zato are blind.
We never see a new face.
There is one in
particular whom we seek.
And we know how tightly
knit your blind guild is.
You are speaking about
Toudouza, are you not?
If you are looking for
a Toudouza member...
...why do you not
ask Kengyou-sama?
Ken--...?
Kengyou, you say...
We cannot receive an audience
with Kengyou due to our class.
You know this, and yet you still
suggest we meet with him.
Toudouza is an
autonomous organization.
Kengyou Shizuhata is the
highest ranked man in it.
He once played a biwa
lute before Lord Ieyasu,
the Tosho-Gongen, and was given
excessive distinction for this.
With his acupuncture skills,
he is currently the
personal physician of
Tadanaga Tokugawa, the Suruga
Dainagon and the Lord of Sunpu.
How touching it sounds...
For music played
by a person of sight.
Preparations for your audience
at the castle are complete.
Watch your back.
Same to you.
Hikobee Mariko...
He possesses
Herculean strength,
second only to
Gonzaemon Ushimata.
Each part of his body,
without exception,
is a complete weapon
in and of itself.
This room seems much larger now.
His dominant hand...
it must have festered.
Here is your payment
for the three tigers.
Thank you very much.
But tell us, Okitsu-dono...
What about the
three who still remain?
With those three?
It may take longer to
find the right opportunity...
It is rare they
drop their guard.
So, they are the true tigers.
Exactly.
I will take my leave now.
Okitsu...
Was Irako in the house
you just came from?
Fujiki...
...are you going
to spend the rest of
your life in that room
for the Tiger's cubs?
You still think there is a
future for the Kogan Style?
The Kogan Style's future...
is within Mie-sama.
Mie-sama?
You fool!
The vessel called the heart...
Once it cracks...
...once it cracks it
can never fully be--
It will never heal!
This technique
is something I stole...
...from you Fujiki!
When we punished Irako...
...you recklessly showed
this secret to everyone...
The move that took
you so much effort...
See how inept you are...?!
You bastard!
Fujiki...
As I suspected...
You are...
on another level...!
That room...
For the Tiger's Cubs...
Today, becomes even larger.