We need to take cover!
It hurts.
It hurts so badly.
Bertholdt...
It hurts...
It hurts so badly.
Wait, are you...?
Whoa. Sasha!
You're in horrible shape.
What happened to you?
You're up!
Eren.
Armin. I'm so glad you're back.
'Bout time.
Captain!
What happened?
I saw Bertholdt transform,
but then everything gets kind of blurry.
Did we fight them off?
Is everyone okay?
It sounds like your recent
memory was just about wiped out.
Huh?
Eren. Tell him everything.
Okay. Are you up to speed now?
Yeah.
We won.
But of the Scout Regiment,
there are only nine soldiers left alive.
The nine of us.
That's what it looks like.
The fighting ended four hours ago.
We've been searching for survivors, but... no luck.
So, to be clear, we resealed
Shiganshina's gate, securing Wall Maria.
Reiner and the Beast Titan escaped,
along with that quadruped.
You managed to capture Bertholdt.
And then, with both the commander and me wounded,
you had to choose which of us to give the injection to.
And you did.
I transformed into a Titan and killed Bertholdt.
I ate him.
Here.
Why though?
Why'd you pick me?
No matter how you look at it,
Commander Erwin's the one humanity needed the most.
Captain!
Why'd you give me the injection?
Tch. Hey.
I thought I told you to tell him everything, Jaegar.
There was a short debate.
Your friends here argued that you
were the one we needed to revive.
And when I disagreed, they staged a little mutiny.
It's true.
Punish us as you will.
You'll certainly be disciplined for your insubordination.
But getting punished isn't the same as making amends.
I know.
Thing is,
I was the one who chose to revive you in the end.
Or no.
It's more like I chose this to
be the place where Erwin died.
Sorry. I just don't understand.
How could letting Erwin die be the right thing to do?
What are the Scouts without him?
If he's gone, then how will we go on?
You're right, Armin.
I believe it should've been used on Erwin, too.
To be brutally honest...
Nevermind.
It's a shame we had to choose in the first place.
It's over now.
Erwin told Levi to use the syringe as he thought best.
And Levi chose to use it on you.
What's done is done.
Erwin's life and the power of a
Titan both rest on your shoulders.
No matter what anyone says, that's the truth.
It's part of who you are now.
Accept it.
Wait... so does this...
...mean that I need to become Erwin's replacement?
There's no way.
I can't!
Don't misunderstand us.
There's no chance in hell that you could replace Erwin.
That said,
your self-doubt aside,
you have a strength within you that no one else can claim.
Don't let any of us regret this.
Not me,
not either one of our mutineers here,
nor anyone else.
And especially don't regret it yourself.
Consider that your new mission.
Shut the hell up.
Yup. That's our Sasha.
She's always been one to speak her mind.
You know,
since Erwin chose me to succeed him as commander,
I'm more or less in the same boat as you.
We'll just have to grin and bear it,
while doing what we can.
I'll try.
Good.
Now that we know Armin's all right,
let's check out that cellar.
Eren, Mikasa.
You two can come guide me and Levi.
The rest of you stay. Keep an eye
out for hostiles from here on the wall.
...Got it.
Eren, do you still have the key?
I do.
Let's do this.
Eren.
Behave while I'm gone and I'll let you
in on what I've been doing in the cellar.
Agreed?
Eren!
How many times have I told you to stay out of there?
I don't get why it's such a big deal.
Because your father keeps his work tools down there.
Medicine, too.
It's dangerous for children.
Fine.
It's why I ask your intentions.
They could be the key to turning the tide forever.
You could save us.
Intel suggests that the cellar of Jaeger's home in
Shiganshina holds a vital secret regarding our enemy.
We will form an expedition to find this secret.
With that achieved,
we may finally be able to break free from the Titans,
and bring an end to their hundred-year reign.
Well, takes us to your house.
Yeah. Right.
Is this the place?
Hey, Dad!
When'll you show me what's in the cellar?
Well,
perhaps when you've realized
the most important thing of all.
Luckily for us, the fires burnt
out before they got this far.
This is it.
The stairs to the cellar are beneath this door.
All right.
That's a relief.
I was worried that it might've flooded by now.
Let's go.
Do it, Eren.
Right.
You okay?
What's wrong?
Hurry it up.
I can't.
The key...
It doesn't go to this door.
What?
That doesn't make sense.
I'm sure it's the key that Dr. Jaeger had.
Step aside. I'll open it.
Wait, what?
That'll do it.
It almost feels like a laboratory down here.
My dad was a doctor,
so he was always cooped up down here mixing medicines.
That makes sense.
Actually, if we assume that
all of this is labeled accurately,
most of it seems to be widely available.
And all of the books on hand relate to medicine.
This looks like a normal doctor's study.
There isn't a single thing here
that would rouse my suspicion,
as I'm sure your father intended.
Right.
If you wanna hide something from the Interior Police,
you wanna be sure not to give them any leads.
Hey.
Don't just stand there, get to work.
Erwin's hunches are rarely wrong.
Right.
Thanks for the drink, Mikasa.
Looks like another all-nighter.
Eren.
Hm?
Look. I found a keyhole.
Try it.
That got it.
It's empty?
Look closer.
There's a false bottom.
The cloth smells like peppermint oil and charcoal.
Guess he was using these to ward off moisture and bugs.
If what we were looking for exists, then we've found it.
After all this time,
Dad might finally explain himself.
Then Erwin raised his hand
and asked the strangest question.
"How can we be sure there aren't other
humans living far away from the walls?"
His thinking was that since we'd never
been able to search freely beyond the walls,
we had no way of confirming that the rest of
humanity had been wiped out by Titans completely.
And yet, that's exactly what our historians would claim.
Hmm?
Think.
If our history books would claim to be unbiased,
the phrasing should be "it's believed
that the rest of mankind was killed."
If I'm being honest,
I feel like you're just splitting hairs here.
I'm not!
This was a deliberate choice they made!
These books...
They're commissioned and issued
by the royal government itself.
Get it?
Their intent is to make us
believe we're the only humans left.
Maybe they just assumed.
Aren't you reading a little too far into this?
Back then I made fun of his theory,
but he may have been right.
If he is, you'll just have to apologize to him.
Look there.
The sun's rising.
If our heroes are going to return, it should be soon.
Um! Pardon!
But the Scouts came back a moment ago!
They did it! They reclaimed Wall Maria!
Is this a painting?
Let me look closer.
No.
This is far too detailed to
have been drawn by a human hand.
Uh... hey.
There's writing on the back.
"This is no illustration.
It was made by gathering the
light reflected off the subject"...
...and burning it into an image on special paper.
Looks quite nice, right?
Where I'm from,
there are many amazing technologies like this.
Mankind isn't gone.
Beyond the walls,
countless humans live in comfortable refinement.
I pray the person who finds
this book will be a fellow patriot.
Hurry, Fay! If we're not fast, we'll miss it!
Wait up, Grisha!
Not so fast. Come here.
Don't forget again.
You can't go outside without your armbands.
And Grisha,
you mustn't go past the walls for any reason.
Hey, wait for me!
Don't worry, Mom, we'll be good.
Yeah, we'll see ya later, okay?
...So where to?
...This way. Come on!
When I first considered
how best I should start my story,
my thoughts turned to that day at once.
Hey!
...Grisha?
...Sorry 'bout that!
Watch where you're going, will you?
And slow down a bit!
Aww, it's leaving.
I love it!
When I'm rich someday,
I wanna ride in an airship
that looks exactly like that one!
What are you talking about?
There's no way either of us'll get rich.
I know, but it's nice to pretend.
I wonder what all we could see from up there.
There it goes.
...Come on, Fay! ...Hey! Wait!
Where are we going?
My teacher told me something.
He said the airships land at a place nearby.
Let's go and watch!
Really?
But Mom said we shouldn't leave the walls no matter what!
It'll be fine! We'll just be gone for a minute!
...Be right back, sir!
Stop right there!
The fateful day that I, just a naive youth,
was made to face the truth of this world.
His story began when he took his
sister's hand and stepped forward,
while gazing up at the sky.
The hope and hatred in his eyes show Eren
a world far from his own, but just as cruel.
Next episode: "That Day."