Levi and the Scouts clashed with Kenny's squad,
charging straight into their defenses.
All to find and rescue Eren and Historia.
However...
We'll re-form our defense at the fallback point!
Time to regroup!
I'm praying right now, Historia.
For God to return and lead mankind once again!
God my ass!
If it's such an honor to become him,
then why didn't you do it yourself?
I'm done with your shit, and
I'm not gonna let you murder me!
That's the spirit! This is gettin' good!
You get the hell out of here.
I'll deal with the rest.
Father.
Uri.
And Frieda.
Just wait.
Might be a way through. But it's blocked.
Shit. If only we had some more gunpowder.
Keep your guns trained on that entrance.
If we hold them here, we win!
That light.
Damn it. No.
Eren!
Everyone, brace yourselves!
Hey guys, this place is about to collapse.
Captain!
It opened up!
Okay, Armin! Moblit!
You two take Hange and find a way out of here!
Stupid bastard. What the hell are you doin'?
Just leave me, Historia!
That Titan's from your family!
Let him eat me and everything'll be all right!
Get out of here!
...Not a chance!
...Why won't you listen?
I might be an enemy of humanity now,
but I'm still your ally!
I can't be selfless, and I don't want to be a god.
But... when I see someone crying,
saying that no one's needs them,
I have to go and show them that it isn't true!
You're feeling like I felt for my entire life.
That's why I need you to be okay!
Uh!
Historia!
...Uh!
...Hey.
Mikasa!
Give me the keys!
Captain. All of you.
Conny, hurry!
Just leave me here. Forget it!
Hurry up and escape!
Stop whining! Ya half-naked weirdo!
We've got gunmen and a Titan coming at us, so pipe down!
Feet're loose!
Whoa. It's even bigger than the Colossal Titan. Crazy.
The ceiling. Look out!
Get back!
Damn it all, Rod!
You really screwed the pooch.
Here I thought you were the one man alive that
understood Titans, but you didn't know enough.
You dumbass!
Captain Ackermann!
No! Get back!
Damn it. We'll be buried alive!
Why? Shouldn't he be trying to eat me?
Should I transform?
No. My Titan would only get crushed.
Sorry. I can't.
I've been dead weight every damn step of the way.
This power never should've been given to me.
I can't be humanity's hope. I'm just too weak.
Armor?
C'mon. Stop playin' the tragic hero.
Of course you're too weak to accomplish
jack by yourself, but no one expects you to.
Yeah, calm it down.
We've been through a whole lot worse than this, man.
Not that I really wanna get used to it.
Still, it's gonna suck tryin' to fly through that mess.
I'll take Eren.
It's gonna take all we have to not get hit.
...So hold on for your life.
...Right.
It's useless. You know we won't make it.
So we should do nothing?
Wanna sit here and hold hands 'til we're crushed?
Or 'til we burn to death?
You know dying here won't make anything better!
Listen. I really hate that I do
this to you all the time, but...
You've gotta make a choice here.
I'm with you!
Eren!
I'm sorry. But since it's the end,
this one time, just let me.
Let me believe I can do this!
Whoa. What the...?
Come on! Get under Eren!
Caven!
What's going on?
Whoa, look out!
We just need to keep moving!
Section Commander! Are you okay?
Yeah. What happened?
What the hell is that?
If it's that big from a distance...
That thing must be at least twice
the size of the Colossal Titan.
It'll break through the wall in an instant.
What now?
We advance!
Eren.
Can you hear me?
Wake up!
Eren!
Not too shabby, Eren.
Even after we cut you from it,
the Titan hasn't disappeared.
This could be a game changer.
I almost forgot.
Listen, before I transformed,
I drank from a bottle that said "armor."
Gotcha. Guess that's all you needed to pull it off,
because this time you did it easily.
You saved all our lives.
You came up with and built everything
we see here in the blink of an eye.
It's not exactly pretty, but I can see its potential.
I bet this is how the walls were made too.
Guess what?
This means we finally have a real
shot at plugging the hole in Wall Maria.
We had a hell of a time getting here.
Took long detours.
Watched friends die.
But as ugly as it's been,
look at the position we're in now.
If we can pull it off, and retake Wall Maria,
I can finally go to the cellar.
But knowing what my dad did...
Mm.
Captain!
We've secured an exit, sir!
Hange's fine! Armin and Moblit, too!
I'm glad to hear it.
Eren!
You okay?
Uh! We're all safe, thanks to you!
But to be completely honest, when
I saw you run off into the light,
stumbling like a drunk and wailing like a baby,
I thought we were screwed!
You looked like an idiot and my fate was in your hands.
It was awful!
Quit your bawling! Have some dignity!
That's what I was thinking anyway.
Relax.
Let's go. We have a big-ass Titan to catch.
Hey. Here.
Uh! Damn it.
It's too hot. We can't get close.
Commander. We can't seem to distract it.
It's an Abnormal. It doesn't care about us.
That's all right. Fall back.
We know what direction it's going.
That tells us enough to make a plan.
We found Levi Squad! They're nearby!
They succeeded, sir!
They have Eren and Historia!
Erwin.
Anyone hurt?
Yeah, Hange took a hit.
Doesn't look like anything too serious.
You've done excellent work, all of you.
I've got a whole slew of things to report, but first...
Anything on that Titan?
It's Rod Reiss.
Look forward to hearing your thoughts on this.
Commander.
Time's short. We can't afford to stand here and chat.
Head back to the wall.
You're gonna let that thing drag
its fat ass all the way to Sina?
Well, more specifically,
I'm letting it continue towards Orvud District.
All right. Time to think.
First off, Lord Reiss was
after the Founding Titan's power.
And that power currently resides within Eren.
Thing is, the Founding Titan can only be
used at full potential by someone of royal blood.
But then, when a royal does
obtain the Founding Titan's power,
they suddenly take on the First King's ideology, which
means they'll refuse to do anything about the Titans.
Well, this certainly is a conundrum.
So the First King thinks this is true peace, huh?
I'm gonna have to go ahead and disagree with him there.
You know, we still have the option to go back.
We just need that Titan to eat me,
and Reiss will become a human again.
We could still have a true Founding Titan.
It's possible.
Wait, you don't mean?
It's worth considering.
Once Reiss turns back into a human, we could capture him,
and undo the First King's brainwashing.
Assuming that it can be done, it
may well open a path to save humanity.
Tell me, Eren.
If that turns out to be our best
bet, are you really willing to do it?
Yes, I am.
Eren. I can't let you.
Let's not forget the other option.
First off, the plan you're discussing is full of flaws.
For one thing, it might not be possible to
free my father from the First King's will.
And no matter how you restrain him,
if he alters everyone's memories, we're finished.
And consider how much there is that we still don't
know about the Founding Titan. This isn't worth the risk.
She's right.
It's not even guaranteed that Reiss
would turn back to normal if he did eat Eren.
That's just a hypothesis.
No one's actually seen it happen before.
Mm.
So far, we've only been led by destructive pacifists.
And if they'd kept the Founding
Titan's powers, that's how it would stay.
This is humanity's first chance to escape from them.
Eren. Your father wasn't evil.
He was trying to save humanity from the First King.
He stole the Founding Titan from my sister,
and then he murdered my father's wife and children
because he had no other choice.
Mikasa's life. Armin's life.
Everyone's life hinges on your
being able to control this power!
You mean...
Yeah, that's right.
The Doctor Jaeger I knew would only have done
something like that if he felt like he had to.
Agreed. He must've known of another way.
A way to save humanity without Reiss blood.
And that must've been why he
left you the key to the cellar.
What? Your cellar?
Oh, yeah, right. I'd forgotten all about that.
You mean it's actually important now?
Apparently, it is.
What matters most to me is that
we have a way to plug Wall Maria.
The way I see it, that makes our choice pretty clear.
You know, that's actually a fairly convincing argument.
For whatever it's worth, I think we
should stick with Eren too. But listen.
Are you sure about this, Historia?
That Titan's a major threat. It's not like we can
just let it wander around freely inside the walls.
Capturing it isn't an option... it's way too big.
Which means that...
...our only way forward is to kill your father.
Eren. I should apologize.
What?
Under the Reiss Chapel.
I really considered turning into a Titan and killing you.
And honestly, it wasn't to save humanity.
I just wanted to believe my father was right.
Even more than that, I wanted him to like me.
But it's time for me and him to part ways now.
Please have your squad stand by in the hall now.
They're almost ready to begin the meeting.
We'll be right there.
Historia. I forgot to tell you.
There's something we need you to do.
What's that?
This is an order from Erwin.
Once we finish off this Titan,
seeing as you're the true successor to the throne,
you'll become queen.
Wait. Queen Historia?
You're kidding, right?
The coup d'état was successful, but the
people won't follow military rule forever.
We need to give them a heartwarming story.
One where the rightful heir
retakes her crown from the pretender.
Oh, I see.
Hey. Uh, you heard what Historia was
saying earlier, didn't you, Captain?
'Cause, well, it sounded to me like, maybe,
in siding against her dad, she finally
broke off from that part of her life, ya know?
It's just like...
Like what? You have something to say, then say it.
Um. I...
Hey, Captain?
What Conny's trying to say, is that Historia
finally broke free from the Reiss family,
and decided she's more than just a bloodline.
So for us to force her into
another role, for that reason... I...
I just don't think it's fair.
It's fine.
Huh?
If my next duty is to become a queen,
then that's what I'll do.
But Historia.
I do appreciate your concern, but whether this
is "forced" on me is really up to me to decide.
And I've decided.
Captain. Before that, I have one condition for you.
And that is?
While my fate is still my own,
I want to put everything I have on the line.
Once you're queen, you can punch
that smug runt right in the face.
Sirs.
We have determined the Reiss Titan's location.
It's southwest, approaching Orvud.
It's fast. At this rate, it'll
reach the walls before dawn.
Right, understood. Commander Erwin.
I'm sure everyone here would like to hear your plan.
How can we evacuate the people in such a short time?
That's not part of the plan.
What's that?
The people of Orvud District
will need to stay exactly where they are.
But Commander.
At Orvud District, Eren and the
others face off against Rod Reiss' Titan.
Despite the danger, Historia is
determined to decide her own fate.
Next episode: "Ruler of the Walls."