Defend him!
To the last man if that's what it comes to!
Eren must reach the gate!
I don't want a single Titan anywhere near him!
They're trying to plug up the hole with that boulder?
That's insane!
They're gambling everything!
For all they know, if Eren gets eaten,
then their best hope'll be gone for good.
His death would be a problem for us, too.
If he goes down, I'll step in with my Titan.
What if he doesn't?
We risked a lot to make that hole.
Should we really let him plug it?
Yeah, we should.
Five years we searched for a lead like
this, and now we've finally found it.
Reiner? Bertholdt?
Sorry, but what were you talking about?
You're gonna "step in with your titan"?
And Bertholdt, you said you made that hole?
What is this?
Uh... Marco.
Everything you just heard was... a joke.
Have you guys lost it?
This isn't like you!
Focus on the mission!
Look, there are more Titans coming!
Let's go!
Humans can turn into Titans.
I know that for a fact because Eren did it.
The Colossal Titan appeared out of
nowhere, attacked Trost, and vanished.
The best explanation is that it's someone like Eren.
The same goes for the Armored Titan.
And if they are human,
then maybe they're hiding among us...
Reiner!
Reiner! What are you doing?
Please... no.
Say it's a joke.
Wish I could, Marco.
Problem is, you're too damn sharp for that to fool you.
Somebody help...!
Annie! You gotta help me!
What's going on here?
Reiner's acting crazy!
Get him off me!
He heard me and Bertholdt talking.
If we let him live, he'll expose us.
You shitheads.
What the hell?
A Titan! It's coming this way!
Annie! Take off Marco's ODM gear!
Huh?
Do it now!
Wait, why should I have to?
Back there, you risked your life to save Conny.
I saw you.
Why'd you put yourself in danger for him?
Seems to me you're becoming sympathetic towards the enemy.
You wanna convince me I'm wrong,
then now's the time to do it!
Think of your father.
He's waiting for you to come home.
If you and he are any different
than the filth within these walls,
then prove it, here and now!
Hey! It's almost on top of us!
Annie!
What're you doing?
Annie! I thought we were comrades!
Please! Please!
I don't wanna die here!
Don't kill me!
You did well, Annie.
This is what makes us warriors.
Reiner. Do we move out?
Not yet.
We have to let them gather up first.
I see.
They waited 'cause they want the Titans to win.
Just wait.
Why do this?
Why are you in such a hurry to kill me?
I don't get it.
How come?
Why aren't you even willing to talk to me?
Why?!
Hey. Why...?
Huh?
Why is Marco... being devoured?
Like I said.
I'm sure Annie's doing fine.
She's certainly isn't getting tortured.
Calm down and consider how unlikely that sounds.
If they so much as scratch her,
she'll turn into a monster that
can take on an army all by itself.
Don't forget, this is Annie we're talking about here.
I bet she's hiding somewhere,
practicing her kicks and what not.
She's fine.
Still, there's no doubt that her identity was revealed.
Annie's smart, but...
It doesn't sound like you're fully committed.
The hell's your problem?
I thought that all three of us came to an agreement.
Did I go to all that trouble for nothing?
We can fight again if you want to.
That said,
the next time that you lose to me,
I'll make you give up your armor to another warrior.
What? No.
I'll do as you tell me to.
Then pull yourselves together.
We have one objective.
Recover the Coordinate.
Do that, and we can bring this cursed history to an end.
It's gone on too long.
We can be the ones to end this.
So let's do it.
Understood, sir.
Till this is done,
I will keep Annie out of my head.
This is a living hell,
but we shouldn't put anyone else through it.
You're right.
This needs to end.
It's settled then.
War Chief Zeke.
Enemy forces are approaching.
They're at the foot of the mountain.
My brave warriors.
With this final battle,
we'll finish our mission once and for all.
Hot!
Ready?
Yeah.
Bertholdt.
I've told you this plenty,
but you and I'll be in separate positions,
so try thinking on your own for once, all right?
Uh, right.
You don't always have to wait for my signal.
Yeah. I know that.
You're supposed to have the most
powerful ability out of all of us,
but you never use it unless your told.
Honestly, I never saw you as reliable.
I know that, too.
Not until today.
We're gonna finish this here, yeah?
That's right.
And there's nothing they can do to stop us.
Hold onto that attitude until
you're back with your beloved.
Huh? I-I don't know what you're talking about.
Annie's pretty cold, but save her from a
dungeon and she just might see you with new eyes.
Hell, if you play your cards right,
she might mistake you for a knight.
Oh, and as for Christa.
We're gonna save her no matter what.
That's the promise we made Ymir.
Yeah. We'll find a way.
I'll see ya.
Don't let me down, 'kay?
I've got your back.
It's been a while since I heard Reiner transform,
but he still hasn't signaled.
Why?
Did something go wrong out there?
We did it!
We blew that bastard's head off!
The Armored Titan just bit the dust!
Ha... ha... We pulled it off.
You were a serious pain in the ass for us.
Serves you right! You scumbag!
What the hell are you crying for?
Stop! Get up!
We still have work to do!
Don't cry for him!
He would've done the same thing to us!
This isn't over!
We'll hit him with another volley just to be sure.
You okay?
I guess so.
It's not like we could negotiate.
Their side has the knowledge.
They make us look just as ignorant as we are weak.
We don't have the ability to capture
someone who can turn into a Titan on a whim.
Which means... there was nothing we could do.
Was that...?
That's the signal! It's time!
Use your Thunder Spears!
If we want him dead, we'll have to destroy his whole body!
That scream just now...
Was it for Bertholdt?
Hange, wait!
We need to fall back for now!
See that barrel?
I'm sure Bertholdt's inside!
If he transforms, we're done for!
C'mon, Reiner! Hang in there!
I'm coming!
They got us.
Shit!
Everyone, move away from the Armored Titan!
The Colossal Titan is falling towards us right now!
No.
Even at this distance...
...we'll all be caught in the blast!
Ground's pretty close.
It's now or never.
I'll blow this whole place to hell!
Reiner!
Are you...?
No way.
What the...?
He's still alive!
He must have transferred his consciousness
throughout his entire nervous system.
We talked about it,
but only as a last resort.
To think that he would actually need to.
It's hard to believe they cornered you like this.
Damn it.
Reiner.
I need you to do something for me.
You're gonna have to move just a little bit.
And if you can't, then I'm sorry.
Prepare for the worst.
I'm ending this war.
Here we go.
Our mission's primary objective
just fell straight into our laps.
You could call this a stroke of luck.
Hey! Look!
Someone's coming our way!
It's Bertholdt!
The plan is as follows!
Armin, you take command of Levi Squad.
Protect Eren!
Everyone else should come with me.
We've got two targets to eliminate!
Right!
Hold on!
What? Why?
This is the only chance we'll get to negotiate!
Stop, Bertholdt!
Just wait a minute!
Armin.
What are you trying to achieve?
We don't have to fight!
Let's talk this over!
If I agree to talk,
would you all be willing to lay down and die?
We only want two simple things!
Eren Jaeger, and the death of everyone in the walls!
That's the harsh truth of our situation.
Understand?
All of your fates have been decided!
What? And who is it that decided that?
I did.
What was that?
It was me, Armin!
I decided your lives should end here and now!
That's a real shame, Bertholdt.
See, I was hoping
I'd finally get to stop hearing Annie scream!
There's only one person who can save her
from the savages in the Military Police,
and that's you!
If you don't, she'll be fed to the pigs!
Fine by me!
Let them feed Annie to the pigs!
If they actually have her, that is!
What's the rush, Armin?
Didn't you wanna "talk"?
Bet you thought that by bringing up Annie,
you could make me lose my cool, like last time.
You thought I was still the timid fool you once knew,
and that you could trick me into letting my guard down!
Stay back, Eren.
You get it, don't you?
Your chances of beating him are damn slim.
This isn't your fight yet.
Shit.
Armin, why?
I know what this is.
You're just buying time, aren't you?
Half your comrades'll surround me.
And while I'm distracted, the
rest'll go and finish killing Reiner.
I can tell I'm right.
Look at the way you're shaking.
You're scared outta your mind, aren't you?
If you knew that much, then why're
you talking to me in the first place?
Because I needed to know...
...if when I faced all of you this time,
I'd start crying and beg you
to put me out of my misery again.
But...
...it seems like I'm fine now.
You'll always be my dear comrades,
right up until I've killed you.
But why?
Do you actually believe that we're the spawn of the devil?
No.
None of you did anything wrong.
I know you aren't devils.
Even so, you can't be permitted to live.
That's just how it is.
Mikasa!
Don't do it. We can't chase him.
There's no telling when he'll choose to transform.
If we don't keep our distance,
we'll just get caught in the explosion.
I don't think Bertholdt intends to do that just yet.
He must've seen how badly wounded Reiner is.
Transforming now would probably kill him.
Our best bet is to take Reiner hostage
and fight Bertholdt with our blades.
That'd make sense, but...
From the look of him, it seemed like he had a plan.
And not only that.
He seemed more determined than before.
Almost like an entirely different person.
Yeah. I saw it, too.
Hurry! The Armored Titan is weak!
We just have to finish him! Uh...
His nape's to the ground now.
What're we supposed to do?
This sure is a peculiar feeling.
I'm not scared at all, for once.
And I see everything clearly.
I know... that no matter what happens,
I can accept how this ends.
Yeah. No one's in the wrong here.
There was nothing to be done.
We had no choice in all this.
Because this world... is just that cruel.
He's going up! Don't tell me...!
But, if he transforms, he'll kill Reiner, too!
We need to get out of here!
Hange, look out!
Are you guys alive?
Hell if I know! Are you?
I'm fine. Hangin' in there.
Mikasa! Armin!
You two okay?
Yeah, it missed us.
Where's Hange Squad?
They were right underneath the blast zone.
Are you saying...
...the only ones who survived...
...are the six of us?
Oh, no.
Armin! What do we do now?
We can't just wait to get flattened by burning houses!
Hey.
You're in command now, Armin. We'll follow you to the end.
We...
We retreat.
Fall back to the commander and request new orders.
To beat the Colossal Titan in a battle of
attrition as planned, we have to keep our distance.
That was the plan, but think.
If we let the Colossal Titan reach
the wall, the others'll be finished.
He'll spread that fire to the houses past the gate.
Our other squads'll be trapped
between the Titans and the flames.
You're right.
Our only hope is to beat Bertholdt right now.
And we won't get help.
We have to do it with the people we have here.
Hey, Armin!
Your orders? C'mon!
What should we do?
I bet you're pleased with yourself.
Your plan's working so far.
What will you do next?
The Colossal Titan makes its move,
setting Shiganshina ablaze.
Meanwhile, Erwin and the others
are forced into a desperate charge.
Next episode: "Perfect Game."