My business with you is over!
Why don't'cha take a look above you?
Now where are Eren and Christa?
You can't win.
If you don't turn yourselves in,
then every last Scout we captured will get the noose!
I entrusted something to Commander Pyxis.
What happens next is out of my hands.
It'll be your choice to make. Yours and theirs.
That's a lot of wagons.
What's all that about?
You mean you haven't heard yet?
Pretty much all of the military
higher-ups are meeting inside the castle.
They're finally disbanding the Scout Regiment.
See? They're building those
gallows to hang the commander from.
He's probably getting his final judgement as we speak.
When facing your enemy, you
can't just guard with a shield.
You need a spear to dispatch the threat.
If you disband the Scout Regiment,
it will be akin to humanity tossing its spear aside.
Suppose that in this very instant Wall Rose was breached.
Once again, half of humanity would be
forced to flee. This time to Wall Sina.
But the earlier evacuation left us with
only a few more days' worth of supplies at best.
And when they run out, locals and refugees
will be forced to fight for survival.
Wall Rose and Wall Sina. All of humanity would split.
And a civil war would quickly erupt.
Even if the walls are not breached again,
Wall Rose is suffering from a perpetual shortage of food.
It may not be Titans that breach Wall Sina.
It's entirely possible that the
residents of Wall Rose will do it first.
Wall Maria must be reclaimed.
If humanity is to have any hope for the future,
then that is the way.
And you think that such an
undertaking requires the Scouts.
Our duty as Scouts has ever
been to charge forth at the enemy.
Cowering in wait behind these walls will solve nothing.
That's my belief.
Unless you have some sort of secret plan
by which we might overcome this ordeal.
A-hem. Commander, it seems you misunderstand what this is.
The reason we brought you here is not
to discuss our future within the walls.
Nor is it on account of something as simple as a murder.
Clause Six of the Charter of Humanity.
One must never prioritize their
own gain over humanity's survival.
You've broken the most sacred of laws.
Indeed. You have refused to hand
over Eren Jaeger time and time again.
And through this selfish action,
you've violated our charter.
But Eren is vital for the reclamation of Wall Maria!
That is not for the Scouts to determine!
Eren Jaeger is a Titan whose
abilities are far from understood!
To shelter him within our walls
is to put all of humanity at risk.
And the very idea of allowing a single
commander to have control of him is absurd.
As shown by the way you
maliciously schemed against the state.
Not only did you feign his abduction
in order to conceal his whereabouts,
you also slew Dimo Reeves when he learned too much.
This amounts to blatant treason.
It's not a stretch to describe
you as a threat to humanity.
Commander Pyxis.
The Garrison and Scout Regiments frequently
risk their lives side by side on the front lines.
How are we to know that you aren't working together now?
I am deeply disturbed to hear that you believe
we would align ourselves with the Scout Regiment.
There is nothing more senseless
than humans killing each other.
In this cramped bit of world that's been left to us,
it would take but a single spark to engulf all.
Just before the battle to retake Trost began
I said as much to the men I lead,
and then sent hundreds to their deaths.
If the Scout Regiment is that fatal spark,
then it should be smothered at once.
Think about it. What if the Titans did manage to break
through the wall only to find next to no one inside it?
The poor monsters might have to go hungry.
Ha! A-hem.
Very well, then. Let's begin deliberations.
Your Majesty. With your permission.
Erwin. Is this how you want it to end?
Now then, in the king's name,
I'll announce your final judgment.
Commander Erwin Smith.
You have been found guilty of violating
Clause Six of the Charter of Humanity.
Your sentence is death.
Your execution will be carried out at once.
Take him.
Erwin, is this what you wanted?
What about your dream?
Wall Rose has fallen! The gates have been breached!
It was just like Wall Maria.
The Armored and Colossal Titans appeared out of thin
air and broke through both gates in Calaneth District!
Currently, countless refugees
are flooding this way from the East.
Secure an evacuation route!
Order all available Garrison troops to make
for the eastern front and defend the people!
We must get those evacuees into Wall Sina!
Hurry and go! Saving the people is our highest priority!
Sir!
No, wait!
Hm?
I want every last gate to Wall Sina closed off.
Not a single refugee will be allowed inside this wall!
U-Uh. But all those people.
Everyone in Wall Rose will die.
You're commanding us to stand by
while half of humanity gets devoured?
Like Erwin said, if we let them
in, then we'll end up in a civil war.
The rule of law must be protected above all!
The government mustn't fail!
Uh! We can't be sure. That's only a
possibility... there's no guarantee that w...
It's enough that the possibility exists!
Our authority is and must always be absolute!
Now follow your orders!
Mm.
Damn it. To think that the wall would
end up getting breached at a time like this.
Although, there is a silver lining here.
We've already secured the power.
Before too long, the vessel will take it
and then our problems will end.
Very well. This is far from ideal, but
there's no point in losing our composure here.
We still have one wall, and
Lord Reiss should be back soon.
Agreed. We're still safe for now.
We have our orders. Let's get those gates closed!
Hold on.
The refugees are coming now!
Who should decide? Who has the right?
What's taking so long? Go do your duty!
Ignoring my orders is an act of treason!
Then I guess I'm a traitor.
...Say what?
...But sir.
I can't. I am a citizen of Wall Rose.
I refuse to shut the gates on those people!
...You dare to d...
...I stand with him.
Pr-Premier Zachary.
Did you find the way they reacted surprising?
Or was it expected?
Surprising? Not a bit.
Premier Zachary. What's the meaning of this?
That report you all just heard was fabricated.
There's no cause for alarm.
As of this moment, there have
been no reports of any Titan attack.
Uh! Bastard! This was all a farce?
It wasn't his plan. It was mine.
Pyxis?
It would appear that most of the Interior
Police are off rounding up Scouts somewhere.
Which worked out nicely for me.
What are you saying?
When you asked me, I declared to you in earnest that the
Garrison Regiment is not aligned with the Survey Corps.
But I forgot to mention something else.
We are not aligned with your assembly either.
That's right. Although I agree
with Erwin on several points,
I was still willing to put my trust in your government,
so long as you could prove yourselves
to be the better choice for humanity.
Because you have knowledge that we don't.
About both the Titans and the walls.
Had you shown that you actually gave a
damn about protecting the people you govern,
I would have stood by and watched
as you sent Erwin to the gallows.
In fact, depending on the choice you made,
all of us were prepared to forfeit our lives.
However. You've made it clear
that our suspicions were correct.
It's true that we soldiers know next to
nothing about the Titans and their powers.
But I daresay that despite this fact,
humanity is safer in our hands.
What? Don't be such a fool!
Just what do you expect to accomplish by threatening us?
You'll fail. The people will never obey you!
The monarchy has ruled for over a hundred years.
You would never gain the support of the nobles!
It would appear that you've misunderstood what this is.
You see, it's far more than a mere threat.
It's a coup d'état.
Interior Police have been subdued.
The capital is secured, sir.
Well done.
To be a soldier can sometimes mean
obeying your commander over your king.
And that's especially true when the king's a pretender.
He'll be exposed and replaced.
This is real? You plan to...
Don't think for one second that
this coup has a sliver of legitimacy!
Given the scenario you were presented with,
your choice to close Sina's gates
broke Clause Six of the Charter of Humanity.
Furthermore, you installed a puppet king in
order to seize the reins of power for yourselves.
This crime is known as treason.
Shit! Wake up!
What, is it dinnertime?
Oh, shut your mouth, you stupid oaf!
Well, Erwin. Looks like you managed to pull it off.
Wait. You don't seem happy.
I'm thinking.
Humanity is on a new path.
One far more dangerous than the last.
Huh?
And there you have it. The coup was successful.
Premier Zachary now has full
control of the capital and government.
For the time being at least,
the nobles seem to be staying in line.
Okay, but what about the incident with Mr. Reeves?
We got a public confession out
of one of the Interior Police.
Reeves' son Flegel really pulled through for us.
Come on! Don't you get it yet?
The government doesn't give a shit about saving any of us!
You can face the truth now,
or you can die wishing you had!
We have to do this! If Titans attack again,
all the things you're protecting will be gone!
There'll be no company. Our families will die!
Let's print the truth before that happens!
It's all written right there.
The abuse of power. The bogus charges against the Scouts.
And that King Fritz was both a puppet and a fraud.
It's clear that we only acted in self-defense.
In short, we're no longer criminals.
That can't be. They beat us?
Looks like Erwin's gamble paid off.
That it did. But it wasn't just Erwin who gambled.
Many people had to make a lot
of hard choices for this to work.
Whereas my choices got three of your people killed.
I'm sorry.
Here's the thing... the Interiors may have lost,
but not all of them know it.
They still have Eren, and Historia, too.
We need to find them quickly.
Right. I think I know where they might be.
Hm?
Let's get there and put an end to this fight.
Largely due to Erwin's actions,
it was declared that the old
system of rule would be dismantled.
Once the military had secured the capital,
they made the announcement immediately.
The declaration was given from the very
gallows that Erwin was meant to be executed on.
That's right.
It's exactly as Premier Zachary explained in his speech.
Please understand that our objective
here is not to establish military rule.
We intend to replace Fritz with a
monarch born of the true royal bloodline.
They'll be responsible for leading
humanity, and that includes us.
I get what you're saying, but
frankly, why should the people believe that your
king is any more legitimate than the one you deposed?
I'm sure you understand that
the people are quite concerned.
No one knows who to trust at this point.
For the sake of humanity,
it might've been better to let that government stand.
Like Commander Pyxis was saying,
they have far more knowledge than us, and
they've kept humanity going at least this far.
Even if they would've watched as
half of the human race perished,
it's better than letting us go extinct.
Should I have given up? Let them take Eren?
Surrendered my life, and put my comrades at risk,
and put my trust in their selfish wisdom?
Too late now. Instead, I endangered us all.
Your duty is as painful a burden as ever, I see.
Perhaps death would've been easier for you.
So tell me, why didn't you do as you just described?
...I'm not sure...
...Why don't I tell you my own reason?
I've hated those arrogant bastards for a long time!
Those self-assured pigs.
They'd feed from gilded troughs
and pretend their shit was gold.
Know what? I think I might grow to like them.
Now that the day I've dreamed of has finally come to pass.
Well, at any rate, if you hadn't done it today, I would've
given it a shot myself before I kicked the bucket.
I honestly couldn't care less about how this
coup of ours ends up affecting the fate of humanity.
Heh. I guess I'm quite the scoundrel, huh?
I'm telling you this because I know that you're the same.
You made the choice that would keep you alive.
Some part of you decided that humanity's
fate only mattered if you could live to see it.
I must be incredibly conceited to think that.
It's your turn to answer now.
Why did you risk it all just to bring them down?
I've had this dream.
Something to prove.
Ever since I was a child.
Hange. You said you might know where they are?
Oh, yeah. Guess I should explain how.
Erwin gave me this Scout report from
an investigation on Lord Reiss' land.
It details a certain incident that
occurred five years ago on the Reiss Estate.
Five years?
That's right. It was the day Wall Maria was breached.
I'll summarize the most
important parts from the beginning.
So, as far as regional lords went,
Lord Reiss was fair and well-respected by the people.
He had five children. The most well-known
of them was his eldest daughter Frieda.
She was a down-to-earth girl who even the peasants adored.
But five years ago, on that night, disaster struck.
With the fall of Wall Maria
having plunged the world into chaos,
bandits raided and set
fire to the only chapel around.
Unfortunately for them, the entire
Reiss family had gathered there to pray.
And so, the entire family was massacred
by bandits that night... save one.
Only Rod Reiss managed to escape with his life.
To top it all off,
this incident occurred just a few days before
Historia's mother was killed by the Interior Police.
So we know that in the immediate wake of
losing his family, Rod Reiss sought out Historia.
And something tells me that it wasn't
out of a newfound paternal affection.
Well, she is of royal blood.
Or do you think that bloodline has some other secret?
It's possible, but I'm not sure yet.
What really stood out to me at least, was the
fact that large parts of the chapel were destroyed.
The chapel was built from stone.
It would take a lot of time and effort to destroy it.
If it was bandits, they'd have taken
what they could and made a quick escape.
Also, Lord Reiss was the only witness.
No one confirmed his story.
Then Lord Reiss rebuilt the chapel with
his personal fortune almost immediately.
What was his rush?
When you think about it,
the story could only make sense
if it involved a Titan attack.
It may turn out that I'm jumping to conclusions,
but it's suspicious enough to merit investigation,
and it's the only lead we have.
What the hell?
Before the night is over,
Reiss' land will be crawling with our soldiers.
Unfortunately, we can't expect him to wait that long.
We have to get there as soon as possible.
Before Eren ends up in someone's stomach.
A Titan gains intelligence and the power to
transform by eating a human being with that power.
If that's actually true...
How and when did Eren first become a Titan?
And who did he have to eat to gain his powers?
Shit!
Historia?
Mikasa and the others head for
Lord Reiss' chapel to save Eren.
Meanwhile, a captured Eren learns a secret.
He learns of his father Grisha's unforgivable sin.
Next episode: "Sin."