Armin once told me that beyond the wall
lies a great expanse of water.
He called it the sea.
And I always wondered... what's beyond that?
Hey, Sasha, you even try to steal any more food, and we'll
have Captain Levi chop you into bite-sized pieces. Got it?
Who, me? I would never! Probably.
Hey! Did you guys wipe the mud
off your shoes before you came in?
Huh? Are you kidding me?
Do you not see all this stuff we're carrying?
You idiot. You really think an excuse
like that is gonna play with Captain Levi?
Bad enough I had to make your bed for
you this morning, now you pull this crap?
Oh, shut it! Who are you, my mom now?
We're back.
Wait, you were chopping firewood?
Gotta stay in shape somehow.
You got grabbed by a Titan!
You should be in bed recovering!
Think you're wasting your breath.
I caught her doing sit-ups earlier, too.
Oh, so you're a nag and a spy!
What? How the hell...
Mikasa, you know you're only human, right?
Funny. Almost feels like we're
back in the Cadet Corps, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Chaos. Makes you wonder why they
chose us for this new Levi Squad.
Protecting Eren and Historia is such an important mission.
Because we're all so talented, I assume.
Sasha, what did you just shove into your bag?
It's something that's definitely not bread.
Really? What did I tell you?
C'mon, put it back.
Hey! Can we focus here?
We've gotta finish cleaning before the captain gets back!
The bread, Sasha.
What's all the commotion?
...done this now?
You know we have to conserve our rations!
You really think you can just keep pullin' this crap?
Well I'm sick of...!
I am quite certain I gave you enough time.
Never mind. We can discuss your
utter failure at a later date.
Eren.
Huh?
Hange is anxious to get the experiment underway.
Right. Yes, sir.
Eren!
What's wrong, Eren? Get up!
The future of humanity depends on you, damn it!
Get up!
Third time, and his form's changed again.
He's not even ten meters tall,
and some of his body lacks muscle.
Plus, Eren's scrawny ass is hanging out.
I can see that!
Eren! Think you can still move?
Give us a signal or something, will ya?
Eren!
Mikasa, wait up!
Great. The brat's at it again.
Off to the rescue.
She never learns, does she?
There's no response. We're done here.
Eren!
Hot! Think you can ease up on the steam a little?
Hey, be careful with him. Can't you see he's bleeding?
You see his face, Moblit?
Sketch! Quick!
We gotta get this!
Section Commander!
Have you no compassion at all?
Um, sorry about that.
Not the outcome we'd hoped for.
We're still a long way from being able
to use Eren's Titan to seal the wall.
Yes. We've known all along this would
be like grasping at proverbial straws.
The plan's strategically sound. And simple in theory.
All we need is to get Eren there.
This could still work, but it's going to depend on him.
Experiment's over. All troops, withdraw at once!
Withdrawing! Go! Make sure we weren't seen!
Right!
You ride back to the house with Eren.
I'm going with Hange's group.
We're headed for Trost.
Sir.
You must find her with all haste.
She is the key.
She may know things we understand but poorly.
I see. Another failure, then.
Imagine if it had worked.
We could've plugged the hole in
Shiganshina in less than a day.
What we need is information.
It's not like there are books on the subject.
That would make things too easy.
We do have Christa... no, Historia Reiss.
Maybe she can give us some
insight into the nature of the walls.
I did some digging and found a
report about her life before the cadets.
The illegitimate daughter of Lord Reiss.
Hers was not a happy childhood.
Lord Reiss is the key to all this somehow.
Why would a mere regional lord
know the secrets of the walls?
Huh?
What are you doing? You should still be in bed!
I'm all right. I already slept a whole day.
Besides, it's my fault the plan got
shelved, so the least I can do is help.
No! You tried, didn't you? Don't beat yourself up.
All I care about...
...is getting a chance to bring down the Beast Titan.
That hairy bastard took everything from me.
I want it dead.
It's about time to switch lookouts.
You ready?
Must be nice.
You and the others know what you
want, even if it won't be easy to get.
But with Ymir gone, I've lost my purpose. I
don't even know what I'm fighting for anymore.
Saving her is something to fight for.
Mm. Maybe.
At the time, I didn't understand what she was doing.
I just wanted her to be safe.
Since then, I've been thinking.
When she left, Ymir chose her own path.
I have no right to change that. She doesn't need me to.
Finally. About time you started talking again.
Hm?
When we got here, you told us your story,
but then you just kept your mouth shut.
Stopped smiling, too.
Why should I bother?
Huh?
Sorry, but the sweet little
Christa you thought you knew...
Well, that girl isn't me anymore.
Good. I didn't really like her.
No one's actually as nice as you pretended to be.
It was unnatural, and, frankly, exhausting.
Oh.
Now, well, now you're just a normal girl.
Stupidly honest, maybe, but still normal enough.
Still, you don't have to decide about Ymir yet.
There's a part of me that still thinks...
How did I forget that?
Hange and the others are back!
We're meeting in the main room.
Now, what's this about?
I'm sorry.
Pastor Nick...
He was murdered.
Today. In the Trost barracks.
Hey!
Messing with our crime scene, Scout?
Don't get any closer.
This isn't your jurisdiction.
A simple robbery murder.
There've been a string of 'em lately.
I'm not buying it!
His nails were torn out...
Which unit are you in?
Section Commander Hange, Fourth Squad.
And I'm XO Moblit Berner.
Heh. You know, when your whole branch is garbage,
being high-ranked doesn't make you smell any sweeter.
Listen. That man wasn't killed by a Titan.
One person killed another. This isn't Scout business.
You're with the First Interior Squad.
Funny. What're the capital's MPs doing down here in Trost?
What's so strange about it?
Somebody has to get the real work done
while you people run around playing soldier.
Yes. You're completely right.
I see now I'm worthless compared to you.
Simply being in your presence is an honor.
Please, allow me to shake your hand!
All right. You said it was a robbery?
Poor Nick. I didn't realize he even
had anything that was worth stealing.
Of course he did.
Everybody knows the Church makes
all its little trinkets out of iron.
Are you saying Nick was affiliated
with the Order of the Walls?
What are you playing at?
He was a friend of mine, that's why I rushed down here.
Except... I thought he was a craftsman.
Making chairs or something.
I even put that on his application to board here.
Let go!
Still. I suppose this is a reminder that we
never really know people as well as we think we do.
Enough. Let go!
Of course! Sorry.
Well, then, I wish you luck with the investigation.
When you catch the culprit, will
you tell them something for me?
"You may feel that what you did to him
was justified, perhaps even righteous.
Well, I don't give a single shit what your motivation was.
I promise you, I will personally
see to it that you are tortured,
and the horrors visited upon you will
be greater than any my friend suffered.
Yes. Far greater."
Please pass that along.
We'll leave you to it.
The pastor. You think they killed him?
Yes, I do. That man's name was Djel Sannes.
The skin on his fist was split open.
Nick was tortured by the Interior Military Police,
and then murdered.
I figured the Church would want to get their hands on
Nick when they learned he was cooperating with the Scouts.
That's why I hid his identity
and had him stay in the barracks.
I never imagined they would use soldiers to kill him.
This was my fault. I should have been more careful.
They tortured him. Presumably for information.
Did they just want to know
what exactly he'd passed on to us?
Most likely.
But these are the Interior MPs we're dealing with,
so you can bet there's something deeper at work here.
Now, how many nails was the good pastor missing?
Uh?
How many? You saw, right?
I only caught a glimpse of him,
but all the nail beds I saw were empty.
People who talk, talk after one.
If they don't, ripping off more won't make a difference.
I'm impressed. I didn't think highly of Pastor Nick.
But whatever his faults, he
stuck by his beliefs until the end.
Which means... they have no idea
we know about the Reiss family.
But, the government is up to something.
And we've got a target on our backs.
Captain Levi, sir.
I have a message from Commander Erwin.
I went to tell him about Pastor Nick,
but he gave me this and sent me off.
Get your gear, now!
We're leaving.
Make it look like we were never here.
That was close. What if they had caught us?
Would they rip our nails off?
How did Commander Erwin know they were headed here?
The government's passed down some new orders.
There's been a freeze on all
Scout activity outside the wall.
We're to hand over Eren and Historia.
Captain. I didn't have time to tell you,
but some MPs came for the
commander right after I left him.
What? Like he's some kind of criminal?
They're bringing this fight out into the open.
No more working from the shadows.
They're going to protect the walls' secrets at any cost.
But why? And what exactly are
they after Eren and Historia for?
They don't want them dead, so what are they planning?
Who knows?
But they want these two and
they're not being subtle about it.
Which makes lingering here dangerous.
We'll move Eren and Historia to Trost.
We're taking them to the same district
where Pastor Nick was just murdered?
Heading toward the interior would be worse.
With Trost in a panic, it should be easy to slip in.
And if things do go all to
hell, we can use these in the city.
That's true.
We don't know the identity of our enemy yet.
I have an idea of how we can change that.
Hange, I'll need you to lend me some of your squad.
No problem.
All right, I'm going after Commander Erwin.
Moblit's with me. The rest of you will go with Levi.
Roger!
Hange!
Here.
I remembered a conversation between Ymir and Bertholdt.
I wrote it down for you. It's all there.
Thank you. I'll take a look at it later.
Hiyah!
Rather quick on the move, aren't they?
Heh. The kid may be small, but he's disciplined.
I'll give him that.
An acquaintance of yours?
An old one.
Try not to walk clustered together.
We'll stand out.
Eren and Historia, just act normal.
Why's the royal flag hanging everywhere?
Today must be the anniversary of the king's coronation.
Once a year they hand out extra rations to celebrate it.
Oh.
May I have your attention, please.
King Fritz has heard of the hardships in Trost.
He is donating the royal family's reserves.
Form a line.
There's plenty to go around.
Oh, thank goodness!
Long live King Fritz!
All that food and he's just giving it away?
It's not as if he needs it all.
Easier to control people when they're not starving.
Handing out those rations depleted
more than 60% of the reserves.
That's a steep cost just to
raise morale a bit, Lord Reiss.
Quite steep.
It was necessary. We had to do something to
improve the public's opinion of the royal family.
Now we just need the other pieces of the puzzle.
And the sooner we have them, the better.
The Military Police failed us again?
I'll return at once. We'll continue the hunt.
No, we'll soon have what we need.
Things are in motion now.
Behind us! Look out!
Armi...
Uh, I mean, Christa and Eren!
Those bastards are running off with them!
Will it really work again?
With that horse face of his, we look nothing alike.
Well, Jean. Good luck.
Yeah. So nice.
Let me hear how much you like it.
Well? How's that?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Come on, I'm dying to hear that sweet voice.
This is why I didn't want to go
through this shit a second time.
Screw being his body double.
Just give me one little moan,
lovely. You know you want to.
How's everything going inside?
If we wait very much longer,
they'll see through Armin's disguise.
He's... getting pawed at.
I see.
How's your leg? Any better?
I can move well enough. Now, then. Did you notice?
These kidnappers are obviously rank amateurs.
Why wouldn't they use professionals for a job like this?
You can handle the rest on your own.
I'm gonna make my way to Eren.
Come and meet up with me when
you're done taking out the trash here.
Yes, sir.
There's one more thing you should know.
Just in case.
Tell Armin and the others, too.
You're sure about this?
These are the two we're lookin' for?
Yeah, they fit the descriptions we were given to a tee.
Huh? Where's the guard?
What the hell?
Don't even think about moving.
Conny! Are these four really all of them?
Yeah, that's all.
No one else in the area.
Move again and you won't like where the next shot hits.
All right! First, we get these guys secured.
Then, we meet up with the captain.
What do you mean?
Those are his orders. He left a message, too.
Huh?
You there! Out of the way!
Captain.
Well?
The road's crowded, but I've seen nothing unusual.
It's not far to Commander Pyxis' from here, so I
think we're good, but how's the body double mission?
A success.
You don't seem very pleased about that.
I'm not.
Something's wrong.
Military Police can't be behind this.
They're too careful of their reputation to use amateurs.
This is more like...
...they'd know the wagon would be followed.
It's support team wouldn't be far behind.
Captain.
Wagon's almost on the move again.
Nifa, you've heard of Kenny the Ripper?
That mass-murderer in the capital?
The one who slit the throats of over a hundred MPs?
Of course, but I always thought
he was just an urban legend.
The stories are all true. He's no legend.
Huh?
I lived with him, back when I was a kid.
Yeah. Very funny, sir.
This isn't really the time to be making jokes.
That's right. He wouldn't care about using amateurs.
The team would trail the wagon from both rear angles.
They'd choose a spot high up.
Somewhere with a clear line of sight.
Nifa!
Long time, Levi.
Still a runt, or have you grown some?
Woo-hoo!
Nope. Don't look like you've changed much at all, boy.
Kenny!
Kenny and Levi meet again.
The enemy has their sights set on Eren and Historia.
In order to get their comrades back,
Levi and the others must take aim and shoot.
Next episode: "Pain."