I should've realized.
Of course this would happen.
Still... trusting your plan was the only choice I had.
But why?
Armin...
Why don't you ever run?
A Titan?
Damn it!
Just try and come closer!
Make one move to take him and I'll slit his throat!
Hold on.
Those markings around his eyes.
Are they what I think?
This must be the Beast Titan.
I found you.
Eren Jaeger, right?
If nothing else, I'll take him with me!
You don't look a thing like your father.
What?
Believe me, Eren.
I get it. I know how you feel.
The both of us are just victims of your father.
I'm sorry, but he's brainwashed you.
What're you talking about?
You're kidding.
He chased me all this way?
What a monster.
Let's call it a draw, Levi.
We're in no shape to fight now.
Bertholdt.
I'm sorry, but this is the end for you.
Eren.
Someday, I'll come back and save you from this.
Huh?
He ran?
Captain!
I just used the last of my gas.
Quick, give me your gear so I can chase him.
Right!
Hurry!
Reiner.
What's this metal case we
found in your left breast pocket?
Before we closed in and chopped off your limbs,
you used what strength you had left to grab at it.
So what's inside?
Suicide pills? A bomb?
Ow!
Sorry, Jean.
It's a letter.
A letter?
What does it say?
It's for Christa.
Ymir wrote it.
Whatever you do with me,
just make sure she gets to read it.
Only after we've inspected it.
Now then.
I've got lots of questions that you could answer, but...
...you're a tough one.
If you don't wanna talk, I can't make you.
So I'll ask.
Will you cooperate and tell us
everything that we want to know?
I won't.
Thank you, Reiner.
It helps to see that you're ready for death.
Hange, wait!
We... need him alive.
So we can steal his power.
Pay close attention.
I'm about to explain how we can
get maximum value from this syringe.
Using its contents,
we can steal any Titan's powers.
That goes for the Colossal, Armored, and Beast Titans.
As for how,
we first need to defeat one of these Intelligent Titans.
Then, we'll inject one of our
comrades, turning them into a pure Titan.
They'll be in that mindless state only for a brief time.
Once they consume the captured foe, they'll revert
into a human, but gain the power to shift forms at will.
If this is achieved,
then not only will we gain
knowledge and a powerful weapon,
we'll also be able to bring one of our
soldiers back from the brink of death.
Should you capture an enemy shifter,
be sure to sever their limbs.
Once it's safe to do so, try to locate Captain Levi.
We have only this one injection.
The captain will decide when to use it, and on whom.
We don't know the situation with Levi on the other side.
And we don't have the time to go and confirm it ourselves.
These Titan powers have exceeded
our understanding too many times.
We thought we had him before.
I refuse to underestimate his power again.
I'll start by beheading him,
but that's not enough on its own.
This isn't like you, Hange.
If we back down from the chance to cure our ignorance,
then what hope do we have of
beating the Titans down the road?
Jean.
We need to find out all that we can about the enemy,
or we'll lose.
Mikasa.
Yeah?
How much gas do you have left?
Not enough to fight anything.
I think I could reach Eren and Armin, but then I'd be out.
Well that's more than I have.
Find them, Mikasa.
Go and evaluate the situation.
Refill your gas, retrieve the syringe
from Levi, and bring it back to me.
If you're unable to do so, then regardless
of the reason, fire off a smoke signal.
That will be my cue to end Reiner.
Understood.
Thank you, Hange. I...
The decision was mine.
You were just a factor.
Why did I speak up for him?
When it comes down to it, am I still...?
Yeah! Hell yeah!
Armin's still breathing.
I hear him!
Keep going!
Don't give up!
You can make it!
That's Armin?
Captain! Get the syringe!
Turn Armin into a Titan, and
then we can have him eat Bertholdt!
Hurry up and inject him!
Right.
Hange!
What the hell?
They're running away with Reiner!
What now?
Shit!
Conny!
Don't chase them!
Huh?
Chances are, you'd just get killed,
even if you had gas left.
Son of a bitch!
This is all my fault.
He'd be dead.
He needed to die. Why'd I open my mouth?
I told you, the decision was mine.
Let's regroup with the others.
Levi...
Captain...
I finally found you.
It's the commander.
He's hurt!
His stomach is gouged, and his
insides are all torn to shreds.
The blood just won't stop!
I thought that injection might be able to help him, but...
...what do you think?
Huh...?
Captain Levi.
It's faint, but he's breathing.
Erwin.
You're alive.
You know what has to happen.
Erwin gets the shot.
You can't.
You told me you'd use it on Armin.
I'm going to revive the person who can save humanity.
Reiner.
You were incredibly lucky today.
You two.
Do you have even the faintest damn clue...
...what you're doing?
It's Erwin...
...the Commander of the Scouts...
...and you're telling me to watch him die?
There's no time for this.
Just get out of my way.
Eren. Check your emotions.
Sorry, Captain. Can't do that.
Tell me.
Why didn't you give Armin the injection right away?
I was thinking about Erwin.
Considering the chance that he might be alive.
But you couldn't have known that
Floch would carry the commander here.
There's no way you would've seen that coming!
You aren't wrong, Eren.
But the fact remains, he's here now.
So I'll revive him.
Hey!
He's too exhausted to stop me.
I could take it from him by force.
You know just as well as I do.
Without Erwin's leadership,
humanity can't beat the Titans!
He's right, Mikasa. Don't be crazy!
There's too much at stake here.
No...
It's the same with Armin.
He's just as important.
Eren!
Think about it.
Think about what he's done.
We used his plan to take back Trost with that boulder.
He's the one who realized what Annie was.
It was his idea to avoid the
Titans by coming here at night!
He's the only reason we uncovered Reiner's hiding spot,
and the only reason we defeated Bertholdt!
We only got this far because of Armin!
I can't save humanity, and neither can the commander!
But Armin can!
Tell him, Mikasa!
Please, Captain. Just let go.
You're just being selfish.
Erwin's our leader.
No. Shut up!
What? And why the hell should I?
Do you think you're the only ones
who've suffered through all this?
Not that you asked, but...
...on the other side of that wall,
there's not a single soldier left alive.
The Beast Titan threw crushed boulders at everyone.
That field is soaked with the blood of my comrades.
Commander Erwin was the only survivor I could find.
He came up with a plan.
Found a way for us to strike back at the Beast Titan,
and so we did.
My comrades were smashed to bits just as he'd planned.
I'm sure the last thing they felt was fear.
All-consuming fear...
When I realized the commander was still alive,
I almost finished him off myself.
But then...
...I recognized that would be a mercy.
And I thought to myself
that he ought to taste more of this hell.
Suddenly, I understood.
If we wanna stand any chance against the Titans,
we need a devil!
I realized that's what Erwin is,
and that it's my mission to bring him back!
That's why a coward like me
outlived the heroes around him.
Because Erwin needs to fight on!
So get out of his way right now!
Don't do it!
Hange.
No. Don't tell me...
No way!
It can't be.
No.
It isn't fair.
I understand how you feel, but most of us are dead!
We can't afford to lose our commander, too!
The Scouts must endure!
If we lose our symbol of hope, we lose everything!
I know that, but Armin could help us, too.
He's special!
You're right. He has an amazing mind.
That said, Erwin is far more experienced,
and he's a leader.
Listen, Mikasa.
There're people I wanna bring back, too.
Hundreds at this point.
Ever since I joined up with the Scouts,
every day brought a new farewell.
Hange, look out!
But... you need to understand.
Eventually, you'll have to let
go of everyone you've ever met.
I know that's tough to accept.
It's tough for me, too.
It's hard to stay sane living like that.
It hurts.
It really hurts.
I know.
But even so, all of us just have to push forward.
Captain.
Do you... know about... the sea?
It's like a lake, but enormous.
So big that it stretches past the horizon.
And its full of salty water.
Armin told me...
Hey! Stop making this harder!
He told me there's a sea beyond the walls.
He said that we'd go there together!
Thing is, that's been our dream since we were kids.
Only I forgot it a long time ago!
I want to avenge my mom.
I wanna butcher all the Titans.
The only thoughts left in my head are full of hate!
Yeah. And Armin's lost as much as I have,
but he just isn't like me.
He cares about more than fighting!
Everyone get out of here right now!
I don't want Erwin to eat one of you instead of Bertholdt.
Right. C'mon, Mikasa.
Shit. Shit!
Bye, Armin.
We'll miss you.
All right, then!
Let's start by finding the sea!
You'll see! It does exist!
If this dream of yours comes true,
what will you do then?
I don't know, and I won't.
Not until it happens.
I just...
...wanted to reach that cellar.
Good grief.
They're all the same.
Whining like brats about this dream or that.
All of us had to spend our lives drunk on somethin'.
Else we'd have no cause to keep pushin' on.
Everyone was a slave to somethin'.
There's more out there, though.
The sea!
Did you just...?
Excuse me...
...but how can we be sure that
there aren't other humans...
...living somewhere far away from the walls?
Give up on your dream and charge to your death.
Lead those crying children straight to hell.
We humans, we're all the same.
Every last one of us.
I'll reach the Beast Titan and tear him apart.
Thank you.
I needed that.
Guys, please!
Help me!
Annie! Reiner!
I don't get it.
Captain... why?
Do you think... you can forgive him someday?
He became a devil 'cause he had to.
We were the ones who put him up to it.
And in the end,
when he had finally been set free from this hell,
we were about to bring him back for more.
But I think... it's time we let him rest.
Erwin.
I told you I would kill the Beast Titan,
but that'll have to wait.
He's already dead.
Oh.
After learning of Bertholdt and Erwin's deaths,
Armin is shaken.
The path before him clear,
Eren heads for the place his father, Grisha,
once promised to show him.
Next episode: "The Basement."