Don't'cha think they have us spread out a little too much?
We're more likely to find them
if we're not all in the same area.
But why'd I have to get paired up with you of all people?
Spill it, Marlo.
You scheme this up so we'd get some alone time?
Look, Hitch. No offense, but
you weren't my first choice either.
Oh, is that right? Well, good for you then.
Anyway, doesn't this seem odd to you?
Why would the Scouts murder a
civilian and run for the hills?
This is the same group of soldiers who
consistently risk their lives for the sake of humanity.
Give me a break. Did you forget?
Think about what they did to Stohess.
The way they turned it into a battlefield.
How many dead bodies do you think we carried?
Annie's been missing ever since.
They still haven't taken her junk out of my room.
It's annoying.
But in doing so, the Scouts also uncovered
a Titan in hiding, and took it prisoner.
I highly doubt that the Military
Police could've done that.
How is disbanding the Scouts what's best for humanity?
Be quiet.
Listen closely.
Don't move!
Turn around slowly.
You must be a Scout.
Not a sound. Don't say a word.
Now listen, and do exactly as I instruct you to...
That's the way.
Now hand your guns to the one in front.
Don't say a word, right?
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Erwin.
I know this is sudden, but
it's time for your interrogation.
So, the Survey Corps murdered a civilian
in cold blood? You're sure about this?
I'm told that the evidence is strong.
But with that said,
I can't confirm anything I haven't seen.
So then, the Interior Police are
running this case without oversight...
...Hey, you cut that out!
I'm sorry about him, Commander Dawk.
Peaure here is still just a rookie.
He doesn't quite understand how things work yet.
Don't worry, the Interior Police
aren't a subject we plan to write about.
And the same goes for their new ODM gear.
Thanks Roy. See ya.
That new ODM gear worries me.
Those guns are useless against Titans,
but they're perfect for human combat.
It's as if that gear were
specifically made for killing Scouts.
Also, judging from the fact that
its existence was hidden from us MPs,
I get the impression that we aren't off
the list of people it could be used against.
Anyway. We should get a report from them soon.
Just be patient.
What's the rush, fat-ass?
Uh!
Way to go! That's a dead-end, idiot!
Dammit!
Shit, he disappeared!
Say what? Check the next alley!
He can't escape!
You're the son of Dimo Reeves, right?
What's your name?
I'm Flegel.
Flegel. Nice to meet you. My name's Zoë Hange.
This is sudden, but if the
MPs are trying to hunt you down,
then I'm assuming that you must know
the truth about your father's death.
Could you tell me how it happened?
I made us stop so that I could piss.
That's when the Interior Police found my dad.
There was a tall guy with a black coat and hat.
He slit my dad's throat.
Anyway, I'm glad to see that you survived.
Now we can make the truth known publicly.
You're crazy! Haven't you seen today's newspaper?
If the MPs say you guys did
it, well, then that's the truth.
My testimony means jack shit!
They figured out I was there.
The Interior Police know I saw everything.
I'll be hunted for the rest of my life.
And all I can do about it is
run and hide until I'm caught.
My life is over now.
Shit!
Yeah. Maybe.
Thing is, that doesn't exactly sound like living to me.
Try looking at it this way.
Instead of spending the rest of your life skulking
around like a scared rat till you get murdered,
you could stand up like a human.
And face your enemy even if they might kill you.
Why the hell would I?
Not everyone has the same
disregard for their lives as you!
Know what? Yeah, I am scared,
and I have every right to be.
Your family. The company.
Don't you think they deserve to know the truth?
Come on! That's just what would be best for you!
Of course it is!
You need to start thinking about what's best for you, too!
Hey! Who's making a racket over my roof?
All right, you're comin' with me, Flegel.
What? You're gang's already lost... just give up!
Why don't you know when you're beat?
That's real simple. Defeat is the only
thing the Scout Regiment has ever known!
Get past the checkpoint disguised as MPs.
Then snoop around until we find out where Eren is.
It's a shit plan, but it's all we have.
There's no time.
If we don't act now, we're finished.
Captain.
Hm?
Now then. You're Stohess District Military Police.
Private Marlo Freudenberg.
Captain Levi! It's really him!
Same assignment, Private Hitch Dreyse.
We'll need to dispose of you.
Because of what you did, Stohess was a graveyard.
Over a hundred people were killed!
Huh?
...Hey!
...You bastards.
I bet you all think you're some kind
of heroes of justice, but you're not.
You dropped dozens of innocent families
straight into hell on that mission of yours!
Yeah. We did.
Hey, you. You're from the Southern Cadet Corps, right?
So you trained with Annie Leonhart.
Were you a friend of hers?
No. She wouldn't have made friends there, either.
Way too gloomy and unapproachable for that.
She was just afraid of people, like a scared little kid.
Now I'll never get the chance to learn anything about her.
She's officially listed as missing... you know why?
It's because one of your Titans turned
her into an ugly red stain on the street!
Actually. No, it's because the Titan
we captured was Annie Leonhart herself.
Goddammit. It makes me sick.
Nobody knows a thing about this world.
Not us or anyone else.
Except for the bastards at the center of it all.
We're letting you go, but we need
to give ourselves a head start on you.
Annie.
Hey! Captain Levi!
Please, let me join in your cause!
I believe that the Military Police are in the wrong here.
If there's any way that I can
fight this world's injustice,
then that's what I want to do!
Easy. Calm down.
I swear, I won't let you down, sir!
No. I have no way of telling if you have
enough resolve to make an enemy of the state.
Let's go. Take them deeper into
the woods and tie them up, Sasha.
Sir!
Hey, Captain.
Would you let me do it instead?
Knock yourself out.
All right.
We'll forget everything we saw here.
I know ya will. Because both of you are about to die!
Ah! No! He said to let us go!
The captain might be a big softie, but I'm not.
I'm ready to do what needs to be done.
You have to believe us! We won't betray you...
we know that you're fighting to protect humanity!
Right? Tell him!
As if I'd take your word for it.
I can't trust you... not with that hair.
Who in their right mind would get a bowl cut on purpose?
So how can I trust a single word you say?
Uh!
Run, Hitch. I'll cover you!
What do you think'll kill faster?
That knife, or the gun at your chin?
Feel like tryin' your luck? C'mon, let's race!
Please. We're on the same side here!
Why the hell would anyone
believe you wanna join the Scouts?
My comrades are getting rounded up like criminals
as we speak... What makes you think we can win?
Because. You haven't quit.
Despite the odds, the Scouts are still fighting.
I made a mistake when I chose my regiment.
But you're a Scout.
You chose to risk your lives for others.
So I'll trust you.
What the...?
Horse-faced jerk!
Stop! He was just trying to test us!
Huh?
Are you crazy?
Even with my hands bound, I could've taken a swing
at you with that knife and done some real damage.
How did you know I wouldn't do it?
Don't ask me how, but you remind me of this annoying guy.
An idiot.
Makes me wonder. Is he one of
the fools Annie told me about?
Couldn't say.
All of us are fools.
Luckily for me, you're just as dumb.
Marlo, I think you proved your dedication.
This should be enough to convince Captain Levi.
We'll be counting on you from here on out.
Far as I know,
this is the least-manned checkpoint in the region.
Good. We'll handle things from here.
Get back to your squad before they're suspicious.
Right.
Marlo, Hitch.
We're grateful.
Sir!
All right. This time we're picking the fight.
Hm?
Stand down.
Captain. Isn't he...?
He's with the Interior Police.
I've got questions for him.
Let's move.
Thanks, dumbass. There won't be any
witnesses in an abandoned dump like this.
Damn it!
I owe you big time. Thanks a bunch, Flegel.
I mean, when you gave us the slip before...
back in that alley... I really thought I was screwed!
My boss would've killed me. I'm serious.
Thanks for comin' back, Flegel. Nice knowin' ya.
No! Wait. Don't shoot yet, please!
Why did my father have to die?
Did the Interior Police kill him?
What? I don't see how that matters to you.
After all, you're about to be
a corpse yourself in a moment.
Please! Before I die, I wanna know.
What did my father do for you to justify killing him?
Huh? I thought you'd know.
He betrayed us and started helping
out those bastards in the Scout Regiment.
So his orders... they came from the Interior Police?
You guys had him kidnap those Scouts?
Well, it was a different squad, but yeah.
Guess old Dimo didn't say too much about it.
At least not to his dimwit excuse for a son.
And what if he'd refused to do it?
Oh, he knew way too much.
We'd've killed him. I mean, we killed him
anyway, but that's what he gets. The damn idiot.
What made him think the Survey
Corps could help this trash city?
You would never understand.
Hmm?
You think you're real smart shit, don't you?
Wanna know the last thing my dad taught me?
He said a good merchant should trust his nose.
And I'm glad I listened,
because it lead me to the people who could avenge him.
And I side with them!
You're gonna die here, piggie!
No need to be brave... go on and squeal!
My business with you is over, asshole!
Why don't'cha take a look above you?
Ow!
Section Commander, that was way too reckless!
We pulled it off! Did everyone hear him?
No. The Scouts are here? But why?
This "dump" ain't abandoned.
Bet it seems unlivable to you.
Yet we're here. The place isn't half as
nice as it used to be, but it's still our home.
We heard everything.
About Reiss. And who had him killed.
Every last one of us is a witness.
Yeah? Well, it doesn't matter.
'Cause it's the government that decides what's true!
Idiots! Don't even think for a
second you can get away with this!
You're in for a world of...
Listen. You'll all be fine,
'cause The Reeves Company will protect you.
You trusted my father, Dimo.
Well, now I'm in charge.
So, from now on you can count on me.
That's a promise.
Glad to hear it, Mr. Reeves!
Speak up next time!
Glad to see you stepped up.
Hey. You give 'em hell, Flegel.
Right.
Hm!
Screw you.
Where'd they take Eren and Christa?
You bastards. You think you're so brave.
That post was manned by recruits.
They barely even knew how to wipe their own asses.
No one's gonna think you're heroes for beating them down.
Yeah, the guilt's tearing me apart.
But what really gets at me is this mouth of yours.
I'm gonna suggest that you start
talking while you're still able to use it.
Now, where are Eren and Christa?
You can't win. All that's left to you now
is to find some filthy corner to hide in!
Covered in mud and shit!
If you don't turn yourselves in,
then every last Scout we captured will get the noose!
Starting with the guiltiest one of all, Erwin Smith!
Hurts, right? That's what you
get for not answering my question.
Some Scout's lives are more valuable than others.
Only those dumb enough to agree to that join us.
Again, where'd they take Eren and Christa?
I-I don't know. Nobody told me, I swear!
Kenny Ackermann doesn't like to make his business known!
Ackermann?
I know Kenny. That his last name?
It is, but...
He never was much of one for sharing information.
Not important stuff, anyway.
But I bet you have a rough idea.
You'd best try to remember.
No. Stop!
You still have plenty of bones left for me to break.
Damn it. Are you insane?
Maybe.
Somebody's coming towards us!
And there's more than one.
Told you. You're beat. Struggle all you want.
One way or another, the Survey Corps will be destroyed.
You've seen better days.
Kinda funny. You were lecturing me just the other day.
Soon, you'll be sent before the king.
Then, his council will determine your
sentence, and what to do with the Survey Corps.
So you came.
Tell me Nile, where do you live?
Stohess, was it?
How's Marie?
How are your children?
I trust they're all in good health.
Marie and the kids are... They should be just fine.
I haven't been home in a while, but
it's in Wall Rose on the east side.
I see.
Why ask that? What's going on?
I entrusted something to Commander Pyxis.
Whenever that crucial moment comes,
what happens next is out of my hands.
It'll be your choice to make. Yours and theirs.
So, what did we learn from the interrogation?
Not much. Erwin didn't even realize that
Pastor Nick was with the Order of the Walls,
so Historia can make all the claims
about her name she wants and it won't matter.
They'll all amount to nothing.
What a farce.
They don't know it, but in truth they're nothing
more than cattle in a pen; simply waiting to die.
Hm?
My apologies. But Erwin Smith has arrived.
Very well. We'll be along.
Once Erwin has been executed,
all will be according to plan.
The secrets of the walls will be kept as safe as ever.
And the king's peace will be ensured.
Forever.
Erwin Smith. Do you have any last words?
In order to protect the kingdom,
they kept the truth of the
walls... and the world... hidden.
But in doing so, they invited an uprising of the people.
Next episode: "Reply."