Long time, Levi.
Still a runt, or have you grown some?
Woo-hoo!
Nope. Don't look like you've changed much at all, boy.
Kenny!
Boom!
Those gunshots?
Are we being attacked or what? Just stay down. Hiyah!
Historia!
Eren!
Hiyah!
Shit. They predicted our every damn movement.
Of all people,
why the hell would you work with the MPs?
It's Levi of the Scouts!
Make yourself at home, sir!
Ready or not.
Shit. If this keeps up, I'll
lose my team, Eren, and Historia.
It's the damnedest thing.
I seem to be smellin' a rat in this fine establishment.
Come on out, little rodent.
The sheriff is here!
And I aim to exterminate all the vermin I can find.
Bang! Bang!
Eek!
Oh, come on! You here or not?
Right here, Kenny. Been a while.
I really thought you'd be dead by now,
what with all the MPs you were butcherin'.
But now you're great friends, huh?
Yeah, well, adults do plenty of
things kids like you can't understand.
Oh, right. My mistake.
You're s'posed to be an adult now, but
you're still such a runt it's hard to tell. Heh.
Always hoped that I might get
to see you in action someday.
I can't say I'm disappointed, either.
Seems you still remember every trick I taught ya.
But didn't I ever tell you what happens to a cornered rat?
'Cause if I had, you'd know that wherever
you run, you'll find a bullet waiting.
Hey, Levi.
You must've become a scout for a reason.
And I think I know what that is.
We were forced to survive in that little hellhole.
Giving everything we had just to stay alive.
So when we found out just how big the world really was,
you can bet it hurt like hell.
But ya know what saved us?
We found something we enjoyed doing.
It's just that simple.
Every man needs himself a hobby.
May be the only source of fulfillment
he'll ever find in this wretched world.
Oh, I see.
Is that why you blew off my people's heads, then?
'Cause it's fulfilling?
Yup. To achieve my grand goal,
I'll kill as many as get in my way.
And you're no different. You
kill too when it benefits you.
Yeah.
Wait! It's the captain.
Thanks for the help, old man.
Huh? A chair?
Damn! Fire!
I hear shooting!
Huh?
From there!
I-I heard close to a dozen shots!
Do you think that they ran into some trouble?
It seems likely.
The captain gave me a message.
As of now, it's not just Titans.
We're fighting humans, too.
Huh? You don't mean...
Hey!
Are they running a training exercise?
Commander. You're needed to check some papers.
Captain. You finally bit the dust or what?
What a dumb question.
How would I answer if I was dead, Caven?
Brat got me good.
I forgot that bar owners are allowed
to keep guns to protect themselves.
Looks like the runt grew up more than I figured.
That's lovely, sir.
Like hell. The boy's a thorn in my ass.
My dream's slipping further and further away.
Look! There they are!
Captain Levi!
The hell is that?
Follow the wagon!
Right!
Listen up! These soldiers were
trained to fight other people.
They've already taken out three of ours.
If you hesitate for so much as a second, you'll be dead.
The moment you see an opening, go for the kill.
Yes, sir.
Tch.
Armin! Secure the wagon with Jean!
We'll keep you two covered.
Uh... sir!
He killed him.
Come on!
Don't move!
Stop.
Jean!
It's a shame that nothing came of our chat with Erwin.
We're no closer to finding Eren Jaegar or Historia.
At this rate, all of our actions against the
Scout Regiment will prove to be for nothing.
True.
So, do we know what kind of information
they might have gotten out of Pastor Nick?
No helping it. If our questions get specific,
we'll risk giving them information
they didn't have in the first place.
No. What they learned is irrelevant.
All that matters now is what they tried to learn.
The Charter of Humanity is clear on this.
We'll deal with them as the law dictates.
Hm?
This is from Lord Reiss.
He's captured Eren and Historia.
And he's going to take direct action
against Erwin and the Scout Regiment.
He requires no assistance at this time.
That's the last of it.
If you want any of your personal
effects returned, ask for them later.
No. That's fine.
But if you have a moment, I'd like to talk.
I'm not really in the mood to reminisce about old times.
Why so cold, Nile?
We were like brothers back in our days as cadets.
Quite soon, this tiny world of ours will be changed.
Will that change bring hope or despair?
Can we trust the crown with the future of humanity?
Who should decide?
Who has the right?
Who will you trust, Nile?
Erwin. Tell me.
What are you planning to do?
I'll make a gamble, same as always.
Was it like this for you?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. I...
Shit! Armin! Jean!
Let 'em go. We're running on fumes.
No!
Eren!
What's wrong? Did all this filth kill your appetite?
No. Jean, there's something I don't understand.
What's that?
When I turned around to try to save you...
...that woman already had her gun to your head.
It's... funny. How could I have shot before she did?
I don't know.
You shot first because she hesitated.
It's simple.
I'm sorry, Armin. You wouldn't've
had to save me if I'd just done my job.
I know what it is.
The woman I shot back there.
I bet she was a really kind person.
She must've had a lot more human empathy than I ever did.
I pulled that trigger so easily.
Without a thought.
I'm...
A killer.
And now that your hands have been soaked in blood,
the person you once were is gone for good.
Why would you say that?
And you shouldn't regret it for one second.
Because if you'd chosen to keep your hands clean,
Jean would be a corpse on a cart right now.
I'll tell you why you pulled the trigger.
Because your comrade was about to die.
Armin. Everyone on our squad survived today
because you got blood on your hands.
Thank you.
Captain Levi, I, uh, I thought it was
wrong for us to fight other humans, sir.
I thought it was wrong that you'd ordered us to do it.
I mean, we became soldiers to protect people.
But now, I see that I was in the wrong, sir.
Next time, I swear I'll shoot.
I never said anything about what was right or wrong.
My moral high ground's shot to hell.
I have no idea who's in the right at this point.
Now then, I think it's time we
heard what our guest has to say.
Mercy, please!
I'm just an old man they use to move cargo.
I didn't want to, but they...
I've met this one before.
He seemed to be a prominent merchant.
Yeah, I know him. Dimo Reeves, right?
This damn job was forced on us by the Military Police.
And now that we completely botched it,
they'll plunder the Reeves
Company for everything its worth.
First, they'll kill me,
and then they'll set up "accidents"
for all my employees. My dumb son, too.
You just gonna lay down and take it?
There's a reason Trost recovered from that Titan attack.
It's largely because of jobs and
money brought in by the Reeves Company.
Tell me, if your company were to disappear,
how many would survive the coming winter?
So, what? You want me to join you?
We just need to know where Eren and Historia are.
If you're in contact with the MPs, I think I have a plan.
And can you give me your word that the
people of Trost won't end up starving to death?
I can't guarantee it. That said,
I believe they'll have a better
chance with us than without.
About time the bastards left.
Our situation just got worse!
I have two things to report, Commander.
First, Eren and Historia have been abducted by the enemy.
Three from my squad were killed in the fighting.
I'm about to meet Captain Levi and follow up on a
lead he might have as to their current whereabouts.
Understood. What else?
Eren remembered a conversation he
overheard between Ymir and Bertholdt.
But, if this is actually true, then...
Shit. I feel like my head's gonna explode.
Are you okay?
What's the problem?
Unless we recover him quickly, Eren will be devoured.
Hey! How'd you find 'em anyway?
They found me. I promised them that I'd cooperate,
and for some reason they believed me.
Are we there?
Reeves, you piece of...
Sorry, gents. That's how it is.
What happens now?
Do you think this means we'll be safe? Or what?
There's no guarantee.
Say what? Then why'd we do it?
A good merchant has to learn to trust his nose.
And not just to smell easy money,
but to sniff out the potential for future profit, too.
Once you have, you bite and you don't let go.
You remember that, son.
I made it! You haven't finished yet, have you?
No. Haven't even gotten my feet wet.
Sannes! I'm only a novice at human torture,
but while I lack experience,
I plan to give this job my all.
Hold on! At least tell me what you want!
Who the hell tortures someone without asking questions?
Oh, yeah. We do have some questions.
Where were Eren and Historia taken?
What do you want with Historia,
and what is the Reiss family?
Come on!
Can't you see that we're in a time crunch here?
Here we go again.
The screams seem a lot louder than
they were when the captain did it.
I know it's to save our friends, but...
...it still makes me sick.
Let's face the facts. We're criminals now.
Our last enemy wanted to eat us.
We don't have an excuse like
that for killing these people.
It's just that their views are different.
No. It's just that they're in another group.
And for that, we'll take their lives.
Armin.
We're not good people. Not anymore, at least.
Sorry. I don't have your knack for peeling nails.
Just how many did you have to
rip off to get so good at it?
More than I could keep track of.
Within these cramped, squalid walls,
war has never broken out, and I can tell you why.
It's because we of the First Interior Squad
dirtied our hands to protect the king's peace!
A teacher too smart for his own good.
A stupid couple who tried to fly.
A whore who screwed the wrong man!
No matter how they'd beg or plead,
we erased them to protect humanity!
You should be on your knees thanking me!
In all my years, I've never seen anyone
take such pleasure from human suffering as you!
You're both monsters!
But I'm determined to face you without fear.
Do what you will. For I... I have my faith.
And I believe in the king and in peace within these walls.
I believe that every last one of my
wretched deeds was justified, but...
To think that it hurt this much...
If you're going to torture me to death, get on with it.
That sounds like a fitting
end for this blood-stained life.
Time for a break.
Ugh. Damn it all.
I'm starting to feel sorry for him.
Quit shovin' me. It hurts.
Ralph!
How pathetic can you get?
Can't believe you started talking after just one nail.
Sannes doesn't have any nails left.
He's a real soldier.
Like I care. He can get tortured all he wants.
The guy never shuts up about peace and the king.
The rest of us all hate his damn guts.
Just do us a favor and kill him already.
We're gonna have to keep him around
until he's verified what you told us.
Yeah? Well, you got everything you wanted
out of me, so why don't you lay off already?
Oh, and about my cell. It'll have a bed, right?
Ready, Sannes? We're gonna try it again!
This isn't easy for me either, but
I'll be the best torturer I can...
Reiss is the true royal family.
So much for keepin' a low profile.
How long is that boy gonna take?
Ya know, the one thing a merchant
should never sell out of is trust.
Was it wise to do that without asking where Levi is?
He'll show up no matter what we do.
How do you know that?
'Cause I raised him, that's how.
Levi Ackermann's not one to give up the chase.
You mean the rightful heir to the throne is...
...Historia?
That's correct. And based on that knowledge,
we're assuming that she and
Eren have been taken to Lord Reiss.
That's him.
Historia.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
One girl's tortured past
holds a secret that could change the fate of a kingdom.
Once this secret is known to Erwin,
he remembers his own past.
Next episode: "Old Story."