Guess what?
This means we finally have a real
shot at plugging the hole in Wall Maria.
The Scout Regiment hurries its preparations
for the mission to retake Wall Maria.
Ooh!
Hell yeah!
We did it, Eren!
Eren?
I'm fine.
Let's just make these weapons quickly,
and then go to Shiganshina.
Seems if I just stick myself,
I'll turn into a big, strong Titan.
Then came another surprise.
One more thing with the potential
to shape the fate of humanity.
Looks like I'm late. Sorry.
Have any luck?
Were you able to establish what's in the container?
We have a vague idea, but unfortunately, with
our technology, I'm afraid we can't dig much deeper.
Like we've heard from Eren and Historia,
it seems to originate from some sort of human body fluid.
However, it vaporizes when exposed to air, making
further analysis virtually impossible to perform.
Whoever made it must have had
technology far superior to ours.
I can't imagine how the Reiss
family could've managed to do it.
Hmm...
In that case, rather than tamper with it,
we should put it to use for our current objective.
But to whom do we entrust it?
To you, Erwin?
No. With my wound, I would be a poor choice.
This syringe, it belongs in the hands of one of our elite.
Someone with the best odds of survival.
Levi, will you accept it?
If it's an order, just say so.
Why even bother asking?
When we need to use this, there may not be time to plan.
We'll be relying on you to make a decision
swiftly, and with little deliberation.
Judging when to use it, and on whom,
will be your responsibility.
Will you accept it?
If this dream of yours comes true,
what will you do then?
I don't know, and I won't.
Not until it happens.
I see.
All right. I'll do it.
Hmm...
Now then, I'd like to discuss that work of mine.
As you know, I'm hoping to unveil it soon.
Have you given it any thought?
You mean you still haven't given up on that?
If the public were to see such a repulsive display,
whatever trust they have in the military would evaporate.
You don't know art when you see it.
You spoke to Sadies, and based on what he told you,
it seems that Grisha Jaeger is a
human who came from outside the walls.
Yes, and like the others, Annie, Reiner, and Bertholdt,
it appears he also had the Power of the Titans.
But where those three sought to undermine it,
he was supportive of humanity within the walls.
If he was really that supportive
of the Scouts and what we do,
maybe he coulda thrown a bit more information our way.
I wonder.
From the moment he entered the walls,
he was searching for the royal family.
A heavy burden to shoulder alone.
If you ask me,
that's not something you do unless you
have an iron will and incredible resolve.
And let's not forget,
that same man later wanted to show his young son,
eager to join the Scouts, something important.
Staring death in the face, he said the
truth of it all was there, in the cellar.
What's down there? What was he hiding?
Things which mustn't be said.
No. Things which can't be spoken.
Things he couldn't say, even if he wanted to.
That which the First Reiss
King wiped from our consciousness.
Memories of our world.
At least, that's my hope.
But speculating more won't accomplish anything.
The final preparations are now complete.
The operation to retake Wall Maria begins in two days.
Wanna know what's in that cellar?
Let's go see for ourselves.
We're Scouts. That's what we do.
I'll leave it to you to alert your squads.
Right. We'll keep it quiet for now, though.
I think our troops deserve some meat on a day like this.
Good idea.
Gotta show those kids the adults can be counted on.
What about Commandant Sadies
keeping important secrets from us.
Forget it. We don't have time to deal with that now.
You must be so disappointed.
You used to adore him!
Shut up!
What is it, Levi?
This may sound impatient,
but what do you think you'll do after retaking Wall Maria?
I'm guessing a defense plan comes first, but after that?
What's next?
Eliminating threats.
Outside the walls, there seems to be
someone hoping that Titans will eat us all,
down to the last person.
As to who, well, if we have any luck,
we'll find that answer in the cellar.
A full plan will have to wait.
First we need to see what's in that room.
You realize I'm asking this now
because you might not live that long.
You're not exactly as spry as you used to be.
Let Hange call the shots on this mission.
In your shape, you'll only be dead weight.
You sit back and wait for the good news.
We'll tell the others I argued till you gave in.
Which I will, so why not make this easier on both of us?
What do you say?
No.
Do what you need to. Use me as bait.
The chain of command still remains.
If I'm gone, then Hange.
If Hange's gone, the next.
It's true this operation will be extremely dangerous,
but it will also be the most
important one in human history.
That's why I've gone to such lengths.
This is my plan, Levi.
Without me leading you, you're less likely to succeed.
That's true. Without you, the operation might fail.
But if you bite the dust out there, we're really screwed.
So just stay safe at your desk
and keep using that head of yours.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's the last thing the Titans would want,
and the best weapon that humanity's got.
No, you're wrong.
Our best option is for me to
gamble it all on the plan that I...
Okay, that's enough. Stop right there.
Any more of those noble-ass excuses,
and I'm gonna break both your damn legs.
Not too badly.
They'll heal just fine, but you'll be way too busted
up to even think about joining us on the operation.
And it'll be a bitch to get to the toilet.
Don't like that idea much.
Normally, I'd agree with you.
A wounded soldier should stay off the battlefield.
However...
That may be the day we learn the truth about our world,
and I'll be damned if I'm going to miss it.
Being there is that important?
More than your legs?
Yes.
More than humanity's victory?
I see.
Fine, Erwin.
In that case, I'll trust your judgment.
This may be a special night, but we
don't need the public knowing our plans.
So, behave like the disciplined soldiers you are.
What? No way.
Is that...? It is.
It's meat.
Am I dreaming?
All right. Here's to the re-taking of Wall Maria.
A toast!
Huh? Wait!
Calm down! Everyone'll get some, okay?
Hey! A piece that big counts as two!
You're crazy!
Well, I'm worth two of you on the battlefield,
so I think I should get your portion!
Like hell!
What the hell do you think you're doing, potato girl?
No way are we gonna let you pull this shit!
Drop the meat, Sasha.
Come on, I really don't wanna have to kill you.
You can't eat the whole thing alone, you pig!
Ah! You're eating me! My hand! My hand!
Sasha! That meat is Jean!
We don't eat our friends, okay?
What, does the Scout Regiment never get any meat?
Really? That's just sad...
Conny, would you just knock her out already?
I'm trying!
It's like her mind's shut down,
but she's still moving somehow!
Hey, I think we've got casualties.
Whose brilliant idea was it to serve meat, again?
Well, I guess now we know what happens
when we blow the whole food budget for
two months on one night of celebrating.
That should do it.
She finally wore herself out.
Jeez, can you believe this freak?
It's crazy to think that she once
offered to share meat with everybody.
What? She did?
Yeah, four months ago,
when we were servicing the cannons.
I totally just helped myself to the Officer's Pantry.
It'll be fine.
Just look at it this way.
Pretty soon, we'll take back
all the room we need for livestock.
They're gonna get in.
They're gonna get in. They're gonna get in!
He's gone!
In the moment, I felt sorry for you.
Hey.
It's hard to believe that it's only been four months.
Yeah, it's kinda crazy.
But think, that's all it took for us to make Levi Squad.
How's that for climbin' the ranks?
It's all because you're a genius. Damn straight I am.
Come on. Let's eat before it gets cold.
Don't you get it?
You've got no experience.
That's why you're in the rear guard, rookie.
I may be less knowledgeable than the rest of you,
but isn't the vanguard the best
place to learn how the enemy moves?
What's this?
You think that you can lecture
a veteran about self-sacrifice?
Isn't that what makes us effective?
Being willing to put ourselves in harm's way?
Listen, everyone starts out as a recruit, okay?
If we throw recruits into battle like cannon fodder,
then they'll all be too dead to learn.
And that's why, for now, it's your
job to watch and learn from the rear.
So you can make it back in one piece.
The ones who really suck are the suicidal maniacs
who think the only way to fight is to charge in blind.
Right?
Are you talkin' about somebody in particular?
Yeah, I'm looking right at him. Suicidal maniac.
You see, the funny thing is that I recently
discovered that I'm actually a pretty normal person.
So, hey, if that's how you really see
me, then maybe you're just a coward, Jean.
Right?
You think you're so cool, don't you, you piece of shit?
That's a pretty shaggy-looking
mane you're growing there, horse face!
What's with those two?
Try not to kill each other.
You jerk!
You're gonna rip my shirt!
What the hell are those two doing?
You bastard!
Show 'em what you've got!
He's losing ground!
It looks like we've got a fight.
I told the idiots to behave.
But seriously.
If you didn't have Titan powers,
you'd be dead ten times over.
Although, I guess Mikasa would've swooped
in every time to save your worthless ass.
You so eager to die?
Fine, then I'll kill you!
Yeah? Okay.
Give it your best shot!
You oughta start showin' your
mom some more respect, Jean-boy!
Would you forget that?
Never!
Should we let them keep going?
I think it's fine.
Why?
Why isn't anybody stopping us?
How long's this gonna go on?
Shit. I think I'm gonna barf up that meat.
Hey.
That's enough celebrating.
Go to bed.
And clean that up.
Yes, sir!
Ahh...
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but shouldn't you guys watch out for me more?
Considering how quickly you heal, I
wasn't especially worried about it.
Some friends you are.
Look, you started it, so don't complain.
Plus, it's good to see you feisty again.
I'm glad we met with the commandant.
I think it helped.
I don't know about being feisty,
but I'll do what I have to.
And honestly, I feel better.
I just kept thinking about
all the stuff I couldn't change.
Spent so much time pitying myself, wondering
why I couldn't be strong like Mikasa and Levi.
I was jealous, but even though you guys are strong,
you can't do all that much alone.
None of us can.
That's why we have to find our own roles.
When we join together,
that's when we become truly powerful.
Everyone's got their own strengths,
and it's 'cause of times like this.
Yeah.
I think you're right.
Once we've retaken Wall Maria
and defeated every last one of our enemies...
...can we go back?
To how things used to be?
Some things will be the same,
but some things have changed forever.
And we'll make them pay for that.
Yeah.
There's more out there, though.
The sea. Remember?
A body of water so big that merchants could spend
their whole lives and still not get all the salt out.
There's so much beyond the walls. Not just Titans.
Water that glows like fire, fields of ice,
giant rocks that take days to climb.
I joined the Scouts so I could
see all those things someday.
Yeah. You sure did.
I remember.
All right then!
Let's start by finding the sea!
I can tell you still don't think it's real, Eren.
You'll see! It does exist!
Heh. Okay, fine.
I guess we'll just have to check it out, then.
That's not good enough!
You have to promise!
Oh, great, here we go again.
This is our chance to explore the outside world!
It's gotta be way bigger than inside the walls!
Okay, I promise.
Just before sunset.
It's finally time.
Hey!
Hange! Good luck!
Flegel?
Go out there and take back Wall Maria for us!
The future of mankind is up to you!
Captain Levi!
Good luck out there! Thanks for saving our city!
You guys come back in one piece, all right?
Yeah! But get us back our land, too!
Someone's got a big mouth.
Yeah, well, that celebration did get a little rowdy.
Actually, we ordered all of that
meat from the Reeves Company, so...
Flegel.
Yeah! You can count on us!
I wonder how long it's been since
the Scouts got a send-off like this.
I dunno. I'm not sure if we ever have.
Well, as far as I'm aware, at least,
this is a first.
The operation to retake Wall Maria begins now!
Scouts, move out!
You two.
Do you have even the faintest damn clue...
...what you're doing?