Thank you for practicing
with me so late.
[YUKARIKO]
Just one moment.
I'll walk you back.
[KIYONE]
Oh, it's all right, Sister.
There have been some
terrible rumors circling lately.
Don't worry; I may not
be much of a singer,
but I know I can
run really fast.
Good night!
[gasps]
Wait, Kiyone!
Everyone around here's
such a scaredy-cat.
"Vampires." As if.
[KIYONE gasps softly]
[leaves rustling]
[pants]
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[KENDO GUYS]
One, two, three, four...
Keep up the pace, guys!
Last one back has to do
another lap around! Ha, ha!
Hmm?
[gasping]
What...?
[KENDO GUYS gasping]
[gasps]
Hurry, go get Miss Sagisawa or
Sister Yukariko right away!
[KENDO GUYS]
Let's go! C'mon!
[MAI]
Huh?
A vampire?
Yeah, you have to have
heard the recent rumors
about vampire sightings.
And now we finally have
a victim to prove it.
[AOI] It was a girl
from the choir, right?
Yeah, but I heard
there were others.
Three that I know of,
and maybe more.
That many...?
From what I heard, the girls
had something in common:
after the attack,
they all had what looked like
bite marks on their necks.
And that's not all.
[GIRLS]
Hmm?
She was naked?!
[RESTAURANT PATRONS]
Yeah. But even though
they were found stripped,
there were no indications of
sexual assault
or anything like that.
[AOI]
Sexual...
[MAI]
...assault?
Meaning?
I still don't get why
everyone assumes it's a vampire.
I mean, think about it
for a minute.
Usually, it would be some
kinda creep or a pervert.
That's even scarier,
thinking it was a real person.
[CHIE] Yeah. Maybe that
explains it, though.
People would rather believe it
was a vampire or a monster
that did this.
That's so typical of our school.
There are always crazy
rumors floating around.
A vampire on campus...
I hope it's not...
[HARUKA]
Do you understand, President?!
Three girls have fallen
victim in a single night!
Now is the time for the
Executive Committee--
No! The entire student
council to pool together
all of its emergency resources!
[SHIZURU sips]
[HARUKA]
Anyway...
...until the culprit is caught,
we've gotta go on
a campus-wide
emergency alert,
and the Executive Committee must
be given the full authority
to investigate this crime!
Well, it seems that the girls
only lost a little blood.
And there was no "fooling
around" if you know what I mean.
So I don't think we
need to go that far.
That's easy enough for you
to say, Vice President;
you are a man!
To a girl, it is the worst
kind of offense imaginable!
Plus, there are rumors that it
was a vampire or a monster
that attacked them!
President!
I need your decision!
I understand.
This time, Miss Suzushiro,
I think I'll have to
go along with you.
We'll put our trust in you.
I'll stake my honor on it.
Yukino!
Oh.
I want an emergency assembly of
the Executive Committee,
and the cooperation
of the Sports Clubs.
Oh. Y-Yes.
Haruka's sure worked up.
She... seems reliable enough,
but are you sure?
I do empathize, being
a girl and all. And besides...
You're saying it's not
one of the usual Orphans
that pop up out of nowhere?
Right, and the people at the top
seem to be quite troubled by it.
Yup. It's as though
someone, or something,
is pulling the strings
from behind the scenes.
Interesting. If he's
an enemy to you folks,
then maybe he's an ally of mine.
[SAKOMIZU]
I doubt that very much.
So, what? You plan on
doing nothing this time?
[NATSUKI] Hmph.
If you're so worried,
why don't you get
your self-proclaimed
"defender of justice"
to do something?
[SAKOMIZU chuckles]
She went into self-confinement
after that fracas
at the cooking lesson
she organized.
She's hunkered down in
the library basement
working on some thesis.
Whatever. I still don't want
you to start counting on me.
I have my own agenda.
You do know that.
What did you find there, anyway?
[NATSUKI sighs]
[SAKOMIZU]
Give it up.
[NATSUKI]
Hmph.
[SAKOMIZU] There's no point
in digging up the past.
It's none of your business!
[NAGI] Hmm. "These young
girls had their blood
sucked from them.
We're looking for more HiME.
If you don't want anyone else
hurt, then surrender them!"
Is that what they're saying?
Gimme a break.
To think they'd use
vampires of all things.
Makes you seriously wanna
question their tastes.
Don't you think so?
[MASHIRO] They must be
as desperate as we are.
We will have to take
action right away.
[NAGI]
What?! No chance!
We can't get carried
away, you know!
[MASHIRO]
I realize that.
But innocent students
are getting hurt.
Aren't you forgetting? They were
able to defeat one of our HiME.
[MASHIRO sighs]
They have enough strength
to control an Orphan.
We'll give them space until
they reveal all their cards.
If we provoke them now, they
might attack in some other way.
The star will come.
It won't wait that long.
I know, I know, you don't
need to remind me.
You can trust me on this, okay?
[GREER] May the Lord
bless you, young child.
Amen.
Thank you, Father.
[GREER]
Sister Yukariko...
Ah?
Everyone's come here
in hopes of being saved.
You mustn't look so forlorn,
or you'll scare them off.
I know, Father...
But poor Kiyone...
If only I hadn't let
her walk home alone...
[doors slam open]
[HARUKA] We're the Student
Council Executive Committee!
Please excuse the intrusion,
but we need to occupy
the chapel temporarily.
I'm sure you've heard
about the recent incidents
that have occurred on campus.
The attacks occurred nearby.
This makes the chapel
the most appropriate choice
to set up our task
force headquarters.
Do we have your support?
I'm always happy
to cooperate,
and you have my full
support if it'll benefit
our dear students.
[HARUKA]
I appreciate it!
Get moving!
[COMMITTEE]
Right!
[MAI]
Miyu!
What's going on around here?
The Executive Committee has
decided to take over the chapel.
[gasps]
Why? What now?
[HARUKA]
Hey, what's taking so long?!
Get that equipment
set up on the double!
And you, girls!
Get back to your dorms, now!
As of today, there's
a six o'clock curfew
for all dormitory residents.
After six, no one will be
permitted outside,
even on school grounds!
What?! C'mon,
you can't be serious!
I work way past six o'clock!
Not an option!
This is a necessary measure
that we're taking
in order to protect
all of you students!
[MAI]
But...
If you have a problem
with our decision,
I can send you inside
to do penance!
[MAI growls]
[MAI] Nagi! Where are you?
I know you're in here!
[NAGI]
Over here!
[MAI gasps]
[NAGI] I'm impressed
you found this place!
Natsuki told me
about it once before.
But never mind that.
What's the deal
with this vampire?!
Probably another Orphan, right?
Oh, that thing?
Well, it's good timing.
'Cause I have a
favor to ask you, Mai.
Yeah, yeah, you want me
to destroy it.
Urr! Wrong answer!
Actually, it's the opposite.
Huh?
For HiME? You mean
they're looking for us?
The mark you all have on
your bodies is the easiest way
to tell that you're a HiME.
They're simply trying to
identify which ones HiME
by chasing down all the girls.
The blood, they're
probably using
for some kinda
genetic testing.
[MAI]
Why would they be doing that?
Who knows?
Now, Mai, I don't wanna hear
that you've gone looking
for a fight, or gotten yourself
caught up in something
you can't handle, all right?
[gasps]
I've been a little worried
about you lately,
seeing as how you've gotten
used to your power.
[MAI]
Get a grip, Nagi.
Why would I do
something like that?
Well, good, that's what
I wanted to hear.
The powers you and the others
possess are primarily
for your own benefit, after all.
[MAI groans]
All units are in
place now, Haruka.
[HARUKA]
Good.
All right, vampire or pervert,
come on out whenever you want!
Now let us commence
and carry out our mission to
usher in the next Golden Age.
There's nothing wrong with using
our power any way we want to.
[MIDORI]
The good always triumph!
I'll get them. I'll do whatever
it takes to bring them down.
[MIKOTO]
Wow!
This looks super yummy!
[MIKOTO]
I need to find my brother,
and I'll fight anyone
who gets in my way.
End of story.
Mai, can you make this please?!
[MAI sighs]
[MIKOTO giggles]
So will you make it for me?
Tell you what, Mikoto.
What do you say we go out and
do something fun tomorrow?
[MIKOTO gasps]
Really?!
C'mon, Akira, how 'bout it?
I'll do whatever I can to help,
so how about doing
that secret ninja thing
to protect the school?
All right! All right!
I'll go outside and do
a little patrol, okay?
Let me come with you!
No, you just stay
put here in the dorm.
If you collapse or something,
your sister will kill me.
Hey! Ah! Aw...
Shiho, we're not supposed to be
out here this late, you know?
But I can't do my homework
without my notebook.
Besides, you can beat up
any perverts we come across!
[grunts]
Maybe, maybe not.
What if it's a real monster?
[SHIHO giggles]
What? You really believe that?
There's no such thing, goofball.
I hope you're right.
Ah...
[SHIHO giggles]
Wah!
I'm a vampire!
[YUICHI whimpers]
[SHIHO]
Come on. What's the matter?
I was just joking around.
[YUICHI whimpers]
[SHIHO]
Hmm?
[screams]
[YUICHI whimpers]
[MIKOTO laughs]
Where do you think we
should go first, Mai?!
Yeah, good question.
[AOI]
Ohh! I'm gonna miss the train!
'Morning, Mai.
Good morning.
You're going out for the day?
[AOI]
Mm-hmm. To a concert.
Where's Nao at?
[AOI] She spent the night out.
Breaking the rules, as usual.
Oh. I'm gonna be
back late. See ya!
But it's dangerous
around here after dark.
[AOI]
Don't worry!
Besides, I heard that
nothing happened last night.
[MIKOTO whines]
C'mon, Mai, let's get going!
Okay.
[HARUKA]
So?
This is the only person
you caught, then?
Don't get your panties
in a knot just because
I was out all night.
I'm not a kid, you know.
[HARUKA growls]
How rude.
Maybe we should teach her
a thing or two
about proper manners
before we let her go.
Sister, she's all yours--
let her have it.
Oh, um. Uh... Listen, Nao.
I'm not certain, but perhaps
you'd rather discuss things
in private, so let's
talk over there?
The confessional...
Fine by me.
I'll give you a nice,
long confession, Sister.
[YUKARIKO]
Please, stop!
--[wails]
--[NAO] Oh, come on.
I'm not even
half way through yet.
I don't want to hear
any more of it!
It's so disgusting!
Huh. You sure have some nerve,
trying to lecture me,
when you can't even listen to
a tame little story like that.
[YUKARIKO whimpers]
[NAO]
See ya!
[ISHIGAMI chuckles]
That's quite a spot
she put you in.
Don't laugh. It's not funny.
I feel like I'm losing
my confidence
when it comes to guiding
these young girls.
[ISHIGAMI]
Hmm...
Then how 'bout immersing
yourself in the secular world
for a change? I'm certain
you'd find it refreshing.
[YUKARIKO whimpers]
For example...
...as my model.
[YUKARIKO whimpers]
[MIKOTO laughs]
Hurry, Mai!
What's taking you so long?
Slow down, we're in no big rush.
[MIKOTO laughs]
Oh... [laughs]
[MIKOTO yells, laughs]
[MAI]
Whee-hoo-hoo!
[MIKOTO]
Hmph.
[KIDS gasping]
[MAI gasps]
[yells]
[MIKOTO growls]
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
[laughs]
[sighs]
This is the funnest day ever!
Mm-hmm! Super fun!
[MAI]
Well, I'm glad we came.
I was kind of stressed
before, but not anymore.
What were you stressed about?
[MAI]
Hey, can I ask you something?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
[MAI]
Why do you think we're HiME?
Have you ever thought about it?
--[MIKOTO] Hmm.
--I mean...
Why am I a HiME?
[MIKOTO]
Don't you want to be one, Mai?
[MAI sighs]
It's just that I'm a
regular high school student
barely managing to deal
with all the other things
going on in my life.
All this talk about the
fate of the world
and District 1 and enemies
and whether to fight or not...
It's all a little too much.
[MIKOTO] Hmm... You are
who you are, though, Mai.
Deal with it however you want.
Don't you think so?
[MAI]
Maybe you're right.
But it's hard to know.
Which way's "my" way?
I don't know what I wanna do.
Or what everyone
expects me to do.
Have some! It'll make
you feel better!
Thanks, Mikoto.
[MIKOTO giggles]
[singing]
Huh?
[MAI]
Hmm?
[ALYSSA] ♪
They're dancing in the shadow ♪
♪ like whispers of love, ♪
♪ just dreaming of a place
where they're free as dove. ♪
♪ They've never been allowed
to love in this cursed cage ♪
♪ It's only the fairy
tail they believe. ♪
[clapping]
What did you think?
[MIYU] It was awesome,
really incredible.
Your voice is
so special, Alyssa.
It's so beautiful and gentle.
It's like looking through
a crystal-clear stream.
You mean you can
see music, Miyu?
That's right.
I can see music, because I sense
things a little differently
from you and the
rest of the girls.
For example, sometimes,
when I look at you,
you appear to me
as a ray of light.
I do? Really?
Yes. It's like...
It's nice and warm,
and very soft...
A golden ray of light.
You're so funny, Miyu.
I guess you see the world
and everything around us
much prettier than we do.
[MIYU] I'm sure you'll
see that beauty as well.
The Golden Age is just
around the corner.
And when it does come,
you and I will
build a snowman together again.
[MAI]
Uh... Miyu?
--[MIYU] Hmm?
--Uh... Sorry.
Am I interrupting?
Not really.
[MAI]
That was beautiful, Alyssa.
I'm so glad we heard you
sing; talk about lucky!
That's nice of you.
[MAI]
I'm Mai, by the way.
It's nice to meet you.
[ALYSSA whimpers]
You're sure cute.
[MIKOTO]
I'll go play by myself, then!
Hmph!
[MAI sighs]
Sorry. I've gotta go.
I have to say...
--[MIKOTO whines]
--Boy...
You two sure are close.
And get along well.
Yes. Alyssa is one of a kind;
like an irreplaceable treasure.
I'm kind of envious that
you can feel so strongly
--about someone.
--Mai!
I'm really gonna
leave, you know!
[MAI]
Coming!
Well, I'll see
you guys at school.
Sure.
[YAMADA] That number turned
out to be a bank account.
The deposits all turned
out to be issued to
a number of front companies.
So I traced the money
to its final recipients,
and found that they ended up
at two organizations.
Who are they?
[YAMADA] If you want me
to dig any further,
I'm gonna have
to charge more.
I am risking my life, after all.
Works for me.
[YAMADA]
One's Iwasaka Pharmaceuticals.
The other one's the
Searrs Foundation.
The Searrs Foundation.
[SHIZURU]
Night has fallen once again.
I hope we have another quiet
one with no more incidents.
[YUICHI sighs]
[MAI sighs]
Well, I sure am tired.
Ah, Mai...
That was fun...
Guess it was all that
running around we did.
[cell phone rings]
[MAI]
Kinda late. What's up?
Your student council
was the one that created
the curfew, wasn't it?
[YUICHI] I figured it's about
time I 'fess up about something.
[gasps]
[EXECUTIVE A]
Gate no. 3.
All clear.
[gasps]
I'm doomed!
[ISHIGAMI]
You must be exhausted,
sitting still this whole time.
Actually, when I pray,
there are times
when I may be in the same
position for several hours.
That's very dedicated of you.
We should be going now.
I'll walk you back.
No, I'll be all right.
What I mean is, the Lord
is always at my side.
Unfortunately, I can't compete
with someone like Him.
[gasps] But I heard that
nothing happened last night!
That's 'cause I told Shiho
not to tell a soul.
Anyway, in the middle of
it all, another one appeared.
It looked like some kind
of giant frog monster,
and it was the reason
we were able to escape.
What the hell was that?!
First, there was that thing from
the Founders' Day Festival,
and the ferry incident!
The fire on the hill, the shrine
storehouse getting totaled!
What're you hiding
from everyone?!
What do you know?
And now, there's this vampire.
There's gotta be
some kinda connection!
Tate...
Yes! Passed the guards.
I'm home free!
[deep growling]
[AOI gasps]
I'm sorry...
I can't...
I can't tell you now...
[YUICHI]
I knew you were involved.
But please... Tell me
you're not on the side
of those monsters or anything...
'Course not!
It's nothing--
[AOI screams]
--[gasps]
--[HARUKA gasps]
Sister! What have you done...?
A... Aoi...
I-Is she...?
[YUKARIKO]
Oh... No!
[YUKARIKO sobs]
No!
[MAI]
Headmaster!
[MASHIRO]
What's the matter, Miss Tokiha?
[MAI] A big crisis
facing the academy!
Is it okay to act
so nonchalant?!
[MASHIRO]
Right...
--[MAI] Right, Fumi?
--[FUMI] Right...
--Headmaster?
--[MASHIRO] Yes?
--Fumi?
--[FUMI] Yes?
--Head-- I mean, Fumi!
--Yes!
[MAI]
I doubt it...