[OLD LADY A]
I am glad you've managed
to overcome this
difficult situation.
Certainly, they must now realize
that they are powerless.
[OLD LADY B] Remember though,
the most important stage
is yet to come.
[OLD LADY C]
As the star gets closer,
the world will start to waver.
But we must not allow them
to continue having
their way with this country
and the world any more
than they already have.
[OLD LADY B] You must give
guidance to the HiME
and be sure to make this
upcoming festival a success.
[OLD LADY A If you can do that,
the land of the rising sun
can look forward to becoming
a great and prosperous nation.
[OLD LADY B]
Yes, yes!
[OLD LADIES laugh]
[OLD LADY A] The Obsidian
Prince shall awaken soon.
And remember, the more
tears that are shed by
the Battle Princesses, the
greater the joy of the Prince.
However, you must
make sure to carry on
the festival without fail.
Kazu...
Hari disappeared.
[gasps]
[AKANE] The person
most precious to me...
--[clapping]
--[gasps]
It seems like you've enjoyed
your night of singing, my HiME.
[MIDORI] Hey! You shouldn't
be climbing up there!
[AKIRA] Now that you
know I'm a girl,
I don't have any other choice!
[TAKUMI gasps]
[NAGI]
It's about to begin.
You are now going to
have a new battle...
...to defeat each other's Child.
The festival is
about to commence!
Now, the time has come!
If you have someone
residing in your heart,
then come, accept the challenge,
and descend upon the
cursed land of Fuka...
...My HiME!
Basically, after this
particular law was introduced,
government agents could
take control of local property
and do as they wished,
leaving the towns and
villages at their mercy.
So this meant people had
to protect their own land.
In order to do that,
they needed to be armed,
and this eventually led to the
development of a warrior class.
[MAI]
What's this about?!
[NAGI]
It's really quite simple.
You have to fight
each other, that's all.
Using your Child.
Those strange creatures
that have been nurtured with
your love--the same love you
have for your precious person.
[MAI sighs]
Unreal.
Jeez!
[NAGI] Oh, don't get
too worked up about it.
[NAGI] You only have to
defeat each other's Child.
[NATSUKI]
But...
...if a Child is defeated,
the person most precious
to its HiME vanishes.
Right?
[gasping]
[NAGI
Bingo!
I see you've done your homework.
I'm betting Akane
told you about it?
Then again, I did
tell you once before,
didn't I?
If you choose to fight,
you'll have to risk
the one thing most
important to you.
[gasping]
[gasps]
No way...
Does that mean... Kazuya's...?
[AKANE shrieks]
[AKANE pants]
[gasping, screams]
[NAGI] That's basically
what it's all about.
--[door jiggles]
--[YUKINO gasps]
[HARUKA]
Hey! Who locked the door?!
[YUKINO gasps]
[YUKINO]
U-Um...
I don't know what happened.
I-I must've locked
it by accident.
[HARUKA sighs]
C'mon.
You've been making stupid
mistakes all morning.
Get it together.
[YUKINO sighs]
Yeah..
Sorry, Haruka...
[HARUKA]
Hmm? Yukino.
If something's bugging you,
please tell me right away.
You're not doing
yourself any favors
by keeping everything
pent up inside.
[YUKINO]
Hmm?
[NAGI
Oh, and another thing.
Let's say that
for whatever reason
you were to be defeated...
...both your Child and the
person most precious to you
will still disappear.
So if you want to protect
the person who means
the most to you, there's nothing
else you can do but fight
and win all of your battles.
Oh, Lord...
Why is this happening to us?
[ISHIGAMI]
Sister?
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
You look as though God
Himself has forsaken you.
[gasps]
Oh, Mr. Ishigami...
[ISHIGAMI]
Hmm? Yukari... ko...
[NAO] In other words,
I just have to keep fighting
and winning until it's all over?
Is that right?
[NAGI]
Exactly.
You catch on quick.
[NAO growls]
Hah. Yeah, sure.
So you think I'm just
gonna go along with
this little plan of yours?
Are you demented or something?
[NAGI]
Hmph. Yeah, sure. Whatever.
The fact is,
you'll have to fight.
There's no way any of you
can avoid that fate.
Besides, that's really
what you and the other HiME
are here for.
[NAO sighs]
There's no way
I'll be defeated...
Jeez. The guy sure
isn't very sociable.
Hmph.
[NAGI] Haven't you
noticed that up there?
[GIRLS]
Hmm? Huh?
It's gotten bigger.
[NAGI]
The HiME Star...
The star that only
you are able to see
is approaching
Earth as we speak.
That red star will bring
great disaster to everything
it comes into contact with.
But its effects
can be felt even now.
The only person that can
counter its force is the HiME
that survives through to the
end, and, of course, her Child.
You will have to
choose that one HiME
before the star
crashes into Earth.
And if that's not possible...
...the world will be destroyed.
I still can't believe it.
Can't be...
[MAI] How do you expect
us to believe that?!
And besides--
Why do we have to do it?!
[NAGI]
Why do you think?
It's your destiny as HiME.
Whether this country--
in fact, the entire world--
prospers or not depends
on the power of you
and the other girls;
the only ones with the ability
to control the Hime Star.
And you people expect us to
sacrifice ourselves for that?
Is that what you're saying?
[NAGI] Mm-hmm. However,
there is one little bonus.
The HiME who wins all
the battles will be bestowed
with a tremendous power.
[gasps]
Hang on! We're not done!
I've gotta go explain
all this to the girls
who aren't here.
Anyway, good luck.
Mai, what're you gonna do?
I'm going to ask the Headmaster,
and she'd better
give it to me straight.
Yukino!
[gasps]
[MAI]
You're here.
I was getting kinda worried
since you weren't in class.
Uh, right...
--[MIDORI] Mai.
--[MAI] Huh?
Yukino, Mikoto, you, too.
Let's talk outside.
[MAI]
No kidding.
So the Headmaster
isn't back yet...
[MIDORI] No, but I'm
gonna talk to her
as soon as she gets back.
Miss Sugiura, we're going
to be okay aren't we?
I-I mean... It's just...
You worry too much.
We're all friends, remember?
The HiME force, right?
Yeah, I know...
We're all part of a team...
But there are other HiME
that we still don't know about.
[MAI sighs]
[NAGI] We're a little
short on girls...
She's got a point.
There are a total 12 HiME.
That much we can be sure of.
So that means there
are still two HiME
that we don't know about.
But what if they...
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
I'm positive they
aren't that stupid.
--[YUKINO groans]
--[MIKOTO] Yup!
Nothing to worry about, Yukino.
'Cause if something
bad happens,
I'll protect both you and Mai!
Mikoto...
C'mon, c'mon.
There's no point gettin'
psyched up for a fight.
Anyway, I'm gonna check
and see if there's any truth
to that kid Nagi's story.
And even if he's
being honest with us,
there has got be a way of
getting out of this predicament.
--[MAI] Mm-hmm.
--[YUKINO] Mm...
[MIDORI] Until then, we've gotta
stay calm and use our heads.
We can at least make a
pact amongst ourselves.
In the meantime, if you
happen to run into Sister,
Natsuki, or Nao, make sure you
tell them about everything.
See? It's gonna be all right.
Nothing to worry about.
[MAI]
Yes. We will be all right.
[NAGI] If you choose to fight,
you'll have to risk
the one thing that's
most important to you.
Takumi...
Oh, Father...
I wonder...
Did you know?
Did you realize... that the
HiME would eventually have
to fight each other?
After all, it is your
destiny as HiME.
[AKIRA] That's why I was
told not to let anyone know
that I was a girl.
And to kill them
if they found out.
--[TAKUMI] Akira...?
--[AKIRA gasps]
[sighs]
Well? How are you feeling?
All right, thanks.
I'm feeling a lot better.
[AKIRA sighs]
That's good.
You found out!
Now that you know my secret...
...you'll have to die!
[TAKUMI groans]
That's okay.
[AKIRA gasps]
If this is something that
you know you've gotta do,
then do it.
There's so many times... I'd be
gone if you hadn't saved me.
Right...? [groans]
Besides, I'm used to
giving up anyway. [groans]
Takumi...
You serious...?
Dead serious.
To be honest...
...I'm tired of it.
Tired of all this suffering.
I haven't said
anything till now,
but my sister's sacrificed
so much for me. [groans]
So...
[whimpers]
[TAKUMI whimpers]
[sighs]
[AKIRA pants]
[coughs]
Why'd... you...?
[AKIRA]
You fool!
How can you give up
on life so easily?!
That's the one thing about
you that I can't stand!
The... one thing...
...I hate about you!
[sobs]
[TAKUMI]
Akira...
Sorry about what I said.
[TAKUMI sighs]
I should be apologizing.
I mean...
...you did tell me
to knock first...
[gasps]
[groans]
Ah!
Forget that! It was
just your imagination.
[TAKUMI]
Hmph.
I'm so sorry.
Now you're even missing classes
because of me and my brother.
[sighs]
Yeah... Well, uh...
I wasn't really into going
to class today anyway.
Well, I sure appreciate it.
[AKIRA sighs]
[MAI]
Takumi, you're going to be okay.
I'll protect you; I promise.
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
Now what?
What do I do?
The most precious... person.
--[knocking]
--Huh?
[MASASHI]
Sorry to come barging in here.
Why, hello there, Takeda.
If you're looking for Natsuki,
she's taken the day off.
Uh. What makes you think
I'm looking for Kuga?
Then you came to see me?
Oh, my goodness...
You are very nice
and all, but...
It's not that!
[SHIZURU]
Hmph.
For the last six months,
I've stayed clear of Tate,
just like I said I would.
I'm sure that he's settled
any issues that he had by now.
So I want him back in my club.
I suppose.
I don't have any problems
with it personally.
But Tate seems to be
preoccupied lately.
Huh?
[YUKARIKO]
Isn't it terrible?
I'm the one who's supposed to
give guidance to the students.
And look at me...
Yukariko...
[ISHIGAMI] Anyway,
let's be calm about this.
Drink up. I'm quite
skilled at making tea.
Perhaps even more so
than painting.
You're right.
It's delicious.
Come on.
What're you so on edge for?
Weren't you just told not to
go around looking for a fight?
Yeah...
[MAI] If you're too cautious,
you could quickly be
taken advantage of when
something happens.
We've gotta be calm now and--
[yelps]
Mai!
[MAI groans]
Who did that?
[BOY A]
Sorry.
[MAI]
Uh?
[BOY A groans]
[REITO]
Are you all right, Mai?
Reito?
[gasps]
Uh, Mai. Your skirt.
It's kinda...
[MAI]
Huh?
[MAI gasps]
Oh, my gosh!
I'm glad you weren't
hurt or... anything.
Uh, please forget about it.
Oh. No problem.
I'm just happy that we
get to talk like this.
Lately, I've had
this funny feeling
that you've been avoiding me.
It's not like I'm...
trying to avoid you.
[REITO]
I'm sorry, Mai.
I apologize for
trying to do that.
I wasn't even thinking
about your feelings.
[REITO] Guess I was right all
along about you and Tate...
[MAI]
Uh, hang on a second!
I don't have any special
feelings for Tate!
[MAI]
Even if I did like somebody...
...I've got too many
things going on right now.
I don't have time
for that kinda stuff.
What do you mean?
Is something the matter?
--[cell phone rings]
--[gasps]
[REITO]
Go ahead and get it.
I won't be long.
Hello?
[gasps]
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
Sure! I'll be right there.
[pants]
Oh! Reito! Watch Mikoto for me!
[BOTH]
Hmm.
[MAI]
Is it true?
Yes. There's finally a heart
donor for your brother...
[gasps]
[NURSE A] All right.
Time for your sponge bath.
[SHIHO groans]
Uh, here.
I've got a change
of pajamas for you.
[squeals]
[YUICHI]
Huh...? [yells]
How embarrassing...
You're such a pervert...
[YUICHI grunts]
[NURSE B] Off you go, you're
gonna have to leave the room.
[SHIHO]
Huh?
Or maybe you want
to take our place?
[YUICHI, SHIHO groan]
[NURSES laugh]
Why do I always make
a fool of myself?
Tate?
Huh? Tokiha?
[YUICHI]
The States, huh?
Well, good for Takumi.
[MAI]
Yeah.
But this is where things
are gonna get complicated.
You've got it rough, too.
You're here taking care of
Shiho around the clock.
I guess. Then again...
...it was my fault she got
hurt in the first place.
[YUICHI sighs] I think you're
pretty amazing, though.
[MAI grunts]
Meaning...?
[YUICHI] Sorry. I know you hate
being told stuff like this,
but you've got enough
on your hands worrying
about Takumi and
his health problems.
Then on top of that, you've got
to deal with being a HiME
and fighting Orphans.
And then there was all
that trouble at the school.
[YUICHI] You know,
I wanted to find something
I could do to help.
But there wasn't anything,
and worse, I left Shiho alone
and she ended up hurt.
[YUICHI]
It's always like this!
I get all psyched up,
I convince myself that
I can deal with a problem,
but in the end, I panic and
end up screwing up big time.
Tate...
[YUICHI sighs] Now I think
I finally understand
all the problems you
had to go through.
I'm sorry for...
...you know...
Well, for not being
very considerate.
Where's all this coming from?!
It's not like you at all!
I mean, why would you
say this now?
After everything...
It's complicated.
I mean... Shiho and I have known
each other since we were kids,
and she's always
called me "Brother,"
which kinda drives me
crazy, sometimes.
[YUICHI]
But still...
...that's why...
...I'm just...
[MAI sighs]
You take care, Tate.
Sure.
You take care, too.
[SHIHO]
Huh?
[YUICHI]
Hey, you feel better now?
Brother, were you
just with someone?
[YUICHI]
Hmm? No.
I was reading
magazines downstairs.
[SHIHO]
Mm.
Did you read anything
interesting?
[YUICHI]
Eh. Not really.
Nothing that you'd be into.
[crow caws]
"I'm rooting for ya"?
It's stupid to say that.
And stupider to believe it.
Besides, Mai, I already know
you're doing your best.
[gasps]
Oh, jeez...
Must be something in my eye...
Now, I'd better
get back quick
and tell Takumi the great news!
[NAGI]
All right, then.
I suppose now is the time
for the young Obsidian Prince
to be awakened.
--[crows cawwing]
--[gasps]
[sighs]
[NAGI] The fact is,
you'll have to fight.
There's no way any of you
can avoid that fate.
[NAGI] Besides,
that's really what you and
the other HiME are here for.
[grunts]
[flute whistling]
[MAI]
Huh?
[whistling continues]
[NAGI]
It's starting.
What?
You...
[WHITE HIME]
Leave this place now.
[screeches]
A HiME?!
[SHIHO] Brother, are you sure
you weren't with someone?
[YUICHI]
Uh, yeah.
[SHIHO]
Oh... Then what about me?
--[YUICHI] Yeah, but that--
--[SHIHO] I knew it!
You stupid, stupid idiot!
[YUICHI] I seriously think I'm
a goner, on so many levels.
[MAI] If that was supposed to
be funny, it wasn't.