[MIYU] Eclipse 1 Artemis
reached its objective,
with an error of two
meters East-Southeast.
Certainly within
acceptable range.
And I'm pleased to say the
target has been obliterated.
Wonderful. Thank you, Miyu.
Now... I have a message to
send to the entire Golden Fleet.
[ALYSSA] Tell them to open
the door to Valhalla.
[GREER]
I can't believe this...
How could you do such a thing?
You have no right to
criticize me.
Especially after you
wasted all my time.
Just keep quiet and watch.
It's almost time.
But before that...
...we have lots to do.
Did you see that
blast last night?
Yeah, the smoke was unreal.
[BOY C]
I thought it was an earthquake.
[BOY D]
Me too; it hit really hard.
[GIRL A] You think it was
lightning again?
[GIRL B] What if it was a
missile from somewhere?
[BOY E]
It's definitely weird.
There's nothing in
the papers about it.
[MIYA]
Yeah, I know.
It's weird...
That there's no mention
of it on TV either.
That bridge really did
collapse, didn't it?
[CHIE] It went down
like a ton of bricks!
I haven't been able to get
online since last night, though,
so I can't even fish for rumors.
[groans]
How did things turn out
like that anyway?
We're gonna be really
late for school, you know.
[SHIHO growls]
Look, I'm telling you, I dunno
what got into me last night.
It's not a big deal, okay?
[SHIHO]
Hmph!
[YUICHI groans]
[tolls]
Okay. Let's start homeroom.
Sit down and--
--[SADAOKA] Tanks!
--Huh?
[CHIE]
Tanks?! What?
Yeah, over there!
Whaddaya mean, tanks?
[CHIE]
This is major.
[SAYURI]
What's going on?
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[GIRL D]
Are they shooting a movie?
[STUDENTS murmuring, chattering]
[BOY F] It's not
an emergency drill, is it?
[ISHIGAMI gasps]
Oh, no!
[BOY G]
It's Suzushiro!
Is that Haruka?!
[CHIE]
Wow, there she goes.
That's our fearless leader of
the Executive Committee for you.
[MIYA] She might be in
over her head this time...
[gasps]
[SAYURI]
She kicked it!
And again
Executive Committee leader
single-handedly attacks a tank.
[MIYA]
Oh, no! The soldiers are coming!
[STUDENTS gasping]
Haruka!
They're armed!
--[door slams]
--[STUDENTS gasping]
Hang on! What're
you guys trying to--
[YUKARIKO]
Lord, our Father.
May you bless this day
with peace and tranquility.
[door slams]
Sister, over here!
[YUKARIKO]
Mr. Ishigami?
[MIYU]
B-1 secured.
C-1 through C-7 secured.
Areas E and F secured.
B-2 through B-5 secured.
And D-1 has been surrounded.
[ALYSSA]
Good.
Then I guess it's time
to get going, Miyu.
You're right. Of course, Miss.
Deploy Einferia.
[sighs]
I guess there's no point in
hiding in the bathroom forever.
[MAI gasps]
[MAI] This is
actually the girls'...
[gasps]
Miss Mashiro, they'll
be here any minute now.
[MASHIRO]
Mm-hmm.
Good afternoon,
Miss Mashiro Kazahana.
[MASHIRO] Is this the
method of your country?
Using force to get what you
want, Miss Alyssa Searrs?
[MIYU] Any means is acceptable
in order to carry out
the mission of the
Searrs Foundation.
[ALYSSA]
The Valkyries...
The power of those
maidens you call HiME
ought to be put to use by
more appropriate people...
...right, Queen of Hades?
[MASHIRO]
You certainly are well-informed.
You've obviously
done your homework.
But let me remind you.
Students who disobey school
rules must be severely punished.
I understand.
You have permission
to fire on her
if she decides
to put up a fight.
Just make sure you
bring her in alive.
We have captured Mai Tokiha.
Will I be able to talk to her?
Not any time soon, I imagine.
You could give it
a try, if you like.
[groans]
K-Kazu...
Please... Kazu...
--[door opens]
--[NATSUKI] Hmm?
They've just put their
plans into action.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Under a direct command
from the Japanese Government,
we have been deployed
for your protection.
We ask that you remain calm,
and obey our instructions.
There is currently
a communications ban.
And I'm sure you know that the
bridge was destroyed last night.
There's a good possibility that
the people responsible
have escaped onto
the academy grounds.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, and they're probably
armed with more
of the same explosives,
as well as a new
and deadly virus strain.
We're asking for
your cooperation.
Well. Whatever will you do
if we refuse, I wonder?
Don't wonder.
Refusal is not an option.
[SHIZURU]
Is that so?
--[cats growling, yowling]
--[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
[growling continues]
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
[squeals]
[MIKOTO]
Mai?!
What's going on around here?
[YUICHI]
Great...
Hey, Shiho. You go on home.
I'm gonna have a look
around here a little more.
No way...
I wanna go where you're going.
[sighs]
You better not slow me down.
[gasps]
Miyu... Alyssa.
Why are you doing this?
[ALYSSA]
Because it is necessary.
We must acquire the power
of the Valkyries, the HiME.
Therefore, we need you
and Fuka Academy--
That's no reason!
[gasps]
[MIYU] I'm sure you understand
what will happen
if you use your powers.
This sword has the
power to neutralize
Highly-Advanced
Materializing Equipment.
I can defeat you all
if I have to.
Miyu...
Please...
[MIYU]
Now, tell me.
Where are Mikoto Minagi, Natsuki
Kuga, and Yukariko Sanada?
Also, are there any other
HiME that I should know about?
I don't know.
And I wouldn't tell you
even if I knew!
You saw the bridge
collapse, I'm sure.
If you don't tell us, we'll do
the same to the entire school,
destroying you HiME
and all of the students.
[whimpers]
I don't get it.
You two were so beautiful
in the park that day...
It doesn't make sense!
How can you be so cold?!
I know that you have
compassion; I've seen it!
The bond between
Miyu and I is stronger
than the bond between others.
But that has nothing to do with
our feelings toward you people.
[MIKOTO yells]
Mikoto!
[MIYU grunts]
[MIKOTO yells]
Let's go!
[MAI]
Hmph!
You won't get away from me!
[gasps]
[MIKOTO grunts]
[ALYSSA grunts]
[ALYSSA groans]
Are you all right?
Don't push yourself.
You shouldn't summon
so many Orphans.
I'm okay now.
Thanks for helping, Miyu.
[YAMADA] Those guys
aren't regular military.
And I've heard that the
Searrs Foundation controls
a large private army
that operates strictly
on a for-profit basis.
[NATSUKI]
Do you think that's them?
[YAMADA]
Probably.
There's definitely
something wrong with this.
--What?
--I'm gonna sneak out
and see what's going on.
You stay right here
until I get back.
Uh... Sure thing.
[OFFICER A] We're going to
conduct a basic health exam
of all you students.
There's a strong possibility
that the people responsible
for the bombing have released
a virus in this area.
[GIRLS gasping, murmuring]
[NAO growls]
Now, why would you
only examine the girls?
Yeah! Come up with
a better explanation
if you want our help! 'Cause
so far, we're not buying it!
I hope it's not...
Begin your search
of the school grounds.
The gates to
the road to Valhalla
must be somewhere in this area.
What're you just
standing there for?
Get over there and
help them with the search.
[GREER]
Err, yes.
[NAGI] They sure are making
a big show outta all this.
But this is gonna
cost you big time...
...Alyssa Searrs.
[YAYOI groans]
Oh, don't cry.
Hey, guys! Can't you try to
handle this a little better?
Let me talk to
someone in charge!
Or else I'm gonna
create some real trouble!
[AKIRA]
I knew it. It's them.
[FEMALE SOLDIER grunts, groans]
[thump]
Right!
O, Lord...
why is this happening?
Please give me some guidance.
Men are all the same,
even if they are soldiers!
--[SOLDIERS grunting]
--[NAO giggles]
Yukino, escape and make
contact with the outside.
Huh?!
I don't know what this
virus thing is about,
but I'm not gonna
sit back and do nothing.
You go make an
official complaint.
But...!
Here goes...
[wails]
My stomach!
I have a chronic
gastritis condition!
[groans]
--Wha...?
--[SOLDIER A] Huh?
[HARUKA grunts]
Move it, Yukino!
--[YUKINO gasps]
--[SOLDIER A grunts]
Haruka!
Go! Hurry up, Yukino!
[SOLDIER B grunts]
Takumi...
[MIKOTO]
What should we do, Mai?
If only we could get in touch
with the other HiME somehow...
[SHIHO screams]
[gasps]
Brother...!
[whimpers]
[YUICHI growls]
--Tate!
--Tokiha!
[MAI whimpers]
[MIKOTO growls]
I'll take care of these things!
Just go!
This way!
--[YUICHI grunts]
--[SHIHO gasps]
[pants]
Would ya mind telling
me what's going on?
Who are those guys?
I can't say...
Cut it out, would ya?!
Don't pull that on me again!
The whole school
is involved now!
[SHIHO growls]
Fine, then...
"HiME"?
Yeah. That's what they
call me and the other girls
who have these special powers.
We've been brought to
this school for a reason.
We're here in order to fight
monsters called Orphans.
Like the ones back there, and
the one you saw underground.
Or, that was the plan.
[MIYU] Midori Sugiura, Nao
Yuuki, and Yukino Kikukawa...
The three of them have escaped.
Oh? It wasn't hard to get them
to expose themselves after all.
[giggles]
So you're saying that
these guys are taken over
because they're after
the power of HiME?
[MAI]
Mm-hmm.
Then, if you people all left,
they would, too!
Shiho!
I'm right, aren't I?
Why should the whole school
have to get involved?!
It's got nothing to do with us!
--Stop it, Shiho!
--It's not like it's my fault!
[SHIHO growls]
[MAI sighs]
[MIKOTO]
Mai!
[BOTH gasp]
There's a cave over that way!
Hmm?
Mai? Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
You hide here
for a little while.
We're gonna head back
to the school.
--Hey, Tokiha--
--[SHIHO grunts]
[YUICHI groans]
[MAI, MIKOTO pant]
I didn't-- It's not my--
[MIKOTO]
Hmm? Um, Mai?
I always saw myself
as a victim in all this.
I mean, it's not like I asked
for any of this to happen!
I didn't want HiME powers,
or the school to get involved.
And now all this...!
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MAI]
Why'd you stop?
There's one over there!
[gasps]
Guess we gotta fight.
It's our only choice.
There's no other way, seeing as
we're the only ones with powers.
[MIKOTO]
I like when you laugh and smile.
I don't like it when
you're sad and crying.
How can I make you smile again?
Huh? Good question...
I wish there was no fighting.
I wish I was just
going to school,
working at my part-time job,
and hanging out with friends.
That's how
Then let's make it happen!
[MAI]
Hmm... Mikoto...
[MIKOTO growls]
[NAGI]
Looking good.
Keep up the nice work.
Nice of you to finally show up!
So I guess this is a
big enough crisis for you?!
Remember the underground shrine?
Anyway, if you can manage to
make it there, you'll be safe.
Good luck finding your way.
Come back!
[MIKOTO grunts]
Mai!
[gasps]
[groans]
Gimme a break!
What's the matter, Mai?!
I can't summon Kagutsuchi
when it's like this.
Call him! Let's get 'em all!
Not on humans!
--[gasps]
--[SOLDIERS grunting]
[gasps]
Natsuki!
Close your eyes!
Duran!
[NATSUKI]
Load Flash Cartridge!
Fire!
[MIKOTO screams]
The Valkyries have escaped
from the academy perimeter.
[ALYSSA]
Miyu.
How much longer do we
have to wait until Artemis
is in position to fire again?
[MIYU]
Eleven hours and 52 minutes.
[NATSUKI]
I see.
What about Midori
and the others?
[MAI]
I dunno.
Either they've been caught
or they've somehow escaped.
[NATSUKI] I still can't
believe a place like this
was under the school
all this time.
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[MAN IN BLACK A]
I been waiting for you.
[GIRLS gasp]
[MAN IN BLACK A]
Come right this way.
Hey. What do you think
about this guy?
Can we trust him?
[NATSUKI]
Hmm. We're covered.
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSUKI]
Huh...?
What is that thing?!
[gasps]
[MIKOTO]
Sister! Nao!
[MIDORI]
Hey! Is everyone all right?!
Midori, you're here!
Yukino, too?
[MIKOTO laughs]
Hey!
[MASHIRO]
My dear HiME...
[MASHIRO] I am pleased
that you've all made it here.
Obsidian Palace.
Lying at the very core,
it's the last fortress
protecting the land of Fuka.
[FUMI giggles]
[gasping]
[MAI]
What a shocker!
Sister and Yukino
are HiME, too?!
[MIDORI]
Now, we've got everyone!
We've got a commander
and an underground base!
It's time to hit them back!
I can't wait!
[MAI]
Can't wait, huh?
[MIDORI]
What's the matter?
[MAI groans] I just don't know
if I share your excitement.