[MAI]
Here.
Hey. Thanks, Sis.
How do you feel?
Any better now?
A little bit, I guess.
Didn't I tell ya it
wasn't a good idea
to take the boat there.
I don't know why you always
want to do things that'll
make you sick.
Heh. But the boat's fun.
So what if I get seasick?
Okay. If you say so.
[TAKUMI]
I hope it's a nice place.
[MAI]
Hm?
[TAKUMI]
Our new school, I mean.
[MAI]
We'll know soon enough.
The ocean air sure is fresh.
This trip's definitely gonna be
good for your health, Takumi.
[PASSENGERS chatter]
[TAKUMI
That's totally amazing!
I'm so glad we came
by boat. It's great.
C'mon. We didn't come here
to go sightseeing, silly.
[MAI gasps]
[TAKUMI]
You seeing things again?
[MAI]
Huh?
Yeah. Beside the moon.
I was thinking how beautiful
that small red speck is.
Huh?
My eyesight's good,
but I don't see anything.
[MAI]
That's no big surprise.
You know how the saying goes.
Some things can only be seen
by people who're honest.
Sure, whatever.
You're hilarious, sis.
[TAKUMI]
Huh?
Uh, Sis?
[MAI]
Hm?
Do you see that
thing in the water?
[MAI]
What thing?
[TAKUMI]
Look. Over there!
Huh?
[MAI]
Hm...
[PASSENGERS chatter]
[MAI gasps]
[PASSENGER chattering continues]
♪
Hurry! She's swallowed
a lot of water!
[CREW B]
Hey, what's that in her hand?
[CREW C]
How should I know?
She was holding it
when I dragged her out.
[CREW A] She won't let go
of it. C'mon, help us out here!
I can't believe this.
Hey, kid, think you
can give us a hand?
Uh, me?
What's she clutching
onto that thing for?
[CREW B grunts]
[CREW 1-B]
Hang on a second...
Hurry it up.
[grunts]
There. Got it!
[CREW shout]
[BOTH gasp]
[CREW A]
Never mind about us!
The girl needs CPR!
She's not breathing!
A-All right!
What was the first part of
artificial resuscitation, again?
Does anybody here
know how to do CPR?
[PASSENGERS murmur]
[MAI]
Uh...
Man, why me?
[YUICHI grunts]
[SHIHO]
No!
What'd you do that for?!
Cause you had a perverted
look in your eyes!
Gimme a break! I've got
work to do here!
--[SHIHO] No!
--[YUICHI grunts]
[SHIHO] I can't stand it
when you turn into a pervert
like that!
[YUICHI] There's nothing
perverted about it!
We've gotta do something.
[MAI]
Hm...
Move over!
I know what to do.
O...kay. No arguments here.
[gasps]
[YUICHI]
What're you waiting for?!
I know what I'm doing.
[MAI exhales]
[MAI grunts, exhales]
[coughs, pants]
[PASSENGERS chatter]
[MAI sighs]
[YUICHI]
Hm!
[MAI]
Hm.
[sighs]
Nice, Sis.
I'll say. That was impressive.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
It's no big deal.
Never know when your First
Aid's gonna come in handy.
Who would've thought it'd be to
save a drowned girl like this.
[sneezes]
[MAI]
I'm all wet.
[TAKUMI] Here. You don't
wanna catch a cold.
[MAI]
Thanks, Takumi.
What?! What're you
staring at, creep?!
I wasn't looking at
your chest! Really!
Really? That's not what I saw.
What's your problem?!
You're disgusting!
Wait! Lemme explain.
I was just...
Now you're on my case?
Quit crowding me, here!
Whatever, pervert!
[YUICHI]
I don't think so!
[YAMADA]
I can't see the girl anywhere.
She might've been
picked up by a ferry.
[NATSUKI]
What?
[MITOKO groans]
Miroku...
[metallic clang]
[MAI]
Hm.
Oh!
[MAI]
Hm.
Unbelievable.
What's Takumi's problem?
He didn't take his
afternoon medicine.
He's gonna get it.
[MAI]
Huh?
How'd I end up with the
same mark as her?
[MAI]
Huh?
[yelps]
Why'd I have to be so helpful
and do CPR on that girl?
There's only one way to see it.
That girl was my first kiss.
Hold on!
Mouth-to-mouth doesn't
count as a first kiss!
I was doing CPR.
That's all it was!
Nobody could say that
was a first kiss, 'cause...
'Cause it wasn't like that.
Huh?
Aw!
A change of clothes.
I knew I forgot something.
Huh?
I guess this leaves
me no other choice.
[sighs] It's an unfortunate
series of events, that's all.
Oh yeah? So then you
guys are taking this ferry
'cause your on the way
to your new school.
You got it.
Cool. So which school is it?
It's an independent
school and--
[MAI]
Takumi!
[TAKUMI]
Huh?
[YUICHI, SHIHO]
Hm?
Where've you been?
I've been looking for you.
Your uniform.
Why're you wearing that?
[giggles]
You noticed.
I guess I put all my regular
clothes in the checked luggage.
If that's your school uniform,
then you must be
transferring to our school!
[gasps]
Y'mean...
Too funny. We're all gonna be
students of Fuka Academy.
[SHIHO]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Yeah... right.
[WAITRESS A]
Here you are.
I'm really sorry about my
brother making a total fool
of himself.
I'm an innocent victim here.
Oh, yeah. My name's
Takumi Tokiha.
I'll be going into first
year of middle school.
I apologize for my
sister's behavior.
What're you doing, Takumi?
I'm Yuichi Tate.
First year high school.
And I'm Shiho Munakata!
Second year, middle school!
Mind letting me go?
Your surnames are different.
Parents aren't married, then?
That's right-- I mean,
you got it all wrong. You see,
Shiho and I have been friends
since we were little kids.
What? Then you're not
brother and sister?!
No chance!
He's basically my brother!
And you're traveling on
the ferry by yourselves,
unchaperoned?
Correct!
Would you knock it off
and give me some space?
[giggles]
Wow! It's true when they
say that rural people
are more progressive.
Uh, you're being rude, sis.
Enough!
[grunts] She followed me;
we're not traveling together!
And she's being a total
pain in the butt!
Are you serious?
[YUICHI groans]
Now look what happened.
He made that poor girl cry.
Rude, Mai. Totally rude.
So! What's your story?
Oh. My name's Mai. Mai Tokiha.
I'm Takumi's genuine
older sister.
I'll be going into
first year of high school,
pleased to meet
your acquaintance!
Oh... We're in the same grade?
Beg your pardon?!
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, there you are. Hi guys!
[ALL]
Huh?
[YAMADA]
I can see it. Up there.
[MAI] Doesn't it seem kinda
strange to you, though?
If the captain wanted to thank
us for helping in the rescue,
you think he'd come and
see us personally.
Just look outside.
There's no way he's gonna leave
the bridge in this kinda fog.
Gimme a break.
You think I'm stupid
or something?
[YUICHI groans] You have
been whining since we met,
so whaddaya expect?
I tried to be nice,
but I'm fed up.
"The fare's too high."
"What do the
waitresses get paid?"
I don't know and frankly,
my dear, I don't really care.
[gasps] I was doing you a favor,
trying to lighten things up and
give you a chance to
make it up to me,
after your sexual harassment.
You just don't understand,
do you?!
Wha...? Sexual harassment?!
You're blowing this thing
totally out of proportion!
You, my friend, are delusional.
Oh, yeah? You're one to
talk about delusions!
As in your girlfriend!
"Brother"!
Isn't that what she calls you?
You must think you're hot stuff,
but you don't fool me.
I already told ya.
You got it all wrong!
I'm only describing what
I saw, nothing more.
There's a cruiser coming
in from the stern!
[HELMSMAN A]
Captain!
It's an Emergency, men!
Hard over!
[BOTH yelp]
[MAI, YUICHI grunt]
[gasps]
Oh, man. What on earth
was that all about?
[MAI]
Hm?
[YUICHI gasps]
[MAI]
Huh?!
[MAI gasps]
Wait, hang on a sec!
Stupid! Pervert! Sicko!
Hey, c'mon, that was
an accident!
I didn't plan it!
[MAI]
Huh?
[YUICHI grunts]
[MAI gasps]
[MAI grunts]
[NATSUKI] You picked up the girl
with the sword. Where is she?
What?
What in the world
was that about?
Did you get in touch
with the coast guard?
I can't get through!
It seems like our
transmissions are jammed!
It must be that boat!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Attention, all passengers.
This is an important
announcement.
We're experiencing strong
tidal currents and--
[MAI gasps, groans]
[MAI gasps]
What do you want from me?
[MAI grunts]
[MAI gasps]
[MAI gasps, grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
What?!
[MITOKO]
Hm.
[MAI gasps]
--[NATSUKI gasps]
--[MITOKO shouts]
[ALL shout]
[YUICHI grunts]
Can't believe it.
She really punched me hard.
[CREW F]
Hey! What was that noise?!
[CREW G]
It was from mid-ship!
[CREW F]
Oh! The infirmary!
[YUICHI]
Huh?
Where'd Mai go?!
[MITOKO grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Don't think about it!
You've caused me
enough trouble already.
[MAI grunts]
[gasps]
Those guys are only using
you for their own objective!
Why don't you
understand that?!
[MITOKO grunts]
[NATSUKI] I can't let any
more of them congregate
on Fuka territory.
The Hime!
[MITOKO grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Don't!
[MITOKO grunts]
[MAI yelps]
[NATSUKI grunts]
Hime...?
So I guess I'm
wasting my breath?
[grunts]
Sorry to hear that.
'Cause I'll have
to get serious.
[grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Duran!
[howls]
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Go!
[MITOKO grunts]
[gasps]
[MITOKO grunts, yells]
[MAI yelps]
[YUICHI, CREW A grunt]
[YUICHI]
Fire!
Stay back!
[alarm buzzes]
[NATSUKI grunts]
[MITOKO grunts]
What's going on?
[CAPTAIN A]
Attention passengers.
It appears that a fire has
broken out on the vehicle deck.
Move it, kid!
[YUICHI]
Uh, yeah.
Coming!
[YUICHI gasps]
Hm? It's her!
Hey!
[MAI gasps]
[CREW A]
The crew will assist you!
Please remain calm and evacuate
as quickly as possible!
C'mon. Hurry up, you two!
[TAKUMI]
But my sister!
[SHIHO]
I can't find my brother!
I'm sure they got
on another lifeboat!
Now, hurry!
[TAKUMI]
Wait!
[SHIHO]
But Yuichi!
Don't you worry!
[SHIHO]
No!
There you go!
[MAI grunts]
Thanks.
No prob.
[MAI gasps]
[YUICHI gasps]
[MAI sighs]
[gasps]
[YUICHI grunts]
--What was that back there?!
--[YUICHI] Hang on...
[BOTH grunting]
Tell me! What happened
a couple of minutes ago!
Would you mind telling me
what you're talking about?
You sure pack a mean punch.
[MAI]
Hm. I know.
Consider us even for what
happened earlier, okay?
Sound like a good deal?
What are you talking about?
The sexual harassment.
Would you drop that?!
Yes, I'm going to.
This is what I'm saying.
[YUICHI, MAI pant]
[MAI]
Takumi...
It looks like everyone
abandoned ship in a big hurry.
I'm starting to dread what'll
happen next on this trip.
Hey. What kind of place
is Fuka Academy, anyway?
It's not some kinda creepy
school or anything, is it?
You've been watching
too many horror movies.
It's just your average
private school.
All right.
Tomorrow's gonna be
a normal school day.
C'mon, let's get outta here.
And don't complain about
losing your stuff!
[gasps]
Aw...
[YUICHI]
Hey, don't do this to me.
C'mon!
[NATSUKI, MITOKO grunting]
That was your
last chance, Hime.
That's it. You are
finished here.
[MAI grunts]
It's gone! I can't find it!
It's not here! Where is it?!
What're you asking me for?!
[MAI gasps]
You're looking for what?
[MAI] A little container!
There's medicine in it!
[MITOKO, NATSUKI grunting]
Duran!
Load Silver Cartridge!
[NATSUKI]
Fire!
This wouldn't be what
you're looking for...?
[MITOKO grunts]
[MAI gasps]
That's it!
[MAI yelps]
[grunts]
[YUICHI gasps]
[MAI gasps]
[yelps]
[gasps]
[MAI]
Oh my god!
Hey!
[YUICHI]
Huh?
Give that to Takumi!
I'm counting on you!
Right! If I can
stay alive, that is!
[MAI]
This is ridiculous!
There's no way I'm going to
die in a place like this!
[gasps]
[MAI grunts]
[MAI]
Huh? What the...?!
[DURAN howls]
[gasps, grunts]
Duran!
Those flames!
[gasps]
What's this light?!
[NATSUKI]
Hey!
[MAI]
Huh?
[MAI grunts]
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
So that's what you are.
[MAI]
Huh?
Then I guess... you can see
that star near the moon as well.
Uh...
[MAI]
Hm...
That stupid fool!
It's going exactly the
way they wanted it to!
Hey, girl!
Take my warning.
Don't go to Fuka Academy.
[MAI gasps]
If you go, you will die.
[MAI]
Die?
[MAI gasps]
Hm? Oh, no!
[MAI screams]
[screams]
[YUICHI gasps]
I think she's still in there!
What?!
[TAKUMI]
No way... Mai!
Mai!
[NAGI yawns]
I thought this wait
would never end.
Unbelievable.
Oh well, it's over.
Mai-Hime plus one, welcome.
And now, on with
the arrangements!
[MAI grunts]
[MAI]
Huh?
[MAI gasps]
[gasps]
[MAI]
Where am I?
[STUDENTS murmur]
No way...
--[SHIHO gasps]
--[YUICHI] Look. There she is.
[chuckles]
[MAI shouts]
♪
[SHIHO] Hey. I thought this
was supposed to be a steamy,
burning hot story
set in a school.
[TAKUMI] It was burning.
The ferry and all those cars.
[SHIHO]
No. That's not what I meant.
[TAKUMI] The next episode
will take place at school.
[SHIHO gasps]
Will there be passion?
[TAKUMI]
Yup. Burning passion.