[HARUKA]
Now explain yourself!
What were you doing
sprawled out on the lawn?!
Eh-heh... Funny you ask.
[MAI] Actually, I don't
really know myself.
[HARUKA growls]
You enter school property
after visiting hours
with a totally
questionable stranger!
Then, you selfishly damage
our beautiful lawn--
the student's one place
for some peace and quiet.
You presented yourself in
a totally inappropriate manner!
While offending and
polluting the minds,
sensitivity, and moral
decency of our students
with your obscene display.
And on top of everything,
you bring a weapon here!
[MAI sighs]
[MAI groans]
[HARUKA] I want a good
explanation for all of this!
Are you listening to me?!
[MAI]
Uh...
I'm waiting, Mai Tokiha!
[REITO]
Now, now.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Haruka. Why don't you have a cup
of tea and chill out a little?
Huh? You, too, Mai.
Before it gets cold.
'Kay. Thanks.
[HARUKA growls]
Oh, this is so good.
So...
I'm Kanzaki, third year.
Class Vice President.
Nice to meet you.
--Hello.
--[HARUKA growls]
I don't care if you are
the vice president, Reito!
You should just
stay out of this one!
[gasps]
[HARUKA gasps] It's the
Executive Committee's job
to maintain a proper
atmosphere at the school
and to ensure the safety
of our fellow students!
Oh, Haruka...
[REITO] Now, now. You don't
need to get so uptight.
[HARUKA] I'm so sick
of your "now, now!"
People like you always
wanna let these miscreants
off the hook,
but you're only making
the Executive
Committee's job harder!
We're the ones
that have to answer
for all the strange things
that've been going on
around here lately!
[REITO]
Now, now.
[HARUKA growls]
There you go again!
[MAI]
Huh?
There's someone here
to visit the accused.
[MAI]
Hmph! Who'd that be?
[TAKUMI]
Sis!
[gasps]
Huh? Takumi!
--[TAKUMI] Mai!
--Oh. Thank goodness.
[TAKUMI sighs]
I was worried about you.
[MAI sighs]
I'm sorry.
[HARUKA groans]
[SHIZURU]
Miss Suzushiro.
It's the Executive
Committee's responsibility
to ensure safety in the school.
Isn't that correct?
Uh, yes. Of course.
It is, President Fujino.
I knew you'd agree.
Then perhaps you should be
celebrating the fact
that Miss Tokiha
has come to our school.
[giggles]
[growls]
Now Takumi. Don't cry.
[MAI]
Ugh! I can't believe it!
What's Suzushiro's
problem, anyway?!
Acting like she's more
important than everyone!
It's nauseating!
The Executive Committee
officers are on edge
with all the strange
stuff going on.
I can't say
I blame them, either.
She's only a student
though, right?
Yeah, but at Fuka Academy,
the student council
is responsible for governing the
discipline of the other pupils.
It's part of the
academy's slogan--
it's a school run by the
students for the students.
So what's your story?
How did you become a member
of the student council?
You hardly seem the type.
Thanks for the
unsolicited opinion.
I'm not an officer or anything.
I'm only helping out.
Underling.
[YUICHI]
Whatever.
Make that "lackey."
[YUICHI]
Shut up!
--[clicking]
--[MAI] Hmm?
[MAI]
Hmm...
[YUICHI]
Hey, wait.
What happened to that girl
we found on the ferry?
Huh? Oh, her.
She's in the infirmary.
Still hasn't come to,
as far as I know.
[YUICHI] Hey, about
that time on the ferry...
Huh?
Uh, never mind.
There's only so many
near-death experiences
a guy can handle in a week.
[MAI]
Hmm.
Just for the record,
I don't remember begging
for your help back there.
Don't blame me for your choices.
My bad.
Sorry I ever got involved.
You're not cute at all.
[MAI growls]
[TAKUMI]
Hey, guys...?
Huh?
Uh, is this it?
The staff room?
Get this straight!
I don't want anything to do
with you or that girl
who almost drowned!
If you wanna be irresponsible,
you're on your own!
Do whatever you want!
[MAI]
Hmph.
[YUICHI Man, despite all that,
I'm still stuck with her.
[MAI giggles]
I'm Mai Tokiha.
It's nice to meet you all.
[CHIE]
Hi, Tokiha!
[MAI squeals]
[gasps]
Little ticklish around there?
Sorry.
[MAI groans]
Um, do you want something?
Nope. Figured I'd say hi though,
since we'll be neighbors.
You wanna have lunch with us?
The food in the cafeteria
here is pretty good!
Sure.
[AOI giggles]
Considering it's school food,
sure is expensive.
Think so?
You gotta pay for quality.
The students love the food here.
[MAI]
Right...
[gasps]
He's adorable!
He must be in middle school.
[MAI]
Huh?
Oh! Takumi! Over here!
Heh!
Mai. You know who that boy is?
[gasps]
This is my brother, Takumi.
He's in first year
of middle school.
Takumi, these are my classmates.
I'm Aoi Senou!
I can't wait to get to know you!
Chie Harada. The one-stop
shop for school news.
I know all the gossip.
The pleasure's mine.
[YUICHI sighs]
[SHIHO] Hey! Are you
sure there was nothing
between you and that
girl on the ferry?!
Between us?
Like what, for instance?
With that girl named Mai!
[YUICHI growls]
'Course not!
Now shut up and let me eat!
[SHIHO whines]
[YUICHI]
And stop lookin' at me!
[HARUKA] There's just something
about that Tokiha girl.
I don't like it.
I'm positive she's
hiding something.
[YUKINO] I-I don't really think
what happened on the ferry
has anything to do with what's
been going on here at school.
[HARUKA] You're wrong!
They're definitely related!
I've got a gut
feeling about this.
[YUKINO groans]
This would be so much easier
if the student council
wasn't so incompetent!
We have to get to the bottom
of this--the sooner the better!
I'll put that trouble-making
girl in her place!
Listen up, Yukino.
I want you to
keep an eye on Tokiha.
Anything strange happens,
you come straight to me!
[YUKINO]
Okay.
[MAI]
So what's the deal, Chie?
Everyone's talking about
strange stuff going on
at the school lately.
[CHIE]
Right.
Like a certain transfer student
creating crop circles, you mean?
[AOI]
We're lucky!
One of the world's unsolved
mysteries, right here!
Yeah, there's definitely lots
of weird stuff going on,
but the latest gossip is
all about you... Mai Tokiha.
How did you make this
crop circle anyway?
Heh. It's a long story...
[gasps]
Hey, who's that girl
with the long hair?
[CHIE]
Huh?
Natsuki Kuga.
You don't see her around much.
[AOI]
She always looks so pretty.
You mean she's one of
the students here?
Natsuki's in the
class beside us.
Although, she doesn't
show up very often,
[MAI]
Oh, great...
Where ya going?
[gasps]
Wait, Miss Sekisawa!
[YOKO]
Hmm?
Hmm. She's gone.
Sometimes things
simply get out of hand.
That's when it
becomes a problem.
[And clean up's no
piece of cake, either.
Ah, well... Who knows?
The people at headquarters
might be happy
about all the work
they're getting.
They knew, didn't they?
There was another girl
on that ferry.
From what I hear,
they knew all right. Yup.
They told me about her this
morning; quite the surprise.
The stupid fools.
[sniffs]
[KENDO GUY A]
Are you serious?
You mean that upperclassman
hasn't returned
to the kendo club since then?
[KENDO GUY B]
Nope.
I heard his injuries
were all healed up, too.
What a waste, huh?
[KENDO GUY A]
I mean, he was a regular
in national competitions, right?
Hey! Speed it up!
Lunch hour doesn't last all day!
[KENDO GUY A]
Okay! Coming!
Huh...?
It's gone! My lunch!
[yells] Somebody took my
super-spicy dynamite curry bun!
[MIKOTO whines]
[screams]
What's goin' on out here?!
Look, Captain!
[gasps]
Over there!
Who's there?!
Show yourself at once!
[yells]
[MIKOTO yells]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[gasps]
Ow...
[MIKOTO whines]
[NAO screams]
[MAI]
Wait!
[MASASHI]
Please, Sister Yukariko!
You have to believe us!
We saw it with our own two eyes.
It looked like some
kinda monster cat!
[KENDO GUY B]
No, it was a black demon!
It was the devil himself!
[KENDO GUY A] How come there
are so many creepy things
happening these days?
I understand.
No wonder you're
feeling anxious.
Rest assured though,
your fears are not all that
difficult to overcome.
All you have to do
is kneel before God.
Now, let's pray
together, shall we?
[gasps]
That's all we have to do?
Right. Calm your spirit,
and pray from the
bottom of your heart.
Pray, and you'll tame the
unbridled passions of youth
that are misleading you.
They're what's causing you to
see things that do not exist.
[giggles]
[MASASHI] Uh, what was
misleading us again?
[YUKARIKO]
Passion.
If you change it to
the passive voice,
the sentence structure
changes as well.
I hope you haven't
already forgotten this?
Okay, here's the next example:
"She wrote him a long letter."
Now, let's use
the passive voice.
Uh, Mr. Nakamura...
[MAI sighs]
Skipping class on the
very first day of school.
What am I doing? Ah!
[groans]
That's great.
Now I'm also getting all
covered in scratches.
[gasps]
What is this place?
May I help you with anything?
Ah! You didn't happen to see
anyone come this way, did you?
Did you see anyone, Fumi?
No. Wait a sec.
Come to think of it,
I might've seen a cat...
...that way.
Great.
Thanks, and sorry
to interrupt you.
[MAI]
Weird.
[NAGI]
She's the last of the HiME.
Pretty lively
and cute, isn't she?
She hasn't awakened
to her powers yet.
Who knows? Things may work out
well now that she's joined us.
Plans are already in the works.
With one, passionate kiss,
the sleeping princess
will suddenly awaken.
Mai-HiME.
[chuckles]
I think I like her already.
[MIKOTO gulping]
Huh?!
Hang on a minute,
I'm not trying to hurt you!
[grunts]
[MIKOTO growls]
You...
[MAI whimpers]
--[stomach growls]
--Huh?!
What th--?!
[sniffs]
[MAI]
You must be hungry.
[MIKOTO whimpers]
I could've done better
than noodle soup,
if I'd had the
right ingredients.
[MIKOTO]
Heh.
It's nothing fancy,
but I'm pretty sure
you're gonna
like my cooking.
[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO slurps]
[MIKOTO]
Huh...?
[sighs]
Ah!
Goodbye, Father.
Goodbye.
[TAKUMI]
She's been gone all afternoon?
[YUICHI] Yeah. You...
haven't heard from her?
[TAKUMI]
No.
[BOTH]
Huh...
Hang on, Mai!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TAKUMI]
Wait for me, Sis!
[MIKOTO laughs]
[MAI]
How was it? Are you all full?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-ha, mm-ha!
I'm Mai!
That's my name--Mai.
What's your name?
Mikoto.
Okay. So, Mikoto.
There're a few things I wanna
ask you, if that's okay.
Like...
For starters,
where did you come from?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm...
[MAI] Okay, do you know
where you're going?
[gasps]
I'd better go!
To where?
[MIKOTO]
I'm looking for my brother!
[gasps]
That was awesome soup, Mai.
You're a good person.
[MAI gasps]
No, wait!
It's the third floor!
Guess it didn't matter.
[gasps]
Oh, no...
She got away from me again!
[TAKUMI wheezes]
[TAKUMI]
Sis...
[MAI pants]
[MAI] There was no point
in me taking her in!
[gasps]
So it seems you
didn't drown after all.
[growls]
What's the matter with you?!
How can you just
stroll back to school
after causing such a disaster?!
I should go to the police
and tell them what you did!
The police couldn't do
anything if they tried.
They don't stand a chance
against the powers
that are lurking in
the shadows of this school.
[MAI groans]
[NAGI]
You'll understand, eventually...
...my... princess.
Nagi!
[MAI]
Not again!
Who are you, anyway?!
I'm a HiME. That's who.
HiME?
[NATSUKI] Highly-advanced
materializing equipment.
That's what the people
at District 1 call me.
At District 1?
[NAGI]
Enough with the lecture.
I wonder why I get this
feeling something terrible
might happen you continue
to stand around
chatting all night like this.
What's that supposed to mean?
Can't guess?
A poor "lost one" is here.
An orphan!
[NAGI]
Mai!
[MAI]
Mm? Ah?
Take my advice.
I think you in particular
should get a move on.
[TAKUMI pants]
[NATSUKI]
Move!
[MAI]
No!
[NATSUKI]
Move!
Never!
[NATSUKI]
Get on!
Huh?
[TAKUMI grunts]
Takumi!
[gasps]
He has a bad heart!
[NATSUKI] Her powers
haven't even awakened yet.
[NATSUKI
Duran!
Go!
[DURAN howls]
[MAI pants]
Takumi! Takumi!
Behind you!
[MAI gasps]
[NATSUKI] Out of the way!
You can't handle it!
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Huh...?
[MAI]
Who are you, anyway?
[MIKOTO]
I'm Mikoto!
[MAI]
I know that...
Ugh. How could I have given up
my first kiss to this girl?!
[MIKOTO]
Fine. I'll give it back.
[MAI]
Hmm? No, wait...
Mikoto-- [grunts]