[GIRL A]
Hey, how did it go with Mamoru?
[GIRL B] Nothing really
happened this summer, either.
[STUDENTS chatting]
[MIDORI]
Why didn't you just call me?
[MAI]
I did call. Lots of times.
[sighs] I needed you, but you
weren't answering your cell.
We were in serious
trouble, you know.
What a shocker though...
Finding out about Miyu.
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm! She was strong.
Real strong.
What was she?
An android?
Robot. Cyborg.
Whatever you call her, she
is not a regular human being.
An andro-bo-borg?
Android.
This is like a bad joke.
So a girl who controls
Orphans, an android,
a mysterious organization
that's going after HiME...
Ah! This is getting exciting!
We sat through the previews
and now the main attraction's
about to start!
Except... Miyu and
Alyssa are gone.
They're not here.
I've heard things about
the Searrs Foundation.
It seems they've been looking
into the power of HiME
for quite some time now.
I doubt that they'd
give up so easily.
We'd better be very careful.
[MIDORI]
It's almost time for homeroom.
And remember, it's the first day
of second trimester,
so don't be playing hooky.
[NATSUKI]
It's me. Right.
Iwasaka Pharmaceuticals, huh?
What did you say?!
[MIDORI] There's me,
Mai, Mikoto, Kuga, Nao,
Sister Yukariko,
and the mysterious "Diana"
who told you guys about Kuga.
And there's the girl with the
frog monster that saved Tate.
So that's eight of us.
There must be another four.
What do you mean?
There're 12 HiME in all,
so that leaves four.
[MIDORI] Then there's
the Golden Angel...
Maybe it's weird
to call her that now.
If she's a HiME as well,
then there're only
three left to find.
[MAI]
Hmm...
Hey...
Hey, in your opinion,
what is a HiME?
Good question-- that's
what I'm working on.
HiME powers...
...and the religious
rituals here at Fuka...
How they relate to
the Battle Princesses.
Religious rituals?
That rock painting
at the shrine,
you saw it, right?
[MIDORI] I'm positive
that rites involving HiME
have been taking place here
every few hundred years or so.
Brother, are you sure I can't
talk about what happened?
Absolutely not.
What you saw was just
an illusion, right?
Besides, I didn't see anything.
Well, I did!
It had red eyes!
[growls] And sharp fangs!
[YUICHI]
You must've been hallucinating.
[SHIHO] Hmph! If I
promise to keep quiet,
then will you...
Ah! Huh?
Oh, hey, Mai!
[SHIHO gasps]
[SHIHO]
She didn't say "hi."
What's the matter? Huh?
It's nothing.
[SHIHO]
Oh...
[MIDORI] Something happen
between you and Tate?
Hardly.
Huh. Anyway, I'll look into
the whole HiME thing,
so leave that to me.
I'll be going to the Fuka Shrine
during the Tamayura Festival
as part of my research.
[MAI]
Tama-what?
[MIDORI]
Are you serious?
Tama?
[MIDORI] You're a 16 year-old
girl; get it together.
Sure, I know there's a lot
going on in your life,
but it wouldn't hurt
to make yourself
a little more available.
After all, love at 16 can
only happen when you're 16.
[school bell chimes]
Um...
Here.
Thanks...
[CHIE] Check it out--
it's heating up already.
The Tamayura Festival is
pretty famous in these parts.
Most of the action is centered
around the Fuka Shrine...
...but this is a
popular spot as well.
[HARUKA]
I can't believe it!
The festival doesn't
even start till tomorrow.
Yet look at all these
inconsiderate people in here!
[CHIE] Unfortunately, the
ribbons usually removed
by the Executive Committee.
Anyway, the students
have this legend
about the Crystal Hall, here.
[REITO] If you write the name
of the person you like
onto a ribbon and tie it
to the hand railing,
the two of you will
end up as a couple.
[BOTH gasp]
Well, hello, Mai.
Hi, Reito...
I heard you talking.
Do you have plans
for the festival?
The festival?
Not really.
I'm glad to hear that, Mai.
In that case...
...would you be
my date tomorrow?
[gasps]
Your date?
[GIRLS gasping]
[sighs]
[CHIE] So, what are you
gonna tell him?
I'm turning him down.
How come?!
I-I'm working.
That's why--
You said you had
nothing planned.
[MAI groans]
Great...
What am I gonna do?
[MIKOTO]
Mai, did you hear?!
--Hear what?
--About these!
[sighs]
Ribbons...
You're going to try
your luck, too?
[MIKOTO]
Yup!
[MAI] Whose name are you
gonna write on them?
Your name!
[MAI] Thanks. I'm so happy,
I'm almost in tears.
But that's not all.
I have one for Yukino
and Chie and Aoi.
And I also have ones for
Shiho, Nao, and even Reito!
[MAI]
Hmm? Uh--
It's good to like
people, right?
Heh... I guess so...
[MAI]
Let go!
There's nothing you can do
about it, so leave me alone!
[YUICHI grunts]
[YUICHI groans]
[MAI] Why would you care if
something happened to me?
[YUICHI] She's right,
it's got nothing to do with me.
[SHIHO sighs]
[SHIHO] Mai said she'd do
whatever she could to...
...help me and Brother
get together.
How'd it go?
[GIRL E] I was kinda scared
at first, but he was so gentle.
It totally felt
like he loved me.
[GIRLS giggle]
[SHIHO]
I'm okay with "it," you know.
I'll do it, too.
If that's what you want.
[SHIHO gasps]
[squeals]
I'm so embarassed!
Such a pervert!
[NATSUKI] So you didn't have
any luck digging up those files.
[YAMADA] No, I was only able
to hack into the directory.
Except... Get this...
Under Fuka Academy,
I happened to see a file
for Akane Higurashi.
Her?
Why would she have one?
[MAI grunts]
All right!
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MAI] I've gotta focus on what's
most important to me,
and that's Takumi.
I've got way too many
complications in my life,
and being a HiME doesn't
make things any easier.
That's enough!
I don't have time to be
distracted by anything else,
so I won't!
Huh...?
[TAKUMI] Akira's always
taking care of me,
so I promised him that I'd
make his lunches from now on.
Thanks, Sis,
but starting tomorrow...
I tried to turn him down,
but he wouldn't let me.
Problem solved: I'll make
your lunch, too, Akira!
[TAKUMI]
No, don't.
I can handle it.
Anyway, you gotta know I can't
be a burden on you forever.
Oh, uh... Yeah, sure...
Okay.
[AKIRA] I know you said
you'd make my lunches
in exchange for me doing
the patrol rounds
during that
vampire thing, but...
I dunno.
Are you sure about this?
I saw your sister.
She seemed totally
shocked, you know.
Yeah... But I've been thinking.
I rely on my sister
way too much.
I've gotta start
looking after myself,
even if it's just
the little things.
[AKIRA]
Hmm.
[grunts]
All right! Well said, Takumi!
Now you're starting
to sound like a man!
What do you say?
Will you go to the
festival with me, Mai?
[MAI]
Mm... Well, I...
Sorry!
Huh?
[MAI] It took me a lot longer
to get ready than I thought.
It looks good on you.
Great, even.
[gasps]
Mikoto, you're here.
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm!
[CHIE] So she's stuck
with a tag along, huh?
Trust Mikoto to get in the way.
Wow, Reito looks
so good in his yukata .
What a waste. They might
as well be babysitting.
Yeah, I kinda see what you mean.
What was the point in me
coming all the way here
if I can't see them together?
[CHIE] I know. Whaddaya
say we stir things up?
[BOTH giggle]
[SHIHO]
Mom and Dad aren't around today.
You can do it, Shiho!
You look great!
This is it.
I'm really serious
about tonight.
Let's go there!
Not now.
Wait till we get to school.
[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO gasps]
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
[CHIE]
Gotcha! Hello, Mikoto.
Hi?
[MAI]
Mikoto!
[REITO]
Ugh. You take your eyes off her
for one minute and she's gone.
--[cell phone rings]
--Huh?
[MAI]
Hmm?!
[SHIHO]
Brother!
[YUICHI]
Hmm?
Gimme a break.
First you force me to come out,
and then you show up late?!
[SHIHO laughs]
[YUICHI]
Uh...
Le... L-L... Le-Let's get going.
And don't be slow, okay?
[gasps]
[MIDORI]
My name is Midori Sugiura.
I teach Japanese history
at Fuka Academy.
You don't say...
Haven't we met somewhere before?
[MIDORI]
Mm! Nah...
Doubt it.
You wanna get to the
fourth floor, underground.
That's likely where it is.
[NATSUKI]
Hmm.
[NATSUKI grunts]
So, Mai. Anywhere
you'd like to go next?
Just name it.
I dunno...
[REITO]
I didn't invite Takumi's sister
or Mikoto's guardian on a date.
I came here with
a very cute girl
who's two years younger than me.
[MAI]
Uh... Huh?
So, tell me what
you'd like to do.
Otherwise, I'll end up
looking pretty silly.
I was the one who asked you out.
And not too timidly, either.
Okay, Reito...
[TAKUMI groans]
Aw...
You're hopeless.
Gimme those things!
[TAKUMI] Cool! The secret
ninja does it again!
Hey! You making fun of me?!
Nah, I'd never do that!
[BOTH laughing]
Hey, we've gotta go and find
ourselves some fun, too.
Right!
[NAGI] There's not much time
left until contact.
You go, Mai.
Have fun while you can.
[MASHIRO]
It's been a while.
[JIN]
Well, how about that.
[MIDORI]
Headmaster! You're here!
Miss Sugiura. Nice to see you.
Mr. Munakata.
I'm looking forward to making
the rounds again this year.
Take your time and
enjoy yourself.
[JIN]
She comes every year.
[MIDORI]
Huh.
Oh, right. You were asking about
the history of this event.
The Tamayura Festival is
based on the legend
of the Battle Princesses.
It's well known in this region.
These maidens fought hard
to protect the ones they loved,
but their lives were fleeting,
as they all died in battle.
[JIN] They say that the
tradition of tying ribbons
to the Crystal Hall railing at
the school comes from a story
of how the maidens tied their
headbands onto a tree
that once grew in that spot.
[JIN] This was their
prayer before going into
that final battle that
they would once again
be reunited with
the men they loved.
[SHIHO]
Make my wish come true.
For me and Brother
to be together.
Aren't you going
to tie one, Haruka?
Now why would I want to
create more work for myself?
Ah?
[sighs]
I-I-I guess you're right...
[HARUKA] They're so
shameless about it, too.
Do you think that's for Kuga?
Well, if that's not deffective,
I don't know what would be.
It's "effective."
Miss Fujino...
Ah! Where, where?!
That's weird.
[CHIE] Um. How many of those
are you gonna put up, Mikoto?
One for everyone I like!
There are ribbons
for you guys, too.
Right here!
Okay. I kinda think you're
missing the point, though.
Your "like" isn't the same
as everyone else's.
Y'mean there are different
ways to like a person?
[AOI]
Hmm... Uh...
Uh. How're we gonna
explain this one?
Yeah. Not today.
[SHIHO]
I call this one "Goldy,"
and this red one here
is "Bug Eyes!"
[giggles]
Seeing you like that...
You haven't changed much
at all since kindergarten.
Then again, I guess you
are still just a kid.
Right, Shiho?
--[SHIHO gasps]
--So. We're all done here.
Let's head back.
[SHIHO]
You're wrong.
--Huh?
--[SHIHO] I'm not a kid.
[YUICHI]
Hmm?
[SHIHO grunts]
Look!
I'm not a kid anymore!
[YUICHI grunts]
Stop it, Shiho!
[SHIHO]
No!
[gasps]
[YUICHI sighs]
[SHIHO]
I'm all grown up now.
Look at me.
Please, Brother...
[MAI]
I'm sorry.
I got carried away and
probably asked for too much.
[REITO]
It's not a problem.
The only thing
that matters tonight
is that you have a good time.
So don't apologize.
[MAI] Thanks so much for
bringing me tonight.
I had a lot of fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
You... seemed a bit down lately.
No, it's nothing like that.
I'm actually pretty happy.
[REITO]
The vampire incident...
[gasps]
Something happened... didn't it?
I-- Ah...
[REITO] If you don't
wanna talk about it,
that's okay with me.
Besides...
it's all over now, right?
[MAI]
Yeah, that's over.
But I'm almost positive
something like it
will happen again.
That's why...
Reito... after tonight...
...I don't think you should
have anything to do with me.
[REITO sighs]
There you go again.
Shutting everyone out.
Do you plan on living
your life alone?
[gasps]
[REITO] You're always
watching out for Takumi
and you're constantly
worried about your powers.
You take on all
this responsibility,
but you force yourself to
shrug it off like it's nothing.
[gasps]
[REITO] If you don't wanna
talk about it, I understand,
but don't pretend that it
all means nothing to you.
If you find it tough,
then just admit it.
Go ahead and cry
when you need to.
I'm here.
Cry on me.
Reito...
Thank you...
[grunts]
That hurts, Brother!
[YUICHI groans]
[SHIHO]
Huh...?
--Tokiha!
--[gasps]
[gasps]
[SHIHO]
Ah...
[REITO growls]
[SHIHO]
Huh...?
[AKANE]
Isn't it beautiful?
I dressed up for you, Kazu.
'Cause, well, you
know how I feel.
[AKANE]
Come on.
Say something.
Hey, Kazu?
[AKANE]
Answer me.
Say something.
Hey, Kazu?
Kazu?
Kazu?!
[AKANE shrieks]
[MAI]
Tate...
Wait.
This isn't what--
I wasn't-- It's not like--
What're you doing?
You don't owe him
an explanation.
Tate.
Why did you interfere?
I knew it.
There is something
between you two.
[MAI gasps]
[gasps]
No, it's...
I just...
I didn't... mean to...
Huh? Ah...
Stop it!
[BOTH gasp]
Brother?
It's not... Not true...
I hate you.
You're mean, Mai.
[gasps]
[SHIHO] You told me
you supported me
and Brother getting together.
[growls]
Liar.
Liar!
[gasps]
[NAGI]
Searrs's... Child...?
A fake HiME like her,
pulling something like this off.
Now that's what I call nerve.
[MIYU] Eclipse 1 Artemis
reached its objective,
with an error of
two meters East-Southeast.
Certainly within
acceptable range.
And I'm pleased to say the
target has been obliterated.
Wonderful. Thank you, Miyu.
Now. I have a message for
the entire Golden Fleet.
[ALYSSA] Tell them to open
the door to Valhalla.
[REITO] Mai, too bad
we were interrupted.
Now, where were we?
[MAI]
What? You can't be serious!
[ALYSSA] Oh? Maybe we should've
waited a little longer.
Right, Miyu?
[MIYU] Yes. It was
an unfortunate error.
[MAI]
Hey...