[MAI groans]
You gotta be kidding.
Another brush fire?
[SHILL A] Hey, the action's
right here! Come on in, folks!
The night's still young!
[MIKOTO'S GRANDPA] You have
grown into a fine girl, Mikoto.
Now you are a full-fledged HiME.
Grandpa!
[MIKOTO'S GRANDPA]
You must leave.
Go with Miroku.
To the land of Fuka. That is
where your older brother is.
My brother...?
My brother is there, Grandpa?
Grandpa!
[MIKOTO]
Brother...
[MIKOTO giggles]
Mikoto...
Huh...?
[gasps]
Brother!
[MIKOTO groans]
[MAN A] Hey, are you the girl
that sent me the email?
[NAO]
Bingo! Guilty as charged.
Huh.
[MAN A]
Is that uniform for real?
Yeah, it sure it is.
[MAN A]
I love it!
C'mon, let's do what
we said in the email.
Her...
[MAN A]
Seriously? In here?
Wow. Never done this before.
[NAO]
Didn't think so. It'll be fun.
[MAN A]
It's like I won the jackpot!
[NAO]
Wait till you see what's coming.
[NAO moans]
No, don't...
Stop it... We just got here.
Slow down. I hate it
when guys are impatient.
C'mon.
Look, we've got
all night together.
So let's make this last, okay?
[MAN A]
Whoa! Hey... What the...?
You've been played...
..."babe."
Hah!
[MAN A gasps]
[screams]
[NAO] I was planning on
screwing you all along.
So let's say we're even now.
[NAO]
Who's there?!
[MIKOTO]
Hmm.
I know who you are.
Oh. If that's how you want it.
[MAI]
Come on!
You overslept because
you were out late.
What were you doing last night?
Do I have to tell you
everything I do?
Can't I have a little privacy?
[MAI]
Huh?
[MIKOTO groans]
[AOI]
Mr. Takano told me to make sure
that you're not late
for classes today. Come on!
What's the big deal?
Takano will give me
a break; he always does.
[AOI]
Heh.
Good morning, Mikoto.
[MIKOTO]
Hmph. Morning, Nao.
[MAI]
Huh?
I knew they were
in the same class,
but I didn't realize they
got along with each other.
Nao Yuuki, was it?
She's pretty cute, huh?
--[AOI chuckles]
--[MAI] Huh?
[AOI] She seems that way
on the surface.
[NAO] Last night was a shocker,
running into each other.
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm.
[NAO]
So...
You remember
the promise we made?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm.
Don't tell anybody
about it, now.
It's our little secret, okay?
[MIKOTO]
Mm. Mm-hmm.
[school bell chimes]
What's the matter with you, Nao?
[BOY A]
Something wrong, Nao?
[TAKANO]
Yuuki!
Back to your seat.
First class is about to begin.
Oh, Mr. Taka--
--[groans]
--[BOYS gasp]
--I gotcha!
--[TAKANO] What's the matter?
I'm sorry. I'm a little anemic.
Anemic? Have you
had enough sleep?
Please, sir.
Don't make me explain it.
It's embarrassing.
Oh, how rude of me.
I... Uh... It's just...
Why don't you go rest?
[NAO giggles]
[YOKO]
What a surprise. [chuckles]
I thought you were still
enrolled in university.
Trust me, it's a long story.
Right. Professor Sasaki, is it?
Ugh!
Hyaah!
What's that?
My "shut up" move.
[YOKO]
You haven't changed one bit.
Gimme a break.
Oh, you know I'm just kidding.
How 'bout we celebrate
our reunion and go out
for a little drink?
I guess we have that in common.
[door rattles open]
Huh?
Excuse me, I'm not feeling well.
I need to rest a bit.
Feeling sick again, Yuuki?
[NAO]
Yeah, unfortunately.
[MIDORI giggles]
You're faking it.
No, that's not true.
I'm honestly sick.
Uh-huh. Fine.
Pick whatever bed you want
and sack out for a while.
[NAO sighs]
Thank you...
Who's runnin' this place?
[MIKOTO slurping, gulping]
[NATSUKI]
This is our reality.
The reality we HiME
have to deal with.
[MIDORI] Our mission as HiME
is to save humankind
from the evil hands
of the Orphans.
[MASHIRO]
You must decide for yourself
what direction is right for you.
[MAI sighs]
I don't know what's going on...
[AOI] So, what are you
going to do, Mai?
Huh?
The Founders' Day Festival.
We're talking about who
you're doing the rounds with.
You going with Tate?
Wh-What?!
Why would you bring up
his name all of a sudden?!
We're not seeing
each other or anything!
C'mon, it's obvious. Right?
And that job...
You spent the night together.
[MAI groans]
Give me a break, would ya?
If you're not going with Tate,
then I guess you'll be
with Mikoto and Takumi.
[MAI] Um, actually,
I wouldn't mind a little time
without having to chaperone
Mikoto every second.
[MIKOTO] I don't need
any chaperone, thank you!
Yeah, sure, whatever.
You can't do anything on
your own and you know it.
[MIKOTO]
Can so!
Well, I'm done here!
[NAO] What? And you
got upset over that?
Mai always treats
me like a little kid
and I'm getting sick of it.
[NAO giggles]
What's so funny?!
That's the sort of thing I would
expect to come from Tokiha.
I'd have to agree that you're
still pretty immature, though.
No! I'm a grownup! I'm no kid!
When I find my brother,
I won't even need Mai...
[NAO] Then how about we go look
for your brother again tonight?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm!
But before that,
I'm gonna give you the chance
to tag along with me
for a bit as well.
[AKIRA]
Damn! What a drag!
Talk about bad luck,
getting picked for this.
I'm actually kinda happy
about it myself.
Hah. Please tell me
that you're kidding.
Excuse me, Teach?
Hello, Okuzaki.
What're you doing here?
[AKIRA] I was picked to help
on the Prep Committee
for the Founders' Day Festival,
so I won't be able to come
to club meetings for a while.
Oh, my. That's very unfortunate.
I'll miss you here.
Hmm! And you are...?
[AKIRA]
Hmm?
[ISHIGAMI grunting]
[TAKUMI]
Uh...
Nice! How 'bout modeling for one
of my paintings, young man?!
Uh...
[REITO]
For the Founders' Day Festival,
we make offers to
businesses and shops
that have a strong
connection with the school
and give them an opportunity
to open a stall at the festival.
It gives the community
a chance to interact
with the student body.
It is different from the Culture
Festival we have in the fall.
I hope you all work hard
putting this together.
[door rattles open]
I'm sorry. I hope
we didn't hold you up.
No, glad you could make it.
In fact, you're both
going to come and do
a little job with me, boys.
[school bell rings]
[MAI pants]
All right! Off to work!
[YUICHI]
Hey, Tokiha!
[MAI]
Hmm?
Hi, Tate, hi, Shiho.
How's it going?
[MAI]
Uh? Hmm...
What? I've gotta get going.
Well, Shiho here really
wants to go shopping
and she's been trying to get me
to go to Tsukimori with her.
Thing is, I'm busy with
the Student Council...
I said I would wait for you.
Yeah, I know,
but what if I'm late?
So, if you're not busy,
do you think she could
hang out with you?
[MAI groans]
She wants to get
girls' stuff anyway.
And besides,
she seems to like you.
[SHIHO groans]
[gasps]
'Fraid... I can't!
I've gotta get to work!
You'll have to go together.
Sorry, I'm in a bit of a rush!
Hey!
Guess I'm stuck with you, then.
[SHIHO]
Hmm.
[MAI pants]
Jeez, why do I feel like
I'm running away from them?
[NAGI]
What, you're not going to go?
[gasps]
[NAGI]
I had a favor to ask you, too.
[gasps]
Hello, Mai.
What do you want this time?
[NAGI] I want you to
go to Tsukimori tonight.
Yes?
[MAI]
No way!
I'll never listen to what
you tell me to do!
[NAGI]
You sure are a hard-head.
Actually, there's a problem
with one of the girls.
And Mikoto might be in
a little danger, I'm afraid.
[gasps]
Besides, it seems you've
been having some trouble
coming to grips with your
own power lately, haven't you?
I think this might even turn out
to be a good experience for you.
What... is this about?
You'll have to go and
find out for yourself.
[MAI] Okay, right.
So she's not back yet.
Oh, no, it's nothing, really.
Thanks anyway, Aoi.
[CUSTOMER A]
I didn't order this.
[AKANE]
Oh, I'm sorry about that, sir!
What is with everyone?
Mikoto, Aoi, and Chie?
Tate and Nagi...
They all seem preoccupied.
[BOTH sigh]
[MAI]
Listen, Akane...
I'm not very good
at this sort of thing.
Uh...
I kinda suck, really.
But has something happened?
You just seem a little
different lately.
[gasps]
Mm...
How embarrassing!
So I've got you worried
about me, too, huh?
[sighs]
Okay! I've decided!
Oh.
I don't care if it doesn't work.
And nothing's gonna change
unless I make it happen!
Akane? What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
You probably don't know
what I'm talking about.
After I clear the tables,
do you think you could listen
to me for just a while?
Sure thing. I'm here for you.
Really.
--[phone rings]
--[NAO] Oh.
[NAO]
Hmm...
[MIKOTO]
He's coming!
[NAO chuckles]
[YOKO]
Oh, I love all this neon.
I would have to say alcohol
is the greatest invention
in all of history!
Uh, you lost course credits
back when you were an intern
because you used to drink
the medical alcohol?
And you were
my partner in crime?
That must've been someone else.
Look!
I wanna go there!
[YOKO]
No chance.
We can't afford to go to
a restaurant like that
on our salaries.
[MIDORI growls] Who would eat
at a place like this anyway?!
That was very good, thank you.
Ah. Then...?
Yes. I'd be very honored if
you would set up a food stall
at our Founders' Day Festival.
[PROPRIETOR]
Thank you very much!
Taking part in such a
prestigious event
at Fuka Academy is like being
rated as a 5-star restaurant.
Unless I make it
happen myself, huh?
Right.
[gasps]
Tate...
[BAR GUY A chuckles]
[laughter]
[BAR GUY B]
Whoa, check it out...
Whoo-hoo! Hoo... Baby...
[PATRONS laughing]
Any information for me?
[MAI pants]
Come on!
That Mikoto sure is
a handful sometimes.
Ah, Mai?
[MAI]
Huh? Takumi? Kanzaki?
[NAO] This wasn't
the right one, either.
[MIKOTO]
Why do we have to go this far?
[NAO] No wonder everyone treats
you like a kid all the time.
Men are stupid,
violent creatures, Mikoto.
This is the best way
to deal with them.
Yeah? You sure?
[NAO] Positive. Now it's
your turn to have a go.
[MAI]
I'm sorry, Kanzaki.
[REITO chuckles]
Just call me Reito.
Sure. Reito.
Takumi and Okuzaki,
stick together.
Let's split up and search.
Takumi... Don't strain yourself.
I'm sorry, Okuzaki.
[AKIRA]
It doesn't really matter.
Thanks!
[NATSUKI sighs]
No choice.
Guess I'll have to
go there myself.
[MAI pants]
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
You!
[YOKO]
C'mon!
Didn't I tell you to stay away
from that middle aged man...?
Shut up! I can do
whatever I want!
[MIDORI]
Heh...?
You sure this is
the right place?
Yeah, this is it. The people at
the bar told me it was here.
What were you doing at a bar?
Look, you don't
have to know-- Shh!
[MIKOTO]
Hey.
[MAN C]
Hmm?
Uh. I've got nothing to do,
so I was wondering...
I mean...
I was thinking...
Wanna hang out... with me?
[gasps]
Are you in middle school?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm. That's right.
[chuckles]
[MAI groans]
What on earth is Mikoto doing?!
Well, she's... Uh...
[BOTH gasp]
That girl!
[blows landing,
glass shattering]
[MAN C grunts]
What a fool.
You were an easy catch, boy.
Too bad. Now, you're
going to regret it!
[MAN C]
Wh-What is that?!
[NAO] I'm going to punish
a very stupid man.
Nao... Hey...
What? Are you chickening out?
He's not a fighter or anything.
And I just...
Hang on a minute, girl.
You're the one
who brought him here.
And what do you think
he was expecting?
--[NATSUKI] That's enough!
--[NAO] Huh?
[gasps]
Hey! You, there!
Go on, get out of here!
Just don't ever do this again!
[MAN C yelps]
Mai...
Why would you
do something like this?!
I can't believe
you're so stupid!
[NAO laughs]
[NAO] I've heard
all about it from Mikoto.
You two are HiME as well, huh?
Then you must understand
that there's nothing wrong
with using our power
any way we want to.
[MAN C yells]
[NAO] Even that kid school
headmaster said it--
We decide on our own what we do.
And this girl...
She was all sulky because you
were treating her like a kid,
so I showed her a thing or two.
I taught her how
she could use her power.
Mikoto...
[MIKOTO groans]
Hey. Do you wanna
know something, Tokiha?
I can't stand girls like you.
Always acting like
you're so good.
Such a good sister.
Things are oh-so-tough on you.
I hear so much from Aoi,
it feels like my ears
are gonna burst!
"Mai is working so hard!
What a great girl!
What a great girl!"
You're not fooling me, idiot!
You make me wanna puke!
[gasps]
Mai...
[NATSUKI chuckles]
All right, all right,
you have a point.
I'll give you that much.
The folks at District One
brought us together
at the school, but that doesn't
mean we have to do
everything the way they want.
And how we use our powers is
completely up to each one of us.
You understand me, then.
But, hey...
...it's also my choice to
say whether or not I like it!
Isn't it?
I suppose so.
Hey, stop it, you two!
Please!
Then do you wanna be
the first to die?
Nao!
[MIDORI, slurring]
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Hold on a minute!
Stop the fighting now!
[hiccups]
Midori...? Uh...
If you don't stop...
...I'm gonna punish you all!
[MIDORI groans]
Ugh. Who is this person?
[gasps]
You! You total idiot!
You should be taking
care of your po--
[grunts]
Gonna barf...
[NAO gasps]
--[MIDORI retches]
--[NAO screams]
[sighs]
[MIDORI retching]
[NAGI]
Okay. That's enough of that.
--Nagi!
--[gasps]
You...
Just for the record,
I don't intend to accuse Nao
of misusing her power.
It really is up to
each of you to decide
how your powers are used..
However, HiME are absolutely
not allowed to fight each other.
Why not?!
Look at them, they're so...
If you keep
complaining like that,
I will personally see
that you're punished...
...Nao.
[growls]
[MIDORI]
I mean, really!
If you're gonna act
like an airhead,
you'll regret it when
Mister Right comes along.
Yeah! I guarantee you will!
[NAGI laughs] That's pretty
good advice, Midori!
[NAO growls]
What would you know?!
Any of you!
I'll teach you a lesson
you won't forget.
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
[rumbling]
Let's get out of here!
We'll be crushed!
Mikoto!
[MIKOTO whines]
[MAI]
What're you doing?! Hurry!
[gasps]
Mikoto!
You fool!
[NATSUKI groans]
No...
Mikoto...
Mikoto!
[gasps, sobs]
[sobs]
That guy...
Reito... [gasps]
Kanzaki?
[MIKOTO'S BROTHER]
You all right?
You're out of danger now.
Brother... [sighs]
[MIKOTO'S BROTHER]
Huh. That was a very close call.
[REITO]
You could've been badly injured.
Mikoto!
Mai...
[MIKOTO groans]
Ah... Mikoto...
You fool...
[MAI whimpers]
You had me so worried!
Mai...
[police sirens approaching]
[MASHIRO] I had a feeling
that you'd be coming by
sooner or later.
What is a HiME, anyway?
And why do we have these
powers? What's the point?
To fight Orphans with.
Is that a good enough
answer for you?
[MASHIRO] All I can say
is that the future...
The future of this
entire country--
no, the whole world--depends on
the powers that HiME possess.
That's all.
[MAI]
Mm?
Are you still mad at me?
No, Mikoto.
Hey, what do you want
for dinner tonight?
You can have anything
you like--your choice.
[gasps]
I know what I want!
Some of your
three-minute noodles!
One order of three-minute
noodles it is, then!
Mai!
[MAI] Before dinner, you've got
cleaning duty as punishment.
[MIKOTO]
Uh-huh.
[GIRL] ♪ They're dancing in the
shadow like whispers of love. ♪
♪ Just dreaming of a place
where they're free... ♪
Incredible. What a voice.
No kidding...
That's Alyssa Searrs,
from grade school.
They call her
the "Golden Angel."
Really?
[MAI]
Miyu...?
So, she is capable of
expressions like that...
[inaudible]
[AOI] Mai, have you
ever kissed someone?
[MAI]
What?! Well, uh...
[AOI]
You have! Lucky you!
Hey, tell me what
your first kiss was like!
[MAI]
Mm....
It was... salty.