[MAN A] It's a great spot.
Nobody'll see us here.
So why not?
--[WOMAN grunts]
--[NAO] Because!
[WOMAN yelps]
[NAO]
No way, cut it out.
[MAN A]
Aw, come on, babe.
Don't tease me.
[NAO]
Jeez...
You sure are impatient.
We've got the whole night
ahead of us. Slow down, 'kay?
[giggles]
[WOMAN growls]
See ya later!
[SHIHO gasps]
Hey, Brother--!
[SHIHO]
Hey, Brothe-- Ah!
[growls]
What's with you?
You're in the second year
of middle school now.
It's about time you grew up
and stop acting like such a kid.
But I am growing up, Brother.
See?
That's not what I meant!
Oh, right!
That job thing.
I told you about it--
you'll still do it, right?
Well, I can't say no
to old man Jin, can I, huh?
Yes!
We'll probably need one other
guy and a couple more girls
to get it done properly.
Hey, do you know anyone else
who might wanna help out?
[YUICHI]
Hmm... That's a hard one.
Oh...
[SHIHO]
Hmm...?
What? You're gonna
quit work, Midori?
Yeah, that's right.
I found something better;
a real job this time.
Real? As in career?
Are you serious?
Hey, how old are you, anyway?
I'm 17.
Uh...
Are you serious?
Cross my heart and hope to die.
It's time for me
to get out of this rut
and do something different.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. I've made up
my mind, and I'm going for it.
And when a girl
decides to go for it...
...she's gotta give it her best!
Don'tcha think?
[gasps]
I dunno, Midori.
You're a lot more focused
than most people.
And you seem sure
about everything.
Got a problem?
Looking for advice?
--[glass shattering]
--[BOTH] Hmm?
[AKANE whimpers]
[AKANE]
I'm sorry!
What's up with Akane
these days...?
Oh! Here!
[MAI]
Hmm?
Hang on, I'll help!
Ah...
--[door opens]
--Huh?
Oh. There she is.
[MAI]
Hmm?
You're planning a wedding?
And you want me and Takumi
and Mikoto to help, too?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
Yeah, it's for her grandfather.
He's the priest
at the local shrine.
It's an ancient place
called the Fuka Shrine.
That's where
the wedding will be.
[MIDORI]
Huh...
[MAI] Is this that "budget"
ceremony you were talking about?
Exactly.
You told her?
[YUICHI]
Never mind that.
Just explain to her
what it's all about.
[SHIHO]
Hmph. All right.
Normally we don't do events
like weddings at our shrine.
But this time, there's this
person who's insisting
on having it there, and we're
looking for people to help out.
What're you pouting for?
Somethin' wrong?
I'm not pouting.
[MIKOTO gasps]
Uh?
[MIKOTO]
Mm...
Huh...?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?!
Yummy!
No, it's better than yummy!
Why don't you just have it all?
[MIKOTO gasps]
Shiho!
Mm! You're the greatest ever!
So. It looks like we've got
enough people here
to make it happen.
Yeah, my weekend's
free now,
and Takumi was just looking
for some kind of job,
so this works out for us.
Sure it's all right
with her, though?
Of course it is. Right, Shiho?
Whatever you say, idiot.
Pardon?
Oh, nothing. Just drop it.
You're weird.
[MAI giggles]
Wha--?!
Midori! What're you doing?!
[MIDORI]
A wedding, huh?
Hmm! I was thinking...
I'm very talented.
Do you think you
could use my help
on that wedding you're doing?
Wha...
Oh...
Midori...
Didn't you just take over
my weekend shift
'cause you're gonna
be quitting soon?
Oh? Uh... Don't remember.
Actually, you insisted
on taking over for me.
Yeah? You sure about that?
If you don't work
this weekend,
Akane will have to run
the place by herself.
That'd be a cryin' shame.
So, no.
[TAKUMI gasps]
You're totally mean, Mai.
--[SHIHO hupping]
--[YUICHI groans]
These stairs are brutal.
I'm not used to this climb.
Takumi, you want me
to carry that?
I'm okay. It's not that heavy.
[SHIHO giggles]
Come on, you guys!
You can make it!
[JIN]
Up here, kids!
Shiho!
[JIN chuckles]
[JIN] Thanks for coming
out to lend a hand.
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
You know, I haven't organized a
wedding here since my wife died.
You sure are a big help.
[YUICHI]
Ah...
The first thing I'll have you
do is take all the things
we need for the wedding
out of this storeroom.
[CUSTOMER A]
Excuse me!
Coming!
[WOMAN A]
Could somebody take my order?
[MAN A]
I'm starvin' over here.
[AKANE]
Coming right up!
[MAN B]
Can I get some water?
[AKANE]
Yes! Right away!
[WOMAN B]
How 'bout the bill?
[AKANE]
Just a moment, ma'am!
[WOMAN C]
Ugh! We're still waiting.
[AKANE]
Right away...
[groans]
[AKANE]
Midori...
Why aren't you at work?!
[YUICHI] Watch your feet,
there's stairs ahead.
[TAKUMI]
Right.
[MIDORI]
Hmm...
[MAI]
Huh?
Hey, Shiho.
I guess we have to check
this room as well.
[SHIHO]
Ah! Don't touch that!
Sorry. That door's
gotta stay closed.
--Oh.
--[SHIHO] There's an old legend
that's been passed down
at this shrine.
A big scary god that used
to terrorize the town
is locked inside,
so the door has to stay sealed,
or there'll be
serious consequences.
Oh.
I guess it's good idea to
take these things seriously.
But...
Nothing bad'll happen
if I leave it alone, right?
[YUICHI grunts]
I'd say that's about it.
[MAI] Yup, now we just
have to take to the hall.
There aren't too many
heavy boxes here,
so we might be able
to do it in one trip.
[MIDORI whimpers]
--[MIDORI] That's it.
--[door creaks]
[YUICHI]
Done.
Long as nobody's forgotten
anything, we're outta here.
[GROUP]
Okay!
[MIDORI]
No biggie.
I've got an ace up
my sleeve if I need it.
More importantly...
[MIDORI]
Hmph.
[yelps]
No way!
Edo Murasaki
by Korekiyo Torii?
And this one's Udagawa's
Hamachidori !
Ha! These are all cult books!
Like the
Wakan Sensaizuroku !
And Toraibo's
Iyohouryaku Engi !
I've hit the jackpot!
[MAI sighs]
Not only do we get paid, but we
get dinner and a bath as well!
This job rocks!
[SHIHO groans]
Huh?
Oh, this?
I've had it since I was born.
Shows up pretty good
when I take a bath.
[SHIHO]
Oh...
Then...
[SHIHO]
That, too?
Doesn't that look
a lot like mine?
I was shocked when I saw it!
Wow...
Hey, Shiho.
You sure have clear skin.
--Ooh.
--[screams]
[MAI]
There's not a mark on you.
[SHIHO] Knock it off!
Get your hands off me!
[growls, gasps]
[MAI]
Shiho, what're you doing?!
[SHIHO]
They're floating in the water!
It's just not fair!
[MAI laughs]
What do you mean, "not fair"?
I said, no! Cut it out!
[YUICHI] I hope they're not
putting on a show for us.
[TAKUMI]
Aw, Sis...
[JIN] So there's
still nothing going on
--between you and Shiho, then?
--[BOTH] Huh?
Nothing at all!
Why not? I can't count
the number of times
you've seen Shiho
naked in the past.
--[TAKUMI] Uh...
--Give me a break, Gramps.
That was way back when
we were in kindergarten.
Oh, I get it.
You're going after that girl
with the great big melons!
Ugh! Get your mind outta
the gutter, you dirty old man!
Jeez!
[TAKUMI]
Mm...
[MAI]
This is so much fun.
It's like being
on a school trip.
[SHIHO]
Glad someone's having fun...
[MIKOTO groans]
I gotta pee...
[SHIHO]
Hmm? Ah!
Huh...?
[SHIHO]
Um, don't go in there.
The bathroom's this way.
[MIKOTO]
Uh-huh...
[SHIHO]
Oh, that.
[gasps]
Is that for the bride tomorrow?
[SHIHO]
Mm-mm.
No. It's my wedding dress.
[MAI]
What?
It was my grandma's.
Grandpa says I should
wear it when I get married.
What a sweet idea.
--[SHIHO] Mai...
--Huh?
[SHIHO]
About Yuichi...
My brother Yuichi...
[wails]
I'm begging you!
Don't steal Yuichi from me!
Beg your pardon?
[toilet flushes]
That could never happen.
Don't worry.
[SHIHO]
I mean...
My brother's really
into big chests,
and you're sure
blessed in that area.
Plus, lately, you two seem to
be meeting up with each other
all the time.
That's why I thought...
Oh. You must really like him
from the sounds of it.
[SHIHO]
Mm-hmm.
Trust me, Shiho.
You've got absolutely
nothing to worry about.
You have my word.
Really?
Really.
Then... will you be there
to support me?
So that me and brother
can become all lovey-dovey?
Shiho, you get
right to the point.
[SHIHO]
Huh?
Okay, I'll be there for you.
I dunno what I can do,
but I'll be right behind ya.
[gasps]
--Mai!
--Huh?!
[SHIHO]
You're the best!
Shiho... Calm down!
[SHIHO]
Huh...? Ah!
Those are my melons.
[sighs]
Ah...
[MAI yelps]
[SHIHO whimpers]
[MAI]
Hey, Mikoto! Stop that!
[YUICHI]
Why do they have to be so noisy?
Uh, Yuichi?
[YUICHI]
Hmm?
Do you like my sister?
I mean--
Oh, don't take the old man
so seriously, kid.
Loud and stubborn girls
like her wear me out fast.
But she does have a kind
and gentle side to her.
Sister complex?
[TAKUMI]
Ah! No! Of course not!
Let's get to sleep.
We've got an early day tomorrow.
You've got it
all wrong, you know.
[MIDORI gasps]
Ah, oh! Mm!
[gasps]
[laughs]
The bride and the wedding
party is here, people!
--[SHIHO] Okay!
--[YUICHI] Oh!
[SHIHO] C'mon, let's get
this show on the road!
Well. What a transformation.
--Meanie!
--[MAI giggles]
[JIN]
I have to thank you again
for offering to
help today, kids.
[GROUP]
Okay!
[NAGI] The seal
hasn't been broken yet,
but it seems like it's
only a matter of time.
You think so?
It'll be an
excellent opportunity
to bury it once and for all.
But I won't be getting
involved, personally.
That looks wonderful
on you, Miss Mashiro.
Thanks for saying so, Fumi.
[SHIZURU]
Well, if it isn't Mai!
[MAI]
Hmm?
Isn't it just the
nicest day for a wedding?
[MAI]
Council President!
Were you all invited
to the wedding?
Yes. Seeing as it is
student council business.
Actually,
the father of the bride
is one of the
school's governors.
And the groom happens
to be my former schoolmate.
[MAI]
Oh.
If you don't mind me saying so,
you sure look good
in that outfit.
What?
Come on, Kanzaki,
you're making me blush.
Enough with the flattery.
No, I'm serious.
You're really quite striking.
Hah. That's very kind of you.
[SHIHO]
Mai!
Huh?
Well, excuse me!
Enjoy yourselves!
Good luck today!
You should be careful flirting
with such an innocent girl.
What?
Never thought I'd hear something
like that from you, Shizuru.
[YOKO]
I'd have to agree with her.
--No. You, too, Miss Yoko?
--[laughs]
[YOKO]
You can't have her, you know.
[REITO]
What're you talking about?
[MIDORI snores]
[gulps]
[gasps]
[MIDORI]
Ah! It's morning!
Oh, stupid me! What an idiot!
It's all cuz I'm
super smart and curious
about all kinds of stuff!
Enough with the regrets.
So...
Here goes.
[MAI]
I checked it so many times.
I'm counting on you, sweet Mai.
There's no mistake.
This is the door.
After this, I'll be able
to wrap up my thesis.
--[door creaks open]
--[gasps]
[MIDORI groans]
[chuckles]
Midori?
What're you doing here?
Mai! What a surprise!
Well...
I'll tell you all about it,
but it'll take a while,
'cause this whole thing
is deep and complicated,
even deeper than
the Mariana Trench.
[gasps]
No!
You took it off!
--What?!
--Put it back! Now!
Why should I?!
[MAI]
To avoid the consequences!
Huh...?
[BOTH yell]
[screaming]
The seal has been broken.
Way to go, Mai.
[BOTH groaning]
[MAI]
What is this place?
[gasps]
Look at this...
HiME!
Mai, you...?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yelping]
Midori!
Well, I guess that's the end
of that old rock painting.
--[gasping, murmuring]
--[GUEST A] An earthquake?
[MIKOTO]
Huh?!
[MAI grunts]
[gasps]
Midori!
[yells]
[gasps]
[MIKOTO growls]
Thanks, Mikoto!
[BOTH gasp]
[MAI]
Kuga!
[NATSUKI growls]
Too late!
[MAI, MIKOTO scream]
[NATSUKI growls]
Hurry up and bring
out your Child!
Don't be ridiculous!
Do you want those people out
front getting caught up in this?
No, but think!
What if that Kagutsuchi goes
on a complete rampage
around the shrine?
How else are we supposed
to kill this monster
if you don't summon him?
We don't have any choice though!
[ALL scream]
[gasping]
[ALL grunt]
[VOICE]
The Orphan...
An entity that has always
threatened humanity.
People have been living
in fear for too long!
Their suffering
must come to an end!
Fortunately, a passionate
young maiden concealing
a fighting spirit in her heart
makes her appearance,
bravely standing up
to the threat.
Her name is...
The HiME of Wind!
Midori Sugiura!
What?!
Midori?!
[MIDORI grunts]
[growls]
Ha!
You guys to to be
a lot more aggressive.
Our mission as HiME is
to save humankind
from the evil hands
of the Orphans.
We cannot hesitate
in the face of evil!
We must all work
together as a team!
[MAI]
Uh...
Remember these words
as we save the world.
And they are "justice,"
"love," and "friendship!"
Friendship?
[groaning]
Never mind.
You just leave this one to me!
Come on out!
The steely claws...
Gakutenou!
[GROUP]
Gakutenou?
When you go for it, you gotta
give it everything you've got!
Gakutenou!
[MIDORI]
Tornado!
The ground shakes as
the wheels go by!
Gakutenou!
Spiral... Dasher!
Tokkan!
[MIDORI grunts]
[MIDORI]
The good always triumph!
Midori?
[JIN] Kakemaku mo kashikoki
Izanagi no Ohkami .
Thank you, Midori.
No, don't worry about it.
It's my fault for ripping off
that seal in the first place.
You know that painting?
What was that?
[MIDORI]
Hmm... No, not just yet.
When I finish my thesis,
I'll make sure
you're the first to read it.
Thesis?
Who are you anyway, Midori?
A defender of justice.
But you can't make a living
out of a job like that.
Midori?
[MIDORI]
As you all know, Mr. Sawada's
still in hospital recovering
from his accident.
So I'll be taking over his
Japanese history class
as the new substitute.
I'm Midori Sugiura!
But you can call me Midori!
[MAI]
How old are you really, Midori?
[MIDORI]
Like I said, I'm 17!
[MAI]
But you're a teacher.
[YUKARIKO]
Miss Tokiha?
[MAI]
Sister?!
[YUKARIKO] If your teacher
tells you she's 17,
it means that she's 17.
Have faith in her.
[MAI]
Right...