You won't be able
to hide this any longer.
Look at all the destruction...
It doesn't matter, really.
There's no need to
conceal this any more.
Although, we will keep it
from getting out to the media.
It'll be 300 years till
this happens again.
By then, this event will be
remembered as nothing more
than a legend or fairy tale.
So this is going to
keep on repeating itself?
--[SMITH] I would think so.
--[BOTH gasp]
There's a certain
government agency
which does not officially exist,
known as District 1,
that has been controlling
the HiME festivals,
as well as supporting this
country from behind the scenes.
Hey, aren't you--?
It's been a while,
hasn't it, Mr. Sakomizu?
And a pleasure to meet you,
Princess Natsuki.
[growls softly]
I'm in charge of the
Searrs Foundation
Publicity Department, Number 4,
and the name is John Smith.
[SAKOMIZU gasps]
Oh, please. There's
no need to be rash.
Seeing as our chairman
has passed away,
we've decided that we
would not interfere
with the HiME
Festival this time.
My job is simply to
clear up the mess
that our former chairman
left behind; nothing more.
Then you're the one.
The person who wanted to trade
some information with me.
[gasps]
That's right.
Then why don't I
just cut to the chase?
The remains of Miyu Greer.
Would you know where
I might... find them?
Huh?
You see, it's a bit of
a conundrum, I'm afraid.
It seems as though we lost
her retrieval signal.
Therefore, I thought I'd ask
someone who had had
the opportunity to fight her.
[NATSUKI] And what information
do you have to offer?
Let's me see...
How about the truth behind
the circumstances that led
to the death of
Dr. Kuga, your mother?
--[SAKOMIZU gasps]
--What did you say?!
[NATSUKI]
Mother!
[SAKOMIZU]
Ah! Don't listen to him!
This man is--
[SMITH] I suggest you
keep your mouth shut,
you District 1 lackey.
This deal is strictly
between her and me.
[NATSUKI sighs]
[NATSUKI]
I don't know first-hand.
Except...
You mustn't tell him!
[NATSUKI] There was some talk
that flowers of ice had bloomed
by the lake over the back hills
immediately after the fight.
It's possible that...
[SMITH] That's where
her signal was lost.
Trust me, we've already searched
that area very thoroughly.
[sighs]
[SMITH] It sounds like you
really don't know.
Oh, well.
At least you seemed to have
answered me honestly,
so I'll reciprocate
in good faith.
After all, as I understand it,
you could have become a part
of our organization.
What?!
Smith! Stop!
Dr. Kuga was trying to sell you
to us as a research subject,
and when that was uncovered,
she was dealt with.
[gasps]
It really was unfortunate.
We'd already paid her
up front, and then that.
[YAMADA] That number turned
out to be a bank account.
So I traced the money
to its final recipients,
and found that they ended up
at two organizations.
One's Iwasaka Pharmaceuticals.
The other one is
the Searrs Foundation.
It's a lie...
[NATSUKI screams]
[grunts]
[REITO]
I've put a little brandy in it.
It'll warm you up
and help you relax.
This house belongs
to my parents, actually.
But since I'm the only one
in the family who's around,
I decided that it
just makes more sense
for me to live in the dorm.
[REITO]
I come home on the weekends.
Or at times when
I want to be alone.
If you need me to,
I'll stay right here beside you.
All right?
[MAI]
Will you hear me out?
I wanna tell you everything
that's happened up until now.
This is ridiculous!
Where is that bumbling girl?!
How could she just
abandon all her duties
at a time like this?!
[MIDORI]
Hey, Yukino!
[YUKINO]
Miss Sugiura...
I need to borrow her a minute!
Wait, I--!
Just what's going on
around here?!
[MIDORI]
What's going on?! Where's Mai?!
And what happened with Takumi?!
You've gotta tell me!
All right...
[gasps]
Gimme a big smile now.
[shutter clicking]
This isn't nearly
as fun as it should be.
I don't get it.
Why aren't you fighting back?
Don't be ignoring me.
The problem with
making you suffer
while you're droopy
and lifeless...
...is that it doesn't
make me feel any better.
My eye still hurts
as much as ever.
[growls]
[SHIZURU]
That'll be enough.
[NAO]
Huh...?
I'm not gonna let you
do anything to harm Natsuki.
It's you.
Shizuru...
Miss Yuuki. Isn't that right?
Jeez. The Student Council
President knows my name.
I must've gotten pretty famous.
Oh, dear. You poor little thing.
Huh?
[SHIZURU] Perhaps you're just
too aware of everything.
If you were somewhat
more dim-witted,
you probably wouldn't
have suffered so much.
I'm guessin' you were
probably goverened
by strict rules as a child,
so it's no surprise you
sought the approval
of everyone around you.
Am I correct?
Heh. So that's what
you've wanted to tell me.
What, now all of a sudden,
you've turned into some
kind of counselor?
You don't seem to understand
the situation here.
Shizuru... Ah...
[chuckles]
Anyway, that's how it is.
[SHIZURU]
I'd have to agree.
Whatever past
you might have had
has nothing at all
to do with me.
I'm only interested
in one thing.
And that's saving Natsuki.
Shi... zuru...
I will never allow
anyone to hurt her
and get away with it.
Whatever the reason.
[giggles]
Hilarious. The rumors are true.
If you think one of us
around here is in need
of some counseling,
I'd pick you.
You're getting on my nerves.
Heh.
Kiyohime.
--[rumbling]
--[gasps, screams]
I still can't believe
what's happened,
even as I talk about it.
It's unreal.
How could it...?
[gasps]
[sobs]
It seems so unfair
that Takumi's health was so bad,
and that you're one of the HiME.
Plus, the outcome.
Listen, though.
If everything you've
told me is correct
it may be too soon
to give up hope.
If the HiME who wins
all the battles
can attain
incredible power
like you say...
Well, then there
may still be a chance.
Besides, you've already
realized it by now, I'm sure.
The feelings
that you have inside.
For that person who's more
precious to you than anyone.
[REITO] In a world where nothing
goes the way you want,
there might be just one thing
that you can count on.
It's love. Your love for
another. For those feelings,
and for that special
person you desire...
You might even be willing
to become a demon.
[REITO] You might even be
allowed to become a demon.
Reito, I don't...
[REITO]
I've got to go now.
I'm worried about what's
going on at school.
You should stay here
and get some rest.
[REITO]
I'm sorry.
I hope you'll forgive me
for saying those things
without any consideration
for your feelings.
[MAI]
Um...
Thank you, Reito...
For everything...
Heh.
There's hope...
[NAGI] What a gentleman.
You had a good chance, too.
Even if I could have her body,
her heart would still
belong to someone else.
Let's carry on as planned.
[NAGI]
Hmm.
I'm at your command, Master.
Where am I...?
You're safe here.
This place belongs to
one of my tea students.
Just relax.
No one knows about this place.
You and I are
the only people here.
I certainly held myself
back for a long time.
I was fairly sure that
if you knew I was a HiME,
you would constantly
be worryin' about me.
I know that you had your
suspicions and all,
and I'm glad that you kept it
to yourself for so long.
But this time...
...I wasn't able
to keep it from you.
I'll do anything,
abandon everything,
even my work as
Student Council President.
[NATSUKI whimpers]
Really... I didn't care
what happened to me.
[NAO groans]
You haven't seen
the last of me yet...
Why is everyone coming after
me anyhow? I don't get it.
[gasps]
I really do like you, Natsuki.
So you have my word,
I'll do whatever it takes
to protect you.
[NATSUKI]
Me, too.
I like you, too, Shizuru.
Perhaps... But the meaning of
your "like" and my "like"
is quite different.
[BOY A]
The school's closed?
I wish they would've
told us before we came.
[BOY B] You really think
a fire did this?
[GIRL A] I heard that someone
saw what looked like a dragon.
[GIRL B] I heard it was
some kind of squid monster.
[GIRL C]
What's up with this school?
[BOY C]
Remember?
There was that incident
the other day, too.
This place could be dangerous.
[GIRL D] I was talking
to my mom and she said
I should come home right away.
[STUDENTS yelling]
Suzushiro!
The Student Council's
gonna have to give
an explanation to the students!
If we leave it as is--
Trust me; I would've
done it already if I could have!
Unfortunately, the President's
the only one with authority.
This is ridiculous! I can't
believe that bumbling idiot!
I'm so disappointed that we
haven't heard a peep from her!
[sighs]
The only positive
attribute she had to offer
was her dedication to her work.
Don't be upset...
[HARUKA] And not a word
from the Headmaster, either.
What is going on
at this school?!
[CHIE]
Well, this sure is a mess.
Yeah. What a shock that was.
I was right in the middle
of a nice bath, too!
[CHIE]
What?!
Did you run out naked?!
[gasps]
I had a towel around me!
[YUICHI]
Hey! Where's Tokiha?!
--[AOI] Tate...
--What happened to her, huh?
[AOI]
I dunno.
[YUICHI groans]
[AOI] Mai and Mikoto haven't
been around since last night.
[groans]
Tate?
[MIDORI] You've gotta
do something about this!
Look what's happened
to Mai and Mikoto!
It's insane!
[door latch clacks]
Miss Mashiro! This came for you!
Have they seen right through it?
It's strange that an invitation
would arrive before
we even know who he is...
Miss Sugiura...
[MIDORI]
Huh?
I have to tell you,
there is something
that I need to
explain to you still.
[MIDORI]
Huh?
A barrier, huh?
Interesting.
I wonder what they could be
talking about in there?
No way!
Yes. These are the
ritual machinations
of the Battle Princesses.
[MIDORI sighs]
The Obsidian Prince...
The Crystal HiME...
[gasps]
Wait! Then you're...!
I remember you said
that a person could change
her destiny by the
power of her will.
[MIDORI]
Yes?
Well, we're going to have to
count on that theory of yours.
I'm going along, too!
I'm entrusting this to you.
Guard it closely.
[FUMI] No, Miss Mashiro!
She's still not--
[MASHIRO]
Yes, I know.
But the recovery will
soon be complete.
I'll leave it up to you
whether or not to awaken her.
Yes, I understand.
[sighs]
[growls]
Damn it!
They're about to enter
the Obsidian Palace!
I'm afraid I've placed
a heavy burden of responsibility
on Miss Sugiura.
I think you were right
to do it, personally.
I have to admit it--
I honestly do like Miss Sugiura.
Fumi...
I'm so grateful you've
served me all these years.
Thank you.
The pleasure has been all mine.
And, Miss Mashiro,
I am your maid.
Delicious.
[FUMI sighs]
[MASHIRO sighs]
This is obviously
some kind of trap.
Nevertheless, we must
still go to see him.
[MASHIRO]
It is our duty to do this,
our turn to make up for forcing
battles on the HiME,
even when we knew of their fate.
It seems that they've
been planning it all along.
To defeat you, I mean.
Thing is...
...they never really
knew who you were.
I hope you're grateful
for all that I've done.
Heh.
It looks like they've arrived.
I'm surprised that you
decided to seek me out.
Have you been dissatisfied with
your throne, Queen of Hades?
So you were the vessel
for the Obsidian Prince...
...Reito Kanzaki.
All of my memories have
come back to me now.
I must say, you've been working
hard the past 300 years,
Mashiro. Or rather...
...Crystal HiME.
[REITO chuckles]
[MASHIRO]
I will defeat you
in order to break the curse
that haunts the HiME.
[REITO] So you put your
soul into a Child,
and decided to live as a doll?
You were so determined
to defeat me
that you went that far?
Yes. Because, in the past,
you were the one I loved.
You, my brother.
[REITO]
Hmph.
Now, Fumi!
[FUMI grunts]
[MIKOTO grunts]
[gasps]
Anybody who dares to
try and defeat my brother
will have to go
through me first!
You've done it again! Stop this!
Even if I crush you,
the only thing that will happen
is that your power as a Child
will be wasted.
Now, Mikoto...
...my adorable little sister.
The time has come for
you to fight for me.
Yes. Of course, Brother.
[MIKOTO growls]
Mikoto...
Unfortunately...
there's no choice...
Miss Mashiro?!
[MIKOTO growls]
[MIKOTO]
Uh?
Miroku!
Headmaster... Ah...
Fumi...
[REITO] Thank you all,
for the work you have done
while I was away
these past 300 years.
The moment of destiny is near.
From now on,
all matters will be...
...under my authority.
[MASHIRO] That certainly
caught me off guard,
finding out that Reito is
the Obsidian Prince.
[NAGI] Really? Didn't he seem
suspicious from the start?
[FUMI] Why would he?
He awakened just recently.
[NAGI]
Oh, right.
Then I guess he's just
the shady type by nature.
[REITO]
Well, excuse me.