[MIYU]
All safeties disengaged.
Anti-materializer at full power.
Zero, two, six...
Exceeding power limit.
What?!
[MAI grunts]
[MASHIRO] Now is the time
to break free of our fate.
That was a nice try,
but it's too late.
[REITO] No one can change
the destiny of the Star.
I don't get it!
All the pillars
have all risen...
Usually, there are 12
HiME for each festival.
But this time, the situation
is a little different.
Although she may
have been a fake,
she did undeniably
possess powers.
[gasps]
You mean Alyssa?
Mikoto...
Mai...
I'm sorry, Mikoto...
Huh?
[MAI] There were many things
I didn't understand before--
not just about you,
but also about myself.
Tell me...
What were you
crying about before?
Huh?!
Mikoto!
--Uh!
--[MAI growls]
I have no choice.
All I can do now is fight.
Because that's what
my brother wishes.
Mikoto...
Mikoto!
[MIKOTO yells]
[REITO]
Hmph.
[yells]
Mai! Get serious!
[grunts]
Otherwise... I'll do it!
For real!
[MAI grunts]
Kagutsuchi!
[MIKOTO growls, yells]
[MIKOTO yells]
[grunts]
I am begging you, Mai!
Mikoto...
[REITO] I'll extend the
offer one last time.
Mai. Join me, and we'll
create a new world together.
What if I agreed to join you?
Then what about Mikoto?
She'd gladly let you
strike the fatal blow.
Isn't that right... Mikoto?
Yes, Brother.
[MAI]
Huh...?
I'll never say "yes"!
Not on your life!
[REITO]
Why not?
You and I can re-create
the world any way we desire.
That's just plain psycho,
wanting to mold the world
to your own liking!
I won't be a part of it!
[REITO growls]
Unbelievable.
Women can be such a nuisance.
What're you doing?!
Stand back and stay
out of this, Mikoto!
[growls]
Mikoto...
[REITO]
Mai...
This is it...
[MAI gasps]
[gasping]
No...
Oh, it's for real, Mai!
Yuichi...
[REITO growls]
The time has finally arrived.
You must awaken, my HiME.
[gasps]
[MASHIRO] Now is the time
to bring our long years
of fighting to an end.
And the chance to free ourselves
from the yoke of a cursed fate.
[MASHIRO] Since ancient times,
many young maidens
have been sacrificed as
offerings of these festivals.
[MASHIRO]
Use their tears.
Let their feelings
be your nourishment.
This is the time to
perform the true dance
of the Battle Princesses.
[HARUKA]
Ow!
[MASHIRO]
Your love for someone precious,
and the power of that love!
[YUKINO]
Haruka!
[HARUKA yelps]
[YUKARIKO gasps]
[SHIZURU sobs]
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me, Natsuki!
--I--!
--It's okay, Shizuru.
Don't cry.
[SHIZURU gasps]
C'mon.
[SHIZURU]
Hmm.
Curse him. Nagi screwed up.
What do you think you
can accomplish on your own?
You gave up your will
and the power to fight...
...Yuichi Tate!
You've got a point there.
But you know what?
That guy you remember is dead.
[REITO]
Hmph.
That's ridiculous logic.
What are you doing, Mikoto?
You're supposed to be fighting!
[gasps]
[MIKOTO growls]
--Miko-- [shrieks]
--[YUICHI] Mai!
[REITO yells]
[YUICHI grunts]
[MAI] Mikoto, I think I
might finally get it now.
[MIKOTO growls]
[MAI] I understand
what it is to truly love.
And I know I have to
trust my own feelings.
I can't doubt it. If I love a
person, I have to tell him that.
Otherwise, he'll never know.
[MIKOTO growls]
[YUICHI grunts]
[MAI] This scary, yet happy
feeling living within me.
A single, warm,
incomparable feeling...
...that I can
convey to everyone!
[screams]
I get it...
Mikoto!
I know now--
I love you, Mikoto!
[gasps]
Forgive me...
I'm sorry for everything.
Mai...
Mai!
[BOTH sob]
You must realize
that there's no way
you can possibly beat me.
Oh, yeah. But then again,
I'm in too deep to pull out now.
Is that so?
Then you shall... die!
--[YUICHI grunts]
--[BOTH gasp]
[yells]
[MAI yells]
--[YUICHI] No!
--[MAI grunts]
[REITO groans]
[
Mai!
[REITO] Pretty impressive move,
I'll give you that much.
Now... time to finish this off.
[YUICHI]
Not on my watch, buddy.
I'm gonna protect Mai.
And that's because...
[REITO growls]
...I love her!
Yuichi...
[MIKOTO gasps]
That's garbage!
[gasps]
No, Brother!
[REITO gasps]
Mikoto...
How could you...?!
Let's stop this, Brother.
I'll go with you.
Just stop...
[MIKOTO]
I love you... Brother.
[grunts]
Mikoto!
Brother...
What...?
[TRUE OBSIDIAN PRINCE]
You fools...
I am the Obsidian Prince.
Since ancient times,
I have guided the power
of the HiME Star and have
controlled the misfortunes
and so-called miracles that
have occurred in this world.
[MAI] So you're the one
that killed my friends!
[TRUE OBSIDIAN PRINCE]
And what if I did, Mai-HiME?
Kagutsuchi!
[TRUE OBSIDIAN PRINCE]
Hah!
Kagutsuchi?!
[TRUE OBSIDIAN PRINCE]
How foolish of you.
As long as the HiME Star exists,
Miroku and I will survive.
Hey! I'm here!
Same for me!
I sure hope I can do this.
[YUKARIKO] Not to worry--
the Lord will be by your side.
Sister's right! Let's do it!
[NAO]
Fujino! You...!
[SHIZURU gasps]
[NAO growls]
[SHIZURU]
Uh...
Miss Fujino...?
Forgive me, girls!
[NAO, YUKINO]
Whaa--?!
Hey! This is no time
to be fooling around!
Is everybody ready?
On three!
HiME Force deploying!
[MIDORI]
Ah--!
I didn't say "three" yet!
[MASHIRO]
My Battle Princesses,
the ones guided
by the HiME Star.
Your power stems
from the pure, special
feelings that you have
for the ones you love.
[MASHIRO] And those
feelings are exactly what
will carry us into the future.
What the--?!
[gasps]
[TRUE OBSIDIAN PRINCE]
The HiME Star!
Kagutsuchi!
[screams]
[grunts]
Those girls did it this time.
Oh, man... They did it...
I worked so hard to
make sure this wouldn't happen!
[yells]
Mikoto! Say something! Please!
Uh... Mai...
[REITO groans]
[grunts, chuckles]
Mai...
You know I love you...?
For real...
I know that.
And I love you, Mikoto!
[gasps]
Kagu... tsuchi...
[KAGUTSUCHI whines]
Huh?
[MIKOTO]
Hey...
The fighting is over now...
Mai, don't cry anymore...
I like you so much better
when you're laughing...
Mikoto!
It feels... [groans]
...so good to love...
...right...
...Mai...?
No... Mikoto...?
Mikoto! Say something!
--[sobs]
--[YUICHI whimper
Don't leave... Mikoto...
[screams, sobs]
Come back!
[NATSUKI]
Mai!
Mikoto?!
No way...
Mikoto...
[MAI sobs]
[stomach growls]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
Mikoto...?
I'm starving... Mai...
I'm... a goner...
[MAI]
Uh... What?
[FUMI] We've experienced
all kinds of trouble
around here lately.
But the reason you students
are all here together
today is due to the love
you have for
this academy.
Congratulations
on your graduation.
Let's be together forever.
Nothing can ever hurt our love.
Oh, you!
[KAZUYA]
Akane!
[AKANE]
Kazuya!
[BOTH laugh]
[HARUKA growls]
Please read this message.
'Cause it's for the next
head of the Execution--
Executive Committee!
[YUKINO]
Haruka...
I dunno. Think I can manage?
Without you, I mean?
Don't start crying.
This is your time
to shine, Yukino.
You just have to do what you
think is right. Simple as that.
Okay.
[YUKINO]
Listen, everyone,
you're only allowed
to tie ribbons--
You made a mistake with
one of the characters!
[gasps]
[MIYU] Calculation complete.
Chance of being chosen
to take part in the choral
competition is 0.3 percent.
Virtually zero.
[NAO] But the Lord sayeth this
about defeating the enemy...
"It's best to strike
them from behind."
[chuckles]
[KIYONE] Enemy?!
What are you talking about?!
If you took out all your rivals,
then you'd be guaranteed
to take home the prize.
[KIYONE] Isn't that
getting carried away?!
I was just seeking
the Lord's guidance!
[ALYSSA]
You're an awfully pathetic girl.
If you don't have
the desire to win
in the first place,
then you shouldn't bother
entering a competition at all.
Right, Miyu?
Yes, you are correct,
Miss Alyssa.
Uh... Never mind about me!
I'm outta here!
Just when we were about
to get down to business, too.
It's your fault
for being so intimidating,
snot-nosed little brat!
[ALYSSA]
Hmm?
I won't allow anyone
to insult Miss Alyssa!
[YUKARIKO]
Sister Nao! Sister Miyu!
How dare you tarnish
the purity of this church!
[NAO sighs]
[SAKOMIZU] Well, I guess
it's all behind us now.
The HiME and Star
have disappeared
and the organization's
dissolved. Even I'm all through.
[laughs]
Just a regular teacher.
[SAKOMIZU]
Where are you off to now?
I dunno.
Except...
...I could use some time
to think about my life.
That's what I'll be doing
for the time being.
Hang on there a second.
[clears throat]
There's something that I have
to tell you as your teacher.
[NATSUKI]
Hmph. What?
It's your attendance this year.
You've missed
far too much school.
Unless you take make-up classes,
you'll have to repeat
first year, all over again.
Wait! Can't you do something?!
Like, maybe...
Uh, heh... pull some strings...?
I'm afraid I can't.
I guess that throws a wrench
in your little journey
over the holidays, doesn't it?
No! Wait! You can't!
[SHIZURU] Repeating a year?
Oh, that doesn't sound too bad.
Shi... zuru...
Maybe I'll do the same.
Graduation can wait.
Uh... Hey, Mai?
Uh! What?
Uh... Well...
I was thinking...
We've never really...
--...you know...
--[MAI whimpers]
Anyway...
[MAI squeals]
[YUICHI grunts]
Why'd ya--!
Over there.
[YUICHI]
Huh?
[SHIHO]
Brother...!
[YUICHI grunts]
You can't go ahead
without my approval!
That's right.
You know, you've got to give the
competition a fair chance, Tate.
Reito!
[MIKOTO] Forget it! You and
Yuichi better back off, Brother!
Because Mai belongs to me!
[MAI squeals]
Hey, would you stop
being so reckless?!
You just got five stitches!
It's hardly even
a flesh wound!
Look, Mai! What do you think?!
Jeez...
Hey...
Was that a bra I just
spotted under there?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm! Natsuki gave me one!
Uh, not that she's anywhere
near actually needing one.
Natsuki...
[MIKOTO]
What're you talking about?!
I'll be bigger than
Mai, pretty soon!
Stop flashing people!
Huh? What's that?
[TAKUMI] The surgery went well,
and I'm recovering just fine.
Looks like I'll be able to
make it back for next term.
[AKIRA]
That's what he thinks, anyway.
The doctor says that
he wants to monitor him
for a little while longer.
But there's nothing
to worry about.
I'll be taking good care of him.
Sounds like he's well.
That's great.
[
Yeah.
[YOKO]
Oh, I got this from Midori.
[MIKOTO gasps]
Here we go, Sugiura!
We'll protect the Balagan Ruins!
All right, Prof!
--[TERRORISTS scream]
--[MIDORI] Comin' through!
Sounds like our Midori.
Is that prof of hers
an idiot as well?
She sure seems to be
having a good time, though.
--Yup!
--Huh?
[TAKUMI] P.S. It all seems
like a dream to me right now,
but I think all the things
that happened back home
made me stronger,
so I could be ready for this.
Thanks, Sis; it all
worked out for the best.
[MAI]
I think so too, Takumi.
[AOI groans] I'm glad
spring break starts tomorrow.
Here's an idea.
What do you say to going
on a date with me, Mai?
[YUICHI gasps]
No chance! Mine!
[MAI chuckles weakly]
Why do I have to
have club practice?!
You can't let your pal
Takeda down, now.
You're sure popular, Mai!
Yeah... I guess...
Oh? That's a change!
She actually admitted it!
Well... it's a good thing
to be liked by people!
Right, Natsuki?
Mikoto?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm!
[NATSUKI chuckles]
[CHIE] Hmph! Now we've got
her blushing big time!
Check it out!
So, Mai! What've
you decided to do?
Give us the details!
[MAI]
Hmmm...
Okay, I know!
[BOTH gasp]
The thing I love
to do most...
What I wanna do most...!
[gasping]
[laughing]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Mai Tokiha!
[cheering]
[NAGI] Just because the
HiME Star has disappeared
doesn't mean that the world
is free of disasters.
In fact, the future is even less
clear now than it's ever been.
It was the girls that
made the final decision.
I'm sure they can handle it.
[FUMI]
Mm-hmm.
What's the deal?
Since the war, girls and socks
have gotten so much tougher.
Right?
[MASHIRO sighs]
It's time to return.
Let's go back to
where we ought to be.
--[MAI gasps]
--What's the matter?
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
[MAI]
Hmph. Let's go! Natsuki! Mikoto!
[MIKOTO giggles]
[school bell chiming]