--[MAN A] This is the girl?
--[MAN B] Yes.
She has ighly-advanced
materializing capabilities.
She's been created as a
practical application
of the technology.
[SEARRS]
Alyssa...
Bring the Golden Age
to the Searrs Foundation.
[ALYSSA]
Huh...?
Ah...
I'm better now.
Thank you.
But your vital signs
aren't back to normal yet.
Don't worry.
I don't have time to be resting.
I've lived my whole
life for this day.
Yes, but...
[NAGI]
Ugh! I can't believe this!
[NAGI] Boy, you sure
made a mess of my hideout.
It would upset anyone.
Don'tcha think?
I assume you're Nagi. Correct?
You know, you can try all you
want,
but the star isn't going
to do what you hope it will.
Oh, and count on a whole
lot of payback for the mess
you've made of my plans.
Do what you want.
But don't be so sure
we're the bad guys here.
You are hardly innocent.
Gimme a break...
The attitude of kids today.
[MAI] Um, Headmaster,
why did you call us all here...?
[MASHIRO]
This is no trivial matter.
I want you to save our school.
[MAI sighs]
The Searrs Foundation has taken
occupation of the academy.
They're after you,
with the goal of keeping you
from acquiring the power
of the HiME star.
The Foundation has
their HiME, Alyssa Searrs,
and her bodyguard, Miyu Greer.
If they don't get
what they want,
they'll destroy the school, as
well as the entire student body.
Just like they did when they
destroyed the bridge.
[ALL gasp]
The bridge?
So Alyssa was behind that.
[MASHIRO] The satellite
Eclipse 1 is going to harness
her power and become her Child.
Alyssa? No... N--
It's us HiME that
they're looking for.
So if we leave the
school grounds,
they'll probably release
the other students.
[NAO scoffs]
What're you talking about?
That's not gonna happen.
[NATSUKI] They hardly seem
like the type to negotiate.
But...
Hey, will you please
clarify one thing for me?
Is Akane Higurashi a HiME?
I'm afraid that
Akane was defeated
at the hand of Miyu Greer.
As long as they're here
threatening the academy,
they're a danger to you HiME.
That's why I need your help.
[NATSUKI]
All right, then.
I don't like the idea of
helping you District 1 people.
But now isn't
the time to be picky.
[MIKOTO]
Hmm.
--[MAI] Huh?
--[MIDORI] We're the only ones
that can take on Searrs and
save everyone from danger.
Don't the HiME
fight for justice?
Midori...
Think I'll pass.
You can carry on
without me, ladies.
Fine by me.
As long as you're sure you
can escape without any help.
[NAO growls]
Mai.
First, I need you to
promise me one thing.
Promise you'll make
the safety of the students
your top priority.
You have my word.
All right, then.
[MIDORI]
It's settled.
[YUKARIKO]
Oh, Lord...
[NAO]
"Oh, Lord," is right.
HiME? Takumi's sister?
[NAGI]
You've come all this way,
and you're not gonna
say hello to anyone?
You're too shy for your
own good, you know.
But you will help out, right?
Or else your precious Takumi
will be in trouble, too.
[AKIRA gulps]
You think I care about him?!
[laughs]
Huh?
[gasps]
Diana!
[MAI] So this prevents them
from seeing what's going on
outside the buildings?
[MIDORI] Now that's
what I call convenient.
[MIKOTO]
Super cool, Yukino!
Miss Mashiro.
It's time to begin.
Okay, girls.
Our preparations are complete.
There're about six
hours until the satellite
is in position to lock onto us.
If we can evacuate the students
and hold Alyssa Searrs back
until then,
we will have succeeded.
Good luck, girls.
[GROUP]
Hmm.
[MASHIRO]
Mai and Miss Sugiura,
your job is to fight back
the main enemy fleet
taking position in the bay.
Natsuki, your team will
handle the land forces
that have surrounded
the area with tanks.
May the Lord protect us.
[NAO groans]
All right, all right, I'll go.
One more thing.
Understand that you are
essentially acting as decoys.
Please remember that the success
or failure of the evacuation
depends on your ability
to draw the enemy forces
away from the school.
[MAI]
Hmm.
Everyone is in position
and ready to begin!
Operation "Recapture
Fuka Academy..."
...commencing!
[MAI]
Kagutsuchi!
[MIDORI]
Gakutenou!
Go! Duran!
[DURAN howls]
[MIKOTO growls]
[MIKOTO yells]
[DURAN howls]
[MIKOTO snarls]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
Hi, boys!
If I'm gonna help out,
I'm definitely gonna have
as much fun as I can.
Tokiha!
Takumi...
Everyone...
Let's go, Kagutsuchi!
[GREER]
The Valkyries are...!
[MIYU]
We know that already.
Just relax.
[GREER]
B-But...
Don't worry.
It's going as planned.
[MIDORI]
Spiral Dasher!
I'd get off those ships
if you wanna make it
through another day!
[gasps]
That's going a little overboard!
Jeez!
The evacuation plan outlined in
that note seems to be for real.
[SHIZURU] Then I suppose
we'd better get going as well.
[HARUKA]
Huh?!
[GREER]
Yes. Leave it to me.
[chuckles]
The soldiers have just
started moving!
It's a good time to run for it!
Go now, Shiho!
[SHIHO]
What about you?
[YUICHI groans]
I'm staying.
I'm going back to the school.
[gasps]
[sobs]
[SHIHO]
Do you really...
Do you really like Mai
that much, Brother?
[YUICHI gasps]
It's not like that.
It's just...
It's just that I...
Anyway, just try to get as far
away from the school as you can.
Brother!
[MIKOTO]
Everyone's still alive.
You sure we don't have
to finish them off?
Just leave them.
Yukino. Fill me in.
Sure thing.
Let's see...
[gasps]
Tate?!
[YUICHI pants]
[YUICHI]
What is this?
[SOLDIER G groans]
[YUICHI gasps]
[NATSUKI] What're you doing
wandering around here?!
Kuga!
Let me help out somehow!
[NATSUKI]
You're in the way!
--[gasps]
--Just get outta here.
There's nothing that
you can do to help us.
[YUICHI growls]
Brother...
[gasps]
[SHIHO shrieks]
[MASASHI]
Huh...?
Reito!
We're evacuating
the school at once!
[SHIZURU]
Head to the back hills!
[NATSUKI]
Where's Alyssa?
She hasn't appeared yet?
[YUKINO gasps]
I see her! She's on the
cliffs along the sea!
[ALYSSA] ♪ Who are those
little girls in pain? ♪
♪ Just trapped in castle
of dark side of moon. ♪
♪ Twelve of them shining
bright in vain ♪
♪ Like flowers that blossom
just once in years. ♪
[NATSUKI]
You!
♪ They're dancing in the
shadow like whispers of love. ♪
--♪ Just dreaming of-- ♪
--[MAI] Alyssa!
[ALYSSA]
Hmm?
Let's just stop this mess.
Okay?
Impossible.
[MAI]
Why?
[MIYU] We have an objective
and conviction with regard
to the use of your powers.
That's why we fight.
[ALYSSA] You, on the other hand,
have no purpose whatsoever.
That's why you're always
asking for reasons.
[gasps]
[ALYSSA] You believe in nothing,
and you have no resolve.
You don't know
what you truly desire,
or what you should
even be doing.
We cannot allow people like you
take the power of the star.
[alarm blares]
Miss Mashiro!
Huh?!
That satellite's
already above us!
[ALYSSA]
Just because it's a satellite
doesn't mean it's always
traveling at the same speed.
I've outmaneuvered you.
[NATSUKI growls]
[ALYSSA] The students
can run all they want,
but no matter
where they are,
they cannot avoid
Artemis's blast.
Please, Alyssa!
Stop this!
Only on one condition.
Surrender to the
Searrs Foundation.
You leave me no choice.
Artemis!
The Golden Lightning!
[gasps]
Kagutsuchi!
No, Mai!
What's she doing?!
No, don't!
[MAI] How can you talk of
resolve and conviction
when you're only
fighting for power?
You're wrong.
I'll fight...
Because--
No! Mai...
Why'd you do it...?
[YUKARIKO whimpers]
Oh, Mai...
[gasps]
[MIDORI gasps]
Mai!
[MAI groans]
What...?!
[screams]
[MAI grunts]
[shrieks]
[GROUP gasps]
[MAI]
What?!
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[MIYU gasps]
Miss! Are you all right?!
[SEARRS gasps]
[yells]
[SEARRS MEMBER A]
Orders from the Foundation...
Eliminate everything.
It's all over.
Give it up.
Miss Alyssa...
[MIDORI gasps]
Missiles!
Run!
[MIKOTO grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Snow?
--[NAO gasps]
--Think it's from the explosion?
So... basically, I was useless.
[GIRL A]
Come on, Shiho! Wake up!
--Shiho!
--Huh?
[GIRL A]
Please! Open your eyes!
Shiho!
Shiho...?!
[MIYU] If we can get to the
other side of these mountains,
we can escape.
Please, you need
to be strong, Miss.
Water... Some water...
Yes.
[MIYU gasps]
Miss Alyssa!
Joseph...?
But why...?
Well, I am just carrying
out my direct orders
from the committee.
If the plan failed, I was to
eradicate any trace of it.
In the end, it seems that
artificial Valkyries
were not meant to
exist in this world.
[grunts]
Miyu...
[MIYU]
No!
Please, try and
be strong for me!
Miss Alyssa!
For my whole life...
...I've been told
I shouldn't even exist
But you were always there.
Always...
[ALYSSA laughs]
[ALYSSA]
So warm...
Don't leave! Be strong!
One day, we'll build...
...a snowman together...
It's gone.
Her beautiful light is gone.
The soft, warm, golden light...
She was so adorable... [sobs]
And so lonely...
How could this happen to her?!
Who are those
little girls in pain?
Just trapped in castle
of dark side of moon.
As of now, we are
suspending this plan.
Is that acceptable?
[SEARRS MEMBER C]
I suppose.
And our next opportunity
will be in 300 years?
[SEARRS MEMBER B]
That's not a very long time
for the Searrs Foundation.
They're dancing in the
shadow like whispers of love.
Just dreaming of a place
where they're free as dove.
They've never been allowed
to love in this cursed cage.
-- It's only a fairy tale
--It's time to go.
-- they believe.
--I promise,
I will always be by
your side, Miss Alyssa.
[MIYU] I will continue to
protect you for all eternity.
They're dancing in the shadow
like whispers of love.
Just dreaming of a place
where they're free as dove.
They've never been allowed
to love in this cursed cage.
It's only the fairy tale
they believe.
[MIKOTO]
Mai?
How come Mai hasn't come back?
Midori?
Where is Mai?!
[MIDORI grunts]
[whines]
Mai...
Mai!
[NATSUKI]
Mai has fallen from the Heavens.
[NATSUKI] A sad funeral march
rings across a sky so blue
from the sacrifice of
one young maiden.
[MAI]
Hang on a minute...!
[NATSUKI]
Thank you, Mai... Good bye, Mai.
The star of the show from the
next episode on shall be me!
[MAI]
Hello?! I'm not dead yet!