[school bell rings]
[SAWADA]
That's it for today, class.
Be careful on
your way home, now.
[MIYA]
Hey, Chie!
You're going to
Poitier today, right?
Yeah, for sure!
On the way home.
Me, too!
Count me in for cake!
You won't get any taller
by eating cake, Yayoi.
[YAYOI growls]
Hey, Mai...
Huh?
You wanna come along with us?
It's an all-you-can-eat
cake buffet.
Definitely!
Oh, hang on...
I just remembered,
I gotta go to work.
See ya.
Too bad, her loss.
Tokiha must be on the
early shift at work today.
Oh, that's right, you work
at the same place don'tcha?
With Higurashi!
Will you stop with that
creepy laugh of yours?
[MAI]
Hmm?
It's raining.
[GIRLS giggling]
[GIRL A]
You always have a yummy lunch.
[GIRL B] My mom and I make
lunch together every morning!
[GIRL C]
Wow! Lucky you!
[GIRL B] Don't you help
your mom make lunch?
[MAI]
Hi, Miyu. Wanna come under?
I can walk you to the chapel
if you want me to.
An umbrella...
Right. I guess it is raining.
[MAI] We are right in the
middle of the rainy season.
[MIYU] A seasonal
rain front is moving north.
It's expected to pass
through to the Sea of Japan
between this evening
and tomorrow.
Yeah, anyway, I heard
some of the students
saying that you were
the daughter of Father Greer.
Is that right?
Joseph Greer is officially
my adoptive father.
Why? Is that a problem?
Ah. Not at all.
Isn't the chapel that way?
[MIYU] Take the path to
the right, and go straight.
Yeah, thought so.
[MIYU]
Then turn left after 300 meters.
[MAI]
Right.
I was thinkin', why don't we
go to the beach or something?
Maybe even take
a trip to Okinawa!
What? No way! Really?!
Aw. They're working hard
together so they can save up
for their summer trip.
Lucky them.
It's nice to be young.
[AKANE giggles]
And since we were hungry,
we thought we might as well
come and cheer up our friend
while she's slaving
away at her job.
You're too kind.
Hey, Mai, I was wondering.
I heard that Takumi Tokiha
is your younger brother.
Is it true?
Yeah. Why do you
wanna know about him?
Because! Is it true that he's
rooming with Akira Okuzaki?
I haven't heard that.
Is he really?
Yeah, that's
pretty much the story.
[CHIE] I don't think
you understand, Mai.
Think of the implications.
The top ranked "pretty boy"
at our school, Akira Okuzaki,
is roommates with the new
rising star, Takumi Tokiha.
Picture them sleeping and waking
up in the same room every day...
[GIRLS gasping]
Just the two of them...
Together morning and night...
[BOTH]
Think of what could happen!
That's my little brother
you're talking about!
And I'd appreciate it if you
stopped dragging him
into your twisted imaginations!
[AOI] Oh, right--
she's his older sister.
Anyway, from what I hear,
I don't think there's
anything to worry about.
Hey, Akira, I ended up
making too much dinner
for myself. You want some?
Don't be such a wus!
Real men don't waste
their time cooking!
Have you gone out of
your mind or something?!
Uh... I just--
--[AKIRA] Feet!
--[gasps]
You are over the line!
You are in my territory!
[TAKUMI]
Whoa, sorry.
So, was that a "yes" for dinner?
[AKIRA]
Back up slowly...
Sounds pretty crazy to me.
It'd be nice if they
got along better.
Akira sure is cute, huh?
Heh. Hey, that reminds me,
Mai, do you like karaoke?
Love it!
[SAYURI] We've got a free coupon
that's good until tomorrow.
What do you think?
Tomorrow's a day off, right?
A day off, huh...
Uh... Actually, I gotta work
first thing in the morning.
Sorry. I'll have to pass.
But I'll go next time for sure!
[door bell jingles]
[MIYA]
She turned us down again.
What's she going to do with
all that money she's saving?
I'm sure Mai's got a good
reason for doing what she does,
so let's not butt in.
--Yeah, but--
--Just drop it.
[MAI]
Huh...?
Hello?
[MAI]
Mikoto?
--[MIKOTO groans]
--Huh?
[gasps]
[MAI]
Mikoto!
[MIKOTO whimpers]
What's the matter?!
What happened to you?!
Food...
Need food... I'm starving...
Why have you been
waiting all this time?
I showed you how to
buy the meal tickets
--for the school cafeteria.
--[MIKOTO groans]
But I like your food better.
Huh...? Yeah, nice try, there.
Flattery's not gonna
get you any more food.
[MIKOTO sighs]
[alarm beeps]
[MAI groans]
Does she have to
sleep on me...?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm...?
[yawns]
[MIKOTO]
Hmm...? Um, Mai?
Huh.
[MAI] "I'm off to work.
I'll make you dinner
when I get
home tonight,
but you'll have to manage
lunch on your own. Mai."
[MAI] So, how are things
going with Akira?
[TAKUMI] It's not easy
living with a total stranger.
But at least we're starting
to get along better
than we were before.
Oh, yeah? Then I guess there's
nothing to worry about.
Nope. I'm getting used to my
classes and Kanzaki's been
pretty nice to me at the dorm,
showing me around and stuff.
So, what about you?
[MAI]
Hmm... I'm okay. I guess.
Actually,
I'm having a good time.
You have your letter
of introduction?
--Yeah.
--Oh, and make sure you go
and say hello to the transplant
coordinators while you're there.
I know. Hey, Sis,
are you sure...?
I'm feeling kinda--
We already talked about
that and sorted it all out
before we came to this school.
I know...
Know what'll happen if
you bring it up again.?
I'll tell everyone how
you used to insist on
taking baths with me,
and that you still do.
Oh, no, Sis, you wouldn't!
[intercom rings]
[train horn blares]
[MAI gasps]
I must be imagining things.
Well, I've gotta get to work.
[AKANE]
Stop the bus! I'm coming!
Thanks for waiting.
[AKANE]
Mr. Sawada.
[MOCHIZUKI] I'm going to send
it off to an American hospital
that I'm affiliated with.
They said that they would
do an analysis for me.
Thanks, Doc, I appreciate it.
Doctor, there's been a
bus accident on the highway.
The ambulance'll
be here in five minutes.
All right, Takumi.
I'll talk to you later.
[TAKUMI]
Uh... Yeah.
Thanks again for everything.
[MIYA]
Hey, did you hear the news?
Poor Mr. Sawada!
Yeah, I saw it on TV.
I heard he was pretty banged up.
You take that same bus route
all the time, don't you, Akane?
[AKANE]
Yeah...
I got so worried
when I saw it on TV.
[AKANE]
Mm...
[MIYU]
Good morning.
[BOTH gasp]
[AKANE whimpers]
Good morning...
[KAZUYA]
Hmm.
He's been hospitalized
at your dad's, hasn't he?
Yeah, I asked Dad about him, he
said it's not life-threatening.
But he won't be getting
out any time soon.
[YUICHI] Figures.
Sawada's getting pretty old.
[MAI]
That time...
No, it can't be...
--[AOI] Mai.
--[gasps]
[AOI] What's the matter?
You look pale.
The day's just starting,
Mai. Get it together.
Do I look that bad?
'Cause I feel totally fine!
[CHIE] Let's go to
the café for lunch today.
[MAI] Sure. I'll bring
Mikoto along, too.
[SUBSTITUTE A]
Take your seats!
[SAKO MIZU] Yes. They're
the ones who caused it.
Our people are already
dealing with them.
I have to say, Mr. Sawada
was unlucky;
in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
But at least he's
been stabilized.
And it looks like
he'll be transferred
to a regular hospital now.
What about the Orphan?
I have no idea.
On another note...
There is evidence of a battle;
that much is undeniable.
With another HiME.
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
I understand.
Yoshina will take care
of things on this end.
[FUMI] I'll make some tea.
You should take a little break.
Thank you, that'd be nice, Fumi.
[MASHIRO] It may be
their destiny as HiME,
but we've forced a very
difficult mission upon them...
How cruel...
[CHIE]
Hello! Anybody in there?
[MAI]
Hmm? What?
That.
[MAI gasps]
Come on, Mikoto, don't be
dropping your food.
[MIKOTO]
Hmm?
Finders keepers!
[MIKOTO whines]
Mai?
We can go and see him now.
Good. We'll visit on behalf
of all the girls in the school.
And maybe Tate and I
can represent the boys.
[YAYOI]
I just saw him over there!
Okay, we'll ask the others
if they wanna chip in.
Changing the subject
for a minute here,
but has Tokiha got
a younger brother?
She sure does.
His name is Takumi.
[TATSUHIKO]
Right. That's what I thought.
--[gasps]
--I get it.
That's why she puts in
so many hours at work.
What do you mean by that?
It's like this...
[YAYOI]
Takumi is?
--[SAYURI] Flowers...
--[MIYA] Fruit...
--[YAYOI] And cold tea.
--[SAYURI] That's it.
[YAYOI]
What about the bus fare?
Looks like we've
got it covered.
Hey, you guys free tonight?
I really feel like getting
out and singing karaoke!
Whaddaya say?
I'll make up for all the times
I turned you down
and we'll have fun!
Ah, uh!
Sorry!
I'm kinda busy today, too.
Oh. Right... That figures.
We're really sorry
about this, Mai.
No. It's my fault for
springing it on you
all of a sudden.
Don't worry about it, 'kay?
[MAI]
Just my luck.
Everyone's busy with
their school clubs today.
[BOY A] ...how hard
you've practiced.
Well, live and learn, I guess.
[GIRL D]
C'mon, race you there! [laughs]
[GIRL E]
You're on!
[MAI sighs]
[MAI] Taking a day off
work is great and all,
but there's nothing
for me to do.
[MAI sighs]
Might as well go home.
[gasps]
My mind's made up;
I'm not getting involved.
I don't get it.
Ohh!
Follow that bus!
I need you to hurry!
[TAXI DRIVER A]
The bus?
[MAI]
Yes! Uh...
As far as this'll take me!
[NATSUKI gasps]
This is fine! Let me out here!
Miss! Your change!
And your bag!
Ah!
[explosion]
[gasps]
[pants]
[LITTLE GIRL sobbing]
[WOMAN A]
A monster...
What was that thing?!
[gasps]
You okay, Kuga...?
Damn! It got away!
[sirens blaring]
They sure got here fast enough.
C'mon!
Hurry!
[MAI]
Who are those people?
[NATSUKI]
They're from an organization
called "District One."
They're assembling
HiME at the school.
And check it out--
Those ambulances aren't real.
Huh?!
[NATSUKI] They're sent
to hospitals and clinics
that are affiliated
with District One.
And people who saw
anything are "processed"
so they have no memory of it.
You can't be serious.
That's way too freaky.
I don't know what you
think about your powers, Mai,
and it doesn't really matter.
This is our reality.
The reality that we HiME
have to deal with.
[MAI]
Mm...
Yukimi No. 4's
already transporting?
I didn't hear about that.
Huh? Over there.
[AMBULANCE MAN A]
Hey! Are you hurt?!
Are you okay?
[AMBULANCE MAN A]
This girl needs treatment!
[GROUP gasps]
How come you're here...?
[gasps]
What? You guys.
How's it going, Mai?
[GIRLS groan]
[YUICHI]
What's the matter with you guys?
Didn't you tell Mai that
we were coming to visit
Mr. Sawada in the hospital?
[TATSUHIKO] Weren't we supposed
to take up a collection
from everyone in class.
Were you trying to
leave her out, or what?
Seems pretty childish
if you ask me.
That's not it!
[YUICHI]
Then tell me how it is!
It's like...
It's just that...
[SAYURI]
Well...
[YAYOI groans]
We heard all about
her brother Takumi
and his health problem.
We know it's serious.
Really serious.
You heard? From who?
[GIRLS groan]
Uh. I overheard my dad, and
let it slip to the others...
Sorry...
[SAYURI]
We wanted to talk to you,
but... it's not exactly
easy to bring up.
[MIYA] It's only been a short
time since you transferred here,
so we didn't wanna butt in.
[MAI]
Oh, come on!
I should be the
one to apologize!
I mean, for making you guys
get all worried about me.
You mean you're not mad at us?
'Course not! That's crazy.
There's nothing for me
to be mad about, is there?
You sure are dedicated
to your brother.
I really admire you.
Nah, it's no big deal.
If you wanna see my notes,
or even study for an exam,
just let me know!
[MAI]
Thanks!
[YAYOI]
Good luck with everything, Mai!
We'll all be rooting for you!
I really mean that.
[MAI]
Hmm.
[SAYURI]
Bye now.
See you tomorrow, guys.
[MAI pants]
[NURSE B]
Oh, Mai.
If you're looking for Takumi,
your father came to pick
him up a little while ago.
You're such a dedicated girl,
Mai; always trying so hard.
I'll be rooting for you.
[YUICHI]
Hey. You still here?
How come you are?
Oh, nothing special.
Just wanted to say hello to
a doctor who treated me before.
Don't you have an umbrella?
Well, don't expect
to get under mine.
Whatever. I would've
refused if you offered.
Umbrella... Don't need one...
[laughs, gasps]
Are you okay?
[MAI gasps]
Hey, wait! Hang on! Mai!
[MAI sobs]
[YUICHI pants]
I said wait!
I was only joking about
the umbrella, all right?!
So why'd ya have to...
Here, get under.
[MAI whimpers]
[wails]
[YUICHI]
Have a drink.
It's better hot.
Come on! Don't be so demanding.
Haven't you noticed
what time of year it is?
Just kidding.
I just felt like being
spoiled, that's all.
[YUICHI]
Oh, man...
[MAI]
I'm sorry for all this.
I just couldn't
keep it all inside.
Doesn't that ever happen to you?
Nope, never.
Never, huh?
I guess not.
[MAI] You don't say things
like that, do you?
[YUICHI]
Like what?
[MAI] Like, "I'm rooting
for ya," and stuff.
[sighs]
That's for losers.
It's so stupid to say it. And
even stupider to believe it.
Besides, Mai, I already
know you're doing your best.
How much harder can you try?
[gasps]
I mean... Forget it,
I'm just rambling here.
At the very least,
you deserve that
hand-delivered can of coffee.
And a cold can of coffee it is.
Very, very cold.
Makes sense.
Cuz I'm such a cool guy.
[MAI laughs]
What're you talking about?
You? Cool?
What's funny about that?
[MAI] Nothing. So ya
figure you're cool, huh?
[YUICHI]
Uh, yeah? You--
C'mon, just loosen up a bit.
[STUDENT A]
Hey, Big Brother!
What?! Grr!
What'd you call me?! Hey!
Good morning, Tate!
[YUICHI]
Hmm? Mai.
Thanks for yesterday.
--[gasps]
--Ooh! Ah! Uh!
It's hot!
Uh! Eh! Ooh!
Unlike someone I know,
I don't go out of my way
to try and convince
everybody I'm cool.
She's such a dork...
[MIKOTO]
Mai!
[giggles]
Glad you're back to normal, Mai!
Mm-hmm!
'Course I am.
What'dya expect?
C'mon. Let's go, Mikoto!
[MAI] The rainy season.
Endless rain...
--The rain of tears...
--[MIKOTO] Mai?
--I hate rain, it's like tears
--What's happened to you, Mai?
--falling from the sky.
--Get a grip!
[MIYU]
My brain is waterlogged.
The verdict: I don't like rain.