[SHIZURU]
Tell me something.
Do you think you should
be able to get away
with anything,
as long as it's for the sake
of the person you love?
Just as I thought.
I think so as well
[BOTH gasp]
No, Shizuru!
[MAI] Yeah. I'm willing
to go along with your plan,
but first, I wanna meet
the Obsidian Prince.
Mikoto?
[MIKOTO]
I will destroy her.
Under orders from my Brother.
[MIKOTO growls, yells]
[MIDORI grunts]
[MIKOTO yells]
[yells]
Agh, I would've let
you sleep forever
if it were possible.
[COMPUTER]
This unit has memory remaining
from the previous operation.
Do you wish to format the data
and assign a new master?
Memory...?
[yells]
[MIDORI gasps]
[MIKOTO growls]
--[MIKOTO yelps]
--I won't let you do it!
She's the only remaining
hope we have left!
[MIKOTO growls]
Miroku!
[MIDORI grunts]
Gakutenou!
[gasps]
You go and check it out.
And I will watch over you...
...Mai-HiME.
[MAI]
Midori!
[MIDORI groans]
You okay?!
--[MIKOTO] Mai...?
--[gasps]
[MAI gasps]
Mikoto...?
Mai...
You're alive...
Ugh... Mai... Be careful...
[MAI gasps]
[NAGI] First, I wanna
see proof that you're
actually serious about this.
[growls]
So that's what he meant.
[MAI]
Is that your Child, Mikoto?
My Brother, the Obsidian
Prince, gave me this power.
Obsidian Prince?!
Gakutenou...
[MIDORI]
Mikoto! No! Not that!
[yells]
[MIKOTO growls]
[MIKOTO yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
Miyu...? No way...
[MIDORI]
I'm sorry, Professor...
But you'll... be proud
of me, right...?
[MAI gasps]
[MAI]
Midori!
Mikoto!
I'm happy to see that
you're still alive,
but why? Why do this?!
[MIKOTO] I was brought up
to serve my brother.
Brought up to love no one
other than my brother.
[MAI gasps]
That's why I love him so much!
You're wrong! That's not
what love really is!
Then tell me what
it's all about!
[MAI gasps]
What does it mean...
...to truly love?
[gasps]
My brother tells me
that he loves me.
That he's happy when
I'm there for him.
[gasps]
That's why I've decided.
I'll continue to fight.
For his sake.
Mikoto!
Fujino...?
Miss Fujino! You, too?!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[gasps]
Uh!
[NATSUKI]
Stop it, Shizuru!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIZURU]
Natsuki!
[NATSUKI pants]
Were you... listening to us?
[NATSUKI grunts]
Natsuki... Please...
[NATSUKI gasps]
No!
[whimpers]
[SHIZURU gasps] I never wanted
you to find out about it.
This wicked love...
...it isn't the kind of love
that can be requited.
I understood that, but still...
Miss Kikukawa...
[SHIZURU]
The time is fast approachin'.
We're gonna have
to settle this.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?!
[YUKINO gasps]
[NATSUKI]
No, Shizuru! Stop!
[YUKINO whimpers]
What is this thing?
No, Haruka!
Gimme a break!
I never expected you to be
so cheap and shameless,
that's for sure!
You want to threaten us
with this big blade
just 'cause we happened to see
you in a moment of weakness?!
As Student Council President,
that's pretty low.
Let's just see you try it!
Don't push her,
Haruka, I mean it!
Be quiet!
What's the matter?!
Can't do it?!
Then get out of here
before you pull anything
even more embarrassing!
I won't let you lay
one finger on Yukino!
[SHIZURU]
Huh. Step back.
There's no place for you
in this matter.
I've heard more than I care to.
Kiyohime...
[BOTH whimper]
[KIYOHIME roars]
Shizuru, stop it!
I'm begging you!
Stand back, Haruka!
--So what?!
--Please!
You've gotta run away!
Duran!
Come out, Duran!
[SHIZURU]
Natsuki...
[gasps]
I will always be here
to protect you.
Kiyohime...
[roars]
--[YUKINO grunts]
--Yukino!
Diana!
[HARUKA gasps]
[gasps]
[YUKINO gasps]
No! Haruka you're...!
Huh? I what?
--[heartbeat]
--[groans]
[gasps]
Haruka!
[HARUKA groans]
What is it? What's happening?
[growls]
So that's how it is.
[YUKINO]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
You just watch!
[YUKINO]
What?!
[HARUKA] Fujino,
maybe you think this means
you've gotten rid of me...
...but you forget you're
dealing with Haruka Suzushiro.
You can't take me
out that easily...
...because I am right!
Human value isn't
determined through
cheap magic tricks like this...
[gasps sharply]
Don't kid yourself...
[SHIZURU grunts]
[HARUKA grunts]
Yukino!
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Yukino...
You're amazing, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
I...
Haruka...
[NATSUKI sighs]
[SHIZURU]
Heh. Oh, how amusing.
[NATSUKI growls]
[SHIZURU]
Pathetic.
I wonder if she actually
thought she could fight me.
[chuckles]
[NATSUKI growls]
There's nothing to
hide from you now.
Natsuki... you must know...
...I truly am in love with you.
Shizu... ru...
Don't worry. I'll defeat
all of the other HiME.
If there's anything
you don't like,
I'll take care of it
for you, Natsuki.
[NATSUKI]
Huh...?!
You just watch.
Wait! Shizuru!
Shizuru!
Oh, how frightening!
I'm impressed!
It's exactly as you predicted.
Nagi. Please go and tell her
where to find Natsuki's enemy.
And the reason why District 1
is called District 1.
[NAGI]
Yes, sir! What?!
It's become quite clear to me
as I awaken after 300 years.
This world is no good.
However... as long as those
old ladies are around,
everything will
repeat endlessly.
The future must be built by
the hands of young people.
Hey... Are you the
Obsidian Prince?
Or maybe Kanzaki.
No, Reito Minagi.
[REITO]
Hmph.
[MIDORI]
"Dear Mai.
I promised you'd get
first look at my thesis
when it was done.
I'm still not finished,
but I want you to hear
what I've learned so far
about the HiME battles.
Do you remember
that place underground
where all those
pillars were located?
Apparently, a pillar
rises up every time
someone precious
to a HiME vanishes.
When 11 pillars have risen,
in other words, when there's
only one HiME remaining,
the final door opens.
Then that last HiME will
be able to attain the power
of the HiME Star.
But only in exchange
for a certain destiny.
To become the wife of
the Obsidian Prince.
Mai, I don't know who you hold
most dear in your heart.
But don't lie to yourself about
whom you give your love to.
Because for us to love
a person strongly,
means to put that
person's life at risk.
So, at the very least,
it's important
that you're true to yourself
about how you feel for someone."
[MAI] I'm sorry, Midori.
But it doesn't matter anyway.
Either way...
Then tell me
what it's all about!
What does it mean...
to truly love?
[echoing]
...to truly love?
[gasps]
[grunts]
Why did things have
to turn out this way...?
[YOKO] Did she write anything
that might be of help to you?
Huh?
Uh... [sniffs] Yeah.
Good. I'm glad to hear that.
So she can be a little teacher-
like, when she wants to be.
[MAI sighs]
[YOKO]
Sister accidentally forgot that.
It seems she wasn't feeling
very well yesterday.
So she was getting some rest.
Is that right?
She was very grateful
for everything.
It was her first time.
As a patient, I mean.
From what I gather,
she's very healthy.
She's never even been
sick or injured before.
Are you sure?
[YOKO]
Yes.
But what about that time
when she hurt her arm?
[YOKO] Hmm? I never treated
her for any arm injury.
And when I examined her,
I didn't see any scars or
signs of past injury.
Sister...
Damn that kid!
My last chance, he says?!
What a joke!
Stop staring!
Don't look at me like that!
I'm the man that sullied you!
You ought to hate me!
And I still need you
to fight for me!
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
I love you, Wataru...
Are you really
gonna leave me now?
Yeah. I've got some things
I need to get at the store.
Then promise me something.
You know that park
across the street?
Meet me there at
3 o'clock this afternoon.
[YUICHI]
Hmm? Why go to all that trouble?
Oh, I knew it...
You don't remember, do you?
[YUICHI sighs]
Okay, okay.
You want me at
the park at 3, right?
[gasps]
It's a promise!
And don't you forget, either!
That Shiho sure is a handful.
[gasps]
Kuga!
[SHIZURU]
Don't worry.
I'll defeat all
the other HiME.
If there's anything
you don't like,
I'll take care
of it for you, Natsuki.
[NATSUKI]
No, Shizuru!
No!
--[YUICHI] Hey.
--[gasps]
Apparently, you
collapsed on the street.
You were brought
here in an ambulance.
They shouldn't have bothered.
They could've just left me
in the street for all I care.
[YUICHI] Hmm?! You've
gotten all strange, too.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
You're a HiME, aren't you?
What's happening?!
Tokiha's acting weird, too!
Mai is?
[MAI] There's something
I wanna ask you.
[YUKARIKO]
Certainly.
I see. Mai as well, huh?
The fate of the HiME
will destroy everything.
Tell me, are you
in love with Mai?
[YUICHI]
Hmm?! I don't really know.
'Specially 'cause...
How could she...
How could she just...?!
[NATSUKI]
Hmm.
HiME battles put lives at stake.
The lives of people
we love the most.
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
When a HiME is defeated,
the person most precious
to that HiME is... lost.
Ah! Then Takumi was...!
No, Takumi was lost as the
loved one of another HiME.
Come to think of it...
...back then, the person
that Mai loved the most
might have been changing.
[gasps]
That's the kind of
person I am, you see?
Now, goodbye.
No! That's why...
[NATSUKI]
Tate?!
Agh!
[YUICHI]
Damn!
Damn! Damn!
[YUICHI]
Mai!
[MAI] The real battle
began that night
when you came running back,
claiming that Nao
had attacked you.
That was a deception.
That was something
created by my Vulas.
Then it was all
because of you! [growls]
[YUKARIKO]
If you're going to crush me,
I would be more
than happy to oblige.
Except that...
...I don't want you to
commit a sin for the sake
of someone you love.
[ISHIGAMI groans]
It's too late for that!
You lied! This is
all your fault!
Lied?
I suppose you're right.
So you intend to defeat me,
and the other HiME,
to become the
last one remaining?
Yes! I'm going to win
and take Takumi back!
And him, I can--
[YUKARIKO] Are you absolutely
certain that's what you desire?
[MAI gasps]
[MAI] What do you want
outta life, most of all?
[gasps]
[NATSUKI grunts]
[screams]
[NAO]
Welcome back.
You sure took long enough.
I've been waiting for you.
For... ages.
Nao...
[SHIHO] Do you remember
what day it is, Brother?
Today's the anniversary of
the first day you and I met.
[SHIHO whimpers]
[screams]
[SHIHO groans]
You promised...
to meet me here.
[NAO]
My eye is still killing me.
Did I mention how much it burns?
The pain won't go away no
matter how many men I tie up.
It probably won't feel better
till I finish you off.
That's what I'm thinking.
[YUKARIKO] Mai, most
people desire one thing.
More than any other.
Just one thing.
[YUKARIKO] There are times when
people simply have to choose.
They must decide
what the one thing is,
that they cannot live without.
[YUICHI groans]
[SHIHO pants]
[whimpers]
[YUKARIKO]
Mai, don't be afraid.
Don't fear your true desire.
Don't fear the world
that you hope for.
[NATSUKI] Quite a ploy,
taking cover as a holy woman.
[YUKARIKO] I don't
need you to tell me that.
[NATSUKI] And Mikoto seems good
at the part of the evil villain.
[MIKOTO] I'm not
too happy about that part.
[NATSUKI] This is where
we get to see true evil!
Bring it on!
[YUKARIKO]
Pardon?
[MAI]
Say what?