Fumi.
How do you feel about all this?
Do you think that what
we're about to attempt
is the right thing to do?
I don't know if
it's right or wrong.
However...
...if you feel that
it needs to be done,
you can be sure that
I'll remain by your side.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
The time has come.
Soon, he will awaken.
[gasps]
[grunts, screams]
[MAI screams]
[gasps]
[MIKOTO yells]
[grunts]
Mai! Are you all right?!
[MAI]
Mikoto...?
Uh, Mai...
[growls]
How dare you...!
You'll regret that!
Nobody lays a hand on Mai!
[gasps]
[MIKOTO growls]
[yells]
--[growls]
--[MAI] Stop!
[gasps]
You shouldn't fight!
Don't do this, Mikoto!
Why do you say that?!
She's our enemy!
Please stop!
But why?
You, there!
Why are you doing this?!
I don't know who you are, but we
have no intention of fighting!
[MAI gasps]
Are you all right, Mai?
Not hurt or anything?
[MAI]
I think I'm okay.
[NAO]
Hmm...
[AKIRA]
I wonder if Father had any idea.
If he knew what this
battle was all about.
[NINJA A]
I do not know.
But I do know that you mustn't
let yourself be defeated.
That's the message the Master
wished to convey to you.
[AKIRA sighs]
Send my father a message.
Tell him I understand.
[NINJA A]
Of course.
[WHITE HIME]
Leave this place now.
[MAI whimpers]
Yes.
There's finally a heart
donor for your brother.
After all this waiting,
we have our chance at last.
I can't be defeated.
Huh? Stupid me.
This is exactly the way Nagi
would want me to think.
You've gotten much
better, Mikoto.
But you still seem to be
holding back somewhat.
Remember, those who attack
you are your enemies.
And enemies have to be defeated.
You mustn't hesitate when
the time comes to fight.
Understand?
[MIKOTO]
Mm-hmm!
I'll do what you
want me to, Brother.
[giggles]
You're such a good girl, Mikoto.
[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO]
Uh...?
[MIKOTO gasps]
It's hot...
[MAI]
What's the matter, Mikoto?
[MIKOTO gasps]
[MAI]
Better get back to sleep.
[MIKOTO]
I was having a dream.
Tell me about it.
[MIKOTO]
Mm... All right.
Hmph. I already forgot.
Typical.
Hey, thanks for
saving my life today.
[MIKOTO giggles]
But I think I should remind you.
You're not supposed to
fight the other HiME.
You understand that, right?
Hey, Mai.
Do you think it's wrong
to defeat an enemy?
Whaddaya mean...?
I really like you a lot, Mai,
so I wanna protect you.
The problem is...
It's just that...
I don't know what I can do.
[MIKOTO giggles]
Whatcha thinkin'?
Well, I'm thinkin'...
...I appreciate the sentiment.
Ah. Mm-hmm.
[giggles]
[MAI]
It's finally gonna happen!
It was a long wait,
but it was worth it!
The doctor was saying that
he wanted to examine you
then transfer you into
the hospital in the States
as soon as possible.
Then I'm sure
everything'll be fine!
And this American surgeon
has done tons of these
organ transplants before--
I hear he's one amazing doctor.
[TAKUMI]
Hmm.
[AKIRA sighs]
Nothing but good news,
right, Takumi?
Sis, I've been thinking...
[gasps]
[TAKUMI] I'll go to the
hospital and everything,
but first, do you think I could
have some time to myself?
[MAI]
But...
Yeah, I know.
It's just happening pretty fast,
and I could use some time
to get used to the idea.
[MAI groans]
[BOTH grunt]
--Tokiha!
--Tate...
Good morning.
Yeah...
I wonder what's going on
between those two.
Maybe something changed
about their relationship.
Yeah? What?
You think there's a complicated
love quadrangle going on with
Shiho and Reito?
It's anybody's guess. Who knows.
[AOI]
Hmm?
Anyway...
Let's just sit back and cheer
her on from the sidelines
this time, instead of
sticking our noses in it.
[YUKINO]
Mai...
Oh, good morning, Yukino.
Umm...
Miss Sugiura wants to see us.
[school bell chimes]
[MIDORI] Look, we won't
be doing ourselves any favors
by getting into fights.
So let's stay away from
anything that seems risky,
and that especially
goes for you, Nao.
[NAO] Huh, this is why you
called us all out here?
And what, are we supposed
to ignore what'll happen
to the world if we don't decide
who the most powerful HiME is?
Actually, it's probably
too late for that, anyway.
I dunno who, but someone's
serious about messing
things up around here.
Right?
[MAI gasps]
What is it, Mai?
Sorry.
I was planning to tell you all
about it later, but...
Here's the thing, everyone...
[YUKINO]
No way!
[NAO] If you ask me,
that white HiME
was seriously out to get you.
And I'll tell you, if
that girl comes after me,
I'm definitely fighting back.
[MIDORI]
Nao-- Ah.
[MAI] You know what happened
to Kazuya, don't you?
It was tragic...
We can't let that happen
to anyone again.
[NAO] Don't tell me you've
already forgotten.
Or maybe you're clueless.
But you defeated Alyssa's
Child, remember?
That means you've
already eliminated
someone out there, Mai.
[gasps]
You girls just don't
see it, do you?
Haven't you even stopped
to think what you'd do
if this girl got serious?
Her Child is an incredible
monster that has the ability
to go into outer space.
[gasps]
[MIDORI growls]
Take my advice
and watch your back.
You might wind up getting
back-stabbed by someone
you thought was your friend.
She's right...
That's what I've done...
I'm responsible...
Oh, Mai...
[YUKINO whimpers]
[MIDORI] Don't beat
yourself up over it--
You had no idea
that would happen.
Besides, it seems as
though Alyssa wasn't
a typical HiME anyway.
You did what you
had to that day,
and I'm glad you stood up
to the challenge.
Otherwise, the rest of us
wouldn't even be here.
You had no choice.
[SAKOMIZU]
We know that you despise us,
but we'd like you to
set aside any thoughts of
personal revenge and concentrate
on winning this battle.
Are you saying there's
no way to avoid it?
[SAKOMIZU]
Yes.
Besides needing to
do it for the greater good
of the world, this just
happens to be your destiny.
So I'm supposed to
sacrifice myself, huh?
Well, do you expect me to
be satisfied with that?
[SAKOMIZU]
Hmm. Hardly.
Okay, good.
Then that's the way it'll be.
Well, there's definitely
no disputing
she's the daughter
of Doctor Kuga.
[ISHIGAMI]
Now that's disappointing.
I'm fairly certain
it's against the rules
to leak information to a HiME.
If the people higher up
found out about
some of the things
you've done, you'd be in
much more trouble
than I would.
What're you talking about?
If you don't know
what I'm referring to,
then I suppose there's nothing
to be concerned about.
I suppose there isn't. Well...
Have you been getting
enough sleep? You look awful.
Never mind that.
Just give me some vitamins and
something for my headache.
All right, but the best
thing you could do
is get some sleep.
Is that a love letter or
something from Professor Sasaki?
Not quite.
It's actually an issue of a
journal that's been put out
by some local historians.
Ah... And I need to go
through it all today.
For your thesis, huh?
You sure you wanna
go back to university?
[MIDORI] Huh. Ah, right.
Going back to university
was my goal in the first place.
I completely forgot.
If you want my
personal opinion,
I think teaching's
a perfect fit for you.
Yeah. You know, you may be
right. But that's exactly why
I don't have time for sleep.
Don't you want any water?
[MIDORI]
No, these're pretty tasty.
Natsuki!
[MAI]
It's stupid.
You'd think I would've realized
it when I first heard
about all this from Nagi.
There's no point in
regretting something
that's already happened.
And besides...
you had no choice.
Anyway, my concern right now
is about that HiME
that attacked you.
'Cause if we fight, we'll only
be making the guys
at District 1 happy.
I asked about
this before, but...
Why do you wanna
get back at them?
Tell me: How old
do you think I am?
Huh?! Aren't you
high school age?
[NATSUKI sighs]
Of course! Don't be stupid.
I'm actually 17. I took
a whole year off of school...
...when my mom died
in an accident.
My mother was part
of District 1.
She was one of the
researchers. Thing is...
...when I think about it now,
she must've known about
the destiny of a HiME.
In order to let me escape,
she betrayed the organization.
[NATSUKI]
All of a sudden,
everything I took for
granted was gone for good.
[MAI]
I kinda know what you mean.
Sometimes, I think it'd be
so amazing to just be able
to live a normal
and ordinary life.
You see, the rest of you all
seem to be afraid to fight,
because you don't wanna lose
the people that mean
the most to you.
But I don't have anyone.
That means there's
nothing for me to fear.
If District 1 wants us
to fight each other,
then I'll do whatever
I can to ruin their plans.
Then...
Let's get something straight:
I'm not doing this for you guys.
I'm out to get revenge.
[MAI] Hmph. So, you won't
admit your true feelings.
[NATSUKI]
Look who's talking.
[YUKARIKO screams]
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[MAI]
Hmm!
--Sister!
--Say something!
[YUKARIKO whimpers]
What's the matter, Sister?!
What happened?!
[YUKARIKO]
A Child came out of nowhere...
[BOTH gasp]
Who was it?! Was she
wearing a white kimono?!
[YUKARIKO]
Mm-mm. No, no.
It was Nao...
[BOTH gasp]
[NAGI]
Welcome home.
You sure took your sweet time.
Take the long way or something?
We already had one battle
take place while you were away.
Too bad you weren't
here to see it.
It sure didn't take long
to get everything started.
That stupid idiot!
[MAI]
Hang on, Natsuki!
No way, what does this mean?
[cell phone rings]
I don't know exactly
what you told the girls,
or how you would've
explained it,
but I have serious
doubts that they'll
blindly go along with
everything you said.
They all grew up
in an era of peace.
Hah. Why do you think
I've been working so hard
and making all these
arrangements up until now?
Those girls already have
their own agendas.
Isn't that right?
Even if they don't like it,
they know how to use
the powers they have, and
they've already had the chance
to use them in practice.
Also, each of them has their
very own reason to fight.
They gotta protect their
precious person. Right?
The way things are now,
the girls are basically dolls.
Just light a match
and stand back...
[NAO]
Hmm...
[gunshot]
[NAO]
Huh?!
[gasps]
Nao!
[NAO]
Hah! Ugh, Kuga!
I want answers!
Why did you attack Sister?!
[NAO]
What're you talking about?
You're the one trying
to stir things up.
[NATSUKI] Hmph. If you wanna
play dumb with me, fine.
But I'll promise you one thing;
I'm gonna make sure
that you never pull
anything like that again!
[NAO]
Seems my instincts were right.
I never liked you
from the start.
You're pathetic.
What about the Obsidian Prince?
Has he awakened,
or are we still waiting?
Good question.
Not that there's a need
for you to know if he is.
Or who he is.
What's with the gloomy
look all of a sudden?
Remembering something sad
from your past, maybe?
[NAO grunts, giggles]
[DURAN howls]
[MAI]
Stop it, you two!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Nao!
No! This is terrible!
You get on my nerves, too!
[BOTH gasp]
[MAI gasps]
A... spider...?!
[MIKOTO]
Mai!
Stay back, Mikoto!
[MIKOTO growls, yells]
--Mikoto!
--[YUKINO gasps]
[MAI screams]
Julia!
[NAO yelps]
[gasping]
[NAO groans]
Duran!
Nao, why...?
[MIDORI]
Stop this right now!
What is this all about?!
When'd you get here?
I told you not to fight!
Are you all right, Nao?
[NAO]
You'll pay...
Ugh... I'll make sure of that...
[groans]
[gasps]
I promise you people.
You won't get away with this!
[MIDORI]
Nao!
[NAO]
Julia!
[gasping]
[NAGI]
Finally.
This is where the
real battle begins.
[MASHIRO sighs]
[YUKINO] I thought we
promised not to fight...
To overcome this as a team...
[sobs]
No!
I don't want things
to end this way!
[sobbing]
Yukino...
Yeah. It's going to be okay.
If you cry, you're going
to make me sad, too!
[YUKINO, MIKOTO sobbing]
[AKIRA]
Has it started already?
[MIDORI] In that issue, there's
a story about an accident
that happened on the way
to an archeological dig.
The name of the girl
who died in it
was Mashiro Kazahana.
I thought that we'd
eliminated all traces of it
from the public records.
I suppose we didn't do as
thorough a job as I remember.
[MIDORI]
That's hardly the issue here!
What I wanna know
is who you are,
what your purpose here is,
and how we might be able
to put a stop to this sick
and twisted "festival"!
I'll tell you one thing.
This festival must go on,
and I'm not going to
try and stop it...
Teacher Sugiura.
Teacher, she says.
Huh.
I used to think teaching was...
just a way to pass the time
until I finished up my thesis.
But I didn't count on
some students getting attached
to a half-baked
teacher like myself.
And so I thought,
maybe I'd get more serious
about the profession.
That's why I'll protect them.
No matter what the cost!
[MIDORI] I don't have any
more time to waste here.
I'm gonna get the truth,
even if I have to
force it out of you!
I understand.
And you know my position.
So then, we must duel.
Forgive me, Miss Sugiura.
I should've known.
I'm all right now, Vrus.
[YUKARIKO]
A lie, an illusion...
What happened to me?
[ISHIGAMI]
Are you not going to pray?
[YUKARIKO gasps]
[sighs]
Oh, that's right.
How could I forget?
You have lost the
privilege of serving God.
[YUKARIKO gasps]
--[ISHIGAMI] Sister...
--[YUKARIKO whimpers]
[ISHIGAMI]
You aren't to blame for that.
I am the one that corrupted
you and made you lie!
You can lay all the blame
and guilt at my feet!
Sister, go ahead and hate me!
Please, do this
any place but here.
I will attain the
power of the Star!
[YUKARIKO grunts]
No!
[MIKOTO]
Mai!
I'll protect you
no matter what happens!
[MAI]
'Cause of me?
Or is it because
I make you food?
[MIKOTO]
Food.
[MAI]
What?!
[MIKOTO giggles]
Was it something I said?
[MAI] You've sure
developed an attitude.