[MIKOTO groans]
Nao...
[MIDORI]
Hmm...
[MIDORI growls]
Miss Sugiura,
I need your advice.
If one wants to, can a person
change their destiny?
Of course one can.
You really believe it.
Then I encourage you
to use your resources
and do whatever you can.
For the sake of the HiME.
[GIRL A] Sure are a lot of
earthquakes these days.
[BOY A]
They say Mt. Fuji's gonna erupt.
It's like the end of
the world or something.
[YUICHI]
See ya.
[GROUP]
Bye! See ya later!
[SAYURI]
Tate sure is devoted.
He's headed to the
hospital again, right?
Yeah, he's been going
pretty much every day.
Ah! Hold on, Tokiha!
[MAI]
Huh?
[TATSUHIKO] Dr. Mochizuki's
been asking about Takumi.
[gasps]
Oh, sorry.
Could you tell him that
I'll definitely send
Takumi over there tomorrow?
Guess I was wrong.
Tate and Shiho must be
together after all.
He used to act like
he didn't want anything
to do with her.
[SAYURI]
Yeah.
Shiho's always
stuck by his side though,
even when Tate was going
through that tough phase.
[MAI]
What tough phase?
[TATSUHIKO]
Didn't you know?
Tate was actually...
Hey, Captain...
Tate. I came to hear
your answer in person.
[MIKOTO growling]
[sighs]
Knock it off.
You've got that creepy look in
your eyes again, Mikoto.
[MIKOTO]
Mm? Mmm...
[MAI]
Hmph.
[TATSUHIKO] Tate used
to be an ace fighter
and assistant captain
of the Kendo Club
back when he was
still in junior high.
[SAYURI] But right before
the national tournament,
he injured his left knee
during practice.
It didn't take long to heal,
but in that short time,
he totally lost interest
in everything.
He became really
moody and reckless.
[YAYOI] Right. He was
kinda scary back then.
[SAYURI] Yeah. Until
Student Council put him to work.
[YAYOI] And even though everyone
else went out of their way
to avoid Tate,
Shiho stuck it out with him
and did her best
to cheer him up.
It's only natural
he's been looking after her
like he is, considering
all they've been through.
Tate...
"I'm rootin' for ya"?
It's stupid to say that.
And even stupider to believe it.
That's why. No wonder.
[MIKOTO]
Hmm? Did you say something, Mai?
Nope. Mm-mm. It was nothing.
[MASASHI]
Are you absolutely positive?
[YUICHI]
Think about it.
What if she doesn't get better?
She might never be able to run
again for the rest of her life.
And it's my fault.
That's why...
Ever since I hurt my knee,
I've had all kinds of doubts,
trying to figure out what
my purpose in life is.
But... for now...
...it's only right that
I stick by Shiho's side.
So you're doing this for her
because you're to blame.
Well, that sounds nice
in theory, but hey--!
[gasps]
[MASASHI]
Is that what you really want?!
Will you swear on this kendo
stick, the stick you staked
everything on
back in junior high,
that this is what you want?!
Yes.
[MASASHI]
Hmph.
I'll take your nametag
down in the dojo.
[YUICHI]
I'm very sorry, Captain.
Oh, you're here.
I was wondering where
you'd gotten to.
[YUKINO gasps]
[HARUKA] Do you have any idea
how many times I called you?
Your cell phone's turned off,
in case you hadn't noticed.
Oh. Uh, I-I'm sorry, Haruka.
[cell phone tone jingles]
--[rings]
--[gasps]
Is that more junk mail?
Let's see it.
I'll track down the filthy
culprits and force them to stop!
[YUKINO]
Ah! It's no big deal.
Uh... Forget about it.
All right?
[MIKOTO]
You're going to see Takumi?
[MAI] Yeah, when it
comes right down to it,
he's got not guts.
And that's where I come in--
[AKIRA] Takumi, why aren't
you going to the hospital?
[MAI]
Huh?
[TAKUMI]
My mom died a long time ago.
And ever since then...
...Mai's been there
to look after me.
I didn't think anything of it
when I was a little kid.
What's he saying?
It's different now.
I'm older and we live apart.
I've started to realize
something for the first time.
Her life's been so hard
and I've put so many
demands on her.
It's gonna cost a lot of money
to have an operation overseas.
We had to sell the house,
switch schools 'cause of
the scholarships we got.
Plus, my sister's gotta
work part-time every day.
And we still don't have
enough for the operation.
Besides, the success rate
for this type of surgery
isn't very high. If it failed...
...we'd still have
all our debts to pay.
Anyway, it's got me thinking.
I dunno if living is
worth all that trouble.
[gasps]
Sis always stays positive.
Smiling and stuff.
Sure, it makes me happy
and everything.
It weighs on me, though.
[MAI gasps]
You idiot!
A real man would
want that operation,
want to recover quickly,
and want to pay off those debts
as soon as he could!
You can't just decide
to give up on life!
Your sister wants you to live;
that's why she's working
so hard without
ever complaining!
Even I'm-- [gasps]
[TAKUMI]
Huh...?
[AKIRA sighs]
I mean...
I want you to live.
I really do.
What?
Seriously? [gasps]
Akira...
[AKIRA sighs]
[MAI grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[AKIRA gasps]
That is your destiny as a HiME.
[AKIRA growls]
[BOTH gasp]
--[cat meows]
--[BOTH gasp]
[TAKUMI laughs]
[AKIRA] Ugh! Jerk!
What're you laughing at?!
[TAKUMI]
Sorry! But it's funny!
[train horn blares]
I can't believe Akira's a HiME!
Hmm... Hang on a second.
Akira's a HiME...
...but HiME are girls...
So that must mean...
[TAKUMI]
It weighs on me though.
I dunno if living is
worth all that trouble.
[MIKOTO]
Akira's gotta be a girl!
[gasps]
What a shocker, huh, Mai?
I totally had no idea
that Akira was a girl!
How about you?
Had you figured it out?
That he was a she?
And she was a HiME?
--Shut up!
--And she and Takumi--
Huh?
[MAI whimpers]
Ah--
--[MAI] Don't.
--[gasps]
[MAI sighs] Please.
Leave me alone for a while.
Okay...
[YUKINO groans]
The greatest obstacle...
Now I know how
I'm going to attack.
Let's call it quits
for the day, shall we?
Something's suddenly come up.
[YUKARIKO sighs]
All right.
[SHIZURU]
Huh?
Hmm...
Natsuki...
[NATSUKI groans]
Huh...?
It seems like like you
were having a nice nap.
Ah... I must've just, uh--
Sorry...
[SHIZURU]
There's drool on your mouth.
Just kidding.
Shizuru!
It's probably
none of my business,
but it seems like you've
been working hard lately.
You must be exhausted.
A little... I guess.
[SHIHO] Is there anything
I can do to help?
Asides from letting
you use that?
Thanks, but no.
I'd better get going.
Sorry to interfere
with your work.
Natsuki.
I want you to know that I'm
always thinking about you.
I hope you never forget that,
no matter what.
I appreciate that, Shizuru.
But please...
...I don't want you to get
too close to me, understand?
Later.
[BOTH gasp]
Hi! Kuga!
Uh... Nice timing!
--Uh, I mean--
--Hey, you, too, stupid!
What?
[REITO]
What's the matter, Mikoto?
Huh?
Reito...
Uh... Mai was really mad.
I've never seen her like that.
Hey. What do you
think I should do now?
Well, I don't know the
details or anything,
but I see that Mai must be
very important to you.
If you sincerely want
to offer your help,
you'll just have to do whatever
you can to support her.
Oh, yeah? Do what I can?
Yes. Then she'll definitely
know that you care about her.
--I'm positive.
--[gasps]
All right! I'll do it!
Good luck now.
[MIKOTO laughs] You're totally
like an older brother!
See ya!
[TAKUMI gasps]
[TAKUMI]
Huh...?
Takumi, at the very least,
you should talk to
your sister about it.
[TAKUMI]
Mm-hmm.
[AKIRA]
If I know her... [gasps]
Hey! That's personal!
Sorry--
So... Did you see anything?
[TAKUMI]
Uh... Kinda...
[groans]
Takumi! Are you all right?!
Takumi! Say something!
Takumi!
Takumi... I don't get it...
Sis always stays positive.
Smiling and stuff.
Sure, it makes me happy
and everything.
It weighs on me, though.
C'mon, though... I had to...
The only thing I could do
was be positive...
And smile...
[gasps]
Was I wrong to do that?
Is that why...
Takumi...
[MAI gasps]
If Akira's defeated,
Takumi will...!
[TAKUMI]
It weighs on me, though.
[cell phone ringing]
[YUKINO]
Stop!
[whimpers]
Diana...
[HARUKA]
Listen, Yukino!
[gasps]
[HARUKA] I can't stand things
being done cowardly or halfway.
It's gotta be done right!
You'd better remember that
if you're gonna be my partner.
Haruka...
[MIKOTO laughs]
I'm gonna do whatever
I can to protect Mai!
Ah! Hmm...?
Mai!
[MAI]
Huh...?
[yells]
[YUKINO screams]
Who's that?!
[MIKOTO'S BROTHER] Enemies have
to be defeated, don't they?
[MIKOTO yelling]
Yah-- [screams]
[YUKINO gasps]
[MIKOTO coughs]
Mikoto!
Huh? What is it?
[gasps]
[YUKINO]
I'm sorry...
I really am sorry...
Please! Forgive me...
[MIKOTO]
Huh...?
Somebody said that they
were going to defeat me
and that Haruka would disappear.
But they said if I followed
Mai and defeated her...
[whimpers]
That's why I did it!
[gasps]
That's why...
Yukino...
[MAI]
Go.
[YUKINO]
S-Sorry...
I'm sorry...
So. Why did you do it?
[MIKOTO]
Hmm? Whaddaya mean...?
I told you over and over
not to fight,
but you didn't listen.
Don't you understand?
Why won't you do
what I tell you?
'Cause I...
Because I like you.
That's why...
Like me?
Then how could you turn
around and do something
like that to Yukino?
Didn't you say that about her?
Didn't you say that
you liked her, too?
It weighs on me, though.
You don't know what it's like
looking after someone you love.
Making sacrifices.
And getting hurt!
You don't have a clue
what it's like!
[gasps]
Everything's gotten so
complicated with you around.
Why can't you just
leave me alone?
[gasps]
You mean...
You don't want me around?
I'm a nuisance?
[MIKOTO sobs]
[grunts, wails]
[cell phone rings]
[MAI]
Yes?
Yes...
[gasps]
[MAI] Boy, Takumi.
You had me worried for awhile.
I'm glad you're all right. I--
Huh...?
What is it, Sis...?
Oh! It's nothing...
I can deal with it.
It's not anything you have
to worry about, okay?
Got that?
Listen, Mai. It's okay now.
[gasps]
You've sacrificed so much
for me all these years.
And forced yourself to smile
when you wanted to cry.
So, please-- Don't lie
to yourself anymore, okay?
I-I'm not.
I've been wondering, Sis.
What are your dreams?
What do you want outta life,
most of all?
What do I want?
[TAKUMI]
Mm-hmm. Being sick...
...I didn't know if
I wanted to go on.
But now I'm sure
that I wanna live.
So I'll have the operation.
I'll go to the States.
And I'll go by myself.
[BOTH gasp]
Go alone?
Don't say it.
It's not like I can't
walk or anything.
I wanna do this on my own.
I want you to live for yourself.
Don't live for me, Sis.
You've got your
own life to live.
I guess I should
feel glad about it.
Takumi's finally going
for his operation...
[TAKUMI]
Don't live for me, Sis.
You've got your
own life to live.
Yeah, sure. My life.
It's just... I dunno...
...what that is.
Mai Tokiha:
works part-time after school,
likes to cook for people,
and is Takumi's big sister.
[sobs]
That's it...
That's all I am...
[TAKUMI] What do you
want outta life, most of all?
[MAI sobs]
I don't know...
I have no idea
what I want outta life...
[SHIHO]
It sure is nice to be outside.
I had a great time!
What? All you did was have a
sundae at a family restaurant.
You sure are easy to please.
Everything's
delicious as long as
I'm with you, Brother.
Yes, of course...
It's a pleasure to be of
service to you, Princess.
[SHIHO giggles]
I'm much obliged.
Yeah, yeah, whatever you say.
[giggles]
[gasps]
[MAI sighs]
Huh...?
[YUICHI]
Hmm? Hello?
Hey. Question for you.
Huh? What is it?
[SHIHO] Are you being nice to me
because you feel guilty
about me getting hurt?
Is that what this is all about?
[gasps]
No way.
[SHIHO]
Really? Then kiss me.
[gasps]
Kiss me!
Shiho?
I don't want you to
be all nice to me
if you're just faking it.
I wanna know how
you really feel.
[YUICHI sighs]
Love only me and nobody else.
[MAI groans]
[SHIHO sighs]
I'm so happy...
--[creaking]
--Huh?
[MAI sighs]
[gasps]
What's the matter, Brother?
Forget it. It's... It's nothing.
Oh...
[MAI panting]
[TAKUMI] What do you
want outta life, most of all?
That can't be it...
I must be wrong...
It can't be... No way...
Because...
...it's too cruel...
Now, of all times...
[MAI]
Gone.
Everything's gone...
[TAKUMI]
You weigh on me, Sis.
[MAI]
What?! Have I gained weight?!
[TAKUMI] What do you want,
more than anything?
[MAI]
I'll take cash!
[NATSUKI]
I understand how you feel,
but that I didn't need to hear.
[MAI howls like a dog]