You didn't notice it before?
Offically, my actual full
name is Aria Holmes Kanzaki!
As in Sherlock Holmes the 4th!
Sherlock Holmes? You sure?
Yep.
The strangest
Holmes ever. It can't be.
Kin-Kin!
How come you haven't
replied to my emails?!
I heard that you're living
with a girl, is that true?
Who's that?
I'm coming in, okay, Kin?
I knew you'd be here!
Aria H. Kanzaki!
Shirayuki, no! Wait!
You're taking this all wrong!
It's not your fault, Kin.
You've just been tricked
and besides that you're
just a man. You thieving cat!
You've soiled my Kin-Kin
and now must pay for
that sin with your life!
Hey, what's her deal?!
Calm down, Shirayuki!
I haven't been soiled at all!
Aria H. Kanzaki!
It's time for you
to meet your maker!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?!
Feeeel my wraaath!
Holy crap?!
She knows sword catching?!
Why are you doing this?!
Shut up, you thieving cat!
Get off!
I'm gonna make you disappear!
What are you talking about!
Listen to me, you nutcase!
Stop!
Please both of you knock it off!
I tried to be rational!
It's time to pump some holes!
Hey!
You're a paranormal?!
Yep.
She's a paranormal Butei.
Simply put, she's got
supernatural powers.
Hotogi Shrine is located
in a suburb of Aomori.
Shirayuki hails from
a long line of maidens
who've served the Hotogi Shrine.
And when it comes
to Shrine Maidens,
you can be sure of two things:
They're always armed,
and they wield a supernatural
power called kidojutsu.
I've always been
skeptical of people
with supernatural powers,
but they do exist.
The fact Riko
turned out to be one
is still pretty
fresh in my mind.
Butei High even has a
wing for paranormal Butei,
the Department of Supernatural
Selective Research,
otherwise known as SSR.
Shirayuki's apparently
at the top of her class.
And when you match
Shirayuki's powers
with an S-rank Butei like Aria.
Well, it tends to
turn out like this.
You are stubborn.
You know that.
Yeah.
You're one to talk.
So, why don't you girls
give talking a try now.
Kin-Kinnnn!
I'm sorry!
You wouldn't have
chosen a girl like her
if I'd had more courage!
You're not exactly lacking in
bravery, you maniac!
It's bad enough you
and Kin-Kin are in love!
Don't rub it in!
What? There's no love here!
How stupid are you?
I don't give a flaming
crap about being in love!
I've never been in love
and I'm never going to be!
Wait, then you and Kin-Kin...
He's not your boyfriend?
No, of course not!
Then what is he?!
He's my... my uh... my slave!
Your--he's your slave?!
You, you mean you're already
doing kinky stuff like that?!
I mean, sure, I admit it.
I've often fantasized about
being Kin-Kin's
slave before. But!
What?!
Dammit Kinji! Explain this!
Explain what?
Look. We're working
together as Butei...
I'm Aria's temporary partner.
Huh? Really?
Do you really have that
much trouble believing me?
No. I-I believe you.
Sooo...
If that's all it is,
then you two aren't fooling
around or anything, right?
Fooling around?
Y'know.
You haven't kissed, right?
Then, you did?
Calm down, Shirayuki,
it's not like you think!
Yes, it's true we kissed,
but it meant nothing!
And it's fine!
There's nothing to worry about,
because I didn't
get pregnant from it!
Huhhhhh?!
Well, my father told
me kissing someone
is what causes
you to get pregnant!
Of course not!
Shirayuki.
Hey! So listen, about yesterday.
Hey. Hold on.
I take it she's
still pissed off.
Class, the "Adosiade,"
the annual Butei
competition, is coming up.
Since the event is being
held at our school this year,
we'll have Butei students
from around the world
coming to compete,
plus their families--
Hey Kinji were you planning
on participating in any of
the events for this thing?
Well that's a
dumb question, man.
They don't want an
E-rank Butei participating.
I thought so.
Do you wanna work
reception with me then?
'cause Shiranui
backed out on me.
I'm in the shooting competition.
Aria dropped out.
So they're forcing
me to take her place.
Huhhh. Well, I don't
mind working at reception.
But why did you
drop out of this, Aria?
Jeez, what the hell
are you reading about
this early in the morning?
So that's what men really want.
Huh?
You're a bunch of perverts!
You should've dodged that,
you worthless Butei.
Okay. I wish I could have.
Well.
I guess we should
work on it then.
Huh?
Helloooo? Aria! Heyyyyy!
Guess who!
You're the one who asked
me to meet you here.
You could have--
You should never allow
anyone to sneak up on you.
Um.
Why are you dressed like that?
Oh, I thought I told you.
I signed up to cheerlead
at the Adosiade.
So I've gotta practice.
Cheer. You mean Arkata?
If you're asking me to help
you practice, I have to decline.
You've got a split personality.
Huh?
I looked into it right
after the hijackings.
You've clearly got
dissociative identity disorder.
It's probably a coping mechanism
from some childhood trauma.
And that personality takes
over when you're in combat.
You're not the sleuth
your great-grandfather was.
Hysteria mode isn't
a psychogenically--
acqquired condition.
It's a neurogenic
inherited condition.
Hey! Listen to me!
If you need that
kind of combat stress
to activate your other side,
then I will be
happy to provide it!
Ow!
We're gonna tame
those wild mood swings!
Then you can turn your
abilities on and off at will.
That freakin' hurt, you nut.
I've decided the
most effective way
to properly tame you is to start
by teaching you how to block
attacks using the sword
catching technique.
You can't be serious!
Now, the best way to learn
this is through muscle memory,
so I want you to practice
catching an imaginary
one, understand?
500 reps.
So it's imaginary training?
We can still use this
if you really want to.
The other way is fine.
Let's get started.
There you go.
I like it when you're good
and obedient, Kinji.
Now you keep
it up and work hard.
You should be showing
better results by now.
It's only been a few hours!
We'll continue with
your taming tomorrow.
What? Who says
you get to decide--
You're my partner,
so it's my responsibility
to make sure you're properly
tamed and ready for anything.
Attention Shirayuki Hotogi.
Shirayuki?
But they never call
her to the office.
Please report to
your Master's office.
Your homeroom teacher--
Kinji.
Yeah.
This is our chance.
Huh?
It's the perfect time to
discover her weak points.
Huh?
Shirayuki almost
killed me today.
And? You almost killed
each other last night.
But it was for real today.
Somebody tried to set a trap for
me in the girls' locker room.
A trap?
She must've
anticipated me having
to step further into my locker.
So she strung up piano
wire to lop off my head.
Piano wire?
That's way too brutal for her.
I know she's mad at you,
but Shirayuki wouldn't--
Or, uh, she might.
No, there's no way.
On top of that, I feel
like I'm being followed.
And someone dumped water
on me from the bridge.
And I found a letter
with "thieving cat" written
on it in my shoe locker.
Know anyone else who's
called me that lately?
Shirayuki.
What's goin' on with
these test scores?
It's just not like you
to score under a 90.
I- I know, I'm really
sorry, Ms. Tsuzuri.
Well, It's not the
scores I'm worried about.
They just struck
me as a red flag.
I've gotta ask.
He hasn't tried to make
contact with you has he?
"He" who?
Look I've already
read the report
that Lezzad filed ranking
you as a likely target.
And the same prediction
came in from SSR, as well.
I'm talking about Durandal.
Oh.
She said Durandal?
But everyone says that
Durandal's not even real,
that he's just a myth.
Yeah, but what do you plan
on doing if he's not a myth?
Everything I've
heard about him says
that he only abducts
major paranormal Butei.
I don't see why he'd
wanna come after me.
C'mon, Shirayuki, you're
one of our best students.
I think you should play it safe
and at least keep a
bodyguard around, you know?
But, uh.... If I've got
a bodyguard with me,
well, when will I take
care of Kin-Kin?
The school is gonna be crawling
with outsiders
once Adosiade begins.
Why not hire one
until it's over?
It should help you relax
some, at least. Right?
Yeah, but still, I--
What the--
Look no further!
I'll be your bodyguard!
Aria! What're you
doing up there?!
I'll work around the
clock as your bodyguard
and I'll do it for free!
Huh?
Wow. You're an S-rank Butei
and you'll guard her for free?
Well that's great news.
No! No way.
The thought of spending
that much time around her?
It makes me sick!
If you don't hire me,
I'll just have to shoot you.
Aria! Butei
Article 9! Article 9!
Kin-Kin!
Ohhh, I get it.
I've always wondered what this
Kin-Kin of yours looked like.
What do you wanna do, Shirayuki?
Fine, I'll agree to hire
Aria as my bodyguard. But!
Huh?
The only way I'll do it is
if Kin-Kin guards me too!
And I'm talking
about around the clock!
And! This means...
I'm going to move into
Kin-Kin's dorm room!
Why me? What did I do?
G-good day. My name's Shirayuki.
And I'll be living
here with you.
Um.
Let me know if I can help you.
I'll do anything.
Why are you acting like
we don't know each other?
I'm a little nervous
about the whole thing.
Living with you and all.
Well, I should do some
cleaning before I make dinner.
Seriously.
What happened to the
peaceful life I used to live?
Hey.
What exactly are you doing?
Oh.
I'm adding a
new security system.
That's the first step
to guarding someone.
Why don't you just drop the act?
You're just trying to figure out
all of Shirayuki's weaknesses.
Nope. I've got a new goal.
I'm gonna catch Durandal.
What?
He's on my list.
He's one of the many
people who framed my mom.
If I can capture him,
it'll knock another life
term off her sentence.
If it works out like
I'm hoping it will,
we might be able
to get her a retrial.
She gets even more intense
than usual when it
comes to her mother.
I thought it was
common knowledge
that Durandal is
just an urban legend.
It's not like anyone
has seen him.
That's a load of crap!
I guarantee you that he's real!
Oh, yeah?
I take it you've seen this
guy with your own eyes then?
Uh. Well. Not really.
Thought so.
But that doesn't
mean he's not real!
He framed my mom,
so he's gotta be!
How do you know it
wasn't someone else?
I just know it
was him, so shut up!
Whatever.
Why don't you
make yourself useful!
Go check the dresser in
the hallway for booby-traps!
You're kidding now, right?
I'll install the system
in the bedroom.
Go on! Move it, move it!
Shirayuki must've brought
this dresser with her.
I doubt there's
anything dangerous--
Okay. That's a different
kind of dangerous.
No!
What's the matter, Shirayuki?
Did you break something?
Oh, Kin-Kin. I'm so sorry!
Your extra strong cold medicine.
I remember you telling
me that's the only stuff
that works for you
when you get sick.
It's really
expensive too isn't it?
No. You just have
to go out to Ameyoko
to find a store that carries it.
It's really not a big deal,
don't worry about it.
You haven't changed
at all, Kin-Kin.
Just as kind as
you've always been.
Come on. Who would
get mad over this?
You just go ahead with
whatever you were doing
and I'll clean this up, okay?
Sure.
Well! Bon appetite!
Whoaaa.
I tried hard to think of
everything you might like.
Wow.
Well, thanks a lot,
it all looks delicious.
Do you want a bath after dinner?
I could draw the water.
Or, y'know, I could--
Huh?
Alright. You tryin'
to starve me now
since the piano
wire didn't work?
Are you serious?!
If you're going to start
complaining, I'll fire you!
Alright, that's it!
Fine, you wanna go?!
I'll get to use the trump card
I was hiding the other day!
Well I was hiding
two trump cards!
So what're ya
gonna do about that?!
I'm gonna win because
I was hiding three!
Well I've got four!
Five!
Thousands!
Hundreds of thousands!
At any rate, this is how Aria
and I started
protecting Shirayuki.
We all walk to school together.
Aria handles the
duty during class.
Open up, Kin-Kin. Say ahhhh!
And then I join
them during lunch.
It was my shift after school,
but I felt more
like a therapist.
What? You guys got
in another fight?
She's ordering me around!
She told me that the lunch
break is dedicated to taming
and that I need to
quit interfering with it.
Yeah, it's training, not taming.
She's gotta get on your nerves.
She pokes her nose
into everything you do.
And she tries to act like she's
a part of our little world.
I didn't even know
we had a little world.
On one level, I think
she's kind of amazing.
Well, on a certain level.
I'm afraid she'll
steal you from me.
She's so much more
charming than I am.
Like I told you.
She and I only work together.
Besides, I've known
you way longer than her.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's funny to think.
I can't believe
it's been so long.
But you really are one
of my oldest friends.
It was against the rules for me
to leave the Hotogi Shrine,
but I remember how
you convinced me
to sneak out for the first time.
You took me
to see the fireworks.
And they were so beautiful.
Yeah, but you got in
serious trouble for doing it.
It was worth it, though.
And you kept coming
back to visit me.
So I was happy.
We were so young.
But even then, I think
I must've sympathized with her.
♪ The crane and the
turtle slipped and fell. ♪
♪ Who's behind you,
behind you now. ♪
♪ Caged bird,
caged bird, all locked up. ♪
It's probably because
I heard what all
the adults called Shirayuki
and her sisters whenever
they weren't around.
They called them
the caged birds.
♪ Caged bird, caged bird,
poor caged bird. ♪
What?
Um, hello?
Shirayuki!
It's me!
Kin-Kin?!
Kin-Kin, what's wrong?!
Hey!
What're you-?!
Why did you call my
phone and say "help me"?
What?
Why would I call you
from the bathroom?
I don't know, but I know it
was your voice on the phone.
I, uh... Kin-Kin,
you--you're not wearing.
Huh? So?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I admit I was just now
fantasizing about seeing
you naked in the bathtub!
But I wasn't trying to!
It was just having a fantasy!
I'm such a bad girl!
Hey, don't worry 'bout it.
But. What's up
with this phone call?
It's only fair.
Huh?
It's only fair if you
see me get undressed.
That way we'll be
even with each other.
Whoa, hold on!
Stop it! We're even!
No!
We're not even until you
see me with my shirt off!
Hey! I don't want things
to be even, alright?
Stop, Kin-Kin!
Just let me do it!
Please cut it out!
Hey, I'm back.
Why, you. You dirty pervert!
Worthless degenerate!
You're an animalllll!
No, stop it!
Don't shoot me, Ariaaaaaa!
It's time for the
festival of holes, you scum!
Quit acting like a poor sport.
What?!
You're calling me that?!
You're just mad because you
found Kinji embracing me.
Are you kidding?
I don't care about that!
Kinji. I heard
you've got a cold.
I wonder whose fault that is.
Well don't worry.
I found some old
natural folk remedies...
Try to hold your breath
for as long as you can.
Then drink a glass of
water while upside down.
Press the accupoint behind
your ear and think about tofu.
Boil some water with persimmon.
Boo! Well, did it work?
Aria.
That's how you cure hiccups.
Next time on
Aria the Scarlet Ammo!
"Caged Bird."
Now watch out or
I'll pump some holes in you!