Would you like another
cup of tea, Miss?
Yes, thank you.
It's so quiet today.
And look, everything
here is so beautiful.
It is, and don't the
flowers look happy.
You're silly, Aria.
And, cut!
That was a good one, Aria.
It only took a week of training
and now you're the perfect maid.
S-ranked Butei
are quick studies.
Oh shut up. You know why.
I'd never be doing this if
it weren't, for my mom's trial.
Now, now. Don't
be such a sour puss.
Hey, Kinji.
Don't you think Aria was
cute in that last scene.
Uhh, I don't think there's
anything right to say here.
Oh yeah? Spit it out, Kinji.
Well. How should I know? Really.
It's easy. Just tell me whether
you thought it was good or bad.
Answer quick, or I'll
pump you full of holes.
You know that's nuts, right?
This is all working out so well.
I can't wait for the real thing.
Riko's late.
Well, I really
doubt she'd miss this
since the whole operation
is completely for her benefit.
I guess you're right.
I can't believe
we're going to stay
at Vlad the Bad's house for two
whole weeks; that's a long time.
When I got the approval
for this operation
they didn't even review
the docs I submitted.
They just said yes;
at least you'll be getting
some of the credits
you need for your class.
I wish I could get class
credit without risking my life.
Kinji! Aria!
Good morning.
Kana?
Thanks for waiting.
Don't tell me that's
Riko under there.
Vlad knows what I look like
so it's probably best
if I go in disguise.
Fine, but what made
you pick that face to use?
I thought you'd
feel more comfortable
if you had a
familiar face around,
and who better than Kana?
I'm not going waste time
letting your stupid
joke upset me. Let's go.
Wait, Kinji.
What the heck am I missing?
What's so special about
that face she's using?
And who is this Kana person?
Stupid Kinji.
She was Vlad's
prisoner as a kid.
So I guess I can
understand the disguise.
As you know.
Riko lost her parents
when she was a kid and,
well, she was then taken in
by someone claiming
to be her relative.
She was locked up.
Confined for years by herself.
Here Aria, try a bite.
Huh?
For someone with such
a terrible childhood,
she sure doesn't act like it.
Would you take a
look at this place?!
Are you sure we're
in Yokahama city?
Yes?
Good afternoon.
I'm with the temp
agency and I was told
to bring a couple of
housekeepers over here for you.
Ahh.
I've been expecting you.
Yeah, so this is a
little unexpected, huh?
Yeah.
Our housekeeper is
only going to be gone
for two weeks so I told the
agency it didn't really matter
who they sent to me.
I didn't think
they'd send me some
of my own students, though.
Yes, that's quite a coincidence;
out of all the clients,
they end up
with one of their
teachers from school.
At least now we don't
have to introduce ourselves.
And with an S-ranked
Butei running the house,
I can get to my research in the
basement without any worries.
Yes and when the owner of
the house gets back in town,
you'll have a funny
story to tell him
about the temp maids we brought.
Yes, but I think he's overseas
for business at the moment.
He's not supposed to be
back for quite some time.
It sounds like he's busy person.
Actually, I don't know.
We've never met in person,
so I can't tell you much except
that he lets me use
his research facility.
So they just chat
online or something?
Well, I guess I better
get out of your way
and let you all get to work.
I expect you to do your best,
even though he is your teacher.
It kind of surprised
me to find out
that you lived in a
mansion, Mr. Sayonaki.
Yeah, I only wish it were mine.
The owner started out
by letting me use his
basement research facility.
And I was practically
living here anyway
so he ended up making
me the caretaker.
This room will be yours Aria.
And you're across
the hall, Kinji.
This isn't school
so you're on your own.
There should be a uniform
that fits laid out
for you in your room.
Make sure to read over the
note our housekeeper left you.
Oh yeah.
I'll be pretty swamped
with my research
so I probably won't
see you guys very much.
Just remember to let me
know when it's time to eat.
Okay, we put in some
time like normal help
until they start to
trust us around here.
Hey, Aria. It's time
for kitchen duty.
Aria, what are
you doing in there?
Well, I guess it's okay to dress
like a working girl
every once in a while.
I knocked on the door
and you didn't answer
so I let myself in.
What would you like me to
do for you, Master Kinji?
I'm good. Really.
I wouldn't mind not
getting killed if that's okay.
Try peeping on me again and
I'll pump you full of holes.
I don't really think
"the help" is supposed
to be playing pool in
the house where they work.
Don't worry.
He told me we could
play as much as we want
as long as we didn't
have any work to do.
Well. I guess that's cool.
Of course, we should get
to relax every once
in a while too, right?
Looks like you dropped this.
What?
You're a terrible artist.
I didn't draw that thing!
So, unless we attack these
eye patterns at the same time.
We can't defeat Vlad?
That's right.
And that's not all.
Apparently, we have to find
his hidden fourth eye, also.
Well, that's assuming we even
ever get the opportunity
to fight him at some point.
Right.
Uhh, hey.
I almost forgot.
She's scared to death
of thunder and lightning.
Hey, you're okay.
I'm right here with you.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, this is going to be our
regular conference call time
so I can stay on top of any
developments from you guys.
Yay!
You're a little
hyper, aren't you?
Uh-oh. I can't believe a
whole week has passed already.
How's everything going?
We'll start with Aria's report.
Do you have anything
you want to tell us?
Your rosary is being stored
in the safe in the basement,
just like you said.
I saw it today
when I went down
there with Mr. Sayonaki.
It's a small,
blue rosary with a cross
that looks like a
pierced earring, right?
It was on a shelf.
Yeah, that's the one, Aria!
But Mr. Sayonaki's
research lab is down there,
so he almost never leaves.
It'd be a real pain
to break in there.
That's exactly why
I sent you in as a team.
This job is too
tough to do alone.
I say we go with a
classic decoy diversion.
A decoy operation, huh?
Correct.
One of you will lure him out
and while he's gone the other
gets to sneak in to the safe.
It's called the Odd-Man play
and the set-up is
pretty straight forward.
Whoever can get closer to
the mark will take the lead
and develop the first...
Here's your grilled
Kobe Black on skewers.
On the side, we have
Yuzu chili peppers.
Wow, it looks really
delicious, again.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
I don't get it.
It can't be healthy to only
eat extra rare meat everyday.
It's very unbalanced.
Hasn't he ever heard
of fruits or vegetables?
Grozav.
That's Romanian, right?
That's right.
I'm surprised
that you knew that.
So you're pretty good
with foreign languages,
like everything else.
I'm okay.
I worked as a Butei in Europe.
Can I ask why you
speak Romanian, sir?
The owner of this
house is Romanian,
so I learned in order
to communicate with him,
otherwise we'd never talk.
I'd be curious to know how
many languages you speak, Aria.
I think seventeen or so.
Isn't that funny?
That's similar to the breed
of roses we have on the estate.
It's one of my hybrids
I'm most proud of.
I used seventeen
different varietals
to make it nearly perfect.
I haven't been able to think
of a name for it till now.
Aria, that'll fit
it just perfectly.
I might never have figured out
what to call it if you
hadn't caught my Romanian.
Here's to you, Aria.
Okay, I really can't
believe we're in Yokohama.
Kinji, Riko.
This is bad,
I only got a quick look
while I was cleaning,
but it looks like our little
safe in the basement
is very heavily guarded.
The front is covered by state
of the art infrared sensors
and the floor is
pressure reactive.
Seriously?
Don't worry about
everything so much...
I've got a contingency
worked out for that...
I don't care how
heavily guarded it is.
That's my rosary
and nothing is going
to keep us from getting it back.
This'll be a piece of cake.
Okay, so which of you
thinks they've gotten
the best look inside his
brain and can lure him out?
I dunno.
Oh yeah, right Aria.
I think you might
have a little connection
since he named his
prize rose after you.
What do you mean?
It's not like we bonded.
He just named his
stupid flower after me.
I'd watch out if I were you.
He's the type of
guy who probably has
a string of girls
following him everywhere.
He doesn't really look
like that type of guy to me.
Something about
him is suspicious.
Aww.
Are you two having
a lovers' quarrel?
No we're not!
Anyway, I guess that decides it.
Aria will keep Sayonaki away
while Kinji hits
the basement safe.
Do you think you can do it?
I'll do my best.
He's pretty obsessed
with his research.
I don't know if I could keep him
away for more than ten minutes.
If you could stretch
it to fifteen minutes
that'd be plenty of time.
Maybe you could try flirting
with him or something.
I'd say flash your chest but
I'm not sure he'd even notice.
Hey, that's rude.
I'm gonna fill
you full of holes.
Oh, I'm so scared.
The mission is set for the
afternoon of your last day.
Kinji.
Yeah, what?
So what if I liked having
a rose named after me?
You know, you didn't have
to be such a jerk about it.
I wasn't being a jerk to you.
Yes, you were.
Why would you care
what I think anyway?
So, who's Kana?
You started acting so weird
when you thought you
saw her, not like yourself.
I don't know.
It kind seemed like,
she might have been an
old girlfriend or something.
Listen.
I'm not going to say this again,
that's none of your business.
You're right.
I shouldn't have been
so pushy. I understand.
I mean everyone has something
they don't wanna talk about.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Yeah.
Well I might've been a little
on the harsh side just then.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I should go. Have a good night
Yeah, good night.
I'm honored.
What a considerate
idea to invite me
to see the rose with you.
It's very sweet.
You honored me.
Thank you.
It's my last day working here,
so I wanted to end
it with a good memory.
That's pretty smart.
I can't leave my
research for too long
so I can only stay for a bit.
I'm just glad you said yes.
Can you hear me?
Com check.
The mole is headed
into the field now.
I read you loud and clear, plus,
did you know how much sexier
your voice sounds over the com?
I can't believe I dug all this.
Pretty good for two weeks.
They're beautiful, aren't they?
We keep only the perfect ones
and get rid of any that show
the imperfections we don't want.
After several generations
of work you end up
with superior blooms,
like these here.
It's worth it.
They're simply exquisite.
This is Kinji.
The mole is now a bat
Okay, that gives
you seven minutes.
Got it.
Are you receiving picture, Riko?
Yeah, perfect.
We can get started
on the rail operation.
First, connect
A1 to the Z1 wire.
Then connect B11, F23, A7,
and B15 twice in a row.
Then, C19, C15, A13, E12.
Roses are like
humans in that way.
A superior person is naturally
born into a superior family.
Wouldn't you agree Aria?
Uhh, of course.
Kinji, hurry up.
If I go too fast,
the rosary will start
to swing and touch
the infrared rays.
This has been a pleasant
break from the routine.
I'm sorry but I'm afraid I have
to get back to my research now.
But we just got here.
Aria, you have to stall
him for a little bit longer
or Kinji is going to get caught.
Got it.
Hold on. Mr. Sayonaki.
Yes?
I was just thinking, uhh,
isn't it a beautiful day today?
Actually it's rather cloudy.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
She's not going
to be able to do it.
What? Don't tell me
my line got cut off.
Aria, there's no other way.
You're going to have
to pull a honey trap.
He likes girls.
We have to use it.
Okay, I'll try.
I guess their
lines are still live.
I better hurry up.
Just throw yourself
into his arms
and see if he'll
start touching you.
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
She's really going to do it?
Before I do. Kinji?
Can you hear me?
What the hell?
You shouldn't be talking to me.
Sayonaki's distracted.
He's not paying
attention right now.
I have to tell you,
all this time.
You're the one I liked.
Do we really need to
be talking about this now?
Whatever he does to me today.
I'll let you do the
same to me later.
Whatever you want, I promise.
You what?
You can have me all
night long if you want.
We can skip school together.
I'll let you do
whatever you like.
Forever.
Now I get it,
this is Riko, right?
Poor stupid Kinji.
Since you figured it out,
you must be in Hysteria Mode.
Yeah.
The interference from before
was you cutting the line
between Aria and me;
everything that happened
after that was just
more of your play acting.
You know, it's
really insulting that you
go into Hysteria Mode
so easily for Aria.
Bad girl.
You're gonna get a
spanking from me later.
Promises, promises.
I should be bad more often.
Sayonaki is coming your way.
You're out of time.
Can you make it?
Don't worry.
These past two weeks
you've done exceptional work.
You've both been very helpful.
Thank you.
Our pleasure.
We'll look forward to
seeing you at school.
Indeed.
By the way, try to take your
tests a little more seriously.
Okay, Kinji?
Yeah, sure.
This is the one
you wanted, right?
That is it!
It's my mother's rosary.
Riko.
I hate to interrupt
your celebration
to remind you of
the promise you made.
Oh silly you really don't
understand me at all, do you?
Well, Kinji?
Well, what?
Why don't you open your present?
It's a thank you gift but
you have to unwrap me first.
You're a bad girl, ya'know that?
What is wrong with you?
What do you think
you're doing, Riko?
I'm so sorry, you two.
But like Kinji said, I'm
really just a bad girl at heart.
As soon as I got this back
there was no more reason
to pretend since I now have all
the cards stacked in my favor.
Nothing is wasted
in my little scheme.
I use you two to
get my rosary back,
and then once you hand
it over, I destroy you both.
Give it your best shot Kinji.
After all, I gave you
something special.
Don't you think it's
ironic you're the first boy
I've ever kissed,
cause I'll be your last!
Hey, you look familiar,
what was your name again?
Boy, you sure know
how to hurt a guy.
It just slipped my memory!
It's on the tip of my tongue!
Yuji! No, Saito!
No, uhm... Uhm...
It's Ryuji.
That's right! Ryuji! Ryuji!
I knew it. I told you I knew it.
I was just playing
the whole time, right?
Aria, starting today,
I'm no longer your partner.
Next time, Aria the
Scarlet Ammo episode 12!
"Vlad."
I'll give you
some serious holes!