On the evening of December 24th.
A fire broke out aboard
the cruise ship, Embellir,
causing it to sink while
off the coast of Uraga,
Kanagawa Prefecture.
According to the passenger list,
there was a Butei on board.
Apparently an operative
of the Butei Agency.
A witness claims
the fire erupted
within close
proximity of this Butei.
Butei are specifically trained
to prevent these kinds of
accidents aren't they?
I thought that was
the point of Butei.
Was it your older
brother's incompetence
that risked the lives
of hundreds of people?
Shouldn't you
apologize on his behalf?
Just a dream.
Damn it.
Screw being a Butei.
Screw this life!
My older brother got caught
in the middle of a
cruise ship accident.
He managed to lead
everyone on board to safety,
but he wasn't able
to save himself.
People still blamed
him despite his heroics.
That pretty much
sums up being a Butei.
Give your life to save someone
and they'll just wipe
their feet on your corpse.
And that's why--
Kin Kin.
Are you enjoying
your Sunday so far?
I just heard some news about
the Butei Killer copycat--
I can't be a Butei anymore.
Your haircut's really cute.
Yeah!
Thank you.
Aria.
She got her bangs cut.
She's all dressed up.
I wonder if she's got a date.
I don't even know why
the hell I'm doing this.
It's not like I have
something to say to her.
A police station?
You call that tailing?
I can still see
your big bushy tail.
Aw, jeez.
Ya could've said something if
you knew I was following you.
I was deciding whether or not
to let you know
where I was going.
Especially since the
Butei Killer targeted you.
Huh?
Oh well, you've followed me this
far, you might as well join me.
Mom!
Well. Who's this, Aria?
I didn't know you
had a boyfriend.
What, no way, c'mon, Mom!
He goes to high school with me.
His name's Kinji.
And he's definitely
not like that!
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kanae. Kanae Kanzaki.
You must be a good friend
to come down here with her.
Umm, I guess.
Visiting time's too
short for small talk
so I'll get right to the point.
The Butei Killer tried to
go after Kinji the other day.
I knew it wouldn't be very
long before he resurfaced.
And it won't take me
long to catch him, either.
Try to hang on!
If I can prove definitively
that you're not the Butei Killer
that will get one of your
life sentences overturned.
Then I can start working
on getting the other
seven thrown out.
I can disprove those before your
case goes to the Supreme Court.
That's sweet of you to try, but
it's more important that
you find a partner first, Aria.
Well, I know, but.,,
You need to have someone
who truly understands you
by your side before
you confront an enemy.
But I know I can
do it by myself.
You can't, Aria.
You need a partner to
harness your inherent talent.
It's the only way.
Your great grandfather's
legacy would be nothing
without his partner, right?
Yeah, I know.
People treat me
like I'm defective
because I haven't
found a partner by now.
But there's not enough time!
You need to focus
on living your life.
You're bound to slip
and fall if you rush.
Kanzaki, time's up.
Just hang on, mom!
I promise I'll capture
every single person
who framed you before
you make it to trial!
No, Aria!
You just aren't
ready to confront I-U!
I-U?
Now! Time's up!
No, Mom!
Let go!
Don't you dare hurt my mom!
Aria, promise me you'll
find a partner first!
Please!
That scar on your
forehead tells me
that you can't handle
this by yourself!
I love you.
Stop it!
Come back!
Mom!
Don't follow me.
Aria.
Just leave me alone, Kinji!
I can't leave you
when you're cry--
I am not crying!
I'm not crying.
I'm not.
Many are the
mountains in Yamato.
The next day,
Aria didn't come to school.
So that's when her mom
got taken into custody.
But Aria's convinced
that she was framed,
and she's hell-bent
on proving it.
Listen up, I've decided that
you should become my slave.
You need to find a partner.
She didn't mean slave.
She was just too
proud to say partner.
But--
You're not the one
I was looking for.
I guess I was wrong about you.
But I've gotta quit.
There you are, Kinji.
Oh, what's up, Shiranui?
What're you doing down here?
I've been looking
all over for you.
I thought you might be
interested in the news
that I heard earlier.
It's about Aria.
Apparently she's decided
to go back to London.
What?
She's taking a charter plane
from Haneda at
seven o'clock tonight.
Then she's gone.
I thought you'd rather
hear about it from me.
I can't believe
that Aria's leaving.
But I'm sure it's for the best.
It's not like I could
really be her partner.
Ah! Kinjiiii!
I'm so happy that
you could make it!
Come on in, sit down!
What's with the private room?
You don't need
to worry about that.
Just sit back and
let me take the wheel.
What are you talking about?
And what's so important
that you have to make
such a deal about it?
Relax Kinji.
Now, open up.
Get that outta my face.
The Butei Killer.
If you simply open your mouth,
then I'll tell you
all sorts of fun things.
Say "Aahh."
Now, let's see.
Where would you
like to begin Kinji?
So soft!
Right here?
Or maybe.
You'd rather start right here?
That wasn't the deal!
I know, I know.
You only care about my intel.
Hey, what're you--?
Cut that out!
Not every crime is
accurately reported.
Huh?
Just because they
were filed as accidents
doesn't mean the Butei Killer
didn't actually commit them.
Wait.
You're saying the hijacking
cases weren't the only ones?
This file does make me wonder.
I found it at
the police station.
This is your older
brother's name, right?
Could this've been
a boat hijacking?
The Butei Killer
killed my brother?
But why?
Lovely.
Just lovely, Kinji.
You have such haunting eyes.
I get chills looking at them.
Je t'aime a croquer.
What?
Just relax!
No, Riko.
Stop it!
You couldn't possibly
be any more clueless
to the way girls work.
You really don't get it.
It's too late to stop this.
Dammit! No!
She's sending me
into hysteria mode!
You and I are the only ones
who'll ever know what
happens in this room.
Shirayuki's at training camp
and Aria's gotta be
on that plane by now.
So what do you think, Kinji?
Sorry, doll, but that's
all you get for today.
What?
Kinji?
What are--?
Tomorrow's a
school day, young lady.
It's getting close
to your bedtime.
If I'm adding
everything up correctly--
Then Aria's in danger.
I've come down
from hysteria mode.
Although.
Hey! Hold it!
I'm a Butei!
I never would've
connected all the pieces
if I hadn't gone
into hysteria mode.
The previous killings,
my brother's case,
all hijackings,
and now this airplane.
There's no doubt that
the Butei Killer is onboard.
What? Sir!
Butei!
Cancel the takeoff!
But we can't!
There's not enough
time to explain!
But this plane cannot
leave the runway!
Uh. Yes sir!
Just in time.
Talk about a decked out plane.
Guess you can't expect
the rich to fly coach.
We're moving!
Eh, 'scuse me.
It wasn't possible.
The captain said it would be a
violation to stop at this point.
That leaves plan B.
And she honestly knows you?
I know you're a Butei.
But I'm not supposed to do this
without the
passenger's permission.
Kinji!
Hey, what's up, Aria?
Well.
Please take a seat
and fasten your seatbelt.
The plane's about to take off.
Hey! What's the deal?!
I doubt you'll believe this,
but the plane is--
It's rude of you to barge
in here without an invitation!
That sure is funny
coming out of your mouth.
C'mon, the plane's taking off.
We need to sit down.
What're you doing here, Kinji?
What makes the sky look blue?
How are birds able to fly?
Shut up!
You want new holes in you?
Article 2 of the Charter.
Honor your client's
contract no matter what.
Huh?
I made you a promise.
I promised I would
solve the first case
with you and only that one.
But we haven't solved
the Butei Killer case.
Why are you
bringing this up now?!
Seriously, thanks to you,
I've come to realize
that I'm gonna have to work
alone for the rest of my life!
There's not a single
person out there
worthy of being my partner!
And I'm fine with--
You're not frightened, are you?
What, why would I be scared?
Don't be stupid.
Anyway, what I was saying--
Why don't you just
hide under the covers
if you're that scared?
I don't think either of us
want you to piss yourself.
Shut up!
Stupid Kinji!
Good evening, this is
your captain speaking.
We're taking a slight detour
to avoid some thunderstorms.
The weather's gonna
keep up for a little while,
but it shouldn't cause
us too much turbulence.
Please tell me you've got
an extra pair of underwear.
Sh-Shut up!
I'm, I'm, I'm gonna, pump you--
Of all things,
I never would've expected
this to be her weak point.
Just quit picking on me, Kinji.
There's nothing to be scared of,
everything is just fine.
But the-- How do
you know it's fine?
Her hands.
They're so small and delicate.
She may not seem like it,
but she's an ordinary girl.
Well, I may not be her partner,
but I can still be her friend.
Kinji.
I need to tell
you something, Aria.
I've got a strong feeling
the Butei Killer is--
That was a gun.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience,
but this plane
has been hijacked.
I know that voice.
It's the Butei Killer!
Dammit! I wish I'd
been wrong about this.
On the other hand,
Butei are welcome to roam.
I'll be waiting in
the downstairs bar
if you'd like to
come play with me.
Fine by me.
I'm gonna pump the
creep full of holes.
I'm right behind you.
I've got this one.
Are you sure?
Fine. Come with me.
The Butei Killer started off
by hijacking a
motorcycle and a car.
And he killed a Butei
while hijacking a boat.
I'm pretty sure that one
was a direct confrontation.
Why's that?
'Cuz there was no remote control
radio signal detected that time.
There was no need to use one,
because the killer
was on the boat.
It's just a hunch, but I get
the feeling he's on the plane.
He attacked me on my bike,
and then he attacked the bus.
So the only thing left--
A plane?
But how were you so sure
he'd choose this plane?
He framed your mom and
now he's finishing the job.
He's declaring war on you.
So you think I've been
the bastard's target
from the get-go.
He wants to mess
with me, does he?
Then I'll show him a real mess.
Turn around now.
It's kind of sad how easily
you fall right into my traps.
Riko!
Bon soir, Kinji.
And you. Ohl-mes.
Ohl-mes?
Alright.
Who the hell are you?
Riko Mine Lupin the fourth.
That is my true family name.
Lupin, that's--
Exactly.
The French master
thief, Arsene Lupin.
I'm his great granddaughter.
Wait, what?
So maybe you are
Lupin's descendant,
but why the hell
are you doing this?
I'm doing this because
my name's Riko.
Not once has anyone
from my family called me
by my given name.
My mother gave me this name
and what do they call me?
It's Lupin! Miss Lupin!
Lupin the fourth!
Even the servants called
me Miss Lupin the fourth.
My whole life.
You're serious?
That's the reason
you're doing this?!
They've ignored my existence!
Treated me like a number!
Like I don't matter!
All they care about
is my genetics!
The only way to
become my own person
is to surpass my grandfather.
So I joined I-U for the power
they promised to give me.
And with this power I'll show
the world my true identity!
Hold on, Riko!
Are you seriously
the Butei Killer?
You planned the hijackings?
The hijackings were nothing
but a mere prologue.
Holmes the fourth is my target.
Which means you. Aria.
The confrontation between our
great-grandfathers
concluded with a stalemate.
So, if I am able to
defeat Holmes the fourth,
then I will have exceeded
my great-grandfather's legacy.
And don't try to skip out
on playing your role Kinji.
What?
It's a necessity that
Holmes has a partner.
The first Holmes would have been
absolutely nothing without his.
In order to balance the odds,
I had to make sure
you partnered with Aria.
Do you mean that you
orchestrated our meeting?
That's right!
All I had to do was plant
a bomb on your bike.
And then the remote radio
signal led her straight to you.
But it seemed like you
needed extra incentive,
so I hijacked the bus.
It boggles the mind
that you never noticed
I'd tampered with the
clocks in your dorm room.
You're a terrible Butei, Kinji.
So you've been able to
pull off every single step
of your plan without a problem.
Well, not entirely.
Hard as I tried, the
two of you simply refused
to team up with one another.
You wouldn't even
get off your butt
until I mentioned
your older brother.
Oh, I'm sure you've
figured this out,
but the culprit in the
case with your brother.
All meeee!
So you...
you killed my brother?!
Well actually.
I'll let you in on
something fun.
How exactly should I put this?
See. Your brother's
my boyfriend.
Enough of your crap!
Calm down, she's provoking you!
You expect me to be calm now?!
No, no, I don't think so, Kinji.
We both know you're
useless in a battle right now.
You aren't the only one
who uses two guns, y'know?
As a rule, Butei
never go anywhere
without their
bulletproof jackets.
This fact tends to complicate
up-close gun battles.
The only way to win is
to score a direct hit
at point blank range.
Or to land a head shot.
That hurt!
And if they're equally skilled,
it comes down to
who's got more bullets.
Which means,
Aria's in a bad spot.
Luckily.
Kinji!
Give it up, Riko!
What's truly amazing,
Aria is just how much stuff
you and I have in common.
Our family history, our cute
figures, and our nicknames.
What?
I know it's weird, but
I've got the same nickname.
I'm Riko the Quadra.
Although. Your Quadra
isn't the real deal.
Aria!
Aria. Aria!
Where am I?!
Last thing I remember
is getting shot.
Thou art deep in
the world of dreams.
What are you doing here, Kinji?!
My name art not Kinji.
I art a dream spirit.
Oh, is that so?
There art unfinished
deeds thou must accomplish.
I'm aware of that.
I've gotta take down Riko.
Next time on
Aria the Scarlet Ammo!
"Butei Charter
Article 1" tis next.
I shall pump thou full of holes!
Great, I'm talking like you.