Can you imagine
what it'd be like
to watch a girl just
fall out of the sky?
Yeah.
That'd be a great way to
start off a movie or a manga.
It could definitely
be the opening shot
of some extraordinarily
cool story.
Maybe the main guy
could transform into a hero
and this would be the
beginning of a great adventure
for him and the girl.
But actually wishing
for that to happen to
you would be kinda stupid,
because there's no way on earth
a girl like that
would be normal.
Hey Jerkwad!
You gonna duck or
should I shoot you too?
In real life?
Being shoved into
an unknown world
where you're supposed
to be the hero?
I know it sounds
cool but trust me,
it'd be dangerous and
a serious pain in the ass.
There's a frikkin bomb
planted on this stupid thing!
Get back or you're
gonna get dead!
Article 1 of the Butei charter.
"Trust your friends and
help when they need it."
Are you ready?
That's me.
I'm Kinji Tohyama.
And crazy hero adventures?
Yeah, that's never
really been my thing.
All I ever wanted was
to have an ordinary life.
I didn't want to be
noticed or even talk
to anybody for that matter.
I wanted to get out
of my psycho school.
Just because my last
name 'Tohyama' is famous,
doesn't mean my life
has to be special.
There's my sleepy Kin-Kin.
I've told you ever since we
were little not to call me that.
Time to let that go and
just call me Kinji, okay?
Oh yeah.
I'm sorry.
I was actually just thinking
about when we were kids
on the way over here,
Kin-Kin, so I guess it was--
I just said it again, didn't I?
I'm so sorry Kin-Kin-- Oh. Oops.
Well?
What'd you come here for?
You remember how I told
you I'd be at the Ise Shrine
for training camp up
until yesterday, right?
Well, I just came by to catch up
since I couldn't do anything
for you while I was gone.
You don't have to do this.
But, I want to.
Fine, go ahead.
Check it out.
I made you this.
This is sugar-soy sauce shrimp,
Coho salmon and
Saijo persimmons,
and since
you like omelets,
I went ahead cooked one
of those for you, too.
You went to an
awful lot of trouble.
Not at all.
I just had to wake up at 4:30.
I always worry about
you during summer break
because usually
you eat so poorly--
nothing but fast food, cans of
meat and those sugar things.
Thanks a lot.
But my diet is not your job.
Here's dessert for my Kin-Kin.
Uh, yeah.
Say, um...
Thanks for all the nice
stuff you do, Shirayuki.
But you're always so nice to me.
I should be thanking you!
You really have to stop acting
like this with me at some point.
But I could see how difficult
it was for you to say "thanks."
You just try so hard for me.
Black? Oh crap.
That's gotta
violate the dress code.
Thanks for the food!
Oh man.
That was a close one.
Hey Kin?
In honor of our
first day as sophomores
I had your bulletproof
uniform cleaned.
Yeah, thanks.
And I loaded your
Berretta for you, too.
Those rounds were
laying everywhere.
Great.
Do I seriously
have to go strapped
on the first day of school?
You know you do, Kin.
The school rules clearly state
that students of Butei High
are required to
carry a gun and a blade
within school premises
at all times.
You never know
when another psycho
could pop up,
like that Butei-Killer.
The Butei-Killer?
C'mon, they already
caught that guy, right?
Heard they locked him up
and threw away the key.
Sure, but a copycat might
try to steal his ideas.
This morning's horoscope said
that you'd have trouble
caused by a woman.
If something were
to happen to you, Kin.
I'd just, I think I'd--
Okay, okay.
Besides, if I break the rules,
I'll get an even
worse evaluation,
and then I can't
transfer schools.
You're so lucky, Kin.
The Tohyama family is
filled with legendary heroes
and you're one of them.
Stop saying that.
I'm not anybody's hero.
I'm just a kid.
Go ahead and go without me.
I'll be there after
I check my e-mail.
If you want me to
wait I could clean
and do laundry until
you're finished with that.
You've done enough already.
Okay then.
Do your e-mailings.
Maybe you'll even have
time to send me one.
Oh crap! I'm gonna miss the bus!
On this particular day.
I missed the
7:58 bus for school,
which I would come to
regret for the rest of my life,
starting right then.
Is it too much to ask for
a normal, ordinary life?
That's all I want.
Attention: There is a remote
bomb planted on that bicycle.
If you attempt
to get off the bike
or if you begin to slow
down, it will explode.
Oh great.
This is a joke, right?
Please do not try
calling for help.
It is wired to explode if you
use your cellular telephone.
There's no way.
You never know when
another psycho could pop up,
like that Butei-Killer.
A copycat!
That's just perfect.
Why is he going after me?
I'm nobody.
I don't even want
to be a stupid Butei.
Good morning
first year students,
it's nice to meet you all.
I'll be your Ambulace
instructor at Tokyo Butei.
My name's Mr. Sayonaki.
Today, I'll orient
you to the campus.
I'll start with a basic
introduction of our facilities
and then I'll make
sure you understand all
of the school
rules at Butei High.
Tokyo Butei High is a 2
kilometer long by 500 meter wide
man-made island
known as a Mega-Float
which is anchored due
south of the Rainbow Bridge.
If I stop, it'll explode.
If I slow down, it'll explode.
Even if I jump off, I'll
end up getting shot by an Uzi.
I've gotta think.
Butei High is a comprehensive
educational institute
that trains students to become
armed detectives known as Butei.
Established to fight the
rising tide of violence,
graduates receive
an international license
granting them powers
equivalent to
those of the police,
like carrying weapons
and making arrests.
However, unlike the police,
Butei are freelancers.
Our students are
allowed to take any Quest
they choose within
the scope of Butei Law.
Got it?
It's no use.
Unless I take it
out in one shot,
I'll be Swiss cheese for sure.
Given the nature of the job,
a Butei could end up on
almost anyone's enemy list.
Recently, there was
even a serial killer
who was specifically
targeting the Butei.
Let that serve as a
reminder to all of you,
the life of a Butei
can be very dangerous
and our training
reflects that fact,
so try not to die
during school hours.
Every year I see the new
crop of incoming students
and get a little sad
because I know some of them
won't make it to graduation.
Crap, my legs are almost dead.
This is your last warning.
If you slow down any more,
the bomb will explode.
Is this how I'm going
to die, on a bike?
Can you imagine
what it'd be like
to watch a girl just
fall out of the sky?
Huh?
What happened to me?
I think my bike exploded.
There was a bomb planted on it.
A girl fell from the sky.
And then?
She's cute.
Hey, wait.
I got thrown when
the bomb exploded,
but how did I end
up in this place?
This can't be right!
So this girl risked her life
like that just to save me.
Oh no, this is bad!
This is not allowed!
Forbidden, forbidden,
forbidden, forbidden!
"Aria H. Kanzaki."
That's her name, huh?
From A to B?
She's wearing a push-up bra?!
Wait, the bra's powerless
against her genetics.
Good.
Calming down.
You perv!
You're a gross
disgusting freaky weirdo!
You ungrateful molester monster!
You got it all wrong!
I didn't touch you!
So there were more of them.
Uh, there were more of what?
Those Uzi two-wheelers
he used to kill the Butei!
These 9-millimeter
Parabellums are made
by an Israeli company named IMI
and shoot at 10
rounds per second.
If this vaulting box
wasn't bulletproof,
we would have been
cut to pieces by now.
But I thought you took
that thing out right
before my bike blew up.
I told you there were
more of them, didn't I?
I count at least seven.
That's a problem.
Come on, pull out that Berretta!
I thought you were a
student at Butei High.
Uh, I can't.
Hurry up, we need more
firepower than just what I got.
What the heck?
This is new info.
Breasts are soft even
when they're tiny.
This is definitely
going to send me over.
Are you finished?
I only pushed them back for now.
They're still out there hiding
next to the trees on
the side of the road,
but they'll come out again.
You're strong for a girl.
I'm impressed you
could manage that.
Here's your reward,
my little princess.
Hey. What the--?
Have a seat there
and relax for a minute.
We don't need two people getting
all messy on this one, do we?
What happened to
you all of a sudden?
Have you gone crazy?
Figures.
We're in their blind spot.
They're wasting bullets
shooting like that.
Stop. You'll be shot!
I'll be fine as long
as I know you're safe.
What's gotten into you?
Out of nowhere
you're Mr. Super Stud?
What're you gonna do?
Protect you.
Aria.
Nice pattern.
This doesn't mean I owe you!
Toys like that, I could've
handled them by myself.
It's true.
I would've been fine.
If you're just trying to make up
for your super creepy
grope fest from earlier,
this is not going
to do it for me.
That was sexual assault,
and it's a crime.
Easy now.
That was just a
misunderstanding.
Where my face landed
was not in my control.
Not in your control, huh?
I was passed out and you were
trying to take off my clothes
like some kind of super
creepy pervy douchebag!
On top of that,
you saw my chest!
You're a criminal who got
caught in the act of assault!
You would have done
things I can't even imagine
if I didn't wake up
when I did, admit it!
Okay, try to think
about this rationally.
I'm in High School.
So it shouldn't be a shock
that middle school girls
like you are a little
too young for my taste.
I am not a middle-schooler,
you jerk-hole!
I'm sorry.
I didn't think they'd let an
elementary student be an intern,
but for a kid you did great.
It was really superb work.
Aria?
I should never have
saved a guy like you.
I'm in my second
year of High School!
So you do hand-to-hand
combat, too?
You can't escape.
I've never let a single
criminal cross my path
and get away from me.
Where did my?
How the hell did
you get my magazine?
Give it back right now!
Sorry, princess.
I won't let you
get away with this.
Even if you beg for
forgiveness, I'll make you pay!
Swords, too?
You're a creepy molester man.
Give up now!
I'm sorry.
I must've dropped these.
You jerk!
Don't run off,
you stupid coward!
I'm gonna pump you
full of so many holes!
Hysteria savant syndrome,
also commonly known
as hysteria mode.
It's a rare genetic abnormality
that runs in my family.
The problem with it
is that it also changes
every other aspect of my
personality when it kicks in.
I feel compelled to protect
the girl in front of me
no matter what, and,
for some reason,
I act so completely smug,
that I feel like a total idiot
whenever I look back on it.
I just want to crawl
under a rock and die.
Oh man.
'Here's your reward,
little princess'?
I'm such a douchebag.
Sorry I'm late,
but I had to deal with
something that came up.
I want my seat to be
right next to that guy!
What?
No way!
Why'd she have
to be in my class?
Good for you, Kinji!
I don't know what her deal is
but damn you are one lucky guy.
Hey, teacher!
After we drew
straws I was supposed
to sit next to Kinji,
but I'll give my seat to Aria!
That is so sweet.
Then the seat next to
Kinji will go to Aria.
Umm, actually, Teacher, I uhh.
Hey. I brought your belt back.
Oh! That's it!
Now I got it!
It's so obvious what's
going on between you two!
You're not wearing
your belt, Kin,
and then Miss Double Duty Hair
Freak brings it back to you.
It's hardly a mystery.
I conclude that you
must have done something
where you needed
to take off your belt
in front of her for some reason.
You're right.
My guess is they must be dating.
How are you dating a hot girl?
All this time I thought
he was a nerdy loser.
I assumed he only
liked the guys.
Total waste.
Hey, hold on.
Listen! Relationships
are pointless.
Try to remember that here.
Cause if you act
like a bunch of idiots,
I'll pump you full of holes!
Well that was pretty crazy
for a first day of school.
She sure likes
e-mail, doesn't she?
Hi Kin, how are you?
Inquesta's classes are
over for the day, right?
Looks like the SSR
has classes until night.
I just want to go home already
and think of stuff
I can do for you.
Things are tough on Shirayuki,
too, in their own way.
Now that I'm home,
it's like the whole bomb thing
this morning didn't happen.
I never thought the Butei
Killer would go after me.
Well, a copycat of the
Butei Killer anyway.
Besides it's not like they
were targeting me specifically.
It's gotta be random--they
coulda' picked any Butei.
But why go through all the
trouble of planting a bomb
on a bike like that?
You'd only do that if you were
targeting someone in particular.
Somebody must have a
serious grudge against me.
All right!
I'm coming!
What the hell?
'Bout time.
Oh, it's you again.
You could just say "hello."
Hold on.
Wait. Aria?
You can't come barging
in here uninvited.
Really. I mean it!
Listen up.
I've decided that you
should become my slave.
Just like Shirayuki said.
I had trouble caused
by a woman today.
"You should become my slave!"
Oh yeah, that was a
pretty cool thing to say
and it has a nice ring to it.
What's with you being
all stuck on yourself?
Like I said.
I think you should
team up with me!
No, thank you.
Why would I do that?
I've decided to
quit being a Butei.
Peach buns are so good!
Listen to me when I'm talking.
Next time, Aria the
Scarlet Ammo Episode 2!
"Aria the Quadra."
Watch it or I'll pump
you full of holes.