After all, I gave
you something special.
Don't you think it's ironic
you're the first boy
I've ever kissed,
cause I'll be your last!
Tell me one thing before
I pump you full of holes.
Why were you so hell bent on
getting that rosary back?
It's more than a keepsake
of your mom's, isn't it?
Aria.
Have you ever been held
captive in a small cell,
living off nothing but
rotten meat and muddy water?
I refuse to go back
to that existence!
I'm more than just
a genetic receptacle!
I am Riko! Riko Mine Lupin!
I'm not some machine for
giving birth to the Fifth!
To answer your question,
it's not just an
ordinary rosary.
It's actually the
Lupin's secret treasure.
And my mother
passed it down to me.
When I was locked in
the cell all those years.
I kept it hidden in my mouth
so they could never find
it and take it from me.
And that's how I discovered,
that this rosary.
It's metal endowed
me with powers
that I wasn't even aware of.
And I used them
to escape that cell.
Now let's settle this, Holmes.
After I defeat the two
of you. It'll be over.
I'll have proven my superiority!
Surpassing the first!
And I'll be free!
Mr. Sayonaki? What the hell?
It'd behoove you to stay still.
They will attack if
you make any wrong moves.
So let's try to
keep this pleasant.
They're Caucasian Silver Wolves.
The same type as
the wolf Reki tamed.
That's right.
At one time, he was
my dutiful servant.
I was a little surprised at
how quickly she mastered him.
I really should have
collected her blood.
Even if it had to be by force.
Collected her blood?
Compared to Reki's skills.
Lupin the Fourth.
You're just as
worthless as always.
All this time that
we've spent together
and you still don't
remember the fact
that we'd already
met ten years ago.
You just stay put.
I'm only drawing
a little bit of blood.
Actually, I'm checking
your genes to be exact.
Now I remember you.
You were the one who told Vlad.
That was you, wasn't it?
It was. I just realized.
Your friends don't even know
what we're talking about.
The results of my tests showed
that even though
Riko here is a Lupin--
No, don't tell them!
Not a single one of
their genetic talents
were passed down to her.
In other words.
She is a perfectly useless
fluke in their family's history.
But you are quite skilled at
proving how useless you are.
Aren't you, Number Four?
It's outright laughable
that you tried
to steal this rosary
with such a childish plan.
It must make you sad
to be so incompetent.
Human abilities are
predicated on their genes.
Your genetic makeup
draws the line
between what you
can and cannot do,
no matter how
hard you might try.
To give you an example,
just try to stop me!
Why don't you go ahead
and swallow this junk
so you won't lose it again.
And you thought your
plan went well, didn't you?
I made it as easy as I could
for you to steal it back.
I knew your despair
would be even greater
if you thought you won.
Ohhh, listen to that!
There's nothing more ambrosial
than the sound
of pain and despair!
Alright, cut it out already!
There's no point in
torturing her anymore!
There's actually a
very specific point.
It's necessary for
Vlad's summoning.
Vlad?
Pain.
And despair.
He appears when he
hears a song of agony.
Please.
Now it's building towards
something beautiful.
This can't be real.
Don't tell me you're Vlad.
Well, no, it's not
quite that simple.
I'm nothing more than
an outer shell created
from the many genes
Vlad has collected.
I'm an organic effigy
designed to mimic humans.
Get ready. Here
he comes. It's time.
Just what the hell is he?!
He's Vlad, that's what he is.
Get ready to cover me, Kinji!
I'm only gonna paralyze them.
Not to outright
steal Reki's trick.
Vlad!
You framed my mom
for your crimes
and now she's stuck
rotting away in prison.
I'm gonna make your hairy ass
confess to it on the stand!
The bullets.
The wounds have
completely healed, too!
Do you think you can arrest me?
Huh?
Delusions of grandeur
are clearly a genetic trait
of your family, little Holmes.
I'm dead serious, jerk!
You have such boundless spirit.
It's downright precious.
You've convinced me that your
blood is worthy of sampling.
I suppose I'll just have
to snap your head back
and sink my fangs
deep into your neck.
Oh, yeah. It all makes sense.
Vlad. I know your
true identity now!
You're Dracula, aren't you?
Wait, Dracula?!
The vampire?
Good guess, Holmes.
I am Ogre Vampies.
I've been consuming human blood
and assimilating the genes
into my own constant evolution.
My body and mind
have achieved powers
far beyond your
puny comprehension.
My defenses have
made me impervious
to guns and garlic
and even sunlight.
You've attempted to
harness each one against me
and failed every time.
Haven't you, Lupin the Fourth?
It's been so long since
we've seen each other
and you can't even
give me a smile?
Vlad. You promised.
You said that
you'd let me go free.
As long as I was
able to defeat Holmes.
And I had her right in my palm.
Would you feel the need to keep
a promise you made to a dog?
Forget all about it
and go back to
your cage, you bitch.
You may be worthless
but you still hail
from a superior breed.
If I find the
right mate for you,
you might yet spawn
an improved Lupin Five.
Take a good look.
This is the very last time
you'll see the world
outside your cell.
Soak it up and store it deep
inside that puny brain of yours.
Aria. Kinji.
Why won't you help me? Please?
What took you so long to ask?
Kinji!
Right!
Obnoxious brat.
Looks like you want
me to teach you
a lesson on how to play rough.
You're calling me a brat?!
I'm sixteen years old, dammit!
You're getting dangerously
close to pissing me off.
I love to see the look
on the arrogant ones faces
when I pop their skulls between
my thumb and forefinger.
Alright, you're safe here.
Listen to me.
The only chance Aria
has is to surrender.
Vlad is too strong.
She'll never make it.
We can't defeat him.
It's impossible.
Trust me. We can't.
Many others have
tried in the past.
The past gets
rewritten everyday, Riko.
See, things are
getting better already.
I snagged it when I rescued you.
Riko. You're too
hurt to fight anymore.
Just stay here. Aria
and I can handle it.
Kinji.
Y'know what?
With you and Aria
fighting together,
it just might be possible.
I'll stay, but I can help.
I know where his fourth
weak spot's located.
Aim your gun, at the
middle of his chest.
Aria!
Nothing's working.
I've shot each of those
patterns a dozen times,
but the wounds just
keep on closing up.
It's gonna work this time, Aria.
How, we don't
know the fourth spot!
Yes we do. Riko told me.
It's the center of his chest.
I'll shoot there
and his left shoulder.
You cover the
spots on his right side.
If you say so.
Alright.
I'll count it down.
Five. Four. Three.
Two. One!
Is he dying?
You stupid children.
Did you really think
that girl could figure
out my final vital point?!
No. No!
So. Was that the only
strategy you two had?
Well then. Let me show
you an effective plan.
I've never heard of
Dracula howling before!
Wait. What the hell?
He neutralized my hysteria mode.
Crap! What do I do?
I'm clueless. I'm too normal!
What's wrong with you?!
Kinji!
Riko?
I can't believe you saved me!
Let's just keep going, Kinji.
We can't defeat him,
so what's the point in
us going back there?
Let's run.
And just leave Aria?
Once she realizes
that you've run,
I'm sure she'll
do the same thing.
You know that
she's not like that.
I'm not leaving without her.
She and I are partners, dammit!
But what about Vlad?!
Make him pay!
Are you gonna let him go
after what he's done to you?
Your name is Riko, isn't it?
Aren't you more than
just the number four?!
Help me, Kinji.
I need you to call out my name.
Riko.
Please, say it again.
One more time!
Rikooooo!
You're right.
My name is Riko. It's Riko Mine!
I hope you're ready, Kinji.
I am.
Hey. Do you have a gun?
Yeah. I do.
But it's got one round.
First things first.
We rescue Aria.
If the idea I had
earlier is correct,
then we've got a chance!
Kinji?! You're alive!
You smell delicious
after you sweat!
Do you really think this
is the time to perv out?
It's the perfect time!
We've gotta give Kinji
some extra incentive
to come up with a solid plan!
No. Okay!
What are you doing? Stop!
Now the finishing touch.
Get off of me,
you freaky pervert!
On your feet, right now!
So, Kinji?
Did Aria do it for you?
What?
Yep.
You know me
too well, Riko.
Aria, you're not out
of bullets, are you?
What? No.
There's one in each chamber.
And I've also got one left.
And Riko's got one,
so when you add
them all up we've
got four total.
Let's take another crack
at Vlad's weak spots.
Why? Did you figure
out the last spot?
Aria, I want you to shoot his
left shoulder and his chest.
His chest? We tried that!
Butei Charter Article 1.
"Trust your friends.
Help when they need it."
Aria. I need you to trust me.
I can do that. Let's do it.
Shoot the right shoulder, Riko.
I'll cover his right flank.
I'm on it.
You just don't
know when to give up.
Couldn't you at least
try to be good at losing?
In five. Four. Three. Two. One!
Wasting your bullets again, huh?
He'll simply block
his last weak spot
if I outright aim
for it. Although.
If he sees me aiming
at a different spot.
No! I can't die!
We killed him?
We did.
I'm confused, though.
How did you know where
his fourth weak spot was?
Tell me.
I remembered something.
That first time we shot him?
He blocked his
mouth with his arm.
But it didn't exactly
make sense for him
to do that if he's got
the power to eternally heal.
Unless he's blocking
his weak spot.
That's how you knew?
How d'you feel, Riko?
The three of us were able to
defeat the undefeatable Vlad.
We did it by working together.
Not even the first
Lupin could defeat him.
Good point.
I guess this means
you've officially
exceeded the first Lupin.
But don't expect
me to thank you.
Alright, Holmes?
Our personal interests just
happened to intersect this time.
This doesn't change
the fact that the Holmes's
and Lupins are age old enemies.
Yeah, calm down.
I don't wanna be
your friend either.
But, you are still gonna testify
at my mom's trial.
And if you even
think of backing out.
Aria Holmes Kanzaki,
and Kinji Tohyama.
You've proven yourselves.
I'm through looking down on you.
You're obviously my equals.
And so, I will keep my promise.
Just remember, I'm the only
one that gets to defeat you.
Au revoir!
Riko!
And there she goes.
With everything she wanted.
It won't be long
before she turns up again.
Probably acting like
nothing happened.
I'd love these in a
green if you have 'em.
Oh, and a red and blue.
Jeez.
She needs some girl friends
so I don't have to go
shopping with her.
Kana?
No. I'm seein' things.
Kinji, Kinji!
Hey, Kinnnji!
My mother's attorney
just called me!
Riko just came by to
tell her that she'll testify!
Oh, yeah? That's great, Aria.
This means my mom's
definitely gonna get a retrial!
I bet she's so
relieved right now!
Yeah, she must be.
Oh, hey, Aria.
I think you dropped
these when you hugged me.
What are these things?
You worthless pervert!
What?! Hold on, Aria!
You're such a perverted idiot!
Stupid, stupid!
Pervert, pervert!
Stuuuupid! Pervert!