Dammit.
Oh, Kinji!
How's your cold?
Is there a fever?
Do you have a headache?
No. I'm fine.
I'm completely over it now.
Thank goodness.
I was so worried.
You don't have to
get all emotional.
Okay!
Oh, boy.
By the way, thanks
for getting this for me.
What?
I'm glad you went to buy
this fever medicine for me.
It really did the trick.
Yeah, that's the--
What's wrong? You okay?
It's nothing.
I'm alright.
My room became a fortress and
because of them I caught cold.
Then there are half
naked girls at school.
My safety zone is shrinking.
Kinji!
Owww!
Seriously, it's pathetic!
You could at least
get the sword-catching
right once in a while!
Durandal has a sword that
they say can cut
through any type of steel.
I'm training you this way
because it could save
your life, you big dork.
I hope you didn't come
all the way out here
just to tell me
that little tidbit.
Try not to be a
simpleton, Kinji.
I don't have that kind of
time to waste. I have a job.
I want you to check all
the emails Shirayuki got
on her cell after school today.
What for?
That sounds kinda lame.
I heard that Durandal always
sends a threatening email
to his target on
their cell phone
before he tries to kidnap them.
Shirayuki might've gotten one.
How am I supposed
to pull that off.
She's never going to let
me just search through them.
And besides, she'd tell me if
something like that happened.
Hey, aren't you supposed to
be guarding her right now?
It's ok, I asked Reki
to watch her for me.
But it's only
for a little while.
She's too busy with all her
practice because she's
representing Japan in
the sniping competition.
Oh, really?
Are you even listening to me?!
Yes, I am.
That was rude;
would you try to be at least
a little considerate of your
partner's fragile condition?
You mean.
Can't you lay off for a bit?
I just got over a cold.
Which I got because a
certain someone threw me
into the freezing
cold Tokyo bay at night.
I'm sorry.
I know that I can be a
little overbearing sometimes
but it's for your
own protection.
At least I'm finally
feeling human again.
I'd probably still
be dying if it weren't
for the medicine
Shirayuki brought me.
What? Shirayuki?
Yeah.
It was nice having
someone around
who bothered to take care of me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just glad
you're better that's all.
Aww, come on.
It's not like you to hold back
when you have something to say.
Speak.
Now you care what I think?
Well I'm still not
tellin', so there!
I'm so glad that you had
Shirayuki to take care of you!
Why don't you just
marry her already?
What is with you today?
You know you want to!
You're the bodyguard
and she's the client,
and I catch you taking
off each others' clothes?
It's wrong!
I already told you,
it wasn't what it looked like.
I saw what I saw!
If I'm wrong, fine!
Then show me the proof!
Huh?
I can only believe evidence!
That's how Butei are trained.
Show proof! Proof, proof, proof!
You're my slave,
and you act like this?!
You stupid Kinji! Stupid Kinji!
Stupid Kinji! Stupid Kinji!
If you're so insistent on proof,
why don't you show me yours?
What do you mean?
The proof that
Durandal really exists!
We've been watching
Shirayuki twenty-four seven
and nobody has even
tried to get close to her.
I don't think this
Durandal really exists.
That's not true!
He does exist!
Or maybe you just convinced
yourself that it was true.
Maybe you're so
desperate to find ways
to clear your mother's name that
when you heard
the name Durandal,
you wanted more than anything
to believe he actually existed.
And now, you've managed
to convince
yourself that he's real.
No!
Durandal does exist!
Shirayuki's in danger.
I can feel it.
Then show me some real
proof instead of just words!
You assume things all the time
and then you just do
whatever you think is right.
You're just like
the rest of 'em.
Nobody ever believes
anything I say.
Like right now I can sense
that an enemy is
closing in on Shirayuki.
I'm not anything like
my great-grandfather.
I don't have the words
to explain it logically.
That's why they call
me the defective Holmes,
the one who didn't get the gift.
But I know I'm right this time.
I'm pouring my heart out to you
and you still don't trust me.
Why won't you
listen to me, Kinji?
Why should I believe in this
enemy when he doesn't exist?!
Until the competition's over,
I'll guard Shirayuki
by myself, got it?
Why don't you go
somewhere and cool off?
You- You- You- You- You,
you, you stupid idiot!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
You are so stupid, Kinji!
You deserve an award!
What?
So from now on you're going
to be my bodyguard exclusively?
Are you sure?
Aria's really the one who wanted
to make sure you were safe,
but I made a promise,
so I'm here.
You've sworn a solemn
vow to protect me.
It's like you're a
knight. I'm dreaming.
I wouldn't get too
excited about it.
After all you did get
stuck with an E-rank Butei.
Oh I don't care about that.
You're brave,
and I totally trust you.
Kinji.
I'd be honored if you'd agree
to be my bodyguard. Okay?
Okay, yeah.
Come to think of it,
aren't the other student council
members coming over today?
The competition starts tomorrow
and you guys have to get ready.
But since we're
pretty much finished,
we decided to take a break,
everyone's probably already
at the fireworks display by now.
There're fireworks tonight?
They're shooting them
off at Luckyland in Tokyo;
everyone's been
real excited about it.
So, because you're the
Student Council President
you have to man the fort?
No, they invited
me to go with them
but unfortunately
that's not possible.
Wait, you can't go? Why?
There are rules.
I'm not allowed outside
without permission
from the school and the Shrine.
Huh?
I'm a maiden of
protection for the Shrine.
It's an ancient tradition that
we spend our entire lives
inside the Hotogi Shrine.
Sometimes we're allowed
to leave but it's rare.
But they let you out to
come to school here, right?
Yes, but that was a decision
they let me make in
spite of their disapproval.
So I don't want to upset
my Shrine any more
than I already have.
That's tough.
I'll just be a minute,
if you don't mind waiting.
Poor girl.
I guess it's not much different
for you here at school.
Too bad, from
one cage to another.
Hey, let's take a detour.
What?
Let's go see the
fireworks display.
I'm not allowed to
go outside the school.
You can't have fun
for just one night?
No one else has to know.
You mean, it'll
just be you and me?
That's right.
I've got your security
to think about.
We're not saying anything.
Of course, I usually try to
avoid being alone with a girl.
I can't believe we
can hear the fireworks
from all the way over here.
Oh yeah.
I can't wait to see them.
Yeah.
Kin, I hope taking me out
isn't really boring for you.
Nah, I'm okay.
I don't ever get to talk to guys
that much so I don't
really know what to say.
I'm not very interesting.
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I'm the same way.
This is like a dream.
Looks like the fireworks
are over already.
Sorry. I should've
checked the start time
before we came all
the way out here.
It's okay.
It's not your fault
that we missed them.
Besides.
I don't care if
there are fireworks
or if we just take a
walk on the beach at night.
The only thing that matters to
me is that it's you by my side.
You must be freezing
standing out here.
Here you go, put this on.
Shirayuki!
Hey.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Did something happen to you?
Not at all.
Your jacket, it smells like you
so I felt like you were
by my side the whole time.
It kinda smells like gunpowder.
It smells good.
You're a little weird.
Anyway check it out.
Kin.
Hmm? What's up?
The sparklers are
pretty, aren't they?
Yeah.
Do you like watching fires burn?
Uhh, little things
like this are alright,
but out of control
flames are terrifying.
It's been wired into us.
You're probably right.
I guess it's all done.
Yeah.
I told your fortune
with the shrine maiden's
fortune cards the other day.
What'd the cards say about me?
They said you
were going to leave.
Where am I going?
They didn't say.
Just that you were leaving.
I wonder if that means
I'm gonna transfer.
I thought maybe Aria was going
to take you away
with her somewhere.
There's no way that's happening.
But Aria's made you
a different person.
Ever since you met Aria,
you've become so much happier.
Shirayuki.
I'm so embarrassed, Kin.
I'm sorry.
Hey, why are you apologizing?
Because I always
thought I'd be able
to pay you back somehow.
You've been so nice
taking me out like this
so I could have time
outside the shrine, but now.
This won't make sense,
but I need you to do it.
Pretend I'm your girlfriend.
Just me. No one else but me.
Please kiss me.
Dude, that is so awesome!
Let's do the Dragon, next!
The Dragon, okay?!
Yeah!
I'll light this one!
Man.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Let's go home now, Kin.
Another day guarding
her and no problems.
I guess this is a pretty
easy mission after all.
Hey, Kinji!
Muto is over at
the reception desk.
He's complaining
about you how you forgot
to take over his shift.
You should go.
Is it that late already?
She should be alright with
this many people around.
Shirayuki.
I've got relieve Muto
from reception desk duties.
Yeah, go ahead.
See you later, then.
Kin, I'm sorry. Goodbye.
Oh no.
Where is she?!
Ms. Tsuzuri?!
Where's Shirayuki?
Uh, she should still be
at the student council tent.
She isn't there now.
What?
Look.
I need to know if she
received a weird email.
If he's involved in this
thing there should've been
some warning signs beforehand.
Try to remember!
You mean--
I heard that Durandal
sends a threatening email
to his target on their cell
phone before he kidnaps them.
Durandal!
Get back here, right now!
What did she mean by "Goodbye"?
Come on, pick up, Shirayuki!
Please, pick up! Dammit!
Aria! Come on, answer!
Why isn't Aria
picking up, either?!
Dammit! What am I doing?!
I never should have left her.
Shirayuki asked
me to protect her.
How could I let this happen?!
Aria was trying to
tell me that things
were getting dangerous for
Shirayuki but I didn't listen.
I should have trusted her.
If I hadn't driven her away we
could have kept Shirayuki safe.
Dammit! Where are you?!
Aria?!
No.
This is Reki.
I've just been informed
that our client,
Shirayuki, has gone missing.
Yeah, you have to
help me find her now!
You have to calm down.
Your abilities are cut in half
when you let senseless
panic take a hold of you.
Right now you appear
to be in full panic.
You want to take
a breath and try again?
Yeah.
Who was the last
person to see Shirayuki?
I think it was me.
I saw her 12 minutes
ago near Logi's garage.
She doesn't have any
reason to be over there.
Reki, you notice anything
else that seems out of place?
It doesn't matter how small.
The doors to Logi's equipment
warehouse #3 are open.
Normally, that warehouse
isn't used for anything.
So that's odd.
Equipment warehouse #3?!
I'm on my way.
The place feels deserted.
An elevator?
I wonder where that goes.
You can't be serious.
Okay Durandal, you can come out.
I'm here, now you're going
to keep your promise, right?
Of course.
No harm will come to the
students of Butei High.
especially not Kinji Tohyama.
What do you want
with me, Durandal?
She's here!
I don't have any
extraordinary abilities.
You're being modest.
You're a diamond in the rough.
And because you're such
a poorly protected gem
it seemed like the natural
thing to do to reach out to you.
No, If I fire a gun in here
it could set off
all the ammunition.
Don't you remember?
I called you before.
That sounds, like Kin's voice.
Once I supplied the impetus,
you and Kinji did just
as I expected, especially after
that annoying
Holmes left you two.
Come with me, Shirayuki.
I'll take you to a
place more to your liking.
To I-U.
Stop!
Kinji!
Get behind me! Move!
No! Stay back.
Damn you!
What?!
No, Kin! No! Stop it! Let go!
Let her go!
I wouldn't be worried
about her if I were you.
What?
Not your best work, Kinji,
but your stupidity was the
perfect cover for a set-up.
Durandal, stop!
The kidnapping of a
minor is a serious crime!
You're under arrest.
Hey, Kinji.
Isn't it weird that "Durandal"
sounds kinda like "sandal"?
The only thing
weird here is you.
No, listen!
"Sandals" remind you of
summer and sun and stuff, right?
But Durandal's got ice power!
It's all backwards!
Ahh, but summer's also the time
when people eat
the most sno-cones.
Hey, you're right!
Just what I'd expect
from my slave!
Brilliant deduction!
You being a descendent of
Holmes is the weirdest part.
Next time, Aria the
Scarlet Ammo episode 8!
"Durandal"!
Watch it or I'll pump
you full of holes!