[KAMINE]
More than once,
my new boyfriend has
made the same comment.
You're easy to get
along with, Kamine.
[KAMINE]
I am?
To be honest, I thought
being in a relationship
would be a lot more work.
But you aren't
selfish or clingy,
or act like you own me.
I didn't know there
were girls like you.
[KAMINE]
But the truth is, I am selfish.
I wanna be clingy. And I'm much
more jealous than I let on.
It upsets me when I see
him talking to other girls.
And I wanna text him to
see what he's thinking
all day and night.
Just now, I'm aching to grab him
and hold him here on this bench.
But I'm scared if
I said any of that,
he'd be annoyed
and think I'm a pain.
And what about you?
Are you ever jealous
or possessive of me?
No. Or at least not so far.
Which is probably good.
I hear relationships
like that don't last.
Yeah. You're right.
I've heard that, too.
But what about being
a little clingy?
Sure. A little's probably fine.
[KAMINE]
So what's "a little"?
I dunno. Maybe we could
hold hands when we walk?
[KAMINE] But not when
we're sitting together?
You mean like now?
[KAMINE] No, we don't have
to, if you don't want to.
[GODA]
It's okay. Go ahead.
I'm your boyfriend. You don't
need to be that cautious.
Are you sure?
And if I came a little
closer, would that be okay?
That's fine. You can come
as close as you want to.
What about now? Am I
getting too close for you?
You're okay.
How 'bout if I lean
on you like this?
Doesn't bother me. But I might
smell a bit from practice.
No. I like the way you smell.
Are you all right?
What's gotten into you today?
[KAMINE gasps]
Sorry! Do you mind me
being so touchy-feely?
No. I don't mind.
But you said before
that you didn't really
want a clingy girlfriend.
Actually, this is fine.
And isn't it what most couples
do when they're alone?
Yeah, I guess you're
right. They do.
You see, it's just that,
you didn't seem to want
to be close or cuddle
or do any of that stuff.
[gasps]
[KAMINE]
Huh?
What? Why'd you say that?
You're always quiet and shy.
I didn't think it would be
something on your mind.
Are you saying
you've been wanting me
to be more cuddly
and clingy with you?
Yeah. A little.
I will then.
I wouldn't have
held back this long
if you'd told me that earlier.
And while we're at it, could
we try something else, too?
[KAMINE]
Sure. What is it?
[KAMINE coughs]
I just wanted to do that
once. Please forgive me.
[KAMINE]
I coughed on my first kiss.
I coughed on my first kiss!
[KAMINE] It's all right. Just
that was my first kiss ever.
I wasn't really prepared.
[GODA]
Oh. Sorry.
[KAMINE]
I coughed on my first kiss.
How could I cough
on my first kiss?
Did you want me to try again?
[CHIAKI] I heard a rumor that
this guy, Goda, in my class,
kissed his girlfriend.
And they've only been
together for three months.
Can you believe it?
I sure didn't think
he had it in him.
Yeah. I know. I heard.
So where are we, Chiaki?
[CHIAKI clears throat]
Well, about that,
I've actually been meaning
to talk to you, Kana.
The home team's had a
lotta opportunities,
but they still can't
get on the board.
Your thoughts?
The power forward, Chiaki,
keeps chickening out.
He won't take it to the hole.
Ouch! Oh-ho-ho. Aren't you
bein' a bit brutal, coach?
It can't be all on him.
Chiaki's not the only
one on the team.
Somebody's gotta pass him the
rock before he can drive.
If I passed it to you now,
would you take the shot?
Goda and Kamine alley-ooped
into a slam dunk.
Now?
[KANA] Why not? We've
been dating for a while.
Everyone already thinks
we've at least kissed.
Yeah, but does it really matter
how long we've been together,
or what's been going on
over on another team?
It's not a competition.
We should focus on our own game.
'Kay. Fine then. Do you want to?
You mean right here?
Well, you said "now."
Thought that's what you wanted.
[KANA] Not if you feel
like I'm forcing you.
You aren't forcing me.
You just keep bugging me
about it all the time.
Forget it. I'm not in the mood.
Wait, are you angry?
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Kana? Please don't be mad.
[CHIAKI]
Crap. Technical foul.
Here comes the silent treatment,
Chiaki. Game over.
[KANA]
Hm.
[CHIAKI]
Huh? Is this only a time out?
Is there still a little time
left on the clock?
Yeah! I think there is.
Now's my chance! Shoot!
[CHIAKI] This is a difficult
angle. I can't line up the shot.
What am I gonna do?
All eyes are on me, and I can't
get anywhere near the basket.
But you're so close, Chiaki.
Just go for a layup
before the buzzer!
I'm not mad, I--
[gasps]
--[KANA] He missed!
--[CHIAKI] I missed!
[CHIAKI] Still, I did just kiss
a girl for the first time.
Awesome. Awesome!
Please, coach! Let me
take a free throw.
I can do it!
A what?
I won't mess it up this time.
Just give me one more chance.
Okay. Shoot.
Or maybe not.
Yeah.
[AKAGI]
Yup. That's the right answer.
I gotta say, I think I'm
gettin' pretty good at English.
And it may all be thanks to you.
Then... wanna go
to second base?
We're in the Library.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Didn't we agree to study here
because when we try
to study at home,
we end up fooling
around too much?
Yeah.
So, what was that?
I wanna squeeze your boobs.
You gonna let me?
For a guy who's as
smart as you are,
I'm amazed at the dumb stuff
that can come out of your mouth.
What's dumb about it?
There are other people around.
Why would I let you
cop a feel in public?
I figure that if I'm
persistent enough,
you'll eventually cave.
[KAJI grumbles]
Right? Don't you always
tend to give in?
What? No way! Of course not!
Are you certain?
You usually buckle
under pressure.
I may give in,
but I'm no pushover.
I know you're not.
But you're restraining yourself.
Aren't you? Or is it just me?
It's not like it's that hard.
Don't you want me to put
my arms around you
and hold you close?
Not really.
[KAJI]
What-What are you doing?
Don't hold back.
Indulge yourself.
I told you already.
Not in public.
[AKAGI]
Come on. You know you want to.
[KAJI]
Well, no one's watching.
So I guess there's no
harm in a little cuddle.
[AKAGI] But in return, you have
to let me have a little feelski.
What? Like hell I will!
[AKAGI] So I have to hold
back while you go nuts?
I won't then. Not like I'm
dying to be in your arms.
Here.
[KAJI]
Dammit!
[AKAGI]
Ah-ha. You were holding back.
[KAJI]
You tempted me. It's your fault.
Does this mean that I'm free
to squeeze your boobs?
Is that a "yes"?
Yeah. Sure. Fine.
Do whatever you want!
Great. Then let's go
back to studying.
What? But you said--
I didn't mean it.
I didn't really intend
to feel you up.
Even though you were quite
clearly ready to let me.
Then what the heck
was with all that?
I hold back a lot.
More than you realize
and I wanted you to know.
What? You've got nerve.
You say that like I
made it all about me!
No, but I do want more.
And now that you understand
that, I feel a lot better.
What? Did you want
me to kiss you?
[HOSOKAWA]
My love was like a firework.
The fragile spark of passion
blazed bright, then burnt out.
But the memory of that gleaming
moment still shines in my mind.
I can't forget it.
This is the spot where
I first saw him.
Why did I come back here?
He already turned me down.
[HOSOKAWA]
Katori! You're back!
Are-Are you okay?
Hi there. Who are you?
It's me, Hosokawa!
We met the other day!
I fell from a tree!
You caught me!
I save a lot of girls.
And I'm sorry, but I can't
remember all their faces.
Do you think you
could smile for me?
That might help jog my memory.
[HOSOKAWA]
He's gorgeous!
Ah-ha. Now I see.
You're that little kitten.
[HOSOKAWA] What happened?
How'd you get hurt?
I got in a little
bit of a tussle.
[HOSOKAWA]
I'll call an ambulance!
No, my little kitten.
You mustn't.
If you draw attention,
they'll find me.
[HOSOKAWA]
People are after him!
[KATORI]
I brought this on myself.
Another girl, who was
already taken, fell for me.
[HOSOKAWA]
That's not your fault!
They shouldn't blame you!
Oh, kitten, but it tis my fault.
I'm just to much.
How can I stop girls
from falling for me?
[HOSOKAWA] There's nothing.
He's perfect! It's impossible!
I should go.
If I stay here too long,
they'll catch up with me.
Where will you go?
You're a mess!
[KATORI]
Dunno.
Chances are they're
waiting for me at home.
Guess this tom cat's gonna
be a stray for a while.
Then come with me
and hide at my place!
Stay away from me,
kitten. Or you'll die.
I'm not afraid of
some jealous boys!
Poor little kitten.
You don't understand.
The real threat is
not from those boys
trying to hunt me down.
Why do girls keep
falling in love with me?
What cursed me to
be so irresistible?
There is only one who
could've done it.
Him, and him alone.
Are you talking... about God?
[KATORI]
Cupid!
As long as the god of love
continues to make me so popular,
more girls will keep getting
shot through the heart.
And I really just don't
wanna hurt anyone anymore.
No! You're the one who's hurt!
Let me make you better!
Sorry, kitten, you're caressing
the echo of my beauty again.
You caught me this time.
I must admit, I'm
quite impressed.
Mew miscalculate
my cat reflexes!
That's enough for today.
Quit while you're ahead.
You can't handle my moves.
They're far too intense.
[HOSOKAWA]
I don't care!
I have to be with you!
My poor, little kitten,
you're out of your league.
You may be roaring like
a jungle cat now...
...but with one
finger, just one,
I can stop you in your tracks.
Who do you think
your talking to?
What do you plan to
do with that finger
that you think's gonna work?
[HOSOKAWA screams]
I'm warning you; the flames
grow higher and hotter
the deeper and deeper you fall.
Is it me, Katori?
Is it that I'm just not
good enough for you?
If you can handle the
heat, then come burn.
[gasps]
Just kidding.
I'd never let a kitten play
with fire. Never ever!
Please! I'll be careful!
No. I'm going to find Cupid.
Then I'll beat the crap
out of him to make sure
no more fragile
hearts get singed.
But until I do, beware
the flames of love.
[HOSOKAWA]
I adore you, Katori!
[KATORI]
I know!
[TAKASE, KANDA]
Next episode: "Square One."