It's time to begin
our first game.
We have Class 1 versus
Class 7. Take your positions!
[YAMANE] Today is Sports Day
and we're playing soccer.
[yelping]
I don't know what I'm doing!
Somebody take it!
Somebody take it, please!
[KURIHARA]
Yamane!
Go! Beat Class 1!
[YAMANE]
Kurihara!
I just wanna go back to bed!
[yells]
[KANDA]
Go Takase!
[KANDA] But if I cheer for him,
is it obvious that I like him?
[KANDA, MINAGAWA]
Yeah! Goal! All right Class 1!
[TAKASE] Can I look at Kanda
while she's cheering?
Or would that be too obvious?
[NORO]
Furuya! Pass it!
[HOTARU] Go, Big Brother!
Come on, Furuya! Score!
[NORO]
Yo, Goda!
Looks like it's down to
just your class and mine.
Yeah.
You're goin' down.
We don't have girlfriends
distracting us.
We won't if you keep
handling the ball.
You know you can't, right?
What? Why can't I?
I do in volleyball.
[GODA]
This is soccer.
[NORO]
No fair!
Hey! Good luck in the finals.
I'll be rooting for you.
Thanks, Hosokawa!
Don't you have something
to say to him, too?
Um. Well...
Fine. Don't say anything.
You're a real jackass!
[PATRICIA]
Keisuke.
[KEISUKE]
Uh?
I wanna play in the
boys' soccer final, too.
I'm not sure that's allowed.
[TEACHER A]
She can play.
I'll just have
someone switch out.
[KEISUKE] Seriously? But
who's she gonna switch with?
Can I have your spot?
[KEISUKE]
Mh-hm...
All right. Final game.
Winner takes all.
[ALL]
Go Class 1! You can do it!
Yo! You can leave Goda to me.
Sure. Just don't use your hands.
[NORO]
I'll remember. Don't worry.
Hey, goalie. You ready?
Yeah.
[PATRICIA]
Hmph.
Bring it!
[CLASS 1 BOYS]
Uh...
[whistle blows]
Sugawara is such an
amazing soccer player.
Yeah, he is.
See that kick?
Very powerful.
Look at him go!
Why do you keep telling
me to watch Sugawara?
[SUGAWARA] Is Takano here?
Is she watching me play?
Why can't I let it go? I know
I don't stand a chance.
[gasps]
[SUGAWARA gasps]
[CHIAKI]
Oh. Ugh, that hurt.
[KANA]
Hey. Thanks, Chiaki.
[CHIAKI]
Yeah. Don't read much into it.
I was only trying
to get the ball.
[KANA] What? The ball was
already ours! You didn't have...
[CHIAKI]
So? I saved you! And a minute...
[KANA]
Saved me?
I don't need your
help, you moron!
What's wrong?
Trouble in paradise?
[CHIAKI, KANA] Shut up!
Mind your own business!
You poor saps with girlfriends.
You're whipped,
every last one of ya.
[CHIAKI] Hey, Noro, the
ball wasn't out of play.
Dammit! You tricked me!
[CLASS 1 GIRLS cheering]
[ALL]
Aww...
[MATSUURA] We don't want
Class 4 to lose, do we?
Let's get the boys fired up!
[CLASS 4 GIRLS]
Yeah!
[MATSUURA]
Ready. Go Class 4!
[CLASS 4 GIRLS] Go Class 4!
Go Class 4! Go Class 4!
[CHIAKI]
Kana's not part of that, is she?
There's no way
she'd cheer for me.
Then again, what did I expect?
We're broken up.
Why would she care?
[KANA]
Chiaki!
Quit screwin' around!
You can run faster
than that! Hurry it up!
[CHIAKI]
Jeez. What's her problem?
Is that supposed to
be cheering me on?
Hey. I'm talkin' to
you, you moron!
Chiaki!
[CHIAKI] Dammit, Kana,
you broke up with me.
You're not my
girlfriend anymore.
[CHIAKI] You really think
screaming that I'm a moron
at the top of your lungs
is going make me
want to get back together?
Well, it shouldn't, but it does!
It makes me wanna be
your boyfriend again!
Run! Chiaki!
[CHIAKI]
For you, Kana!
And save!
[CHIAKI]
No!
Ha! Nice try!
But a sucker like you isn't
gonna take me down! Ha-ha!
I wouldn't bet on it, Noro!
I work out every day!
You don't have a prayer!
Oh, yeah!
[ALL]
Go Pattie!
[PATRICIA]
High five! High five! Woo!
[ALL grumble]
[TEACHER A]
And last but not least,
be sure to keep your nose clean
and stay out of trouble.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am.
So hey,
is the soccer team gonna have
practice over the summer?
Uh, yeah. Pretty sure.
A bunch of us are all
planning to go to the beach.
It'd be great if you could come.
[SUGAWARA]
Hmm...
Depends on what coach says.
Takano is supposed to be there.
[gasps]
[TAKANO] The beach?
No thanks. That's not for me.
I'm shy about wearing
a bathing suit.
[YOSHINAGA]
I know. So am I.
But everybody's going.
Kamine, Goda, Pattie.
I'd really hate for
you to miss it.
I don't know. I'm not
really sure I'd like it.
Sugawara's going to come.
See ya!
[PATRICIA]
Bye!
Look, Kana. Chiaki's all
alone. Go make up with him.
Okay. Hey.
[SUGAWARA]
Hey, Chiaki?
You're going to the beach
with everybody, right?
[CHIAKI] Not sure yet.
But I was thinking about it.
If, uh, I came too,
would that be okay?
[CHIAKI]
Why not?
Matsuura told me that
Takano's going.
And I'm worried
that with me there,
things could get
a little awkward.
I live for awkward.
Please come.
Wait, so Sugawara's not coming?
[MATSUURA]
He said he didn't know,
that he'd have to ask
his soccer coach first.
Oh.
What about you? You and Takano
are in for sure, right?
Yeah!
[KANA]
You have do this, Kana.
If you try to meet Chiaki
once summer break starts,
it'll just be weird.
All right, I sent it.
Now will he stay?
[CHIAKI]
Crap. My battery's dead.
[TAKASE] ♪ I don't know,
but I've been told. ♪
[PLAYERS]
♪ I don't know... ♪
[SUGAWARA] I could go to
the beach if I wanted.
There's actually no
practice that day.
But if I do,
it'll get me thinking about
Takano all over again.
Even if I know she's
not interested.
Just come to the beach.
She doesn't know or care,
so why should you?
[SUGAWARA]
But that's just it.
Going when she doesn't care
would make me miserable.
[KANA]
It's not even marked as "read."
Oh, Chiaki. Did you
really go home?
Hey. Is it all right
if we practice?
What's the big rush, Sugawara?
I forgot something.
So are you gonna come
to the beach, or what?
Don't think so.
[YOSHINAGA] If Sugawara
doesn't come to the beach,
it'll suck, won't it?
[TAKANO]
What?
Will you be upset if he doesn't?
Do you still like him?
[YOSHINAGA]
Uh, no. Not anymore.
But I knew he didn't
have feelings for me,
so I never had a
chance to begin with.
Oh. I didn't realize that.
[YOSHINAGA]
What about you? Do you like him?
Me?
[KANA]
Guess Chiaki lost interest
in trying to patch things up.
[KANA]
Looks like he really left.
And I'll be spending this
summer by myself.
[YOSHINAGA]
Sorry. I shouldn't have asked.
Be right back. I'm gonna
run to the bathroom.
[TAKANO]
Okay.
Do I like Sugawara?
I am always thinking
about him lately.
[TAKANO] And if he doesn't
come to the beach,
I think I would be upset.
[footsteps]
Yoshinaga? Everything okay?
Took you long enough.
Were you doing something?
[KANA] I sent you a text.
Didn't you see it?
[CHIAKI gasps]
Sorry. Dead battery.
And I was waiting for you
so we could talk in person.
Why did you wanna talk?
Were you going to try
and fix things?
No. We've broken up.
What's done is done.
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
No. I left my wallet.
[SUGAWARA] What about you?
Practicing all alone?
Not alone. Yoshinaga's
in the bathroom.
Oh, I see.
[SUGAWARA]
Bye then!
Are you going to come
to the beach, Sugawara?
But if I'm being honest,
I didn't think you'd ever break
up with me no matter what I did.
I took you for granted.
If we were to pretend
that never happened
and try to go back to
the way things were,
it wouldn't be right.
I'd feel bad. Relationships
like that don't last.
So let's end it.
And once everything's
over and done with,
I wanna start again.
[SUGAWARA]
Oh, yeah, the beach trip.
Well, I kinda decided
I'm not going to go.
Why not? Soccer practice?
[SUGAWARA]
Nah.
The beach just really
isn't my thing, ya know?
But I heard you
were going, right?
I hope you have lots of fun.
I don't think I'll have any
fun if you're not there.
[KANA] Fine. Tell me
you have feelings for me.
I'll reject you a hundred times.
[CHIAKI]
Then I'll say it a 101.
You better mean it, understand?
[CHIAKI]
Okay.
I love you. You're more
than my best friend.
So please, will you
go out with me?
[KANA]
Okay.
If that's the case...
...then, I guess I'll
have to go to the store,
and buy a new swimsuit!
Yeah. Me, too.
[TAKANO, SUGAWARA]
And so, summer begins.