Morning, Kana.
[KANA]
Chiaki!
Why'd you ignore
my text yesterday?
I just didn't feel like it.
You're all, "So, what'cha
doin?" like every day.
[KANA]
Oh, shut your hole!
[CHIAKI]
Sorry!
[KANA] Chiaki and I have been
dating for almost a year now.
However, we still
haven't even kissed.
What? You two still
haven't kissed yet?
Well, no. But it's only been a
year. It's still early for that.
More like a bit late.
Hasn't Chiaki said
anything to you?
Not really. He's more like...
Man. I just totally
blew up the bathroom.
[KANA]
Seriously?
--You took a dump?
--Yeah. So?
Everybody poops!
There's a book about it!
[KANA]
You are such a two-year-old!
Now that I think about it,
it's more like we're
brother and sister.
Hey, Chiaki. We get
along okay, don't we?
Bang!
Uh! I've been shot!
Well, we're in sync,
that's for sure.
A hundred percent.
Are you happy with how
things are with us?
Relationship-wise?
What? Are you not?
I'm fine, it's just
sometimes I wish things
were more physical, ya know?
Ohh.
Ready to rumble?
I kid! I kid!
[KANA]
Ugh!
No! That's not what I
meant and you know it!
You could've said so
without smacking me.
You're so violent. It's awful.
You just wanna beat me up
for your own amusement!
I'm trying to be serious.
I'm talking about
kissing and stuff.
[CHIAKI] Hold up. Why
would you wanna go there?
It's not like we're dating.
Look, I know it's embarrassing,
but we're in a relation-- Wait.
What'd you say?
Yeah, why kiss me?
Wouldn't that just be
a waste of your time?
Save that stuff
for your boyfriend.
But... you're my boyfriend.
What? Who is?
You are.
Whoa! Back up a sec!
We're dating?
I told you I had feelings
for you last spring!
Don't you remember?
Hey, Chiaki. I just want
you to know, I like you.
Whatevs. I totally
like you more.
I thought we were
doing a bit. I'm sorry.
I knew something wasn't right.
You wouldn't even
try to hold my hand.
I figured maybe you were
embarrassed or something,
but I was okay with that.
Because you've always
been my best friend.
No matter what, you're
right there next to me.
We hang out all the time.
We make each other laugh.
We've always been close, but
I guess not that kind of close.
What? Kana, why are you crying?
[KANA]
Because, because...
I've been texting you
practically nonstop,
and smacking you and
horsing around with you...
...as if we were
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Except that we aren't.
[CHIAKI] Then let's be
boyfriend girlfriend.
Is this just another bit?
Hell no!
I've kinda thought about dating
you for a long time now.
But I couldn't tell how you
felt, so I didn't say anything.
But I really do like you.
Will you go out with me?
You mean that?
Absolutely.
I'll be texting you constantly.
Text all you want.
Can I still smack you around?
Sure. Go ahead.
Okay. Then why don't
we give it a try?
[CHIAKI]
Ha, ha! Psych!
That was another bit.
You idiot!
[CHIAKI]
Bad joke.
[MATSUURA] I told the guy
I had a crush on how I felt.
[MATSUURA]
It didn't go so well.
[MATSUURA] I'm gonna go
home and crawl into bed.
[KATORI] Matsuura!
You're not leaving are you?
Where are you going?
We've got club!
Is this sabotage?
Or just skipping? Both?
[MATSUURA]
I'm feeling a little sick
so I thought I'd go home early.
Really?
Because judging by
the look on your face,
I'd have guessed your
heart was broken.
[laughs]
No way!
Did I nail it?
I'm so sorry. My bad.
Should I not've said anything?
No. It's fine.
[KATORI] You told him
you liked him, right?
Yeah.
[KATORI] That took guts.
It's pretty awesome.
I guess.
Too bad he can't see you now.
You're beautiful when
you're embarrassed.
Are you messing with me,
Katori? What's going on?
I'm not messing with you.
I'm just trying to figure out
how to get you to stop crying.
You don't need to do that.
I'm not crying.
Oh, yes you are.
On the inside.
I didn't mean to
hit you that hard.
Hit me as hard as you want.
[MATSUURA]
Huh?
See, while you are
physically hitting me,
you really wanna hit yourself.
You are messing with
me. Knock it off.
I promise you, I'm not. Really.
And didn't beating me up
make you feel better?
[MATSUURA] Wait, Katori
did that on purpose?
Not that I'm going to thank him
for acting like a total jerk.
[KATORI] Anything else
you wanna take out on me?
I'm good for now, but why
do you even care so much?
I'm a senior. You're young and
naïve. I look out for you.
Now, think you can make club?
[MATSUURA]
Yeah.
Deep down, Katori is a nice guy.
Nice. But annoying.
[KATORI]
Great! Then let's get going.
Can't leave the club without
its resident "pretty boy."
[MATSUURA]
Really annoying.
What's up? Come on.
Nothing's up. Now
quit staring at me.
[KATORI]
Uh-oh.
You've fallen for
me haven't you?
Sorry for being so hot.
[KATORI] Huh? Something wrong?
Where's she going?
Am I a badass?
Oh, hi?
[YAMANE] My crush pulled me
aside, and asked to talk to me.
Would you like to have
lunch with me this weekend?
[YAMANE]
What? Why?
I wanted to thank
you for what you did
for me the other day.
I hope you don't
already have plans.
[YAMANE]
N-Nope. I'm free as a bird.
[KURIHARA]
Thank goodness!
Okay then, see you
Sunday afternoon!
[screams]
[YAMANE] Why is such a cute
girl asking out a guy like me?
[YAMANE]
Uh?
Did I get here too early?
[YAMANE] I've been secretly
in love with this girl
who takes the same bus as me,
but never been brave
enough to talk to her.
Then the other day--
[YAMANE]
A groper!
Oh good morning, Kurihara!
I didn't know you took this bus!
What a coinkydink!
Hey! How's up?
I mean, what's life
been treating you?
[YAMANE] I thought I'd
totally creeped her out.
I never imagined
she'd wanna thank me.
Wait, could I have imagined it?
'Cause there's no way
she'd 've asked me out.
Yup. Must've been all
in my mind. Case closed.
[KURIHARA]
Sorry I'm late.
[KURIHARA yelps]
[YAMANE] What the hell?
How could she be this cute?
Is something wrong? Why are
you staring at me like that?
Ah! No, I wasn't staring at all!
I don't think you're
cute or anything!
No! That's not what I meant!
I meant your outfit! I think
your outfit's cute! Well...
Don't stress so much, Yamane.
What do you wanna
eat? It's on me.
Eat?
[YAMANE]
What am I supposed to do here?
I know I shouldn't pick
something that's too pricey.
Maybe some cheap fast-food?
How about soba?
Would that work for you?
[KURIHARA]
Yeah! That sounds great.
There's a standing counter
right over there.
What would you like?
Actually, is it okay if
I pick the restaurant?
Uh, sure.
Go ahead and get
whatever you want.
Okay then.
Should we order
something to drink first?
Don't worry. I'll go home
immediately after we're done.
Not a problem.
Of course, it's not
that I want to go home!
I'd stay with you
forever if I could!
Oh, wait! That was creepy!
Forget I said that!
I'll go home as
soon as possible!
Please don't freak out!
[KURIHARA]
You probably didn't realize it,
but I actually noticed you
on the bus all the time.
[YAMANE]
What?
[KURIHARA]
If an elderly person gets on,
you always give them your seat.
[YAMANE]
Well, with a mug like mine,
ya kinda have to be a nice guy.
And the other day,
you came to my rescue when
that guy tried to, you know...
[YAMANE] Forgive me for
reminding you of it!
[YAMANE]
What the hell is wrong with me?
She asked me to lunch
and I'm ruining it!
Has anyone every told
you how funny you are?
[YAMANE] You mean my face?
Yeah, I get that a lot.
I think you have a lovely face.
[YAMANE]
Maybe during the Dark Ages,
but this is the 21st Century.
People can see!
She's got to be kidding.
Or maybe she's just
into dorky mascots.
Yamane.
[YAMANE] Why does she have such
a serious look on her face?
You've gotta be kidding!
This can't happen to me. No way!
Girls have ignored me for years.
Don't get your hopes up, Yamane!
Would you maybe want to...
[YAMANE] Don't hope! Don't
hope! You'll only regret it!
But what if she really is?
[KURIHARA]
...be my...
[YAMANE]
Wait, I'm not prepared for this!
[KURIHARA]
...boyfriend?
[WAITRESS]
Yes?
We'd like two sodas.
[TAKANO] The other person on
cleanup duty went home already.
This sucks.
[SUGAWARA]
Takano?
[TAKANO]
Oh. Hey, Sugawara.
[TAKANO] Sugawara and I
are in the same class.
Lately, we've been
talking a little.
[SUGAWARA]
You cleaning by yourself?
Why don't I help with that?
No. It's okay.
That's way too much
for one person.
I'll go get a broom.
[TAKANO]
He's a good guy.
What? Why are you
cleaning, Sugawara?
Practice is about to start.
I know. I won't be long.
Okay.
If there's something
else you have to do,
I don't wanna
keep you from it.
Don't worry. It's fine.
I'll go in a bit.
[TAKANO] Why is he so
determined to stay and help?
Does he like doing
school chores?
Or maybe he's a clean freak.
Do you help with
clean up duty a lot?
[SUGAWARA]
Uh, no. Not usually.
But, like, since it was you...
[TAKANO] Since it was me?
I don't understand.
Am I doing a crappy job
and he's afraid to tell me?
Sorry. I'll stop talking
and get back to work.
All right.
[SUGAWARA]
Did she just figure it out?
Just so you know, I didn't
mean anything weird.
Sorry if I made
you uncomfortable.
No. It's my fault for
not realizing earlier.
What do you think I should do?
What to do? I can't tell
you that. It's up to you.
[TAKANO]
Oh, I see. Never mind then.
But you are helping because
you saw me cleaning
and you noticed me, right?
Yeah, I've noticed
you too, Takano.
For a while now.
[TAKANO]
knew it.
I'm sorry.
I never really learned
the right way to do this.
That's okay.
I never learned about this
kinda thing either, but still,
moving forward,
what did you wanna do?
I'd like to get better at it.
Better at it? How?
I don't know. I just think
I could clean up better.
Clean up? That's ridiculous!
You're pretty just the way are!
If you say so.
But then what should I do?
Well, I've been
wanting to tell you--
No, it's probably best
not to rush things.
You take your time.
I'll wait for you.
[TAKANO] Does that mean
I'm cleaning too slowly?
[TAKANO] I'm sorry this
is taking me so long.
Don't apologize.
You did nothing wrong.
I shouldn't be in such a hurry.
But I'm glad you
know how I feel.
And maybe next time I see you,
you can tell me how--
No. You're right.
I'll learn to clean faster
now that I know the truth.
Thank you.
[SUGAWARA]
Hm?
Sorry. What?
It's hard to tell
people these things.
You're a nice guy to
be so honest with me.
Wait, honest about what?
How I need to get
better at cleaning.
Oh.
Right?
Oh, totally! Cleaning!
That's what we
were talking about.
[TAKANO laughing]
[CHAIKI, KANA] Next episode:
"Romantic Comedy."