[MOTOYAMA]
My name is Tomomichi Motoyama.
I am a nerd, who's not
remotely good-looking.
My friend asked me to
meet him behind the school.
I wonder what he could want.
What's up, Yamane?
Hey, Motoyama.
[MOTOYAMA]
Uh.
This sweet girl is Kurihara,
the kindly angel who has
shown affection for Yamane,
repellant though he is.
You guys are all alone
out here, Yamane.
Why did you want me to
come along and meet you?
Well, ya see, Kurihara
asked me to meet her here
and it's the first time
a girl's asked to meet me
behind the school.
I felt nervous
coming all by myself,
so that's why I asked you.
[MOTOYAMA]
Huh?!
So here we all are
behind the school.
What did you want from me?
[gasps]
Oh, I made too much
pudding the other day,
so I thought I would share it.
[MOTOYAMA] She's adorable.
What a flimsy excuse.
Oh. That's nice.
But you really shouldn't
have. I don't deserve it.
[MOTOYAMA]
Wha--?
Poor Yamane.
He's so hung up on
his own hideousness,
he has no idea what
she's trying to do.
Nonsense. Accept it with
the greatest of gratefulness.
I'm sure she made it
with you in mind.
Are you saying she's lying?
Of course she didn't!
Don't insult her like that.
[MOTOYAMA]
Yamane, you fool.
Maybe I'll have
better luck with her.
Kurihara, please excuse me.
I think perhaps I may have
interrupted something.
I'll just be on my way.
Uh. No, please. You can stay.
[MOTOYAMA]
What? You're chicken, too?
Yamane, Kurihara
made you pudding.
Accept it and say "thank you."
[YAMANE]
Huh?
But it wouldn't be fair
if only I get some.
Oh. No need to worry.
I brought two jars of it.
Wow! You brought two?
How 'bout that, Motoyama?
Are you in fact the stupidest
man on the planet?
She made that pudding for you!
[BOTH gasp]
What the heck are you
talking about now?
Kurihara made extra.
She's just being nice.
Open your eyes.
She asked you to meet
her behind the school.
She's not just being nice.
If you haven't noticed by now,
you're blinder than I am.
She obviously has
feelings for you.
What? That's ridiculous!
She only asked me back here
because rumors
would start flying
if she gave me pudding in
front of the whole school!
Little miss sugar is
offering you her sweets.
Accept it and take
the damn pudding.
How...? How could you?
You're being incredibly
disrespectful.
[MOTOYAMA yelps]
All right. Ya got me.
Point taken.
Huh? What?
How'd I "get you"?
I didn't push you that hard.
[MOTOYAMA] I can see
the writing on the wall.
Your lover has obviously become
more important to you than me,
your best friend.
Now then, if you don't mind,
I'll be on my way.
Yamane has made his choice.
You two enjoy your pudding.
No, Motoyama! Don't leave!
[KURIHARA]
Hang on.
[MOTOYAMA]
Please take a hint already!
My acting is so terrible,
it's embarrassing.
I'm trying to leave you alone!
Motoyama.
Next time, I'll make some
pudding for you, too, 'kay?
[MOTOYAMA] She's even more
caring than I imagined,
practically a saint!
Best of luck, you lovebirds.
I'll leave you to it.
Here ya go. I have to
hurry and get home now.
Thank you. I'll see you later.
[growls]
[GODA] I think my girlfriend's
been a little on edge lately.
Goda, you're strong.
Open this for me?
[GODA]
Here ya go.
Wow. Thanks. That
was easy for you.
[growls]
I wonder what's wrong.
Kamine, did I do something
lately that bothered you?
Uh, why do you ask?
I keep getting the sense that
you're somehow mad at me.
No. I'm not mad.
You've done nothing wrong.
Why would I be?
Okay then.
[PATRICIA]
Yo! Takeru!
Let's you and me arm wrestle!
You ready? One, two three.
[growls]
[GODA]
Despite what she said,
I'm certain she's angry
about something.
Hey! Goda!
[GODA]
I must've upset her.
I'll meet her at our
spot and apologize.
She's not here.
Is she running late?
[GODA] Is she blocking me or
something? She's that mad?
[KAMINE]
Guess who.
Kamine. It's you. You're here.
Of course. Did you
think maybe I went home?
More like I thought
you were blocking me
and you were done
with me forever.
Oh. So sorry you thought that.
I wanted to make
you worry a little,
but I guess I was
being a bit mean.
[GODA] You're so angry at me
that you're being mean to me?
I'm sorry, Kamine. We can
just go home if you want.
Don't you wanna stay
and hold hands with me?
I mean, you held hands
with Patricia in class.
[GODA]
Hm?
Did you not like that I arm
wrestled with Patricia?
Is that why you're so upset?
You could've told me.
You're my girlfriend. I'd have
arm wrestled with you, too.
That's not it! I don't
wanna arm wrestle with you.
In fact, that's kinda
the last thing I want.
What does that mean?
Forget it. You'd probably hate
me if I told you anyway.
So don't worry. I'm sorry
I troubled you.
There is nothing you could ever
do that would make me hate you.
Understand? I'm your
boyfriend. I love you.
You can always say
anything to me.
You-You really mean it?
Promise you won't hate me?
I won't.
Okay, then.
Don't be too friendly
with the other girls.
Starting today, call me "Ayaka."
And I don't blame Patricia.
She didn't know.
But going forward
I'm the only one
who gets to call you "Takeru."
And don't hold hands with other
girls, not even to arm wrestle.
You can only hold hands with
me. Just me and no one else.
You can help other girls open up
bottles if you really want to,
but if you're nice to them,
then you have to promise
to be even nicer to me!
[GODA]
So that's what it was.
I'm really needy and
demanding, aren't I?
[GODA] It's fine.
Just a little surprising.
It's not fine. I know I'm being
totally stupid and jealous.
[GODA]
Honestly, I don't mind.
Does that mean you'll
start calling me Ayaka?
Uh. Whatever you want.
Why not?
[CHIAKI]
It's been a while
since my girlfriend
and I started dating,
but we haven't even kissed yet.
I want to, but I don't know
how to make it happen.
Hey, Chiaki, stop for a sec.
What's up, Kana?
Something wrong?
You gotta poop?
No, dumb-dumb! Look over there!
[CHIAKI]
Uh...
Are those two Goda
and Kamine from class?
They're not super
"lovey-dovey" at school,
but they sure are here.
Um. Hey, Takeru.
Yeah, Kamine? What is it?
No. Gotta call me
by my first name.
[CHIAKI, KANA]
Didn't Kamine used to be shy?
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
Sorry about that, Ayaka.
Much better.
So what's up?
There wasn't anything.
I just wanted to hear
you say my name.
If you like hearing it,
then I'll say it as
much as you want me to.
Ayaka.
[CHIAKI, KANA] Since when is
Goda thoughtful and romantic?
I guess it's true. People do
change when they're in love.
You think so? I mean,
you and I haven't changed.
Kamin-- I mean Ayaka.
You've changed since
we started dating.
[KAMINE gasps]
Oh, no. Am I more annoying?
Not a bit. You're
even cuter now.
[CHIAKI] You're even
cuter now, too, Kana.
[KANA]
I'm gonna kill you, Chiaki.
We should get going, Kana.
I don't think I wanna
watch any more.
Yeah, we probably should go.
Then if you don't mind,
can I ask you for something?
[GODA]
Sure.
I kinda... wanna kiss you again.
[BOTH gasp]
You mean right now?
Oh. Do you not want to?
[CHIAKI]
Why would he?
It's broad daylight and they're
in public. Is she nuts?
[KANA]
Seriously!
Of course I want to.
[BOTH gasp]
Does kissing actually
work like that?
She says she wants to and he
just goes right in and does it?
No. I think Goda's
got the right idea!
He takes the initiative,
whereas, you don't.
Hey! You're not being fair!
Goda! What was that?
You went before I was ready!
[GODA]
Oh? You weren't?
Goda--
I mean, Takeru, you always
kiss me without warning.
[GODA]
Uh. Sorry.
Well, now it's my turn.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHIAKI, KANA]
No way!
See that?
Kamine was brave enough
to kiss her boyfriend.
Are you saying it's all on me?
What? There's nothing wrong with
a girl making the first move.
Good grief. Come on
and grow a pair already!
We'll do it right next
time. No more surprises.
Yeah.
Guess there's no sense
in fighting it, is there?
Nope. Don't think so.
Did you want to just kiss
me and get it over with?
Uh. I'm okay with
doing it if you are.
Okay. On the count
of three, we kiss.
On the count of three.
One, two, three, go.
[KAMINE] Hey, look!
It's Chiaki and Kana.
Hey, Goda! Hey, Kamine!
What a surprise.
[GODA] Yeah. What are you
and Kana doing here?
Oh. Just passing by.
What were you and Kamine up to?
We, um...
...were also passing by.
[BOTH]
What a coincidence!
[CHIAKI] I invited
Kana over after school.
Hey, Mrs. Uchimura!
[CHIAKI]
Uh, she's not here. No one is.
Huh?
[CHIAKI] I'm finally
gonna kiss my girlfriend!
Yeah. My family's
away on vacation.
So you can stay all
night long if you want to.
[CHIAKI]
Or maybe we'll go even further.
Well, Mom said I have
to be home by eight.
Oh, okay.
[KANA] Dammit, Chiaki.
We still haven't even kissed.
I mean, I assumed maybe
we would make out,
but not more than that.
[KANA sighs]
[KANA] Crap. Did I put on my
good bra and undies today?
[CHIAKI] I have till eight.
I have till eight. All right!
So, uh, wanna study
for the physics test?
[KANA]
Sure. Good idea.
Uh, d'ya think I should I
turn on the air conditioner?
Yeah. Why not? I guess
it is warm in here.
[CHIAKI]
What am I doing?
I decided to make a move
today and I meant it!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Ki-Ki-i--
Kinematics, you think
that'll be on the test?
Maybe.
Ki-Kinetic Energy, too?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it will.
[CHIAKI]
Uh! It's getting late!
Wow. Studying hard
sure makes you thirsty.
I'm gonna get us
something to drink.
[KANA]
Oh. Okay.
[CHIAKI] I'm about to
strike out yet again.
Why can't you just
go for it, Chiaki?
You're running out of time!
[KANA] Where is he?
We don't have much time.
To make it home at eight,
I have to leave by seven.
Then again, I do want the mood
to be right for our first kiss.
And these things
can't be rushed.
[burps]
What's wrong with you, Chiaki?
Nothing's wrong with me.
What happened to the drinks?
And why's your face all red?
Kana, kiss me. You know
you really want to.
[KANA]
He reeks!
Kana--
Hold on a sec!
Did you get drunk downstairs?
I'm not gonna kiss you
like this! You're wasted!
But you keep saying you want
me to show some initiative.
That doesn't mean I wanted you
to go and get totally smashed!
Our first kiss is supposed
to be something
that both of us
remember forever.
Kana!
Back off! Get away!
Listen to me. I do wanna
kiss you, Chiaki.
But I wanna kiss the
normal you, not this.
I don't need a pretty setting,
and the mood doesn't
have to be perfect.
None of that matters.
All I want is a regular
kiss with the real you.
You're absolutely right.
I shouldn't be drunk
when I kiss you.
Chiaki.
[CHIAKI]
Psych! It was all an act!
Huzzah! I finally
kissed my girlfriend!
[KANA]
You're despicable.
[CHIAKI grunts]
Why ya bein' all serious-like?
Come on. Ya gotta play along.
Next time why don't you
start by acting like
you're getting attacked
by an evil space alien?
Or how about you just
scored on a penalty kick
and won the big game?
Ow, that hurt.
I'm going home.
Why? Are you actually upset?
I was just doing a new bit.
Didn't ya like it?
I'm done. I'm so done
with this duo!
What did she say?
If that was a set-up for
a joke, I don't get it.
Kana?
[TAKANO, SUGAWARA]
Next episode: "Tuning."