[CHIAKI] My girlfriend found
my stash of American porn,
of all things.
Uh, hey, Kana,
aren't we supposed to
be studying for exams?
Ha! "Study," my ass!
Obviously this is the reason you
asked me to come over today!
No. That's not true at all.
If you're that
desperate and horny,
then let's just do it!
Don't you think
it's way too early
to be taking things
to this level?
Things aren't gonna go anywhere
if you never make a move.
We haven't even kissed.
That's not my fault.
The mood's never
been exactly right.
What are you, chicken?!
[CHIAKI]
H-Huh?!
Chicken?
Who the hell are you calling
"chicken"? I'm not scared!
Then get your butt over here
and let me give you a hickie!
Okay.
[CHIAKI]
Kana's got pretty big boobs.
I really wanna squeeze 'em.
This means I can, right?
Okay. Here goes.
Aren't you gonna kiss me first?
Wait, never mind,
forget I said that!
No, no! You're right!
We should go in order!
[CHIAKI]
I have no clue what I'm doing.
How do other people handle this?
[CHIAKI]
Just start with a kiss.
She said that's what
she wanted anyway.
How's my breath?
Are my lips chapped?
Am I sweaty? Did I put on
boxers or briefs today?
Should I have shaved my
chest? What if I fart?
Wait, I gotta poop.
You just pooped a minute ago!
Quit stalling already!
I only wanted to make
sure I was prepared!
They say that you're
not supposed to try
and rush this stuff, ya know?
And like, just because
we're dating,
doesn't mean we have
to jump into bed.
[CHIAKI yelps]
[CHIAKI] Kana, a lady
shouldn't be so quick
to take her clothes off
in front of a man.
Shut up, you moron.
I don't just wanna
make out with you.
I want more than that.
I wanna be closer to you and
to learn more about you.
And I want for you
to really know me too.
I just want us to have
an intimate connection!
Kana.
[KANA]
Close your eyes!
They're shut.
If you want me to know you,
then why can't I look?
[KANA] Shut up, you perv.
Go turn the lights off.
Just so you know, I don't
have that good of a body.
And I didn't get a chance
to shower today,
so I might be a little sweaty.
You looked smokin' hot when
I caught a glimpse a second ago.
[KANA]
Idiot!
Ow! Hey, that was
a compliment, Kana!
Wait! We can't do this.
I just realized I don't
have any protection.
[KANA] Don't worry
about that. It's fine.
No, it isn't!
I'll go run out real
quick and buy some.
[KANA]
Wait.
You don't have to. My mom
made me bring some with me.
They're in my bag.
Oh.
So then, I guess we're all set.
[KANA]
Hey. Chiaki.
I love you.
And I love you, too. Kana.
[KEIKO] Chiaki! I brought some
snacks for you and Kan--
Oh, boy, I should've knocked.
I'll just leave these
here for you kids.
You can eat them
when you're done.
Honey! Don't come upstairs
right now, okay?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
My family's the same way.
Should we pick up
where we left off?
Yeah.
I love you.
[KEIKO] Kana, did you take
your pill today, dear?
D'ya need one of mine?
Really, Mom?!
[KAJI] The student council
president caught me smoking,
but instead of turning
me in, he kissed me.
Now we're dating, but only
on condition that I quit.
Damn, I want a cigarette.
Wait a sec, why the hell
am I doing this to myself?
[KAJI]
I didn't agree to it.
I never even said
I'd go out with him.
Hello, Kaji.
Was there something
that you needed from me?
Listen to me.
You may know my weakness, but
I won't let use it against me.
Like when I pay you a
compliment and make you blush?
No! My smoking you moron!
I never agreed to
quit or date you!
Oh. Well then, let's
make it official.
Hell no! One kiss does
not mean we're dating.
We've kissed twice.
[KAJI]
Whatever!
It's not like that was even
my first kiss or anything.
If you think you can get a girl
that easily, you've got--
I'm going to win your heart.
Tell-Tell me why you're
interested in me.
[AKAGI] Let's start
with physical intimacy.
Come here.
I don't want a hug!
Why do you want to go out with
me? Do you even like me?
I can't say that I don't.
You're such a liar!
How can you like
someone you barely know?
You have a point.
I don't know that
much about you.
Well, duh. Told ya so.
Other than all I've
observed at school.
Like what?
[AKAGI]
You don't have many friends.
You're always sleeping in class.
You don't do any after
school activities,
so you could go home, but you
stay and smoke instead.
I caught you out
here on purpose.
You've been on my
mind for a while.
Because what,
you thought I'd let you
sleep with me if you asked?
[AKAGI]
Mh-hm.
You seemed lonely.
So I figured you'd throw
yourself at the first guy
who paid you any
kind of attention.
As it turned out, I was right.
Had I been a player, you
would've been played.
Still...
Even though you're skinnier
than my usual type, I--
[KAJI]
I knew it!
You walk around like you're
all high and mighty,
but deep down you're
a horny bastard!
Yes, I find you attractive
and would sleep with you
if I could.
I see. Then why don't
we just get on with--?
That's why I wanted to
make you my girlfriend
before someone came and
took advantage of you.
Your girlfriend? Dude,
what are you talking about?
[AKAGI]
I want you to be mine, Kaji.
Let go of me! You're the
student council president!
You could have any
girl that you want!
So why me?
[AKAGI]
Probably because I like you.
What do you mean, "probably"?
Honestly, I don't know.
I've never felt this way
about anyone before.
This has to be love, right?
If not, you tell me what it is.
How the hell should I know?
Then why don't we
find out together?
If that's all right
by you, of course.
I'm not going to force you.
[KAJI]
I, uh--
What do you say? D'ya wanna try?
I wasn't really looking
to date anyone, but I--
But you what?
I'm, uh, I'm not sure.
Just say, "Yes, Akagi."
It looked so cute and fluffy...
[FURUYA]
Minagawa told me she liked me
and asked me to go out with her.
But I've been putting off giving
her an answer for months now.
[FURUYA] I really should
give her an answer.
[MINAGAWA]
Hey there, Furuya.
I've waited long enough.
Are you ready to finally
give me an answer?
But class is about to
start; we can't talk.
That's fine.
See? Now we can
message each other.
So you gonna answer or what?
Please don't say it like that.
When you do, it feels like
you're just playing
with me again.
Sorry, sorry. I'm going to
try and ask more seriously.
What is your answer?
Well, Minagawa. The thing is...
--I, um...
--That's a "no," isn't it?
All right then, if
you're not interested,
I'll stop bugging you.
That's not true, Minagawa.
It's not that I'm
not interested.
I just can't seem to
get the words out.
Are you trying to mess
with me now, Furuya?
Because saying "yes"
or "no" isn't hard.
I swear, I wasn't.
[MINAGAWA]
Forget it. I give up.
Class is about to
start anyway. Bye.
[FURUYA]
H-Huh...? What just happened?
I didn't think she would
give up so easily.
Then again, what if
this is a ploy?
What if she's acting and
wants me to try to stop her?
[FURUYA]
Idiot! Stupid, stupid Furuya!
I made her wait too long.
Maybe I should try talking
to her after class.
She's been pining for me for
months, she might regret it.
She's not gonna
regret it, is she?
She didn't give up.
She lost interest.
Can't say that I blame her.
I'm so indecisive.
[FURUYA]
How could she tell?
Wait, wasn't she
was angry at me?
[screams]
[MINAGAWA] "Just kidding. I felt
like teasing you a little.
I'm not in any hurry for
an answer. Besides..."
[FURUYA]
"Actually never mind."
[MINAGAWA]
Ah! Thank goodness!
He was actually staring at me.
[TAKANO] My friend, Yoshinaga,
handed me a love letter today.
And begged me to
deliver it for her.
[TAKANO]
Sugawara?
Yeah. What?
I hate to do this in
the middle of exams,
but we need to talk.
Can you make time after school?
Yeah. Totally!
That's no problem at all!
If you need me, I'm there!
[TAKANO]
He really is a nice guy.
[SUGAWARA]
A letter? For me?
[TAKANO]
Mh-hm.
Wow. I mean, thank you.
I never thought you'd
write me a letter.
[TAKANO]
I didn't. That's from Yoshinaga.
Oh, that's so nice
of her. I'm flattered.
I just thought...
She asked me to give it to you,
wait while you read it,
and then go back and
give her your answer.
Don't worry. I won't
make you wait long.
I know that this must be
pretty awkward for you.
That's very considerate.
You're so nice, Sugawara.
Please tell her I'm sorry,
but I'm not interested.
There's someone else I like.
There's someone else?
Have you told her how you feel?
[SUGAWARA] Yeah, I confessed
I had feelings for her,
but she kinda didn't notice.
I didn't realize
that could happen.
You gonna try again?
[SUGAWARA]
Not sure.
She seems to think of me
as just "a nice guy."
She sounds like someone
who's a lot like me.
[SUGAWARA]
Then maybe you can help me.
What if I told you I
had feelings for you?
Oh, I'd tell you "No way."
I don't know the first thing
about being in a relationship.
You wouldn't have
fun dating me at all.
Yeah. That's what I think
she might say, too.
Seriously? Wow.
Sounds like a pain.
Got any suggestions?
Maybe you should try
something that's more obvious
and super hard to miss.
Like make a move on her.
What if you tried putting
your arms around her
and whispering in her ear?
You know, like they
do in the movies.
So then, if someone did that
stuff to you, you'd like it?
Of course not. It's creepy.
I figured.
But you're a nice guy, Sugawara.
So it might be okay
if you did it.
Want more ideas?
Then we should
be getting home.
Come on. We've got
more exams tomorrow.
Yeah. We need to study.
[SUGAWARA] I've decided to
give up on telling my crush
I have feelings for her.
Oh? How come?
[SUGAWARA]
I'd rather just stay friends
than risk losing her completely.
Like you said, if I tried
making a move on you,
it might scare you off.
Why does it matter that
it could scare me off?
I'm not the girl you like.
[SUGAWARA] If you'd be
creeped out, so would she.
So it's hopeless.
Was it a mistake for me
to have told you that?
Not at all. Your input
was really helpful.
And about my answer
to Yoshinaga's letter,
I'll tell her myself tomorrow.
Really?
You may have been the messenger,
but she had the courage
to say how she felt.
And I have a lotta
respect for that.
That's sweet.
[TAKANO] Sugawara is
so kind and thoughtful.
He really is a good guy.
If I was the one he wanted
to put his arms around...
I like you.
[TAKANO]
...I wouldn't mind.
But that'll never happen.
[GODA, KAMINE] Next episode:
"Watching You From Afar."