[HOTARU] Furuya's been
smiling a lot lately.
I bet it's a girl.
[HOTARU] Bathroom's free,
Furuya. Your turn.
Mom says remember not
to take too long.
[FURUYA]
Okay.
[HOTARU] Now then, let's see
what big brother's been up to.
Passcode is still his birthday.
Oh, Furuya, so careless.
Yuki Minagawa. Ha! I knew it.
Evil witch, seducing my innocent
brother. I will make you suffer!
[FURUYA] "Sorry, but can you
please stop talking to me now?
I'm trying to study,
and it's very distracting."
Oh! It's Hotaru!
[MINAGAWA] "What? Why?
Did I do something wrong?
Is it because of,
well, you know,
'what happened' the other day?"
[HOTARU]
"What happened"?
Did she do something
to piss him off?
Bet she did.
Wouldn't surprise me.
[FURUYA]
"It is."
[MINAGAWA] "But what
happened only happened
because you wanted to."
[HOTARU]
"Wanted to"? Wanted to what?
Did he ask her to help with
his homework or something?
Whatever. I'll just
pretend to be mad.
[FURUYA] "I don't care anymore.
Forget it. It didn't matter."
[MINAGAWA] "You're despicable!
It was my first time!
How could you say that?"
[HOTARU] I'm totally lost.
First time doing what?
Let's see,
something that would've
been the first time for her
that he would've wanted.
Oh! That must be it!
[FURUYA]
"What's the big deal about me
wanting to go out on a date?
Everybody dates.
Besides, it was my first time
going out with
someone else, too."
Adorable! She doesn't
get it at all!
[MINAGAWA]
"Hmph.
So does that mean our date
didn't mean anything to you?"
Just as I thought.
No wonder he came home
late the other day.
He was with her!
[FURUYA]
"Nothing."
[MINAGAWA]
"And I suppose sleeping with me
meant nothing, too?"
Huh...?
[HOTARU] They like took a
nap together? Is that it?
Sleeping on a date? Really?
My big brother is so weird.
[FURUYA]
"All we did was sleep."
[MINAGAWA] "Then how did I
end up carrying this baby?"
[HOTARU]
Huh?
She is what?!
[HOTARU]
But-But--
A guy and a girl need to
have sex to make babies.
And there is no way my
brother would do that.
[FURUYA] "Are you
absolutely sure it's mine?
What proof do you
have that it is?"
"I haven't slept
with anyone else.
O-N-L-Y you."
[screams]
[HOTARU]
This can't be true!
Furuya's only in high school.
What the--?
Hey, Hotaru, what are you
doing with my phone?
Mom! Mommy!
Okay?
What did she do?
[HOTARU] Mom! Furuya and
some girl made a baby!
I did what now?!
[GODA] I'm in a relationship
with this girl in my class.
After a while, the feelings
just get stronger. You know?
But I'm not sure what that means
or what I'm supposed to do now.
Kamine, do you like
spending time with me?
What? Yes. Of course I do.
Uh. Good.
I'm still not great
at relationship stuff.
So let me know if there's
anything I can do better.
Well, there is one thing.
Something wrong?
Oh, no. I'm fine. It's
nothing like that. Really.
It's just, I think I understand
what you've been feeling,
and all I want is
to hear you say it.
I want you to tell me
that you love me.
Sorry, Goda.
I didn't mean to put you
on the spot like that.
[GODA]
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
But you already know,
so why bother?
That's true.
And I do feel kinda
silly for asking,
but I still wanna hear it.
You're right, Kamine.
Please forgive me.
The reason that I'm quiet
is because I'm not very
good at expressing
what's on my mind.
But I'm going to be
better from now on.
No, "from now on"
isn't what I meant.
[GODA] I'm confused.
When did you mean?
Um, well, now might
be a good time.
Oh, I see now.
You need me to prove it.
I should make a
show of good faith.
Uh. I don't think
you understand.
Help me, then. What can
I do to show you I care?
What if, maybe,
I took you somewhere?
We haven't had our first
actual date, yet.
Would that make you happy?
Listen to me! I don't want
you to take me on a date!
[GODA]
What?!
I want one simple thing.
In your own words,
say that you love me!
But why?
Because I can tell that you do,
but you still
haven't said it yet.
[GODA]
I-I haven't?
Going on a date would be nice,
but hearing you say "I love
you" means a lot more.
All right. Here goes.
Wait. No, don't.
But you said you wanted me to.
[KAMINE]
But you don't want to.
I'm pretty much
making you say it.
So forget it. I'm sorry
I made things complicated.
[GODA]
No. It's okay.
About that date though,
if the offer is still go--
[GODA]
I love you, Kamine.
I mean it. Kamine, I love you.
And I'm not saying it
because you asked me to,
I'm saying it because, well...
I love you!
I do. From the very
bottom of my heart.
I love you!
I'm sorry.
I know I should've
told you a lot sooner,
but I'm just a big, dumb jock.
What's wrong now?
Your face is red.
Are you angry at me?
[TAKASE] "You know those
people who confess by text?
I think that's pretty lame.
Okay, good night!"
[KANDA]
"I'm interested in you, Takase.
Sorry to tell you like
this, but I like you.
Please go out with me."
[TAKASE] We had a texting snafu
and now things are awkward.
Kanda.
Minagawa! How was
your English test?
Huh? I had an English test?
[TAKASE]
This is so, so bad.
[TAKASE] I wonder if she read
the message I sent after.
Maybe I should send it again.
No, I should tell her
in person, not by text.
But she won't talk
to me. What do I do?
[TAKASE]
Uh... Hello?
Sorry. I'm a little curious.
[TAKASE]
Oh, yeah? About what?
Well, I'm pretty, so I'm not
clever enough to elucidate,
but you, you look just like I
once did, ya heart-breaker.
[TAKASE] Okay. That was odd.
Who is this guy?
Listen, pal, I'm flattered
and all, but not interested.
It's a girl, and
things got messed up?
[TAKASE]
Wha--?
Hey! How'd you know?
I didn't, but like I said,
you remind me of me.
And I, too, have left many a
woman devestated and in tears.
[TAKASE] Hang on. I haven't
left that many in tears.
But you did make her cry, right?
The last one in the world
you wanted to hurt.
[gasps]
[TAKASE] Maybe I should ask
this guy for some advice.
You want my help, don't you?
Do I look like a dating master?
[gasps]
Well, I am.
A dating... What?
Never heard of one.
[KATORI]
Ah. Seeing you takes me back.
So many days like a lost puppy,
wandering in the rain.
What am I supposed to do?
I screwed up. And now,
she won't even talk to me.
No clue. I'm dumb.
I've got no idea
what to tell you.
But I would go to her,
wrap my arms around her,
hold her tight,
and never let her go.
[TAKASE]
Wow!
You know, I think you
might be on to something.
Then isn't there somewhere
else you need to be right now?
Hey, uh, thank you
for the advice and all.
I really appreciate it.
I gave you advice?
What advice? I don't recall any.
I just prattle on about myself.
A dumb, pretty-boy, pleebs like
to call: The Dating Master.
Teach me your ways.
Now, now. Hurry up
and go to her.
Catch her before she leaves.
Right! I will!
But before I do, will you
tell me who you are?
[TAKASE]
No!
[KATORI]
See ya!
[TAKANO] Lately, I've been
feeling kinda listless.
And I find myself staring
at random things in class.
[TAKANO] Something in my chest
hurts a little bit, too.
Takano, are you all right?
Uh. Oh, sorry.
You've been acting weird
recently. Are you sick?
Yeah. I've got something.
[TAKANO]
And I don't know why,
but I keep thinking
about Sugawara.
I can't seem to stop.
It's strange. This has never
happened to me before.
[TAKANO]
I think I may be sick.
[heart beating]
[TAKANO] My heart's
pounding. I know I'm sick.
Oh. Takano. Is something wrong?
Yeah. I feel like
I have a fever.
What about you? What happened?
Not much. I, uh, hurt
myself at practice.
Where's the nurse? Do you know?
Oh. She left a few minutes ago.
So she's gone?
Yeah.
Uh, do you like being
on the soccer team?
Yeah. I guess so.
[TAKANO]
What am I doing?
I can't make small talk like
this. My head is spinning.
I should try to focus and carry
on a better conversation.
Hey, Takano.
Do you need to have your
temperature taken or something?
[gasps]
Oh. That's right I did.
I think I might have
a little fever.
Oh. I hope it's not bad.
Well, I should get
back to practice.
Wait. Don't go.
What? How come?
[TAKANO]
Uh...
I don't know.
That came out wrong.
I mean, I don't know where
the thermometer is?
Oh, okay. I'll go
get it for you.
I'm sorry.
You had such a red
face when you said that,
I thought you might
have been blushing.
[gasps]
Really? My face was
actually that red?
[SUGAWARA] Yeah.
At least, compared to usual.
But I wasn't--
Or I didn't mean to.
[SUGAWARA]
I know you weren't.
You aren't the kind of girl
who would get lovesick.
It's new. State-of-the-art.
Supposed to only
take five seconds.
Oh, yeah?
I really hope you aren't sick.
Me, too.
[TAKANO] But... what does
it mean if I'm not?
If a fever didn't make my
face red then what did?
[thermometer beeping]
[TAKANO]
It's normal.
Looks like I do have
a slight temperature.
Seriously? You should
go home right away.
[COACH A]
Water break's over, boys!
[SUGAWARA] I better be
getting back to practice.
'Kay.
[SUGAWARA]
Get well soon.
Thank you.
[TAKANO] If it's not a fever,
then what is it?
[KATORI, HOSOGAWA] Next episode:
"Bruised-Up Angel."