[SWIM TEACHER]
All right, last safety check
before we hit the pool.
If you think you
might be sick...
[TAKANO]
During swim class,
whenever I look over at
Sugawara, our eyes meet.
Almost like he was
looking back at me.
It seems like it's
been happening a lot.
Is it just a coincidence?
Or was he...?
No. There's no way he'd
actually be looking at me.
[SUGAWARA] Takano just caught
me staring at her again.
I have to stop, or
she'll get creeped out.
But I can't help it.
She looks so cute
in her swimsuit.
I can't take my eyes off her.
[gasps]
[SWIM TEACHER]
Okay. Time for warms-ups.
Here we go: One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
[TAKANO]
But if Sugawara wasn't looking,
then why do we keep
making eye contact?
Maybe he's looking
at someone else?
[SUGAWARA]
Crap. We locked eyes again.
Now she knows I'm
staring at her.
I guess I should say "hi"
instead of trying to
pretend nothing happened.
[chuckles]
[groans]
[TAKANO] He just waved at
someone. I wonder who.
It doesn't look like anybody
waved back to him.
Unless... Was he waving at me?
That was embarrassing.
[SUGAWARA] What should I do?
Should I apologize?
Yeah. I'll tell her
I'm sorry after class.
[TAKANO] He wasn't looking at
me. He couldn't have been.
I feel stupid for waving back.
It wasn't meant for me.
[SUGAWARA]
But the longer I leave it,
the worse things could get.
I'll try to do it quick,
and not make a big deal.
[TAKANO] I think I'll ask him
who he was looking at
so that next time
I don't get confused.
[SWIM TEACHER]
Two at a time on my mark. One...
Hey, so... I'm sorry about
what happened back there.
What are you sorry for?
Well, you caught me
staring a few times.
And I didn't mean
for it to be weird.
Oh, no. You're fine.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
Wait. You interrupted something?
Yeah.
You were trying to
look at another girl
and I got in the way, right?
Was she behind me?
Or was it the pretty
girl next to me?
No. It was you.
[TAKANO]
Uh... What did he just say?
[SWIM TEACHER] C'mon, Takano!
You're holding everyone up.
Oh. Sorry!
[TAKANO]
So it was me.
He was actually
staring at me? Why?
Sure, I'm in a swimsuit,
but my body's not that great.
There's nothing to
look at. So why?
And why does the thought
of him looking at me
make my heart race?
Hey, Sugawara.
I think maybe...
I noticed you staring
because I was looking at you.
That's nice.
But I'm not Sugawara.
[SUGAWARA]
I told her.
Did you want me to pass that on
to him next time I see him?
[TAKANO]
Mh-mh...
Forget it.
[KANDA]
I told Takase that I like him,
and ever since then,
things have been awkward.
If he doesn't like me,
I can give up on dating him,
but I hope we can go
back to being friends.
Still, I'd rather be his
girlfriend if I could.
[bell chimes]
[TAKASE] It's been a month since
Kanda texted that she liked me.
I haven't be able to
say I like her back.
When I try to talk to
her, she avoids me.
And when I tried to message her,
this was her only reply.
Should I keep at it,
even though she doesn't seem
to wanna talk to me?
Would that just be annoying?
Can I tell her how I really feel
about her? Or is it too late?
[KANDA]
I'll apologize to him.
I'll say I'm sorry and
everything will be normal again.
Here goes.
[KANDA]
Oops! Dropped my eraser.
Here. I got it.
Uh. Thank you.
How are you?
Oh. I've been okay.
[KANDA] This is weird.
How do I talk to him?
I know I used to.
[TAKASE] Okay, it didn't feel
like she avoided me that time,
but maybe it's nothing.
Crap is--
I mean, class is starting.
[KANDA]
You try to say something to him,
and that's what comes out?
Hey, Kanda?
What's wrong with you?
Did I do something?
No. It's me. I'm sorry.
What? No. It's okay.
I'm sorry, too.
No, no. Everything was my fault.
[TAKASE]
No, really, it was me.
No, no, no! It was
totally me! I'm sorry!
I've been meaning to apologize,
but the timing just
never seemed right.
It's okay. There's somethin'
I've been meaning to say, too.
[KANDA] I can talk to him!
I can be honest with him!
Please, don't worry about it.
I don't really care anymore.
[KANDA] Wait. That may
have come out wrong.
It almost sounded like I
don't like him anymore.
But maybe it'll be
easier to make up
and go back to being friends
if he thinks that I'm over him.
So you really don't
care anymore?
Is that what you're telling me?
[gasps]
[KANDA] Is he asking
because he's relieved?
Or is he disappointed?
But if there's still a
chance, I have to take it.
Um. Would you...?
If it's fine with you, Kanda.
[chuckles] Yeah,
let's be friends again.
[grunts]
Sure. Love to.
That's a great idea. Really.
It's just that, uh...
[KANDA]
Huh?
That's what I wanted, too,
and I'm so happy about it.
Great. I'm so glad.
[KANDA]
If he's happy, I'm happy.
[TAKASE]
Ah! It's too late!
Why couldn't I have just told
her how I felt about her?
[KANDA] Guess I was being set up
to get friend-zoned all along.
I'm glad I didn't
lose him completely,
but now I'm not sure how I feel.
Now that things are back to
normal, can we hang out again?
Sure. I'd like that.
[chuckles]
[KAMINE]
The other day in the park,
my boyfriend and I
had our first kiss.
But it happened so out of
the blue that I choked.
Who on Earth coughs
on their first kiss?
I wanna kiss him again.
And this time, I'll do it right!
[GODA] Kamine's been acting
a little weird lately.
She's got this look on her face
like she wants to say something,
but she never does.
Is it about that kiss? Is she
mad that I did it so suddenly?
Was it too soon to
have done it at all?
[KAMINE] I wonder if Goda is
planning to kiss me again today.
Maybe I should ask him.
[GODA]
Of course she's mad.
It's not like she ever
asked me to kiss her.
She must be upset about it.
[KAMINE] I really hope he tries
to kiss me like that again.
I don't wanna have to ask
him to. That'd be weird.
[GODA] I can't be impulsive
like that. Not ever again.
Hey, we're back at the park.
And look, Goda, it's empty.
Nobody's here.
Nope. Not a soul.
Just the two of us.
We're the only ones here.
That we are.
It kinda reminds me of
the last time we were here.
That time when we kissed.
Wanna go somewhere else, then?
No. I'm fine.
But doesn't this
place bother you?
Why would it bother me?
I love being here in the park.
Don't you like it here, Goda?
Doesn't it make you
wanna, you know?
Nah. I'm good. We don't
need to go any further.
Oh. Well, I'm happy if you are.
Yeah. Happy!
[KAMINE]
Darn.
It doesn't look like he's
gonna go for it today.
Maybe I didn't set
the right mood.
[GODA] She seems pretty anxious
I might try something again.
I should be careful
or she'll think I want her
for the wrong reasons.
Oh, boy. Today was exhausting.
I'm already sleepy.
Wanna go home?
No. I just wanna shut
my eyes for a bit.
Okay.
[GODA]
She's laying there?
[KAMINE] I can't believe it.
My head's in his lap!
My heart's beating so
fast it might explode!
But if this is what it takes to
get him in the mood, so be it.
[breathing heavily]
[KAMINE]
Oh my gosh. He's sleeping!
He's actually sleeping!
I suppose he must be
tired from practice.
Guess another kiss
isn't in the cards.
[GODA gasps]
Whoops, sorry.
Dozed off for a sec.
Good thing I woke up.
I nearly got ya in the face.
Are you all right, Kamine?
What is it?
Is something wrong?
[KAMINE squeals]
[FURUYA] So, Minagawa, the
other class rep for our grade
has been telling me she
likes me for months.
I like you.
Please, Minagawa.
Are you serious or not?
[gasps]
Definitely not.
You're not? So you've been
kidding me this whole time?
Wha--? No! I'm not joking.
Don't misunderstand.
I do like you, Furuya.
That's the honest truth.
But this is not
me being serious.
[FURUYA]
Huh? I don't get it.
[MINAGAWA cackles]
You have not seen serious
yet. Not even close.
But guys prefer "light
and fluffy," don't you?
[FURUYA] Depends on what you're
calling "light and fluffy"?
Usually it's something like:
"Hey, you, you're
so totes adorable."
So you are messing with me.
I like you.
Now see that one was more of a
"You look so cute
when you're mad."
How am I supposed to
finally answer you
when you act like you're
playing some kinda game?
Wait, you were finally going
to give me an answer?
Well, I never intend on
dragging this thing out forever,
so yeah.
Then I shall seriously listen.
But I can't talk
to you seriously
unless you're serious about me.
If you really think that you
can handle me being serious,
then fine, I'll be
completely serious.
[MINAGAWA yells]
Hey! You're making a
joke out of it already!
I'm not trying to, but this
isn't easy for me either.
Hmm. Okay.
You ready?
Yes.
I like you.
And... I like you, too
Sorry. I take it back.
That one was actually more of a
"I also like your serious face"
kind of "I like you."
Being completely
serious is really hard.
[FURUYA]
Oh? Was it?
I didn't think it was that hard.
I like you.
I like you!
I don't know. None of
them feels right.
It's not coming out
how I really mean it.
Maybe I just can't
say it in words.
I'm not sure I understand.
Quick. Close your eyes.
Close my eyes?
Just do it.
I can't be serious with
you staring at me.
Are they closed tight?
Now don't open them
again until I say.
Keep them closed just
a little bit longer.
[FURUYA]
Wait, what? She's kissing me.
Is this okay? We aren't
even dating yet.
But I like her. I just need
to make it official.
[MINAGAWA]
Okay. Open them.
So? Was that being
serious enough for ya?
How was that at all serious?
You used your fingers to pretend
like you were kissing me!
Why do you think you
kissed my fingers?
I didn't say that.
You can tell the difference
between someone's lips
and their fingers.
So which do you think
you kissed? Well?
[MINAGAWA giggles]
[FURUYA grunts]
[CHIAKI, KANA]
Next episode: "Lovers."