[TAKASE] The girl I like said
she wanted to talk to me.
[TAKASE] She must wanna
confess her feelings.
I couldn't be happier.
[shivering]
[TAKASE] We've been out
here for ten minutes.
Are you scared? Say something.
[TAKASE]
Hey, um--
Please wait!
[TAKASE gasps]
Do you, uh, do you have a crush
on anyone or anything, Takase?
[TAKASE]
Uh...
[TAKASE] What's the right
answer in this situation?
Should I be honest with
her and say, "You"?
But then I'd be robbing her
of her chance to confess to me.
Though it's not like
I don't have a crush.
Oh! So you do?
[TAKASE]
Wait. No, I didn't mean that.
Takase, you aren't making sense.
Do you have a crush
or don't you?
Fine, then I don't have a crush.
[KANDA]
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I don't have
a crush on anyone.
You really don't?
Wasn't there something
you wanted to say to me?
[KANDA yelps]
Not really.
Just what I said. I wanted
to know if you liked anyone.
'Kay, I told you. So now what?
[TAKASE] So, are you done then?
'Cause I should get going.
[KANDA]
What? No. I'm not done.
There was more.
But I guess I kinda
blew it for today.
All right. Then I'm gonna leave.
[KANDA]
Huh?
Takase, wait!
[KANDA]
Hey, um... Would-Would you...?
[TAKASE]
Yes! Here is comes!
Would you be willing to
meet up again tomorrow?!
[sighs]
[TAKASE]
Maybe I should just do it.
I'll tell you tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, sure.
I'll come back, but first
there's something...
You mean it?
You'll come tomorrow?
Sorry about dragging
you out here today.
I wanted to say something,
but I kinda forgot.
Yeah, about that...
Come back tomorrow, Takase!
And I'll tell you I like you!
[TAKASE]
uh...
Okay, bye! See you tomorrow!
[FURUYA]
Minagawa is the class rep,
but she doesn't do her job.
[FURUYA] Could you help me out
a little with this, Minagawa?
[MINAGAWA]
Help?
But I'm lazy. You know that.
Then why on Earth did you
become the class rep?
Because I like you, Furuya.
Could you please not
mess with me like that?
Hold on. Are you mad?
That wasn't my intent.
I'm sorry. Please don't be mad.
[FURUYA] It's not like
I'm angry or anything.
Good, 'cause I
really do like you.
[FURUYA] So is that supposed
to be a confession?
[MINAGAWA]
Yup. Will you go out with me?
[FURUYA]
I-I don't know.
There are rumors you go out
with lots of guys, Minagawa.
So? I'm still a virgin.
[grunts]
Yeah, I have a lotta guy
friends, but we just hang out.
There's nothing like
that going on.
Oh, is that all?
Do you think that I'm lying?
Not really. I just think that--
[MINAGAWA]
You think I'm easy
and that I'd just sleep
with anyone, is that it?
No. Well, not exactly.
Now you're getting horny
just sitting here
thinking about me having sex.
[FURUYA]
No, I'm not!
I knew you were just toying
with me. Cut it out!
[MINAGAWA]
Ha-ha. Sorry.
But these things are always
kinda awkward, ya know?
That's why I can't tell
if you're serious or not.
Then if I asked you
without any joking around,
what would you say?
[FURUYA]
You mean will I go out with you?
But why me? You could
be with anyone.
I don't even know you that well.
I don't have a clue
who you really like--
You.
What about you? You like me?
Um.
I kinda don't know anything
about dating yet,
but if you want, we could,
maybe, I dunno... Hm?
[giggles]
[grunting]
What are you smiling about?!
Oh, Furuya, you really
are too adorable.
That's it. We're done here.
Done? But you still haven't
given me an answer.
No matter what I say,
you're just gonna laugh
at me more, aren't you?
[MINAGAWA]
Mh-hm.
Uh-oh. You're mad.
Did I make you hate me?
Well, I definitely hate
how cheeky you are.
Then reject me and
get it over with.
Can we just not talk
about this right now?
So you don't totally hate me!
Maybe I do now!
[KAJI] The student council
president caught me smoking.
Dammit.
[AKAGI] You know
that's not good for you.
Oh, great! You're gonna
rat me out, aren't you?
Relax. I'm not a total monster.
Just this once, I'm
willing to let it slide.
Thanks. I appreciate
you being cool.
That is, I will if you kiss me.
[KAJI]
Huh?
Is that a joke?
[AKAGI]
I'm totally serious.
In fact, it has to
do with something
that's been on my mind.
You see, I've never been
in love with a woman.
Ha. Are you gay or somethin'?
I'm not gay. I tested that.
What? Tested?
I don't understand what's
so fun about dating.
I've had a hard time
finding interest in girls.
And you wanna kiss
someone to try and find out?
Sure, why not? Sounds fun.
Since you don't know how to kiss
a girl, I'll be your teacher.
No. When it comes to
kissing, I know how.
Oh, sorry.
You're surprisingly cooperative.
Well, yeah. It's not like
it's my first time.
I'll lock lips with
anyone for the right price.
[AKAGI] Really? What do you
charge to go all the way?
[KAJI]
Uh...
A hundred thousand yen?
Perfect. You take cash?
[KAJI]
You've got that much on you?!
What's wrong? Are you scared?
Hell no! I'm ready to
go whenever you are.
[AKAGI] You've never actually
prostituted yourself, have you?
What? You callin' me a liar?
The going rate,
it isn't 100,000 yen.
If you'd ever really
done it, you'd know.
A hundred thousand is far too
little. Especially for you.
I think you're worth
a lot more than that.
Akagi.
[AKAGI] Regardless,
I do still expect that kiss.
[KAJI]
You do?
Of course. That was
our agreement, wasn't it?
Unless now you're too scared.
I'm not scared. I'm totally
not scared at all.
Good. Let's go.
Wow. You reek.
You smell like an ashtray.
Shut up! What did you expect?!
[AKAGI]
You should really quit smoking.
Bite me! What are you,
my boyfriend?
Why not? Sounds good to me.
[AKAGI]
Yes.
I think you are someone that
I could fall in love with.
That is, as long as
you quit smoking.
[KAJI]
Piss off!
[SASAHARA]
This is Yukawa.
He's a third year and
he's graduating tomorrow.
Pretty please. Show me the
stars just one last time.
No. You're way too annoying.
You suck, Yukawa. I was gonna
confess my love for you.
This would be, what,
like the thousandth time?
[chuckles]
Yeah, maybe.
[YUKAWA]
Well, I'm sick of it.
[SASAHARA]
This is a bad habit of mine.
I tell him how I feel,
then pretend it's a joke.
[SASAHARA]
But tonight I want to tell him
I have feelings
for him for real.
First, though, it's important
to set the right mood.
Hey. It's cold.
Would it be okay
if I sat with you?
[YUKAWA] Whatever.
Just stay out of my way.
[chuckles]
Do you maybe wanna
cuddle a little bit too?
What?
Nothing.
This is our last time
stargazing here.
It is.
This is my last time
stargazing with you, too.
It is.
But, I mean, it
doesn't have to be.
We could always do it
again if we really tried.
[YUKAWA]
Please quit yammering.
Haven't you learned any of
the stars' names by now?
Names? I, um, well,
uh... I know Spica.
Spica? But that's the very
first one I taught you.
Of course!
If it's a star that
you showed me,
there's no way
I'd ever forget it.
All right then, point out Spica.
It's, uh, in the...
[sighs]
Get it together, huh?
Come next year, you'll be
the only one in this club.
Don't blame me.
That's all your fault.
You always look like
you're in a bad mood.
Then why'd you join?
Why weren't you scared away?
Me? Well, I joined because
I'm in love with you.
Yeah, yeah.
All the first- and second-years
worship the ground I walk on.
How would... you feel
if I really did?
Like you, I mean.
[SASAHARA]
I did it! I finally did it!
I told Yukawa how I felt about
him without making it a joke!
But what if he's not happy about
it? What's with that look?
Was this a mistake?
Did I blow it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sasahara.
Ha! Got ya! You thought
I was serious!
[laughing]
[SASAHARA] That's it. I blew it.
I can't ever tell him the truth.
There's no way he
would believe me.
I've said I liked him a million
times over the past two years,
but never that I
really meant it.
Now he's graduating tomorrow,
and I just messed
up my last chance.
[SASAHARA]
I think I'm going to cry.
No. No! I can't cry
in front of him.
He'll worry! It'll be awkward!
I just want him
to smile like when
he first showed me the stars!
Keep it together, Sasahara.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
[SASAHARA]
Don't let him see you cry.
[YUKAWA] I'm sick of
hearing you say you like me.
Yukawa. You're awful.
[YUKAWA] That ends tonight.
No more joking around.
I wanna hear you say it.
Just one more time.
If you won't, then I will.
Oh, Yukawa!
I love you! I really do!
[YUKAWA]
Stop crying.
[SASAHARA, KAGA]
Next episode: "Spring."