[HOTARU]
My name is Hotaru.
Today is my very first
day of high school.
I also have a big brother,
Furuya. He's awesome!
[HOTARU] Furuya's the
class representative.
It's his job to take care
of the whole class.
Too bad he's so serious
and can't get a girlfriend.
Ha-ha! Furuya!
[MINAGAWA] Isn't it great?
We're in the same class again!
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
[HOTARU]
Big brother.
What? Uh, Hotaru.
Your sister?
Yeah.
Thank you for being
so nice to my brother.
Oh! That's so sweet.
You're welcome.
Don't read into it.
I'm just being polite.
Furuya! Who is this?
Is she your girlfriend?
Are you two dating? Are
there others besides her?
Hotaru, stop. Don't be rude.
You really love
your brother, huh?
[HOTARU] What do you
mean? Of course I do!
It's normal!
[FURUYA] She's a bit
over-attached. Sorry.
Don't apologize. It's cute.
What exactly are you
to my brother, anyway?
That's a good question.
What is she? Just spit it out!
It can't be what I think.
but just to be sure,
tell me you're not dating.
We're not. Your brother
and I are just friends.
I thought so.
What else would you be?
He's not really--
For now, anyway.
[FURUYA]
Hotaru, you're hurting me.
I confessed that I
really, really like him,
but he hasn't told
me how he feels,
so nothing has happened yet.
She's trolling me, right?
You can't possibly
have feelings for her.
Well, um...
Why are you hesitating?
Just reject her and
get it over with.
You'll only hurt her
if you lead her on.
Hotaru, you don't--
No, your sister's right.
If you're not
interested, say so.
Well, um, it's hard to say.
I can't find the right words.
And hurting you is the
last thing I'd wanna do.
Let's go! Let's go!
Kick her to the curb!
The thing is, it's not
that I don't like you.
Furuya, you idiot!
I'm trying to look out for you,
like a good little sister.
Can't you see that?
She's just toying with you.
If you date her,
you'll only get hurt.
Hotaru. I wasn't
planning on dating her.
Does that mean I've
just been shot down?
Bullseye!
You don't need
a girlfriend, do you?
'Cause you already have me.
I'm sorry, Minagawa.
But I can't date you without
thinking it all through, first.
I mean, if I were
to go out with you,
it might lead to marriage,
and to kids, and all that stuff.
[MINAGAWA] You're that serious
about me? I had no idea.
[FURUYA] No, wait.
That's not quite what I meant.
Of course he is!
My brother's always serious!
You're absolutely right.
He is always really serious.
That's why I like him.
How about I give you some more
time to think things over?
That's totally up to you.
[MINAGAWA] You'll be rooting for
me and your brother, right?
No way! You can't
take him! He's mine!
Well, if that's the case,
then I'll just have to
adore both of you.
I freakin' hate you!
[KAGA] Is there a point
in joining any of these?
There's nothing I'm
actually drawn to.
I don't have any
interests or hobbies.
Basically, I'm boring.
But then again, does anyone
really care about what they do?
[SASAHARA]
Hi there!
[KAGA]
Uh.
Hey! You look like
you're into stars.
Wanna join the Astronomy Club?
Thanks, but no. Not interested.
[SASAHARA]
Wait!
Come on, at least hear me out.
Now then, what's your name?
It's Kaga.
Have you chosen
a club yet, Kaga?
Uh. Not yet.
Then why not join me
and feast your eyes
on an orchestra of stars?
Jeez, he's not even
cracking a smile.
Stargazing: Be honest
with me, is it fun?
Of course it is!
Stars are pretty!
But don't you get bored
just watching them?
[KAGA]
I'll take that as a yes.
Any other reasons I
should join this club?
Oh, yeah. Members
are super popular.
So far, 100% of them
have hooked up!
How's that for a reason?
[KAGA]
Yeah, right.
I get the feeling that you don't
actually like stars that much.
So why are you in
the Astronomy Club?
Well, I guess that...
I just like it.
Hard to beat the view, y'know?
Yeah? How many are in
the club besides you?
[SASAHARA]
Uh...
[KAGA]
Oh, don't tell me "zero."
Please consider it.
None of the other clubs
interest you, right?
[KAGA]
Well, no.
Then let me tell you
a story about the stars
that's sure to excite you!
Look there! Up in the sky.
There's a star
somewhere up there.
A bright star called Spica.
It looks like one big star,
but it's actually two.
They spin around and around,
and they're always like pulling
on each other or something.
Like this.
Two stars helping one another
become one big ball of light.
Doesn't that sound
philosophical?
Maybe.
[SASAHARA]
Interested now?
Not really.
Dang. That's should've worked.
Anything else you wanna try?
Think. Think, Sasahara!
[SASAHARA]
Mars! That's it!
The other day I had octopus
balls while watching Mars!
My friend who just
graduated was like,
"Octopuses kinda look like
Martians, don't they?"
So I made octopus balls
while we watched Mars.
Actually, he watched Mars.
Stared at it the whole time.
He couldn't take his eyes off
it. Not for hours. That ended...
[KAGA] This isn't even
about stars anymore.
...I ate all the
octopus balls myself.
My friend was kind
of annoyed that I ate...
[KAGA] She must really
love the Astronomy Club.
I've never seen
anyone so excited.
She's so absorbed
and passionate.
I wish I could be the same way.
[SASAHARA]
Come on, Kaga, join!
You'll love it! I guarantee!
[KAGA]
There's not really anything
I've been interested in.
But I'm so boring,
and I'm sick of it.
So I've been looking
for something to like.
Could this be what I've
been searching for?
Something I finally care about?
Maybe. Maybe not.
But I know one thing.
I wanna see more of her smile.
[KAGA]
Okay.
[GODA] Kamine sits next to me.
Yet she often avoids me.
Why?
[KAMINE gasps]
[GODA]
Why?
Kamine, aren't you going home?
Yes. I will. In a minute.
[GODA] She won't even
look me in the eye.
Did I do something
to offend her?
[KAMINE gasps]
[GODA]
Guess I should go.
[KAMINE]
Goda!
What's wrong?
Well, I, um,
I just realized I lost
one of my contact lenses,
and um, I wanted to...
I see. I won't step
on it. I'll leave.
No, please don't leave!
Help me look for it!
All right, then.
Let's look for it.
[GODA] Maybe she doesn't
completely hate me.
Do you lose your contacts a lot?
Just sometimes. Like if I'm
sweating and I wipe my face.
You are sweating quite
a bit right now.
Kamine. Did you want
to talk to me?
Is there anything you would
like to confide in me?
What?
Whatever it is,
I promise you can tell me
and it will be all right.
So go ahead. Just say it.
Um, it sounds like you don't
really need me to say it.
Given what you said,
you already know.
[GODA]
Hm?
I'm still not sure I
understand how we got here.
Was it something I did to you?
Remember a while back?
When I was having a hard time
in class because of my eyesight?
And you let me borrow
your notebook?
[GODA]
Yeah. What was wrong with that?
Nothing. It was very kind.
[GODA]
Now I'm more confused than ever.
[GODA] Sorry, Kamine.
I didn't realize--
[KAMINE] Please, you
don't need to apologize.
Why don't we just
find your contact?
It's the least I can do.
[KAMINE]
Goda?
[GODA]
Hm? Did you find it?
[KAMINE]
How do you feel?
About what?
Oh. Never mind.
I just wanted to
tell you how I felt.
If you've got nothing to say
to me, that's fine. Really.
[GODA] Are you telling me you
won't be happy unless I own up?
Not at all!
I just wanted to know what
your feelings were, Goda.
[GODA] Fine then. If that's
what you really want.
[GODA]
I'm sorry. It's me, not you.
And well, to be
completely honest,
I don't understand
how girls feel.
Oh. That's okay.
[GODA] I'm sure that every
moment I'm near you,
I'll just make
even more mistakes.
[GODA] But if you could find it
in your heart to tolerate me...
[gasps]
Look! It's your contact.
Why are you crying?
[KAMINE] Does that mean
you'd be willing to like,
go out and spend time with me?
Of course it does.
That was pretty much implied
by everything I just said,
wasn't it?
[KAMINE]
Thank you, Goda!
What's the matter, Kamine?
Are you all right?
Have I gone crazy or something?
You're fine.
I'm sorry. I know this
doesn't make any sense.
And I still haven't
come right out
and told you how I
really feel, have I?
If there's anything left
that you still wanted to say
to me, feel free to go ahead.
I like you.
[TAKANO] It wasn't
supposed to rain today.
[SUGAWARA]
Takano? No umbrella?
[TAKANO]
Sugawara is a guy in my class.
I've never really
talked to him before.
[SUGAWARA]
Here. Take mine.
I'll just make a run for it.
But it's wet.
[TAKANO]
I felt bad for him.
So I suggested we walk
part way home together.
I'm sorry. Must be embarrassing
walking home with a girl.
No. Or, at least,
with you, it's not.
[TAKANO]
Hm?
[TAKANO] I guess he means no one
would think anything of it,
if it's just me.
That's good.
Your shoulder's getting wet.
Oh. It's fine. Don't worry.
No. Come closer.
Get all underneath.
[TAKANO]
Almost.
A little closer.
[SUGAWARA yelps]
[SUGAWARA] Aren't you a
little self-conscious?
Huddling under an
umbrella with a guy?
[TAKANO] Not really.
There's no one around.
But what if someone was
here and they saw us?
Like maybe your crush.
I don't know. I don't
have a crush on anyone.
Why are you smiling?
I've never thought
much about dating.
What if someone told you
they had feelings for you?
There's no one who
would do that.
Hypothetically, what if someone
confessed their love?
Uh... I think I'd
probably turn them down.
Why say no?
Because there must be
something wrong with anyone
who'd have feelings for me.
I'm not pretty or cute.
I'm just gloomy.
That's not true. You are cute.
And you have plenty of
other attractive qualities.
You help people clean and
take care of the pupfish.
I've seen you.
You're a hard worker.
Those are some of the
reasons I, uh, uh...
[TAKANO]
Hm?
So this is where I catch my bus.
Was there something
else you wanted to say?
No. It wasn't important.
[TAKANO]
Okay. See ya.
[TAKANO] Dating, huh?
I'm not sure I could.
Sugawara was nice, though.
I bet he dates a lot.
[TAKANO gasps]
What are you doing here?
I started to tell you something,
and I figured I'd finish it.
I have something
to confess to you.
I like you, Takano.
Thanks, Sugawara.
I know you're trying to cheer
me up, and I appreciate it.
What? You weren't?
Well, no, I...
Nevermind.
[SUGAWARA]
So this is my stop.
Oh. Bye then.
[TAKANO] Sugawara's nice.
He's a really good guy.
Maybe I'll bake him some cookies
as a thank you for the umbrella.
[CHIAKI, KANA] Next episode:
"Point-Blank Relationship."