Takase!
[TAKANO] Lately I keep catching
myself watching Sugawara.
I can't seem to help it.
What's the matter with me?
[YOSHINAGA]
Takano? Is something wrong?
You've been really distracted.
Anything you wanna talk about?
Oh. Sorry. It's
nothing. Don't worry.
Yeah? So then are you in love?
[saxophone squeaks]
[YOSHINAGA]
Oh my gosh! So you are?
[TAKANO] What? No,
I'm not. How could I be?
I don't know anything about
love and all that stuff.
[YOSHINAGA]
But when you see couples,
doesn't it make you jealous?
Especially Kamine and Goda.
They're so cute.
I haven't really
thought about it.
Hey.
Hi, Kamine! Your ears
must've been burning.
The two of us were
just talking about you.
Really? You were?
We wanna know,
how did everything start
between you and Goda?
What?
[YOSHINAGA] Come on, Takano.
Aren't you curious, too?
No. Not so much.
What are you doing here, Kamine?
Did you need something?
Oh. No. I was just looking
for the music teacher.
Aww. You don't even wanna
gossip a little bit?
We really shouldn't.
It's rude to pry.
[KAMINE]
Well...
...if it's a little,
I don't mind.
[TAKANO]
She doesn't?
[YOSHINAGA] Yay! We're gonna
get some juicy details!
I don't care.
[YOSHINAGA] Okay, so who told
who they liked them first?
[KAMINE] Well, this is kinda
embarrassing to admit,
but I told him before
he confessed to me.
[saxophone squeaks]
Miss your fingering
there, Takano,
or could it be that
you're interested?
No, I'm not.
Do you have a crush
on someone, Takano?
She's been spacing out
and sighing nonstop.
What? That's not true!
Ah, I remember that.
I would do those
things all the time.
[gasps]
It's what happens when
you like someone.
You just can't help it.
[YOSHINAGA]
Yeah.
But there isn't anybody
I have a crush on.
At least, I don't think I do.
[KAMINE] With Goda, I'd catch
myself watching him
no matter where he was.
Or thinking about him
without even realizing it.
And during club,
I was always distracted.
Sounds like you, Takano.
Are you sure you
don't like anyone?
[TAKANO] Sugawara is a boy
in my class. He's a good guy.
He's helpful.
And nice to everyone.
[KAMINE]
Is the guy you like Sugawara?
No, it can't be.
It's not him.
But if I did like a guy,
why'd you guess him?
No real reason.
There's just a rumor
I heard about him
that's been going around.
People are saying he
has a crush on you.
[YOSHINAGA]
Yeah, Takano.
I heard the same thing.
Sugawara likes you.
[TAKANO] The girl Sugawara
has a crush on is me?
Someone actually likes me?
And that someone... is him?
[KAMINE] It's just a rumor
though. Who knows if it's true?
Maybe you should tell him
you like him and find out.
[TAKANO]
No way. I couldn't do that.
Anyway, tell us more about
how you confessed
your feelings to Goda.
Yeah? You want me to?
No thanks. I'd rather practice.
[CHIAKI]
My girlfriend dumped me.
I hate this. Can't we
just get back together?
[KANA]
That's so totally ridiculous.
[CHIAKI] Kana! I'm sorry
about the other day.
Let's go.
What about Chiaki?
[KANA]
I don't care. C'mon.
Sorry!
[CHIAKI]
I want to die.
What? Why did you break up?
Because he gave me the
weirdest first kiss ever.
That is a big screw
up, but it's Chiaki.
You sure you really
wanna end it?
Yeah. We're through.
[CHIAKI groans]
[CHIAKI] Still no reply.
Not even marked as "read."
I should stop messaging her.
[KANA] I've been ignoring
Chiaki for a while now.
Should I let it go
and forgive him?
I mean, it's not like he
was trying to be awful.
I'm going to text her one
more time, then I'll give up.
[KANA] I'll forgive him, if he
apologizes one more time.
[CHIAKI]
Would an e-mail be better?
Or would that be creepy?
[KANA]
What's keeping him?
He's messaged me every day since
that kiss. Why not today?
Hurry up and apologize, idiot.
[CHIAKI] Yeah. This is
the best way to do it.
I'll say I'm sorry
with my own voice.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[KANA screams]
What? Come on! No way!
Are you serious?
[gasps]
No! I wasn't able to
read it! What did he want?
[CHIAKI]
She's not answering.
And she always has
her phone with her,
even when she takes a bath.
So she must be ignoring me.
[KANA]
It's okay. Don't panic.
I bet that was just
his daily apology.
I can reply to him tomorrow.
[CHIAKI]
Guess I'll give up, then.
[KANA] But what if that
text was the last one?
What if he's ready to give up?
After how long I've ignored him,
I wouldn't blame him if he did.
He might even hate me now.
I don't want him to hate me.
He pisses me off sometimes,
but I love him.
And he's my best friend.
I wanna say I'm sorry
for ignoring him.
Please. Please turn on. Please!
You have to turn on!
[KANA'S MOM]
Kana! Are you ever coming out?
Why are you sitting
on the floor naked?
I dropped my phone
in the bathtub
and now it won't turn on.
Don't worry.
I'm sure it just
needs a good whack.
I'm not-- Ah!
Stop it, Mom! What are you
doing? You're gonna break it!
No way! It turned on.
Your mama's good
with technology.
Yeah. Apparently you are.
[phone ringing]
[CHIAKI]
I can't give up. Not yet.
C'mon, Kana. Let me apologize!
[KANA] He's calling me!
He hasn't given up!
[CHIAKI]
Please, please pick up!
Hey, Chiaki!
[BOTH]
Is that you?
[gasps]
[CHIAKI] She hung up
on me? What the hell?
Fine! Have it your way!
No more calls!
I'm blocking you, too!
What happened? Did it die?
Well, that's technology for ya.
[KANDA]
Uh-oh.
Did I forget to bring enough
pencil lead for the test today?
I could've sworn I
put some in my bag.
[BOTH]
What if...?
[TAKASE] What if I offered to
give her some of my pencil lead?
Would she think I had
an ulterior motive?
[KANDA] What if I asked
Takase for some of his lead?
Would that be weird?
Would he think I had
an ulterior motive?
[BOTH] Then again, I do
have an ulterior motive.
[ENGLISH TEACHER] All right,
class, take your seats.
[KANDA]
Minagawa. Got extra pencil lead?
I do. But I'm afraid that
it's all .4 millimeter.
[KANDA gasps]
Why don't you ask
Takase for some?
I mean, you're sitting
right next to him.
Well, I could.
Come on, ask him for some lead.
Minagawa!
Don't say it like that!
[bell ringing]
[KANDA]
Crap. I'm out of lead already?
I should've asked
Takase earlier.
What am I gonna do now?
[ENGLISH TEACHER]
Time's up.
Everyone pass your
exams to the front.
Thanks for the lead.
That was nice.
No problem.
Happy I could help.
I'll bring you some tomorrow.
You don't have to.
[sighs]
[MINAGAWA]
They'd sure make a cute couple.
Why aren't they going out?
[KAJI]
Okay.
So if "a" times "x" equals "b"
and "b" divided by
"a" equals "x,"
then what the heck is "x"?
[KAJI'S MOM] So now you do
want to go to college?
But you're a third year?
Aren't you too late to
start studying for that?
Well, I'm studying
'cause I wanna go now!
Ryoko, you know we
don't have money.
Especially not for
a private school.
You don't have to remind me.
[KAJI] I told her I'd find
a way, but she's right.
I've always been a slacker.
And this late in the game, can
I even get in to public school?
I heard that "you-know-who"
is gonna be there too.
[KAJI]
Damn it!
Up to now, I always slept
through all my exams
or just skipped them.
Now that I'm actually trying,
everybody else looks so
much smarter than me.
They're all calm and focused.
Uh.
[KAJI] Maybe I did start too
late, and this is all pointless.
[KAJI]
C'mon, Kaji! Concentrate!
[KYOUKO] Kaji reviewing
notes before a test?
That's new.
Yeah, I'm surprised too.
But good on her that she's
taking school more seriously.
You might wanna try
that yourself, Kyouko.
It's the boyfriend.
Uh?
She's been dating the
student council president.
Didn't you know that?
[CLASSMATE A]
Uh-uh.
[KATORI] Your lady over there
looks a bit tense, Akagi.
Aren't you going
to go talk to her?
Give her a few last words
of encouragement?
No. It's good practice
for the test.
I can't help her.
She'll be on her own.
[KATORI]
Hmm?
You say that,
but you look like you wanna
jump up and run to her.
If I try, you have to hit me.
Knock me out cold.
With pleasure.
[MATH TEACHER]
Time for the test!
Everyone, take your seats.
[KAJI]
Okay. Just stay calm.
Try to remember what
you studied with Akagi.
[AKAGI] That problem you're
working on there.
What? Is it wrong?
After you're done with
it, can I kiss you?
Just die.
[KAJI]
Never mind. Forget it.
[KATORI] If "x" equals sexy,
then "x" equals me.
And done.
[KAJI]
Is this the right answer?
I mean, I think it is.
But wait, did I forget a
step in the calculations?
No. Get outta your head, Kaji.
You reviewed this over and over.
You are going to pass this test
and go to college with Akagi!
[KAJI]
Uh-oh.
I'm not supposed to get outta
my seat so what do I do?
Oh, right! Ask the teacher!
[KAJI] But if I raise my hand,
people will notice.
They'll say to themselves,
"What's that juvenile delinquent
doing taking the
entrance exams?"
"Why is she trying
to go to college?
She doesn't have a chance!"
And they'd be right.
No matter how hard I try now,
it won't be good enough.
[CLASSMATE A]
Excuse me!
Someone dropped their eraser.
Could you pick it up please?
[MATH TEACHER]
Sure. No problem.
I'll come get it for you.
Oh. No, sir. It's not my
eraser, it belongs to Kaji.
[MATH TEACHER]
Ah. Here ya go, Kaji.
It's nice to see you really
applying yourself.
You'll do great.
Um. Thank you.
[CLASSMATE A]
I know you can do it.
You got this, Kaji.
What's wrong, Kaji?
Are you feeling unwell?
[KAJI]
No. I'm fine.
[CLASSMATE A] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
[KAJI]
I'm not upset!
[MATH TEACHER]
You wanna go to the nurse?
[KAJI]
I said I'm fine!
[SANO]
Can I go to the nurse?
I'm sleepy.
I wanna take a nap.
[MATH TEACHER]
You can nap in college.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[MATH TEACHER]
Settle down. Back to your exam.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
[TAKANO, CHIAKI] Next episode:
"Summer Is Coming."