[YUKICHI] As vile
a special ability as ever.
[OUGAI]
Now, my dear Elise,
make sure that he
gets his shots.
[OUGAI]
He draws the sword so deftly
that you don't even see it.
I'd expect no less
of the Silver Wolf,
once the government's best
sword-wielding assassin.
[OUGAI]
Uh.
[YUKICHI]
Guard duty?
[OUGAI]
Yes.
I've been told that you are
an exceptional bodyguard.
[YUKICHI] I'm busy preparing
to open a detective agency,
so I'm abstaining from
that work for now.
I'm only making an exception
by order of Master Natsume.
You're taking a break?
It would be a real shame
if your skills got rusty.
[YUKICHI grunts]
Doctor! Our man's
down! Please help us!
Very well. But don't
start a fight here.
I'm also treating
the one who shot him.
[MAN A]
Understood.
[OUGAI]
Oh, you can relax.
This clinic is considered
a neutral zone.
There's never a
dull moment here.
I hear all kinds of stories
from the underground.
[YUKICHI]
Underground Doctor Mori.
What a shady character.
Why would Master Natsume
possibly order me
to protect him?
[MAN B]
Doctor Mori.
Because your little
clinic's in a safe zone,
you must pick up a
lot of information
from your criminal clientele.
Enough to shut down a smaller
organization overnight.
I know your side job. Trading
info on the black market.
Me and my boys wanna know
where the Port Mafia
is hiding their weapons stash.
[MAN B] Their boss has been
goin' on a rampage lately
and knockin' people off.
So we've come up with a plan.
We use their weapons
for our crimes
and turn the Port Mafia
into our scapegoat.
[OUGAI]
I already know that.
You attacked a medical
transport truck last week.
You see, I love everything
about this city.
I even love its dark side.
But parasites like you
make me sick to my stomach.
--[ALL gasp]
--[door opens]
[OUGAI]
What do you think, Fukuzawa?
[ALL gasp]
The hell?! We had at least
a dozen guards out front!
I killed all of them.
[MEN gasp]
Stay back! Or I'll ice him!
Do as you like.
Don't be like that.
[YUKICHI] You were just buying
time for me to arrive, right?
[chuckles]
We have the same stench--
the disgusting stench of death.
[OUGAI]
I pretended to be caught
so they would reveal
where their hideout was.
It's time to deliver
a little payback.
Just as Master
Natsume planned it.
Master Natsume?
[OSAMU]
Yes, Natsume.
The legendary gifted
who was instrumental
in founding the
Armed Detective Agency.
His whereabouts are
a mystery to everyone.
Rumor has it,
his ability is unrivaled,
allowing him to see
through anything.
Uh... Sardines?
[YUKICHI] Didn't you tell me
I could handle this on my own?
There were far more enemies
than your information
suggested, Mori.
But what a treat to witness the
Silver Fox's talent up close.
And I only had to handle
half of them by myself.
Was it not in vain?
How do you mean?
[YUKICHI]
This conspiracy was no more
than a grain among
the sands of calamity.
Until the tyranny of the
Port Mafia is done away with,
disasters will
continue to strike.
I'm aware of that.
It's for that reason
I'll be taking on
Master Natsume's
three-party framework.
[YUKICHI]
Three-party framework?
[OUGAI yells]
[OUGAI] Ever since we
battled here 12 years ago,
the two of us have fought and
clashed time and time again.
But when we fought
alongside one another,
we were invariably unmatched.
[yells]
Rintarou... I'm sorry.
I'll be waiting for you
on the other side.
I expected that
this would happen.
[YUKICHI] This is the end of
the three-party framework.
[OUGAI]
Master Natsume's vision...
...it entailed that
the military police
and Special Operations Division
would oversee the day,
the Port Mafia would
oversee the night,
and finally, the Armed Detective
Agency would oversee
the twilight, thus maintaining
order in the city.
After implementing
his frame work,
Master Natsume disappeared
from the public eye.
There was one important thing
we never did learn about him:
The exact nature of
his special ability.
Fukuzawa, there's something I'd
like to tell you before I die.
[YUKICHI]
Hm?
[OUGAI] The Detective Agency
and the Port Mafia
are not of equal value.
If you die, the fighting between
our organizations will cease.
However, if I am to die here,
the Mafia will become akin
to a vengeful spirit,
escalating this feud to an
even more gruesome state.
[thud]
[ATSUSHI] Katai was Kunikida's
friend for over a decade
and now he's dead.
I don't know if Kunikida
can really handle it.
Katai's always been a
troublesome individual.
I dragged him out of his room
and made him join the
Armed Detective Agency,
but even then, he'd just
bring his futon to the office
and live there like that.
[ATSUSHI] The futon he
called Yoshiko, right?
There's something strange
I noticed in that footage.
What did you see?
[DOPPO]
When Katai was shot,
the futon he was under
wasn't Yoshiko.
He wouldn't use another futon
unless he had a good
reason to do so.
I'm guessing the one from
the video was bullet-proof.
In other words...
he's still alive.
[ATSUSHI] But how did he get
himself outta that mess?
[DOPPO]
That's what I still don't get.
Someone else was smart
enough to deceive Fyodor.
Who saved Katai?
[OUGAI] I could not have
won by might alone,
so I decided to play
to your pathos instead.
This, too, must be destiny.
It's such a shame.
[NAOMI] I'm thinking back
to all those things
that happened whenever
Mii disappeared:
Stopping the military's
illegal activities,
the bombing attempt on
the police building...
Somehow all these
disasters were prevented.
And now, three days ago when
this terrible virus began,
Mii up and vanished again.
[KIRAKO]
Hmm.
At the same time
the president collapsed.
[NATSUME] You have no idea what
a pain the both of you are.
[YUKICHI gasps]
Na--!
Master Natsume!
[NATSUME] Can't you let an
old man enjoy his retirement?
I passed on the duty of
protecting this city
for a reason.
[KATAI coughing]
[KATAI]
Natsume, sir! Where are you?
[KATAI coughing]
[NATSUME]
Heh.
Young Katai here has figured out
where the Rats are hiding.
But the enemy is the
epitome of craftiness.
If they realize they're being
pursued, they'll disappear,
never to be found
or captured again.
Will you seize upon
this opportunity?
I see.
They don't know if one of us
has actually died yet.
Until they learn the
outcome of our battle,
they'll stay close to home.
You have 12 hours
before the effects of the virus
become irreversible.
I've already given
your subordinates
the information they
need to succeed.
I won't have a mere
pack of Rats
chewing up the organizations
I approve of.
Let's begin!
I trust that the two of
you won't let me down.
[ATSUSHI]
C'mon, just lemme go!
Not a chance.
You two are gonna
work together again,
whether you like it or not.
--Dazai!
--Ow, my tummy!
Please don't move around
like that, Atsushi.
You're gonna reopen my stiches.
This is our retaliation mission
to save our president.
Why is he even here?
It's all part of my plan,
just trust me.
The two of you are gonna sneak
into the enemy hideout together.
Huh?
[OSAMU] The enemy base is in
an old, abandoned coal mine.
The interior is several
hundred kilometers wide,
and equipped with sensors
and traps to stop intruders.
Our main target is the gifted
who controls the virus.
Unless we can disable
his special ability,
both leaders could die.
Our secondary target is
the mastermind, Fyodor.
Isn't this all the more
reason not to involve him?
This mission's important,
and you know how much
Akutagawa hates my guts.
I doubt he'd agree to
work with me anyway.
Well, Akutagawa? You in?
If that's the plan,
I can do it.
[ATSUSHI] Why is he so
focused all of a sudden?
Did you know it's
been four years
since you've been
under my command?
I'm hoping to see you're a
little more capable than before.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Yes.
Are you sure you're Akutagawa?
You're actually gonna
team up and fight with me?
Yes.
What did you have for
dinner last night?
Yes.
[sighs]
[ATSUSHI]
That sure is a lotta guards.
[OSAMU] They all have
wireless communicators, too.
Their people will know
right away if we charge in.
There's a sensor at the entrance
to counter
Junichirou's illusions.
Also, their vital signs
are being monitored
and continuously transmitted
back to their headquarters.
If the guards even so much as
become excited or nervous,
they'll know instantly
that something's wrong.
[ATSUSHI]
We can't let them get worried,
let alone just go in
and take them out.
[AKUTAGAWA] I have two simple
rules for you, weretiger.
[ATSUSHI]
Hm?
Keep up or be left behind.
Get in my way and die. Got it?
He left you behind.
I'm going, too!
Wait, Atsushi! Just how
are you going to--?
Well, he certainly made
that look easy enough.
Guess we should get
to work as well.
C'mon, let's get started.
[ATSUSHI]
Slow down!
Dazai wanted us
to stick together.
In four years,
this is my first opportunity to
prove to him that I am superior.
I would actually prefer
if you were taken out early.
[AKUTAGAWA]
That was sluggish of me.
What I should do is cut
you down and report later
that you were apprehended.
I don't have a problem
if you wanna go at it.
But now's not
the time for this!
We'd just be giving the
target a chance to escape.
Is that what you want?
Know what your problem is?
You're too obsessed
with the kill
to even look two
feet ahead of you.
It's no wonder that Dazai up
and left you without a word!
[ATSUSHI]
Aw, crap.
As someone who's lived his
life constantly worrying
about what other's think,
there's one thing
I have a knack for:
realizing when I've
bring up something
that should never be mentioned.
[ATSUSHI]
It's like I can sense the switch
that goes off in their head.
Yes, you're right.
Akutagawa, wait!
There's a sensor up ahead.
If it sees us,
they'll know we're here.
[MAN #49] So why did you
decide to work here?
[MAN #48]
I snuck into this country.
Why else would I take up
such a sketchy job?
[gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
They're coming this way.
What do we do?
With the sensor, we're between
a rock and a hard place.
Rashoumon.
Wait, don't kill them!
Their fate is in
their hands now.
Listen up.
Speak without permission
and I'll kill you. Got it?
[MEN grunting]
[static]
[MAN D]
Hey, 49, 48.
Your vital signs are
slightly elevated.
What's goin' on?
Answer him.
But I'll advise you,
whether you get to live or die
hangs on your next words.
[BOTH grunt]
F-Forty-eight, reporting in.
It's nothin'. There was
a snake, but it ran away.
[MAN D] You sure it was
the snake that ran away
and not you?
Get your asses back to work.
Disable the microphones
on your devices.
Do as he says.
This is the Black-Caped
Beast we're dealin' with.
Huh? I thought that was
just a fairy tale.
Where can we find the person
who employed you two?
We don't know! We're just
tryin' to make a little dough.
Shall I start with your ears?
[MAN #48]
I-I swear!
I don't even know
what this facility is,
let alone what the
boss looks like.
I don't think he's lying.
Fyodor's not the type to
trust any of his underlings
with important information.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hmph.
And these bumblers haven't
proved themselves to be worthy.
[ATSUSHI] So what are you
gonna do with them?
We can't kill them
or leave 'em here.
Since you won't make
yourselves useful,
I'll just cut off your toes
to keep you from running.
[MAN #48] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hang on a second.
I-I may not know
where the boss is,
but I did see a blast
door over there.
It's got hi-tech voice and
fingerprint recognition.
Does it lead to their base?
We know someone named Katai
who might be able to hack it.
You work for us now.
The Port Mafia will
pay you tenfold
what you were paid before.
Uh--
[BOTH chuckle]
Well, looks like Lady Luck's
shinin' down on the two of us.
Thank you.
Now then, Port Mafia friend.
Has the cannibalism
ended as planned?
It seems our boss and
Fukuzawa fought in a duel.
For reasons we don't know,
there was an explosion.
It's unclear if
they're alive or not.
That's too bad.
[PORT MAFIA AGENT] Look, I gave
you the information you wanted.
Please, deactivate the bomb.
Oh, my apologies.
You can disable the
device in your necktie
by removing the blue wire.
[sighs]
[FYODOR D.]
Now, let me see...
[ATSUSHI] Do you think
you can open it, Katai?
[KATAI]
Maybe. It's an isolated network.
But it could be pretty
tricky to pull off
with my connection speed.
Then I would suggest you
prioritize locating
the virus user.
If we aren't able
to track them down,
the boss' life is forfeit.
You got it! Just gimme a little
more time with that, bro.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Did you just call me "bro"?
I'll kill you.
[ATSUSHI]
Hey, Akutagawa.
Why do you think Dazai
made us work together?
[AKUTAGAWA] Only a fool would
try to understand Dazai.
Questioning his motives is
an exercise in futility.
I have a question
for you in return.
Why did you decide to
participate in this operation?
Risking your life for another?
I can't comprehend
such behavior
coming from someone
as cowardly as you.
I just feel the need
to help is all.
Why is that?
I guess because
it's the right to do.
Based on what?
[ORPHANAGE MAN A]
Those who cannot save others
do not deserve to live.
[KATAI]
Guys! I got it!
Our target, Pushkin,
I know where he's located!
What? Where is he?
[KATAI] Very close.
About two meters away.
Behind you!
[AKUTAGAWA gasps]
[PUSHKIN laughing]
Looks like I missed.
But it's no big deal.
[ATSUSHI] He's the gifted
controlling the virus!
Our primary target!
Stop!
[PUSHKIN chuckles]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Get in!
[ATSUSHI]
Akutagawa!
Don't underestimate
small wounds!
As someone with a much
weaker power than yours,
it puts a smile on my
face to see you suffer!
[ATSUSHI]
You okay?
This is...
...the virus ability.
[AKUTAGAWA]
This gifted is quite adept.
We'll take him down
within a minute
and then go after the tram.
[ATSUSHI] Akutagawa. Are you
thinking what I'm thinking?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Of course. How many times
do you think we've
tried to kill each other?
[ATSUSHI] Next time on
Bungo Stray Dogs , Episode 37:
"Echo."
[AKUTAGAWA] Beast Beneath
the Moonlight, Rashoumon!
[AKUTAGAWA, ATSUSHI]
Kokuto Zessou!