[CHUUYA] I only have memories
of one part of my life.
Unlike you, I didn't lose
my memories from trauma.
My life only really
started eight years ago.
Before that...
everything was just...
...darkness.
[CHUUYA]
Somewhere in that darkness,
I was floating aimlessly.
[CHUUYA]
Eventually,
someone's hand broke through
the outer edges of that void
and dragged me into
the outside world.
That hand was yours, wasn't it?
[CHUUYA]
Where did you find me?
To find the answer,
I decided to follow this case.
Now, tell me everything
that you know.
[RANDO]
Very well then.
Of anyone, you have
the right to be told.
[CHUUYA groans]
Why didn't his
gravity powers work?
[RANDO] Unlike a bullet,
the subspace I control
doesn't abide by
the laws of physics.
It is of another world
entirely which has been
closed off from this one,
and I alone hold the key.
As such...
...only if I allow
you to, may you enter.
And only if I allow
you to, may you leave.
[OSAMU] You left me outside
of the subspace you deployed.
Then you must know
what my ability is.
[CHUUYA]
You son of a--!
That blast didn't kill you, huh?
Nothing less from Arahabaki.
[CHUUYA grunts]
Nice try, but it is of no use.
You cannot hope to reach
me while I'm in this space,
while I, on the other hand,
can strike you at will.
[CHUUYA yells]
Any kind of ability that
touches that kid gets nullified.
If you try to quarantine
him with your subspace,
you'll make a good
opening for me.
[RANDO] His existence
is truly heretical.
The ultimate,
anti-gifted weapon,
unrivaled, even
back in the west.
The west?
But that's fine.
[OSAMU groans]
[BOSS chuckles]
It's been awhile, hasn't it?
[OSAMU]
Yeah.
You look good for
someone who's dead, Boss.
[groans] Well...
...former boss.
There's no way he could
have hurt that idiot
with his special ability.
[OSAMU]
You're right.
His giant scythe isn't
an ability at all.
It's as real as you or me.
[CHUUYA]
I see...
So there's a possibility it
could really kill you, then.
The former boss is dead...
[OSAMU]
What exactly did you do, Rando?
[RANDO]
My ability can turn corpses
that reside in my subspace
into supernatural beings
which I command.
The only draw back is that I
can only control one at a time.
Quite impressive.
You've been hiding that
ability from the organization
this whole time?
Just who are you really?
[RANDO]
Before joining the Port Mafia,
I was a gifted spy
from the west.
I traveled to this country
to obtain a being--
one of incredible power
that the government of
Japan had discovered,
or so they say.
And that "being" was Arahabaki.
[RANDO] The sole purpose of my
plan from the very beginning
has been to kill you, Chuuya,
and then use my powers to
control you and Arahabaki
from beyond the grave.
Dazai.
If the boss were to learn
what you just have about me,
he would surely attempt
to have me assassinated.
Because of that, you must
die here, along with Chuuya.
[OUGAI]
It's nothing serious.
You won't be in
any kind of danger.
No big deal.
Danger's fine with me.
--[OSAMU] Hey.
--[CHUUYA] Hm?
I say we kill them both.
Together.
Huh? You mean you
actually wanna live now?
Believe it or not,
I'm starting to actually like
working for the Port Mafia.
In the outside world, death is
kept away from everyday life.
But in the Mafia's world,
death is an extension of, and
even a part of everyday life.
I personally find more truth
behind that way of thinking.
After all, dying isn't
the opposite of living
like the majority of
people think it is,
but a part of the
experience of life itself.
Without observing death
up close, one can't capture
the full picture of
what it means to live.
Really...
You, the suicidal maniac,
actually wanna live.
You serious?
I figure it's worth
giving a shot.
I can't promise more than that.
You won't have to.
Time to die, children.
Oh, really?
[CHUUYA grunts]
You see it now, right?
What you need to do?
Don't you start
giving me orders.
[CHUUYA grunts]
[CHUUYA grunting]
[RANDO]
Eight years ago...
...I tried to take Arahabaki
as my supernatural being.
But the moment that
Arahabaki emerged,
it decimated its surroundings
in the blink of an eye.
I won't make the
same mistake twice.
This time I'll make
certain to end your life,
then subsume you!
[screams]
[RANDO laughing]
[RANDO]
What?
You were able to
absorb the impact
by increasing your density,
using your gravity ability?
[CHUUYA]
Hey.
Wanna know why I've been
keeping both my hands
tucked away this whole time?
It's a simple way for
me to keep my cool.
It helps me stay rooted when I'm
afraid I'm gonna lose myself.
But the gloves are
coming off now.
Wonderful!
Once I subsume you, perhaps the
coldness I feel will disappear!
Let's go, Chuuya!
[RANDO]
Hm?
Better move your ass, Dazai.
You piece of shit.
[OSAMU chuckles, grunts]
This is the end for you!
Dazai!
[RANDO chuckles]
What?!
You ready?
Yeah! Let's go!
You can't!
Impossible!
[OSAMU grunts]
[RANDO groans]
[CHUUYA]
It's over.
[RANDO growls]
Not even you can escape gravity.
[BOSS growls]
[OSAMU]
If Rando's subspace vanishes,
naturally, so will you.
Anyway...
[yells]
[OSAMU] I won't get another
chance to say this,
so thank you.
[CHUUYA] You some kinda
shitty magician now, Dazai?
[OSAMU]
Really, Chuuya?
Did you think I was wearing
a cast for no good reason?
You'll tell us everything
we want now, won't you, Rando?
It was on that day,
eight years ago.
I had infiltrated this
country with my colleague.
And that is when
it all happened.
What did?
[RANDO] We came here in
order to steal a being
of remarkable power
that was being housed
in a secret military facility.
But upon reaching our target,
before I was able to obtain it,
my partner betrayed
both me and our country.
He and I fought over the entity,
and amidst the struggle,
we were discovered
and apprehended
by the Japanese military.
In order to escape with my life,
I had no choice but to unleash
you, the being I had stolen,
from your dark prison,
and I attempted to use my
ability to take control.
But before I could react,
you blew up the
facility in an instant.
Their records were lost,
along with my memories.
[RANDO]
My name isn't Rando.
Someone I met
here simply mistook
the type of hat
I wore as a rando,
and that became my name.
[OSAMU]
What happened to your partner?
[RANDO]
I killed him with my own hands.
Chuuya...
[CHUUYA gasps]
[RANDO] I suspect you are not
in fact Arahabaki itself,
but a human vessel that was
chosen to keep it restrained.
You're very strong.
Not because of Arahabaki,
but simply your strength
as a human being.
Sure, whatever.
[RANDO] Regardless of what's
living inside of you,
you'll always be yourself.
That's solace enough, is it not?
Every human being,
every living creature...
They go about their
lives on this Earth
without knowing
what they truly are.
[RANDO]
How strange...
For the first time...
...my body feels warm.
[CHUUYA] Even in death,
you're a real pain in the ass.
Of course, the Port
Mafia confiscated
all the records you'd
collected on Arahabaki.
[CHUUYA]
So I'm back to square one.
Well... even if you were alive,
you probably wouldn't have told
anyone about that stuff anyway.
[CHUUYA]
I'll be back.
Hm?
[SHIRASE]
There you are, Chuuya.
[CHUUYA]
Shirase.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to come an'
apologize to you.
We did some soul-searchin'
after what happened.
[SHIRASE sighs]
We have a good handle on
what the Sheep's
problems are now.
So we all talked it over and
agreed on what the solution was.
If you decided it
together, I won't--
[CHUUYA]
You...
[CHUUYA groans]
We'd wait until you
let your guard down,
then go ahead and
move in for the kill.
That way you wouldn't have
time to use your ability.
That makes sense, right, Chuuya?
[CHUUYA groans]
What are you doing?
[SHIRASE]
It's no use strugglin'.
I rubbed rat poison
on the blade.
You'll go numb soon and
you won't be able to move.
It's only because
you're so damn powerful.
Otherwise we wouldn't have
had to do it this way!
All of you?!
[SHIRASE]
This is the answer we agreed on.
We're teaming up with the GSS.
We all came to realize
the terrible truth--
that if you were really
gonna join the Port Mafia,
it'd end up getting each
and every one of us killed!
I would never betray the
organization! [groans]
[SHIRASE] The GSS doesn't
change its alliances on a whim
like you do.
They can be trusted as
long as they make money.
This is the smartest
thing that we can do!
It's the best way to
wipe out the Port Mafia!
It looks like...
...I was just a fool.
--Get 'im! Fire!
--[KIDS gasp]
[SHIRASE]
Go find him right now!
He may be weakened
by the poison,
but it won't be
enough to kill him.
So finish the job!
[CHUUYA groaning]
Their "leader" my ass...
All I was doing was holding
the organization back.
[OSAMU]
Hey there, Chuuya.
You look like you're in a bind.
[CHUUYA] Why are you here,
you piece of shit?
You wanna join the
festivities and kill me, too?
[OSAMU]
Mori sent me with a message.
He wants me to
officially invite you
to be a member
of the Port Mafia.
[CHUUYA] In return for
saving my life? Is that it?
[OSAMU] Uh, I don't really
even care which you choose.
I'm just here for the bloodbath.
Mori is a pretty
demanding employer.
The moment I joined
the Port Mafia,
he put me in charge of the army.
Now that two of our enemies,
the GSS and the Sheep,
have formed an alliance,
we have to shut them down
before they become
completely coordinated.
If I do my job, by noon today...
...they'll all be dead.
[CHUUYA grunts]
You'd actually hurt those kids?
[OSAMU]
Our policy never changes.
That said, there is
another possibility.
If someone who was
familiar with the enemy
asked me not to
go through with it,
I would take that
under advisement.
Someone on your team, you mean?
[OSAMU]
Right.
A fellow colleague
in the Port Mafia.
I could trust the
suggestion of one of my own.
So you wanna make a deal.
You really are the devil.
Don't forget though
that I won those games
we made bets on together.
You'll be working for me
in this organization
and I have every intention
of working you to the bone.
I'm gonna tear you
to shreds one day.
[OSAMU]
I like the look in your eyes.
Like a wild beast.
[CHUUYA]
Just don't kill the children.
[OSAMU]
Very well.
Listen up, everyone.
As we discussed earlier,
none of the kids
are to be harmed.
I see.
He knew this was gonna happen
and planned accordingly.
It all started when he made
that phone call at the arcade!
--[gunfire]
--[CHUUYA groans]
[CHUUYA] He purposefully did
that in front of my people
to spread doubt.
That damn son of a bitch.
[CHUUYA groans]
[CHUUYA] If that's how
you wanna play it, I'm in.
[CHUUYA]
What's up with this hat?
[OUGAI]
It's tradition in the Port Mafia
that the person who
recruits a new member
is responsible for
their well being.
To symbolize that, they hand
down one of their belongings.
In Dazai's case,
I gave him my coat.
For you, it's that hat.
It's seen better days.
[OUGAI] Yes. It actually
belonged to Rando.
Uh--
[OUGAI] It seems that he'd
been investigating Arahabaki.
Apparently the military
facility he infiltrated
was researching the creation
of an artificial gifted
by combining gifted
and ordinary humans.
[CHUUYA]
An artificial gifted...
[OUGAI] Those documents
there are the ones
he collected on the subject.
Not so fast.
Huh?
I regret to inform you, Chuuya,
but only executives have
clearance to look at those.
What makes you think I won't
beat the crap out of you
and just take it?
[OUGAI] I know you're
not as foolish as that.
[OUGAI]
Besides...
...I wouldn't be able
to answer the question
that's most pressing
in your mind if you did.
It was that easy to
see through me, huh?
Tell me, then.
What's it mean to be the
leader of an organization?
[OUGAI]
A leader of an organzation
is someone who acts as both
its king and its servant.
To protect the group,
they gladly put themselves
through all manner of
filth and tribulation.
They hone their
subordinates and place them
where they are best suited.
Otherwise, if deemed necessary,
they discard them.
They must take on
any act of barbarism
without hesitation.
That is a leader.
It's all for the
sake of the group,
as well as for the protection
of this city we so cherish.
[CHUUYA]
I see...
So that's what I was missing.
I've made my decision.
I'm dedicating my life
entirely to you, Boss.
I will work to see that this
organization is protected,
and decimate those
who stand in our way.
Our enemies will soon come
to fear the crushing weight
that my powers of gravity
can inflict on them.
They'll think twice
about opposing us.
Welcome to the Port Mafia,
Chuuya Nakahara.
[CHUUYA]
Hey, old lady.
Why are you taking
me to this meeting?
[KOUYOU] I would appreciate it
if you stopped calling me that.
I'm not elderly yet.
And you're going so you
can be better informed.
The group we're
meeting with today
is a front organization
for the Mafia.
In the course of this meeting,
even the smallest of actions
will affect the
Port Mafia's future.
You sure you want me in
on a thing like this?
What if I happen to
piss 'em off or somethin'?
[KOUYOU] We'll cross that
bridge if we need to.
If the boat is so
easily tipped over,
the best course of action
would be to destroy it now
in a blaze of glory.
[KYUSAKU giggles]
Hi, I'm Kyusaku!
Hey, you wana play a game?
--[growls]
--Please, please?!
[OSAMU] Now, now, maybe
a little later, all right?
Huh?!
[CHUUYA]
You!
[OSAMU]
Hey!
What do you think you're
doing here with her, Chuuya?!
Don't forget that you're my dog!
What?!
[OSAMU] That means if my
leg itches, you scratch it.
If I want noodles, you drag
a shop owner to come here
and make me the best
noodles in the world!
So what are you doing
working under Kouyou, huh?
You think you're just gonna
glide on up the ladder?
You gotta pay your
dues before that!
Shut the hell up,
you selfish, scheming bastard!
I joined the Port Mafia
on my own accord.
Not to be your henchman,
your slave, or especially...
Was it really a wise decision
to have these two working
under the same roof?
What happens next?
"Only a diamond can polish
another diamond." Heh.
[KOUYOU]
Huh?
Master Natsume...
Those words that you imparted
to both me and Fukuzawa...
I'm going to find
out for certain
if you were right or not.
[ANGO] This concludes the
summary of events surrounding
the recruitment of
Port Mafia executives
Chuuya Nakahara and Osamu Dazai.
The Port Mafia's
influence soon spread
significantly under
Mori's new leadership.
[ANGO]
Another year later,
Chuuya Nakahara discovered
the truth of his own origins,
and went to confront
the gifted spy
who had befriended and
then betrayed Rando.
It turns out he wasn't dead.
I will provide a separate
report on that matter.
Document Number I-4190 C:
"History of the Young Gifted
and their role in the
Arahabaki Incident."
Report by Ministry
of Internal Affairs
Gifted Special
Operations Division
Assistant Counselor,
Ango Sakaguchi.
[FYODOR D.] I've never done
anything bad before.
I've never cried before.
No one in the world
is kinder than I am.
My ability allows me to control
space and consciousness.
Now... how many lies
did I just tell?
Next time on
Bungo Stray Dogs , Episode 29:
"My Ill Deeds Are
the Work of God."
May you be freed from the
shackles of your crimes,
and your soul be salvaged.