[ANGO] Those 88 days
produced more casualties
than any other in Yokohama's
criminal underworld.
Numerous organizations
were involved
in what would be known...
as the Dragon Head Conflict.
[ANGO]
One year prior to the events...
[gasps]
The King of the Sheep!
[yells]
[CHUUYA]
Run as much as you like...
...but you'll never
escape gravity.
Damn monster!
You're just the beginning.
I'm gonna kill all
of the Port Mafia.
[OUGAI] Things aren't
looking good for us.
Our weapon smugglers are
two weeks behind schedule.
If this keeps up,
our men will literally be
bringing knives to a gun fight.
And while the violence
continues to rise,
contracts for our protection
business continue to dwindle.
[OUGAI sighs]
[OUGAI]
What do you think, Dazai?
Are we not actually
cut out for this work?
[OSAMU]
Really now, Mori?
Not having money,
or intel, or supplies,
or even the trust of
our subordinates.
You knew that was going
to be the situation
from the beginning.
That's so harsh.
By the way, is there
a reason you're mixing
hypertension and
hypotension medications?
I thought taking them together
might be a cozy way to go out.
Listen, Dazai.
You were the sole witness
when I inherited
the boss' position,
so as a result,
you're the only other one
who can verify his will.
I can't afford to have
you senselessly die.
[OUGAI] How are you
feeling today, Boss?
[BOSS] Doctor, tell the
board this is an order:
Kill all enemy organizations,
military police,
anyone else who opposes
the Port Mafia by sundown.
[OUGAI]
That would be most unwise.
I don't care how many
of our own need to die.
Just kill them.
Just kill them all. Kill them.
Kill them. Kill every...
[OUGAI]
I hear you loud and clear.
[OUGAI] The boss has
succumbed to illness.
He left behind a will
entrusting me with his position.
You're the witness to
that fact. Understood?
[OSAMU]
Looks like you made a mistake.
Your reasoning to choose
someone who attempts suicide
as your accomplice was sound,
but here I am a year
later, still kicking.
[OUGAI]
I made no mistake.
It seems to me that you and I
were successful in our mission.
The mission isn't complete yet.
I haven't been silenced and
I'm aware of the assassination.
If I'd committed
suicide afterward,
then I would've been
the perfect accomplice.
The reason I took my own life
wouldn't have
mattered to anyone.
Once my testimony had already
helped you become boss,
nobody would've suspected.
[OUGAI]
You remind me of someone.
[OSAMU]
Huh?
You know, if I was
going to shut you up,
I could've done so
a long time ago.
If you'd like me to,
I can prepare something
that would end your
life peacefully.
You could?
[OUGAI] But in exchange, I want
you to do something for me.
It's nothing serious. You won't
be in any kind of danger.
No big deal.
[OSAMU]
I'm not buyin' it.
[OUGAI] I trust you already
know about Suribachi City
in the Yokohama settlement.
There's a rumor that a certain
individual from the past
has been sighted in that area.
I want you to go and
investigate this rumor.
Take this contract with you.
It's called the "Silver Oracle."
Show this to any member
of the Port Mafia
and they will do whatever
you ask of them.
Who's the rumor about?
[OUGAI]
Take a guess.
[OSAMU] Huh. It'd be a rumor you
don't want picking up speed.
Ah. I see. It'd have to
be him, wouldn't it?
The subject of the rumors
has to be the previous boss.
[OUGAI]
Precisely.
There are some people who must
never raise from their graves.
I trust you understand
where I'm coming from.
[OSAMU]
Just make me that drug.
[OUGAI] This will be
your first official job.
Welcome to the Port Mafia.
[OSAMU]
Oh, right.
[OUGAI]
Huh?
Who was this "someone"
you said I reminded you of?
Myself, of course.
Tell me, Dazai, why
is it you wish to die?
[OSAMU]
Let's turn that question around.
Is there really any value
to this thing we call "living"?
[HIROTSU]
The Yokohama foreign settlement.
There was once a
giant explosion here.
In the resulting crater,
people began building
what would eventually become
known as Suribachi City.
[OSAMU]
Hmm...
They drink metal plating to
kill themselves overseas, huh?
Wait.
But it melts down their organs
while they're still alive?
Yuck. Glad I never tried that.
Hey, did you know about
that? Mister, uhh...
[HIROTSU]
It's Hirotsu.
I'll keep that fact
in mind, thank you.
[HIROTSU] This is the boy
who was with the boss
when the previous
boss passed away.
I shouldn't underestimate him.
[gasps]
Dazai.
[OSAMU]
Yes?
[HIROTSU] This area is
in a state of conflict.
You should be careful.
How so?
[HIROTSU] The Port Mafia
is currently pitted
against three organizations:
First, Takasekai. Second, GSS.
And finally, an army comprised
entirely of juveniles
referred to as
the Sheep, which--
Boss is calling.
What's up?
Mm-hm. I've learned
a few things.
Long story short,
I found the whereabouts
of the previous boss.
Looks like he came back.
Straight from the pits of Hell.
Mm-hm. I'll give you a proper
report when I get b--
What was that?!
[CHUUYA laughs]
[CHUUYA]
Ahh. This is perfect.
It's just a kid!
They're really scrapping
the bottom of the barrel,
those Port Mafia.
I think you should know
I really hate pain.
I'm gonna give you two choices.
Die now, or die after
giving me information.
Either's fine with me.
Kill me now, then.
If you can make it
painless, all the better.
[CHUUYA] Sheesh. What kinda
suicidal punk are you?
[OSAMU]
You're a punk, too, ya know.
[CHUUYA] Except unlike you,
I'm not just any punk.
Enough of this chit-chat.
Tell me about this "Arahabaki"
you're lookin' for.
Oh? Arahabaki?
How interesting.
So that's the target.
You've heard about it then.
[OSAMU]
Nope. Never have.
"Those who step into
the Sheep's territory
will be met with
vicious retaliation."
I see. So you're the
King of the Sheep.
Chuuya Nakahara,
manipulator of gravity.
I'm not their King, all right?
But I do have a trump
card up my sleeve.
[OSAMU] Oh. You're a cocky,
over-confident child.
I hate people like you so much.
[CHUUYA]
Oh, yeah?
Well, I hate condescending
little pricks like you
more than anything
in this world.
[HIROTSU]
That's enough of that.
[CHUUYA]
Huh?
Come quietly, or else.
[CHUUYA] Ooh, I'm shakin'
in my boots, old man.
Do you even know who I am?
The King of the Sheep, was it?
[CHUUYA]
No, dumbass!
I just happen to have
a good card up my sleeve.
The card of power, perhaps?
So you're a gifted, too, huh?
Be careful.
This kid controls the gravity
of anything he touches.
Understood.
Is that all you've got, old man?
I was expecting a little more.
Don't disappoint me now!
Too slow.
[HIROTSU]
It's all over for you now.
What're you talking
about? I've beaten you.
[OSAMU]
You sure about that?
You've lost your ability
to control gravity now.
Oh?
[OSAMU] I'm able to nullify
the powers of others.
[HIROTSU]
Now, boy.
It's time you faced a reckoning.
[gasps]
[OSAMU]
He got me.
Right before you could use your
special ability, he kicked me.
Once I let go, he was able
to use his powers again.
He used his gravity
ability to fly backwards,
and got away unscathed.
[CHUUYA] I'll deal
with you later, twerp.
Let's go, "Grandpa."
[OSAMU]
Watch out!
The old boss.
[OUGAI]
You must be Chuuya Nakahara.
Welcome to the Port Mafia.
Thank you for the
warm invitation.
[OUGAI] I hear you put my men
through their paces yesterday.
[CHUUYA]
Yeah, but we were interrupted
thanks to a "mystery guest."
But I'm guessing
that's why I'm here.
Why are you
investigating Arahabaki?
[door opens]
[OUGAI]
Ah, Dazai.
You've arrived.
Huh? You're that kid with a
death wish from yesterday!
[OSAMU] And I see that
you're as lively as ever.
Thanks to you, I'm sporting
some pretty bad injuries here.
Having only known each
other for a day,
you two seem to have
really hit it off.
Huh?
Now then, I'd like
to talk to you
about what happened
yesterday, Chuuya.
Rando, would you
please release him?
[RANDO] Sir, I don't believe
that would be very prudent.
This boy is quite dangerous.
[OUGAI]
I have measures in place.
By the way, Rando,
you look colder than usual.
Are you all right?
[RANDO] Much to my
embarrassment, I'm freezing.
I feel I could die
at any minute.
You're cold?
Dressed in all that?
You may step down.
[RANDO]
Thank you, sir.
If you would excuse me.
[CHUUYA] It's not even
remotely cold in here.
Clearly he's just a wuss.
Believe it or not,
he's a secondary executive
and an excellent ability user.
[CHUUYA] Psh, whatever.
That dude doesn't interest me.
Mori, can we get to
business already?
Oh. My apologies.
Moving on.
Would you be interested
in affiliating
with the Port Mafia, Chuuya?
Huh?
Well, I suppose I
should've expected that.
I still believe that
our over-all goals
are probably in alignment.
Give it some time
and think it over.
You can make a decision
after we determine
what we can offer each other.
Don't you dare make
it sound that easy.
You forget what you've
done to this city?
[OUGAI]
Our previous boss' rampage...
It was he, and his tyrannical
rule, that led this city
into a state of chaos and still
haunts people to this day.
But he is no longer
with the living.
I witnessed his passing myself.
That's why, if rumors exist
that his rule of violence
and terror has returned,
we must discover their origins.
For the protection
of our people.
Mori...
[CHUUYA] I've heard some damning
rumors about you as well.
They say the old boss
didn't die of illness.
That you actually
murdered the bastard.
It is a little hard
to swallow that
right before kicking the bucket,
he'd give his position
to his doctor.
You're right.
I murdered the previous boss.
[gasps]
[OSAMU groans]
[OUGAI] I used this
trusty scalpel of mine,
then I blamed on it
on his disease;
said it had killed
him in the end.
Do you have a problem with that?
[grunts]
You're serious?
[OUGAI]
Chuuya, would you participate
in a joint investigation?
The rumors we've heard about
the previous boss' return
and this "Arahabaki" that you're
after are clearly related.
I think we could achieve a
mutually beneficial relationship
simply by sharing information.
[CHUUYA]
And if I refuse?
[SHEEP MEMBER]
Hey, Chuuya, are you there?
We need your help.
The Port Mafia caught us.
You can get us
outta this, right?
Please, come and save us,
like you always--
[growls]
Your group controls prime
real estate in Yokohama,
and even owns artillery.
But for a group so bent on
vengeance, excluding yourself,
all of you are no
more than children.
As a fellow leader,
I sympathize with your
difficult circumstances.
Bastard.
See that? Such bloodlust
from this one.
It's clear the most aggressive
wielder of violence
in this room is this boy here.
But to us, violence is merely
one tool at our disposal.
The Mafia's true nature is
to control our surroundings
using a plethora of means.
Boss, why are you lecturing
me about this right now?
Indeed. Why would that be?
[CHUUYA] I'll consider
exchanging information.
But you're gonna have
to spill the beans first.
We'll see how I feel afterwards.
[OUGAI]
Very well.
We're investigating a rumor
that the previous boss
has reappeared.
Dazai's intel shows
he's been seen
three times in two weeks.
And in each of those cases,
he was sighted in
Suribachi City.
You saw him the fourth time,
when he fought you yesterday
with that flurry
of black flames.
The dead don't
come back to life.
I don't disagree with you.
But as of now, we must
consider all possibilities.
[OUGAI] This security footage
is of the Port Mafia's vault.
It's by far the most
difficult room to enter
in our headquarters.
Is that him?
[BOSS] I have returned from
the smoldering pits of Hell.
Do you know why, Doctor?
It's pure anger...
He feeds incessantly upon it.
It was he who summoned
me back from Hell
with the intention of having
me breed even more anger.
The beast of the gods...
Arahabaki of the black flames.
[OUGAI] That's all the footage
we have in our security records.
Very few people know about this,
and the ones that do
are under a gag order.
[OSAMU] That may contain
the situation here,
but what if he gave that same
speech somewhere else in town?
[OUGAI]
He may have.
And perhaps he said his
death was by assassination.
If his supporters
were to find out,
a third of our organization
would turn against me.
[sighs]
[OUGAI] Win or lose, the Port
Mafia would be finished.
[OSAMU sighs]
Tell me, Chuuya, how much
do you know about Arahabaki?
I'll tell you what I've
learned about him.
Arahabaki is a legendary
servant of the gods.
But because he is so ancient,
his true form is unclear.
[CHUUYA]
Hmph.
You don't actually believe
in that stuff, do you?
[OUGAI] You entertained the
notion as well, did you not?
You hunted down the same
rumors that we did,
and were willing to follow them
whenever they took you.
We get a lot of people
coming and going.
There's no easy way to find
the source of the rumors.
Do you know how Suribachi
City came to be?
There was a mysterious explosion
at the end of the
boss' rampage.
It was built in the aftermath.
Word around town
is that explosion
was caused by Arahabaki.
[OUGAI]
Hm?
[CHUUYA]
Eight years ago,
they say a captured,
foreign soldier was tortured
at a military facility
in the settlement.
His rage and hatred
summoned Arahabaki,
and a torrent of black flames
annihilated the facility,
along with everything
and everyone in it.
That explosion led to
the creation of...
[OUGAI]
Suribachi City, as we know it.
What do you think of
the story, Dazai?
[OSAMU] Whoever was responsible
seems to have a special ability
we don't know about.
As for the video, if what
we saw is actually real,
that doesn't bode well for us.
[OUGAI]
So true.
Dazai, I have an order for you.
Before the previous boss'
staunch supporters
catch wind of that message,
find the one responsible.
Understood?
Will I be working by myself?
It seems time may
be running out.
[OUGAI]
You won't be alone.
Chuuya will be there to
assist you in your mission.
What?!
Absolutely not!
Why in the world would I need
to work with that little punk?
You wanna run that by me again?
I'll beat the shit
outta you, kid!
[OSAMU] Stop talking like
you're older than me!
You're still a kid--
a very small one at that!
[CHUUYA]
Why, you...
[OSAMU] You really oughta
drink more milk,
it might help you get bigger...
[CHUUYA]
Lay off about my size, jackass!
I'm only 15! I'm still growing!
That's enough from both of you.
[OUGAI]
Chuuya.
I trust you understand you're in
no position to refuse my orders.
You, too, Dazai.
If the boss' supporters
discover the truth,
as my accomplice,
you will surely be tortured.
Death will not be swift.
You really think pairing
us together is wise?
I have a number of
reasons for doing so.
Interviewing witnesses
will be far easier
if done by an outsider.
Chuuya also needs
to be monitored
in case he tries to betray us.
And the rest...
[OUGAI chuckles]
[OUGAI]
...is a secret.
[CHUUYA]
Hey, you wanna maybe tell me
what's goin' on, asshole?
[OSAMU] Sorry. Would you mind
not talking to me right now?
I'm busy breathing.
[CHUUYA] I'm gonna rip your
head off, you suicidal maniac.
Now how 'bout you
answer my question
and tell me what we're doing!
[OSAMU]
We're going to investigate.
Huh?
[OSAMU]
We're interviewing people
who were closest
to the explosion.
[CHUUYA]
Explosion?
[OSAMU] A week ago,
there was an explosion nearby.
Similar to the one we
experienced yesterday
in our battle.
The previous boss wasn't
sighted at this incident,
but looking at the similarities,
the cause is likely the same.
We're going to go speak with
a survivor from that explosion.
"Survivor" implies that
there were casualties.
Yes. Members of the Port
Mafia--not that you care.
This survivor we're
meeting with is gifted.
Actually you've already
met this person.
[explosion]
[OSAMU]
Oh, my.
It looks like the culprit's
already gotten to them.
Then quit gab'n
and move yer ass!
[sighs]
[CHUUYA] Don't think we're
gonna score an interview here.
[SOLDIER] Put your arms up
and slowly turn around.
[CHUUYA]
Hm?
Check this out.
We didn't even have to go
hunting for our dinner.
I didn't feel like doing
an interview anyway.
I'd rather just skip all
the boring, chatty crap
and deal with the one
who's directly responsible.
Stay back. I'm gonna enjoy this.
[OSAMU sighs]
[OSAMU]
What a child.
[OSAMU] Well, it was certainly
an interesting story.
I understand everything now.
Thanks to you,
the mystery is solved.
[CHUUYA]
Then tell me who's behind it.
[OSAMU] Why don't we
have a contest to see
who can identify
the culprit first?
But if I win...
you're my dog for life.
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
Episode 27: "God of Fire."
[CHUUYA]
Fine! Bring it!