[ATSUSHI]
I just received a message.
It said, "Do not fight
the Port Mafia."
Our president gave that
order from his deathbed,
so shouldn't we
forget about fighting
and find a way to capture
whoever controls the virus?
Yes, but we've already
attempted that.
The enemy is a crafty one.
It'll be impossible to uproot
all of its meticulously
prepared traps in time.
Even for you, Rampo?
That's precisely
what I'm saying.
Regardless, to fight is
a violation of our orders.
And?
[RAMPO]
Each of you to need to decide
what action you will take.
Rampo, are you
asking us to choose
between obeying the president
or fighting the Mafia?
[RAMPO]
That's right.
But we don't have much
time to mull it over.
If the Port Mafia finds
out our president
is in a protected ability space,
they'll switch tactics.
Our friends and family--
anyone important to us--
might be taken hostage.
They might even be killed.
Unless we give
them the president.
Even the Agency
may have no choice
but to buckle to such threats.
[HIROTSU]
The only path open to us
is soaked with blood and
littered with human entrails.
It's a path the Mafia is
accustomed to traveling.
[JUNICHIROU]
I'll do it. I'll fight.
Let's face it.
We usually have to hurt somebody
in order to protect
somebody else.
I'll go along as well.
Let's just say I have a bit
of a bone to pick with Mori.
I'm sure he would find
a certain poetic beauty
to such an ending.
[KYOUKA]
I'm afraid of him.
[KYOUKA] But if my knowledge of
the Port Mafia can be useful
to everyone here,
then I should go, as well.
You sure, Kyouka?
[KENJI] Whether what we're
doing is right or wrong,
I have no idea.
But still, if our people
walk into trouble,
they'll need help,
so I'll go with them.
Kenji, I...
Kunikida, what about you?
We have our orders.
The president wants us to keep
this city safe and stable.
To protect the
citizens from Fyodor,
who wants to destroy
everything in Yokohoma.
So then, do you intend to
try to find the gifted?
[DOPPO]
No.
If I attempt that,
more innocent people will die!
Like that little girl.
If another death like that
happens before my eyes...
...how do I live with myself?
[RAMPO]
Kunikida, you are the strongest
and most virtuous
of us in the Agency.
That's why the enemy tried
to break you down first.
Don't ever forget that.
[ATSUSHI] We can't get into
a fight with the Port Mafia.
We'll be playing right into
the mastermind's hands.
But it's not like the others
don't already know that.
[RAMPO]
Atsushi, you coming?
Or maybe you have a plan for us
to go after the
mastermind instead.
Is that it?
Well, I-I... I'm still
figuring that out.
Thought so. You contacted Katai.
Didn't you ask him to look into
the Rats in the House of Dead?
[RAMPO] That investigation
has been ongoing, right?
[RAMPO] There's a very
slim chance that Katai
managed to find the
mastermind's location.
Go find out if he has.
Got it.
[PORT MAFIA AGENTS shouting]
[KENJI]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
That really stings!
The Port Mafia sure
does pack a punch.
Okay, my turn!
[ALL gasp]
Here we go!
[PORT MAFIA AGENTS screaming]
[AKIKO]
Move in!
'Kay!
They actually charged
through the front door?!
I'm on my way. Protect the boss.
Shit!
[RAMPO] I can't let you go
and do that, Mr. Fancy Hat.
[CHUUYA]
Hm?
[RAMPO] I can't have you
lowering our chances of success
with your involvement.
So, with that said,
I am here to stop
that from happening.
[CHUUYA]
You serious, buddy?
I know you're a big deal
to the Detective Agency,
but I doubt you're
much of a fighter.
[RAMPO] Maybe, but aren't you
the one who lost to Dazai?
[CHUUYA]
You wanna feel what it's like
to crushed by gravity?
[chuckles]
[RAMPO] Nothing's impossible
for a great detective.
[knocking]
[ATSUSHI]
Katai, I'm coming in!
It's urgent!
[ATSUSHI]
He's gone?
Katai would never leave
his futon behind.
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
Mr. Kunikida!
Katai's not here. Where is he?
What're you doing?!
[ATSUSHI]
What's that?
[DOPPO] Katai had been
recording footage of his room
in case anything happened.
Mr. Kunikida, why aren't you
fighting the Port Mafia?
If we disregard the
rules and go after him,
more innocent people will die.
[DOPPO] I may not have been
able to save that girl,
but I can save the president,
along with the rest of the city.
I can't think of a better way
to try and honor her memory.
There he is. Looks
like he was working.
[KATAI]
So this is their...?
[DOPPO gasps]
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[PORT MAFIA AGENTS chattering]
[ICHIYOU]
Hm.
A doll?
[KYOUKA]
Move and you're dead.
Tell me what the code is
to the underground room
where the boss is sleeping.
I heard you joined
the Detective Agency
and stopped being an assassin.
That last part seems false.
[KYOUKA]
I won't kill without a purpose.
That being said, if you don't
tell me the entry code...
...I'll make sure you can
never fire a gun again.
The moment I decided
to take on this job,
I was prepared for that.
Oh. That's a shame.
It's been a while, Kyouka.
[ICHIYOU]
Akutagawa, sir!
[AKUTAGAWA] Go and inform the
higher-ups of the intruder.
I'll handle it from here.
[ICHIYOU]
Understood.
[AKUTAGAWA chuckles]
Haven't fought someone with
a spine in a long time.
[CHUUYA]
You wanna feel what it's like
to be crushed by gravity?
[RAMPO chuckles]
Nothing's impossible
for a great detective.
[CHUUYA yelling]
[RAMPO]
Do you like mystery novels?
I can't get my fist out!
There are a thousand
characters in this one.
And half of those
characters are murderers.
Assuming we don't die in
this ability-less world,
I'll be seeing you again
when we make it out.
[PORT MAFIA GUARDS gasping]
[PORT MAFIA GUARD gasps]
[POE] I was so eager to write
a good mystery novel
for his little game.
I'm afraid Rampo really
took advantage of me.
[POE]
This elaborate tale of massacre
will take a top
agent like Chuuya,
and even dear Rampo,
several days to escape from.
Or maybe both of
them will perish,
and I alone will stand in
the spotlight of victory!
[laughing]
Oh.
If Rampo really were to
die in that world though,
what would I do with myself?
Not good enough!
[AKUTAGAWA] You're an
assassin who specializes
in black ops and ambushes.
You can't win when you challenge
a stronger opponent head on.
I'm not convinced being
with the Detective Agency
is the right path for you.
You're wrong about that.
You don't know who I am anymore.
[AKUTAGAWA] She dematerialized
and escaped my bonds.
I can't even touch her
with physical attacks.
Very well...
Devoured Space!
[KYOUKA] You used to tell me
I had one purpose in life--
to kill people.
[AKUTAGAWA]
It was a decoy!
[KYOUKA]
Goodbye.
[YUKICHI] To be knocked down
by such a crude ability...
[static]
[AKIKO]
We're under fire,
pinned down like a
butterfly to a board.
Ugh. How are things
over there, Atsushi?
[ATSUSHI]
No leads so far.
Also...
...Katai's been eliminated.
[AKIKO]
Katai?
[AKIKO] Tell Kunikida that even
more people are about to die.
As hard as it'll be, he can't
afford to mourn for him
until after we've won.
At this rate,
we might be next to go.
[ALL]
Huh?
Why'd they stop firing?
What in the blazing
hell is that?
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[KYOUKA]
Demonic Armor.
I can't free my blade!
[AKUTAGAWA] You really
have changed, Kyouka.
Your eyes, they're
not the same ones
as when I last knew you.
[KYOUKA]
Tell me.
Are you the gifted
who can cut anything?
And what if I am?
[KYOUKA]
Cut down Demon Snow.
Avenge my parents.
And then, after you take down
Demon Snow... its master.
[KYOUKA]
Kill me.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Your eyes were filled
with vengeance and self-hatred.
They reflected no value
in your own life.
How would you be able to
know something like that?
Because I once knew a man
who had the same eyes as yours.
[KYOUKA]
What happened to him?
[AKUTAGAWA] The same thing
that happened to you.
He joined up with
a certain someone,
and that person helped calm
his desire for death.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Kyouka, I'm happy for you.
[gasps]
[ICHIYOU] Sir, you need
to retreat for now.
The Lemon Runway is coming!
[ICHIYOU]
Sir, are you there?
[AKUTAGAWA]
I hear you.
[laughing]
[MOTOJIROU] It took me three
days and nights to develop this!
I was so exhausted,
I forgot to put on underwear!
Now is the time for
us to rush the door.
Hold it. Something's
not right here.
Now then,
please allow me to introduce
today's science experiment!
I've named this one
"Watching Fireworks Up-Close"!
Don't tell me those are
all filled with...
Everyone, we need
to get outside, now.
--[JUNICHIROU] Why?
--Just do it!
[MOTOJIROU laughs]
[MOTOJIROU] I like to think of
this as "The Lemon Runway"!
My path in life is filled with
nothing but pure explosions!
[AKIKO]
Go near him
and you'll be blown
into so many pieces
even I won't be able to help.
[MOTOJIROU] This world has
always been an empty vessel.
Even happiness is but a simple
signal firing off in the brain.
Hence, the only way to discover
the true meaning of life
is to use science to dance
and play with reality!
I won't allow anyone
to kill the master
who makes my own
playtime possible!
I'll protect rule of the
universe to the end!
[MOTOJIROU laughs]
[AKIKO] Let's go.
This is a full retreat.
[LUCY]
I won't stop you.
I'm not technically
an Agency member.
Even so, as someone
who took care of you
when you were ill,
you could at least tell me
where you're going.
I'm meeting with an old friend.
[AKIKO] As long as that
idiot bomber is out there,
we're not gonna be able to
get close to their building.
[phone ringing]
[AKIKO]
What's the matter?
What did you say?!
The president's disappeared?
Stand down from your
battle stations!
The boss has vanished
from his bed.
[HIROTSU] Missing from a
contained, underground room.
I'm baffled. Perhaps we
should call a detective.
[ICHIYOU]
Sir.
[HIROTSU]
That was a joke.
We received word of a sighting
from the guards outside.
It seems the boss left
of his own free will.
He just left?
Where would he have gone
at a time like this,
knowing the Agency's after him?
I don't know.
But yet, I can think of
a reason that he left.
[HIROTSU]
He's trying to protect us.
[NAOMI]
Haruno?
[KIRAKO] Mii hasn't been home
for over two days now.
I'm gonna go look for him.
[NAOMI]
You can't!
It's dangerous out there.
Yeah, but the thing with Mii is,
when he doesn't come home,
something bad always
ends up happening.
The bombing attempt on the
police, and before that,
the illegal military activities.
I'm sacred if I don't
bring him back,
something awful will
happen to the president.
I'm sure Mii can
take care of himself.
It's you that I'm
really worried about.
The president.
Even though... Even
though he was bed-ridden,
he ignored his illness and
went out on his own to save us.
[OSAMU]
Any update on where
the president's gone,
Junichirou?
I'm afraid not.
We've got everyone we can
muster looking for him,
but we still haven't
found anything out.
[OSAMU]
That figures.
The president would've gone
someplace no one could find him.
If there's anybody who
knows where he is,
it'd be someone he has
a strong connection with.
But who is it?
And what'll they
do now, I wonder?
Who is who?
Hey, isn't that...?
That's Haruno's cat.
What's it doing here?
[OUGAI]
This place brings back memories.
[YUKICHI]
Indeed.
We were fated to meet here.
A place none of our
people know about.
We never even had
to plan for it.
It was inevitable.
I also had faith that you
would come to this place.
[YUKICHI]
Have you brought backup?
If I had, it would only
have incited another war
between our organizations.
[YUKICHI]
There's only one way to avoid
such needless bloodshed.
The two of us will duel,
one-on-one, to the death,
thus stopping the cannibalism.
[OUGAI] We both have so much
more to protect now, don't we?
[YUKICHI] It has been ten years
since last we fought each other.
[OUGAI]
Indeed.
Sadly for you, this place
will become your grave.
[OUGAI]
Vita Sexualis.
Come!
[YUKICHI] Your ability
is as vile as ever, Mori.
[OUGAI]
You draw the sword so deftly
that you don't even see it.
I'd expect no less
of the Silver Wolf,
once a sword-wielding assassin.
Fukuzawa, there's something I'd
like to tell you before we die.
[YUKICHI] Next time on
Bungo Stray Dogs , Episode 36:
"Cannibalism, Part 3."
[OUGAI]
Now, my dear Elise,
make sure that he
gets his shots.