[DJ] Our next request is
from The Nutcracker Suite :
"Waltz of the Flowers."
[PUSHKIN] Yo, Ivan.
I carried out the orders.
Hey, Ivan, you there?
Can you hear me?
Hey!
Silence please.
I'm not able to hear
my Tchaikovsky.
[PUSHKIN]
Listening to the radio again?
Look, I infected the
intruders with the virus.
So... what's the next
order from the boss?
[FYODOR D.]
Hmm.
Our master instructs you to
do what you can to escape.
[PUSHKIN]
No backup?
You know, if I get caught,
the virus'll be lost, too.
I have no intention
of protecting anyone
but our master.
[sighs, chuckles]
I'm so blissed out.
Really?
I'd give anything to be there
to see the look on your face
when the bliss fades.
The look on my face, huh?
If the master were
to ask it of me,
I would gladly peel it off
without a second thought.
You are definitely a nutcase.
[groans]
[PUSHKIN]
Those bastards are after me.
[chuckling]
I'll see you on the surface.
[phone ringing]
Finally. A connection.
Go ahead, Dazai!
[OSAMU] I trust you're chasing
the gifted with the virus.
His virus infects the victim
through open wounds.
The fever and the nausea make
it difficult to even stand up.
Don't let it so much
as graze you.
I'll take care of Fyodor.
Make sure you don't let that
gifted out of your sight.
[PUSHKIN chuckling]
Damn it. Can't reach him.
[PUSHKIN chuckles]
[BOTH yell]
Weretiger!
Akutagawa!
Neither the wretched
dog nor the weretiger
live up to their reputation.
Huh?
What in the hell is that?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Go faster than him!
You're quite the
rough ride, you know.
Shut up!
Go left!
Right!
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?!
Pick up the pace!
Don't think. Just run, you fool!
Enough! You're not
paying for this ride!
[ATSUSHI]
Got ya!
You're too late.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Weretiger!
[ATSUSHI]
What is that?
[PUSHKIN]
Catch ya later!
Damn. He's getting away.
[IVAN sighs]
[IVAN]
I'm so fortunate.
My wonderful master, Fyodor,
has given me a very
important task,
and it's an even
bigger responsibility
than guarding him.
Prepare yourself, weretiger.
We'll take him down
within a minute,
then go after the tram.
Looks like they're
on the move.
Dazai, three cars just left
the abandoned mines
from the north.
Contact the surface team
and have them followed.
Ignore them.
[JUNICHIROU]
Uh--
[OSAMU]
Those are decoys.
They're meant to slow us down.
But how can you be sure?
Because that's exactly
what I would do.
[JUNICHIROU]
Uh. Understood.
Hey, Junichirou, a cargo truck's
leaving west of the mines.
[JUNICHIROU]
Could that be the one?
[OSAMU]
No, it's not.
Ignore it, too.
[JUNICHIROU] Now we're seeing
several armed soldiers
moving to the southeast.
It looks like they're
escorting someone in a hood.
[OSAMU]
Ignore them.
Uh. Really? But, what if--?
[OSAMU]
We're trying to capture a demon.
We need every hand we
can spare. Ignore them.
[yells]
[IVAN laughs]
[IVAN]
You're wasting your time.
My ability allows me to
manipulate the earth.
There's no amount
of cutting or crushing
that could ever defeat
my stone giant.
Weretiger!
[IVAN]
Keep this in mind, too.
You're now trapped in
the belly of my ability.
Even the ground upon which
you stand is your enemy.
[gasps]
[IVAN] I'm impressed
you survived my blow,
with only the mere
ability of the weretiger.
It seems that there's a
lot more pain to be had
before we can reach an
equal amount of happiness.
[ATSUSHI] If we can't
defeat the stone giant,
we'll have to go after
the gifted himself.
But if this ground
can be controlled
by his special ability, just
getting close will be difficult.
Our only choice is...
Akutagawa.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Yeah.
[ATSUSHI] Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Of course.
How many times do you think
we've tried to kill each other?
You stay here, you lunatic.
And you keep running, idiot.
It's no use!
What?
It can't be...
[IVAN] He's using the black
cloth like a foothold
to avoid touching the earth.
I can't tell where he is!
[ATSUSHI]
Gotcha!
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[IVAN] I'll create
a fully enclosed defense
using fast-spinning rocks.
If I can't tell where
you're coming from,
I'll just protect myself
in all directions.
Now, wretched dog,
it's your turn!
[AKUTAGAWA] "Even the ground
upon which you stand
is your enemy."
I'm afraid to say I've
said those same words
to my enemies countless times.
[ATSUSHI]
Damn it. You used me as bait.
You're the one who charged in
knowing full well
that'd be the case.
Of course I knew it.
"How many times have we
tried to kill each other?"
[AKUTAGAWA] Mmm. Let's go
after the tram, weretiger.
Be my horse.
Oh, c'mon! Not that ag--
[AKUTAGAWA]
Weretiger!
It's a golem.
It's just a fake.
[AKUTAGAWA gasps]
Oh, no. It's the virus.
[IVAN] My generous master
is the only one
who brings joy to
this godless world.
Evil are those who
stand in his way.
I just infected you with the
virus through your wound.
I barely have any strength left.
I can't go on.
And I can't chase that tram,
even if we do beat him.
[laughing]
[JUNICHIROU] Dazai, there's
an unidentified helicopter
approaching from the east.
There's no way we can fight
them with our equipment.
Call in the military police!
Copter?
Do you see anybody
on the ground there?
[JUNICHIROU]
Hold on.
Kenji, are there any
people down there?
Looks like there's a hiker
at the base of the mountain.
I can't see his face
'cause he's wearing a hat.
[OSAMU]
He's the one!
Huh?
Do all you can to
stop that hiker.
Send in Mori's men,
too, immediately.
[JUNICHIROU]
Uh. Got it.
Dazai, it's not him!
It's a normal guy, handcuffed
with grenades in his mouth!
It's not Fyodor!
[gasps]
[IVAN]
You two are surprisingly strong.
It looks like there's
no end in sight.
[BOTH gasp]
[IVAN] I guess I'll just
have to drown you slowly.
[ATSUSHI]
My body's sinking
and I don't have the
strength to escape.
Bye now.
Oh, shit.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Weretiger.
Answer my question from earlier.
Tell me why it is you fight.
We don't have time for that now!
There's still a way for us to
escape. It's our last resort.
But you must answer me first.
Why do you fight?
You know the answer
to that question.
[ORPHANAGE MAN 1]
Those who cannot save others
do not deserve to live.
[AKUTAGAWA] You fight to escape
your childhood memories.
You fight so that you can
earn the right to live.
Except I heard that your
childhood master died.
No, he's not dead.
He's standing behind
you right now.
[AKUTAGAWA gasps]
[ATSUSHI] He will always
be alive inside my head.
His words keep repeating.
All I can hear is,
"Do what's right."
I'll never get revenge against
someone who is dead.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hm. That's rather brutal.
It makes my death seem
trivial by comparison.
What the hell?!
[AKUTAGAWA]
If I'm a wretched dog,
then you're a wandering dog.
This is the solution
to our problem.
So you'd better fight
and give me that answer!
'Cause if you lose like this...
[AKUTAGAWA]
...I'll never forgive you.
[gasps]
[IVAN gasps]
[IVAN]
One of them has escaped!
The ground is missing,
space and all!
[gasps]
[IVAN]
Teleportation.
He carved out space
with his ability...
...and was able to move!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Don't bother.
[gasps]
He just carved up my
stone like it was paper.
[AKUTAGAWA] Only those
who've tried to kill him
know what he is capable of.
It's his tiger claws.
They cut through the very
fabric of an ability.
Therefore, by expanding
and contracting the space,
he detached.
He did the very same thing
when he cut through
my Rashoumon.
[screaming]
[AKUTAGAWA] Our abilities have
become a unrivaled sword!
Physical armor and powers
are defenseless against it.
Let's go, Akutagawa!
Obliterate him, weretiger!
[ATSUSHI, AKUTAGAWA]
Beast Beneath the Moonlight,
Rashoumon!
Kokuto Zessou!
[yells]
[PUSHKIN laughs]
[PUSHKIN]
I made it out.
I win!
Fyodor and the Rats in
the House of the Dead
are all tools for
my entertainment.
Ha, ha, ha!
Weak men like me can
get away with anything!
If I had my way,
the strong would choke to
death on their own vomit!
[chuckling]
[PUSHKIN]
Huh?
[OUGAI]
See? Just as I said.
[YUKICHI]
What a simplistic escape plan.
Far too predictable
when compared to Fyodor.
He's the master of phantoms.
It's not possible!
[DOPPO] Well, we were all put
in grave danger because of you.
What have you got
to say for yourself?
[PUSHKIN] Forgive me! I'll
disable the virus right away!
I'll turn myself in! Please!
I suppose that's a good
enough apology for now.
Yes, let's forgive him.
[sighs]
[YUKICHI, OUGAI]
Absolutely no chance!
The virus is gone.
That must mean the
mission was successful.
Except...
[DOPPO]
Fyodor's missing?
[ATSUSHI] Yeah, he's
nowhere to be found.
[DOPPO]
He wasn't in the helicopter
or in the escape vehicles.
He must still be in
his hideout then.
[ATSUSHI]
But...
[chuckling]
[AKUTAGAWA]
What's so funny?
[IVAN]
I'm just happy.
I'm consistently
overcome with pure joy.
My master removed the part
of me that feels unhappiness.
Tell me, did anyone
ever once guarantee you
that capturing this base would
actually lead you to my master?
What's that?
No way.
[WAITER]
Would you like more tea?
I don't think so,
but thank you very much.
[AKUTAGAWA]
So are you suggesting
he was never even
here to begin with?!
[laughing]
Impossible.
There's no connection
to the outside world.
We've been monitoring
all communications
with a hacking ability,
and this place can't be
manipulated from the outside.
All you have to do
is listen to the music.
Music?
[IVAN] The requests being
made on this music program
are serving as a secret language
so he can relay his orders.
Our communications
make brilliant use
of all the radio waves
throughout the air.
No amount of hacking
can stop us.
So you can see now how you'd
already lost from the beginning!
[DOPPO]
Atsushi, what's going on?
Mr. Kunikida.
[DOPPO]
What?
[ATSUSHI] The Rat is
already outside the hole.
The "St. Matthew
Passion" by Bach.
It seems my time is up.
Still, they weren't nearly as
formidable as I'd thought.
It looks like I'll be
able to eliminate them
with my next move.
Hey there. Nice café, huh?
[FYODOR D.]
Huh?
I've never seen you look
so shocked before.
Don't you want to know
how I found you?
I really played my cards right.
[FYODOR D. gasps]
And my best card was
right in front of me.
I couldn't have asked for
a better card than this.
He's the one who
caught the demon.
[chuckles]
It's been a long time, you Rat.
This is excellent!
You used Eyes of God?
[OSAMU]
That's right.
The inescapable eyes that
integrate surveillance footage
from all over the city.
It's extremely helpful.
I used that power
to find this place
while you were
distracted by your base.
He helped us on the
condition we'd take back
the Guild's hidden assets,
which you stole.
I have no interest in
money once it's gone,
but my pride wouldn't allow
me to leave it with Rats.
[footsteps]
[FITZGERALD]
Hm?
Don't anybody move.
We'll take it from here.
If that's all right
with you? Huh, Dazai?
[OSAMU] Sure. That's
why I called you here.
[ANGO] Put your hands
where we can see them.
[gasps]
Wait, don't touch him!
[FYODOR D. chuckles]
He's dead.
If you try anything else,
we'll shoot you on the spot.
That's fine.
Let's get going then.
[FITZGERALD]
Detective.
Do you have any idea
what his ability is?
No, sir. I don't.
This is really bad.
Yes, it is.
Are you sure it's bad?
We straight up disobeyed
the president's orders
not to fight the Port Mafia.
If that's not a bad thing,
I don't know what is!
We could get the ax.
Really?! I've never
gotten the ax before!
[JUNICHIROU]
Yeah...
Do you know what it
means to get the ax?
I know what it means.
Several people were axed
at my previous job.
It was a pain to
clean up the mess.
Oh, forget it. She doesn't know
what the word means, either.
[RAMPO]
Ooh! Look at all these snacks!
[JUNICHIROU]
Rampo!
I see that you made it
out of the mystery novel.
Of course. I identified
all 500 criminals.
Mr. Fancy Hat's still inside.
He gave up on the mystery novel
and just started
beating everyone up.
It's the president.
[DOPPO] We will accept any
punishment to the full extent.
[YUKICHI] Your punishment will
be determined at a later date.
[YUKICHI]
But I am deeply grateful
for your work on this matter.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[YUKICHI] Well done,
everyone. Very well done.
I've never seen such
a beautiful place before.
[OSAMU]
Yeah. It's a fine ship.
Atsushi.
Yes?
[OSAMU] How was it working
alongside Akutagawa?
[ATSUSHI]
It was awful.
I never wanna partner
with him again.
[OSAMU chuckles]
And why's that?
[ATSUSHI]
We're completely incompatible.
He's so short sighted.
Besides...
[AKUTAGAWA]
In six months...
...I'm going to kill you.
Prepare yourself well.
When we first fought
each other on the ship,
I utterly despised you for
being so incredibly fortunate.
But I see you somewhat
differently now.
However, until I defeat you,
it will be impossible
for me to move on.
And so... you must die.
[OSAMU]
What'd you tell him?
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, c'mon, Dazai.
I'm sure you can
guess what I said.
[OSAMU]
Yes, I have a vague idea.
[ATSUSHI]
All right.
But on one condition.
Don't kill anyone for
the next six months.
Hopefully there's
a simple lesson
you'll take away from that.
You might finally learn
how to win Dazai's approval.
And the fact that
weakness and strength
aren't always what they seem.
You might also figure out
you're already ahead of me.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Very well.
[ATSUSHI]
I'll get stronger.
I'll ask Mr. Kunikida
to teach me to fight,
and I'll train to control
my ability better,
so I can face down
Akutagawa's strength
six months from now.
[ATSUSHI]
And then,
I can be freed from the
shackles of that bind me.
I figured you'd say
something like that.
Huh?
[OSAMU] A Mafia member
who doesn't kill, huh?
You and Akutagawa
are both fighters.
[OSAMU]
Just like the rest of us.
Raise your glass.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
All right, but what
are we toasting to?
Heh.
To the Stray Dogs.
[ATSUSHI]