[Sho screams]
[SHO] It's called Guyver...
Guyver!
[VAMORE] That's the Guyver!
[explosions]
[Ramotith death roar]
[SHO] I wonder if my
body will be all right
after transforming like that.
[FUMIO] Aren't you hungry, Son?
[Sho slight surprise]
You aren't still sick, are you?
No, I'm fine, Dad.
[FUMIO] Oh, you know
that cement factory
that went out of business?
[FUMIO] The lady next
door was telling me
that apparently a bomb or
something went off over there.
[Sho shocked]
[FUMIO] And then there was that
deal with the police car.
These days... you never
can tell. Just be careful.
There's some really crazy
stuff out there.
Know what I mean?
[SHO] Thanks for dinner!
Well, I guess I'm going
up to my room now.
You don't wanna watch TV?
[SHO] Nah, not today.
Oh yeah, Sho.
Next week we should...
That boy. I don't know
what's wrong.
Oh well... I guess
he's just at that age.
There's a lot of crazy
stuff out there, he says.
He doesn't even know
the half of it. Man...
[crashing sound]
[Sho alarmed]
Who's there?!
[TETSURO] Sho, it's me!
Tetsuro? Oh...
What are you doing
outside my window?
[TETSURO] Don't you remember? I
used to sneak in like this
all the time back when
we were kids.
Come on man, lemme in.
Whatdoyamean when we were kids?
What the hell are you
talking about ?
[TETSURO] Shh, be quiet.
[SHO] All right...
Don't hurt yourself.
[TETSURO] Man, that's a lot
harder than it used to be.
That wore me out. Hey? What's
with the alarm clock, dude?
Oh, this thing? It's nothing!
I gotta be really careful,
you know.
[SHO] Oh yeah... me too, huh?
You're fine. You shouldn't
have to worry Sho.
[TETSURO] It's not you
they're after.
It's the Guyver.
Yeah, but remember those guys at
the factory saw me transform.
But that doesn't really matter
since they're all
dead now, right?
They're all dead...
[TETSURO] Don't let
it get to you.
I mean... they were monsters,
weren't they?
Anyway, you gotta make sure
those guys don't find out
anything about you.
You better stay away from my
house for the time being.
And I won't be coming
here anymore either.
I'm taking time off school too.
-No way...
[TETSURO] I don't want to
get other people
involved in our problems.
Of course, that doesn't
mean I'm just going to
hide out and do nothing.
I'm going to go try
talking to some people
on the world wide web.
It's a long shot,
but someone out there
might be able to help us.
[SHO] But... wouldn't it be
better just to go to the police?
Come on, use your head here!
[TETSURO] Those Chronos guys
are doing all this weird stuff
out in the open and the
police and media pretend
like nothing's happening at all.
Whoever those guys are,
I bet they have connections
all over the place. Sho...
Yeah?
All that happened today finally
opened my eyes.
This isn't science fiction we're
talking about. It's reality.
And if we're not careful, we
could both wind up dead.
[TETSURO] It's a matter
of survival.
Survival?
To be totally honest with you,
I think it would
probably be best if we both left
town as soon as possible.
[TETSURO] But we can't just
leave our families behind.
Tetsuro, hold on a minute!
[TETSURO] We should at least
think about changing schools.
We'll go to different ones,
of course.
Okay, good.
C'mon! This is
completely insane!
[SHO] What if I don't want
to change schools?
You can't just burst in here
and start deciding
what I can and can't do!
Listen, this a matter
of life or death!
[TETSURO] I don't think you
realize the situation here!
You're a part of this too!
Okay, I get it.
You don't have to shove it
down my throat like that.
[TETSURO] You DON'T get it!
For as long as I've known you,
you've always been the type to
let the world pass you by.
You can't just sit around
and wait!
Yeah, and you've always been
the type of person
who jumps the gun, haven't
you, Tetsuro?
[TETSURO] Yeah, i's called
"seizing the opportunity!"
[SHO] Faster doesn't always
mean "better", you know.
You need to slow down and
give this more thought.
Coming up with a plan is better
than sitting and doing nothing!
I'm being cautious, all right?
I'm being cautious too!
You're being reckless!
When we found the unit by the
pond, you were the one who...
[building reaction noise]
Hey! I'm done with the shower!
[SHO] Uh... Okay!
[TETSURO] Listen...
I'm going home.
Hey!
Tetsuro... I'm... going
to think this over.
Yeah, whatever.
[GENZO] I can't believe he was
able to defeat Vamore!
The Guyver's abilities are
beyond comprehension.
Just look at Inspector Risker.
When he merged with the Guyver,
he gave off readings far greater
than even the most
powerful Zoanoids.
I had no idea it was
that powerful.
[GENZO] We have to remedy this
mistake at all costs!
Has there been any progress in
the search for the missing unit?
It seems to have slipped through
our blockade at Mount Narisawa.
Yes, we discovered signs
indicating that the unit was
appropriated after
the explosion.
Judging by the footprints
we found in the area,
we assume that someone took
it from the site.
What do you mean "someone"?
Welcome back home, Father.
I finished next year's
operations research.
If you'd like to read it, it's
on the desk in your study.
I want you to launch an
immediate investigation
to find out if anyone else
is involved in this!
[MAKISHIMA]
Father, is something wrong?
If there's anything
I can do to help...
You stay out of this,
understand me?
[MAKISHIMA] So this isn't
an issue with the company
but with Chronos.
When I say "stay out",
you stop asking questions!
You need to learn your
place, boy.
[MAKISHIMA] You should
worry less about business
and more about saving
your neck, Genzo Makishima.
You won't be getting the units
back... not a single one.
[MEDICAL STAFF MEMBER]
No abnormal readings.
It looks like
you haven't been
affected by the unit.
No, it's changed me.
Bring back up the
data you collected
when I merged with
the Guyver unit.
[MEDICAL STAFF MEMBER] Yes, Sir.
[RISKER] To think that I could
achieve such tremendous power...
I wonder what the
look on his face
would be if he found
out about this?
[laughs]
I'm so stupid.
I really didn't mean to get
angry at Tetsuro like that...
[SHO] See you later. Oh, I'll
take out the trash, okay?
[Fumio agrees]
Bye.
[MIZUKI] What do you mean,
you're taking off school
for a while? Are you getting
sick or something, big brother?
[TETSURO] None of your business!
None of my business?
You can't do whatever you want,
just because Mom and Dad
are out of town!
Oh wait, I get it.
Your diet didn't work out
and you don't wanna take the
physical exam at school!
[TETSURO] Shut up!
Oh, whatever!
[relieved sigh]
Oh, pardon me.
[MIZUKI] Hey, what's going
on with Tetsuro?
Did something happen to him?
He said he wasn't coming to
school all of a sudden.
I dunno why, but he's been
acting really strange.
So have you, Sho.
How's that?
It was just a feeling.
But it looks like I was right.
I know you guys have always
tried to keep secrets from me.
But still. Playing hookey
is going too far!
[MIZUKI] Come on! What's up?
Nothing...
I'm not stupid, you know!
[SHO] Just forget about it!
So, what do we need
to forget about?
Oh, hey! Good morning,
Makishima!
Is this about the
student council?
Oh, no.
It's nothing important, really.
Oh, I wanted to ask you,
what are we doing for the column
in the next Student
Council Newsletter?
Well, why don't YOU try
writing it this time?
Huh?
[MAKISHIMA] I'll help you out,
all right?
[MIZUKI] Are you sure?
It's really okay?
Hey, Sho!
[MAKISHIMA] He doesn't look
like much, but he's a Guyver.
He's worth using.
Hey, who do you think you are?
What are you doing
behind my desk!
Get up and put out that cigar!
You know,
Commander-in-Chief Guyot
is on his way to
Japan right now.
What? Commander-in-Chief Guyot?!
[RISKER] As I'm sure you know,
you'll be held accountable for
the loss of our company's
top-secret Guyver Units.
But thanks to you,
we should be able to
get an idea of how
the units operate.
That should make it a little
easier for us to recover them.
So you say, but those Zoanoids
you were so proud of
were powerless up
against the Guyver.
It's my responsibility.
I'll find a way to
recover that Guyver.
[gasps]
From now on, I'll take care
of the Guyver s recovery.
You've allowed them to run wild
for far too long.
[Risker] I'd start
coming up with excuses
to tell the Commander-in-Chief
while you still can.
Now, the only one who can
capture the Guyver
is another Guyver.
Ya catchin my drift?
Kimura!
[Risker laughs]
Bastard!
I'll go. Let me handle this.
[GENZO] Looks like you're the
only one I can count on.
The Japanese Branch must recover
the units no matter what!
You can't let Risker get
to them before you do!
Sir!
Hey Fukamachi, you forget
your gym clothes, dude?
[MISAWA] We're having physical
exams in fifth period today!
You haven't eaten lunch
either, have you?
I had a ton to eat,
so I'll have plenty of energy
for the strength test.
[KAWADA] Yeah, but now you're
gonna be overweight.
[KOBASHI] Aw, shut up, man!
[MISAWA] Anyway, you should at
least take your shirt off, Sho.
Where ya goin?!
Don't tell me we're
out of coffee.
When we found the unit by the
pond, you were the one who...
Damnit! I have too
much work to do!
I don't have time
to be sleeping!
They wouldn't attack
me in broad daylight
in the middle of a neighborhood,
would they? Nah...
[SHO]
I don't think they went away.
I hope they didn't get bigger.
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi?
Sorry, am I disrupting your
train of thought?
[SHO] Oh, no...
[MIZUKI] Huh? Sho?
[MIZUKI] Don't you have a
physical this afternoon?
Mizuki! Um, shouldn't you be
in class or something?
Well, we were just discussing
the next student
council news column.
It's usually my job, but
I asked Segawa to write it
because I've been
so busy lately.
It's nice to have
reliable council members
like her to help me out.
If you don't mind, you can help
write the report too.
What do you say, Sho?
That's great, Sho!
[MIZUKI] This is a really
good opportunity!
I'm sorry. Thanks, but I really
gotta go home for the day!
[MIZUKI] Hey, wait! What about
your checkup? Sho!
[MIZUKI] I'm sorry. He's been
acting really strange lately.
It's all right, but listen...
Let's talk about that column.
Yeah, sure thing!
Jeez, Sho!
[MAKISHIMA] Aah...
So that's how it is.
Anyway, what were you saying?
[MISAWA] I guess Fukamachi
isn't showing up, huh?
Man, I really envy the kids that
are in good shape right now.
No kidding. I'm worried
about my liver, dude!
Oh no, I'm being followed.
Tetsu, is that you? Why
aren't you in school?
Oh, Mr. Tanaka.
I, uh, caught a cold. [coughs]
I'm sorry to hear that. You seen
a doctor about that cough?
Uh, yes, Sir. But, uhm...
I feel like that black BMW over
there might be following me.
That one over there?
Yeah, they've been
with me a while.
I see... Hold on.
I'll check it out.
[TANAKA] Ahh, excuse me.
Where are you...
Oh, I see. There's one in the
park. Yeah, that park.
Needed a restroom.
Huh?
[TANAKA] She was just
looking for a restroom
for her little boy to use.
[TETSURO] Oh...
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
You know that area up at Mt.
Narisawa you were
asking about earlier has just
been reopened.
Mount Narisawa?
[TETSURO] Sho?
[SHO] Tetsuro...
[TETSURO] Why aren't
you at school?
[SHO] We have physical exams
today and... well,you know.
Anyway, my feet
just sort of took me
in this direction, ya know.
[TETSURO] I guess I felt like
coming here too.
[SHO]
Standing here with you
sure brings back
alotta memories.
We were pretty excited the first
time we came here, remember?
Yeah, cause' we
thought we had uncovered
some kind of hidden
swamp or something.
[TETSURO] Of course, everyone
knew about this place,
but we acted like it
was our secret hideout.
We didn't even tell Mizuki, huh?
[SHO] I wonder if
someday we'll be able to
look back at what's
happening now and laugh?
[GERGOLE]
Target sighted.
Securing him now, Sir!
Dammit!
Those guys again!
Sho! Get out of here now!
I'm the one you guys are
looking for, not him!
Take me and let him go!
-Tetsuro, no!
All of our units' helmets
have video recorders
installed in them.
So, the footage from
the fight with Vamore
was transferred straight
to our headquarters.
[Gregole transformation roar]
[GREGOLE] We know that you're
the Guyver!
Recover the unit at all costs!
[SHO] I have to protect
Tetsuro... Here goes.
I won't run away!
Guyver!
Sho, wait!
[SHO]
Tetsuro! Here's your chance!
You have to get out of here!
[GREGOLE] You can't escape me!
We'll see about that!
[TETSURO] Come on, Sho, run!
[GREGOLE] Little punk...
[CADAN] Forget him.
[GREGOLE] Follow the Guyver!
[GREGOLE] In the name of
the Japanese Branch...
we'll capture you!
[GREGOLE] No!
[Gregole death scream]
Whoa!
You did it! Sho!
[SHO] Tetsuro!
[screams]
[SHO] Are you all right?
[TETSURO] Yeah, but look!
So you were able to wipe out
five Zoanoids at once.
That's quite impressive.
However...
[voice deepening]
Your time is up.
I'm not like them. I'm
in a class of my own!
[SHO] What the...
[SYNEVITE] I, Synevite, will
bring you to your knees!
[SHO] All right then, follow me!
Wait, Sho!
[SHO] Okay, I'll just use this
again. What? I can't shoot!
[SYNEVITE] Bwhaha, it's
massive power output
restricts it from
firing more than once.
[SHO] Arghh...
[SHO] Hoo-ya.
[Synevite chuckles]
[SYNEVITE] You're
wasting your time.
[SYNEVITE]
My body is soft and pliant.
It can absorb and
diffuse all impact.
You can't win!
[SYNEVITE] Your back is exposed,
Guyver!
[SHO] Damn it!
[Sho grunts in pain]
Sho...
[SYNEVITE] Ha ha ha...
I've done it...
[SYNEVITE]
I've really done it!
I've captured the Guyver,
just as ordered!
This is the power of Synevite!
[SHO] I... I can't move.
Is this... the end?
Sho! You can't lose now!
Don't give up!
[SYNEVITE] Useless worm!
Those who witness the secrets
of Chronos must perish!
[SHO] Don't you dare...
touch him...
[SYNEVITE] You still move?
[SHO] Guyver, give me the
power... to defeat him!
[SYNEVITE] I..impossible!
How could he...
I see. That looks like the
Guyver's... third weapon.
[SYNEVITE] Die!
[spinning growl]
[SYNEVITE] N..no!
[Synevite's death rattle]
[TETSURO] Are you okay?!
[SHO] Tetsuro!
That was great! Listen, I'm
not gonna run anymore.
We can face this, Sho.
[RISKER] That power
is completely wasted
on someone like you.
You can barely even defeat
a pathetic little Zoanoid.
Oh no, not another one!
[RISKER] Don't mistake me for
trash like them.
I'm Risker, an inspector
from Chronos.
However... I'm also... Adapt!
[SHO] Great...
[RISKER] A Guyver, like you.
No, it can't be...
He's a second, Guyver?
[dramatic music crescendo]
[NARRATOR] A second Guyver
has appeared before Sho.
Is he his enemy, or his ally?
The two fall into
a one-sided battle
and an unexpected conclusion.
Commander-in-Chief Guyot
and his subordinates
have finally arrived in Japan.
Those who believe only in
power begin to take control.
The deafening roar of a
hyper-Zoanoid thunders
through an empty schoolhouse.
Next: "The Visitor at Dusk"