Makishima!
[sounds of roof collapsing]
[ZX-TOLE] What?
Sho!
[ZX-TOLE] Looks like
you're just in time.
Now we can finish you
both off at once.
[MAKISHIMA]
Be careful, Guyver I.
They're not like anything
we've encountered so far.
[groans in pain]
[MIZUKI] Makishima!
[SHO] Makishima?
[THANCRUS] How dare you
turn your back on us?!
[THANCRUS]
You're quicker than I expected.
But not quick enough!
My blades vibrate at
an ultra-high frequency,
just like yours.
They can even cut bioboosted
armor to pieces!
One touch and you're through!
[FUMIO] Is that really Sho?
That... That thing?
[MAKISHIMA] This is looking bad.
If it keeps up like this,
I don't think we're
going to make it.
[THANCRUS] Die!
[piercing high frequency whine]
[THANCRUS] What the hell?
I see, the frequencies are
reacting to each other.
[GASTER] Let me finish him off
with my projectiles.
I'll show you...
[high frequency blast]
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi! Let's go!
[SHO] Dad!
[GASTER] Oh, no you don't!
[high frequencey blast]
[MAKISHIMA] Damn it, with the
condition I'm in now,
I can't attune myself
to his frequency
and get a good shot off.
[SHO] All right,
hang on tight, Dad.
[FUMIO] Right...
[DERZERB] Get back here!
[Zoanoids in confusion]
[TETSURO] Did he make it?
[MAKISHIMA] It looks
like he escaped.
[SHO] Thank God. That was close,
but I didn't think I'd be able
to get my dad back so soon.
Still, I bet this is a pretty
big shock for him...
...seeing me like this.
[FUMIO] I think it's better
just to trust him.
I'm sure he'll open up and
talk to me some day.
I just have to be patient.
[SHO] Even though he's been so
understanding of me,
all I've done is make him worry
by hiding the truth from him.
[FUMIO] Sho...
[SHO] Yeah?
Well, I, uh... guess
that getup would
make it pretty hard
to go to school, huh?
[SHO] Uh, no, I can take
it off if I want.
Oh, that's right.
You can do that, can't you?
But I bet taking a
bath is tough.
[SHO] Yeah...
[FUMIO] What the heck am I
saying? This is just silly.
Can't I think of something
more normal to talk about?
But what is normal anymore?
What am I supposed
to say to a son
who's been fighting like that
with those monsters?
[SHO] I wanna say something,
but what can you say
at a time like this?
[MIZUKI] Sho! Mr. Fukamachi!
[SHO] They all made it!
[FUMIO] You two aren't hurt,
are you?
No, we're fine!
[SHO] I'll talk to him
after he's had a
chance to settle down.
Now's not the best time...
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi! Look out!
[Sho screams in agony]
[TETSURO] Sho!
[ELEGEN] You're not getting away
from us that easy, Guyver!
[Sho countinues to scream]
Sho!
[SHO] Dad... you gotta
get out of here!
Hurry! Get in the car!
[SHO] Tetsuro, don't worry,
you can trust him! Just go!
[ZX-TOLE] Dammit, you
ain't making this easy!
[SHO] Dad!
[Sho screams in pain]
Sho! SHO!
My dad, no...
[MIZUKI] Mr. Fukamachi!
[Elegen laughs] You're finished!
[MURAKAMI] Damn it!
[Elegen wails in pain]
[MAKISHIMA]
Don't be so careless.
[ELEGEN] You still live?!
[MAKISHIMA]
That's what you get
for underestimating the
Guyvers' regenerative powers.
With an injury like that,
you don't stand a chance
without your partners.
[MURAKAMI] Not bad. He scared
them off with a simple bluff.
[BARCAS] Then we've lost them?
[GUYOT] Yes, in fact, those
hyper-Zoanoid "elites"
you're so proud of have
come away injured.
If that's the worst
the Guyvers can do,
I don't think we have
much to worry about.
Half a day in the
optimization tanks,
and they'll be good as new.
Well, in any case, even if
they've slipped away for now,
I doubt very seriously they'll
be able to make it out of town.
[police sirens]
[MIZUKI] I can't believe it!
It looked like such
a bad wound too!
I bet If you hadn't fired your
mega-smasher just then
you probably would have
recovered even faster.
[MIZUKI] Makishima, you did
it to save Sho, didn't you?
Are... Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm actually more
concerned about Fukamachi,
since he's still unconscious.
[MIZUKI] But he'll be all right,
won't he?
I mean, he'll be back
to normal in no time,
just like Makishima, right?
[MAKISHIMA] Yeah. Hey, Segawa...
About that Murakami guy...
[TETSURO] Uh huh?
He seems to know an awful lot
about what's going
on, doesn't he?
Uh, I guess, but really I don't
know anything about him.
That gun of his makes me
kinda nervous.
[MURAKAMI] It's natural that
you should be suspicious,
but for now, your only choice
is to trust me.
Oh, uhm, I'm sorry. I guess you
did save us, didn't you?
[MURAKAMI] No, I understand.
Anyway listen, the police have
already cordoned
off the whole town.
They're being paid
off by Chronos,
so there's no point
in going to them.
Then how do we get out?
With the state Sho's in right
now, we're not going anywhere.
If we can, I'd like
to find someplace
to lay low for a while.
[MAKISHIMA] If I'm going to
take advantage of Sho's power,
I'll need to have the
Segawas around.
The problem is,
I have to make sure this
guy doesn't get in the way.
Excuse me...
[MURAKMAI] Is something wrong?
Let's get everyone in the car, I
know a place where we can hide.
Trust me.
[MAKISHIMA] If he has some sort
of ulterior motive,
then I'll have to try and use
that to my advantage as well.
[GUYOT] This is the
data on the Zoanoids
that were created at
the Japanese Branch.
[BARCAS] Rather interesting.
[GUYOT] It might not compare
to your work,
but the Japanese Branch was the
leader in Zoanoid development.
[BARCAS] It seems they
haven't been able to
locate the Guyvers yet.
It's only a matter of time
before we have them back.
After all, we have a
valuable hostage now.
With Sho Fukamachi's
father at our disposal,
he should fall right
into our hands.
[BARCAS]
Yes, but the question is,
how are we going to
utilize that hostage?
I think I've found an
amusing solution.
Dad! Where are you?! Da...
Over here! Help me Sho!
[Fumio screams]
[SHO] DAD!
Sho! Sho!
Where am I?
[SHIZU] So you're finally awake!
[SHO] Who are you?
So you're up already, huh?
My name's Shizu.
Nice to meet you.
Oh good! I thought I heard
you talking.
You should let the
others know too.
Sure, I'll do that now.
Um, where am I?
[YOHEI]
There's nothing to worry about.
This is a villa, or actually
more like a safe house
that Master Agito prepared
out here in the woods
in case he ever needed
to get away.
[SHO] A safe house?
[YOHEI] My name's Yohei Onuma.
I've been serving Master
Agito and his family
since he was a little boy.
These days my
granddaughter Shizu and I
help out by
maintaining the villa.
Sho!
[SHO] Tetsuro! Mizuki!
You were out so long we were
afraid you'd never get up!
Sorry, I'm all right now though.
I'm glad. We were worried
about you.
By the way, Shizu,
I didn't know you had
gotten certified as a nurse.
I thought that it might come in
handy if there was an emergency.
Yeah, good idea.
[TETSURO] Forget it!
Listen, I understand that you're
worried about your dad and all,
but you've gotta rest
a little longer.
Thanks to everyone's help,
you finally have a
chance to sit back
and recover from everything
that's been happening.
I know you have the will
to fight now,
but you've gotta build up
your strength!
Yeah, but what if something
happens to my dad?
Do you really think
you can rescue him
with the state you're in now?
Yeah, don't do anything
reckless, all right?
[MURAKAMI] Why would he need to
prepare a safe house like this?
Who is he hiding from?
[MIZUKI] Where's Makishima?
[SHIZU] Master Agito
doesn't usually have
anything to eat
in the evening,
especially if he has
something on his mind.
Well that can't be very good
for him, can it?
Hold on, I'll go get him.
[SHIZU] Don't trouble yourself.
I'll bring him some leftover
soup later tonight.
So did Sho agree to
sit tight for a while,
or did he try and take off?
Well, he doesn't really
speak his mind very much,
so I'm not sure how he feels.
He took some sleeping pills
though, so he's out for now.
I'll try to keep an eye on him,
just in case.
Hey, you should watch
out too, Mizuki.
Are you listening?
[MIZUKI] Huh? Oh, uh, right.
[MIZUKI] Soup's not going
to be enough for him!
After all, he's got to
keep his strength up
in case he ends up in another
fight with those monsters.
Shizu probably doesn't
know what's going on.
He needs all the help
he can get.
[SHIZU] The bruise is
starting to heal up,
but I'll put another compress
on it just in case.
[MIZUKI] There's no reason for
me to be running away really.
But somehow...
I just...
I don't know.
[TETSURO] That's quite a gun
you've got there!
Yeah? Wanna take a look?
Yeah! Sure!
[MURAKAMI]
It's a modified .44 Magnum
that fires 12-gauge
dum-dum rounds.
Meaning, that the ammo holds
seven times the normal
amount of gunpowder.
It does some serious damage.
[TETSURO]
How the heck did he end up
with a crazy weapon like
that in the first place?
[MURAKAMI] You all right?
[TETSURO] Oh, uh sure...
[TETSURO] I think I'm gonna go
to bed though. See you tomorrow.
You think you'll be able
to sleep like this?
I think so. I mean
there's no guarantee
that Sho won't take
off on his own.
I've gotta keep an eye
on him, right?
[MIZUKI] Still, I wonder if
Mr. Fukamachi's okay?
[TETSURO] Yeah, I'm really
worried about him,
but dwelling on things like
that won't change anything.
That goes for you too.
[MIZUKI] Yeah, I know.
I mean Makishima.
Don't let his relationship
with Shizu get to you.
Wh..What do you mean?
Where did you get that from?
I... Th..That doesn't
bother me at all!
Shh!
[MIZUKI] Really!
Who would worry about that
at a time like this?
Wait, where are you going now?
[MIZUKI] I'm taking a bath.
[MIZUKI]
Yeah, I get it, all right?
I know what's going
on between them,
but I'm not letting
it get to me.
I'm not letting it
bother me one bit!
[YOHEI] Master Agito,
I cashed in part of your
remaining shares of stock,
just like you asked.
It should be enough to last you
for a while at least.
[MAKISHIMA]
I really appreciate it, Yohei.
[YOHEI] Think nothing of it.
[MAKISHIMA]
As always, I'm grateful
for all you and Shizu
have done for me.
[YOHEI]
Please, don't flatter me.
I owe your parents a
debt of gratitude
that I'll never be
able to repay.
It's my pleasure to do
whatever I can for you,
and I intend to do so for
the rest of my life.
I've brought Shizu up with
instructions to do the same.
Shizu was only about six when
she first came to our house,
wasn't she?
Yes, Sir. After she
lost her parents,
it was very kind of your
father to take her in
and treat her like
his own daughter.
You two were quite the pair!
I imagine we caused you
a lot of trouble.
It's only natural for
kids that age.
Agito, for Shizu's sake,
and for my sake
there's something I'd
like to ask of you.
That's rare.
You don't ask for much.
Don't take revenge.
It's not worth it.
This...
[SHIZU] It's Master Agito
when he was a child.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should have asked first. Here.
[SHIZU] Don't worry about it.
So, I guess you and Makishima
have been together since you
were both really little?
Yes, I really miss those days.
Until HE came...
[YOHEI] Sir, why?
Why would you let a man like
that adopt the young master?
You aren't going to let him take
over this house, are you?
Please, say something! How can
you do this to your own son?!
[YOHEI] I hate Genzo Makishima
for what he did.
I hate him for
cornering your father
and taking over the household.
And more than anything else,
I hate him for driving your
parents to an early grave!
I despised that wicked man so
much I wanted to kill him.
Believe me when I tell you
I understand how you feel.
But it's all over now.
He's already dead!
So please, you don't need
to do this anymore.
[MAKISHIMA] That's enough.
Even if I wanted
to give this up,
Chronos would never let me go.
[YOHEI] Then run where they
can't reach you!
[MAKISHIMA]
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Chronos has branches all
over the world.
There's nowhere for me to run.
[YOHEI] Master Agito...
[MAKISHIMA] You said this
was for Shizu's sake too,
didn't you?
Is this how she feels?
Well, she, uh...
[MIZUKI] Shizu, wait.
Then you mean you already
knew that Makishima was trying
to overthrow Chronos
before all this?
[SHIZU] That's right.
[MIZUKI] And you know
all about the fights?
Then, aren't you worried
about him?
I'm sure Master Agito
will be fine.
Shizu, are you and
Makishima, uhm...
[MIZUKI] I mean, do you...
[YOHEI] Master Agito!
Don't look! Agito!
Come on, let's go!
It's all right...
[SHIZU] Master Agito!
[Shizu gasps]
[SHIZU] Master Agito! Wha?!
All I want is to be able
to protect Agito.
That's the only thing
that matters to me.
[MIZUKI] Protect him?
[SHIZU] No matter what.
I can't... compete with that.
[MAKISHIMA] Yohei, the truth is
things have changed.
I'm no longer interested in
something as petty as revenge.
[YOHEI] What then?!
I realized that Genzo was
nothing more than a pawn
in a much greater scheme.
Chronos is the true enemy.
It was their power
that moved him.
They're the ones who
killed my parents.
In this world,
power is everything.
Before that,
revenge is meaningless.
That's why I will
obtain power so great
that I will never
again be manipulated
by the ambitions of others.
I will rise above all authority.
And I will stop at nothing
to do so.
Guyver, Chronos and
everything else in this world
are nothing but tools.
I will use them as I please!
Master Agito...
[MAKISHIMA] I am Zeus.
I am the god who will
rule this world!
[SHIZU] I knew that the tears
you cried that night
were not tears of sorrow,
but tears of frustration,
tears of helplessness.
Even back then, I knew the path
that you would take.
And so I decided
my path as well.
Don't be afraid, Master Agito.
I promise I'll protect you,
until the end.
[GUYOT] Good news.
We found where the
little rats are hiding.
[BARCAS] Oh?
[GUYOT] I imagine it won't be
long before they
make their move.
So how's it coming?
Almost according to plan.
We're missing a
large amount of data
pertaining to the
original Enzyme.
So this one's just become
one of my new designs.
Interesting. I can't wait
to see it in action.
[a child sobbing]
[FUMIO] Sho, you were playing
with my razor, weren't you?
Don't hide in the closet
like that, all right?
Now come on out.
Were you afraid I was going
to be mad at you?
Is that it? Because I bet you're
actually glad I found you.
I'm sorry, Dad.
[FUMIO] You let me know right
away if anything ever
happens to you.
[SHO] That's right...
I was really happy when
Dad found me back then,
and I feel the same way now.
Why did I try to hide
things from him?
I'm sorry, Tetsuro,
but I can't wait.
I have to go rescue
my dad right now.
Guyver!
[SHO] Someone's following me.
A Zoanoid? No, who is it?
[SHO] Makishima?!
[MAKISHIMA] Let me help you out.
[MAKISHIMA] To defeat Chronos
your strength is
absolutely necessary.
I can't just stand back and
watch you dig your own grave.
Let's go together.
To Mount Minakami...
[SHO] Right...
[NARRATOR] Makishima is forced
to face the staggering power
of the elite hyper-Zoanoids
once again.
In the desperate struggle,
Murakami reveals a
glimpse of his powers.
Meanwhile, a ruthless
plan is devised
to take advantage of the bond
between father and son.
Sho's reunion with Fumio
is short-lived,
as Barcas' psychic powers induce
a horrific transformation.
Next time:
"The Tragic Enzyme-2"