[BLOCK B] This is Block B.
We have confirmed a massive
explosion in the vacinity.
Fires are spreading
throughout the block.
[CONTROL] Understood. Lock down
the damaged sectors immediately!
Activate the confinment walls!
[soldier screams]
[BLOCK B] Commander Guyot!
[Guyot breaths menacingly
as he advances]
[BLOCK B] Wh-What are you...
[electronic beeping]
[Guyot laughs]
[crashing sounds from beyond
shield door growing closer]
[GUYOT] Damn...
[Guyor growls as he
gathers his power]
[ARCHANFEL] This has gone
far enough, Richard.
This rebellion is an
act of futility.
It ends now!
[Guyot roars in defiance]
[CONTROL] Emergency, emergency!
[alarm sirens wailing]
Block B has sustained
serious damage
and has ceased
communication!
[ZX-TOLE]
Where's Commander Guyot?
[CONTROL]
Well, Sir, he's exited Block B
and is currently making his way
through Tunnel 4
towards Block C.
It looks like he's being
pursued by someone,
but we haven't been able to
identify them yet.
[DERZERB]
What the hell's going on here?
Why would the commander
be running away?
[CONTROL] I... I'm sorry, Sir,
but all the monitors the
commander passes are shorted out
by some kind of interference,
and since losing contact with
all the operatives in the area,
we're in the dark.
Must be a Guyver.
I mean, you don't think it
could be Aptom, do you?
Hard to say. The thing is, the
commander's a Zoalord.
I don't think the Guyvers
or Aptom
are strong enough to chase down
someone on his level.
[CONTROL] The commander
has reached Block C!
Listen up! Our only objective is
to verify the current situation.
If at all possible,
avoid involvement in the battle
between the commander
and his adversary.
[Guyot roars as he
flies through]
[ARCHANFEL] Come now, Richard.
Stop this nonsense and hand
over the Remover.
[Guyot growls angrily]
[GUYOT]
Don't make me repeat myself.
I already told you.
The answer is NO!
What a pity.
Run while you still can.
You'll soon find obedience
is your only option.
I'm sorry, we lost their signal.
All the Zoanoids at the scene
have been wiped out.
I don't know what's going on!
So, what happened to
Commander Guyot?
From as far as I can tell,
he's broken through the
floor in Block C
and is currently making his
way to the lower levels!
[ZX-TOLE] Derzerb, I want
you to come with me.
We're going to have to look
for Doctor Barcas.
Doctor Barcas?!
We don't know what Commander
Guyot's planning right now.
This situation is getting
out of hand.
At this point, I'm afraid only
a Zoalord can handle this.
Hold on a second,
I'll go with you.
You wait here.
I need you to stay behind
and try to stabilize the
situation with the other units.
But, Sir...
[ZX-TOLE] Think about it.
If the Guyvers or Aptom snuck
into the base right now,
there's no telling how much
damage they could do.
[APTOM] That's a pretty
interesting attack, Gaster!
Next time, I'll have
to absorb you!
[DERZERB]
Probably better this way.
You can't fire off your
missiles inside the base, right?
[GASTER] Right...
We'll meet up with you
later, Gaster.
[GASTER]
Aptom sneaking in HERE?
Not likely.
Continue to follow the movements
of Commander Guyot, understand?
[CONTROL] Sir!
While he's doing that, you scan
for the doctor's thought waves.
[OPERATOR] Yes, Sir!
I must hurry.
If this Remover is what I
suspect, this could be serious.
A power that great should only
rest in Archanfel's hands.
If someone like Guyot were
to aquire it,
it could mean the destruction
of Chronos.
[footsteps in corridor]
I see, no survivors.
I... I wonder...
what must've become
of Dr. Barcas?
I hope he survived.
[ZX-TOLE] Derzerb, look out!
[Derzerb roars as he transforms]
[DERZERB] Aptom!
I didn't think you'd have the
guts to show your face in here!
I've been waiting for this.
Now, I can finally send
you to HELL! [roars]
[ZX-Tole] DIE, APTOM!
[Aptom screams as he dies]
[DERZERB] [disgusted sound]
Man, Look at that.
That sick bastard's still alive.
[ZX-TOLE]
Hah! Well, he's dead now.
[DERZERB] That should be the
last we see of him.
Disgusting freak got
what he deserved.
[ZX-TOLE] I'm starting to
think we shouldn't have left
the control room after all.
In fact, that may be the last
thing we should have done.
[DERZERB] Hmm?
[ZX-TOLE]
Come on! We're going back!
[DERZERB] But shouldn't we keep
looking for the doctor?
[ZX-TOLE]
Think about it for a second.
Dr. Barcas has the power to
contact us whenever he wants.
It doesn't matter where he is.
If he needs to give us orders,
all he has to do is form a
psychic connection.
[DERZERB]
So, you're saying the doctor
would have wanted us to
stay in the control room?
[ZX-TOLE] Right, with Aptom
sneaking in as soon as we left,
I'm starting to think that
this was a setup.
He probably targeted Gaster
after we left the control room.
That's why nobody warned us
before he made his attack.
[gasping and wheezing]
[ZX-TOLE] Gaster?
[GASTER] ...Tole!
[DERZERB] Gaster!
What's wrong? Hey, hang in
there! What happened, man?
[ZX-TOLE]
Derzeb, that's not Gaster!
[Derzerb roars in pain]
[ZX-TOLE] This is insane!
If that was Aptom just now,
then what the hell was that
thing we killed earlier?
Naw, couldn't have been...
[Derzerb groans]
[ZX-TOLE] Are you all right?
[Derzerb breathes heavily
and then roars]
(labored breathing]
[Derzerb roars in pain as
he transforms]
[ZX-TOLE] Derzerb!
No, don't tell me he...
He must have infected Derzerb
when he grabbed his arm!
But that's impossible!
He barely touched him!
[Aptom groans, chuckles and
then laughs outloud]
[ZX-TOLE] You bastard,
you killed Gaster the same
way, didn't you?
[APTOM] That's right, ZX-Tole.
Did you forget already?
The last time we met,
I told you that Gaster was
going to be my next target.
[ZX-TOLE] So, you infiltrated
the command room,
then devoured him while we were
busy fighting with your double.
[APTOM]
Double? Don't be ridiculous.
The Aptom you defeated earlier
was
as much myself as the man
standing before you now.
But more than that, I suppose
you could look at it
as a single member of the colony
of bodies united under
my consciousness.
[ZX-TOLE]
What are you talking about?
[APTOM] You still don't get it?
I'm saying that each Aptom you
see is another part of my body,
acting under my will, the same
as the rest of me.
[ZX-TOLE] So, are you saying you
sacrificed half of your own body
only so you could devour
Derzerb and Gaster?!
[APTOM] Sacrifice? I wouldn't
call it a "sacrifice". [laughs]
In fact, you know, I feel
better than ever!
Those friends of yours
really hit the spot.
They've more than made up for
the parts I lost fighting you.
[laughs evilly]
[ZX-TOLE] Shut your mouth, you
repulsive bastard!
I won't let you get
away with this!
Even if it costs me my life,
I'll kill you for what
you've done!
He's fast!
Damn it!
[APTOM]
Don't look so surprised ZX-Tole.
It's not like you haven't seen
these attacks before.
Remember, I inherited this
power from your old comrades.
[ZX-Tole screams in
pain and rage]
[APTOM]
But there's no need to worry,
I'll feast on your
powers as well!
[ZX-TOLE] What?!
[screams in panic]
[ZX-Tole groans in pain]
[APTOM] Ah, you're still
alive, huh? Not bad.
But I suppose
should expect as much
from the elite
hyper-Zoanoid Five.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't suppose I can call you
the "elite five" any more,
seeing as there's only one of
you left. [laughs gleefully]
[ZX-TOLE] This is it. At this
rate, I'm as good as dead.
I have no choice.
I'll have to use it after all.
[APTOM] It must be lonely
without your friends.
So what do you say, ZX-Tole?
Why don't you give up this
useless struggle
and become a part of me?
[ZX-TOLE] If I screw this up,
it's all over.
If I use it inside the base,
there's no telling what kind
of damage it will cause.
[APTOM]
Elegen, Gaster and Derzerb...
They're calling out to you,
ZX-Tole. Can't you hear them?
They're all waiting for you to
join them, inside me.
[ZX-TOLE] It doesn't matter
how risky it is.
If I don't kill him now,
he could bring down
the whole base.
I said, shut your mouth!
I'm sick of your ranting,
you freak!
I already told you...
I won't let you get away
with this,
even if it costs me my life!
[APTOM]
What kind of trick is this?
[wings buzzing]
[APTOM]
The temperature's dropping.
I get it, those glowing
wings of his
are absorbing the heat and light
from everything in the area.
I'm impressed, I didn't think
you had that kind of power,
but it's still not enough.
You should know that I can
withstand temperatures
much lower than this.
No, that's not it.
He's not trying to freeze me.
He's absorbing the heat and
light to turn it into energy!
[ZX-TOLE]
See you in Hell, Aptom!
[Aptom screams]
Now what's going on?
Don't tell me...
Is this part of Richard's
plan, too?
[sounds of destruction continue]
[ODAGIRI]
So, how do things look, Sho?
Now that you've made contact
with the control center,
do you think you can move the
Relic
and thus bring down the base?
[SHO]
I should be able to pull it off.
There's one problem though.
Even if the ship's operational,
it's been dormant for so long,
I don't think it has enough
energy to fly yet.
So then?
[SHO] Don't worry, I think
it'll be okay.
It's low on power now,
but it looks like it's sucking
energy
from some underground
heat source.
Underground heat source?
[SHO]
Yeah, I'm not sure what it is,
but I'm sensing a large heat
source
about 4 kilometers
down from here.
Must be a magma pool!
[SHO] That's probably how the
Relic has stayed active
for all these years.
It must draw up energy from the
magma automatically.
He's quite right.
It's moving slowly,
but the energy from the magma
is definitely making its
way up to the Relic.
Sho, at the current rate,
how long do you think it'll
take for the ship
to replenish its energy stores?
[SHO] If you just need the ship
to take off,
it shouldn't take more
than an hour or so.
In any case, I'll see if I
can speed things up.
The Relic must be causing
these earthquakes.
When it siphons energy
from the magma pool,
it shakes the foundation
of the base.
That's bad, even as is,
the structure of this place is
naturally weakened
by the Relic's biowaves.
With an earthquake,
we might be buried alive.
[RESEARCHER] Doctor,
I've got some bad news.
A communiqué just came through
reporting a series of massive
explosions in blocks C and J.
What?!
[RESEARCHER] I don't have the
full details yet,
but a section of the elevator
shaft was seriously damaged
by one of the explosions.
From the looks of things,
most of the elevators have
stopped working.
[ODAGIRI] So, unless they get
the elevators working again,
we're stuck here on
the lowest floor.
Wait a second,
what if we put the Relic's
energy transfer on hold?
[ODAGIRI] It's too late.
We don't have any time.
I don't know what's happening
on the higher levels,
but by this point, I'm sure that
Guyot and Barcas have noticed
the intensified bio waves
coming from the Relic.
If we stall, they'll
find us out.
[SHO] Dr. Odagiri...
[ODAGIRI] Yes?
[SHO] There's one place I know
will be safe
from the earthquakes.
What do you mean, Sho?
Just say it.
Wait... No way, you mean...
[SHO] The Relic...
Here, inside the ship.
[APTOM] What incredible power!
Maybe even stronger than
the mega-smasher.
[gtunts with effort]
But surely, after an attack
like that,
he must be completely drained.
[ZX-TOLE] [panting] Looks like
you managed to survive.
That blast took a lot out of me,
but don't worry,
I still have enough energy
to finish you off!
This is the end, Aptom.
The END!
[Aptom groans,
then begins to laugh]
[ZX-TOLE]
Have you lost your mind?
[Aptom continues to laugh]
[ZX-TOLE] Huh? What the...
Impossible! You mean there
was another one?!
[APTOM] Lucky for me, I happened
to come across the corpses
of three Chronos soldiers
on the way here.
I split into three parts,
using each of their bodies
as another form.
And now, I'll have your
body too, ZX-Tole!
[ZX-TOLE] I don't think so!
Crazy bastard blew his own
leg off to get away.
[APTOM] It's all right,
he left behind a tissue sample
for us to use.
[Aptom roars in pain]
[APTOM] I'm sensing a large
concentration of power
originating from somewhere
below.
I can feel it! It's him!
What's going on here?
Who is he?
Is that Richard?!
[Guyot growls in anger]
It's Archanfel!
[ARCHANFEL]
Don't you understand?
It doesn't matter how
much you struggle.
Before me, your strength
is meaningless.
You couldn't even give me the
slightest scratch.
[Guyot growls in anger]
Richard, I'll give you but
one word of advice.
You shouldn't anger a demigod.
[GUYOT]
Stay calm, it's all right.
I have him right where
I want him.
There's no way I'll miss from
this distance.
I don't care who he is,
there's nothing on Earth
that can withstand an
attack like this!
This is the only way!
I can't allow a creature that
powerful to exist!
Damn you, Richard! You can't!
You're going to kill us all!
You have to escape, Archanfel!
Hamilcar?
[Guyot roars with power]
This is the end, Archanfel!
Go to Hell!
What?!
[Guyot laughs with pleasure]
This power, it's...
[NARRATOR]
Taking refuge inside the Relic,
Sho prepares to launch the
ancient ship
and escape the collapsing
Chronos Base.
Then, Guyot appears before
them,
setting his sights
on the two Guyvers.
As he calls on the power of the
Remover,
the situation becomes desperate,
and Murakami is forced to engage
his final transformation.
Next time:
"Countdown to Collapse"