[GENZO] No! Stop this!
This is insane! You can do this!
Please! I'll do anything!
I'm begging...
[GUYOT] You should be
grateful, Makishima.
I'm giving you a chance to
serve me one last time.
As an experimental
anti-Guyver Zoanoid.
[RISKER] "Anti-Guyver?" What
a needlessly extravagant title
for a Zoanoid.
Whatever it is,
I'm sure it's no match
for the Guyver.
The downfall of Genzo Makishima
coupled with Zerbebuth's defeat
will no doubt make
them reconsider
the value of my Guyver II.
Because in the end,
the only worthy match for
the Guyver is another Guyver.
[NEWS REPORTER]
Police and fire teams
have been working around
the clock to determine
the cause of an explosion
that occurred yesterday evening
at Narisawa High School
in Narisawa City
As this could have been a
deliberate criminal act
against the school,
investigators are asking
those who were present if
any suspicious individuals
were seen around
campus at that time.
Fortunately, the explosion
occurred after school hours,
and though the intense blast
caused part of the school
building to collapse,
there have been no reported
casualties.
[SHO] No casualties? What are
they talking about?!
Maybe you were right and
Chronos really DOES have
some kind of influence
over the police and media.
Maybe, but I think I
was just overreacting.
[SHO] No way. I... I mean...
I mean, Mr. Tanaka and
his partner were murdered!
By Chronos'... Zoanoid!
Hold on, don't get so riled up.
Just calm down and
listen to what...
[SHO] I AM calm!
Forget about the explosion, what
happened to the pool of guts
they should have found
at the school?!
This isn't just an oversight!
They're trying to cover up
the fact that two police
officers were murdered!
Sho!
[TETSURO] I'm sure... no...
Actually, I'm positive that
the police and the media
are reporting everything
they know about what
happened yesterday.
Look at this.
It's today's paper.
[SHO] While on patrol,
two officers were in
a traffic accident?
A collision between a truck and
tanker? This is wrong...
[TETSURO]
There was an accident at school,
the cause of which
is still unknown,
and two police
officers are dead.
The TV and newspapers aren't
lying about that at least.
But now we have to assume that
Chronos is destroying evidence
and working behind the scenes to
make the public think
that the school bombing and the
officers deaths are unrelated.
Yeah, but...
since the Zoanoid showed
up at the school like that,
there might have been someone
who saw it fight
with the Guyver.
[TETSURO] There very well
may be, but...
But...
it's not that simple, Sho.
If someone tried reporting this
to the police or the media,
what do you think would happen?
They'd think they were crazy.
They'd turn them
away at the door.
Or even worse, maybe the
police would pin THEM
as a possible suspect.
To anyone on the outside
who doesn't know
about Zoanoids or the Guyver,
what happened yesterday...
it's nothing.
Little news in a big world.
[SHO] That's terrible...
It's just awful!
By this time next month, I'm
sure people will have forgotten
that anything happened at all.
Chronos has probably been
operating in the shadows
like this for a long time.
Hey, Sho... I don't really
know how to put this,
but it's not your fault that
Tanaka and his partner died.
Don't be so hard on you--
[SHO] Yeah, I know.
It's... just frustrating when
I think that things could
have gone differently.
When I think that...
that this could have happened
to you or even Mizuki...
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that!
I need to stop stressing
out like that.
Uh, it's okay...
[SHO] I should walk Mizuki
home from school!
[TETSURO] Walk her home? But
the school's shut down...
[SHO] Right, but the student
council is moving their
documents and stuff out of
the council room today.
So all the members are supposed
to be there. See you later!
Hey, Sho, wait up!
[light grunting]
Awww... You can't give up on me
now, we're almost finished!
Uh... Right...
[Mizuki] Um, is something wrong?
[SHO] Oh, it's nothing...
but after we're done with this,
let me walk you home.
[MIZUKI] Huh?
[SHO] Tetsuro's gonna
get worried if we keep
him waiting for too long.
[MIZUKI] Listen Sho, I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can
go home with you today.
Huh?
[yells]
It's just... well, you know,
they're letting us use the rooms
at that other school until
repairs are done here and...
So... I still need to talk to
Makishima about that.
Yeah, but Mizuki, you were doing
that all day yesterday.
If you don't come home,
Tetsuro will get worried.
Uh... just tell him I'm busy
and I'll be a little late, okay?
See ya!
But... But wait a minute!
[SHO] Mizuki!
Uh...
[Mizuki] What are you doing?
Um, just hold on a sec...
[Mizuki] Sho, that hurts!
[SHO] Wait, it's not
what you think!
[MIZUKI] Oh yeah? If it's
not what I think,
then what are you trying
to do to me?!
Look, I... I'm sorry. It's just,
I'm worried about you!
[MAKISHIMA] What's going
on here, Segawa?
[loud music crash]
Makishima...
I don't mean to intrude on a
private conversation...
and I'm sorry if I'm mistaken...
but it seems to me that
Segawa didn't care for
your treatment of her.
I'm sorry about that.
Excuse me...
What's wrong?
Mr. Tanaka...
[TETSURO] Oh, you're done?
Where's Mizuki?
[SHO] Oh, well, she...
[TETSURO] What happened?
[BURGER EMPLOYEE] Hello!
Welcome to Sandy Burger!
Will your order be for here
or to go, Sir?
[TETSURO] I see. Makishima, huh?
Well, listen...
Look I mean, maybe this is
all for the best, you know?
Our enemies are
after the Guyver,
so it'd probably be better if
I stayed away from Mizuki.
That's just an excuse.
No, I mean, it's just that...
Hey!
Say "ah."
Okay, but no pickles, right?
No pickles. C'mon, say "Ahh".
Ahh...
Aw... Just forget about it.
Hey, let me ask you something...
[TETSURO] Yeah?
[SHO] What kind of guy is
Makishima anyway?
You two were in the same class
up until last year, right?
[TETSURO] Well, let me think.
That's tough.
He's got a pretty bad temper...
and it's hard to figure out
what he's thinking sometimes.
[SHO] I thought someone
said he was adopted?
[TETSURO] Yeah, you didn't know?
People have been talking about
it for like three years now.
His so-called dad is really his
uncle. Supposedly his real dad
lost a lot of money on some
failed business venture
and was skipping town when
his brother showed up and
took care of his business,
his family and everything.
Excuse me. Please pardon
my tardiness...
Commander-in-Chief Guyot.
[GUYOT] You must be Agito.
Risker told me all about you.
I wanted to ask you inspector,
your work hasn't been
too taxing, has it?
No, on the contrary, I've never
felt better in my life.
I'm pleased to hear
that Inspector.
I've been told that you
attend the same school
as the boy who has the Guyver.
Yes.
[BURGER EMPLOYEE] Hello, and
welcome to Sandy Burger!
Uhm... will your order... be
for uh, for here, or to go?
Takeout.
[NOSKOV] If you don't mind.
[SHO] It's getting dark already.
Do you have any
plans for tonight?
[TETSURO] Let me guess.
Your dad's gonna be
working late again,
so you think it'd
be a good idea if
Mizuki and I spent the night at
your place, right?
[SHO] Well, yeah... I mean,
that'd be nice!
Damn. Lost again. You say
"that'd be nice",
but the look on your face says
"I'm begging you".
Uh, I mean, really it's
just that I think we...
I hate to break it to you,
but I'm afraid you'll be
spending this Saturday
night with US.
[TETSURO] Who are you?
[SHO] Get outta my burger joint,
you Chronos creep!
Oh? So you want to fight
me here do you?
That's fine by me... but let me
warn you... if we face off
in a crowded place like this,
it could get rather messy.
[TETSURO] Sho...
[SHO] What should I do?
If I turn into Guyver
and fight him now,
it's going to involve a lot of
innocent people. Still...
I suggest you accept
defeat gracefully and
avoid making a scene.
You can sit there and glare
at me all you want,
but that won't change the fact
that there's nowhere to hide
and no way to escape.
Maybe I can't hide,
but if you think there's
no way to escape...
you're wrong... I won't let you
use innocent people in
your plans! GUYVER!
[TETSURO] Gotta go!
Nice...
[GUY] Huh?
Well, he certainly knows
how to gauge a situation.
I'll give him that, at least.
Myumelzee... I'm sending you
his sonic
signature. Trace it
and capture him.
[NOSKOV] Keep an eye on him,
but don't do anything
until I get there.
[TETSURO] Looks like we...
got away, huh?
[SHO] Yeah.
That was insane! You can't just
transform like that
with all those people around!
[SHO] What would you have done?
I have to protect my friends,
don't I?
Are you saying we should
have given up?
But...
[TETSURO] Well, at least it
worked out in the end.
[SHO] I'm sorry.
[TETSURO] So, what are
you going to do now?
[SHO] I'm worried about Mizuki.
I'm gonna go back to
the school and...
[TETSURO] What's wrong?
[SHO] The air... it's vibrating.
[building power surge]
[SHO] Watch out!
[SHO] What the hell?!
[MYUMELZEE] Nice dodge, Guyver.
If that had been a direct hit,
it would have been
all over for you.
[SHO] So you're with
Chronos too.
[NOSKOV] I have to applaud
you for your dramatic escape
from the restaurant earlier.
[MYUMELZEE] However...
I'm afraid all you've done
is fallen right into
the palms of our hands.
Then you must be Zoanoids.
Ah man, this sucks!
We're more than just Zoanoids.
We're completely unlike
anything you've
ever seen before!
[growling]
[NOSKOV] I am the
hyper-Zoanoid, Noskov!
[MYUMELZEE] I am the
hyper-Zoanoid, Myumelzee!
See you in Hell, Guyver!
[Sho screams in pain]
[TETSURO] No way... What
kind of attack is that?
[SHO] Wh..what the hell was
that? I didn't see a thing.
[MYUMELZEE] Hmph!
So you were able to survive our
combined sonic wave, huh?
[NOSKOV]
I should have expected as much.
This is going to be
a real challenge.
One more time, Myumelzee!
[MYUMELZEE] Hey, no problem.
It doesn't matter how
hard his shell is.
We keep on pounding, it's gotta
crack sooner or later. Watch!
[Tetsuro coughs]
[NOSKOV] That's enough!
We lost him!
[NOSKOV] Don't get carried away!
You'll just complicate things!
[MYUMELZEE] What do you mean?
I just turned a boring mission
into a fun little game!
[NOSKOV] I can't believe it.
Theoretically, we should be
able to smash anything.
How did he withstand our attack?
[SHO] Sound waves?
[TETSURO] Yeah, you saw those
speaker-looking things
on their shoulders, right?
[TETSURO]
I don't know how they work,
but somehow they emit some kind
of low-frequency vibration
that pulverizes
anything in its path.
[SHO] A sound wave cannon, huh?
So, that's why I couldn't
see their attacks.
But how do I fight a
weapon like that?
Hold on. They still have
limitations.
[TETSURO] Look, no matter
how strong it is,
I think it's safe to assume that
a weapon like that would require
a certain amount of time for its
vibrations to destroy a target.
It's probably no more than
a few seconds though.
You think that's enough time
for you to beat them?
[SHO] Tetsuro!
[MYUMELZEE] Playtime is over,
Guyver! Let's go!
[SHO] I think I understand.
Take cover and watch me work.
[TETSURO] Yeah... Right!
[MYUMELZEE] Die!
What are you shooting at?
Your aim sucks!
[SHO] That's what you think.
[MYUMELZEE] What?!
[SHO] Now's my chance!
[MYUMELZEE] Not so fast!
Damn!
[Myumelzee screams in pain]
[NOSKOV] Using our own
attacks against us, huh?
Not bad, Guyver... but
if you think you've won,
you've got a lot to learn!
Now Guyver, cower in fear
before our true power!
Let's do it, Myumelzee!
[TETSURO] Their horns are
glowing. Watch out, Sho.
We don't know what these
guys are capable of.
[SHO] Give it up! I've already
figured out your attacks!
[Sho gasps in surprise]
What's... going on?
I... I can't hear anything!
No, it's not that I
can't hear... I...
it's like all the
sound disappeared.
[Sho screams in pain]
Damn... this is bad.
Without sound,
I can't sense their attacks!
Fighting without sound is like
fighting with my eyes closed!
[NOSKOV]
Sound is composed of waves that
vibrate within the
medium of air.
With this horn I can locate all
available sound waves
and create a completely
opposite waveform
which I then emit into the air.
The clashing waveforms
negate each other
until both are annihilated and
only a sea of silence remains.
[MYUMELZEE LAUGHS]
Are you surprised, Guyver?
Humans first sense danger
by sound, you know.
Now that we've thrown you
into a void of silence,
you're completely helpless.
I guess you can't hit what
you can't hear, huh?
[Sho screams in pain]
[NOSKOV]
You should have given up
while you still had the chance.
[MYUMELZEE] Consider this
payback for my arm.
I'll make you suffer!
I'll make you cry out in agony
as I crush you to pieces!
[Sho screams in pain]
[NOSKOV] Come on, Myumelzee.
Stop screwing around!
[MYUMELZEE] Shut up! I'm gonna
break that bastard's arm!
[Sho screams]
[NOSKOV] H..He reversed
my sonic eraser!
[Myumelzee screams]
[NOSKOV] Myumelzee!
[MIZUKI] Wh... What was that?
Mizuki!
[Sho gasps]
[NOSKOV] I am truly sorry, Sir.
I have failed. Myumelzee is...
[GUYOT] Irrelevant.
Listen carefully.
Somewhere near you there
is a girl named Mizuki.
Take her hostage and
get out of there.
[NOSKOV] Huh? Sir!
You have to get out
of here, Mizuki!
Wh..What are you talking about?
Listen, we don't have
time to argue!
[Noskov grunts in pain]
[Mizuki screams in terror]
[SHO] Mizuki!
[TETSURO] Let my sister go,
you son of a bitch!
[SHO] Damn it! Come back here!
[TETSURO] I said let her
go, you bastard!
What part of "let her go"
don't you understand?!
[Tetsuro grunts]
[NOSKOV] I have taken the girl
and retreated as commanded, Sir.
Now please... send
reinforcements!
[Noskov cries out in
surprise and pain]
No... it can't be...
[MAKISHIMA] You're not going to
get away with those two.
I'm not letting that rat
have his way.
Now is not the time.
[SHO] Mizuki!
Noskov? But how...
[TETSURO] Sho!
[SHO] Tetsuro! Where's Mizuki?
[MAKISHIMA] Relax.
Your girlfriend is safe.
[SHO] A... Guyver?
[TETSURO] Yeah, he rescued us
from that Zoanoid.
[MAKISHIMA] I'm sure our
paths will cross again.
I look forward to that day...
Guyver I.
[SHO] The third Guyver...
who the heck is he?
[RISKER] Guyver III...
[GUYOT] Really?
[RISKER] It's finally happened.
All three units
have been unleashed.
[NARRATOR] With nerves
at their breaking point
and conflicting feelings
seizing their hearts,
Sho and Tetsuro are summoned
to fight once again.
The anti-Guyver Zoanoid
prepares for battle
as the emotions of a fallen man
flare into a bitter hatred.
One man lashes out at the world
that has betrayed him,
as another seeks to bring his
battle to an end.
What awaits at the end
of the fight?
Next:
"Beyond the Desperate Battle"