[SHO] All right, energy
replenishment is complete.
Activate thrusters!
Get ready! I'm taking
the ship to the surface!
[Guyot yells in surprise]
[Murakami lets out a battle cry]
[Guyot screams in pain]
[Guyot screams as he falls]
[MURAKAMI] It's over...
This is the end, Murakami.
But it's a new
beginning as well.
I'm glad we could see this day.
Doctor...
Doctor!
Doctor Odagiri...
[Murakami sobs quitely]
[APTOM] Sounds like things are
starting to get ugly down there.
What the hell is that thing?
[Aptom yells in alarm
then grunts in pain]
Is that the Creator's ship?!
There's no way!
How did they get that
thing moving again?
Damn it...
Those energy waves it's putting
out are acting like a barrier.
Well, I guess this is it.
My only choice now is
to get out of here.
So long, Relic's Point.
It's been fun.
[people fleeing in panic]
Commander Guyot!
H..Help me!
[strangled noise]
[CONTROL] Research and
development has been destroyed!
No response from the executive
sectors either!
[SOLDIER] Where's the Doctor?
Shouldn't we have received
orders from him by now?
[CONTROL]
We can't wait for orders.
We gotta get the hell out of
here before we're all killed!
[soldiers screaming]
The gravity disturbance has
scarcely been resolved,
and then all hell breaks loose!
[SIN] I'm getting a tremendous
biometric response.
A massive power is rising up
from the ground.
No, it can't be...
[BARCAS] The Relic has awakened.
After millennia of lying
in dormancy,
it has sprung to life once more.
I'm glad youre here!
[PURGSTALL] It's good to see
you well, Doctor Barcas.
We were concerned.
Doctor, what do you mean,
the Relic has awoken?
It's regained the powers that
the Creators
wielded so long ago.
Soon it will take to
the heavens.
As it climbs higher and higher,
it will tear down everything
that stands in its path.
But... but how?!
Who's responsible for this?
I've been wondering that myself.
At first, I thought that
Richard might have activated it
when he fell to
the bottom floor,
but now I'm starting to think
that other things were at play.
Guyot?
[PURGSTALL] Surely not! This is
beyond Guyot's power.
[SIN]
True, but I can think of someone
who IS strong enough
to launch the Relic.
[CAERLEON] Archanfel!
Doctor Barcas, do you think
Archanfel is here as well?
[Archanfel struggles
and screams]
I encountered him shortly before
escaping Relic's Point.
He launched the ship!
[BARCAS] I wish that were so...
[SHO] Here, Murakami,
come inside with everyone else.
Such a powerful presence...
I've never felt anything
like this before.
It must be a Zoalord.
No, the Council of Twelve...
[SHO] Hey, Murakami, is
something wrong?
It's dangerous out there!
You gotta come inside!
[MURAKAMI] Right...
[Murakami gasps in surprise]
[GUYOT] Don't look so surprised!
You didn't really think you
could beat me that easily.
[MURAKAMI] Guyot?!
[Guyot laughs]
[MURAKAMI] Damn it, I thought
I finished him off!
[GUYOT] You did a good job of
disabling my right arm,
but I still have the
Guyver Remover.
It's all right!
I only need ONE arm to repay you
for last time, guinea pig!
[Murakami groans in pain]
Murakami!
[GUYOT] What's wrong, prototype?
Where's all that bravado?
How many times do I
have to tell you?
A piece of garbage like you is
no match for a true Zoalord!
Murakami!
Let him go!
[GUYOT] Oh, you think you can
just swallow me up, do you?
[MURAKAMI] Don't do it, Sho.
It's too risky.
You can't let him inside
the Relic,
not as long as he has
the Remover.
[GUYOT]
Sho? Ah, now I understand.
So, the Guyver I is piloting
the Relic after all.
Excellent!
[Murakami groans in pain]
[Guyot laughs as Murakami
continues to groan]
Stop it!
[GUYOT] You hear that Guyver I?
Your friend is dying.
You'd better move it,
or he's as good as dead!
[MURAKAMI] Sho, please don't
worry about me.
Either way, I...
[screams in pain]
NO!
[MURAKAMI] Either way, my
life cannot be saved.
What do you mean?!
[MURAKAMI] Is it still possible
for me to transform?
[ODAGIRI] I imagine you could
do it once more,
but your lifespan will
be drastically reduced
in the process.
One more time, huh?
I think that should be enough.
I appreciate it, Doctor.
[loud crash in the hallway]
[ODAGIRI]
I didn't know you were there.
[MURAKAMI] Could you keep this a
secret from everyone else?
[MIZUKI] But...
[MURAKAMI]
Please, especially from Sho.
[MIZUKI]
Murakami, all this time, you...
you were ready to
sacrifice yourself,
just so we could escape.
Mizuki, did you...
did you already know?
[GUYOT]
I'm getting tired of waiting.
Get out here, Guyver!
He's running out of time.
[MURAKAMI] Don't do it!
Don't listen to him!
[screams in pain]
STOP IT!
[rumblings from within
the mountain]
[Murakami screams in
intense pain]
[Sho screams in fury]
[5PURGSTALL] The Relic!
[SIN] After all these years,
it's risen at last.
[GUYOT] So, you finally decided
to come, Guyver I.
[MURAKAMI] Sho, why?!
I told you to stay inside!
[SHO] All right, Guyot,
keep your promise.
Let Murakami go.
[GUYOT]
Well, I suppose he's outlived
his usefulness to me anyway.
See if you have any use
for his corpse.
Night-night, guinea pig!
[SHO] Stop it!
[Murakami screams]
[SHO] NO!
[SHO] You've gotta hang on!
[Guyot chuckles wickedly
in anticipation]
[sudden noise behind Guyot]
[GUYOT] Gottcha!
What was that?
Listen, everyone,
I need your help.
We're going to attack the Relic.
Attack the Relic?!
But, Barcas, why?
I don't understand.
[BARCAS] I trust you all saw
that flash, just now?
That was a Guyver's
mega-smasher.
I'm afraid the Relic has fallen
under their control.
But still, this is too much!
The relic is the greatest legacy
of the Creators.
We can't...
And what if they manage
to escape with it?
What do you think will
happen then?
Can you even imagine what the
consequences might be
if they obtain the technology
hidden on that ship?
Yes, you're right.
[BARCAS] We must destroy it,
while we still have the chance!
[SHO] Hang in there, Murakami!
Don't die! Please!
[MURAKAMI] I'm counting on you,
Sho, and the others.
You're mankind's last hope.
It's up to you.
Carry on my will...
the will of Doctor Odagiri...
and Doctor Yamamura.
Listen to me, Sho.
Please, don't let our
sacrifices...
be all in vain.
[SHO] Murakami? [sobs]
Guyot...
[GUYOT] [laughs]
That Guyver unit is a weapon,
not a toy for a little
brat like you!
Now, at long last, it will
belong to a more worthy master!
Guyot, you'll pay for this!
[Guyot laughs]
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi!
[SHO] I'll make you suffer for
what you did to him!
[MAKISHIMA]
Fukamachi, use your mega smasher
before he can fire the Remover!
[GUYOT] I don't think so, boy!
[SHO] DIE, you bastard!
[GUYOT]
The whole Council! Dammit!
What's going on out there, Sho?
[SHO] Who's attacking us?
[MAKISHIMA] It must be the
Council of Zoalords.
[SHO] What are they doing here?
[GUYOT] There's no way
I can take on the Guyvers
and the Council.
I'm at a clear disadvantage.
[SHO] Guyot, get back here!
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi!
[Makishima screams in pain]
[SHO] Makishima!
[MAKISHIMA] Forget about me!
Don't let Guyot get away!
[GUYOT] Well, as long as
I have the Remover,
I'll have as many
chances as I need
to recover one of
the Guyver units.
What the hell is that?
[ARCHANFEL]
Not so fast, Richard.
Where do you think
you're going?
[GUYOT] But I thought you...
Well...
[PURGSTALL] It's Archanfel!
He must have come here to
take back the Relic!
[BARCAS] He returned from beyond
the event horizon.
Even death bows to
his strength.
[ARCHANFEL] I will have your
Zoacrystal back now.
[GUYOT] No, stop! NO!
[ARCHANFEL] And the Remover...
[Guyot gasps in sudden pain]
[Archanfel yelps in surprise]
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi, use
your smasher! Hurry!
[SHO] A..All right!
[ARCHANFEL] So, these are the
little bioboosted insects
that have given Chronos
so much trouble.
[SHO] Who the hell is he?
[MAKISHIMA] I don't know.
I'm just sure he's our enemy,
and a very dangerous
one at that.
[MAKISHIMA] FIRE!
SHO!
It's over.
The Relic's been destroyed.
The final legacy of the
Creators has been put to rest,
lost in the folds of time.
[ARCHANFEL] Another earthquake?
Magma...
What a disaster...
The Remover is no more.
[NARRATOR]
In a world under Chronos' rule,
there is a deceptive
feeling of peace.
Hidden in a tiny corner of
this bizarre reality,
Mizuki and her friends hold
fast to the belief
that Sho has somehow survived
his last battle.
As an unbearable melancholy
creeps into their minds,
desperate hearts call out
to lost comrades.
Next time:
"In a Conquered Town"