[MIZUKI] Wow! Really? I'll have
to give it a try some time.
Sure! You can borrow mine as
long as you give it back!
[TETSURO] Hey, Mizuki.
[MIZUKI] Tetsu!
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Are you ready to go?
I guess this is the first time
in a while
that we've all had dinner
together, huh?
We should give Sho's
dad a call too.
Leave it to me! I'll give
you guys a meal to remember!
Just sit back and relax!
Aw man, it's morning already?
You must be beat from keeping
watch all night.
I can handle it now, you
need to get some rest.
It's okay. I'm not tired yet.
Besides, I can't transform.
What am I good for if I
don t do this huh?
C'mon, Sho...
Hey, guys! Why dontcha' come on
down and get your breakfast?
[TETSURO] Wow!
I wasn't expecting this much!
[SHIZU] If we hadn t been in
such a rush,
I could have brought more.
[TETSURO] What, are you kidding
me? This is fantastic!
Well, don't be shy!
Everyone help yourself!
[MAKISHIMA]
Murakami, I have a question.
You mentioned some
secret about the Guyver.
Ya mind elaborating?
I was in Chronos myself for a
while,
but there are still a lot
of things I don't know.
All right then, if you think
you're ready,
I'll tell you everything I know,
the truth behind the Guyver
units,
the Creators and the Zoanoids,
including the truth behind
humankind itself.
There was a race of alien
creatures
who came to Earth from far
beyond our galaxy,
"The Creators".
We know now that
they manipulated
the Earth's ecosystem
over the course of
several billion years
in an attempt to give rise to a
very specific kind of life form.
They needed something with
high intelligence,
strong survival instincts
and the ability to adapt to
any environment.
A fearsome, aggressive life-form
meant to serve as a weapon.
After countless years,
a creature that could serve
as a base for that life-form
was created.
And those creatures were us,
all of humankind.
[MIZUKI]
You expect me to buy that?!
You're telling us that we're
nothing
but a bunch of living weapons
created by some alien race?!
That's what people are?!
It was difficult for me to
accept as well, but it's true.
Now that you mention it,
Guyot talked about the
exact same thing,
that we were all made as the
basis
for a series of bioweapons.
It makes sense. After all, human
history is built on conflict.
We seem to have a
powerful inclination
towards war and brutality.
Perhaps we're subconsciously
fulfilling our purpose.
[MIZUKI] What's going on here?
It's like they don't even care!
How can they just sit there
and talk about this like
it's nothing?!
It's sick! They've lost
their minds!
Or maybe not. Maybe I'm the
one who's losing it.
You see, the Zoanoids are just
normal humans
who have been "optimized"
for combat.
Optimization is the process of
artificially inducing
genetic mutations
in order to create a new form,
or augment a specific ability.
Human attributes allow for the
possibility of transformation
from their default into
a secondary form.
However, all Zoanoids are
subject to
the will of the Zoalords.
Like Guyot and Barcas,
they can command large
numbers of Zoanoids
through
psychic manipulation.
And you have the same powers,
because you were a prototype
for Guyot's Zoalord form.
That's correct. I was able
to use those powers to
destroy the Enzyme IIs,
even if I couldn't break Barcas'
psychic control over them.
Just as Zoanoids are forced to
submit to the Zoalords,
the Zoalords are genetically
programmed to demonstrate
absolute obedience to
the Creators.
But now, it's all history.
In the end,
humans were never
used in combat.
Shortly after completing their
experiment,
the Creators departed
from the Earth.
Perhaps some interstellar war
that they were involved in had
drawn to a close,
or perhaps they were influenced
by some outside force.
Unfortunately, their intentions
have been buried
beneath the sands of time.
Scarcely had it been created,
when mankind was abandoned
before its true purpose
could be realized.
Left without the guiding
hands of the Creators,
optimized Zoanoids crossbred
with normal humans
and bit by bit their
legacy faded away.
But there's still a chance that
some of them survived.
The monsters spoken of in
folklore throughout the world
may have been the descendants
of those very Zoanoids.
Then what about the Guyvers?
We already know that they're
organic weapons.
Were they created using
humans as a base too?
[MURAKAMI]
No, they're different.
Originally, the Guyvers were
to be used by the Creators.
Creators?!
Believe it or not, they were
standard equipment.
As you know, the Guyver unit
fits itself to its host's body,
then optimizes their
conditioning
and enhances their physical
capabilities.
Even if the Creators had been
a group of many different
alien races,
the units would be able to adapt
to each of their needs.
It may be the most versatile
weapon ever created.
And then the Creators
had an idea.
What if they equipped a human
being with the Guyver unit?
They were probably interested to
see what would happen
if two different living weapons
were combined.
It was like a game to them.
However, they got far more
than they bargained for.
The bioboosted human,
exhibited power that was
hundreds of times greater
than when the Creators
themselves donned the unit.
But what was more terrifying to
them than anything else
was the fact that the Guyver
unit freed its host
from their mental control.
They had accidentally created a
monster
far more powerful
than the Zoanoids
that was no longer subject to
its master's commands.
The Creators called it
abnormal, nonstandard,
"out of control", or in their
language, "Guyver."
Their curiosity lead them to
discover
something even more terrifying.
If a Zoalord were to equip one
of the Guyver units,
it would become a super-being,
with a power far surpassing
that of the Creators'
themselves.
That's incredible...
That may be why the Creators
suddenly abandoned the planet.
They were running away.
Everything else I've told you
is based on information
Professor Yamamura and Chronos
procured from various ruins
throughout the world.
However, the last piece
about Zoalords equipping
the Guyver units
is most likely a secret
even to Chronos.
Other than myself, the one man
who may know is Richard Guyot.
Guyot knows?
Then, that must mean his
goal is to...
Right, he wants to have
a Guyver unit of his own.
Then he'll use it to destroy the
other Zoalords.
He'll rule this world with the
power of a god.
[SHIRAI] Good news.
I've finished the analysis
and the results indicate
that the unit does possess the
properties you spoke of.
Really? Is that so?
Indeed, but I'm afraid I
will require more time
in order to determine how
we're going to execute the
specifics of the operation.
Attend to it immediately, and
tell no one of your findings.
[SHIRAI] Of course.
Listen, you must ensure that Dr.
Barcas doesn't suspect anything.
[GUYOT] I have a feeling that
old man is
catching onto my plan.
I bet he really came to Japan
to keep an eye on me.
If Yamamura knew the secret of
the Guyver units,
then I'm sure the test
subject also knew.
And that s why they targeted
me in the first place.
Murakami knows too much.
If he opens his mouth at
the wrong time,
Barcas might learn the truth.
If that happens, I'm finished.
Why does this have to happen
now? I'm so close!
Just a little while longer and
I'll be able to separate a
Guyver unit from its host!
It can be done, I'm sure of it!
But first I have to deal with
him.
He's a threat as
long as he lives.
I have no choice but to take
matters into my own hands
and eliminate
him personally!
Mizuki?
[MIZUKI] I just need to take a
little walk, okay?
[TETSURO]
All right, but don't go too far!
[MIZUKI] I can't take this
anymore!
I've had enough of those
crazy stories!
I feel like I'm losing my mind!
How can Tetsuro and Sho keep a
straight face
in a situation like this?!
How can they act like this
is all right?!
It's like they
don't even care!
I can't take it. I just
want to go home.
I want to go home... [sobs]
[MURAKAMI]
Once Guyot discovered the secret
behind the Guyver units,
he feared that the other
Zoaloards would find out too.
So he eliminated every member of
the staff
that was involved in the
study of the units.
However, Professor Yamamura
escaped his notice,
since he was only a private
advisor
for one of the staff members.
He corresponded with the
other researchers,
sSoon discovering that the
"unit" in question
was actually an object that he
had uncovered in the ruins
at Mount Minakami several
years earlier.
If someone were to
obtain the unit,
the professor knew they would
have enough power
to oppose Chronos.
It was the only way to stand
up to their strength.
But the only problem was it
could fall
into the hands of Guyot or
the other Zoalords.
I see. That's why the zoalord
test subjects sided
with the professor.
You wanted to finish off Guyot
before he had the chance to
obtain one of the Guyver units.
[MURAKAMI]
But we failed.
The team of Zoalords overpowered
us
before we could put
up much of a fight.
I had the fewest injuries, so
the professor and the others
gave their lives to protect me
while I escaped to
the desert above.
With Chronos
thinking I was dead,
I returned to Japan and used my
connections as a journalist
to track their movements.
I had been searching leads
on the Guyver units
when I found that they were
actually right under my nose.
I knew that Guyot would be
coming for the units,
so I had to get to them first.
I would secure all three, then
equip one myself
and launch an attack on Chronos.
It was a mission that I alone
had been entrusted with.
But then, it all slipped
out of my control.
I'm sure you know how the
rest of the story goes.
By the time I caught up to the
units, it was too late.
All three of them had been
unleashed,
and one of them had
been lost forever.
But wait, if all three units
have already found hosts,
then we shouldn't
have to worry about
Guyot getting his hands
on one anymore.
So, in a way, the problem has
already been taken
care of, right?
I wish that were the case.
[TETSURO] What's wrong?
I was just thinking, Mizuki's
been gone a while.
Yeah, I guess she has, huh?
It's no surprise.
All of this has come as quite
a shock to her.
[TETSURO] Yeah, I can't really
blame her for getting upset.
She kinda got hit with a
lot of things at once.
I guess we should have told
her
about all this stuff sooner,
huh? What's up?
I'm going to see if
I can find her.
[MURAKAMI] Sho can be pretty
predictable sometimes.
Murakami...
What's the matter?
It's him!
He's here! Right behind us!
Good morning, gentlemen.
[TETSURO] G..Guyot!
[APTOM] Well, I'll be damned.
The Commander decided to
show up after all.
This is getting very
interesting.
So it's you. You're the test
subject that got away.
That's right. We meet at
last, Richard Guyot!
[BARCAS] Just as I expected.
Good work, Aptom.
For now, I'd like you to stay
hidden and await further orders.
As you wish, Sir. Understood.
[BARCAS] Patience, Richard.
There's no need for you to
get so worked up
over a mere test subject.
If my suspicions are right,
I'm afraid Murakami will be the
least of your worries.
[GUYOT] Arrogant fool!
Do you really think a miserable
little prototype like you
can stand up to the real thing?!
I'll show you the power
of a true Zoalord!
[GUYOT] What's the matter? Lost
your nerve?
You're not giving up
already, are you?
Guyver Bioboost!
[MAKISHIMA] Who said
anything about giving up?
Actually, I'm glad you came!
You saved us the trouble of
going all the way
to Relic's Point to
finish you off.
[GUYOT] If nothing else,
it seems that your tongue is
as sharp as ever.
But let's not be too
hasty, Agito.
I brought these two gentlemen to
keep you entertained.
[MAKISHIMA] Enzyme II, huh?
[GUYOT] Listen up, you
contemptuous traitor.
I'll personally tear the control
metal from your pathetic carcass
after these two finish you off!
[MURAKAMI]
Not gonna happen, Guyot!
I have the powers of a
Zoalord, just like you!
[MURAKAMI]
I'll send you to Hell,
even if I have to drag
you there myself!
[SHO] C'mon, she's gotta be
around here somewhere,
doesn t she?
Now where... Hey!
What the heck are you doing
all the way out here?
Did you get lost? Everyone's
worried about you.
C'mon, let's go!
Go away. I just want to go home!
[SHO] Hey, hold on!
Mizuki, wait! Wait!
[MIZUKI] I said leave me alone!
I'm going home, all right?!
Hey, what's gotten
into you? What's wrong?
Think about it for
a second, Sho!
Mizuki, I...
[MIZUKI]
I was attacked by monsters,
kidnapped and locked up.
I find out you and Makishima are
practically monsters yourselves.
And then you tell me that
humans are nothing
but tools made for
some alien war?!
Enough is enough!
Why, Sho? Why is all of this
happening to us, huh?
What did we do to deserve
all this suffering?!
Just a few weeks ago, we were
nothing
but normal high school students!
Why did everything have to fall
apart?! It's not fair!
Why?! Tell me why!
I want my life back,
like before. [sobs]
[MIZUKI] Sho...
[SHO]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Mizuki!
It's all my fault for getting
you guys involved in this.
[SHO] I'll do something.
I promise I'll make
it better somehow!
[SHO] Come on, let's get back
to the others, okay?
[MIZUKI] Okay...
[MAKISHIMA] If I could just fire
off my mega-smasher,
I could take them both
out in one shot.
But they're way too fast.
They'd tear me up
while I was charging my
energy.
[Murakami yells]
[GUYOT] Is that the best you can
do? Pathetic!
Here, let me show
you how it's done!
Well? What do you think
of my gravity bullets?
Rather effective, even at
only 20% output.
[MURAKAMI] Damn it...
[GUYOT] Insolence!
[Murakamki screams in pain]
[MAKISHIMA] Murakami!
[Makashima groans in pain]
[MURAKAMI] No!
[GUYOT] Looks like the end of
the road for you.
It was fun, but playtime's over.
Don't despair. Consider it an
honor to die
at the hands of a true Zoalord.
[Makashima screams in pain]
[Enzyme II chuckles evilly]
[Enzyme II roars in pain]
[GUYOT] Damn, out of time since
I pulled them out
before their optimizations
were complete.
[MURAKAMI] Now!
[Guyot screams in pain]
[MURAKAMI] Makishima, go!
[MAKISHIMA] Right!
[MAKISHIMA]
You're finished, Guyot!
[Guyot screams in denial]
[MURAKAMI] Did you get him?
[MAKISHIMA] I think so.
I was only able to
fire from one side,
but there's no way he could
survive a direct hit like that.
[footsteps]
[GUYOT]
You dirty son of a bitch...
[MURAKAMI] How?
[GUYOT] Now you've really pissed
me off, you filthy maggots!
Prepare to be annihilated!
I'll send every last one
of you to Hell!
Sho, wait! Isn't that?
[SHO] No! The others are
still up there!
[NARRATOR] A soul gone
mad with bitterness...
A wounded heart lamenting a
harsh reality...
He must protect Mizuki.
Pierced by the twisted
arm of a Zoanoid,
traces of kindness flash
through Sho's dying heart.
With all of his strength, he
cries "Guyver" once more.
As his heart opens to the truth,
his hopes become a reality.
Next time: "Arise, Guyver I"