[SHO] How much farther
do we have to go?
[MAKISHIMA] The Block 2 elevator
is right around the corner.
That's the last one.
[MAKISHIMA] Getting tired?
[SHO] No, not really.
I was just wondering if there
was a reason why we're
changing elevators
every other floor.
[MAKISHIMA] There are too
many security checks
on the main elevator.
We're less likely to
get caught this way.
[SHO] You know, it wouldn't
exactly hurt
if you would help
me push the cart.
[MIZUKI] I'm sorry, Sho.
I mean, I guess I am
kinda heavy.
[SHO] No, not at all!
Uh, anyway, are you getting
enough air in there?
Yeah, I'm fine. Just a
little hot, that's all.
[SHO] Hang in there. Just a
little bit longer
and we'll get to
see Tetsuro again.
[MAKISHIMA] Sorry, but could you
please refrain from talking?
Remember, we're in enemy
territory here.
[SHO] Sorry about that!
[MAKISHIMA] Just keep your wits
about you. We're almost there.
[MIZUKI] Makishima...
[SHO] What are we doing here?
Where are we going?
Makishima, what's going on?!
This isn't the way to
Mount Minakami!
[MAKISHIMA] Unequip
your armor, Sho.
[SHO] But...
Sho?
[SHO] Oh, right.
We wouldn't be able to make it
through the secret passage
with our Guyver suits.
[SHO] Secret passage?
[MIZUKI] What is this?
An old well?
[SHO] Looks tight.
I guess we'll have to squeeze
through one at a time.
[MAKISHIMA] I'll stay here and
hold the ladder in place.
Segawa, you go down ahead
of Fukamachi.
What is it?
[SHO] Well, you've taken this
passage before, right?
[MAKISHIMA] Yeah, why?
[SHO] Then would you
mind going first?
It's pretty
dark down there,
so if Mizuki loses her footing,
I'm afraid she might fall
and hurt herself.
All right, just follow me.
So, uh... so everyone's
really okay, right?
They're fine.
Actually, I'd say your brother's
even more energetic than usual.
[SHO] All right, hold on.
I'll go next.
[MIZUKI] That's fine,
but I better not catch you
looking up, all right?
[SHO] Right...
[MAKISHIMA] Would you
stop chatting
and start climbing, please?
[MAKISHIMA] Be careful, Segawa.
We'll probably be stopped
by two inspectors at the
next checkpoint.
Try not to make any noise.
[MIZUKI] Got it.
[SHO] Hold on just a
little longer.
[OFFICER] What are you
two here for?
[MAKISHIMA] We're delivering
lab materials.
[OFFICER] I haven't been
informed of this.
[SHO] Hey, there's a camera.
[MAKISHIMA] Just leave
this to me.
Here's our authorization form.
We've been instructed to deliver
radioactive markers
for testing in the lab.
They're conducting a
search upstairs,
so even the regular service
personnel
are stuck doing deliveries.
[RAZELL] Hey, kid,
what type are you?
You got a pretty small build,
so I was wondering what
type you were.
Ramotith? Or Gregole?
[SHO] Uh, I'm a Ramotith.
[OFFICER] Doesn't seem like this
should be a problem.
[MAKISHIMA] Then we'll
be on our way.
[RAZELL] Did you hear
that?!
This little shrimp is tellin'
me he's a power-type Ramotith!
What's up with that?!
I'm twice his size,
I'm a frikkin' Razell!
[SHO] Be careful, all right?
There's some really important
stuff in there, pal!
[RAZELL] Open it up.
Come on, we gotta verify the
contents of all containers
going through
the checkpoint.
It's required because we're
on Alert Level 5.
[MAKISHIMA] That's no good.
There's radioactive
material in there.
It's not safe to
open it out here.
[OFFICER]
Don't give me that crap.
I'm sick of people dragging
junk through here.
Just the other day, those idiots
downstairs
were bringing in an
optimization tank.
Whatever you've got in there
we need to report to
the guys upstairs.
[phone beeps]
[RAZELL] If you're trying
to hide something from us,
then you'd better speak up
before it's too late.
Come on, what's the deal? You
hiding a woman in there or what?
[OFFICER] Yes, but... Yes, Sir.
Hey, guys, you can go.
[RAZELL] Wait, what's going on?
[OFFICER] Well, the guys
downstairs got all pissed off
because they thought we were
gonna contaminate the facility.
[RAZELL] Goddamnit!
Are they monitoring this
place or something?
You wanna come down here and
tell me what to do?!
[OFFICER] They left a message
for you too.
[RAZELL] Whaddya mean?
[OFFICER] They said if you're
not happy being a Razell,
they'll put in a request to have
you reoptimized by Dr. Barcas.
That sound good?
[RAZELL] What, you kidding me?
He'd tear me to shreds!
[SHO] Phew...
[MAKISHIMA] Looks like you're
sweating, Fukamachi.
[SHO] That was a close call,
can you blame me?
Besides, you're sweating
as much as I am!
[ODAGIRI] [chuckles]
I never thought I'd see you
so nervous, Agito.
[MAKISHIMA] Thanks a lot
for the help, Odagiri.
If you were watching us that
whole time,
you could have said something
a little sooner.
[SHO] Who is that?
[MAKISHIMA] His name's
Doctor Odagiri.
He's the research director
of the bottom level
of Relic's Point.
He's also the one who covered
for us back at the checkpoint.
[ODAGIRI] You're Sho Fukamachi,
right?
It's okay, you're safe now.
The cameras, sensors and
everything else
on the lowest level
are all under my supervision.
So as long as you're down here,
your presence will go unnoticed.
Welcome to what we call
the "free zone" here
at Relic's Point.
My name's Odagiri. My
research associates and I
are here to help you,
so don't worry.
Excuse me, where are my friends?
We let them know you were coming
to the lab,
so they should be
here any minute.
[SHO] Waitasec... Is that us?
[HAYAMI] This is what you
call a "dummy image".
The two of you will be seen
leaving here in 45 minutes.
3 hours later, you will join
a search team.
After a short while, the team
will split up
and lose sight of you.
Then it'll be like you
never existed at all.
It's all under control.
I'm Toshiaki Hayami.
I've been watching your battle
with Chronos.
Nice job, young man.
[SHO] Uh, nice to meet you!
Uh, there's no need to clap.
Sho!
[SHO] Tetsuro, it's you!
[TETSURO] Of course it is!
You're the one that
was in trouble!
It may sound cheesy, but now
that you're here,
it's like God
answered my prayers.
I know what you mean.
Tetsuro!
[TETSURO] Mizuki!
[MIZUKI] I'm so glad
you're all right.
Don't worry, Sho took good care
of me while you were gone.
[TETSURO] I know. It's okay now.
You don't have to cry.
[MIZUKI] Thank you...
All that matters is that the
two of you are safe.
[SHO] Mr. Onuma! Shizu!
This is great!
Everyone... everyone
made it out okay!
Uh, by the way, I don't see
Mr. Murakami anywhere.
He's okay, isn't he?
Tetsuro, show them.
Yes, Sir.
Hold on, Mizuki.
What's wrong?
[TETSURO] There's nothing
to worry about.
It may look bad, but he's
still all right.
[SHO] Mu..Murakami?
[fluid bubbling]
Wh..What happened?
We think he's just resting.
He exhausted all of his energy
trying to save us.
Did you get attacked by Zoanoids
after we split up?
Yeah, tell us what happened!
Right after you guys ran off
into the woods,
Guyot showed up and attacked us.
It took everything Murakami
had to protect us.
[MURAKAMI] No! How did he...
[GUYOT] Now you've really pissed
me off, you filthy maggots!
He's powering up again!
[MURAKAMI] All right, listen up!
He's about to hit us with
another gravity attack.
Everyone gather around me, and
I'll try to hold it off!
[ALL] Right!
[GUYOT] I'll send every last
one of you to Hell!
Gravity Crusher!
What just happened? Is it over?
[GUYOT] A barrier?
I bet you think you're clever,
don't you?
I'll have to show you the
power of a true Zoalord,
you impudent lab rat!
[MURAKAMI] When he launches his
next attack,
have your gravity
controller ready.
[MAKISHIMA] All right.
[GUYOT] I'll pound your
bones into dust!
[MURAKAMI] Now!
[GUYOT] [laughs evilly] Behold
perfection incarnate!
Pay the price for your defiance!
[Makishima breathing heavily]
[MAKISHIMA] We barely
made it out alive.
[TETSURO] I can't believe you
could protect all of us
with your barrier.
That was pretty risky, given
your condition.
Are you gonna be okay?
[MAKISHIMA] Well, we somehow
managed to survive,
but it looks like we aren't
going anywhere.
Murakami...
Hey, Murakami!
This is bad,
I think he passed out!
[MAKISHIMA] What?!
[YOHEI] Water's flooding in!
Oh no, it looks like his
barrier is giving out!
What're we gonna do?
[MAKISHIMA] Damn it! At this
rate, we'll be buried alive.
Huh? There's a... cave?
Yohei, you and Shizu stand back.
I'll use my pressure cannon to
blow a hole in the wall
so we can escape to the cave.
Did you say "cave?" Hey, are you
sure this isn't a lake?
[MAKISHIMA] I'm positive.
Don't worry.
I can sense a large manmade
structure behind this wall.
It has to be... a tunnel!
[TETSURO] Watch your step,
it's slippery.
[SHIZU] Okay.
[MAKISHIMA]
It looks like the tunnel
is still under construction.
[YOHEI] They probably stopped
digging when they ran
into an underground water vein.
From the looks of things, they
never bothered to clean up.
Makishima! Isn't this...
[MAKISHIMA] Yeah, I thought
this looked familiar.
We're back on the transport
line
we took to escape from
Relic's Point.
Now what should we do?
A breeze?
[MAKISHIMA] Looks like they
sent a reception.
[ODAGIRI] Wait! Don't shoot!
We're allies!
Our allies?
[ODAGIRI] We are those who
carry out
the will of Professor Yamamura.
You mean Murakami's old friend?
Who are you?
I'm Odagiri, a researcher
from Relic's Point.
We may work for Chronos,
but all the men in my
department
are sympathizers of
Professor Yamamura.
After the incident in Arizona,
we were forced to lay low.
We've been waiting all these
years
for an opportunity like this.
Please, let us help you fight.
[SHO] I... feel so worthless.
What do you mean, Sho?
Yamamura, Murakami, Odagiri...
They're all so brave.
They've given up everything for
their cause.
They risked their lives
to help this world.
But look at me. Even though I've
got the Guyver,
I've only thought of myself.
[TETSURO] Well, you protected
Mizuki, didn't you?
You risked your life to protect
my sister
and bring her back
safe and sound.
Thank you, Sho.
You don't have to thank me.
[MIZUKI] Hey, you guys!
Oh, I'm so sorry! You weren't,
like, having a moment, were you?
No! You got the wrong idea! We
were just talking about you!
[MIZUKI] You don't have to be
shy.
I know you two are
all lovey-dovey!
Okay, Mizuki, that does it!
[MIZUKI] When's the
wedding? [laughing]
[TETSURO] I said, cut it out!
You're really starting
to make me mad!
Professor Yamamura...
[SHIZU] Here, have some
herbal tea.
[ODAGIRI] Thank you.
It's made with chamomile leaves.
It'll help you relax.
[HAYAMI] This stuff is great!
[IJUIN] It sure is nice having a
girl around to cook for us.
[TORII] What'd you say this was?
Chamo... chamo...
[YOHEI] It's called
"chamomile," Sir.
It imparts a sense of
tranquillity.
[MAKISHIMA] Doctor.
Is Murakami doing any
better now?
[ODAGIRI] Well, there's been
improvement,
but he's still comatose.
For some reason, he's also
remaining in his battle form.
Fortunately, after we ran the
normal optimization process,
his damaged tissue healed.
But I'm not an expert on
Zoalords,
so when it comes down to the
specifics
of his nervous and energy
exchange systems,
I can only make inferences
based on my experience
with normal Zoanoids.
So you're saying there's nothing
we can do about the coma?
[ODAGIRI] No, he'll have to
recover on his own.
[MAKISHIMA] But this is serious!
As long as he stays in his
battle form,
he'll keep putting strain
on his body, right?
[ODAGIRI] Yes, I wish there
was something I could do.
Hm? Listen, none of you need to
worry about this mess,
just concentrate
on your work.
[IJUIN &amp; HAYAMI] Yes, Sir!
What's going on here?
An earthquake?
[MIZUKI] Ah, this feels great.
Wake me up when you beat
Chronos, okay?
[TETSURO] Oh no, you don't!
That's MY bed.
Go sleep in your own room!
[MIZUKI] No way. I'm scared.
What do you mean, you're scared?
We're safe down here.
[MIZUKI] I'm scared
of Makishima.
[TETSURO] You mean because he
killed all those people
in Takeshiro after
they turned into Zoanoids?
[MIZUKI] How could he do
something like that?
He just murdered them!
I thought I knew him!
I mean, we went to
the same school,
we talked to each other
every day!
We even served on the student
council together.
But now, I feel like I don't
know him at all.
Well, in that situation,
I'm sure he didn't have
much of a choice.
[MIZUKI] I know... I get it, all
right? But still...
It wasn't their fault they were
turned into Zoanoids.
They were no different
than Sho's da...
[TETSURO] Uh, hey, Sho. You
finished your bath already?
[MIZUKI] I'm sorry! I...
[SHO] Don't worry about it.
I think it's good to have
someone around
who can make level-headed
decisions like that.
Not like me.
Don't let it get you down, Sho.
There's nothing wrong with
feeling sympathy
for those people.
It's just that sometimes you
have to be a little heartless
in a situation like this.
[alarm going off]
What's wrong?
[SHO] Did something happen?
Guyot's coming. He picked a fine
time to pay us a visit.
[TETSURO] Oh no!
No way! Does that mean he
know's we're down here?
ODAGIRI] I doubt it.
He's probably just stopping by
to visit Dr. Shirai, as usual.
Wait, who's Dr. Shirai?
Although we rarely see him,
he's actually the top
researcher in our group.
He's obsessed with his work.
I suppose you could say he's
a bit eccentric.
That's why Dr. Odagiri is in
charge,
even if he's not the highest
ranked scientist here.
We're lucky Dr. Shirai is too
busy right now to notice us.
Doctor! Guyot's about to
be in range
of our surveillance cameras.
[IJUIN] It looks like he's
going to Shirai's lab.
What's he doing?
[MIZUKI] Why does Guyot keep
coming down here, anyway?
[HAYAMI] Funny you ask...
For whatever reason,
Dr. Shirai doesn't upload
his research data
to Relic's Point's
main computer.
His work's a complete mystery.
Whatever he's researching,
it looks like it's a secret even
to Dr. Barcas.
Even Barcas doesn't know?
What could they be doing?
[GUYOT] I can't afford to
wait any longer.
Now that I've targeted
Murakami,
I'm sure Barcas is aware of
my true intentions.
He may have even reported
it to Arizona by now.
Damn you, Shirai.
If you can't build a Remover
soon, I'll be as good as dead.
[odd vibration sounds]
What is this power I'm sensing?
[ODAGIRI] What's the matter?
We're receiving data from
the Relic, Sir.
[ODAGIRI] What does it say?
[TORII] There's a rapidly
intensifying biometric response!
[SHO] What are you
talking about?
[HAYAMI] Vibrations
rapidly increasing!
[IJUIN] None of the
potentiometers set up
around the relic are responding!
[ODAGIRI] Everyone, stay calm!
Remain at your stations
and record as much
data as possible!
[TORII] The biometric response
is intensifying!
[SHO] Wait, what do you
mean "biometric"?!
[ODAGIRI] The Relic is reacting.
It's alive.
[SHO] What?
[ODAGIRI] It may not appear so,
but the Relic is a living being.
[SHO] N-No way!
[ODAGIRI] I can't blame you for
your shock.
At first, I found it
hard to believe too.
But even the Creators'
spacecrafts
were living creatures
produced to fit their needs.
In that sense, they were no
different than humans.
Now you see that mankind is
not the only thing
the Creators left behind.
For tens of thousands of years,
another piece of their
legacy lay in wait,
surviving in a state of
suspended animation.
And still it lies, here within
this mountain,
imparting so
few of its secrets.
[MIZUKI] Tetsuro! Sho!
[TETSURO] What's wrong?
[MIZUKI] Something's
happening to Guyot.
It appears he's synchronizing
with the vibrations!
[HAYAMI] We've got
a problem, Sir!
Status report, Hayami?
[HAYAMI] It's the
optimization tank!
Murakami?!
[GUYOT] What the hell
is going on?!
[fluid bubbling]
[BARCAS] What are these
vibrations?
They seem to be coming
from below.
It must be the ruins.
But what does it mean?
[Guyot screams in pain]
Tetsuro, the door opened!
Yeah, the circuit shorted out.
[HAYAMI] I'll close it manually.
Yes, please!
We've got to act fast.
In its weakened state,
Murakami's body can't withstand
these vibrations
for much longer.
[GUYOT] What the hell was that?
What just happened to me?
[HAYAMI] There.
[SHO] Murakami!
Wait! Sho!
[GUYOT] It felt like the Relic
was calling out to me.
Perhaps it was reacting to
my Zoacrystal.
But why? I've been down here
many times,
but that's never happened.
It felt like...
No, it couldn't be.
What's he doing?
I don't know. I've never seen
anything like this before.
[SHO] Murakami!
[NARRATOR] It's the calm before
the storm at Relic's Point.
Guyot desperately moves to
activate the Guyver Remover
as the Council of Zoalords
plot his demise.
But before he can, a mysterious
man
with terrifying power
blocks his path.
As the enemies of Chronos
assemble for an all-out attack,
Sho and Makishima seek to
uncover the mysteries
of an ancient relic.
Next time: "The Night Before
the Final Assault"