It's gotten to the Enzymes
that are being optimized
and now it's...
[chokes]
[GUYOT] Guyver III?
Then the one that appeared in
block number 7 must be...
[Zerbebuth cries out in pain]
[TETSURO] Guyver?
[TETSURO] Sho? Sho!
Sh..Sho, it's really
you, isn't it?
[TETSURO] But... that isn't
possible! I mean, you were...
[SHO] Tetsuro?
[SHO] Tetsuro?!
Huh?!
What's going on here?
I mean, where are we?
[TETSURO] This doesn't
make any sense!
Last I remember,
I was fighting Enzyme.
But, it's like my mind went
totally blank after that.
It's really you?
I can't believe this.
You really are Sho, aren't you?
Yeah, at least, last time
I checked I was.
I'm so glad you're alive!
Oh! I'm so glad!
I don't care how,
I'm just thankful!
Te..Tetsuro, wait.
What's going on here?
[SHO] I don't understand.
[SOLDIER] It's the Guyver!
Watch out!
[RISKER] It's me, you fools.
Calm down.
[SOLDIER] Inspector Risker...
Excuse me, Sir! We are under
orders from Commander Guyot
to bring the injured Zerbebuth
to the optimization room.
[RISKER] You're too late.
[SOLDIER] You mean...
[RISKER] His wounds were fatal.
I put him out of his misery.
It was the last favor I
could do as his friend.
[SOLDIER] Yes, Sir!
[RISKER] I'm sure the commander
knows what really happened...
But at this point,
it doesn't matter.
My power is completely
unstoppable.
After all, Guyver I has proven
that we are virtually immortal.
Right now, my powers surpass
those of hyper-Zoanoids.
No one can defeat me, not
even Commander Guyot himself.
[laughs]
[SHO] I MELTED? Are you serious?
[TETSURO] Uhm, well yeah...
That's what it looked
like at least.
What was it like?
Was it really bad?
[TETSURO] You don't
remember at all?
Well no...
[TETSURO] What about that?
[SHO] Did I do that?
[TETSURO] If you didn't,
I don't know who did.
When I came to, I was
standing over there.
I don't know what the
heck's going on anymore.
Did that Zoanoid kill me?
[TETSURO] Let's just
forget about that
and break outta here, okay?
Break out?
[TETSURO] You really are
clueless, aren't you?
This is Chronos Japanese
headquarters.
[Sho gasps in shock]
Yeah, they kinda captured me.
No way! Why didn't you
tell me that sooner?!
[SOLDIER] Up there!
[TETSURO]
Crap! There they are!
[SHO] Guyver!
[SOLDIER] This is block 9.
Guyver I is escaping with
a prisoner from solitary.
Currently in pursuit, Sir!
[SOLDIER 2] Commander Guyot!
I regret to inform you that
Zerbebuth has...
Yes, I know.
[SOLDIER 2] Sir?
Be gone.
[SOLDIER] Sir!
[GUYOT] Risker, you bastard...
[SOLDIER 3] This is the
optimizations section.
We've lost sight of Guyver III,
but are currently sending
out a search party.
[GUYOT] Find him!
Guyver III... I can't
anticipate his moves.
What's his objective?
Excuse me.
I apologize for being late.
I was told that Guyvers I
and III are in the building?
The Japanese Branch
is a disgrace.
Even if it is the Guyvers
we're dealing with,
I should think that with
all of our resources,
we could avoid such
an absolute disaster.
I always tried to tell Father
something like
this might happen.
Our defenses are rather lacking.
[GUYOT] They're
intolerably lacking.
[TETSURO] Hey!
[SHO] What?!
[SHO] Which way do we go?
Up or down?
Uh, well I was kind of shaken
up when I came here.
I remember being dragged
onto an elevator,
but I don't remember if
it went up or down.
[SHO] You've gotta be kidding!
[SOLDIER 4] I heard voices!
They must be close by!
Search the area thoroughly!
[SHO] Tetsuro!
[TSTSURO] All right, up!
[SHO] Sounds good to me!
Let's go!
[TETSURO] Sho, it really
is you, isn't it?
I don't know what happened, but
somehow, you're still alive.
I'm glad, but...
[SHO] Are you all right?
[TETSURO] Uh, yeah...
[SHO] Is something wrong?
Oh, uh no, it's nothing.
C'mon, we should hurry.
Let's go.
[SHO] Tetsuro?
What's wrong?
We gotta get moving.
[SHO] Please, tell me the truth.
I died back there, didn't I?
I shouldn't be alive.
You said I melted, right?
But does that mean I... I...
I see...
But then how did I come back?
Somehow... I guess the power of
the Guyver resurrected you.
It was... like a miracle!
[SHO] That's pretty unscientific
coming from you, Tetsuro.
There's got to be more to it.
Hey... What if you're a clone?
[SHO] A clone?
Yeah, sure!
I bet some of your cells
were left over on
the control metal
and the Guyver used its power to
reconstruct you from that.
That makes sense, right?
I mean, the Guyver can
regenerate pretty fast
so it makes sense if it did
the same thing to you.
[SHO] A clone...
[TETSURO] Uh, well, it's...
just a guess, really.
[SHO] But if you're right...
Does that mean I'm the
same as I was before?
[TETSURO] Well, uh...
[SHO] I don't know a
lot about this stuff,
but aren't clones just...
[SOLDIER 4] There they are!
Right up there!
Sho, as far as I'm concerned,
you're still you.
And that's enough for me.
[SHO] Tetsuro...
[TETSURO] Right now,
let's just get the
hell out of here!
We can't keep Mizuki
and your old man
waiting any longer, right?
[SHO] Right.
[SHO] I bet Dad's worried sick
about me right now.
[FUMIO] He left the house
without telling me.
And there's no one home at
Tetsuro's place either.
Well, I guess he's
at that age now,
but this just isn't like him.
I can't help but think
that something bad
might have happened.
It's just like my father
used to say.
The more parents are
separated from their kids,
the more they worry.
I'm sure his mother would have
felt the same way right now.
Sho...
[claxons]
What's going on?
[SOLDIER] No way!
The self-destruct
system's online, Sir!
[GUYOT] What?!
[COMPUTER]
The self-destruct sequence
has now been initiated.
T-minus 10 minutes.
Please evacuate immediately.
[GUYOT] What is the
meaning of this?
[SOLDIER] I'm not sure, Sir.
It's the Emergency Biohazard
Response system.
It shouldn't have been so
easy to activate.
[MAKISHIMA]
It would be difficult
for an outsider to
pull this off.
[GUYOT] Are you saying we
were betrayed?
Well... I'm simply saying that
it wouldn't be possible
to initiate the
self-destruct system
without having considerable
knowledge of the building.
[GUYOT] Well, I can
think of a certain
overly ambitious employee
who acquired too much power
and let it go to his head.
Would he go that far?
[RISKER] Self-destruct?
What was the Commander thinking?
He's out of his mind.
[TETSURO] Don't tell me they're
going to blow up the building
and take everyone down with it!
[SHO] Isn't that a
little drastic?
Well, whatever! Let's hurry!
[SHO] Right!
[SOLDIER] It's no use,
Commander! We can't cancel
the sequence! Orders, Sir?!
[GUYOT] Calm down!
It can be canceled
within the first five
minutes of the countdown.
[SOLDIER] But, Sir!
Let me handle it.
[conintuing claxons]
[MAKISHIMA] Hm? No good.
[SOLDIER] It isn't working?!
The cancellation program's
been deleted.
So, now what?
There's a backup. I might
be able to restore it.
[SOLDIER] There's no time!
[GUYOT] Enough.
[MAKISHIMA] But, Sir,
at this rate, we'll lose the
entire Japanese Branch.
This place is useless to us.
If it's destroyed,
just make sure our secrets
are buried with it.
You evacuate as well.
Understood, Sir.
As an extra precaution,
I'll do a level five erase
on all network data.
The rest of you accompany the
Commander to the heliport.
See that the others are
evacuating as well.
[SOLDIERS] Sir!
[MAKISHIMA] I'll have Inspector
Risker escort you, Sir.
[GUYOT] Forget about him.
You take care of the rest.
Leave it to me, Sir.
[COMPUTER]
Warning... three minutes
to cancel self-destruct.
When countdown
reaches five minutes,
cancellation
will be impossible.
That's fine. There's no one left
to interfere with my plans.
[COMPUTER]
Warning... two minutes
to cancel self-destruct.
When countdown reaches
five minutes,
cancellation will
be impossible.
[SHO] Tetsuro, get down!
[TETSURO] Huh? Whoa! Hold on!
[MAKISHIMA] Was that Guyver I?
Interesting.
Well, good luck surviving
this one. [claxons continue]
Good. That should take care
of things here.
[RISKER] I see. So you're the
one responsible for this mess.
Wait, we're on the roof?
[TETSURO] It's you!
[SHO] You know him?
Yeah, he's the commander
of Chronos.
[SHO] What?
[MAKISHIMA] If you're trying to
stop the self-destruct sequence,
give up.
Actually, at this point
I don't really care
what happens to the
Japanese Branch.
If there's anything I am
interested in it's you.
It's not every day
that I find someone
with a power that rivals mine.
[MAKISHIMA] I see. So you're
the "overly ambitious employee
who acquired too much power
and let it go to his head."
[RISKER] What?
[MAKISHIMA] Nevermind.
[RISKER] Wait! I want
you to fight me.
[MAKISHIMA] Why?
[RISKER] There is no need
for three Guyvers.
One will do. Adapt!
[MAKISHIMA] Well, that's fine
with me, really. [chuckles]
[RISKER] What's so funny?
[MAKISHIMA] Your work hasn't
been too taxing, has it?
[RISKER] So that's how it is...
[COMPUTER]
Warning... 60 seconds
to cancel self-destruct.
[SOLDIER] Commander, we're
running out of time!
[TETSURO] Wait!
[SHO] Tetsuro?
There's something I still
need to ask you.
You told me that humans
were created as the basis
for some kind of
living weapon right?
If that's the case, then who
was it that created us?!
Answer me, damn it!
[RISKER] Eat this!
[RISKER] Now I get it. This
newfound power of yours
has expanded your ambitions
as well as your ego.
[MAKISHIMA] Ambitions?
[RISKER] With the
power of the Guyver,
it should be easy for you
to achieve an elite
status at Chronos.
[MAKISHIMA] Is that what
you're fighting for?
I'm afraid I don't harbor
such grand ambitions.
[RISKER] What?
[MAKISHIMA] I seek the
Japanese Branch's
destruction, that's all.
For now, at least.
[COMPUTER]
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
Self-destruct sequence
has been locked.
Detonation will occur
in five minutes.
[SHO] Tetsuro, come on! We're
running out of time!
No. I can't leave until
I know the truth.
[SHO] Tetsuro!
Commander!
The Creators. That is the name
we've given them.
Billions of years ago, a highly
intelligent race of beings
descended to Earth from the
far reaches of space.
Their appearance,
culture and home planet
are all a mystery to us.
They left very little behind.
All we know is that
they manipulated life on
Earth for billions of years
in an attempt to manufacture a
very specific type of lifeform,
a tool to serve their needs.
They required a creature
with great intelligence.
Something with highly
aggressive instincts
and the adaptability to thrive
in any kind of environment.
They needed a lifeform that
would serve them
as a living weapon.
Something with unparalleled
fighting abilities.
[SHO] You mean?
After much trial and error,
what they ultimately created
was the human race.
Of course, that was only
the beginning.
Humans are simply the basis for
other bioweapons,
including the Zoanoids.
However, the experiment was
left only half-finished.
For reasons unknown
to us, one day,
the Creators suddenly
departed from the planet,
never to be seen again.
And now... we will finish that
experiment using the knowledge
uncovered from the ruins the
Creators left behind.
We of Chronos will
enable humanity to
complete its transformation!
Its evolution!
Humanity shall perfect
its own form!
[MAKISHIMA] And after that, you
intend to take over the world!
Just so that elites like you
can rule as gods.
Guyver III!
[GUYOT] You bastard, who
the hell are you?!
[MAKISHIMA] Why don't you
just call me Zeus?
[GUYOT] What do you
mean, "Zeus"?!
[MAKISHIMA] This is the end.
Chronos Japan will be destroyed
and you along with it,
Richard Guyot!
[COMPUTER]
Four minutes to detonation.
Commander, there's no more time!
[MAKISHIMA] Get down.
[COMPUTER]
Three minutes to detonation.
[MAKISHIMA]
The metallic orb in your abdomen
is a gravity control device.
If you concentrate, you should
be able to levitate.
What do we do?
[SHO] There's not much choice.
[RISKER] Don't you dare
turn your back on me,
you son of a bitch!
[SHO] Guyver II!
[RISKER] Oh, look who it is.
You just don't know when
to stay dead, do you?
[RISKER] Well, don't worry,
I'll take care of that.
I'm afraid there's only room
for one Guyver, and that's me.
[SHO] Wait! This place is gonna
self-destruct any minute now!
[RISKER] So what? After all,
there's nothing to fear
when you're immortal!
[RISKER] Let's see if you've
gotten any better
since last time.
Is this supposed to be
some kind of joke?
You're as sloppy as ever, kid!
[Sho grunts in pain]
Sho!
[RISKER] If you stop moving,
you'll leave yourself
open to attack.
[RISKER] Too slow!
[Sho grunts in pain]
[COMPUTER]
60 seconds to detonation.
[RISKER] It's been fun,
but I think it's about
time to end this!
You won't be coming back again,
Guyver I!
Sho! Get up! Run away!
[power hum bulid up]
[TETSURO] Sho!
[RISKER] Wh..What's going on?
[TETSURO] This happened
to him before.
That's it!
Sho, get up!
[COMPUTER]
30 seconds to detonation.
Come on Sho, now's your chance!
It's his control metal!
Hit him in the head!
[Risker screams in pain]
[RISKER] What the hell
is happening to me?
Im..Impossible! I'm...
I'm invincible...
You... can't... defeat... me...
[COMPUTER]
10 seconds to detonation.
[COMPUTER] 8... 7...
[TETSURO] Sho!
[COMPUTER] 6... 5...
We gotta get out of here!
4... 3... 2... 1...
zero.
[Tetsuro screaming]
[SHO] Fly... Come on, fly!
[NARRATOR]
For a fleeting moment,
it seemed as if life had
returned to normal for Sho.
Revisiting memories of his
childhood, he is unaware that
Guyot is still alive
and plotting his demise.
As the hyper-Zoanoid Panadyne
engulfs Sho's town in flames,
his precious memories and hopes
for peace are reduced to ash.
However, in the
midst of the flames,
a mysterious new ally appears
to stand beside the Guyver.
Next time:
"Ash and Memories"