Enzyme, you've outlived
your usefulness. Destruct!
[Enzyme growls]
[Sho growls]
Sho... SHO!
He's dead...
[SOLDIER]
The Guyver and Enzyme
have both been
completely obliterated.
All units will now
return to base.
No way... This can't be...
[MAKISHIMA] Now all the
pieces are in place.
[traffic noise]
[GUYOT] So this is it?
[SOLDIER] Yes, Sir.
This is the control metal we
removed from Guyver I's head
before it was destroyed.
[GUYOT] It's unfortunate that I
was unable to see it in action
before it met its demise.
At any rate, if we
can unlock the secrets
of the control metal,
then we can proceed
with our plans without
the Guyver's interference.
Now, as for Guyver II...
[Risker gasps quietly]
Since one of our men
EQUIPPED the unit,
we were unable to conduct
a proper analysis of it.
[concerned sigh]
However, I can still analyze
THIS one as much as I like.
Finally, this will bring
me one step closer
to their knowledge,
to their power.
Hmm?
Are your optimizations
done already?
[ZERBEBUTH] Yeah, the data
from your Guyver II
gave us some insight
into its weaknesses.
So now, they've transformed me
into an even more
powerful hyper-Zoanoid.
I've transcended the Guyver.
It's no threat to me at all.
And I owe it all to my
old rival, Risker.
Or perhaps I should say
"former rival."
[struggling sounds]
[TETSURO] Let me go!
[SOLDIER] Shut up and walk!
[GUYOT] I see. So you're the
highschool student
who was with the boy
commanding Guyver I.
I'm Richard Guyot,
Commander-in-Chief of Chronos.
You son of a bitch!
You killed Sho!
I want my friend back!
You murderer!
[grunts]
There's no need to be so rough.
After all, he IS our
esteemed guest.
Sir!
[groan of pain]
If it's any consolation,
I regret that your friend
had to meet such a
sudden, violent demise.
Unfortunately, Enzyme's
desire for revenge
was way out of my control.
But you know, if this Sho,
or whoever,
had not been SO insistent
on defying us,
we could have resolved things
in a more peaceful manner.
[TETSURO] You bastard!
Just kill me already!
Just like you killed Sho!
[GUYOT] I'm afraid you're too
valuable to dispose of just yet.
You see, I need to ask you about
the third Guyver that
rescued you the other day.
I get it now.
Since Guyver III rescued us,
he must think I know
its identity.
That's probably why he
hasn't killed me yet.
Screw you!
[GUYOT] Well, it's no matter if
you don't want to talk now.
You and I can have a nice
little chat later.
And after that's settled...
I've got it, why
don't we have you
become our next
Zoanoid test subject?
[TETSURO] What do you mean?
I want you to see something.
[curious sound]
Those... Those are!
[GUYOT]
Those are all Zoanoids
in varying stages
of development.
Unfortunately, more
than half of them
don't make it through their
"optimizations" ...alive.
[scared noises]
The escapee that made
off with the Guyver unit
that you found near your school
was one of our test subjects.
[TETSURO] Holy shit! That means
those things aren't monsters
that take on human form,
but normal people who have
been turned INTO monsters!
[winces in distress]
You bastards! Don't you have
any regard for human life?!
Those who cannot
withstand optimization
are defective products.
Such insignificant creatures
have no right to live.
[TETSURO] That's sick!
Why are you making so many
of those monsters?
What the hell are you
trying to accomplish?!
Good question.
Since you're our newest
test subject, I'll tell you.
At this point, it won't be long
until we begin mass-producing
our creations...
At headquarters, they're using
the data we've acquired here
to develop newer, more powerful
Zoanoids as we speak.
But that's only the beginning.
Once we've produced
enough Zoanoids,
we'll secretly deploy them
to the ends of the Earth,
perfectly disguised
as normal humans.
[roars]
Then, after those Zoanoids
have worked their way
into key positions in the
world's governments,
we will put our plan into action
and they will reveal their
true forms all at once!
Can you imagine it?
Without warning,
the world will be thrown into
a state of terror as
invincible monsters,
more powerful than any weapon
the world has ever seen,
suddenly appear within
the command centers
of every nation.
In the ensuing chaos,
the world's militaries
and governments will
beg for our mercy.
Then the world will be ours!
It will be ruled by Chronos!
This global transformation
will usher in a new era
for all of mankind!
It is the birth of
a new humanity,
and a great step forward in
the evolution of man!
Evolution of man?!
A "NEW humanity"?!
Correct! They will be the new
rulers of planet Earth!
You mean those monsters?!
Those repulsive killing
machines?!
[GUYOT] Yes!
These Zoanoids represent what
mankind should strive to become!
Why, you ask?
Because humans were
originally developed
as the base material from which
all Zoanoids would be created!
Wait...
Zoanoids... are made of people?
[phone rings]
[WOMAN] Hello, Taga residence.
Oh, hi, Mizuki!
Hold on a second, okay?
Natsuki! You've got a call.
I'll just leave it here.
[NATSUKI] All right!
Hi, this is Natsuki.
Oh, hey Mizuki. What's up?
Huh? Tetsuro?
No, I haven't see him today.
Did something happen?
[MIZUKI] Well, he hasn't
come home yet
and when I tried calling
Sho's place
his dad said he
wasn't home either.
Sho too, huh?
Well, they're
probably just hanging
or going to the
movies or something.
It'll be fine. I'm sure it's
nothing to worry about.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well... Sorry for calling you
so late like this.
Yeah. Right. Yeah,
okay, goodnight then.
[sonic wave blast]
What the...
[Sho gasps]
[TETSURO] Mizuki!
That thing...
There's no way that wasn't
a real monster!
[pounding on door]
[TETSURO] Open up!
I said, "open up", you bastards!
[pounding continues]
[TETSURO] Damn it...
Isn't anyone there?
Open up!
You ain't making a test subject
out of ME, you monsters!
When Sho gets here, he'll...
Sho, you'd still be alive right
now if it wasn't for me.
Back then... I never should
have picked that thing up.
[TETSURO] Sho! Sho, you mind if
I talk to you for a second?
It's lighter than it looks.
Can't be a mecha, right?
Come on, man, cut it out.
What if the owner comes
looking for it?
Let's just leave it here, okay?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Finders Keepers!
[Sho gasps]
I think... I must've pushed
a switch or something.
[yelps]
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry!
I didn't know this
would happen, Sho!
[grunts]
Forgive me...
[sobs raggedly]
[electronic beeping]
[computer beeping]
[urgent computer beeping]
[SOLDIER] We just lost the
storage room display.
[SOLDIER 2] What? That's odd.
Come on! Piece of junk!
What's wrong?
Try accessing it again.
Right...
[quiet power hum]
Huh?
[HEINRICK] What's wrong?
The control metal is emitting a
faint electromagnetic pulse.
That's bizarre.
It should be completely
inactive at this point.
Hey! Look!
[surprised gasp]
Heinrick, it looks like it's
trying to activate again!
But how is this...
even possible?!
Something is starting
to ooze out of it!
It looks like it's trying to
form something. My God...
[wriggling noises]
We'd better contact the
control room immediately!
Right!
Control Room can...
[surprised gasp]
[SCIENTIST] This is the Guyver's
tissue, isn't it?
It's as if a piece of the
Guyver's flesh was
stuck to the control metal and
is trying to regenerate itself.
No, that can't be possible!
[choking &amp; gasping sounds]
Heinrick!
[gasps]
[whimpers in fear]
[struggling &amp; choking grunts]
[continuing wriggling noises]
[MAKISHIMA] What impressive
regenerative powers,
far beyond what I had imagined.
This has certainly become
interesting.
[claxons]
Why the alarm?
We suddenly stopped
receiving transmissions
from the security camera
in the storage room.
[SOLDIER 2] We're not getting
any signal at all right now.
What's that?
[surprised gasps]
[audible power hum]
Drop the shutter now! Hurry!
[CANDAN] Yeah, right!
[heavy impacts on door]
[surprised gasps]
Come on, we can take him!
Let's go!
[Gregole roars]
[Ramotith roars]
[heavy impacts on door continue]
You little bastard...
[guttural growling]
[impacts continue]
Here he comes. Watch out.
[claxons]
[GUYOT] Status report?
It's the Guyver!
It's launching an attack
in the storage area of
block number 7, Sir!
Just as I thought,  Guyver III
is making its move.
Go take care of him Zerbebuth!
You'd better not lose this time!
Sir.
[roars]
What a perfect opportunity
to show him what
we're really made of.
If we can capture him now,
we'll have all three units back.
[computer beeping]
Speak!
Come in! This is block number 2,
Zoanoid optimization sector!
The Guyver is here!
-[GUYOT] What?!
-It's gotten to the Enyzmes
that are being optimized
and now it's...
[chokes]
[GUYOT] Guyver III?
Then the one that appeared in
block number 7 must be...
Block number 5, computer
surveillance restored, Sir.
[GUYOT] Guyver I!
It's currently advancing
from block number 4
to block number 5, Sir.
It's breaking
through the barriers
and continuing its attack.
What is going on here?
Don't tell me it regenerated
from the control metal alone!
[MAKISHIMA] If these anti-Guyver
prototypes are allowed to live,
it could prove
troublesome for me later.
Better safe
than sorry.
[growls]
I'm surprised. You're
not dead after all.
I guess you're pretty
tenacious, huh?
[laughs] Well that's
fine with me.
I'm going to pay you back
for what you did to me!
Die, bastard!
[chuckles evilly]
My new high
frequency claws vibrate
just like your elbow blades.
But that's not all...
[laughs manically]
Hah! How do you like that?
Your puny little megasmasher
has nothing on this!
Let's go!
[roars]
[laughs evilly]
You can't even touch me.
Those spines
generate a forcefield
that negates the effect
of your pathetic weapons.
I've been redesigned to counter
all of your techniques!
I'm the perfect anti-Guyver
Zoanoid!
See you in Hell, Guyver!
You won't be coming
back this time!
[growls in pain]
[ZERBEBUTH]
Stop wasting my time!
[heavy breating]
[screams in pain]
[audible power hum]
[annoyed sound]
I can't believe an
enhanced hyper-Zoanoid
like Zerbebuth
couldn't stop Guyver I!
Commander Guyot. The Guyver
is currently advancing
towards block number 3, Sir.
Where's Risker? Get me Inspector
Risker immediately!
[continuing strained breathing]
Speak of the devil.
[ZERBEBUTH] Huh? Risker! Thank
God! You've gotta help me!
There's still time! Please!
Take me to the optimization
tank before it's too late!
I believe you said
I was your rival?
Actually, your "former rival".
[chuckles] That's nothing but a
pathetic self-delusion.
An arrogant little
piece of garbage
like you can't even
BEGIN to rival my power.
[Zerbebuth growls in pain]
Adapt!
[ZERBEBUTH] No! No!
Risker, wait!
[roars in pain]
[RISKER] Useless to the end.
What a disgrace!
What the hell's going on here?
[cries out in pain]
[grunts with effort]
[shocked gasp]
[TETSURO] Guyver?
Sho?
SHO!
Sho...
I-It's really you, isn't it?
[NARRATOR] A miracle has
occurred in the midst of chaos.
Rising from the ashes of defeat,
Sho and Tetsuro attempt to
escape the research facility.
As they stand atop the
towering structure,
Guyot reveals the secrets of
the mysterious Creators.
Meanwhile, the ambitions of two
men with god-like powers
collide as the countdown to
destruction begins.
Next time:
"Shuddering Skyscraper"