[ominous music building]
[MIZUKI] Tetsuro, please!
Answer me! What's wrong?!
What happened to Sho?!
I'll explain things later,
Mizuki.
We have to get going now.
What are you hiding from me?
Just say it!
[MURAKAMI] Come on, let's move!
We don't have time to stand
around bickering!
Is... is something wrong?
[MAKASHIMA] I can't expect you
to drive in weather like this
with your eyesight.
I better drive instead.
Why don't you let me drive?
I can handle it.
Shizu?
You must be exhausted,
Master Agito.
Besides I'm a lot more familiar
with this area than you are.
[YOHEI] Shizu's learned a lot
in these past three years.
She's been working
really hard, you know.
She wants to be of use to you
in any way she can.
That's what she told me.
[MURAKAMI] All right, let's go.
[MIZUKI] Am I the only one who
doesn't know what's happening?
[DERZERB] I'm telling you, boss
there's no mistaking it!
That was a Zoalord!
Wh..When he was staring me down,
it's like my whole body was
frozen in fear.
It was exactly the same
as when you or Dr. Barcas
use your thought
waves to control us.
I think this demands
our immediate attention,
don't you, Doctor?
With a power like that,
if we don't take care of
him right away,
he could become an even bigger
obstacle than he is now.
After all, even the strongest
Zoanoids
are helpless against Zoalords.
Teamed with the Guyvers,
he poses a formidable
threat to us all.
Well, perhaps. He may seem
like a threat right now,
but it all depends on if
he's a real Zoalord or not.
Are you trying to tell me
he's not a Zoalord?
[BARCAS] I suppose we'll have to
put him to the test
and see what he's made of.
[TETSURO] It's not your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Sho...
[SHO] Tetsuro? What happened?
What have I been doing?
Just forget it. Don't think
about anything,
you just need to rest.
[SHO] Wait... No, it can't be.
D..Did I do this? Dad...
This can't be happening...
Sho, I...
[Sho screams in anguish]
Sho!
[TETSURO] Sho!
[TETSURO] You're not the one
who did it Sho.
[MURAKAMI] Let's take a break
from driving for a minute.
Are you all right?
[MIZUKI] Uh, yeah...
Grandfather, you ll find some
canned drinks
in the mini-cooler
sitting next to you.
Could you get her
something, please?
Oh, sure. I hope you like
this flavour alright.
Anything's okay, thanks.
Um, Shizu, is this really all
right?
I just... I don't know what I'm
supposed to do.
I mean, in a situation like
this, what CAN you do?
[thunder rumbles]
[SHIZU] Well, in my case,
I'm just trying to
serve Master Agito in any
way that I can.
[MIZUKI] Even with all that's
happening,
she only thinks about
Makishima.
[thunder grows louder]
Now what? I'm not sure where
to take it from here.
Well, I guess we, could go
back to town right?
We might be able to blend in
with a crowd, or, uh...
[MAKISHIMA] No, that won't work.
They'll be ready for us.
I'm sure Takeshiro is under
their control by now.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sure Barcas and Guyot are
watching the town.
All they have to do is
use their mind-link.
Unfortunately, that
means that no place is safe.
We should avoid being
seen by anyone.
Huh?
[MURAKAMI] Someone s coming.
Maybe they live around here.
No, I don t think so, kid.
Be on your guard, this
could get ugly.
[thunder crashes]
Master Agito!
[MAKASHIMA] Shizu,
stay in the car!
Start the engine and get ready
to pull out of here
when I give the word!
Right.
[chuckling]
[Zoanoid transformation growls]
Zoanoids!
[MURAKAMI] They're not just
ordinary ones either.
They're the most dangerous kind
of opponent we could face now.
[BARCAS]
These are the prototypes that
underwent their optimizations
alongside that boy's father.
Their codenames are
zero-two, three and four.
Fumio Fukamachi was candidate
zero-one,
and while he may have looked the
same as these zoanoids,
there's a fundamental
difference between them.
He was chosen for his
relationship to the boy,
but these are combat
trained specialists.
[GUYOT] A team of Enzyme IIs...
[BARCAS] Yes, the Guyver's
natural enemies.
[TETSURO] Did Sho's dad
transform like that too?
Right in front of his eyes?
Hey, Murakami!
[Enzyme II growls]
[MURAKAMI] Halt!
Good boy, now get out of
here.
Turn around and go right
back where you came from.
[Enzyme II roars]
[MURAKAMI] What the hell?
No! Master!
Please be careful!
[MAKISHIMA] Bioboost!
[MURAKAMI] Why don't my thought
waves work on them? Barcas!
[Enzyme II growls]
[MAKISHIMA]
I'll send you to Hell!
[MAKASHIMA] What is this?!
Be careful! Those things are
packed with enzymes
that've been specially designed
to dissolve bioboosted armor!
[MAKISHIMA] I see. I that means
I'll have to
plan my attacks more carefully
from now on.
[loud crash]
No!
[Enzyme II growls]
Sho's... Stop it!
[Enzyme II roars]
Oh, no!
Sho! You've gotta wake up!
You're being attacked! Sho!
Please wake up! Please!
[Enzyme II growling]
[Sho screams in fear]
Sh..Sho!
Get out of there!
[MAKISHIMA] Fukamachi!
This can't be happening.
There's no way...
Whoa!
[MIZUKI] Sho can't just die,
after all this! He's
gotta be okay!
Tell me this isn't happening,
Tetsuro! It just can't be.
It can't... [sobs]
[metal being shoved around]
Mizuki... Mizuki, look.
[TETSURO] He s alive!
He made it.
[SHO] I heard her voice.
I heard Mizuki calling me.
Tetsuro! Mizuki!
[SHO] Look out! Behind you!
[Enzyme II roars]
[TETSURO] Duck!
[SHO] Mizuki!
[Enzyme II continues roaring]
Sho!
[MAKISHIMA] What happened?
[Enzyme II roars in pain]
Mu..Murakami!
[MAKISHIMA] Look out!
What... What's going on?
Are you all right?!
[MAKISHIMA] You idiot! What the
hell were you thinking!?
Don't disengage your armor in
the middle of battle!
Are you trying to get
yourself killed?
I wasn't trying to disengage it.
It just came off all by itself.
[SHO] It's weird, I feel like
I've seen that kind of
Zoanoid before,
but I can't remember where.
Why is it bothering me so much?
Tetsuro, this is the first
time
we've seen that kind of
Zoanoid, isn t it?
[TETSURO] He doesn't remember?!
It s no good. I can worry about
all that
after I've taken care of them.
Guyver!
Guy..Guyver!
I can't equip it?
Sho...
GUYVER!
[BARCAS] I had hoped that using
the boy's father
would have resulted in
Guyver I's defeat,
but it appears to have had
an interesting effect
on the boy's psyche.
[MURAKAMI]
We're in trouble.
If I don't do something, we'll
all be killed.
I've really only got
one option.
After using my power last time,
it's a gamble,
but I've got to try.
It's do or die.
Now, Theriomorph!
[Enzyme IIs growl in confusion]
Murakami?!
[SHO] That's insane. I've never
seen power like that.
What in the world is he?
Impressive strength.
Indeed, and after seeing him
transform, I know what he is.
Come on Richard, think. Take
a long good look at him.
Notice anything special?
[GUYOT] Well, no matter
how I look at him,
he seems to possess the
battle form of a Zoalord.
No, that's impossible...
[MURAKAMI] I cannot afford to
prolong this.
I'll have to finish
them all at once!
[Enzyme IIs roar]
[MURAKAMI] Not good enough.
[Enzyme II roars in pain]
[MURAKAMI]
Ha..Have I reached my limit?
[Enzyme II's death rattle]
Yes, he did it!
Hey! Is he... Murakami!
[BARCAS]
Well, what do you think?
Striking resemblance to your own
battle form, wouldn't you say?
Yes, that's true.
Then that must mean Mr. Murakami
is one of your test subjects.
So, he is just like me.
[GUYOT] After all, I can't
forget that you were the one
who optimized me, Dr. Barcas!
[SHO] I don't get it. Why can't
I transform anymore?
[TETSURO] He really doesn't
remember what happened?
His father turning
into a Zoanoid?
I guess he wasn't conscious
when the Guyver went berserk
and killed him.
The shock was probably so great
it's caused a temporary
lapse of memory.
I guess I can't really blame
him, though.
Even if he wasn't conscious,
he still...
Goddamn Chronos! They're
nothing
but a bunch of
sadistic bastards!
[MIZUKI]
What happened back there?
How did Sho end up like this?
[Murakami stirs]
He's waking up!
Hey guys, look.
You okay, Murakami?
[MURAKAMI] Yeah,
but where are we?
You didn't miss much.
We're still in the
mountains right now.
Who are you? At this point, it's
obvious
you have some kind of connection
to Chronos.
It's probably okay to let us
know now, right?
About your true form, I mean.
Are you a Zoalord? Or what?
[TETSURO] A Zoalord?
Yeah, now that you mention it,
that's what those two Zoanoids
were calling him, isn't it?
So what is a Zoalord anyway?
Well, I've only heard the word
mentioned before,
so I don't really know
the details myself.
If you really wanna know,
they're Zoanoids of
the highest order.
They have the power to
command other Zoanoids.
They can form mental links with
any number of Zoanoids,
then control them as they
would their own bodies.
To those who have been
transformed into Zoanoids
the Zoalords are something
akin to Gods.
Only twelve individuals on this
planet possess these powers.
The twelve members of the
Chronos Board of Directors,
the men who rule this world
from the shadows.
And Guyot is one of
them isn't he?
No wonder he was able to
block my attack.
But if you're not one of them,
then what are you?
I was a test body for the final
Zoalord,
for Richard Guyot's battle form.
A test subject? So you were
a prototype Zoalord?
It all happened five years ago.
I was working as a magazine
correspondent at the time.
A team of reporters,
including myself,
had traveled to the jungles of
New Guinea to cover a story.
When we got to the site, the
villagers there were
all worked up about
some strange rumor.
They warned us that some kind
of "monsters"
had started appearing
in the area.
The local elders tried to stop
us from going any further,
but we didn't listen
and moved deeper into
the jungle.
It turned out that the place was
one of Chronos'
Zoanoid test sites.
All I could do was
stare in horror
as my colleagues were torn
limb from limb
by these terrible creatures.
I survived, but they weren't
done with me yet.
They took me to an underground
base of theirs in Arizona.
There, I served as their guinea
pig
for optimization experiments.
But then something strange
happened.
I had an unexpected reunion with
an old college professor of mine
named Shinichiro Yamamura.
[BARCAS] It's not just that he's
similar to you,
Richard, he's actually
your prototype.
[GUYOT] Ridiculous. How could a
test subject like that
still be alive after
all these years?
[BARCAS] I want you to recall a
certain event
that occurred five years
ago in Arizona.
[GUYOT] Arizona? Professor
Yamamura's rebellion?!
Correct.
Yamamura, who had been the brain
of Chronos for 15 years,
plotted to incite a rebellion
by stirring up several
of his own experiments,
who had out lasted their
usefulness.
All though test subjects,
they still possessed the powers
of a true Zoalord,
which lead to quite an uproar
at that headquarters.
[GUYOT] I only found out about
the incident later.
At the time, I was in the final
phase of Zoalord optimization.
They went on a rampage,
destroying every optimization
tank in sight.
Although their plan failed, it
was you they were after.
Fortunately, I and the other
Zoalords
were gathered at the base.
It was a ordeal, but the
situation was resolved.
The insurgents were rounded up
and destroyed in the test
subject disposal tank,
as they should have been
in the first place.
Or so we thought. Knowing that
one of them survived,
I'm rather
taken aback.
Now, the question is, why were
the test subjects
so determined to
destroy you Guyot?
Ah, yes, I was wondering
about that myself.
Watch out, Richard. We don't
know Murakami's objectives.
If we don't take care of him
quickly,
he may make another attempt
on your life.
[GUYOT] This is a mystery to me.
When I awoke, my optimization
had ended,
and the situation had already
been resolved.
Professor Yamamura, what
were you plotting?
It couldn't be! Maybe he KNEW!
[TETSURO] So Professor Yamamura
was the one
that made you into one of
Guyot's prototypes.
That's right. At the time,
there were already
three other prototypes that
had sided with the professor.
Unfortunately, they were part
of Barcus' experiments.
At first, they resented
the professor,
but once they knew his true
intent,
they changed their minds.
They knew that he was risking
his life.
They understood the magnitude
of the situation.
20 years ago, Professor Yamamura
advocated the theory
that Mount Minakami was
actually man-made.
His studies lead him to uncover
the secret of the Creators
buried within the ancient ruins
inside the mountain.
By that time, Chronos had
also caught wind
of the mountain's secret,
and kidnapped the professor.
He was then made to cooperate
with them against his will.
For 15 years, he pretended
to be their pawn,
all the while waiting
for an opportunity
to topple the organization
from the inside out.
It was then that he discovered
the horrifying truth
behind the Guyvers.
It was a truth that had shaped
history,
a truth that could
destroy our future.
[NARRATOR] The truth
behind the Guyver units
and their connection
to mankind is revealed.
Unable to accept the grim
reality,
Mizuki flees from her friends.
Sho follows her into the woods
and expresses his own
feelings of doubt.
Meanwhile, Guyot decides to
personally eliminate everyone
that stands in his path.
The powerful cries of a
Zoalord quake the earth.
Next time:
"Guyot Joins the Fray"