[ODAGIRI] Hurry! It's
only a matter of time
before this level
collapses as well!
[SHO] I prepared some
space inside the Relic
where all of you can stay.
It looks like the
earthquakes are getting worse,
so you'd better hurry!
[SHO] As soon as the
energy is charged,
I'll launch the ship and
take us to the surface!
[SOLDIER] Man, where the hell
are our replacements?
We shoulda been relieved
an hour ago, Thomson.
Yeah, I know, but what if
they had a big accident
down there, or something?
Either way, all we can do
is keep waiting around.
I just hope someone gets here
before the storm hits.
Whoa, what was that? Lightning?
This must be Mount Minakami.
Strange, there seems to be a
massive convergence of energy
coming from somewhere
beneath the base.
But there's something else too.
I'm sensing a large scale
distortion in gravity.
Do you think it's him?
There's no doubt. Guyot is
responsible for this.
[Guyot laughs]
[GUYOT] How do you like
that, Archanfel?
This is my ultimate attack!
A 7000 exa-ton quasi-black hole!
What's the matter?
It looks like you're
having trouble
keeping up your force field.
That's what you get for
underestimating my power!
[BARCAS] Archanfel!
Stop it now, Richard!
This is madness!
[GUYOT] So there you are, you
senile old goat.
I was wondering where you were.
You know, you made this all
possible.
You made me the most powerful
Zoalord ever known!
You fool! If I had
known you would use it
for your own selfish desires,
I wouldn't have given you
that power at all!
How dare you turn against
Lord Archanfel?!
Do you realize what would happen
if the black hole is allowed to
continue growing like this?
It will cause irrevocable
damage to the entire planet!
[GUYOT]
Ha! Don't lecture me, old man.
I know the power I wield.
[BARCAS] Then why are
you letting this go on?!
Neutralize it!
[GUYOT] Is that all you wanted?
Do it!
[GUYOT]
Shut up and stay out of my way!
I won't be neutralizing
anything!
Quite the contrary,
I'm letting it build!
I will see Archanfel fall,
no matter how many souls
fall with him!
You imbecile!
If it comes to that,
then the black hole
will consume you!
[GUYOT] So what? [laughs]
If I can't finish him off,
I'm as good as dead!
I might as well take
him with me!
[GUYOT] Begone, Archanfel!
Find your fate beyond
the event horizon!
[ODAGIRI] Come on! Just a
little bit farther!
Something feels really weird
all of the sudden.
[Mizuki screams]
I'm floating!
Mizuki!
[ODAGIRI] What in the world?
What is this?
What fearsome strength!
I had no idea he could
command such power!
Look! Even the clouds
are being affected!
[PURGSTALL]
Surely, you're mistaken.
This can't be his work!
I had heard rumors that
Guyot was the strongest
of the Zoalords, but
this is beyond belief.
I know that he can
control gravity,
but is it really possible
for him to affect it
on such a large scale?
I'm afraid so.
If he calls on
the forbidden power,
there's no limit to
what he can do.
[PURGSTALL] Forbidden power? You
mean the quasi-black hole?
Guyot, you're a fool!
If you keep this up, you're
going to kill us all.
Who could you possibly be facing
that would force you to
unleash such power?
[SIN] No, it couldn't be...
[GUYOT] This is the end!
Begone, Archanfel!
[ARCHANFEL] No!
[Archanfel screams]
Archanfel, no!
[GUYOT] I did it... [laughs]
I actually did it!
[BARCAS] I can't believe it!
[GUYOT] Help me out, old man.
The black hole's grown
beyond my control.
It's going to take both of
us to neutralize it.
[BARCAS] He expects my help
after what he's done?!
[GUYOT]
Do it! Unless you'd rather die.
[GUYOT] Ready?
[BARCAS] Yes.
[GUYOT] Fire!
It's no use! It's grown too
large for us to control!
[GUYOT] Bah! Try it again!
[GUYOT] FIRE!
Vanish, damn you!
[MURAKAMI]
It must have been Guyot,
but where did he get
power like that?
It's gone now.
[BARCAS] I can't believe it.
Even with its size, he was able
to banish the black hole.
[Guyot laughs]
I won! I did it!
I, Richard Guyot, have
defeated Archanfel!
No one can stop me now! No one!
[Guyot continues to laughs]
[BARCAS] Unbelievable!
[TETSURO] I don't understand.
What just happened?
[ODAGIRI] I'm not sure,
but I know we can't afford to
be standing about! Let's go!
[EVERYONE] Right!
Everyone, watch out!
Oh man, now what's going on?
He's come for us.
It's Guyot!
[GUYOT] You?! What the hell do
you think you're doing here?
I see, so they've been
hiding you, huh?
That explains why I haven't
been able to track you down.
You've been right under my
nose the entire time.
[laughs]
Damn! We were so close!
Doctor, stand back.
I'll try to hold him off
as long as I can.
In the meantime, try to get
everyone inside the Relic.
[ODAGIRI]
Murakami, are you sure?
[MURAKAMI] I'm fine, just take
care of the others.
You can't!
Don't do it, Murakami! I mean...
Your body won't be able
to handle it.
[MURAKAMI] Is it still possible
for me to transform?
[ODAGIRI] I imagine you
could do it once more,
but your lifespan will be
drastically reduced
in the process.
One more time, huh?
Hey, thanks for everything.
You take good care of
Sho, all right?
Mizuki...
[MURAKAMI] What's wrong Guyot?
You don't look so
hot. Outta gas?
[GUYOT]
Shut up, bastard prototype!
Spare me the bravado!
I don't know what's
going on up there,
but it looks like it's taken
quite a toll on you.
I have a feeling
you're not so tough
now that you've used up
your gravity spheres.
I bet I could take you down
without even breakin' a sweat!
Come on! I think it's about
time we settle the score,
once and for all!
[GUYOT] Enough!
[MAKISHIMA]
Stand back, Murakami.
Let me handle this one.
You take care of the others.
Master Agito!
[ODAGIRI] Makishima...
[MAKISHIMA] If you want to talk
about settling scores,
I think it's high time we took
care of a few of our own.
Isn't that right, Guyot?
[GUYOT] You're here too?
I see, it's only natural.
[Guyot begins to laugh]
[MAKISHIMA]
Did I miss something funny,
or are you just happy to see me?
[GUYOT] Oh, I'm happy all right.
[Guyot continues to laugh]
In fact, I don't think I've
ever been happier!
And it's all thanks
to you, Agito!
Come to me now, Unit Remover!
[SHIRAI] The Remover's
activating on its own!
[Guyot laughs]
[SHO] No, it can't be!
What is that?
It looks like it
might be that thing
that was missing from the ship!
[Guyot continues to laugh]
Guyot's charging it with
his life force.
It could be some kind of weapon!
Don't let your guard
down, Makishima.
It looks like he
might be getting ready
to fire off a shot.
[MAKISHIMA] Then, I guess I'll
just have to hack his arm off
before he can attack!
[SHO] Makishima, no! Stay back!
[Makishima lets out
a battle cry]
[MURAKAMI] Makishima!
[GUYOT] Damn it, didn't have
a sufficient charge.
Master Agito...
What's going on, Doctor?
I'm not sure, but that device
seems to have the power to
unequip the Guyver armor.
[SHO]
Unfortunately, it's something
much more dangerous than that.
[MIZUKI] Sho?
[SHO] It's called a Remover.
I learned about it from the
Relic's main computer.
It deletes the user data stored
in the control metal's memory.
So, it doesn't just
unequip the Guyver,
it completely separates it
from its host.
[MAKISHIMA] What?!
[SHO] You have to avoid that
thing at all costs, Makishima!
If you suffer a direct hit,
your control metal
will shut down
and the Guyver will return
to its original state,
like it was before you
initialized it.
[MURAKAMI]
Now it all makes sense.
Thats why Guyot stayed
in Japan,
even after all the units
were released.
He was waiting for a chance to
get his hands on that thing.
[MURAKAMI] Listen, I'll
try to hold him back.
Use this as a chance to
get yourself and the
others inside the Relic.
[MAKISHIMA]
Can you handle this alone?
You're going to get
yourself killed!
Just do as I say, all right? We
have two priorities right now.
The first is to get everyone
inside the Relic
so we can bring down the base
and get the hell out of here.
The second...
is to prevent Guyot from
getting his hands on
the bioboosted armor,
no matter what the cost!
[MAKISHIMA] I understand...
Even if you have to
leave me behind,
move out as soon as the
Relic is charged.
I'll try to meet up
with you later.
[GUYOT] Sorry to keep you
waiting so long,
but thanks for giving me time
to get a re-charge!
This is it, Agito!
You've decieved me for
the last time!
Let's see how tough you are
after I've taken
your Guyver unit!
[MURAKMAI] You haven't won yet!
[GUYOT] You just don't know
when to die, do you?
Guyot, I'll stop you from
taking his Guyver
even if it costs me my life!
[GUYOT] Oh?
Theriomorph!
I... I can't transform!
Oh, Murakami...
[GUYOT]
You miserable little worm!
A guinea pig like you
has no right to stand
before a perfect specimen!
[MIZUKI] Murakami!
[GUYOT]
Your dummy crystal is resonating
at the same frequency
as my Zoacrystal.
I can paralyze you at
my every whim,
and you can't even raise
a finger to stop me!
No! Stop!
[Murakami screams in pain]
[GUYOT] I've seen about all
I can stomach of you.
These should finish you
off for good!
[MURAKAMI] Gravity bullets?!
He still has enough strength
to use those?!
[GUYOT] Time to die!
[MAKISHIMA] Odagiri! Doctor!
[cries of concern]
[SHO] You bastard!
What have you done?!
[GUYOT] You're just delaying the
inevitable, you useless maggot.
But that's fine with me. I'll
kill you all if I have to!
So you can still stand.
Tough bastard.
This isn't over...
I'll kill you, Guyot!
I swear it! Theriomoprh!
[MIZUKI] This is it...
This the end, his final
transformation.
[GUYOT] I don't understand.
You were finished!
How did you ever
overcome the effects
of the crystal's resonance?
Damn it! Why won't you die?!
[MURAKAMI]
I can't let it end here!
No matter how powerful you are,
I will find the strength
to oppose you!
I have got protect those
who will carry on this
fight after I'm gone!
Doctor...
[MIZUKI] What should we do now?
[ODAGIRI] Hurry, please.
You have to get
everyone inside the Relic.
[MAKISHIMA] But I...
It's all right, you have to
leave me and Murakami behind.
Murakami is willing to give up
everything to save you.
His sacrifice mustn't
be in vain.
[GUYOT] You bastard!
They're going inside the Relic!
What the hell's going on here?
[MURAKAMI] It has begun.
[SHO] All right, energy
replenishment is complete.
Activate thrusters!
[GUYOT] The Relic, it's moving!
[SHO] Get ready! I'm taking
the ship to the surface!
[GUYOT] I can't believe it!
Those bastards actually found a
way to launch the Relic.
[MURAKAMI] Guyot!
[Guyot yells in surprise]
[Murakami lets out a battle cry]
[NARRATOR]
The long-dormant spacecraft
soars into the sky
above Mount Minakami,
bringing down Relic's Point
as it rises.
The Guyver I becomes the target
of the Unit Remover,
as he risks his life to
protect Murakami.
Meanwhile, the Twelve Zoalords
spring into action
and launch an attack
of their own.
Next time:
"Ray of Annihilation"