I... I'm still here.
I'm still alive.
The creation of
mankind...
bioweapons... Chronos...
Zoanoids...
the Creators... Guyvers...
It's all so overwhelming.
What can we do against
enemies like that?
How are we supposed to deal
with something so huge?
How can we fight back?
It seems pointless
to even try.
But... Sho's known that all
along from the very beginning.
While I was living a
normal life...
he was carrying that weight.
No matter how badly
he's beaten,
he still keeps fighting.
No matter how hopeless it
seems, he never gives up.
What have I been doing?
All this time, I've just
been running away.
He's been carrying that
burden all alone...
and I've been too
afraid to help.
[ZX-TOLE] Judging by all
these scars on the ground,
I'd say this is where
that Zoanoid and the
Guyver faced off.
[DERZERB] Musta been one
hell of a fight.
[GASTER] Yeah.
[ELEGEN]
That gash must have been made
by the Guyver's megasmasher.
[ZX-TOLE] But look, this one
is different.
[DERZERB]
Just looks like it came from
one of Vamore's
biolasers to me.
[ZX-TOLE] C'mon, look at
that trench!
You really think a measly Vamore
could do something like that?
I'm the only Zoanoid
that can come close to
firing a laser that powerful!
[ELEGEN] Then what about
this one?
[DERZERB] Well, the guy
making the report
DID say the Zoanoid was
overpowering the Guyver.
[GASTER] The poor bastard
must have gotten vaporized
by that giant biolaser.
[ELEGEN] You don't think he was
being targeted, do you?
I mean, by the Zoanoid.
[ZX-TOLE] There's no telling.
Found anything?
[ALL] Doctor Barcas!
[ZX-TOLE] Sorry, Sir, but
we were too late.
The Guyver and the rogue
Zoanoid have left the area.
[BARCAS] No matter.
[ZX-TOLE] Sir?
Be careful.
Something's wrong here.
[ZX-TOLE] What do you mean, Sir?
This is a bit suspicious,
isn't it?
The appearance of the Guyver
is one thing
but I'm more concerned about
this unidentified Zoanoid.
For some reason, I can't reach
him with my mind-control.
Although, I didn't have
much to work with,
I looked over the data
for all the Zoanoid types
developed here in Japan.
I had to get down
to the irregular
and failed attempts before
I found a match.
Only one has a laser
like you mentioned.
[ZX-TOLE] What do you mean?
A Zoanoid unknown to the world.
An irregular creation that
should not have
appeared here in Japan.
Actually, this creature
is so unique
that I'm not really certain you
can call it a Zoanoid at all.
[ZX-TOLE] If it's not a Zoanoid,
then what could it be?
[Elegen screams in surprise]
[ZX-TOLE] Elegen!
[DERZERB] Elegen!
[Elegen screams in fear]
[BARCAS] Stay back!
Listen, Elegen, can you hear me?
Use your electric shock!
[Elegen screams in pain]
[GASTER] Elegen?
[ZX-TOLE] This isn't good. He's
lost control of his voltage.
[BARCAS] Is that who I
think it is?
[ZX-TOLE] Something's latched
onto him! Is that a Zoanoid?
[DERZERB] Whatever it is
it's smiling!
[GASTER] You son of a bitch!
Who the hell are you?!
[Aptom snorts in derision]
[BARCAS] Aptom!
[DERZERB] Aptom? That guy from
the Lost Numbers?!
[APTOM] Now that I'm
in control of Elegen,
we can finally have a little
chat, right, Dr. Barcas?
As you know, the Lost Numbers
aren't like normal Zoanoids.
We can't be mind-traced or
controlled by Zoalords.
That's why I've been able to
move around undetected.
After all the re-optimizations
you performed on me,
our link has become so weak
that I'm completely
beyond your grasp
unless I equip that special
transceiver of yours.
[BARCAS] So now you show your
true colors!
I knew you were up to something
when you ceased contact,
but turning on your comrades!
I won't tolerate defiance!
Now release Elegen this instant!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
I need Elegen to
help me regenerate
after my battle with the Guyver.
If I siphon his lifeforce,
I can regenerate myself.
[GASTER] Elegen...
[ZX-TOLE] It can't be!
You mean HE'S the
unidentified Zoanoid?!
[BARCAS] You ungrateful swine!
Have you no gratitude for the
man who gave you these powers?!
Hmph! Don't make me laugh.
This is the price you pay
for using a human as
your personal guinea pig.
It was your experimentation
that set me free!
Thanks to your
incessant tinkering,
your mind control
doesn't affect me,
so I'm no longer forced to
submit to your will!
That's right, Doctor,
I have evolved far beyond the
limits of your lowly Zoanoids!
What you see before you is the
birth of a new lifeform
that refuses to bow to your
pompous threats!
[Barcas gasps]
[APTOM]
Observe, Doctor,
I can absorb Zoanoids
into my body,
and by converting their bio
matter into energy,
I acquire their
special abilities
and incorporate
them into my own.
With each new victim,
I evolve into an even more
powerful battle creature!
What do you think of
your creation?
I... I had no idea...
[APTOM] You've let all that
power go to your head, old man.
It's made you careless.
All this time, I was nothing
but an experiment to you,
but perhaps you should have
been more mindful
to what the outcome of that
experiment would be!
Look at that,
in just a few minutes
I've already been able to
assimilate Elegen's
body into my own.
Can you feel it? Our psychic
link is starting to fade away.
[Barcas growls angrily]
Well, it's been fun!
Farewell, Doctor!
[BARCAS]
ZX-Tole, Derzerb, Gaster!
Dispose of this
traitor immediately!
[DERZERB] You son of a
bitch, how dare you?!
I'll bathe you in the
fires of Hell!
I hate to break it to you,
but the fires of Hell aren't
really cutting it.
[ZX-TOLE] It's no use.
His heat resistance is
the same as Elegen's!
[ZX-TOLE] Look out!
[Derzerb roars in pain]
[ZX-TOLE] Derzerb!
[DERZERB] Bastard...
[GASTER] Let me handle this!
All projectiles, fire!
[GASTER] Did I get him?
[Aptom laughs]
Not bad! That's a pretty
interesting attack
you've got there, Gaster!
Next time, I'll have to
absorb you!
Until then, be sure to stay
alive, all right?
[Aptom laughs evilly]
[ZX-TOLE] This Aptom is a
formidable opponent.
Mizuki...
Mizuki?
Come on, please be all right.
Mizuki!
You're safe! Thank God!
[MIZUKI] Where WERE you?
I can't believe you kept me
waiting for so long!
This is dangerous, you know!
What would I have done if
a Zoanoid showed up, huh?
You can't just leave me alone!
I need you to protect me!
Well, yeah, but...
[MIZUKI] No buts about it!
You've been like this as
long as I've known you!
No matter what happens, you're
always slow to catch on,
and when you do finally
go out and do something,
you always come back late.
You never tell me where
you're going either.
You know, we're
not kids anymore,
so you gotta be more
responsible, all right?
Yeah, you're right, sorry.
[MIZUKI] I'm just kidding.
I'm glad you're safe.
You really scared me.
Mizuki...
I'm just happy to see you again.
I was afraid you weren't
coming back.
It's okay.
Remember what I said? No matter
what, I'll always protect you.
Sho, I'll be okay now.
I think I'm ready.
No matter what happens,
I won't run away.
Because I know that I'm a
part of all this too.
Wherever you guys go,
that's where I belong.
Okay?
Good morning, Sho!
Hi, g..good morning, Mizuki!
Uh, I... I guess you're
hungry, huh?
Yeah...
[MIZUKI] You didn't have
dinner yesterday, did ya?
Well no, not really.
So what do you think...
we should do now?
I mean, I wonder what happened
to Tetsuro and the others?
[SHO] Listen, for now, I think
we should just look for
someplace safe to stay.
Wh..What do you mean by that?
[SHO] Well, I was thinking...
we should try going someplace
where there's a lot of people.
That way... we can
blend in with a crowd,
and maybe find a way to contact
Tetsuro and the others. You
think it would be
safer there?
Yeah, if there's lots of
people around,
then Chronos' agents
probably won't risk
turning into Zoanoids
in the middle of town.
Besides, if we can
blend in with a crowd,
I doubt they'll be
able to find us at all.
You're right.
That was the only idea I
could come up with.
But what should we do now?
I guess we should start walking
till we hit a town.
We can figure out everything
else once we get there.
As long as we keep moving, I
think we should be okay.
[MIZUKI] Sounds good.
[BRESNEL]
We have located
both Sho Fukamachi
and Mizuki Segawa, Sir.
They are both currently
at the 3rd Street shopping
center in downtown Takechiyo.
If they want to
get away from us,
they're going to have to
try harder than that.
Capture them, even if you
have to transform.
But, Sir, are you sure?
[BARCAS] This is an emergency
situation!
In the worst case scenario, we
can just seal off the town.
We can't let the Guyver
get away!
Understood.
What's wrong?
Mizuki...
Run!
[MIZUKI] Wh..What?!
What's going on?
[dog barking]
[Bresnel roars]
No way!
[Bresnel growls threateningly]
Damn! I didn't think they would
transform in the middle of town!
[Bresnel roars]
[Bresnel roars &amp; growls]
Oh no!
[Bresnel continues growling]
[SHO] Guyver!
What's wrong?
Did a gas line blow?
[dog barking]
[Bresnel growls in surprise]
[COMMUNICATIONS] He bioboosted!
Sho Fukamachi's recovered, Sir!
He's able to transform into
the Guyver I again!
[ZX-TOLE] Doctor! We can
take care of this.
Just give us the order
to move out.
[BARCAS] No, you'll stand by
and await orders.
Remember, we still have
Aptom to consider.
I think I see a way clear
to remedy this situation without
you having to get involved.
[Bresnel roars]
[Bresnel's death rattle]
[second Bresnel roars]
What the...
what the hell is that?!
[second Bresnel growls]
Oh please...
I get it.
He's holding back because
he doesn't want any of the
townspeople to get involved.
We'd better come up with
a new plan, fast...
[WOMAN] Honey, there's something
terrible going on out here!
Shouldn't we call the police!
[heavy breathing and slobbering]
[WOMAN]
Hey, are you listening to me?
[beastial growling]
[WOMAN] What's gotten into you?
Get a hold of yourself!
[transformation roar]
[woman screams]
[Ramotith growling]
[transformation growl]
Minoru!
[rampant growling &amp;
transformations]
[Zoanoid transformations
continue]
Everyone in this town
is a Zoanoid?
That's terrible...
[Zoanoids hissing &amp; growling]
[Ramotith roars]
[MIZUKI] I see, he can't fight.
No, of course not.
He can't hurt these people!
Because they're just like...
[LITTLE GIRL] Daddy?
[man grunts in pain]
[dog barking]
[LITTLE GIRL] Hey, what's wrong?
Does your tummy hurt?
Do you need to go to
the doctor, Daddy?
Where does it hurt?
Can I kiss it and
make it better?
[low growling &amp; gurgling]
[dog continues to bark]
[transformation roar]
Dad..dy?
[begins to sob loudly]
[Zoanoids growling &amp; hissing]
[SHO] I can't do it.
I can't fight them.
It's all right, I understand.
But now what?
[SHO] Right now, all we can do
is try to get out of here.
All right, Mizuki,
hold on tight!
[MIZUKI] Right!
[Zoanoids roar &amp; growl]
What's wrong? Why is the
whole town like this?
[SHO] They were probably
captured and converted
into Zoanoids without
even knowing.
A Zoalord must have
used thought waves
to force them to transform.
Now, they have no choice but to
fight to the death.
How could they?
It's just like with your...
[SHO] Yeah, it's just like
what happened to my dad.
I'm sorry...
[SHO] Mizuki, grab on!
[Mizuki screams]
[Zoanoids growl]
[SHO] Looks like
taking the high ground
is dangerous too.
They have all the
bases covered.
[Zoanoids growling]
[SHO] Hold on just a little
bit longer.
We'll be outside of town in
just a minute, all right?
We should be safe now that we're
away from all the people.
[Gergole laughs arrogantly]
We've got you now, Fukamachi!
[Zoanoids growling &amp; hissing]
[SHO] An ambush...
[GERGOLE]
Now, come along with us,
WITHOUT the Guyver
activated of course.
You don't think you
can win do you?
And even if you could,
you'd have to slaughter
every last one of us.
You wouldn't want to kill
all these poor,
innocent townspeople!
[SHO] I... I can't...
What's wrong?
[GERGOLE] Give it up, boy!
You can't fight, you can't win
and you can't escape!
[Gregole laughs arrogantly]
[MAKISHIMA] I can't speak
for Fukamachi...
[Gregole continues to laugh...]
[but is cut off in mid-chortle]
...but I'll slaughter every
last one of you.
[RAMOTITH] G..Guyver III?!
[SHO] Makishima!
[MAKISHIMA] Stand back.
[GREGOLE] Retreat!
[SHO] Makishima, no!
[SHO] How could you do
that to them?
[MAKISHIMA] Once Zoanoids
like them transform,
they can't return to
their human bodies.
Those people were trapped
in a living Hell.
I saved them in the
only way I could.
I gave them a quick,
painless death.
Don't tell me, after all this,
you were going to let Mizuki
fall into their hands
over some petty sympathy!
[SHO] I... I just...
[MAKISHIMA] We'd better hurry.
If we stay here too long,
they'll send reinforcements.
Come on, Segawa and the
others are waiting.
Makishima, wait, you mean
Tetsuro and the others
are all right?
[MAKISHIMA] Don't worry.
Everyone's alive and well.
[SHO] They're all... okay?
[MAKISHIMA] Believe it or not,
we found a place to take refuge.
It's only temporary,
but everyone's
waiting for you there.
[SHO] What? Where are they?
[MAKISHIMA] (chuckles) I'll tell
you, but you'll be surprised.
They're all inside
Mount Minakami.
On the lowest level, hidden
within Relic's Point.
[NARRATOR] Journeying to the
deepest depths of Relic's Point,
Mizuki and Sho are finally
reunited with their comrades.
Aided by the research associates
of Professor Yamamura,
they are offered a temporary
haven from their adversaries.
Then, as Guyot makes
an unexpected visit
to the bottom floor,
a mysterious power echoes
through the ancient ruins.
The Creators' legacy awakens.
Next time: "Vibrations"