[SHO] Tetsuro...
Our town, it's...
Yeah...
[gasps]
Wh-What's wrong, Tetsuro?
It's Mizuki!
[GUYOT] It would seem that
Panadyne has failed us.
[MAKISHIMA] Should we send in
more Zoanoids to handle this?
Or perhaps this situation calls
for the Lost Numbers.
[GUYOT] Hmmm... That's an
interesting proposal.
It's difficult.
If we continue to haphazardly
toss out Zoanoids as
we've been doing,
we'll only be wasting
our resources.
I agree. The Guyver's combat
abilities seem great enough
to decimate an entire
legion of Zoanoids.
Even all the Zoanoids in Japan
might not prove to be enough.
Well, what can I say?
It's a powerful weapon.
It's turned a mere child into
a virtual killing machine.
Remarkable, isn't it?
He's had no military training
or prior combat experience,
and yet he can
surpass some of our
most formidable
hyper-Zoanoids.
[laughs]
However, one thing still
bothers me.
That Sho boy, I can't get
inside his head.
Agito, I'd like to hear your
opinion on the issue.
Why does he do it?
Why does he insist on
defying us at every turn?
Be as candid as you like.
After all, the two of you
are friends, aren't you?
Well... It must be his
emotional makeup.
For example, he shows a
very powerful attachment
towards daily life.
Daily life?
I don't quite understand.
Actually, I believe you
said it best yourself.
Sho Fukamachi is a "mere child."
He's just a nobody.
His unextraordinary nature is
precisely why he clings to that
which ordinary people cherish.
Things like a peaceful,
mundane life shared
with friends and family.
When we of Chronos threaten
that sheltered existence,
he bares his fangs,
and lashes out.
How very human of him.
It's human to a fault.
Agito, I want you to
round up everyone
who has anything to do
with the Guyver I.
We're going to do everything
possible to utterly destroy
this "everyday life" he clings
so desperately to!
[MAKISHIMA] Yes, Sir.
[cars passing,
sirens in the distance]
[Recording]
We're sorry,
but the cellular caller
you are trying to reach
is either unavailable or outside
of the service
area at this time.
Sho...
[MAKISHIMA]
Your target is Fumio Fukamachi.
Age 47, father of Sho Fukamachi.
It's assumed that the Guyver I
will attempt to interfere
with this mission.
That's right, you should avoid
engagement at all costs.
[MAKISHIMA]
It is of the utmost importance
that Fumio Fukamachi
be taken unharmed.
Understood?
[MAKISHIMA] This is all coming
together quite well.
If I want to make use
of Guyver I's power,
it's necessary for Chronos to
target Fukamachi's loved ones.
However, if I want this to
play out right,
I can't have someone like
Guyot interfering.
I'm taking him out!
[MAKISHIMA] Your time is up
Richard Guyot. Prepare to die.
What the hell? Guyver III?
[both men straining &amp; grunting]
[GUYOT] Damn it, Dyme! What the
hell have you been doing?!
How could you just let
Guyver III waltz in here
without even noticing?!
[APTOM] Something's wrong...
Commander Guyot! I've been
here with him all night,
and I assure you Dyme
hasn't let anyone inside.
[GUYOT] What?!
[MAKISHIMA]
I'll crush you like an insect!
[MAKISHIMA] I don't believe it.
How can he keep this up?
Does this mean he has strength
comparable to a Guyver?
Guyot, you bastard,
what the hell are you?
[GUYOT] Calling yourself "Zeus"
seems presumptuous
when you don't
even have the power
to overthrow your
father, Chronos!
Commander!
[DYME] That burns!
Are you all right, Dyme?
[APTOM]
You're gonna pay, wiseguy!
[MAKISHIMA] Damn it,
with the Lost Numbers here
I might be at a serious
disadvantage.
I still don't know the extent
of their powers.
Guyot! I'll let
you live for now,
but you haven't seen
the last of me!
Get back here!
Where'd he go?
[MAKISHIMA] What's going on?
[SOMLUM] Master Agito!
We were just attacked!
You all right?
[APTOM] Let's go!
We can't let him escape!
No, don't bother.
[APTOM] But, Sir...
Let him go for now.
[GUYOT]
It's fine.
After all, we can always
catch him later.
[phone ringing]
[TETSURO] Hello? Ah, yes,
Sir, he's just fine.
Yeah, he's right here with me.
Sure. I'll put him on.
Hold on a sec.
Sho, it's your dad.
Hello, Dad? It's me.
[FUMIO] Oh, Sho, thank God
you're okay.
I was worried about you.
Nothing bad happened, did it?
Well, I, uh...
I got worried 'cause
I couldn't get a hold of
you on your cell phone.
I'm sure glad you're all right.
[SHO] Dad...
I'm sorry, but...
the thing is, our house...
What? Sho, you're starting
to break up.
It's a weak signal or something.
Well, anyway I'm just glad to
hear that you're safe.
[SQUAD LEADER] Target in sight.
We will proceed to contain him.
Hey, Sho, right now I'm
waiting at the bus stop
in front of the subway.
I should be...
[SHO] Hello? Dad?
I can't hear you.
Is something wrong?
Dad!
[FUMIO] Wait, what are you
doing? No, stop! Stay a...
Hello? What's wrong?
Hello?!
Hey, did something bad
happen to your dad?
Sho...
[SHO] Tetsuro, I...
I'll be right back.
I understand.
Mizuki...
[MIZUKI] Yeah?
Guyver!
Sho...
You promised, remember?
You said when the time was
right, you'd tell me everything.
Yeah...
Tetsuro, I think I
deserve to know.
Yeah, you're right.
[SHO] This is Dad's briefcase!
[electronic scanning noises]
[city noises]
[FUMIO's VOICE] Stop!
What are you doing?!
Let me go! Who are you?
Where are you taking me?
Let go of me right now!
[SHO] Dad!
That way!
[MAKISHIMA] What? You think that
whoever has the Guyver III
is a member of Chronos that's
targeting us from the inside?
[GUYOT] Well, if it's so, then
it'd explain how he appeared
at the Japanese headquarters
and activated the
self-destruct code.
The answer seems obvious,
don't you think?
[MAKISHIMA]
It certainly does.
Commander, it's too
dangerous here.
For now I believe
it would be best
if you came along with us
back to Relic's Point.
Really? You think?
Our encounter today should
have made it painfully clear
that he's the one in danger.
Right now, I'm sure that
he's aware that his betrayal
may result in deadly
consequences. Right?
[MAKISHIMA] At this point,
there's no doubt in my mind
that Guyot suspects me
as the Guyver III.
But what is he getting at?
What's the point of this farce?
But why not pursue him? Even if
he is aware of your power,
isn't it too great of a risk to
allow him to go free like this?
Judging by his previous actions,
he'll likely stop at nothing,
Commander, to kill you.
[GUYOT]
I'd like to see him try.
If that fool's willing
to go all out against us,
we'll make him regret it.
But for now, let's just sit back
and watch the show, shall we?
[phone rings]
Excuse me... Hello?
[SQUAD LEADER] This is Team
Bravo. We need reinforcements.
Now!
[tires squealing]
[MAKASHIMA] What's going on?!
[SQUAD LEADER] We're being
pursued by the Guyver I!
Requesting reinforcements
as soon as possible!
At this rate, we'll all be ki...
[screams]
That was the unit I dispatched
to capture Fumio Fukamachi.
They're being assaulted
by the Guyver I,
so I highly doubt they'll be
able to hold out much longer.
I don't suppose that should
come as much of a surprise,
should it?
I'll take a team of Zoanoids
and head to the
scene right away.
[APTOM] Just a moment, Sir.
With all due respect...
you're still only a humanoid,
Master Agito.
If we send you with a team of
Japanese Branch Zoanoids,
the results won't be good.
Commander, we're far better
suited to deal with the Guyver.
Why don't you let us
handle this instead?
Very well, feel free
to show the Guyver I
the full power of the
Lost Number Commandos.
Sir!
Agito, proceed with the plan to
destroy Fukamachi's way of life.
Do whatever you can
to break him down.
Sir.
[MIZUKI]
So that's how it is, huh?
You're surprised, aren't you?
Of course I'm surprised.
[TETSURO] I, uh...
I mean, I'm surprised, but...
This situation is
pretty extreme.
The truth is, I'm really just
feeling sort of overwhelmed.
You know?
[TETSURO] Overwhelmed?
Is that all?
What's wrong with that?
Just because I'm
not freaking out
doesn't mean I'm not worried.
Sorry.
[MIZUKI] Tetsuro...
I wish you would have told
me all this sooner.
Sho's been risking his
life to protect us,
and I didn't even know!
Yeah...
It's just...
The thing is...
Sho didn't want you to find out.
More than anybody else,
he didn't want you to
know about him.
[TETSURO] Well, you know,
he's got a pretty
big crush on you.
And I don't wanna hear you tell
me you didn't know either!
I never saw him like that.
I mean, we've been
friends for so long,
I never even thought about it.
I know it's a bad time,
but I wanted you to have
at least some idea
of how Sho felt too.
Take them away.
[APTOM] There he is.
Are you two sure? I hope we're
not making a big mistake.
I can't... take it.
[screams]
The heat... the pain...
No! No more experiments!
[Somlum screams]
He's right. I don't think we can
take this crap much longer.
I've had enough of them
screwing around with me
day in and day out, like I'm
some kind of lab rat. It's sick.
[Aptom screams]
All of this because our
optimizations failed.
We have to suffer because they
made us into freaks of nature
and can't replicate our forms.
Those bastards have never
given us the same treatment
as other Zoanoids.
There's no guarantee
that we'll survive
the fight with the Guyver.
Are you both prepared for that?
We're willing to take
that risk. Right?
[APTOM] This is our chance.
If we can defeat the Guyver,
then Commander Guyot will
recognize our abilities.
We'll finally get the respect we
deserve. Then finally,
we'll be able to leave all of
this pain and disgrace behind!
Let's do this.
[transformation growls]
[SHO] Damn it! I don't know
how to handle this.
If I take out the driver,
I might end up hurting Dad.
[SHO] What's going on?
[DYME] [chuckles] I gotcha.
[SHO] Is this another kind
of Zoanoid?
[APTOM] Surprised?
By liquefying his body,
he can combine with
the earth around him
and manipulate the battlefield
to give his allies a
decisive edge in combat.
Only Dyme is capable
of such power!
[SHO] What?!
Now you're facing the
Lost Numbers, Guyver.
It's a whole new game.
[SHO] It can't be!
Another Guyver?!
[SHO] So that means...
there were four?
[APTOM] Not a bad likeness,
don't you think, Guyver I?
[MURAKAMI] Two Guyvers are
fighting each other?
[APTOM] I think I know just
what to do with you.
I'm gonna let you see what
it feels like to be torn apart
by your high
frequency arm blades.
Just like all the Zoanoids
you've murdered!
DIE!
[Murakami gasps]
[APTOM] Shit! Somlum!
[SHO] Wh..What is this stuff?
I can't move my arms!
[SOMLUM] As you can see,
my saliva bonds
and assimilates with
organic tissue.
Once it hardens
and forms itself,
you won't be able
to move at all!
It's no use, give it up, kid!
By this point, that stuff might
as well be part of your body.
If you keep
struggling like that,
you're going to rip
your own arms off!
You get it?
[Sho] Damn it...
What'll I do now?
[DYME] This is our fight.
I won't allow you to interfere.
[Aptom laughs]
[APTOM] Let's see you get out
of this one, Guyver I.
Easy now. Let's not do anything
rash. Someone might get hurt.
[Murakami screams]
[APTOM] At my command, Dyme
can crush your little friend
to pieces and dissolve
his bones to dust!
[SHO] Cowards!
[APTOM] Call us
whatever you want!
[MURAKAMI]
No good. I've gotta think.
[APTOM] Let's see, how about I
take off that head of yours?
[laughs]
Guyver, listen up!
Don't let him intimidate you!
I don't care how
powerful Chronos is
they still can't control
the bio armor!
He may look like a Guyver, and
he may have the same weapons,
but he's nothing but
a cheap imitation!
[SHO] He's right! He doesn't
have the control metal!
Now I get it. They tried
to disable my attacks,
because they're
afraid I'm stronger.
[APTOM] So you finally figured
it out, huh?
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but it doesn't matter if
I'm a Guyver or not!
With Somlum and Dyme
disarming your weapons,
you're no match for us at all!!
[MURAKAMI] I have no choice...
[GUYOT'S VOICE] Dyme!
Release them, immediately!
[DYME] Commander Guyot?
[GUYOT'S VOICE] Release them!
[APTOM] Now die!
What?!
[APTOM] Dyme! What happened?!
What, are you gonna tear the
flesh off your own arms?
You're a bigger fool
than I thought!
[SHO] I have to...
If I'm...
If I'm defeated here, then who's
gonna save my father?!
[Sho strains &amp; moans]
[SHO] I can't give up!
Because, if I lose to you...
Then who's gonna protect
my friends?!
[growls]
[SHO] You don't understand.
This is all I have!
My fight is a fight I can't
afford to lose!
[SOMLUM] Aptom!
[Somlum roars in death]
[APTOM] Somlum!
Dyme! You idiot! Why the hell
did you let them go?!
[DYME] No, w..wait!
This is all wrong!
I was... [screams]
[APTOM] Dyme!
Dyme, no!
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you! [yells]
Damn it...
[GUYOT]
We have secured Fumio Fukamachi
and the Segawa siblings.
The operation is a success.
Withdraw immediately.
[APTOM] But, Commander!
I can't turn my back now,
after he's slaughtered my...
[GUYOT] I said withdraw!
[APTOM] Somlum... Dyme...
Forgive me.
This isn't over yet.
I swear... I swear I'll
avenge you, no matter what!
[APTOM] You may have
defeated my men,
but you fell right
into our trap!
We've captured your father
and the Segawas.
So our mission was a
success in spite of you!
[SHO] What did you say?
[SHO] So it wasn't just Dad,
those bastards went after
Mizuki and Tetsuro too?!
[SHO] Damn it!
Dad...
Tetsuro...
Mizuki...
Now they're all gonna die!
This is all my fault!
If I had known it would
turn out like this,
I wouldn't have taken it this
far! I should have given up!
After all this, is that
really how you feel?
Come on, Sho. Stand up.
[SHO] Who are you?
How do you know my name?
[NARRATOR] Hidden beneath
an age-old mountain,
Sho's family and friends
are torn away from him
by Chronos' wicked plans.
As he races to their side,
Makishima bares his fangs at
his father's organization
and begins a fierce battle with
five elite hyper-Zoanoids.
Looming in their shadow is
a mysterious old man,
grinning strangely.
Next time:
"Relic's Point"