[SHO]
What the hell happened here?
Sho!
It's Guyot!
So Guyot was the one who
caused all of this?
Hey! I don't see our friends!
What do you think
happened to them?
Come on, don't look so...
I mean, they must have
gotten away, right?
Shhh!
[MIZUKI] What is it?!
[SHO] It's Chronos.
[SOLDIER]
Take your squadron
and scan the following
sectors: G... A...
[Zoanoids growling and hissing]
[DERZERB] This seems like a
waste of time to me.
I doubt there's anyone
that could survive Commander
Guyot's gravity attack.
Remember our enemies are
the Guyver III and that
proto-Zoalord.
We shouldn't underestimate them.
That reminds me, I thought one
of the Lost Numbers
was supposed to be monitering
the situation.
Shouldn't he be around
here somewhere?
You mean that Aptom guy?
That prick's always acting like
he's too good to work with us.
Oh well, his loss.
[ZX-TOLE]
I don't see why Dr. Barcas
keeps that piece of crap around.
He's not even an Adaption
Number Zoanoid.
You'd think somebody would just
throw him away
after he's failed to optimize
so many times.
Maybe Barcas just feels sorry
for him, or something.
[ELEGEN] Well, at least he makes
a good guinea pig, right?
That's probably enough reason to
keep him around
till all the experimentation
kills him.
DERZERB] Oh, I get it. So the
doctor's just letting him live
so he can play around with him.
[BRESNEL] Hey, did you hear?
The report says that Sho
kid can't transform
into the Guyver anymore.
That's gonna make our job a
hell of a lot easier!
[RAZELL] No kidding.
Plus, Commander Guyot went ahead
finished off the Guyver III
and that proto-Zoalord for us.
Good thing too I was afraid
we were gonna get torn in half
or blown up or something.
[SHO] So Guyot got to them.
I was afraid of this.
If nothing else, I have
to protect Mizuki.
[RAZELL] Huh? I found them!
Over there!
[Zoanoids growling]
Stand back.
GUYVER!
Oh, no...
[RAZELL] Look at him
trying to scare us!
[BRESNEL] See, I told you!
He can't turn in the Guyver
anymore! He's nothing now!
[SHO] What's wrong? Why
can't I bioboost?
[EURENORM] Give it up, kid.
You're finished!
[GUYVER III] If you want them,
you have to go through me first.
Sho, is that...
[SHO] It can't be, but...
No way...
[RAMOTITH] Guyver III?!
[BRESNEL]
But that's impossible!
He should have been destroyed
by Commander Guyot's
gravity attack!
[GUYVER III] We'll all be in
trouble
if those four
hyper-Zoanoids show up.
Get out of here, now.
Makishima?
[GUYVER III] I said, go!
[SHO] Uh, right!
[GUYVER III] You're not laying a
finger on Sho Fukamachi.
[RAMOTITH] Oh, yeah?!
[GUYVER III] [chuckles]
Because he's MY prey!
[GUYOT] I've eliminated every
one of my obstacles.
Now, if I could only find
a way
to recapture Sho's
Guyver unit...
[DOCTOR] Commander, Doctor
Barcas is here to see you.
You're in much better shape
than I expected, Richard.
It was rather reckless for a
Zoalord like yourself
to put his life on the line,
especially without a plan,
or proper backup.
That so-called "recklessness"
enabled me to destroy
both the test subject and his
traitorous little friend.
[BARCAS] Ah yes, funny that
you should mention Guyver III.
We just recieved word that
Guyver III destroyed
several members of our
reconaissance team.
What'd you say?!
[GUYOT]
That little bastard SURVIVED!
[MIZUKI] Well, I'm glad.
At least, we know Makishima
is all right.
[SHO] Yeah, that's true.
Hey, we should be safe as long
as we hide in here, right?
Yeah...
[SHO] Was that really Makishima?
Maybe it was just
my imagination,
but something seemed
different about him.
[MIZUKI] Hey, Sho?
Since Makishima made it out
okay, then that means Tetsuro...
Well, uh, what I mean is,
everyone should be
okay too, right?
Yeah! After all, they had
Murakami to protect them.
I'm sure they made it out fine.
[SHO] We may be safe for now,
but if Chronos finds us,
we'll be in bad shape.
Until I can find a way
to bioboost,
I can't protect Mizuki.
Mizuki?
Uh... hmmm?
[SHO] Could you help me
out for a second?
I'm trying to get back my
ability to turn into the Guyver.
That's fine, but what are
we supposed to do?
[SHO] That's what we need
to figure out.
Hey, uh, Sho, what are those?!
[SHO] There are these little
growths
that call the Guyver out from
another dimension.
I should have them on my upper
back. are they still there?
You mean these things that
look like scars?
[SHO] Yeah, I'm glad I
still have them.
So, even if I can't bioboost, at
least that means
I haven't been separated
from the Guyver.
[MIZUKI] Okay, whatever! I saw
the scars already.
Now, put your shirt back on!
[SHO] Oh, uh, sorry!
[SHO] I didn't think that was
the problem,
but I can't figure
out what's wrong.
There must be some reason why
I can't bioboost.
[MIZUKI] Hmm...
Well, I-uh, don't know much
about this stuff,
but when did you stop being able
to transform into the Guyver?
Umm, it started when that
white Zoanoid was attacking me.
As soon as I saw it,
everything just stopped.
I've never been just,
seperated from the Guyver
like that before.
[MIZUKI] Then, you think that
white Zoanoid caused it?
Yeah, but it's weird. I felt
like I'd seen one before.
Let's see. I think that
kind was called...
Enzyme II, or something.
What did you say?! There's
something about that name...
Is something the matter?
It's just, I've heard that
name before, but I can't...
[MIZUKI] You can t what?
[SHO] I can't figure out what
Enzyme has to do with me
being unable to transform.
[MIZUKI] Sho, listen. You did go
to Mount Minakami, right?
To rescue your, ah,
Dad from Chronos.
You're right!
I remember now! I went to Mount
Minakami to rescue my dad.
[SHO] But then something
happened.
[retching sounds]
That's enough, okay!
Just calm down and stop thinking
about it! Sho!
No, it's not that I had
forgotten about it,
it's that I was blocking
it out for some reason.
I've got to remember, what the
hell happened back there?
[APTOM] I might be able to
help you with that.
Makishima, you found us!
[SHO] No! Get back Mizuki,
that's not Makishima!
[Aptom laughs]
Very good, sharp eye, kid,
but the charade's over.
You're that same zoaniod!
Oh, so you do remember?
Yes, I'm Aptom of the Lost
Number Commandos.
The last time we met, I
fought beside my comrades,
Somlum and Dyme.
[SHO] Then why did you save us
from those Zoanoids back there?
[APTOM] Don't make me laugh. You
haven't been saved at all!
I just didn't want
to lose my prey
to a bunch of useless weaklings.
The hunt is still on.
[SHO] The hunt?!
[APTOM] That's right. I am the
hunter and you are my prey.
I've come here to avenge
Somlum and Dyme!
I had no choice but
to kill them.
[APTOM] Oh, I almost forgot.
I suppose I should tell you what
happened
between you and your father,
shouldn't I?
It happened on Mount Minakami,
and it was so traumatic that
it made you lose your ability
to bioboost.
Ha! You know, I don't have to
tell you any of this.
I could snap your puny little
neck
before you even
knew what hit you.
But, no! Then my revenge
would be meaningless!
Now, don't you get it? It's not
just you,
but the Guyver I that
I have to crush,
torment and drive
to the depths of Hell!
Only THEN will I be satisfied!
But since you still don't
remember anything,
it must be buried pretty deep.
I imagine when it finally DOES
come back to you,
you'll go out of your mind!
Please, leave him alone! None
of this is his fault!
Hasn't he suffered
enough already?!
[SHO] It's all right.
I want to be able to transform
into the Guyver,
because I have to
protect you, Mizuki!
Such commendable resolve.
If you think you can handle
the truth, I'll tell you!
You killed your father, with
your own two hands!
I killed him? I killed my
father?
No, you're lying! You're lying!
[APTOM] After the five
elites took your father
back to Relic's Point,
Dr. Barcus transformed him into
the test version of the
Zoanoid Enzyme II.
Of course, when you came to
rescue him,
you weren't aware, so
when he transformed,
he was able to split your
head wide open.
Touching, isn't it?
Reunited at last,
a father and son that can't wait
to bash each other's brains out!
That can't be. Sho's Dad would
never do that to him.
[APTOM] After your brain had
been pulverized,
you lost control of the Guyver
and it was forced to enter its
emergency self-defense
mode to survive.
You mean, after I lost
consciousness,
then... the Guyver...
You guessed it!
[Sho screams in anguish]
[SHO] That was his arm... That
was Dad's arm!
I... I killed him.
I killed my own father... [sobs]
Oh, God...
That's right! Aren't you proud
of what you've done?
You murdered your father with
the power of the Guyver,
just like you murdered
Somlum and Dyme!
[MIZUKI] Please, he doesn't
deserve this.
So now do you
finally understand?
This is why you haven't been
able to transform!
Because you hate the Guyver!
You hate it for killing your
father,
and you hate yourself
for using it!
You were afraid to admit it,
but it's all been stewing
deep inside.
You couldn't transform anymore
because of your own
self-loathing!
[Sho grunts in pain]
[Mizuki screams] Sho!
[APTOM] You have no one to
blame but yourself.
When you became the Guyver,
you brought pain and suffering
to everyone you know.
My father died because
of the Guyver...
Because of me everyone will...
will be killed, all because...
Now, you get it. Your father
died because of you.
You got your friends involved in
this
and they ended up dead at the
hands of Guyot.
So who's next? When will it end?
None of this would
have happened!
None of them would have been
killed
if you had never
become the Guyver,
if you had never activated
the unit!
It's not your fault!
[APTOM] Let's see...
[SHO] Mizuki!
[APTOM] Are you going to cause
her death too?
[MIZUKI] Let me go!
Mizuki!
Sho, are you okay?!
You bastard, let her go.
Mizuki has nothing
to do with this.
[APTOM] [laughs] Look at you!
You're pathetic!
Do you expect me to listen
to your whimpering?
Maybe you forgot, I said I
wouldn't be satisfied
until I made you suffer!
[MIZUKI] SHO!
How can you do this to him?!
None of this would have happened
if you just left Sho alone!
You're the ones who forced
him to kill his father!
He never wanted to become the
Guyver in the first place!
He never wanted
to hurt anyone!
I don't know what happened
between Sho and those
friends of yours,
but I know he isn't the one
who started all of this!
Can't you see he hasn't
done anything wrong?!
Shut up, you stupid bitch!
[APTOM] Sho! Look at me!
[SHO] Enzyme II!
[APTOM] Come on, boy. Let's see
you bioboost!
What's the matter?
Are you scared?
I thought you said you were
going to become the Guyver
so you could protect this girl!
G..Guyver!
[MIZUKI] Didn't work...
[APTOM] If you're going to
transform, you better hurry!
Because if you take too long,
I might just cut this poor
little girl to PIECES!
[Mizuki screams]
Leave her alone!
Sho! Please don't die!
[APTOM] You heard me, you
little shit! I said bioboost!
I'm not screwing around!
Mizuki...
Oh, Sho...
[APTOM]
This is your last chance.
You can sit there and watch me
tear her apart,
or you can roll over and
bleed to death.
But either way,
you're both as good as dead
if you don't transform!
So, come on Fukamachi!
What's it gonna be?
[SHO] Power... I need power...
enough to save Mizuki.
I want the Guyver's power!
[FUMIO] Sho...
I understand.
[APTOM] Come on Sho! Bioboost!
Become the Guyver!
Embrace your hatred!
GUYVER!
YES! THAT'S IT!
You're okay!
[SHO] If the Guyver has caused
these problems,
then the Guyver
will settle them!
Now, it's just you and me! Let's
go, Aptom! Come and get me!
[APTOM] Running already?
[MIZUKI] Even after all that,
he became the Guyver.
He did it... for me.
[MIZUKI]
He wanted to protect me.
Oh, Sho...
[APTOM] Get back here!
[SHO] Just like before!
[APTOM] Surprised? Now that I've
been reoptimized,
I can mimic far more
than appearances!
[SHO] A Gregole?!
[APTOM] With only a small cell
sample, I can self-optimize
into any Zoanoid type!
Possess any Zoanoid Power!
[Sho grunts in pain]
[Aptom laughs]
[SHO] Vamore!
Too powerful...
[APTOM] Nice dodge. You've
improved.
But I wouldn't have it
any other way!
If I was able to finish
you off that easily,
then I'd be disappointed!
After all, I won't be able to
avenge Somlum and Dyme
unless I can really
make you suffer!
You know, we Lost Numbers were
just outcasts at Chronos.
Those twisted bastards only kept
us alive
to use us as human guinea pigs!
We had not only lost our pride
as Zoanoids,
but were robbed of our
human dignity!
Our only consolation was the
bond we shared through the
terrible circumstances that
brought us together!
And then you... you crushed my
friends
as if they were worms
beneath your feet!
[SHO] Is that why you went
against Chronos' orders
and let Mizuki and me escape?
Because you wanted to kill me
yourself?
Because you wanted to avenge
your comrades?
[Sho screams in pain]
[APTOM] Oh, you protected your
mega-smasher, huh?
Nice try, but with your arms
like that,
I'd like to see you
try and use it!
It's over, you're finished!
[ZX-TOLE] You said Guyver I
showed up?
I thought the report said it
was Guyver III.
It's definitely Guyver I, Sir.
At present, he's engaged
in combat with a Zoanoid.
There's only one, but somehow
it's overpowering him!
A single Zoanoid beating the
Guyver?! That's absurd!
What type is it?
What? You don't know?!
To tell the truth, Sir, I've
never seen this type before.
[APTOM] Huh?
[SOLDIER] Present location is...
[Aptom roars]
[Soldier cries out and dies]
[APTOM] Damn it! Now it's only a
matter of time
before those four elites
find their way here.
I don't know what you think
you're trying to pull,
but I m running out of time.
So die, Guyver!
[SHO] C'mon Smasher... OPEN!
[APTOM]
His armor, it opened on its own!
[Aptom roars in pain]
[ELEGEN] What the hell was that?
[ZX-TOLE] Move out!
[OTHERS] Right!
[SHO] I'm sorry, Dad. I won't
run away any more.
I promise I'll never forget
your sacrifice.
And I'll take responsibility
for getting everyone wrapped
up in this mess.
I will fight this fate to the
bitter end,
together with this Guyver.
So please, watch over me,
Dad, together with Mom.
[Aptom chuckles]
How interesting,
that was a nice move,
but it looks like this body of
mine isn't ready to give up yet!
[NARRATOR]
A terrifying evolution leads to
the birth of a horrifying
new "Battle Creature."
Underestimating his
own creation,
Dr. Barcas unwittingly paves the
way for Aptom's rampage.
Meanwhile, Sho and Mizuki
retreat to a nearby village,
in an attempt to escape
from Chronos' overwhelming
sphere of influence.
Next time:
"Nightmarish Encirclement"