[SHO] Hello? Dad?
I can't hear you.
Is something wrong?
[FUMIO] Wait,
what are you doing?
No, stop!
Take them away.
[GUYOT'S VOICE] Dyme!
Release them, immediately!
[DYME] Commander Guyot?
[GUYOT'S VOICE] Release them!
[APTOM] Now die!
What?!
[APTOM] Damn it!
[GUYOT] We have secured
Fumio Fukamachi and
the Segawa siblings.
The operation is a success.
Withdraw immediately.
[APTOM] But, Commander!
I can't turn my back now,
after he's slaughtered my...
[GUYOT] I said withdraw!
[SHO] Damn it!
Dad...
Tetsuro...
Mizuki...
Now they're all gonna die!
This is all my fault!
If I had known it would
turn out like this,
I wouldn't have
taken it this far!
I should have given up!
After all this, is that
really how you feel?
Come on, Sho.
Stand up.
[SHO] Who are you?
How do you know my name?
[SHO] Masaki Murakami...
I used to be a freelance
journalist.
I got involved with Chronos
when I was covering a
story a while back.
Really? It sounds to me like
you're lucky to still be alive.
I know how you feel, having
your family taken hostage.
However, if they got their hands
on the Guyver units,
it wouldn't just be your friends
and family who would suffer.
I'm afraid the whole of humanity
would be at the
mercy of Chronos.
Yeah, but, the question is,
what am I supposed to do now?
I don't even have a single clue
where the three of them
were taken off to.
[MURAKAMI] That's easy. I think
I know where we can find them.
Without their Japanese Branch,
Chronos is out of options.
Only Mount Minakami remains.
Mount Minakami?
[MURAKAMI] That's right.
[SHO] So you think we'll
find my friends there?
S'what I think.
[SHO] Who is this guy
and why does he know so
much about Chronos?
I don't have much of a choice,
but I hope I can trust
you, Murakami.
[threatening music building]
We should be there in
about an hour.
Try to keep an eye out for
the exit, all right?
So then... what happens
when we get there?
I mean, what's at the mountain?
A place called Relic's Point.
What does that mean?
What's Relic's Point?
An ancient ruin buried
inside the mountains.
The last Chronos base
left in Japan.
A hidden base?
[TETSURO] How did they hide
such a huge structure
inside the mountain?!
[MURAKAMI] There's a
whole ton of legends
surrounding this place.
For example,
some people say that
the legendary cave of "Awa
no Iwato" is hidden inside.
Other people believe that
it's a man-made mountain
constructed in ancient times.
Scholars claim that
the entire structure
is the world's largest
unfinished pyramid.
It was before your time,
but do you know of the
Takeshiro chain of earthquakes?
[SHO] Unh-uh.
[MURAKAMI] They
happened in 1965.
In the area surrounding
Mount Minakami,
there was a series of
apparent earthquakes.
The mountain itself was at the
epicenter of the quakes.
We can only assume that Chronos
went to investigate the area
and happened upon
the ancient ruins
lying dormant deep
within the mountain.
The ruins inside were
still functional
and now Chronos is
using them as a base.
This is nuts!
There's so many! Way more than
before! I don't believe it!
Hey, move it.
[TETSURO] There must be
something really big
going down here.
Murakami, what kind of things
are they doing there?
Mostly bioweapons research.
It's a huge production facility
supposedly built
by the Creators.
Most complete ruins
they left behind.
The whole place had gone
completely untouched for ages.
A living relic from
ancient times.
The Creators' ruins?
But most importantly,
it's the place
where the three Guyver units
were first discovered.
So they were uncovered when
Chronos investigated the ruins?
Then that means Relic's Point
is where it all began.
[SHO] Dad's diary...
[GUARD] Get in.
Hurry up! Move!
Steady, Sir!
[MIZUKI] Mr. Fukamachi!
Hey, don't be so rough!
[FUMIO] Why is this
happening to us?
It's my fault.
I'm the one who started
all this mess, Sir.
I don't understand.
Tetsuro, please...
Would you mind telling me what
the heck's going on here?
[TETSURO] Sure.
[FUMIO'S VOICE] It was my turn
to make breakfast this morning.
I ate it together with Sho.
So go the lives of us two men...
Things don't change much,
but isn't that what
happiness is all about?
I got up and had last
night's leftovers.
Sho forgot it was his
turn to make breakfast,
which is unusual for him.
He had a slight fever, so he
stayed home from school.
I was a little concerned.
I can tell there's something
he wants to talk about,
but I'm ashamed to admit that
I can't find a single word to
say to him at a time like this.
Sho has seemed unusually
depressed for the past few days,
and I'm starting to get
really worried.
It may be that he's just
not feeling well,
but I'm afraid he might
be going through
a more serious problem
that he's not telling me about.
I've wondered if it's
my place as his father
to demand some kind of answer,
but I think it's better
just to trust him.
I'm sure he'll open up and
talk to me some day.
I just have to be patient.
Sho's a strong boy.
For all of his life
he's kept all of his
sad and painful feelings
bottled up inside,
silently enduring them
all alone.
Of course, it's frustrating
for me to know this,
because I want to be able to
comfort him so much.
[SHO] Dad...
I swear I'm gonna save you!
[computer beeping]
[MURAKAMI] Sho, look.
It's Mount Minakami.
So that's it.
Now I understand.
Poor Sho.
I'm really sorry, Sir.
If I hadn't taken him
to the woods that day,
none of this would
have happened!
[FUMIO] No, thank you for
staying with him, Tetsuro.
This must have been horrible
for the both of you.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I couldn't do anything to help.
Don't say that!
There's no way you could have
known what was going on!
It's my fault too for ignoring
Sho's problems for so long.
That's not true. I'm
sure Sho's just happy to
have you guys as
friends these days.
[TETSURO] Thank you...
I just wish I could have
done something for him.
Sho's been fighting for us
all this time, hasn't he?
[TETSURO] Yeah.
[FUMIO] In any case,
I'm just glad the two of
you are all right.
Don't worry about Sho.
I'm sure he'll figure
something out.
Even though we've
all been captured
and locked up in
a place like this,
I feel like there's got to be
something I can do for Sho.
I am his father.
[car door closing]
They're somewhere
in that mountain.
And once we make it in,
we can rescue them, right?
I'll get them out of there.
We're going back together,
no matter what it takes.
Sir!
At ease, You're relieved.
Go take a break.
But, Sir...
It's all right. Go on, I'll take
care of everything here.
Sir!
Makishima?!
[TETSURO] Makishima!
What the hell is going on here?!
Makishima, explain?
I didn't want all of you
to get dragged into this.
But I'm afraid I no longer have
the luxury to make that call.
That's bullshit!
We weren't just "dragged in",
we were kidnapped!
Get a grip, Segawa!
[TETSURO] How the hell
am I supposed to "get a grip"?
[MAKISHIMA] Listen!
Listen.
My real motive here is
the downfall of Chronos.
What? The downfall of Chronos?
[TETSURO] Do you really expect
me to believe that crap?!
Hold on. I'll prove it
to you right now.
Bioboost!
What? You're Guyver III?!
[MAKISHIMA] Stand back.
[P.A.] The Guyver has appeared
in D Block on the second level!
All combat-ready Zoanoids
move to D Block immediately!
[MAKISHIMA] They're sending in
Zoanoids. We have to hurry.
[Makishima attacks]
[GUYOT] I'm ready for you
this time, Guyver III.
[evil laughter]
[MAKISHIMA] This way. Hurry!
[MAKISHIMA] It would be easier
for me to escape on my own,
but the problem is,
if I leave them here,
I won't be able to
manipulate the Guyver I,
and he may prove useful to me.
Guyot, Sir.
I've located the targets.
They're on
the fourth level.
It appears that they've just
breached the outermost zone.
[GUYOT] I see. He's
trying to use Terminal 2
to get back to town.
He must take me for
a fool if he thinks
I'm going to let him escape
on the transport line.
I want you to cut all power
going to Level 4 immediately!
[MAKISHIMA] Wait, stay here.
[Zoanoids growling &amp; hissing]
[MAKISHIMA] Damn it!
It's just one after another.
[power building]
[sudden heartbeat]
[Sho gasps]
What's wrong?
[SHO] It's the Guyver III.
It's close. I can feel it.
[BARCAS] Damn it, Richard.
Can't you even take care
of one little boy?
Do you need me here
to hold your hand?
But then again, I guess
I'd be disappointed too
if I had to come all the
way to Japan for nothing.
Well, I guess you're up next.
[MAKISHIMA] Well, now at
least they won't be able
to pursue us for a while.
Unfortunately, I don't think
we'll be able to
use the terminal.
Almost. He's definitely close.
That's unexpected.
Something must be going
on at Relic's Point.
[TETSURO] Hey, Makishima,
I'm guessing we're still pretty
far underground, right?
What the heck are you
planning to do now?
[MAKISHIMA] Don't worry, Segawa.
Once I find the right place to
break through the ceiling,
we'll come out on the surface.
Makishima?
[MAKISHIMA] Hm?
Are you sure...
you're not taking this too far?
I mean, it might have
been a little rash
to rescue us like that.
[MAKISHIMA] I don't think
it's a problem.
I had planned to make a move
sooner or later, regardless.
Guyot's pretext for calling
me to Relics' Point
was to have me transformed
into a hyper-Zoanoid
in order to fill a role as one
of Chronos' leaders.
Naturally, they would have had
to examine my body first,
and then they would have
discovered that I was a Guyver.
Taking that into consideration,
I'd say that now is as
good a time as ever to act.
Hold on, I've got a question.
If you knew Sho was the Guyver,
why did you keep your identity
hidden from us all this time?
If our goals are the same,
it would've been better
to be on close terms,
in case we had to join forces,
like we're doin' now.
Wouldn't you think?
[MAKISHIMA] As you
know, I've been dealing
with a rather
complicated situation.
It was necessary to
avoid doing anything
that would arouse any suspicion.
And, knowing you were
under their surveillance all
this time, meeting with you
and talking about the
Guyver wasn't possible.
After all, to
deceive one's enemy,
you must first appear
as an ally, right?
I get it. But why
should I believe
you're giving us
the whole story?
Tetsu, stop!
[TETSURO] "Tetsu"?
What happened to "big brother"
or just plain old "Tetsuro"?
[MAKISHIMA]
Don't take another step.
[TETSURO] What's wrong?
[MAKISHIMA] Five, huh?
Stop sneaking around like rats
and show yourselves!
[ZX-TOLE] Well done, Guyver III.
End of the road, pardner.
I'm afraid this tunnel's
gonna be your tomb!
[MAKISHIMA]
Spare me the bravado.
Just hurry up and transform
so we can get this over with.
[Zx-Tole chuckles]
[transformation growls]
Zoanoids!
[Zx-Tole laughs &amp; transforms]
[MAKISHIMA]
You're underestimating me.
No matter how big you talk,
five Zoanoids aren't enough to
defeat a Guyver with my power!
[DERZERB] [chuckles]
Come on, is that all you've got?
[MAKISHIMA] What?!
Makishima!
[TETSURO] Mizuki!
[MAKISHIMA] Proud of your
brute strength, are you?
Well, in that case...
[Derzerb laughs derisively]
[MAKISHIMA]
He absorbed my beam?!
[Derzerb roars &amp; growls]
[MAKISHIMA]
They're all so much stronger!
[GASTER] Fire!
You're finished!
Makishima!
[MAKISHIMA] Bastard...
I'd like to see you
try that again!
[GASTER] That's it!
[Makishima grunts &amp; screams]
Makishima!
[MAKISHIMA] He can make his
projectiles change course?
[Zoanoids chuckling]
[THANCRUS]
Now do you understand?
Don't mistake us for
ordinary Zoanoids.
[MAKISHIMA] Hyper-Zoanoids...
[ELEGNE] We've been optimized
with the latest
technology available.
We outfight anything produced
at the Japanese Branch.
[MAKISHIMA]
A team of Zoanoid elites, huh?
[GUYOT] This is as far as
you go, Guyver III.
Or perhaps I should
call you Zeus?
[MAKISHIMA] Guyot!
[GUYOT] I was foolish.
I should have realized
who you were the moment
you uttered that name
back at the Japanese Branch.
[GUYOT] You bastard!
Who the hell are you?!
[MAKISHIMA] Why don't you
just call me Zeus?
Zeus, son of Chronos
in Greek mythology,
after hiding for many years,
killed his father
to exact revenge
and usurp his throne
as king of the gods.
In our case, that
means a defiant child
raised by our organization,
fueled by hatred and holding
a high enough position to plot
the downfall of Chronos
from the inside out.
That's none other than you!
Agito Makishima!
Only my closest aide
would be so familiar
with the Japanese Branch
to come and go as he saw fit.
Indeed, it's no wonder
that the Guyver III
would suddenly appear
wherever I went.
[MAKISHIMA]
If you knew that much,
then why did you summon me here?
Look what happened
to Relic's Point.
It could have ended up
like the Japanese Branch.
[GUYOT] I may have let you
go too far but...
[BARCAS] It's still much less
risky than letting you run wild.
[laughing] You sound surprised.
Allow me to introduce you
to a colleague of mine.
Like myself, he is one of the
twelve directors of Chronos.
He is also the
greatest scientist
that the world has ever known...
Dr. Hamilcar Barcas!
[MAKISHIMA]
Barcas?! What is he doing here?
Guyver though you may be,
there is still a human body
that constitutes the
core of your being.
You should know that
its supply of energy
is not without its limits!
That foolish little
rampage of yours
has left your body
completely exhausted!
[BARCAS] I myself have
optimized these hyper-Zoanoids
to be the best of the best!
You were never a match for them.
Not at your strongest,
and certainly not now!
[MAKISHIMA] Take this!
[BARCAS]
Now, Zx-Tole, don't hold back.
Show him your true power!
[ZX-TOLE] As you command, Sir.
[sounds of roof collapsing]
[ZX-TOLE] What?
Sho!
[NARRATOR] After the two
Guyvers endure a brutal attack
from the hyper-Zoanoid forces,
Sho's father once again
falls into enemy hands.
Struggling to find refuge,
Sho and his friends meet two of
Makishima's loyal servants.
In a quiet haven in the
woods, the tale of his past
is recounted with
bitterness and sorrow.
Longing for their dreams,
the two Guyvers depart
for battle once again.
Next time:
"To Each His Own Resolution"