[sirens wailing]
SHO!
[a single heartbeat]
[SHO] Mizuki...
[alarms going off]
[BARCAS] What's going on here?
[SOLDIER] Take a look, Sir.
[alarms still going off]
It's the chrysalis! Damn...
[MAKISHIMA] I'm sensing
powerful thoughtwaves.
Is this Fukamachi's
consciousness,
trying to free itself from
the chrysalis?
It's disappearing!
Bioboost!
What the hell?!
[BARCAS] It vanished!
[TV] This evening at
approximately 10:00 pm,
a state of martial law was
announced over Tokyo.
[TETSURO] He fell!
Behind that building, right?
I know a shortcut. Follow me!
The Regulation Bureau
has mobilized
an elite squad of Zoanoids to
suppress the terrorist group,
but as of yet they have been
unable to do their job.
[NATSUKI] Should be right
around here. There we go!
Sho!
What the...
That isn't Fukamachi, is it?
No, it's not. What the hell?
I... I don't know who that is.
[NATSUKI] What is he?
Some kind of Zoanoid?
[TETSURO] I dunno. I've never
seen one like this before.
But whatever he is,
I'm sure he's one of the two
that were fighting in the sky.
[MIZUKI] It's Aptom!
That's Aptom? It's
really him, huh?
[APTOM] Mizuki Segawa!
But why?
What are you doing roaming
around in a place like this?
That Zoanoid really did a
number on you!
What the heck happened?
Who was that?
It doesn't matter! Why do you
care what happens to me?
Get out of here while
you still can!
Think about it!
What happens if Chronos finds
out you're still alive?!
How did you know?
Hey! I remember! You're that...
You're that guy
with the sunglasses
that's always hanging
around the apartment!
Seriously?!
No way, don't tell me...
So, you've been watching over
us this whole time?
Get the hell out of here!
The way I see it, if
Fukamachi is still alive,
he'll come back to you
as soon as he can.
I figured, if I kept an
eye on you guys,
sooner or later I'd run
into him too.
That's the only reason,
all right?
We aren't alone.
Even after all this time, he
believes Sho is alive too.
[APTOM] Listen, no matter what,
I can't have you fall
into Chronos' hands.
If that happens, or worse yet,
if those bastards
finish off the Guyver I,
Then I will... I will have
lost my purpose to live!
Aptom...
Go on and get the hell
out of here!
Stop standing there and
go, all right?!
He could be here any second!
Who will?
It's too late, damn it.
[ZX-TOLE] Well, well, well,
I come to finish off Aptom,
and look who I find!
Haven't seen you two
for a while!
Tetsuro...
You're ZX-Tole, aren't you?
That's right, you were
the leader of the
hyper-Zoanoid five.
[ZX-TOLE]
So you remember me, huh?
Well, don't run off.
I'll deal with you as soon as
I'm finished with him.
[ZX-TOLE] After what you did
to my friends,
you should be grateful to have
such a merciful death.
There's no coming back
this time.
Die, Aptom!
What?
Whoah! What's that?!
[ZX-TOLE] It can't be...
[TV] The inner and outer lanes
of Route 20 extending from
the outskirts of Shinjuku
all the way to Loop 6
have been shut down until
further notice.
Residents are asked to
take refuge in Central Park
or other local
public facilities.
[YOHEI] Is something wrong?
[SHIZU] Grandfather,
it's Master Agito.
[YOHEI] You can tell, can't you?
You two have always
been that way.
[sirens wailing]
[MAKISHIMA] Where am I?
It looks like Shinjuku.
I see, I must have
somehow gotten dragged
into the chrysalis's
teleportation.
We were moving through some
strange subspace,
but I don't know why it took
us here of all places.
Makishima?!
[MAKISHIMA] Segawa?
[TETSURO] I knew it, you were
all right after all!
[MIZUKI] But wait, what about
Sho? Is he with you?
[MAKISHIMA] Actually,
Fukamachi's inside that thing.
But how? I don't get it.
I don't get it either.
Makishima!
What is this weird thing?
What the heck happened to Sho?
[MAKISHIMA] We'll talk later.
Since this bastard doesn't
know when to die,
it looks like I'll have
to show him.
[ZX-TOLE] You've got nothing to
back up that tough talk now.
No matter, I'm actually
happy to see you.
I was hoping you were
still alive.
Now I have a chance to
avenge Thancrus too.
After I destroy you and finish
off what's left of Aptom,
all four of my friends can
finally rest in peace.
I've waited a long time
for this day!
Let's go, Guyver III!
[MAKISHIMA] Come and get me!
[MIZUKI]
Is Sho really inside this thing?
Sho, can you hear me?
If you're in there,
please answer me.
[heartbeats]
I can hear it. I can hear
Sho's heart beating.
[soft heartbeats]
I knew it! It's Master Agito!
He's all right after all!
I'm sorry I ever doubted
you, Agito!
[ZX-Tole growls in frustration]
Stop running and fight
like a man!
[Makishima cries out]
He's stronger than I expected.
It looks like he's got the power
of all five elite
hyper-Zoanoids.
Actually, he may be as strong as
all of them combined.
Look at him, making such an
outrageous spectacle out there.
But since he's the only one
suited to dealing with Aptom,
we can't risk getting involved.
I'm still uneasy about ZX-Tole
becoming a Lost Number.
If he decides to act on his own,
I won't be able to control
him with my thought waves.
In fact, I can't even monitor
his movements anymore.
Who knows what he could
do with that power?
It's entirely possible that
in the process of hunting
down that monster
he could become one himself.
But in ZX-Tole's case,
with the stress of his
rushed optimization,
his body has already
begun to deteriorate
on a cellular level.
Even if he manages
to survive today,
he'll be long dead
before he has the chance
to run amok like Aptom.
Hello, Intelligence Department?
I want to know the
situation at the scene.
Send out scouts immediately.
Yes, Sir!
[ZX-TOLE]
You're not getting away!
[Makishima cries out]
Damn you!
[ZX-TOLE] You're not looking
so hot, Guyver III.
Where's the bravado?
[MAKISHIMA] I need to buy
some time to use my smasher.
I can't believe this.
It looks like even Guyver III
is no match for that thing!
[Aptom falls to the ground]
Here, give me your hand!
[TETSURO] Aptom?
[APTOM] That guy's just
too damn strong.
I hate to say it, but he even
gives me the chills.
What are you trying to do?
[APTOM]
I'm gonna give the Guyver III
a chance to use
his mega-smasher.
Because I can't afford to
die, not yet at least.
Aim for his blind spot!
[ZX-Tole grunts]
That bastard doesn't know
when to die!
[MAKISHIMA] Now!
[ZX-TOLE] What?!
[ZX-TOLE] I don't think so!
[Makishima lets out
a battle cry]
Did he block it?
He used his electo-wave knife to
split the mega-smasher in two!
[ZX-Tole lets out a battle cry]
[Makishima grunts in pain]
[SHIZU] Master Agito!
[ZX-Tole laughs]
It looks like I've finally
caught you, boy.
I have to admit, this has been a
lot more fun than I expected.
But it can't last forever!
[Makishima cries out in pain]
[SHIZU] NO!
Master Agito!
[TETSURO] Makishima!
[NATSUKI] Makishima, no!
Master Agito!
Please, say something!
Agito, please!
[Shizu sobs softly]
I always believed I'd see
you again someday.
And we'd be together forever.
[ZX-TOLE]
I think I know just the way
to finish you
off, Guyver III!
I'm gonna cleave you in half,
just like you did to Thancrus!
Shizu, no! Get outta the way!
ZX-Tole!
[ZX-TOLE] Enough rat!
[ZX-TOLE] One down.
Sho...
[ZX-TOLE] Out of my way,
little girl. Or else...
Stop it.
Shizu!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Master Agito!
Even if it kills me,
I won't move!
[ZX-TOLE] So be it.
Sho, please!
[ZX-TOLE]
If you want to die together,
then together you shall die!
SHO!
[SHIZU] Master Agito!
That's a Guyver, right?
Incredible...
He made it...
[TETSURO] It's huge!
[NATSUKI] Is that thing...
[MIZUKI] Yes, it's Sho.
[TETSURO] Are you sure?
There's no doubt in my mind.
I know because,
he answered my call.
Right, Sho? That's why
you're here, isn't it?
[ZX-TOLE]
That's Guyver I? Ridiculous!
Take this!
[TETSURO] Mizuki, run!
It's all right!
He'll protect us!
Help us, Sho!
[ZX-TOLE] W..What the hell?
There, see?
[ZX-TOLE] A barrier? Since when
can the Guyver use barriers?
What is that thing?!
I don't care who you are!
No one can stop me now!
[ZX-Tole lets out a battle cry]
You son of a bitch!
This isn't over yet!
It'll take a lot more than
that to beat me!
How could that be the Guyver I?
He should have been obliterated
at Mount Minakami.
More than that, he
seems to have evolved
into something else entirely.
I'll have to go see for myself.
I'm concerned about ZX-Tole's
actions as well.
Dawn is breaking.
No! ZX-Tole wouldn't go
that far, would he?
Stop this foolishness!
Don't you know what will happen
if you release your power now?
[ZX-TOLE] Oh, I know. If I use
it now with the sun rising,
my blaster tempest will eclipse
even the Guyver's mega-smasher!
In fact, with this
much sunlight,
the intensity of the
beam will surpass
one hundred million degrees.
This is the true extent
of my power!
The Guyver will be
reduced to ash,
with all of Tokyo along
with him!
Of course, the beam will
destroy me as well,
but I'm willing
to pay that price.
I never had long to live anyway,
so I might as well go
out with a bang!
Sho, please protect us!
[ZX-TOLE] This is it!
The Final Blaster Tempest!
STOP IT!
[MIZUKI] Don't give up.
I believe in you.
I still believe
that a light will
pierce the darkness
and drive it away.
I still believe...
that someday, we'll be
able to laugh again
under the clear, blue sky.
And I believe that the one who
carries that light is you, Sho.
You...
It's over.
[low growling]
A Zoanoid?!
[MAKISHIMA]
Looks like Chronos has been
keeping an eye on
us all this time.
That's just what I needed.
You're a real life-saver, pal.
One more thing, give Sho
a message for me.
Tell him I'll be dropping by
soon to pay him a visit.
I see, so I guess this means
we're enemies again, huh?
You're back.
Tetsuro...
Well, go on, say hello!
Why don't you?
Mizuki...
Mizuki, no matter what,
I want to protect this world.
I want to be wherever you are,
fighting to protect
our memories,
and fighting to
protect our future.
Sho, welcome home!