[fireworks and cheers]
[BEER GIRL] Beer here!
Get your beer here!
[CHAPATI] The big day
is finally here, folks!
The Grand Magic games will
be getting underway shortly!
This is going to be
a year to remember!
♪
[cheering crowd]
Wow, would you
listen to that crowd.
I didn't think there'd be
so many people watching.
The city is full of wizards
from all over the country.
Of course folks want
to see them in action.
Purple is so lame.
I'd rather wear my regular
clothes instead of this crap.
Purple or not, you'll
just have to deal.
Unless you want to tell
Master why you think
the clothes he picked
are so 'lame'?
You won't hear me complaining;
I think they're adorable.
And comfy.
Skin tight.
[LUCY] It's not skin tight;
you're half naked!
Uhh... I don't really care
about the color.
But I doubt I can
squeeze into this thing.
Oh man, that's perfect!
[LUCY] Well, you could
use it as a sock, I guess.
Did you spend those three months
bench-pressing a mountain range?
She's the one who
should be standing
here with the
rest of you, not me.
[ELFMAN] Do you
think she'll be all right?
You found 'em?
Where the
heck were they?
[HAPPY] Lisanna and I found
them in the palace's gardens.
You with us?
Natsu.
What happened out there?
It's all just a big blur.
Sorry. I wish that
I could remember.
What's wrong?
[PORLYUSICA] She appears to
have magic deficiency syndrome.
[LUCY] Porlyusica!
Wait, what are
you doing here?
[PORLYUSICA] Something
wrong with cheering you on?
No, ma'am!
Calm down,
I wasn't scolding you, child.
Don't be so nervous,
I'm not going to eat you.
[LISANNA] Right.
I'm here because
I was concerned.
I heard what happened and
thought I might be of help.
Now.
A moment ago you mentioned,
"magic deficiency syndrome."
Yes.
It's a condition of
weakened physical strength
brought on by an acute
case of magic depletion.
They've both had nearly all of
their magic power sucked out.
Don't worry; they'll fully
recover with enough bed rest.
Who did this to you?
It's still a big
blur for the most part.
But, I remember seeing
a weird, black animal.
[scream]
[Wendy cries]
Wendy.
[WENDY] I'm sorry.
I let you down.
I trained so hard to help you
but now. I'm just useless!
[WENDY] Hey, Elfman.
[WENDY] Please take
my place. Win for me.
Sure! You can
count on me, kid.
All right. Everybody
needs to leave.
They can't heal if
they don't get proper rest.
[ERZA] Let's go.
There's nothing we can do here.
We might as well try to focus
on the Grand Magic Games.
[HAPPY] You're right.
That's the only way we're gonna
become number one again.
No need for water-works, child.
After all, those ridiculous
games go on for several days.
I'm sure you'll get to
participate, once you're well.
And make no mistake, you will
recover now that I'm here.
On my honor as a healer.
Thanks for all
your help, Grandeena.
[PORLYUSICA]
Do not call me by that name!
[HAPPY] New Guild!
[NATSU] The person who
attacked Wendy, do you think
they're taking part
in the games as well?
[LUCY] I'd say there's
a big possibility.
You gotta wonder
too, if they did it to
weaken our team,
or for some other reason.
Keep your eyes
on the prize for now.
Winning this thing is the best
way to get revenge for Wendy.
We're just moments
away from the
start of the Grand
Magic Games, folks!
I'm lead commentator...
Chapati Lola,
and I'll be handling the
play-by-play while former
Council member Yajima
provides commentary!
Mr. Yajima.
Glad to have you with us sir.
Glad to be here.
And let's not forget
our special guest.
A member of Blue Pegasus
and current holder of the title
"Miss Fiore";
the ravishing Jenny Realite!
Blue Pegasus is bringing
home the gold this year!
Ready?
Let's go.
[CHAPATI] Now!
The time has come
to meet our competitors!
[CHAPATI]
First up, in eighth place:
an old school bunch of
wild wizards from Magnolia!
They had luck in the
prelims, and now they're
raring to take back
first place by force!
It's Fairy Tail!
[crowd boos]
What the hell?
I didn't see that comin'.
I wanna go home now.
Who would've
thought they'd make
it this far after
losing every year?
Securing a spot in the prelims
was no small feat for them.
[CHAPATI] Will the Tenrou
Team's sensational return help
Fairy Tail become
Fiore's greatest guild?
[ERZA] Don't let it get to you.
I'm proud of them.
Way to go, kiddos!
Now get out there and
show 'em what you can do.
[MAKAROV]
Cheer 'til you bust a lung!
Hooray!
Fairy Tail's number one!
The cheers of our comrades
are all the support we need.
[ALL] Fairy Tail's number one!
[NATSU] Hey, do you see that?
[LUCY] Look!
[ERZA] I see it!
[MAVIS] Hooray!
Hooray!
Fairy Tail is number one!
Woo hoo!
Master Mavis, what in the
world are you doing here?
What else?
I came to cheer you on, silly!
Yes, I can see that, but aren't
you, you know, dead?
[MAVIS] There's no way
I was going to miss this!
You don't need to worry.
Only those who bear our
guild's emblem can see me.
Yeah, well.
That's not really what
I was concerned about.
I'm sorry. I couldn't
help myself;
it's so dull being stuck
on Tenrou Island!
Even Master Mavis
came out to cheer for us?
We've got this in the bag.
At least the
ghost likes us.
Next up, the team that came in
seventh place in the pre-lims.
[CHAPATI] The rowdy
army of hellhounds.
Quatro Cerberus!
Let's get wild, ya with me?
I expect a win
this year, fellas.
Don't disappoint me.
And coming in
sixth is a guild filled
to the brim with the fairer sex!
[CHAPATI] The dancers
of the great, blue sea.
Mermaid Heel!
I didn't know there
was a guild full of ladies!
[CHAPATI] In fifth place!
With azure wings that
glimmer in the darkness.
It's Blue Pegasus!
Hey guys!
Do your best!
[CHAPATI] Next, in fourth place!
The goddess of love and strife!
The sacred destroyer!
Lamia Scale!
Why'd you only come
in fourth place, huh?
I thought I told you
kids not to hold back!
Yeah, sorry about
that, old hag.
I wasn't watching
where I was going.
I've never seen her before.
She looks like a smaller
version of that girl Sherry.
Please try to
stay on your feet.
No promises, Lyon.
This is Shelia; she's
one of Sherry's cousins.
[NATSU] That makes sense!
And she's crazy
strong to boot!
I need a lot more love if
I wanna compete with Sherry.
I was praising you!
[YUKA] Calm down and
chase a ball or something.
Being love-crazy
must run in the family.
[LYON] Don't forget
our agreement, Gray.
[LYON] If we win, Juvia becomes
a member of Lamia Scale.
[GRAY] Last time I checked
I never agreed to that bet.
Not that it matters, 'cause
you guys're gonna lose.
Then, if we win, I'll take
Miss Erza as my one and only.
You'll do no
such thing, you troll!
Your parfum is like
candy to my nostrils.
And I'll take you, I guess.
Not that I'm into
you or anything like that.
[LUCY] Thank you, Ren.
It's good to know that
some things never change.
Then I'll take Wendy!
Um.
[EVE] Whoa, you really
sprouted, didn't you?
That's cool,
I'm into thick chicks.
Laugh it up.
Hey, Boss!
If we lose, I wanna
be given to this guild!
Man, I was
gonna call dibs!
Have you ever seen any
of those Cerberus guys before?
[CERBERUS GUILD]
Get wild! Get wild!
Who's the fur?
Some dude?
[ROCKER] Let's go!
Now to introduce
our third place contestants!
What a shocker!
Swooping in from a midnight
dreary, this dark and gloomy
bunch are making their
debut in this year's games.
Give it up for Raven Tail!
What the heck
are they doin' here?
This is bad.
Their leader is Master
Makarov's son, Ivan.
But that means they're--.
Why is a dark
guild participating?
Have you officials
lost your minds or
were you just
incompetent to begin with?
You're making
a scene, Master.
[MAKAROV] Well?
He's gonna bust a vessel!
I'm sensing intense
malice from them.
Isn't Raven Tail a dark guild?
I dunno, I've never heard
of 'em before today.
Well. Their records
appear to be in order.
They're an old guild.
Official sources state they've
been active over seven years,
but they were only
recently approved for
official guild status
by the Magic Council.
If they have official status
then they're technically
not a dark guild and are,
therefore, eligible to compete.
Curse you, Ivan!
I don't know how you
did it, but whatever
you're planning,
I swear I'll stop you.
You really shouldn't get so
worked up old man
it's bad for your health.
[IVAN] I want you to
live to see your guild fall.
[IVAN (ALEXEI)] Fairy Tail.
[IVAN (ALEXEI)] I trust
your friend is recovering?
You were the ones
who attacked Wendy?
I'm gonna make you regret it!
[IVAN (ALEXEI)] The festival's
just getting started.
[MAKAROV] Ivan!
[CHAPATI] Hold on!
We've still got two
teams who made
it through the qualifying round!
Oh, yeah!
I wonder which of the
other teams made it through.
You can bet on one
of 'em bein' Sabertooth.
As for the other one.
Huh.
All the well-known guilds
have already been announced.
So it's possible one of these
teams is somehow tied to Zeref.
That's assuming
Jellal's intuition was right.
I guess we'll know soon.
Our first place runner up is...
Oh wow!
What a surprise!
This year's competition
just got a whole
lot more
interesting, folks!
[CHAPATI]
It's Fairy Tail Team B!
[ELFMAN] Big Sis?
[NATSU] Gajeel?
[GRAY] Juvia?
[LUCY] And Laxus?
How is that fair?
I certainly didn't expect
them to have two teams.
Hold up!
I need some answers!
Someone explain
how Mystogan's even here!
It can't be.
Jellal?
Is that you in there?
Shhh...
[NATSU AND GRAY]
You kiddin' me?
Beautiful.
[SHELIA] So she's the one
you've been fawning over.
[HIBIKI] Of course
they got two teams in.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
[IVAN (ALEXEI)] Laxus and
Gajeel are joining the party.
[ROCKER] How come
they have two teams?
They giving
Fairy Tail a handicap
'cause they suck so hard?
That's way past wild, man.
You know...
I think the newly
implemented rules may
have left our audience
a bit perplexed, Mr. Yajima.
Care to explain?
Sure thing.
The committee in charge of the
Grand Magic Games permitted each
guild to enter two teams,
which they felt would
make the preliminaries
more exciting.
Why didn't you tell
us this was your plan, Master?
[MAKAROV] You like that?
This is how the Fairy Tail guild
takes care of business, baby!
I'm not sure the
committee really
thought this new
rule through.
I mean, this is a
team-based competition.
Won't having two teams
from the same guild
kind of stack the odds?
You worry too
much; to be honest,
I don't think it'll
be a problem.
Well, it's totally
unfair if you ask me.
Let's say there's an event
where each team chooses a
member to compete against
the others in a battle royale.
There's nothing
to stop the Fairy Tail
members from teaming
up with each other.
It does give them
an advantage.
But I guess that's their reward
for being the only guild out
of over one hundred with
two teams in the games.
You certainly
have the upper hand.
Way to go, Mocky!
Mocky?
I see!
That's why so many teams
entered the tournament!
This is a big loada crap!
Being in the same
guild don't mean jack;
if I fight against any of you,
I'm not pulling any punches!
As long as we're
in this tournament you're
my enemies, and I ain't
gonna lose to any of you?
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
I'm lookin' forward to makin'
you eat dirt, Salamander.
Gajeel's a lot stronger
than he was three months ago.
Well, Natsu's
no creampuff either!
Team B has got
some serious power;
it won't be easy
to take them down!
What's the matter?
You look terrified!
That's 'cause I am!
So. What are
you doing here?
This is wrong.
Your master is a very
understanding person.
Once I explained the situation,
he gave my plan his blessing.
You said it was impossible
to get near the coliseum.
[JELLAL] It was.
Until this opportunity
presented itself.
It's against the rules.
You're not an official
member of Fairy Tail.
[JELLAL]
As I understand it, Mystogan
and I are essentially
one and the same.
Don't be so uptight!
This is a festival!
We're all friends here.
Right?
Kiss and make up.
[JELLAL] It'll be fine.
Trust me.
By the way, "Mystogan."
You're not usually
this much of a chatty Kathy.
Keep it in mind.
[JELLAL] Understood.
The hooded
man down there.
He doesn't seem to
be a member of our guild.
[MAKAROV] I'm so sorry!
I had to!
Please forgive me!
I said it was a bad
idea from the start.
Don't think we didn't
try to stop him!
I don't sense any
malevolence coming from him.
[MAVIS] In fact, he seems
to possess the same heart
as those bearing
our guild's emblem.
It'd take way too long
to explain, but I guess you
could say he's technically
a member of Fairy Tail.
I get it.
He's Earth Land'
version of Prince Jellal.
I thought he seemed familiar.
[MAVIS] Is he strong?
Oh yes!
For sure!
It wasn't that long ago
that he was one of
the ten Wizard Saints!
[MAVIS] Then he can stay!
With him on our team
we're sure to be number one!
[DROY]
'Course she's fine with it.
Who cares about
rules when there's
a tournament to win, right?
We should make that part
of the charter at this point.
[JELLAL] So, have you
managed to find anything yet?
I'm suspicious of
Raven Tail but beyond
that I have nothing solid.
[JELLAL] This is their
debut in the games.
We've sensed the
power in previous years
so it can't be them.
[ERZA] What about you? Any
sign of this "strange power?"
[JELLAL] No.
Not yet.
Even Gajeel came to play.
And last, but certainly
not least, is the team
that came in first
place in the preliminaries!
[crowd cheers]
[CHAPATI] That's right!
You know them!
You love them!
Now, get on your
feet and scream for
the most powerful
guild in all of Fiore!
The one and only Sabertooth!
[NATSU] Can't wait
to bring them down.
[STING] Why so serious?
S'just a game.
There a reason you
keep gawkin', pretty boy?
Nothing important.
At least we finally know
who our biggest competition is.
You're the man, Sting!
The best in the
whole wide world!
I'm cheering for you, too!
Isn't that great?
It appears that Sabertooth
has an Exceed cheer squad!
Natsu, Natsu, he's our man!
Burnin' butts across the land!
All in all,
I'd say we have
an impressive group
of wizards here!
Any comments on our
lineup, Mr. Yajima?
Yeah...
Mermaid Heel makes
me pine for my youth.
[CHAPATI] Um, that's
not quite what I meant.
We've kept everyone
waiting long enough!
It's about time we unveil
the official schedule
for this year's tournament!
There's gonna be a lot
of action in the next few days.
Now we're talkin'!
Each one of the rounds
will begin with a contest!
Participants will then be ranked
from first to eighth place!
[CHAPATI] The teams will
be awarded points depending
on how they ranked
in the contest.
Additionally, the teams
are allowed to select which
of their members
they want to compete.
After that, we have battles!
These bouts should come as quite
a treat to all you loyal fans
since it was your suggestions
that created these matchups!
Interesting.
Sounds like they get to
choose who fights who.
So then, if you don't watch
how much magic you
use in a contest,
you could find yourself
thrown into a battle
with no time to rest.
[CHAPATI] The battle
rules are simple!
Each team will square
off as shown here!
The winning teams
will be awarded ten points,
while the losing
teams get jack squat!
[CHAPATI]
In the case of a draw,
both teams will
be awarded five points.
Ready for action? Let's
get things started with the
first contest of the
Grand Magic Games,
one that we call "Hidden"!
[FEMALE 157B]
"Hidden"? What's that?
[MALE 157B] How should I know?
[CHAPATI] At this time,
we'd like each team
to select one
member to compete!
Once your selections are made,
the rules will be
explained in their entirety.
[YAEGER]
Let me start us off right!
It's all yours.
May the Wild be with you!
[ALL] Go Wild!
[CHAPATI] The first challenger
has stepped forward!
Representing Quatro
Cerberus; it's Yaeger!
The first one'll be easy.
I'll size up our opponents.
We're counting on you.
[CHAPATI] From Mermaid Heel,
the adorable Beth Vanderwood!
[IVAN (ALEXEI)] Nalpudding.
You go.
I won't letcha down, boss man.
[CHAPATI]
From Raven Tail, Nalpudding!
I'll take this one.
We're sending
you out there in style!
[HIBIKI AND REN] Look out
ladies, here comes Eve!
[CHAPATI] Blue Pegasus
sends out Eve Tilm!
Gotta love those lively cheers!
I shall handle this.
I'm feeling inspired by
the birds' lovely songs.
[CHAPATI] Keep your
eyes on this one, folks!
From Sabertooth,
the minstrel who
sings to the red
moon: Rufus Lore!
They're going
nuts for the pretty boy?
I don't get it.
Whatever the rules,
I'm sure the name is a clue.
I have a feeling
that stealth and guile
will be essential to win.
If only Wendy wasn't
out of commission.
She'd be perfect.
I'll do it, guys!
I could use a warm up anyway;
you just sit back and
let a real man handle it.
It's called hidden,
so I don't think
sending out a giant
is a great idea.
Sounds like in this
game the smaller you
are the better, so that means
it's down to me or Yuka.
Who're you callin' small?
No.
We shall take the
lead from the start.
Just leave it to me.
[CHAPATI]
From Lamia Scale, Lyon Bastia!
Yeah?
In that case, I got this one.
I've been itchin' to see what
this tournament's all about.
[CHAPATI] From Fairy Tail
Team A, the icy Gray Fullbuster!
If my darling's competing,
then so will I!
Hey!
Don't go throwin' the fight
for your boyfriend, ya hear?
[CHAPATI] From Fairy
Tail Team B, Juvia Loxar!
The competitors
have been chosen
and the long
wait is finally over!
[CHAPATI] Grab a refreshment
and get glued to your seat,
'cause you're not
gonna want to miss a
single nail-biting
moment of "Hidden!"
♪
[NATSU] Ugh, what's
with the army of Grays?
Lame!
[HAPPY] This has gotta
be heaven for Juvia!
[NATSU] But they're
not the real deal!
It's weird!
[HAPPY] I wish I
could use copy magic.
[NATSU]
What would you use it for?
[HAPPY] I'd make copy after copy
of the tastiest fish around!
[NATSU] So you're saying
you'd be a "copy cat"?
[HAPPY] Ugh, and you thought
the "Gray Army" was lame?
[HAPPY AND NATSU ] Next time:
Night of Shooting Stars!
[HAPPY] Watch it or I'm
gonna make an army
of Erzas who're
all really mad at you!
[NATSU] Oh, no!
Anything but that!