- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE,
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WOULD NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- THE REWARD HAS BEEN
RAISED TO TWO MILLION JEWEL.
- FLYING VIRGO ATTACK!
- ( screams )
- SO YOU WANT TO PILFER
"DAYBREAK."
- Lucy: I KNEW THIS BOOK
HELD SOME SORT OF SECRET.
- NOW I'VE GOT SOME
FIRE IN MY BELLY.
- Both: NO!
( both groan )
- WH-- WERE WE BEATEN
BY A FIRE WIZARD?
- HEY, BRO,
TELL ME WHEN THE ROOM
STOPS SPINNING, 'KAY?
- THAT'LL TEACH YOU.
NOW THEN,
GUESS I'D BETTER
GO AND FIND LUCY.
THESE MERCHANT FAIRIES
ARE TOAST.
- Vanish Brothers:
WE'RE MERCENARIES.
- ENEMY OF LITERATURE?
MY MASSIVE COLLECTION
OF BOOKS AND ART
ONLY PROVE I'M CULTURE'S
GREATEST FRIEND!
- BUT THAT UGLY MAID COLLECTION
PROVES YOU DON'T KNOW SQUAT
ABOUT BEAUTY.
- HOW DARE YOU MOCK THEM.
THEY ARE THE VERY
DEFINITION OF BEAUTY.
WHAT SECRET DOES IT HOLD?
LET ME GUESS,
HE BURIED HIS FORTUNE
AND THERE'S A TREASURE MAP
HIDDEN INSIDE.
- ( grunts )
- TELL ME,
OR I'LL SNAP YOUR ARM
LIKE A TOOTHPICK.
- ( grunts, blows raspberry )
- BOYO.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME
TO GET SASSY.
LISTEN, I MYSELF COMMISSIONED
THIS BOOK'S VERY CREATION.
THEREFORE,
ANY SECRET IT HOLDS
IS RIGHTFULLY MY PROPERTY!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- HAPPY!
- ( giggles )
- THAT WAS SO COOL.
HUH?
- WHAT'S THIS? A
FLYING CAT? - ( burbles )
THE NAME'S HAPPY.
- I WOULDN'T STAY IN THERE
IF I WAS YOU.
- BUT THE WATER
FEELS SO GOOD.
- THAT'S SEWER WATER,
HAPPY.
LOOKS LIKE THE TABLES
HAVE TURNED.
BUT IF YOU LET ME
KEEP THE BOOK,
I'LL THINK ABOUT
GOING EASY ON YOU.
ALTHOUGH I'M TEMPTED
TO GIVE YOU A GOOD SMACK.
- OH. A CELESTIAL WIZARD.
BUT FOR A READER,
YOU SEEM TO BE A BIT DEFICIENT
IN YOUR TURNS OF PHRASE.
"THE TABLES HAVE TURNED"
IMPLIES THAT THE WEAKER PARTY
HAS RALLIED TO CLAIM VICTORY.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
YOU AND THAT CAT
COULD EVER DEFEAT ME
AND MY DIVER MAGIC.
BOYOYOYOYO!
- SO HE DOES THAT
USING MAGIC?
I HAD NO IDEA EVERLUE
WAS A WIZARD TOO.
- DO YOU NOT SMELL YOURSELF?
- ( grunts )
- BOYO!
- LOOK, I KNOW
THE WHOLE STORY NOW.
IT'S A HORRIBLE ADVENTURE NOVEL
ABOUT A TRASHY LITTLE CHARACTER
NAMED DUKE EVERLUE.
- YOU SERIOUS?
- I DON'T KNOW THAT I'D CALL
THE PROTAGONIST "TRASHY."
BUT YES.
THE STORY ITSELF IS CRAP.
AND TO THINK IT WAS WRITTEN
BY THE GREAT KEMU ZALEON.
- ( gasps )
- INEXCUSABLE!
( chuckles )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOUR ARROGANCE.
YOU FORCED HIM TO WRITE IT.
- ARROGANT, MOI?
THE WORD DOESN'T
BEGIN TO APPLY.
TO TELL MY STORY'S AN HONOR,
NO MATTER WHAT
THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- THEN WHY'D YOU HAVE TO
BLACKMAIL HIM INTO IT?
- BLACKMAIL?
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- ( gasps )
- HE JUST NEEDED SOME
EXTRA ENCOURAGEMENT
TO TAKE THE JOB.
- OH REALLY?
- ANY FOOL WOULD HAVE
JUMPED AT THE CHANCE
TO HAVE ME AS THEIR MUSE.
BUT HE HAD THE AUDACITY
TO SAY NO.
SO I GAVE HIM
THE ADDED INSPIRATION
IN THE FORM OF
AN ULTIMATUM.
WRITE THE NOVEL,
OR HIS FAMILY WOULD BE
STRIPPED OF THEIR CITIZENSHIP.
- BUT THEN NONE OF THEM
WOULD BE ABLE TO
JOIN ANY OF THE GUILDS
AND MAKE A LIVING.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE
THE POWER TO DO THAT?
- I HAVE THE POWER
TO DO ANYTHING.
I GOT HIM TO WRITE IT,
DIDN'T I?
- ( breathes heavily )
- BUT I DIDN'T LIKE
HIS ATTITUDE,
SO I DECIDED HE'D DO BEST
WRITING FROM A PRISON CELL.
BOYOYO!
HE WENT ON AND ON ABOUT
BEING A BRILLIANT NOVELIST
WHO WOULD NEVER
GIVE INTO THREATS,
BUT IN THE END
I GOT WHAT I WANTED!
- ( whimpers ) - I CAN'T
BELIEVE YOU'D GO THAT FAR
JUST TO BOOST YOUR OWN
STUPID EGO.
HE WAS IN SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT FOR THREE YEARS.
DON'T YOU KNOW HOW HARD
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN?
- THREE WHOLE YEARS?
- ( Lucy and Happy gasp )
- PERHAPS IT TOOK HIM
THAT LONG TO APPRECIATE ME.
BOYOYOYO.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
MORE LIKE HE COULDN'T BEAR
TO SPREAD YOUR LIES.
BUT HE HAD TO
SATISFY YOUR VANITY.
HE KNEW THAT IF
HE DIDN'T WRITE YOUR CHARACTER
AS A HEROIC
CHAMPION OF JUSTICE,
THEN HIS FAMILY
WOULD SUFFER.
- TELL ME, HOW EXACTLY
DO YOU KNOW ALL THIS?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT HERE
IN BLACK AND WHITE.
- WHAT?  I'VE READ THAT BOOK
FROM COVER TO COVER,
AND KEMU ZALEON
ISN'T IN IT.
- WELL, YEAH,
IF YOU READ IT NORMALLY
THERE'S NO MENTION OF HIM.
BUT I KNOW SOMETHING
YOU DON'T KNOW.
LONG BEFORE HE WAS AN AUTHOR,
HE WAS A WIZARD.
- Happy: HE WAS?
- Everlue: WHAT DID HE DO?
- Lucy:
AFTER HE FINISHED THE BOOK,
HE GATHERED ALL HIS
REMAINING STRENGTH
AND CAST A SPELL ON IT.
- ( groans )
WHAT A DIRTY TRICK.
HE TURNED A BOOK ABOUT
A GREAT MAN LIKE ME
INTO A HATCHET JOB?
THE NERVE OF THAT FOOL!
BOYO!
- OH, GET OVER YOURSELF!
- IT'S TRUE THAT HE WROTE
ABOUT ALL THE PAIN AND TORTURE
THAT YOU PUT HIM THROUGH.
BUT THE CHAPTERS THAT FOCUS
ON WHAT YOU DID TO HIM
ARE ONLY A SMALL
PART OF THE BOOK.
IN FACT, ITS SECRET
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- TELL US, LUCY.
- WHAT THE DEVIL DO YOU MEAN?
- I'M NOT GONNA GIVE THIS BOOK
BACK TO YOU, DUKE EVERLUE,
'CAUSE IT WAS NEVER REALLY
YOURS TO BEGIN WITH.
OPEN,
GATE OF THE GIANT CRAB!
CANCER!
- CANCER.
- A GIANT CRAB!
OH YEAH.
NOTHING SAYS
"I'M GONNA KICK YOUR BUTT"
LIKE A CRAB MAN
WITH RAZOR CLAWS
AND TOUGH-GUY SUNGLASSES.
( giggles )
- SHUT UP AND LET ME
CONCENTRATE,
OR I'LL HAVE HIM PINCH
YOUR LITTLE LIPS OFF.
- HEY, LUCY,
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
YOUR HAIR DONE TODAY...
BABY?
- WHAT?!
- I DON'T NEED STYLING.
I NEED HELP.
IT'S THAT GUY.
TAKE CARE OF BALDY OVER THERE.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY, BABY.
- OH, SO HE JUST MAKES
THE BAD GUYS LOOK COOLER
BEFORE THEY KILL US.
THAT'S USEFUL.
YEAH, YOU SHOULD
SEND HIM BACK, LUCY.
- I SHOULD SEND YOU BACK.
- WHAT COULD THE SECRET
POSSIBLY BE?
THE HACK MUST HAVE
WRITTEN AN EXPOSE
ON ALL OF MY
ILLEGAL BUSINESS DEALS.
I CAN'T HAVE THAT.
IF THE MAGIC COUNCIL
GOT WIND OF HOW I ACTUALLY
MADE MY FORTUNE,
MY GOOSE WOULD BE COOKED.
- OPEN,
GATE OF THE MAIDEN!
VIRGO!
- WHAT THE--?
- HE'S USING YOUR TRICK, LUCY.
- DID I HEAR MY MASTER
SUMMON ME?
- VIRGO,
FETCH ME THAT BOOK.
- HOLD UP.
SHE'S A CELESTIAL SPIRIT?
- BABY.
- ( all gasp )
- Happy and Lucy: NATSU!
- YEAH?
- WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP THERE?
- WELL, I SAW HER GETTING UP,
SO I JUMPED ON HER
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
I ENDED UP HERE.
- SO YOU GRABBED
A HOLD OF HER INSIDE THE HOUSE?
BUT THAT MEANS...
YOU MUST HAVE PASSED THROUGH
THE SPIRIT GATE WITH HER.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- LUCY, WHAT THE HECK
DO I DO NOW?
FINISH WHAT YOU STARTED.
- VIRGO, CLEAN UP
THIS RUBBISH.
- AS YOU WISH, MASTER.
- NOW I'M FIRED UP.
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- YOU DIRTY LITTLE MOLE MAN!
- ( grunts )
- CAN'T DIG YOURSELF
OUT OF THIS!
YOU MAKE ME SICK!
- BOYOYOYOYOYOYOYO.
- BABY.
- ( whimpers )
- YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER
GREEDY VILLAIN.
- BOYO.
- OKAY, I'M DONE.
DOES THIS LOOK
FABULOUS OR WHAT, BABY?
- OH YEAH.  WAY TO GO,
CRAB-MAN-- BABY.
- ( rumbling )
- ( Lucy and Happy gasp )
- I LIKE YOUR STYLE.
OUT WITH A BANG.
YOU ARE DEFINITELY
GONNA FIT IN AT FAIRY TAIL.
- BUT AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO NOT DESTROY STUFF?
- I HOPE I DON'T
GET BLAMED FOR THIS.
- ( crowd laughs, cheers )
- AND THEN...
- WHEN I READ "DAYBREAK,"
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT WAS
WRITTEN BY KEMU ZALEON.
THERE'S NO WAY HE WOULD HAVE
DONE SOMETHING THAT BAD.
- YEAH, SO?
- SO THAT'S HOW I KNEW
THERE MUST BE A SPELL ON IT.
- ( gasps )
BUT I REQUESTED
THIS BOOK BE DESTROYED.
WHY ON EARTH ARE YOU
HANDING IT BACK TO ME
COMPLETELY UNSCATHED?
- IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO BURN IT,
THEN I'D RATHER
YOU DO IT YOURSELF.
- I MOST CERTAINLY WILL
BURN THIS TRASH.
I NEVER WANTED TO
SEE IT AGAIN.
- I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU FEEL THE WAY YOU DO
ABOUT THIS BOOK, KABY.
YOU WANT TO PROTECT
YOUR FATHER'S LEGACY,
BECAUSE YOU'RE ACTUALLY
ZALEON'S SON, AREN'T YOU?
- HUH?
- YES, THAT'S TRUE.
- HAVE YOU READ IT YOURSELF?
- NO, I-- I COULD NEVER
BRING MYSELF TO DO IT.
MY FATHER TOLD ME
IT WAS GARBAGE.
- YOU WERE JUST GONNA BURN IT?
- I WAS.
- WITHOUT EVEN BOTHERING
TO SEE WHAT'S INSIDE?
IT'S THE LAST BOOK THAT
YOUR DAD WROTE, RIGHT?
SOME OF US WOULD KILL
FOR THAT KIND OF MEMORY.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, NATSU!
LET KABY EXPLAIN HIMSELF.
- ( sighs )
- PLEASE,
THAT BOOK CAUSED MY FAMILY
GREAT HEARTACHE AND SHAME.
IT WAS 31 YEARS AGO.
- ( door creaks open )
- FATHER?
- FORGIVE ME, SON.
- WE HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING
FROM YOU IN THREE YEARS.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
- SOMEWHERE I'LL NOT RETURN.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
- NO, FATHER.
- I'LL NEVER WRITE AGAIN!
( shouts )
- ( both scream )
- WHOA.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED TO ME.
I TOLD YOU YOU'D REGRET WORKING
FOR THAT HORRIBLE DUKE EVERLUE.
BUT YOU WENT AHEAD
AND DID IT ANYWAY. WHY?
- BECAUSE IT WAS GOOD MONEY.
- WHO CARES?
LOOK WHERE IT GOT YOU.
- ( sighs ) I'M SO GLAD
I FINISHED THAT RUBBISH.
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
DO YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY TO LEAVE
YOUR FAMILY FOR THREE YEARS
TO WRITE A NOVEL
YOU'RE NOT EVEN PROUD OF?
- SON...
I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
THE ENTIRE TIME I WAS GONE.
- THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST
WRITTEN SOMETHING
FOR HIM QUICKLY
AND COME BACK TO US.
INSTEAD, YOU ABANDONED
YOUR PRIDE AND YOUR FAMILY
RIGHT ALONG WITH IT.
YOU'RE A SAD EXCUSE
FOR A WRITER.
SELLING YOURSELF OUT
TO THE HIGHEST BIDDER.
YOU'RE NOT MUCH OF
A FATHER EITHER.
- ( sighs )
- NOT LONG AFTER THAT,
MY FATHER PASSED AWAY.
HOWEVER, THE ANGER AND BETRAYAL
I FELT TOWARDS HIM LIVED ON.
BUT AS THE YEARS
PASSED BY ME,
THAT ANGER SLOWLY
TURNED INTO REMORSE.
AND NOW...
IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME
TO ASK FOR HIS FORGIVENESS.
SO I DECIDED
TO MAKE AMENDS
BY DESTROYING
THE FINAL WORK
THAT HAD CAUSED HIM
SO MUCH UNHAPPINESS.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY.
THE ONLY WAY I CAN
PRESERVE HIS LEGACY.
- ( match lights )
- I'M SURE THAT THIS
IS WHAT HE'D WANT.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
- ( Natsu and Happy gasp )
- KABY, LOOK.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- A SPELL HAS BEEN
CAST ON THIS BOOK.
IT'S THE WORK OF THE WIZARD
KEMU ZALEON,
OR SHOULD I SAY
ZEKUA MELON?
- A SPELL?
"DEAR KABY."
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS BOOK IS HIS LETTER TO YOU.
DISGUISED BEHIND A SPELL THAT
REARRANGED ALL OF THE WORDS
SO NO ONE ELSE
COULD READ IT.
- WOW.
- PRETTY.
- HE DIDN'T STOP WRITING
BECAUSE HE WAS ASHAMED.
HE STOPPED BECAUSE
HE HAD FINISHED HIS MASTERPIECE,
A NOVEL CONTAINING EVERYTHING
HE EVER WANTED TO SAY
TO HIS BELOVED SON.
AND WHEN YOU READ IT
THE WAY HE INTENDED,
IT'S EASILY HIS
BEST WORK EVER.
- "I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
THE ENTIRE TIME I WAS GONE."
- AND NOW THAT
THE SPELL'S BEEN BROKEN,
YOU CAN READ IT
FOR YOURSELF.
- THANK YOU, FATHER.
I SWEAR THAT I WILL NEVER
LET ANY HARM COME TO THIS BOOK.
- WELL, I GUESS WE WON'T BE
COLLECTING THAT REWARD.
- AYE.
- HUH?!
- WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO DESTROY IT.
WE DIDN'T FINISH THE JOB.
- EVEN SO,
LET ME DO SOMETHING.
- YEAH, IT'S NOT OUR FAULT
HE DECIDED NOT TO BURN THE BOOK
AFTER WE GOT IT
BACK FOR HIM.
- LUCY, DON'T BE SO GREEDY.
YOU'RE TOTALLY RUINING
WHAT WAS A TOUCHING MOMENT.
- I NEED THE CASH!
- ( scoffs )
- THANKS FOR OFFERING,
BUT WE DON'T WANT IT.
- UM, YES WE DO.
I NEED TO PAY RENT.
- I THINK IT'S TIME
WE ALL GO HOME.
THAT MEANS YOU TOO,
MR. MELON.
GO BACK HOME.
- ( gasps )
- UNBELIEVABLE.
WHO IN THEIR RIGHT MINDS WOULD
TURN DOWN TWO MILLION JEWEL?
- IF WE HAD TAKEN THE MONEY,
IT WOULDN'T HAVE LOOKED GOOD.
YOU GOTTA THINK ABOUT
FAIRY TAIL'S REPUTATION.
- AYE.
- BUT WE MADE HIM HAPPY, RIGHT?
WE GOT THE JOB DONE
AND NOW WE'RE WALKING HOME.
( sighs )
AND THEN TO FIND OUT
THAT THEY'RE
NOT EVEN WEALTHY?
THEY WERE JUST
RENTING THAT HOUSE
SO EVERYBODY WOULD
THINK THEY WERE RICH.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT MATTERS.
WE WOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE JOB EITHER WAY.
- Happy:
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU.
- OF COURSE I WOULD HAVE!
- SURE, GREEDY.
- BY THE WAY,
THE HOUSE,
HOW'D YOU KNOW THAT IT
WASN'T REALLY THEIRS?
- HMM?
OH, THAT WAS EASY.
'CAUSE THEY SMELLED
LIKE SOME OTHER HOUSE.
SEEMED PRETTY OBVIOUS.
- AYE.
- SURE, TO YOU TWO ANIMALS,
MAYBE.
NOT ME.  I WAS STILL
LOST IN THE CLOUDS
FROM READING THAT BOOK.
- I'VE GOT YOU FIGURED OUT.
ALL THOSE PAPERS I FOUND
ON THE DESK AT YOUR PLACE.
YOU'RE WRITING A NOVEL,
AREN'T YOU?
- Happy: OH, SO THAT'S WHY
SHE'S SUCH A BOOKWORM.
- PROMISE YOU WON'T TELL
ANYBODY ABOUT THAT, OKAY?
- WHY NOT?
- 'CAUSE I'M A HORRIBLE WRITER.
IF ANYBODY READ MY STUFF,
I'D DIE OF EMBARRASSMENT.
- DON'T WORRY.
NOBODY'S GONNA READ IT.
- YEAH, THAT DOESN'T REALLY
MAKE ME FEEL ANY BETTER.
- "I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS,
GUYS.
ARE YOU SURE WE'RE GOING
THE RIGHT WAY," SHE ASKS.
- HAPPY SAYS THIS IS
THE WAY HOME,
SO THIS IS THE WAY
WE'RE GOING,
IS WHAT I ANSWER.
- HAVE SOME FAITH.
I'M A CAT.
I HAVE A GREAT
SENSE OF SMELL.
MY NOSE WILL
LEAD US HOME.
- "IT'S DOGS THAT
HAVE GREAT NOSES.
AND WHAT DOES SMELL HAVE
TO DO WITH DIRECTION,"
SHE ASKS QUITE HAUGHTILY.
- WHY DON'T YOU DO
YOUR OWN WALKING FOR A WHILE?
- "BECAUSE I'M TIRED,"
SHE GROANS EXHAUSTEDLY.
- Natsu: OH, BROTHER.
WHO'S THERE?
- "DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO FIGHT,"
SHE INQUIRES WORRIEDLY.
- YOU CAN TAKE HIM,
NATSU.
IT'S GRAY!
- "WHAT IS HE DOING
IN HIS UNDERWEAR,"
THE LADY QUESTIONS.
- TRYING TO FIND A BATHROOM.
- WHY WOULD YOU STRIP DOWN
BEFORE YOU FOUND ONE?
AND WHO THE HECK EVER
HEARD OF A BATHROOM
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FOREST?
- I WANTED SOME PRIVACY.
I DIDN'T EXPECT
AN IDIOT TO BARGE IN.
- I DIDN'T BARGE IN!
- THEY'RE SO CHILDISH.
- SHE SAYS TO THE CAT.
- SO YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
BACK FROM A JOB?
- YEAH, THERE'S A SHORTCUT
THROUGH THESE WOODS
THAT'LL GET YOU BACK
TO TOWN IN NO TIME.
- SEE? I TOLD YOU SO.
- YEAH, WELL IF YOUR
NOSE IS SO GREAT,
THEN HOW COME YOU DIDN'T KNOW
GRAY WAS RIGHT IN FRONT OF US,
SMART GUY? - THERE ARE SOME
THINGS YOU DON'T WANT TO SMELL.
- ( grunts )
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- I AGREE.  SO GO ON HOME
AND WE'LL SMELL YOU LATER.
- FINE, I WILL.
AND UNLESS YOU WANT TROUBLE,
YOU SHOULD TOO.
- WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
- 'CAUSE ERZA'S DUE BACK
ANY TIME NOW.
- ( gasps )
- THE ERZA?  WHOA.
- YEP, SHE'S THE MOST POWERFUL
WOMAN IN ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
- I CAN'T WAIT
TO MEET HER.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER EVEN
SEEN A PICTURE OF HER
IN "SORCERER WEEKLY"
OR ANYTHING.
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
- All: SCARY.
- ( chuckles nervously )
- WILD ANIMAL?
- A VILE BEAST.
- MORE LIKE A FULL-ON MONSTER!
- ( crowd screams )
- ( groans )
- SHE'S NOT THAT BIG,
YOU GUYS.
- WELL,
SHE'S BIG ENOUGH FOR ME.
- ONE THING WE CAN
ALL AGREE ON
IS SHE IS DEFINITELY
THAT SCARY.
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE SCARIER.
- ( roars )
- YEAH, SHE'S ABOUT THIS SCARY.
- WHAT?  I GUARANTEE YOU
ERZA COULD TAKE DOWN
AT LEAST THREE MOUNTAINS
WITH A SINGLE KICK.
- YOU DON'T NEED TO
EXAGGERATE LIKE THAT, GRAY.
IT'S MORE LIKE TWO.
- YOU KNOW, GUYS,
EVEN IF SHE'S ABLE
TO KICK DOWN A SINGLE MOUNTAIN,
THAT'S STILL SCARY.
- LIKE I SAID,
WE SHOULD GET BACK.
- CRAP, LET'S GET MOVING!
- ( all scream )
- ( coughs )
- WHAT NOW?
- HAPPY?
- HELP ME.
- ( chuckles ) - WE'RE FINALLY
GONNA GET SOME REAL PROTEIN.
- NO BERRIES FOR US TONIGHT.
- MEAT!
- OUR FUTURE HOLDS A FEAST.
- WOW.
- LOOK AT HIM SHAKING. JEEZ.
- RELAX.  YOU'RE GONNA BE
IN OUR BELLIES SOON ENOUGH,
SO THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE SCARED.
- ACTUALLY, I'M NOT SHAKING
LIKE THIS BECAUSE I'M SCARED.
- HUH? - I GOTTA USE
THE BATHROOM REALLY BAD.
- HUH?
- I CAN'T HOLD IT MUCH LONGER.
AND I BET YOU IT'S GONNA
MAKE ME TASTE WEIRD.
- WHO CARES?
NOW COOK HIM.
- MEAT.
- I WILL TAKE MINE
MEDIUM, PLEASE.
- HEY, I'M SERIOUS.
IT'S GONNA MAKE ME TASTE FUNNY.
I JUST KNOW IT WILL.
- Natsu:
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- HAPPY!
- THANK GOODNESS.
NOW I'M NOT GONNA TASTE WEIRD.
- PIPE DOWN.
- THAT'S OUR FRIEND YOU'RE
TRYING TO ROAST, BUDDY.
SORRY, BUT YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
HAVE TO MAKE
OTHER PLANS FOR DINNER.
- YOU'RE ALL WIZARDS,
AREN'T YOU?
WHAT GUILD ARE YOU WITH?
- I'M NOT TELLING.
GET HIM!
- GRAY, LET'S DO IT.
- ALL RIGHT, BUT DON'T GO
TELLING ME WHAT TO DO.
- ( grunts )
SAND BOMB, GO!
- NATSU!
- HE'S FINE.
GO AND HELP HAPPY.
- RIGHT.
- ( grunting )
- HELP!
LUCY'S GONNA EAT ME.
- SHUT UP, CAT!
- MEAT!
- ( screams )
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME,
MR. CHICKEN!
( panting )
- NEXT?
- ( chants )
YOU'LL SEE SOMEONE SPECIAL,
BUT THE STARS POINT TO
GREAT TROUBLE WITH
WATER AND WOMEN.
- YOU'RE TELLING MY FORTUNE?
- ( grunts )
- HE'S NOT USING MAGIC.
WOW.
PUT SOME CLOTHES ON!
- CRAP.
- WHERE DID THESE BRATS
COME FROM ANYWAY?
UH-OH.
- JERK. NOW I'VE GOT
A MOUTH FULL OF SAND
AND IT'S ALL 'CAUSE OF YOU.
( spits )
HERE IT GOES.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
( shouts )
- DON'T YOU THINK YOU MIGHT
HAVE GONE OVERBOARD, NATSU?
- SO WHAT IF I DID?
I GOT THE JOB DONE.
- GROW UP, ALREADY.  YOU'RE AN
EMBARRASSMENT TO THE GUILD.
- WHAT? SHUT UP!
- NO, YOU SHUT UP.
- LULLA.
- HUH?  WHAT'S LULLA?
- LULLABY IS...
- HUH?
- LULLABY?
- INCOMING!
- ( gasps )
- THEY FOUND US. I KNEW WE
HADN'T GONE FAR ENOUGH.
- ( all scream )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- WHO WAS THAT?
- WELL, WHOEVER IT WAS,
THEY'RE FAST.
I CAN'T EVEN SENSE
THEIR PRESENCE ANYMORE.
- BUT WHAT COULD THIS MEAN?
- LULLABY...
- ( crowd gasps, murmurs )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( groans )
WE DID ALL THAT WORK
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN
TAKE THE REWARD.
- BUT THINK ABOUT HOW HAPPY
YOU MADE HIM, LUCY.
DON'T GET DISCOURAGED.
I'M SURE YOU'LL HAVE BETTER LUCK
ON YOUR NEXT MISSION.
- YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT, MIRAJANE.
- ( giggles )
SO, WHAT KIND OF COSTUME
ARE YOU GONNA
WEAR NEXT TIME?
- THAT'S NOT LIKE MY THING,
YOU KNOW!
- Lucy: LOOK, I WASN'T
TRYING TO START SOME
COSTUME-WEARING THING.
- OH, I KNOW.
HOW ABOUT A SWIMSUIT
WITH CUTE LITTLE BUNNY EARS
AND A TAIL?
- Lucy: YOU'RE NOT
HELPING ME OUT HERE, MIRA.