[NARRATOR] The wizards
of Fairy Tail have fought
a long and difficult battle
against the demons of Tartaros,
eventually defeating all
but Kyoka and Mard Geer.
The situation has been
complicated however,
by the appearance of
Acnologia and Igneel,
who are now engaged
in a ferocious duel.
[ACNOLOGIA growls]
[IGNEEL roars]
[MARD GEER]
Curse of Thorns.
[NATSU grunting]
[MARD GEER gasps]
How could he dodge a curse
that he's never seen before?
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon...
Iron Fist!
[NARRATOR] As Natsu fights
to steal the book of E.N.D,
Kyoka takes on her true
form and Body Links
to the Faces'
activation Lacrima.
Offering her life to
speed their detonation.
Empowered by her
transformation,
she bears down on Erza
with a sinister zeal.
[HAPPY] Did she say
she's using Body Link?
So that means...
she's a part of it?
Why would she do that?
They must've wanted the Faces'
detonation accelerated.
[KYOKA] I just made
things very easy for you.
If you kill me, then you
will stop the Faces.
[KYOKA]
Though it really doesn't matter,
because I'll die either way.
[ERZA] Well you certainly
are sure of yourself.
But have you ever even
considered the possibility
that you could lose?
[KYOKA]
No need.
For I have something you don't.
I am Kyoka, Goddess
of the Slave Planet.
[ERZA gasps]
And now I embrace my
true Etherious Form!
What?
Uh!
[ERZA gasping]
No, Erza!
She broke her armor with
nothing but those talons.
That's the way, Kyoka!
Keep on swipin'!
Phoo, Can't even think
of a starting bid
for how much you're
worth in that form.
That lady's real strong.
But Erza'll win, right?
[MINERVA (NEO)]
This i s bad.
And we're running out of time.
[panting]
[yells]
Uh, oh!
Doesn't look like we'll be
getting 30 minutes after all.
At this rate, we won't
even get five.
This is scary.
Tartaros doesn't
have to defeat us.
They only have to wait us out.
Take her down! Quickly!
I intend to.
[yells]
I'm out of your league
now, human. Back down!
Has she grown stronger still?
[KYOKA] Yes. And I
will continue to do so.
This constant,
inexorable strengthening
is the nature of my curse.
[ERZA growls]
My power waxes like
an everlasting moon.
If that's the truth, she's
been toying with us till now.
It seems that curses truly
are superior to magic.
[ERZA yells]
Now that I'm linked to
the activation lacrima,
I've nothing to fear.
I'll surely defeat you.
But my life is forfeit,
regardless.
Why's that?!
[KYOKA]
It's the price I chose to pay.
[KYOKA] One I would gladly pay
again to bring back E.N.D!
I'll do anything to ensure
our return to Zeref!
She's breaking that armor, too!
Such incredible power!
[ERZA]
I don't understand it.
Why's this something
you'd die for?!
Because it's our destiny!
Ha!
Our maker created
us for one reason.
To be by his side as he ushers
in a new age of despair!
How frightened you
must be to know
that your existence is
devoid of any purpose.
We do not suffer from
such existential woes.
Our maker made
his reasons clear.
And what were those?
Did he create you just to die?
How can you know victory when
you've thrown your life away?
Be silent!
[ERZA groaning]
What is she doing?!
[KYOKA yelling]
[PANTHERLILY, HAPPY scream]
[FROSCH, LECTOR scream]
[screaming]
[groaning]
[ALL screaming]
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[IGNEEL]
Come then, and do your worst!
Looks intense.
And it hasn't even hit us yet.
[JET]
Good point.
Run!
[ELFMAN grunts]
We need to take cover!
[ELFMAN]
I've got you!
[LISANNA]
It's so hot!
What do we do?!
[LUMMYS laughing]
[JET]
Well, at least they're gone.
[DROY]
Yeah, and good riddance to 'em!
[LUMMYS scream]
[DROY]
This is it!
We're finally done for!
Don't you go and
give up on me now!
[CANA]
Listen up!
Everybody needs to take
the nearest cover
they can immediately!
[ALL grunt]
[MACAO]
Here it comes!
[REEDUS] At this rate
we'll be blown away!
They've been going
at it for a while now.
And neither one shows
any signs of stopping.
[IGNEEL] I've been fighting
since you were a pup!
Incoming. Get down!
[WAKABA] What the heck
are they doin' now?
[MACAO] Why don't'cha poke your
head out and let us know?
[CANA] There's nothing we
can do but watch and endure.
This fight is way beyond us.
Thought things were
gettin' crazy before.
Natsu.
Don't know where
he went, do ya?
No, I don't. But...
I know that he's fine.
[ALL gasp]
I can feel it.
I actually believe that,
comin' from you.
So, look, for the time being,
we need to focus on
gettin' him a cure.
[MARD GEER] The flames you wield
bear the scent of that dragon.
I guess it must
run in the family.
[NATSU grunting]
[IGNEEL] Make sure you get
a good look at that guy.
See that book?
That's the Book of E.N.D!
Steal that book.
Because you're the only
one who can, Natsu.
Now, listen.
You are not to open
or destroy that book,
under any circumstances.
Just take it. You understand?
For payment, I will tell you
everything you wish to know.
I'm gonna take
that book o'yours.
Ya hear?
[MARD GEER]
Hmph.
[NATSU]
I promised my dad I would.
[ERZA groaning]
[ERZA]
Why... can't I move?
That looks painful.
And it can't help that I've
roughed up your little nerves.
I could torture you
with a feather now.
Not that I plan to.
[BOTH groaning]
Must... hold on!
Can't give in to the pain!
It hurts!
I... don't think I can take it.
[MINERVA (NEO) groaning]
Some of my excess power
seems to have afflicted
your comrades, Erza.
Isn't that interesting?
[exhales]
[ERZA groaning, screams]
It feels like I'm being
stabbed from all over.
Even making the
slightest of movements
causes my entire body
to be wracked with pain!
I'm feel like I'm gonna die.
I feel the same, bud.
But Erza's got it worse,
so hang in there for her.
[ERZA groaning]
You must endure it.
Don't let her win.
[ERZA groaning]
[ERZA screams]
You've gotta keep fighting!
That demon.
This sure does
take me back, Erza.
To the torch-lit
dungeon where we met.
[ERZA groaning]
But this armor...
it's wrong!
Lose it!
I want you just as vulnerable
now as you were then.
Leave her alone!
Come on, Erza.
You're all we have.
After everything, don't
let it end like this.
[KYOKA] My final act in this
world will be to torture you.
One last time.
I'll take everything from
you except for your terror.
Beginning with your sight.
[laughs]
Please, no more!
[KYOKA]
Next, your sense of touch.
Taste.
Smell.
You've already won!
Don't do this!
You're gonna kill her!
[KYOKA]
One sense left, Erza.
These will be the last
words you ever hear.
[KYOKA]
Ha, ha! You fought for nothing!
Perhaps you stood a
chance against us once,
but even if you did,
you've lost it!
I die knowing your
kind is doomed!
No way. It's not true.
[KYOKA]
But you, I'll leave alive.
I'll tell the Underworld King
to make you his plaything.
He'll do it, as a favor to me.
He'll make you suffer till
you beg him for death.
[KYOKA]
Day after day. Piece by piece.
He will dismember you.
Tear you asunder, body and soul.
I must confess, I envy him.
Ha, ha. Come now.
Why the silent treatment?
It's almost like you can't
hear a word I'm saying!
[KYOKA laughs]
I may be blind...
[gasps]
But I can still... see you.
You can strip me bare.
Break my armor, my senses.
[KYOKA]
Uh.
[ERZA] But there's a light
you'll never take from me.
[ERZA grunts, pants]
No way. She's back on her feet.
But how does she know what
to do without any senses?
You're beaten. Lay down.
[ERZA]
Sight. Sound.
These are luxuries, both.
All that's needed
is the light within.
You would understand
that if you had one.
It would've led you to
protect your comrades!
[ERZA yells]
[KYOKA groans]
[ERZA] You were created
to live in darkness!
With pain your only guide,
it's you who must be frightened!
And what a tragic
creature you are.
For you've never known
the light you lack.
Impossible.
You shouldn't be able
to sense anything!
You always find
a way, don't you?
[IGNEEL, ACNOLOGIA roar]
Did they just crash?
I think one dragged
the other down.
Igneel and Acnologia
disappeared.
But where did they go?
[GAJEEL]
Uh?
What's the matter, Gajeel?
[GAJEEL]
There's something beneath us.
[LEVY]
Not the dragons.
I think it is. They must'a
taken the fight below.
What?
Ground's about to
get real unstable.
[ELFMAN] Something tells me
this isn't an earthquake.
You don't think that--
I mean, we saw 'em go down.
On the plus side,
at least we don't have to worry
about getting burnt alive now.
Don't count on it.
I can feel the heat from here.
Nobody's safe. Not while
they're still fighting.
[ROMEO]
Hey, dad?
[MACAO]
I'm here.
[WAKABA]
Yeah, for now at least.
This shaking... What is it?
Could it have to do with th--
[ALL yelp]
Everyone grab onto
whatever you can find!
[WAKABA, ROMEO gasp]
[CANA] We just can't catch
a friggin' break, can we?!
[ROMEO] Dad, you're
on the wrong side!
[MACAO]
Don't worry 'bout me, I'm fine!
[IGNEEL roars]
Ah, you're kiddin' me!
[LUCY, JUVIA, LEVY gasp]
[NATSU] Sounds like Dad
and old Dark Wings
are really gettin' into it.
I'm growing rather weary
of all this chaos.
And I'm gettin' tired
of hearin' you act
like you're above it all!
[KYOKA]
This can't be real.
I've robbed her of almost
every sense she has.
Not to mention,
she should still be writhing
in agony from my curse!
[ERZA yells]
Ah!
There's no possible way
you can see where I stand!
Nor can you track me through
the sound of my voice!
[KYOKA]
So how are you finding me?
This is strange.
Perhaps this means that there
really is a sixth sense.
Maybe losing her other senses
helped that one to pop up!
Hey, I bet you can
do the same thing
if ya lemme blindfold
you n' stuff your ears!
Oh. Yeah!
You guys might be right,
but I'm pretty sure
you're overthinkin' it.
[ERZA growls]
It's 'Cause she's Erza!
[ALL]
That is a good point.
--[ERZA grunts]
--[KYOKA groans]
I'll destroy all of you!
The countdown.
Quick, Erza!
You've gotta stop it!
It's no use!
She still can't hear!
[KYOKA yells]
[ERZA groaning]
[ERZA screams]
Erza, no!
[KYOKA] You dare believe that
a lowly human such as you
can stand against a demon of
the Books of Zeref and live?
I will teach you your place!
[ERZA gasping]
This is dire! Erza's been cursed
to feel the pain of every
single blow a thousand-fold!
I don't know howmmuch more
of this she can withstand.
Not to mention Kyoka's
getting stronger
with every passing second.
[KYOKA]
How...?
How is she not
crippled by the pain?
[KYOKA]
Why is she not cowering in fear?
[KYOKA screams]
[KYOKA]
She's too strong!
She did it!
Forty seconds!
We gotta move fast!
Finish her off
while you still can!
[MINERVA (NEO) grunts]
Come on!
[HAPPY]
Erza!
[MINERVA (NEO) grunts]
[panting]
[MINERVA (NEO)]
She's smiling.
Whoopididoo! We did it!
Every last one of those
Faces has blown!
[ERZA gasping]
[LECTOR, FROSCH whimper]
[FRANMALTH]
We win, you lose! This is it!
The end of all you
worthless wizards!
Tartaros' wish is
finally comin' true!
[MIRAJANE]
In a world without magic...
What are we?
[LUCY] Mard Geer and Natsu
renew their fight in earnest.
Vying for custody of
the book of E.N.D.
At first, Mard Geer
has the upper hand,
but he's interrupted by the
arrival of Sting and Rogue.
Both intent on finishing
what they started.
Natsu takes heart in the
presence of these new allies.
But it seems despair is always
lurking in the shadows.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
The Girl in the Crystal."
The end is nigh.