[NARRATOR] The fighting between
Natsu and Mard Geer intensifies.
As does the bombastic battle
between Igneel and Acnologia.
[NARRATOR] Natsu receives
some timely reinforcement
from Sting and Rogue.
Together, the Dragon Slayers
launch a three pronged assault
against The King
of the Underworld.
Now! Lightning Flame
Dragon Firing Hammer!
[NATSU gasps]
[NARRATOR] Newly reunited
with Lucy and the others,
Wendy and company reveal
that the threat of Face
is far greater than they
had previously assumed.
In fact, the anti-magic pulse
bombs number in the thousands.
The group decides that their
best course of action
would be to tell the
wizards of other guilds
what's been happening,
and seek their assistance.
But this plan is hindered
by the short range of
Warren's telepathy.
Just as the group
begins to despair
that there is nothing they can
do to stop the Face's countdown,
Makarov intervenes.
[MAKAROV] We can use Fairy
Tail's ultimate weapon:
The Lumen Histoire.
[LUCY]
The Lumen Histoire?
[WENDY]
I've never heard of it.
We don't have time for me
to explain everything.
All of you should meet me
at the guild, right now.
[LUCY] Some of us are still
fighting. Can't we help them?
[DROY]
What guild?
I mean, there's
nothing left of it.
Don't mention that.
[ELFMAN grunts]
I'm underneath the
guild. Get moving!
[LUCY] Whatever he's talking
about, he sounds serious.
[WENDY]
Then let's be quick.
I won't be coming.
He wanted all of us!
Why would you stay?
What do you think you're doing?
[ELFMAN] Why'd you
have to come here?
Now I can't let you leave!
This is what I have to do!
[CANA]
Is it a bomb?
[ELFMAN]
This is goodbye!
This is the end for Fairy Tail!
[CANA]
Help!
[ELFMAN grunts]
[CANA] Is he under some
kind of spell? What do I do?
I do not blame you for
the guild's destruction,
nor should anybody else.
[DROY]
Right! That isn't on you, man.
It was Tartaros!
[LISANNA]
You did it for me!
[JET]
Don't beat yourself up.
I bet I'd've done the same
thing if they'd taken Levy.
That's nice of you, but still.
[MAKAROV]
I understand.
Do what you think is right.
But master...
We can't just leave him
here all by himself!
[MAKAROV]
You come, too.
[gasps]
[DORANBOLT]
Private telepathy?
Why? I'm not part of your guild.
[MAKAROV] No, but I'm
in need of your power.
[DORANBOLT]
For what?
[MAKAROV] The Lumen Histoire is
the guild's greatest secret.
Should we prevail,
I'll need you to
erase its existence
from everyone's memory.
[DORANBOLT]
I see.
You're asking me to erase
my own memories, too.
[MAKAROV] I am. But I'm certain
you would do so regardless.
[LUCY]
Let's get moving.
[LISANNA] Are you sure you
won't change your mind?
[ELFMAN]
Yeah.
Uh? You're coming with
us though, right?
Oh, uh. Yeah, sure.
[DORANBOLT]
I don't get it.
What could this
Lumen Histoire be?
C'mon guys.
The sooner we can get outta
their range, the better.
Yeah man, I hear ya on that.
So do I.
That fight's a lot bigger
than any human could handle.
I remember the dragons that
came out of the Eclipse.
They were almost unstoppable.
And it looks like these
dragons are even stronger.
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
What's he doing?
He's leading the other one off!
[ACNOLOGIA]
You won't escape from me.
[IGNEEL] I'm not fleeing.
Nor will I allow you to.
At this height, I don't
have to hold back.
Prepare to face judgment
for your crimes.
Brave words, but empty.
They come from the mouth
of one soon to be dead.
Do your worst.
He's just sittin' there.
Even against three
of us, he seems bored.
[STING]
Hey, Natsu. You all right?
[NATSU]
Course I am!
Been hurt worse by a
friggin' Lucy Kick.
Uh... Don't tell her though.
[ROGUE] Sounds like you're
good to keep fighting.
Damn straight.
No slowin' me down.
'Specially not when I
got a contest to win.
[STING, ROGUE] Is that really
why you're so fired up?!
It'll be a cold day in hell
when I lose to you guys.
[MARD GEER]
Hmph.
Kyoka. What's taking so long?
Detonate the Faces at once.
[KYOKA] If Lord Zeref
requires my death, so be it!
[FRANMALTH]
On the left side of the ring,
we have Kyoka, Goddess
of the Slave Planet!
She's got eyes like a hawk
and a reach as far as
those talons can grow!
The pride of a Falcon!
The hunger of--!
[PANTHERLILY]
Enough!
Our time is short.
We can count ourselves defeated
if that timer runs down.
Yeah Erza! We're all
countin' on you!
[ERZA]
Right. I won't let you down.
Where's Natsu?
Sure hope he's okay.
How frightened you
must be to know
that your existence is
devoid of any purpose.
We do not suffer from
such existential woes.
Our maker made
his reasons clear.
And what were those?!
Did he create you just to die?!
How can you know victory when
you've thrown your life away?!
Be silent!
[ERZA groaning]
[KYOKA growls]
What is she doing?
[KYOKA yells]
[PANTHERLILY, HAPPY scream]
[FROSCH, LECTOR scream]
[MINERVA (NEO) screams]
[MIRAJANE whimpers]
[ALL screaming]
[sighs] Well, so it goes.
Kyoka's become so preoccupied
with slaughtering your comrades
that she's forgotten my voice.
But I suppose she's earned
this last bit of fun.
So tell me,
why do you wanna erase
all magic, anyway?
What do you stand
to gain from that?
Don't you know?
I'd think you could've
put it together.
That tome your friend wants
to steal contains E.N.D,
and its magic that seals him.
You wanna bust him out.
Now you see.
Despite how it may appear,
I'm not our leader.
That title belongs to E.N.D.
There are none among us
who can rival his strength.
Once E.N.D. has
finally been released,
we can fulfill our true
purpose, and return to Zeref.
Makes zero sense to me.
Why would you wait?
If you want to see
Zeref so badly,
why wouldn't you just
do it on your own?
[MARD GEER]
Hmph.
Though raised by dragons,
sadly, you're still only human.
This is likely beyond
your comprehension.
[NATSU]
Get to the point!
Have you ever stopped to
consider Zeref's reason
for creating my kind?
Perhaps you merely thought
of us as his... playthings.
[MARD GEER] You've doubtless
heard my cohorts describe
the call of Zeref. The
urge to return to him.
But none among them
ever questioned it.
When we find Zeref,
what would he have us do?
Why were we endowed
with this instinct?
All we do, we do
for Our Lord Zeref!
[MARD GEER] It's an absolute
command, etched into our genes.
We must see Zeref.
We must return to Zeref.
We must do all for Zeref.
I alone have come to realize
that in truth he
made us to give him
the one thing of which
he's been deprived.
[NATSU growls]
Hmph.
[MARD GEER]
Over the centuries,
Zeref grew to revile
his immortality.
He yearned for death.
[MARD GEER] But death
would not come on its own.
So Zeref strove to make a being
strong enough to slay him.
[MARD GEER] It took him many
years to refine his work.
Dozens of creations.
Before he made one
worthy of the task.
[NATSU gasps]
[MARD GEER] That being:
his masterpiece is E.N.D.
But E.N.D. was prevented
from fulfilling his purpose.
Locked back inside his book.
[MARD GEER] He is held
there by a magic seal.
One too powerful for any curse
or spell in this world to break.
Or so I thought.
That was before I learned
about the Faces.
A magic seal can't exist
in a world without magic.
Very soon, he will be free.
Then, side by side,
we'll slay Zeref.
This is the mission we
were created to fulfill.
It shall be an exquisite
pleasure to carry it out.
All this time, you've
been wanting to kill Zeref?
The hell does that have to do
with the rest of us humans?
Couldn't you just
leave us out of it?
When one is on his way to
an important destination,
he doesn't timidly avoid
the weeds in his path:
he tramples them.
[STING]
Oh, yeah?
Uh!
[STING, ROGUE scream]
Sting, Rogue! Hang in there!
Natsu!
[ROGUE groaning]
[NATSU]
What the heck is that thing?!
This is a Prison Flower.
Fresh from the Underworld.
Damn! It won't budge!
[STING]
Come on, man!
Use your fire!
[NATSU]
Ah! Crap, I'm stuck.
It froze.
[MARD GEER gasping]
[STING, ROGUE]
Uh.
My scarf. I thought
I'd lost it for good.
[GRAY]
You're welcome.
[NATSU]
Uh?
If it means so much to you,
then take better care of it.
[NATSU]
Will do.
Thanks for the save!
He has such power.
When did you freeze his arm?!
[MARD GEER]
This magic... Who are you?
This face is the last thing
you're ever gonna see.
Because you're the thing I slay.
When did you freeze his arm?!
[MARD GEER]
This magic... Who are you?
This face is the last
thing you're ever gonna see.
Because you're the thing I slay.
[MARD GEER]
You're a Demon Slayer?
[STING]
He's a what?
[ROGUE] If the title's
as simple as ours,
then he's exactly what
we need right now.
Mard Geer's scared.
I've come here on
behalf of the fallen.
[GRAY yells]
[MARD GEER]
This magic... It's Silver's!
I never had a doubt that he
would betray us eventually,
but I couldn't have suspected
it would happen like this.
What poetic circumstance! Fate
can be quite amusing, can't it?
He froze every thorn.
Almost effortlessly!
[STING]
Incredible.
[MARD GEER yells]
I don't really see
how fate's to blame
for any of the crap
you've been pullin'.
And there ain't a damn thing
about it I find "amusing"!
My old man sends his regards.
Old man?
[GRAY] I've come to
finish what he started!
[MARD GEER screams]
[STING, ROGUE]
Uh...
You screwed with
the wrong family!
[GRAY]
Ice Demon: Zero Long Sword!
[GRAY growls]
[DEMON A grunts]
[GRAY groans]
[STING]
Gray! No!
Well, that was timely.
He came from that flower.
[sniffs] Wait a sec.
I know that smell.
There's no way.
[ROGUE whimpers]
The man who once
stood at the helm
of the strongest
guild in this world.
But now, he's shed his humanity,
and become something
more powerful.
You knew him as... Jiemma.
Our master.
[NATSU]
It's really him.
Those monsters...
they turned him into a demon.
Just like they
did to Minerva.
Though it does seem
to suit him better.
[JIEMMA]
Of course it does.
Power's always suited me.
That's why I demanded
to be transformed.
And look at me now.
The mightiest demon
that's ever existed.
Was it worth it?
Abandoning your humanity
just for power?
The man's lost
his friggin' mind.
My newest servant
is more powerful
than any of the
Nine Demon Gates.
But I suppose that you and
he are already familiar.
[JIEMMA]
My power stuns the heavens.
I have no master,
for I have no equal!
No one calls me servant!
Do you hear me?!
I'll demolish these
insects first.
But after that,
I'll come for you!
[MARD GEER]
Heh.
[JIEMMA yells]
You can't scare me!
[STING, ROGUE gasp]
[NATSU] Don't let this jerkwad
freakshow get under your skin!
Keep fighting! [yells]
[JIEMMA]
I've no business with you.
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU yelps]
[STING]
Natsu! [growls]
[JIEMMA]
There! You understand now?
Stay down like a good bug.
[ROGUE yelling]
[STING]
You're gonna pay for that!
[JIEMMA grunts]
[STING, ROGUE groan]
[JIEMMA]
You're pathetic! Feeble!
Unworthy to oppose me.
You claim to be
raised by dragons.
Are you sure they
weren't just lizards?
I hate this guy.
[JIEMMA]
Sting.
Rogue.
I've been waiting
for this moment
for quite a long time now.
For the chance
to end your lives.
Ah, crap! Are they okay?!
[STING]
We aren't scared.
[ROGUE]
And we won't stop!
[JIEMMA]
Hm?
[STING, ROGUE yell]
Leave this guy to us, Natsu!
You focus on Mard Geer!
[JIEMMA]
There's a difference
between bravery and
arrogance, lizard boys.
Come on! I'll show you!
He called us out. Are you ready?
Sure am.
Let's make this
quick and get home.
I wanna show M'lady what
we've done with the place.
[MARD GEER chuckles]
[STING, ROGUE grunting]
[STING, ROGUE groaning]
Strong, isn't he?
Though I'll have to do something
about that arrogant streak.
[GRAY]
This is the end of the line.
There's nobody left
to protect you.
[MARD GEER] And you think
I require protection?
You're a fool if you believe
that little power of yours
will have any effect on me.
Not after I've taken
on my Etherious form.
He's changing.
[MARD GEER] E.N.D. is about
to rise from a slumber
lasting 400 years.
The time has come for
me to rise as well.
[GRAY, NATSU gasp]
[MARD GEER] Behold.
I am Mard Geer Tartaros.
Absolute Demon, and
King of the Underworld!
[GRAY]
Natsu--
[NATSU]
Don't say it, I know.
We don't care what you
call yourself king of.
We're gonna take you out!
[MARD GEER]
Come. Give me your all.
For this battle
shall be your last.
[LUCY] In his blind pursuit
of greater strength,
Jiemma has renounced his
humanity and become a demon.
The Twin Dragons, having
rejected his cruel philosophy,
stand as comrades against
their former master.
Mard Geer Tartaros,
the Absolute Demon,
now bears down on
Natsu and Gray.
Even with Gray's new powers,
they'll be hard
pressed to defeat him
now that he's taken
on his true form.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Memento Mori."
Keep fighting. The
future's at stake.