Listen up, it's Code Blue.
I just hit a snag here.
[ALL]
Huh?
[GRAY]
No, no. Not that kind.
Mm-hmm.
Hell if I know.
You should probably
ask him yourself.
Yeah.
All that stuff on him
just faded away.
Uh.
Hold it up to your ear, man.
What's it supposed to do?
[ERZA]
Natsu. This is you, right?
[NATSU gasps]
[GRAY]
Mh-hm.
Congratulations. Your antics
blew Gray's covert operation.
What're you tryin'
to say, Erza?
I'm a spy. Give me some credit.
You really think I would join
some creepy Zeref cult?
It's time to get moving.
We'll explain everything
on the way.
[BOTH gasp]
[ERZA]
Several months ago,
Jellal asked me to do a
favor for Crime Sorcière.
I was to investigate Avatar.
Discover their
connection to Zeref.
[ERZA]
The trail grew cold,
but I'd just happened
to reconnect with Gray.
It ended up being a lucky break.
How are we still hearing her?
We've got a portable
communication lacrima.
Anyway, after our last fight,
this pattern broke
out all over me,
so I went to Porlyusica
to see if she could help.
As you saw, now I'm able to
make it appear and disappear
whenever I want.
So, after we had discussed
our current situations,
it was obvious we needed to come
up with a plan to work together.
It was fate.
Of course, I would
do anything for Erza.
Not only that,
I wanted to get my hands
on the Book of E.N.D.
My dad's last wish was
for me to destroy it.
Yeah, okay. But why didn't
you tell Juvia about this?
She's literally worried sick!
[ERZA]
I know.
It's because I asked him
to keep it a secret.
A covert mission such as this
needs to be kept confidential.
The more people that
are made aware of it,
the more likely it is to fail.
And also, mere
knowledge of the plan
can put someone in danger.
So you kept her in the dark
for her protection, huh?
Still a crappy thing to do!
I feel bad for what Juvia's
had to go through.
And unfortunately for all of us,
the mission has
lasted much longer
than I'd first anticipated.
The situation has
changed dramatically.
It started out as a
routine investigation.
But then, we learned of their
diabolical "purification plan."
[GRAY] Avatar's gonna try
to wipe out an entire city
because they think
it'll summon Zeref.
They actually believe the site
of concentrated death like that
will attract their "Dark Lord."
[gasps]
It's up to us to stop
that from happening,
no matter what it takes.
Why didn't you guys just wipe
'em out in the very beginning?
Somethin' like that would
be easy for you and Erza!
You'd think, but you'd be wrong.
After a little digging,
we found out
Avatar is a way bigger
organization than we'd thought.
I was able to infiltrate
to some degree,
but only inside a single branch.
Each one is kept separate
and has limited contact
with the main headquarters.
That left no room for error.
But we still couldn't let
their plan come to fruition.
Our only hope to stop
it from happening
was to wait until today.
That's right.
The day all the branches will
be gathered in one place.
Before they kill anyone,
we'll destroy them.
Hey, Lucy. Sorry about all
that stuff I said earlier.
But I knew they were watching me
and I couldn't risk blowing
my cover right then.
It's fine.
I guess I should apologize
for slapping you like that.
Well, the maid outfit made it
a little better, to be honest.
I'm not so sure I needed
to know that part.
[GRAY] You guys are
my friends for life,
and nothin's ever
gonna change that.
I feel the same way!
That makes things
a whole lot easier!
We can wreck their
stupid plan in no time
if all of us work together!
Right!
I'm totally in it to win it!
You sure about that?
It wasn't our intention to drag
you into the fight with us.
If you weren't gonna
drag us into it,
then we just have to drag you!
It's been way too long
since Fairy Tail's strongest
team kicked some butts!
There's only one thing to say
at a time like this, right?
[ALL]
I'm fired up now!
Gray and Gomon aren't here
with us. Why is that?
They're dealing with
the prisoners?
That makes sense for Gomon.
But what about Gray?
It's fishy.
[BRIAR]
Calm down, Bottom Lashes.
Because at this point,
none of it matters.
[JEROME]
"Bottom Lashes"?
[BRIAR] Look, do you see
what's happening here?
Every member of every
secret branch in Fiore
has gathered together for
the Purification Plan.
So even if the stripping
iceman or the council
decides to try to stop us,
they wouldn't have
a snowball's chance
against all of our
true believers.
Yes. Very good point.
[JEROME] I could live
with "Bottom Lashes."
This is gonna be so much fun!
I'm ready to purify!
[D-6 grunts]
We're, like, really
gonna meet Zeref!
[ARLOCK] Now, we shall
execute our Purification Plan!
Malba will be sacrificed!
[AVATAR yells]
[ARLOCK] This city is
a trove of innocence.
Thirty thousand lives
abuzz with excitement,
oblivious to what
terror awaits them.
The purity of the
souls we harvest today
will prove to be irresistible
for our Dark Lord Zeref!
He will join our feast!
[AVATAR]
Yeah!
[ARLOCK] We offer this
bounty of 30,000 lives
so he may cleanse the world
and remake it in his image!
Let us purify every
soul in the city!
Charge!
[AVATAR yelling]
Do these fools think they
can stand in our way?
They'll die first, in the
name of our dark Lord Zeref!
We'll purify every last one!
[AVATAR shouting]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
There ain't no way you meatheads
are gonna get past us!
Step on up and I'll roast ya!
So, did you get stronger
this last year too, or what?
Just watch me, ol' buddy.
It'll be pretty obvious.
Check this out, guys!
Here goes! Open!
Gate of the Golden Bull!
Taurus!
I'm so ready to moo-ve!
Did somebody order beefcake?
[LUCY]
Plus... Star Dress!
In cow-girl style!
Moo! Let's round 'em up!
Fullbuster! I knew it!
These infidels will not hinder
our plan for purification!
Let us dispose of them!
I'm sorry, sir,
but the enemy is attacking
from the rear as well!
We're losing soldiers
as we speak!
Say what? The Council's
army is already here?
[AVATAR D]
Uh, not exactly, sir.
[AVATAR screams]
[AVATAR D]
It's just one person!
Aw, yeah!
Been a while since we've
had this kinda party!
We're gonna have
to do it up right.
This really brings back
some memories, huh?
Aye!
You want purification?
We'll start with you!
[NATSU]
Let's go!
Come on!
[AVATAR yelling]
[yells]
[AVATAR screams]
Ow, wow! They tanned
their hides!
Let's show 'em what we've got!
Earth Wave!
[TAURUS]
Moo!
Now, my brothers!
Take her down!
[ALL yelling]
Lucy!
You don't have to worry
about little ol' me!
'Cause in this outfit....
...I can deal with
a lot of bull!
[chuckles]
[LUCY gasps]
[yells]
WTF? They're animals!
They're super scary
creatures! Like monsters!
No offense, but you need
to do some serious work
to strengthen your vocabulary.
I suppose this means we'll have
to purify them ourselves.
[JEROME] Allow me to handle the
enemy attacking from the rear.
The traitor and his
friends are all yours.
[BRIAR] Yes, that sounds
like a perfect plan to me.
It's time these sewer rats
learned the true
horrors of black magic.
This lone fighter is fearsome.
A worthy opponent.
However, this dark sword I wield
was forged in forbidden magic.
And with this blade,
I shall end them.
All right, brothers! Give her
a taste of our magic power!
[ERZA]
Requip!
My Ataraxia Armor!
Soaring blades!
[AVATAR B]
What's happening?
[AVATAR C]
Her swords can fly!
It's like they have a
mind of their own!
Do you still intend to fight me?
[AVATAR whimpering]
Both beautiful and deadly.
Yeah, Jerome is here!
No wizard stands a chance
against the Dark Sword!
You will not disrupt
our sacred plan!
[gasps]
My Dark Sword's magic energy
corrodes everything it strikes.
Be it steel or flesh.
You must be very proud.
[JEROME gasps]
But my sword cuts
without striking.
Summon all your bravery.
[BRIAR]
Gray!
[GRAY]
Briar!
How dare you
betray us like this!
You... You played us for fools!
All this time you spent with
us was a lie, wasn't it?
Yeah, of course
it was, you idiot!
I'm not the kinda guy
who would associate
with a bunch of
murderers like you!
It's purification! Not murder!
And once it's been completed,
Zeref will be among us again!
Tell me, your brave words
about the Book of E.N.D.,
were they just lies as well?
I hate to disappoint ya,
but that stuff was mostly true!
Someday, I will destroy E.N.D.
And when I do, it's
gonna be on my terms.
In a way that'll make
my old man proud.
[TAURUS]
Moo! I'll handle this crew!
Ah! Moo!
[groans]
Uh, I need a second or two.
What's the matter?
You sound like you're
about to start bawling.
Ugh. My stomachs feel
like they're gonna spew.
It's not a moo-d.
I can't fight anymore.
Huh?! Are you kidding me?
[stomach grumbles]
What the--?
Aw, man. Not this again.
[MARY laughs]
[LUCY gasps]
[MARY] You remember my
Virus spell, don't you?
It's Black Magic that can
destroy your frail little body.
[LUCY groaning]
This particular one I'm using
goes straight for the gut.
Yep.
You'd better run and
find a potty soon,
or there's gonna be
an awful mess!
Ugh. Your magic
is freakin' nasty.
Bubble guts.
I'm sorry, Miss Lucy.
But I'm just about to turn
into a fertilizer factory!
OMG, Gray's old
friends are pathetic.
I totally don't get how
Fairy Tail was ever, like,
famous n' stuff.
You guys are so weak,
it's actually kinda hilarious!
[LUCY]
No. You're wrong.
I'm fine. I can handle this.
You should probably know
that my Virus magic
can target any part of your
body I feel like messing with.
Like, if I wanted to,
I could scramble your
brains like an egg.
[gasps]
[HAPPY]
Huh?
[TAURUS]
Moo?
Uh.
Hold on. My stomach just stopped
hurting all of a sudden.
I feel way better!
The pain udderly disappeared!
I got here just in time.
Status ailments are nullified
and immunity enchantment
is activated.
Whatever spells you have
for making people sick
are not gonna work
against my sky magic.
Wendy, it's you!
There's an army of
robe-wearing goons.
You came with her?
How'd you know I'd be here?
Lucy, look behind you!
[screams]
It's payback time!
How 'bout a tummy ache?
Lucy Gut Punch!
[MARY]
Owie!
Ugh. Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Lame. I'm sorry, Grandfather.
What an amazing move, Lucy!
"Lucy Gut Punch." Heh.
I think the most amazing
part about all of that
was your timing, Wendy.
Yeah, how come you two
just showed up here, anyway?
Actually...
If there's one thing
I can't stand, it's a rat!
Hear me?
There's your split-image magic.
I was waitin' for that trick.
I am "Angry Briar!"
And I am "Smiling Briar."
I'm "Sorrowful Briar."
And I'm simply "Loving Briar."
I've never been so
furious in my life!
I find it so funny.
If you think you can beat
us with such weak power,
you must be joking.
It makes me sad. You're so cold.
You've left me with no
other choice but to kill you.
Too bad.
You know, Gray,
I actually let myself
fall a teensy little
bit in love with you.
Say wha--?
[JUVIA] I knew I sensed
the familiar threat
of another woman
trying to steal my man.
[GRAY yelps]
What the heck are you
doing all the way out here?
I'm giving this floozy the
Water Claw that she deserves!
Owie!
You'll wish you never
hurt Loving Briar!
[laughs]
So cruel, it's
breaking my heart!
[growls]
You're all pissing me off!
I think you need to chill out!
No way!
I can't believe that ice
wizard took out Briar
like it was nothing!
I've been dreaming of you, Gray!
[giggles]
It's been so lonely!
My intuition told me you were
in some serious trouble,
so I rushed here as quickly
as I possibly could!
[GRAY] I wouldn't consider
this trouble, exactly.
How did you know where I was?
Because of Wendy and her
strong sense of smell.
[GRAY]
Look, I'm sorry.
I promise I'll explain
everything later, but now...
[JUVIA]
I know.
...we gotta deal
with these losers.
Of course. Anything for you!
Well, sure seems like Juvia's
back to her old self again.
All thanks to Wendy, that is.
Oh, stop.
Thank you, Wendy!
[TAURUS]
Sorry, ladies,
but there's a stampede of
bad guys comin' our way!
So we all gotta moo-ve!
I'm on it!
Let's go!
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Wave Wind!
[AVATAR screaming]
Is that Dragon Force?
We did a little
training of our own!
She's the coolest ever!
[AVATAR yelling]
The rear forces have been
completely eradicated,
Your Eminence.
And the vanguard can't
advance any farther!
These foes... the magic they
use... it's just too strong.
We'll never defeat them!
The enemy's come
to finish us off!
Ah! This can't be real!
We have over 2,000
fighters on our side!
Yeah, that's true. And there's
only a handful of them!
[NATSU]
Doesn't matter how many you got.
The odds are against you.
'Cause chumps like you'll never
beat Fairy Tail wizards.
[ARLOCK] This is all within
the realm of expectations.
And when Iksatsunagi
begins to tremble
the ground beneath us,
the purification will begin.
Oh, yeah?
How about I make you
tremble instead?
[LUCY] Arlock, the high
priest of Avatar,
summons the
fearsome Iksatsunagi,
god of war and calamity,
to the battlefield.
And once he's arrived,
the real Purification Plan
will come to fruition.
The people flee in
terror at the sight
of the war god's
overwhelming power.
Enraged by Arlock's complete
disregard for human life,
Natsu thinks of his friends
and summons a fiery
attack like only he can!
Next Time: "Ikusatsunagi."
The strength of those bonds
will set evil ablaze!