I think we should camp
here for the night.
I wanna get these guys to a
doctor as soon as possible,
but they need their rest.
[PRECHT]
I told you, I'm fine.
[ZERA] I bet there's not
a doctor around for miles.
I'll be back. I'm going to
gather some water for us.
Please be careful.
[MAVIS]
This is all my fault.
We were fighting wizards.
I should have known my
magic wasn't enough.
I was too proud to admit
we were out of our league.
I chose to stay and fight.
And now my friends
are badly hurt.
I wish I were stronger.
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
Ah!
I'm-- I'm so sorry!
I thought that I was
the only one here!
It's time to get out
of the forest now.
[MAVIS]
Huh?
[splashing]
[ZEREF]
Sorry.
That didn't come out
like it should have.
I meant to say it's time for
me to get out of the forest.
But why?
[gasps]
What's happening to the trees?
This is the fate of every
living thing that I encounter.
They all die.
You killed the forest?
It isn't safe for you
to be near me.
So this is Ankhselam
black magic.
[MAVIS] I've only read
about it in books.
It's a kind of ancient curse.
Some people call it the
"Curse of Contradiction."
The greater the
compassion you have
for the living
beings around you,
the more potent your
release of death energy.
Conversely, if you have no
regard at all for living things,
then you'll release no death
energy into the environment.
[MAVIS]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sure you already
know all that.
It's okay. Your
knowledge is impressive.
You're the only person I've ever
met who understands my curse.
I usually avoid
people at all costs.
I won't risk their lives for
the sake of my loneliness.
Do you live in this forest?
[ZEREF]
No, I try to keep moving.
I want as little contact with
living things as possible.
The less I interact
with them, the better.
Living this way is awful.
It's difficult not to
feel like a villain
when everything I touch dies.
It's very kind of you to
stay and talk with me,
but I don't want
to make you sad.
[MAVIS] I'm sure it
must get lonely for you.
Yes, it can be trying.
Though conversing with
you has made me happier
than I've been in a while.
I can't remember the last time
I spoke with anybody.
But at the same time,
I can't ignore the fact
that simply being in my
presence is dangerous
and the last thing I want
to do is bring you any harm.
I've never wanted to kill
anything in my life.
I should leave you be.
It was never my intention
to frighten you.
What are you doing?
Please stay away from me,
for your own sake!
What is all this?
How can they get so close
without succumbing to my curse?
They all have an
immunity to such things.
What?
This is my magic.
They're incredible.
You can't actually touch them,
though I wish that you could.
It's fine. I can
feel their warmth.
Thank you very much.
[MAVIS] Maybe fate brought you
and me together here today.
Perhaps we were
supposed to meet.
You are a powerful wizard.
That's quite easy to see.
I'd like you to help us.
Please teach my friends
and me how to use magic.
We have a battle to fight.
Right now, we're not strong
enough to beat our opponents.
[ZERA]
Uhh...
Who is this guy?
[MAVIS chuckles]
[gasps]
I don't understand why we
have to meditate so much.
What does that have to do
with magic training?
It's important for building
a good, strong foundation.
The power to use magic must come
both from within and without.
[WARROD]
You're too far away!
[MAVIS] We can't get any
closer to him than this.
Spells are the concentration
and physical release
of the magic power
that we possess,
stored within our bodies.
I got a feeling I don't
have any of that
magical energy junk in me.
Perhaps you don't.
But once you understand
how magic power works,
you'll see that isn't
really a problem.
Let me break it down for you.
Magic power is as vital to a
wizard as the air he breathes.
Without it, we can't
do much at all.
The base substance upon
which magic power is built
is called "ether-nano."
[MAVIS]
Ether-nano?
[ZEREF]
Yes.
It can be found in the
atmosphere around us,
and we have the ability to
absorb it into our bodies.
The next part requires
intense focus,
transforming ether-nano
into magic power.
Meditation is the best way
to draw in ether-nano,
so that's why it's
part of our training.
Did you know any of that?
I've read about some of it
in books, but that's all.
Teacher! I have a question.
You don't have to
raise your hand
like we're students
in a schoolhouse.
Precht is the scariest-looking
student I've ever seen,
especially with that eye patch.
[PRECHT grumbles]
[WARROD chuckles]
I understand the concept
that ether-nano
is the source of a
wizards' magic power.
But does it follow that
if we absorb more of it
from the atmosphere,
then we'll be able to use
more powerful spells?
That's a great question.
Every wizard has a "vessel,"
a limit to their capacity
for magic power
and the amount of ether-nano
they can absorb.
When you use a lot of magic,
you empty your vessel,
but your body continues to draw
in ether-nano on its own.
In a relatively short time,
your vessel will be replenished
and you'll be able
to use spells again
without having to do
anything at all.
Not even meditate.
In short, there's no limit
to the amount of ether-nano
in the atmosphere.
That's the best news
we've had yet!
There's one other very important
element to using magic, though.
[MAVIS]
Oh, really? What is it?
To truly be effective,
it requires more than
absorbing ether-nano
and converting
it into magic power.
There is something else that
you must add to that equation.
It's vital.
I'm referring to the great
power of a wizard's feelings.
The power of feelings?
Yes.
It's almost impossible
to use magic well
without feeding off of
our strongest emotions,
so we've got to be
able to access them.
Looks like we've let the
time get away from us.
I think it would be best
if we call it a night
and begin practical
training in the morning.
Good night.
You have a good night, too.
Well, I have always
wondered how magic worked.
Who is he? And where
did he come from?
Like I said, meditation
is the most efficient way
to absorb ether-nano.
[ZERA, MAVIS gasp]
He's really doing it!
[YURI]
That's amazing!
[PRECHT]
Huh? So, it works.
Well, Precht, it would appear
that you were destined
to be a wizard.
I won't be beat!
Yeah, neither will I!
Let's all try our best!
Yuri, don't you think it's
time to call it a night?
Would you please
stop bothering me?
I'm trying to
meditate over here.
It'll never happen if you
keep trying to force it.
Just open your mind
and let it flow into you.
Screw this! I'm going crazy!
Sittin' still just
ain't my style!
But it only works
if you stay still.
Not for me. I think
I'm an exception.
I'm hyper, so I can
only really focus
when I'm moving around a lot!
Huh. I guess that
is a possibility.
Aw, yeah!
[laughs]
Check it out, you guys!
I'm absorbing it!
That's great...
[PRECHT]
Just shut up and go to sleep.
Do you see it? Look at it!
It's so pretty, right?
Man, I'm glowin' like a firefly!
I'm a wizard! I'm a
real life magic guy!
[PRECHT]
Feelings. Right.
[MAVIS]
Focus my feelings.
That's the part that
I've already mastered.
[MAVIS]
I just need to go deeper.
It's harder than it looks.
How are you doing over there?
[ZERA]
Hm?
Hey, stop that!
Don't watch me!
It blows my concentration!
[gasps]
That's wonderful, Zera!
Can you believe it's working?
Yeah, I'm proud of you!
[growls]
I guess I'm just
not focused enough.
[WARROD]
Tch.
[grumbles]
I've always wanted to
train under a waterfall!
All right! I'll get more
ether-nano than those guys!
They're gonna wish
they had my power!
I want all of it!
[screams]
Uh. Maybe that's too much.
[WARROD grunting]
[chuckles]
[YURI chuckles]
[MAVIS chuckles]
[yells]
[YURI]
All right!
Hey, Precht. Your magic is
really somethin' else, man!
I saw you training earlier
and it blew my mind!
Well, I wish you would
train farther away from me.
Your lightning's
very distracting.
Yeah? You saw it?
My magic's pretty
awesome too, huh?
Stop talking and start the fire.
[YURI chuckles]
I know you were impressed.
Well, how about you, Warrod?
How's your training been going?
[WARROD]
It's goin' all right.
So we're all kickin' butt.
[WARROD] We need some more
firewood. I'll go gather it.
Yeah, you're right.
I'd appreciate it, pal.
Stupid magic.
Oh, thanks, but I
don't need any help.
Come on, Warrod,
you know that branches
pulled right off the tree
are too damp to
use for firewood.
I'll help you gather these dry
ones here on the ground.
I don't get why it always
has to be this way.
I can never keep up.
Those guys beat me every time.
When we try new things, even if
none of us have done it before,
they catch on and surpass me.
And now I'm holding
them back again.
But you don't hold them back.
They were just
saying the opposite
a little while ago, actually.
Were they really?
Yes, sir.
Nice!
Hey, you've been going
at your training nonstop
and I just wanna make sure
you're not pushing
yourself too hard!
I never wanna feel the way
I did back in Magnolia.
None of us want that.
And that's the whole
reason we learned magic
in the first place.
That's not it.
I mean, I don't want Warrod
to rescue me anymore.
[YURI]
He's always been the hero.
Whenever I do something reckless
and get us into trouble,
Warrod steps in to save the day.
Without him, I'd have kicked
the bucket a long time ago,
and I wanna give
the guy a break.
[PRECHT]
That's the truth of the matter.
We are deeply indebted to him.
He's been good to us
for all these years.
I've been tryin' to find a way
to repay him for a while.
Maybe now we finally
have a chance to do it
by protecting him for once!
Protecting me? They said that?
Of course they did.
They're your friends, right?
And remember the last thing
we learned about using magic?
Yeah. To use our feelings.
That's right! Our spells
won't even work without them!
So let's join the others.
I'm getting hungry!
I don't think my magic is meant
to create powerful attacks.
That being said,
I wanna be an asset.
Will you teach me
spells I can use
to support my friends in battle?
Very well.
There's a kind of magic
that suits you better.
One that matches the
color of your soul.
It has a color? Really?
Now that's more like it!
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[rumbling]
Whoa! What is that?
Huh? I have no idea!
Now what's goin' on?
Do you think Warrod's doing
that? Is this his magic?
Well, who else could it be?
Makes sense, right?
It's just like him.
[laughing]
[WARROD]
What an amazing feeling!
Aww. I'm the only one
who hasn't gotten it yet.
It'll happen soon, don't be sad.
It isn't exactly
that I feel sad.
I'd just hoped to find a
special magic of my own
that had the power to protect
those I care about most.
[ZERA]
Ugh! What are you doing?
We're trying to have an
important conversation here!
This is awesome! My whole body's
pulsing with magic power!
Mine, too! I think
we're finally ready.
[PRECHT]
Now we can fight.
So what do you all think?
I'm the black wizard Mavis!
You like my new look?
You're getting into this.
I am!
Hey, wait. Where did
our magic teacher go?
Huh. I haven't seen him,
now that you mention it.
When's the last time
you guys did?
I dunno.
It's been a while.
[YURI] That's weird.
I wonder where he went.
[ZEREF] I suppose I
should've said goodbye
after all the time
we spent together.
It's odd for me to
have done what I did.
To teach others to use magic,
to befriend a young girl.
I'm not sure why.
In any case, I'll never
forget my time with them.
And I'll treasure that
respite from my loneliness,
however brief it was, Mavis.
Fairy Tail would be born
just ten short days
after I left them.
I played a large part
in its formation.
Perhaps I was the reason she met
such a tragic end, after all.
[MAVIS]
It's time to strike back.
My friends and I return to set
the city of Magnolia free
from Blue Skull's evil grasp.
Newly empowered by their
individual brands of magic,
Yuri, Precht, and Warrod
unleash a fierce onslaught,
while my newfound
"Fairy Tactician" strategy
aids in the fight.
In spite of all that we learned,
the battle takes
a turn that none of us
could've ever predicted.
Next Time: "Treasure."
Some things must never be lost.