Magnolia used to be
a town full of life.
And our guild was at its heart.
But those warm and
joyous days are gone.
[NATSU snores]
I'll take all the
fish. So yummy.
Oh, my hot icy, hunk.
Cherish those dreams.
And rest well.
[ERZA] Because this may be the
final dawn we face together.
[ERZA]
We'll need our strength.
And each other.
[NATSU]
The final one?
Not if I can help it.
Yeah, that's right.
Because we're not backing
down no matter what.
We're still here.
And we're ready to fight.
It'll be tough,
but Fairy Tail isn't gonna
give up that easily.
Come on, let's go.
[NATSU] We'll bust in
and get our guild back!
[NATSU]
For the sake of our future.
For Fairy Tail.
We shall.
Damn straight!
Indeed!
Aye, Sir!
[LUCY]
And on that morning, it began.
Together, we raced toward
Fairy Tail's final battle.
[ANNA]
The time is upon us.
Ugh. My belly is
so sad and empty.
[HAPPY] I guess I could give
you my fish if you need it.
[NATSU] Meh. Not unless
it's been cooked.
[HAPPY]
Are you crazy?!
Fish is at its yummiest
when it's raw and slimy.
I gotta wonder how
many times I've heard
this exact same argument before.
It's been a whole year
since we've been together,
but you guys make it seem
like no time has passed.
[NATSU] Speaking of time...
Lucy, are we there yet?
[LUCY] I think it's just
a little bit farther.
[LUCY screams]
[LUCY]
Whoa! That's huge!
And so adorable! What is it?
Wait, I think I know what
kind of monster this is.
First, it lures people
in with its fluffy fur,
then it gobbles them
up in a single bite!
[LUCY screams]
[snorts]
[roars]
[LUCY screaming]
Natsu! Time to roast this pig!
[NATSU]
Not really feelin' it.
What did you say?
I heard these things are
supposed to be super tasty!
Yeah? Come on!
[GIANT PIG  roaring]
[yells]
[GIANT PIG squeals]
He's goin' in my belly, pronto!
So, do you prefer your
meat cooked or raw?
[LUCY]
Seriously?
[NATSU] There's nothin' like
a meal you make yourself!
[LUCY] I gotta say, it tastes
way better than it looks.
[HAPPY] You guys can keep it.
I'm a 100% raw fish kinda cat.
[sighs]
What's the matter?
Ya full already?
[LUCY]
I was just thinking about stuff.
That last battle feels
like forever ago.
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Hm?
[LUCY]
Against Tartaros.
[LUCY] We'd never fought
against anyone so powerful.
But still, we rose
to the occasion
and gave it everything we had.
We did. And it
sure wasn't easy.
But we pulled it off.
Just like always.
You're right.
Don't you guys think that this
whole thing is kinda unfair?
[LUCY]
Whaddaya mean?
We scored a huge victory,
and master Makarov went and
broke up the guild anyway.
[LUCY]
Yeah.
I know he had his reasons
for doing it, but still...
[HAPPY]
What?
I never gave up on the dream.
That we'd all be together again.
I know I've said it
before, but it's true.
I'm so glad that we
finally found each other.
Now the three of us can go
look for the other members.
They're all out there somewhere.
[HAPPY]
Hey! What's the big idea?!
I told you nothin'
beats the flavor
of a perfectly grilled fish!
[HAPPY] Come on, ya big meanie,
make it raw again! Please!
Yeah, okay.
Check this out, Happy!
[HAPPY screams]
[HAPPY]
No! That's not raw!
You're gonna turn it into
ashes, ya stupid jerk!
[NATSU]
Whoops! Oh, you're right!
Sorry, buddy! Hey, don't cry!
I'll go out...
[LUCY]
Well, so much for nostalgia.
[NATSU]
I promise!
[HAPPY]
Where are we now?
[LUCY]
Tuly Village.
What do you guys think about
getting a room here
for the night?
Aye, aye!
Uh. Somethin' wrong, pal?
[NATSU]
Huh...
[HAPPY]
Whoa, isn't that the clock tower
you demolished a while back?
[NATSU] Yeah. Looks like
they were able to fix it.
[HAPPY] Sorta. But the new
part doesn't quite match.
[NATSU]
Nah.
[LUCY]
Hm?
Should I trash it again?
Of course not, ya flame brain!
[NATSU grunting]
[screams]
I'm goin' crazy!
A whole year trainin' my
butt off to get stronger,
and for what?
I fought the winners
of the magic games,
but they were all sucky.
I barely even broke a
sweat with those losers!
I had a plan to come back
and put Gray in his place.
And then it was gonna be
on to Erza and Laxus,
the big 'ol lightning dolt!
Yeah, well, Gray's one thing,
but fighting Erza and Laxus
would be pretty crazy.
[LUCY]
You think Gray's easy?
I got an idea, Lucy.
Let's get it on!
[LUCY]
What? No way!
That's the answer you were
expecting, weren't you?
But actually, I've been doing
some super-secret
training on my own.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[LUCY] I mean, I know that
I could never beat you
in a serious fight,
but I'm down to spar
with you sometime.
Hold that thought.
What now?
[LUCY screams]
No, please don't!
All my tools are in there!
I can't work without
them! Please!
Sorry, old timer!
Ya shoulda come out
here with some protection
if ya didn't want bad
stuff to happen to ya!
[BANDIT A]
Yeah, geezer!
[BANDITS yelling]
[gasping]
[BANDITS groaning]
[LUCY]
Jeez!
Were you trying to
kill me just now?
Nope, just doin' my job, Lucy.
[LUCY] Well, just so you know,
I have gotten really strong.
[NATSU] Cool, but I'm still
not feelin' fired up.
[LUCY]
Seemed like it to me!
[HAPPY]
What?!
You told us you've
been searching
for everybody all year,
so what gives?
I gathered as much
intel as I could.
But Fiore's big,
and there are a lot of
members to track down.
So, nobody?
I think we should probably start
heading toward the southeast.
Surely we can turn up
some leads in Marguerite.
That's where Lamia
Scale's guild hall is.
Oh, the one with
Lyon and Jura!
I smell a chance to
show off my skills!
Don't forget about
that doggie-man.
Yup! Wanna guess who else
is in Lamia Scale now?
It may surprise you!
[NATSU]
Hm?
Big king 'stache face?
[HAPPY]
Ooh, do they have a fish now?
[LUCY]
You guys are ridiculous.
[CROWD chattering]
[YUKA] First, and guaranteed to
give you thrills and chills,
is Lyon, a member of Lamia Scale
who always keeps his cool!
[applause]
[CHILDREN gasping]
[CROWD chattering]
Next up we have Toby,
with some impersonations!
[TOBY howls]
So, I'm gonna start out
with me when I'm crying.
[CITIZEN A]
He's impersonating himself?
[CITIZEN B]
That's not how this works!
Our apologies.
I ain't finished yet! Hey!
And now our master, Ohba, will
perform a very special dance!
[humming]
More skin?
[CROWD]
What?!
Our apologies.
I'm not finished yet,
kid! I'll spin you!
And moving right along.
The moment you've
been waiting for!
You brought us to a festival?
Lots of excitement in the air!
This is awesome.
We made it just in time!
[YUKA] Make some noise for
our guild's little angels.
Huh?
[YUKA] The Sky Sisters!
Shelia and Wendy!
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH scream]
[YUKA] They've got a brand
new song they wrote
just for this occasion,
so put your hands together
for "Met's Love Angelican!"
They've been friends since
the Grand Magic Games,
but this is pretty new.
[SHELIA] ♪ I've got a passion
burning deep inside my heart ♪
♪ Wonder if he'll ever know ♪
♪ I am no angel,
though I look sweet ♪
♪ I've still got a
fire in my soul ♪
[BOTH] ♪ I've never cared
about fancy wings ♪
♪ My hand in yours
is all I need ♪
♪ Happy, just you and me ♪
♪ Let's love!
Let's love! Forever! ♪
♪ Wanna hold on to
these feelings-- ♪
[MEN]
Forever!
♪ In your eyes I'll
keep on gazing-- ♪
Forever!
I don't understand
why she's doing this!
They've got the entire crowd
eating out of their hands.
I don't know why
you're surprised
that she joined another
guild after Fairy Tail.
She's still gotta earn
a living, after all.
[NATSU]
No, I mean...
Wendy's not a dragon singer,
she's a dragon slayer!
You go, Wendy!
[LUCY]
Isn't this fun?
It's all for Lamia Scale's
Thanksgiving festival.
You know, like how Magnolia
has its harvest festival?
It's a way to bring the guild
and the townsfolk together.
And build a sense of unity.
All right, it's my
new personal goal
to get Wendy back
on the right path!
How is she on the
"wrong path," Natsu?
Hang on. If Wendy's here,
then where's Carla?
[CARLA] I thought I might
see some familiar faces
in the crowd.
If it isn't Natsu,
Lucy, and the Tom-cat.
Oh, my apologies.
Hello there, Happy.
[ALL]
Say wha--?
[OROCHI A]
Huh.
The whole stupid town's
caught up in the festival.
[OROCHI B]
Let's love! Let's love!
[OROCHI TAMER]
Silence.
Tonight, the hammer of judgment
will fall squarely
upon Lamia Scale.
Give thanks. Soon the streets
will run red with blood.
[WENDY]
Oh my gosh,
I've never been so
embarrassed in my life!
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
You were super cute up there
and everybody loved you!
♪ Let's love!
Let's love! Forever! ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
But why is the song
called "Met's Love"?
Don't get ticked off.
You have some visitors, Wendy.
[WENDY]
I do?
Yo.
Long time, no see!
Hey, Wendy, you remember us?
Oh, wow! I can't believe it!
I missed you guys so much!
[NATSU]
Have you gotten taller?
Sorry. I guess I'm still
kind of a little shrimp.
Glad to hear it!
We're goin' home, okay?
Natsu, wait!
[LYON, YUKA, TOBY]
Hey!
[WENDY] You're traveling around
trying to track down everybody,
and then you're gonna
rebuild Fairy Tail?
[LUCY]
That's the idea.
But ever since the guild
disbanded last year,
nobody's even heard from master.
[LYON]
The council's been concerned.
They've been trying to pinpoint
Makarov's whereabouts
to no avail.
[NATSU]
The Council?
Like those jerks care.
[HAPPY] I didn't know there
was still a council.
Since you two have been
up in the mountains,
there's probably a
lot that's happened
that you don't know about.
[YUKA] The wizard guilds
can't really function
without a proper
Magic Council in place.
So last year, the Ten
Wizard Saints decided
they would come together
and form a new one.
[TOBY sobs]
[TOBY]
And Jura left us in the dust!
[YUKA]
Stop your howling.
[TOBY whines]
Well, if it's made up of
a bunch of those types...
...it must be awesome!
Does that mean
master's a member?
[LUCY]
He was supposed to be,
but then he disappeared
without a trace.
[NATSU]
Sounds like an annoying gig.
I woulda disappeared, too!
Anyway, we'll get to him later.
So get your stuff
together, n'let's go!
Well, uh, Natsu.
I'm a member of the
Lamia Scale guild now.
I can't just walk
away with you.
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSU]
You're kidding!
[LUCY]
Why?
I'm sorry, you guys.
[LYON] You don't have to
stay here for our sakes.
We knew from the start this
time would come someday.
[TOBY] And that's why we're
all ready to say good bye
without making a scene!
[YUKA]
Like that?
But why can't you come with us?
[WENDY]
Because...
[CARLA]
She's clearly made up her mind.
So please don't
berate her for it.
Don't get mad.
[LUCY]
How is she human?
[HAPPY]
How the heck are you human?!
Oh, this? I mastered my
transformation ability.
This form both increases
my magic power
and enhances my clairvoyance.
So what do you think, Happy?
Well, I trained for a
whole year too, ya know?
And I've come a long way.
Now I'm able to wait a little
while before I eat my fishies!
[CARLA]
How does that count as training?
This is no small decision,
Wendy. So be sure!
[HAPPY] Oh, your kitty
form is just the cutest!
[ALL]
You're really gonna stay?
Honestly.
[sighs]
[grunting]
[HAPPY gasping]
[LUCY groaning]
[LUCY]
Uhh...
[laughing]
Stop it! You're gonna
make me wet the bed!
Hands off while I'm
in bed, got it?
[NATSU, HAPPY groan]
Don't be so hard on us.
The whole thing's
just got us in shock.
[HAPPY]
Aye.
I know what you mean by that.
Makes you wonder
if the others'll
feel the same way she does.
I ain't givin' up! No way!
Even if I gotta kidnap
her, she's comin'!
[LUCY]
Don't you dare!
[SHELIA] Hey, Wendy, about
what happened earlier...
[WENDY]
It's fine.
I promise that I'm
not gonna go anywhere!
Sherry moved out
when she got married.
That had to be tough on you.
And if I leave, that means
you're gonna be left all alone.
Well, I don't really
see it that way.
[WENDY]
Huh?
I'll still be right here
with all of my guild mates
by my side.
I mean, we're like a big
family too, you know.
So you shouldn't stick around
because you feel sorry for me.
I want you to do what
makes you happy.
[bang]
What was that? That crash?
It came from the guild!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[LYON]
Get the citizens to safety!
[TOBY howling]
[YUKA]
This way!
[NATSU]
What's goin' on?
[LYON]
Natsu!
[gasps]
The town's under attack!
[LYON] All of a sudden,
a horde of monsters
just appeared out of nowhere.
Like a bunch of 'em?
That's crazy!
I bet the Orochi Fin
guild is behind this!
Those guys have been
trying to take us down
for as long as I can remember!
[LUCY]
Whoa, really?
They're so obsessed with
attacking our guild,
they don't care how many
innocent people get hurt.
And since Jura isn't
here right now,
we're missing our
strongest member.
The big festival gave them
the perfect opportunity
to catch us off guard.
They're gonna pay for this.
[YUKA]
Lyon!
This is just the
first wave of them!
There's a massive
swarm of monsters
coming in from the east!
Yeah, like a hundred thousand!
That many?
We don't stand a chance
against an army of monsters.
All this for revenge.
Orochi scum!
This is gonna be a
real show, fellas.
And this is the perfect place
to watch the whole
thing go down.
[OROCHI C]
With Old Man Jura gone,
this will be like taking
candy from a baby.
They're going to waste all
their precious magic power
fighting my monsters.
And then we'll crush them.
[MONSTERS roaring]
It appears as though they have
a monster tamer on their side.
It does. If we can
just take him out--
With so many beasts swarming in,
that could prove impossible.
[TOBY screams]
There has to be a way.
We can just go up!
Right over their heads!
That's true.
You'd be willing to help us out?
Of course I would!
'Cause I'm fired up now!
Let's go, Happy!
Aye, aye, to the sky!
Sorry about that, Natsu!
Shelia?
Okay.
[SHELIA] Come on, Happy,
we gotta keep going!
[HAPPY]
Uh... aye?
They're attacking our guild,
so it's up to us to
save it ourselves!
[WENDY]
Mh-hm!
That little girl just
cat-napped Happy!
[LUCY chuckles nervously]
[YUKA] Oh, no! The
swarm's inside the city!
[TOBY] I've never seen
so many monsters!
We must hold them
off at all cost.
[screams]
How dare you steal Happy!
Say what?
[NATSU]
I'm comin' for ya!
Natsu!
Is he crazy?
[MONSTERS roaring]
Get outta my way!
[LUCY gasps]
[yelling]
[NATSU]
Move it!
[NATSU yelling]
[LUCY] Orochi Fin unleashed
a massive horde of monsters
on Marguerite,
Lamia Scale's hometown.
And so, the Sky Sisters,
Wendy and Shelia,
fly through the air together
to protect their guild
and the frightened townspeople.
They're going over the monsters
to strike the wizard
controlling the swarm.
Unfortunately, one of the most
powerful foes we've ever seen
is waiting for them
on the other side.
Next Time: "Because of Love!"
The girls fight on bravely,
powered by the undying love that
dwells deep in their hearts!