[CANA]
What is this... this light?
It's like fire
Am I seeing things?
And this rain?
♪
This light is intense.
Is it magic power?
[CANA shouting]
"Here I seal Fairy Glitter, one
of the Three Grand Fairy spells.
May it forever shine
in the darkness."
This isn't her grave at all!
[HAPPY]
The One Thing I Couldn't Say
Alright, jerk wad.
What exactly are you after?!
[BLUENOTE] As I said
before, I want to know
the location of Mavis
Vermillion's resting place.
You'll be looking for a while
'cause we don't know either!
I wonder what he wants
with Master Mavis.
Do you think it may have
something to do with
the second part of the trial?
I think I just
figured out what he's after!
I'm sure we'll end up
dumber once we hear
what you have to say but,
by all means, go ahead.
Mr. Crazy Pony Tail wants
to be an S-Class wizard too,
so he came out here
to make us accept him
as a member of the guild!
There go my brain cells.
No, Happy!
[BLUENOTE]
All right, that's enough!
No more comments from you. I'll
say this once, so listen well.
I don't know anything about a
'trial' and I have no intention
of joining you pathetic fools.
[LUCY]
The only fool I see here is you!
[WENDY]
Lucy, stop it!
Her grave is more than just a
headstone it's sacred ground!
Even if we knew where it was,
we'd never tell someone like...
What do you want!
Tell me!
I want the sparkle
of faeries. Fairy Glitter.
One of your guild's
Three Grand Spells.
'just as powerful, if not
more so, than Fairy Law itself.
[NATSU] Is glitter all you want?
Try hittin' up a craft store!
[LUCY and WENDY]
Natsu!
[NATSU]
Ow! I'm a human pancake!
[BLUENOTE] I want
that merciless light.
Tell me where to find it or
I'll squash you until you pop.
Like we'd tell you.
Stay strong, you can
push through this!
Which of your friends would
you like to see crushed first?
I'm Natsu Dragneel...
I'm the son of Igneel!
It'll take more
than you've got to keep me
pinned to the ground, pal!
[NATSU]
I won't be defeated so easily!
He's running!
Wow. Under that
much gravity? Amazing!
I hear it was sealed away
with Mavis when she was buried.
Tell me where it is
and I'll leave you alone.
He jumped!
He seriously hates losin', huh?
Fire Dragon Iron--
You should listen when
someone's talking to you.
Natsu!
He's down.
Great.
What'll we do?
We can't touch him!
[BLUENOTE] I see you've
brought Mahkarov...
Perfect. I'll just
ask him where it is.
[NATSU] No you won't! Mess with
Gramps and I'll roast you alive!
We're not done talkin'
[BLUENOTE] We're done talking
when I say we're done.
Now are you going to
be helpful or should I
squash you all flat? Well?
[CARLA] This brute is
way too strong for us!
[WENDY] This is bad. He's got
us completely stuck here!
[LUCY]
Someone. Help us!
[CANA] What is this?
Some sort of sick joke!
I'm looking for a grave,
not some stupid spell!
How am I supposed
to finish the trial!
Master. I need answers!
Am I just not good enough
to become an S-Class wizard?
After everything
that's happened,
I fall short at the finish line.
Have the past twelve years
of my life been nothing
but a big waste of time?
[whimpering]
[CANA] On a rainy day
twelve years ago,
my mother passed away.
When her will was read,
I learned that
my father was still alive.
So I set out on my own to
look for him and found myself
at Fairy Tail's front door.
All I knew about him
was his name... Gildarts.
Hey, little lady. What are you
doing in a place like this?
Uh.
[CANA]
It's my daddy!
[GILDARTS]
You should hurry back home.
If you keep hangin' around
your clothes will start reekin'
of booze in no time flat.
[CANA] Wait, Daddy. Come back!
How come you don't recognize me?
I didn't get
to tell you about mom.
Who's the half-pint?
You lost kiddo?
You shouldn't be hangin' around
a rowdy place like this.
'Scuse me. Do you know when
Mr. Gildarts is gonna come back?
Gildarts, huh? Why're you
lookin' for a chump like him?
He break your heart?
I need to see him.
He just left on
a job today, didn't he?
[WAKABA] Yeah, sounded like a
tough one. He could be gone
a few days or as long as
month. Hard to say, really.
[MACAO] Awww, Don't worry!
He'll be back sooner or later!
[WAKABA] Come in and have
some juice. Our treat!
[CANA] I came back to the guild
so many times waiting for
my father to return,
that I eventually ended up
joining Fairy Tail.
[bells ringing, ground shaking]
Why is the city breaking!
This is what happens when
Gildarts comes back to Magnolia.
Two months of waiting
has finally paid off!
[CANA]
But then.
Wow! You look terrible!
[GILDARTS]
Nice to see you too, Master.
[MAKAROV] I guess the job was
rougher than we expected.
But the client was pleased;
they already sent a thank you
letter by carrier pigeon.
[GILDARTS]
Really? Glad to hear it.
[WAKABA]
Welcome back, Gildarts!
[MACAO] Do ya Got a minute?
We'd like you to meet someone.
[MAKAROV] Oh that's right, where
are my manners? This is Cana,
our newest member.
She's very excited to meet you.
Uh. Hello!
Cana? You know. You look
awfully familiar to me.
Wait, I remember you now!
You were that girl standing by
the entrance when I left
for the last job, right?
So you've joined up, huh?
Well glad to have you aboard,
little lady. Work hard!
I need to tell you.
Sorry, I know
you've just returned
but if you have a moment.
I have something to discuss.
[GILDARTS] You're kidding me.
What is it this time?
[CANA] Sometimes my father
wouldn't come back for months.
When he did, he'd turn
right around and leave
for another job.
[GILDARTS]
Yo.
You're sproutin'
like a bean stalk, Cana!
[CANA]
Uh. By the way.
Get a move on, or the train
is going to leave without you.
Uh oh! Catch ya later, Cana!
[CANA]
Later, Dad.
[CANA] The one thing I couldn't
say eventually became
a crushing weight
I couldn't ignore.
I learned how to read
fortune-telling cards
so I could predict when my
father would make it back home.
Hey. When did
ya learn to read those?
You been hidin' under a rock?
Cana's a natural,
all her predictions
have been spot on.
Wow! If you enjoy it,
then maybe you should think
about learning some Card magic.
The ol' wino's actually got
some good advice now and then.
You think I could
learn? Honestly?
But how do I even
begin to learn magic?
[MAKAROV] With your heart. If
you want to learn, you have to
believe in your heart
that you can learn.
Like with your fortunetelling.
You have faith that what you
predict will come to pass.
Learning to use magic requires
the same faith and hard work
as any other useful skill.
If you can believe in
the way of the natural world,
trust in yourself, and learn
to live in harmony with both,
you will easily master
the power of magic.
Just let your heart
be your guide.
My heart.
[CANA] The very next day, I
started learning card magic.
I took to it like
a fish to water.
Hoping that mastering it would
somehow bring me closer to him.
But it didn't.
My father was
the guild's best wizard.
He was placed on a pedestal,
and everyone down below
basked in his radiance.
I was buried beneath them;
out of sight and out of mind.
Years went by, and I still
never told him who I was.
I started to fear telling him.
What if he rejected me?
What if I wasn't good enough?
Then they announced the
candidates for that years'
S-Class Promotion Trial.
[CANA]
Master chose me?
[GILDARTS]
I'm rooting for ya!
[CANA]
I decided then.
I would tell
my father the truth,
when I became an
S-Class wizard like him.
But for four years in a row
now, I've only known defeat.
Even Erza and Mira, who
joined the guild after I did,
managed to become S-Class.
I'm nothing but a failure.
My father could never
be proud of me as I am.
That's why I decided
to make this my last attempt.
Alright, then.
I've been seriously
considering quitting the guild.
[CANA]
Do you understand?
I have to be an S-Class
wizard or I'll never be able
to look him in the eye.
That's why this is my last one.
If I fail, I'll leave for good.
Cana, will you please
let me be your partner?
Fairy Tail just wouldn't
be the same without you.
I promise I can help you
become an S-Class wizard!
[alarm]
Help! Help! Help!
[LUCY]
So, what's with the card?
[CANA] Don't lose it.
If you're ever it trouble,
that'll let me know immediately.
The card I have will start
shining and lead me back to you.
No matter how far apart we are.
[alarm]
Help! Help! Help!
[CANA]
What have I done? Lucy, I...
[CANA crying]
[CANA] No! It wasn't
supposed to be like this!
I never meant to
betray my friends.
I can't do this anymore.
[CANA crying]
[CANA] It's okay if I don't
become an S-Class wizard.
It's okay if I never
tell my father the truth.
As much as I want that.
I want to protect
my friends even more!
'Please! I have to save them.
That's my only
purpose right now!
It doesn't matter whether
I stay in the guild or not!
Because no matter
where I end up,
or who I become, my heart will
always belong to Fairy Tail!
I'm begging you.
I need the power.
And you're the only one
who can give it to me now!
I can't do it alone!
Give me the strength...
...to protect the guild and
family that I hold dear.
[FEMALE VOICE] Dry your eyes.
You have nothing to fear.
[CANA]
Could it be her?
Master Mavis.
Right!
I could be running straight
to my death, but I don't care.
I've got twelve years
of kindness to repay.
And you better believe
I'm gonna deliver!
-- [CARD] Help! Help!
-- [CANA] This way!
[CANA] Hang in there, Lucy.
I'll be there soon!
And I'm bringing
the big guns with me.
The Grand Spell, Fairy Glitter!
Whoever's attacking you is
about to get a face full of it.
With this spell
I can protect everyone!
Help! Help! Help!
[CANA] Are you the one
I need to squash?
Look!
Cana!
She's okay!
Better late than never!
Aye!
[CANA] I'm not letting you lay
another finger on my friends!
You're goin' down!
What's that?
I was gonna ask you!
[BLUENOTE]
It can't be!
Tell me what that magic
is or you die here.
Is it possible she learned
to use Fairy Glitter?
Huh?
[CANA] I'm sorry. For leaving
you in the forest, I mean.
I betrayed you,
and our friendship.
That was unforgivable.
But with this
I can begin to atone.
One shot from this spell
will make sure this creep
doesn't bother anyone again.
Awesome! Does that mean
you found the grave!
What! She did! But if she
found it that means. Man!
I don't get to be
S-Class this year.
[CANA] We can talk about
the trial later, Natsu.
Right now, I need your
help to beat this guy.
Keep him distracted long enough
for me to gather the power
to send him packin'.
Little girl,
you've gravely misjudged
the gravity of your situation.
[BLUENOTE] I never thought Fairy
Glitter would be delivered
to me personally...
Now, if you'd be so kind.
It's time I took
that spell off your hands.
[CANA] Unless you plan on
joining the Fairy Tail guild,
that's not gonna happen.
The spell is useless
to anyone else!
[BLUENOTE] If you knew
the origins of magic,
you'd realize all spells are
fundamentally the same.
Every type of magic that exists
today was once part of a single,
unified whole.
[LUCY]
A single type of magic?
That sounds familiar,
but I can't remember why.
[BLUENOTE] I've approached
the Abyss of Sorcery.
I don't need to join your guild
to use that spell or any other.
Cana!
[NATSU]
I... can't move!
[BLUENOTE]
I have a question for you .
Did you think you
were capable of wielding
an advanced spell
like Fairy Glitter?
Got a problem with that, jerk?
[BLUENOTE It's an ultra-level
spell that uses pure light to
deny the existence of anyone its
wielder deems to be an enemy.
You bet I've got a problem
with an amateur who thinks
she could control such power.
Don't worry.
I intend to relieve you of it
as painfully as possible.
Oh Natsu!
I guess even his
strength can't stand up
to this level of gravity.
Just watch, I think
he'll surprise you.
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon!
Roar!
He did it!
Cocky little brat!
[CANA]
Nice one, Natsu!
Go! Now!
[CANA] This amateur's
about to rock your world.
Assemble. O river of
light guided by fairies!
This is what a member
of Fairy Tail can do!
She's doing it. But how!
The sun's breaking
through the rain clouds!
Sun light with moon light
and the light of the stars!
[CANA] May your radiance
shine and vanquish
the fangs of wickedness!
Adios, you bastard!
Go! Fairy Glitter!
[LUCY]
Whoa! This light's intense!
[WENDY] I guess this
is what we should expect
from our Grand Spell!
For my family!
[BLUENOTE]
Fall!
[BLUENOTE] So that's the skill
it takes to use Fairy Glitter?
Don't make me laugh.
I guess even ultimate power
can be garbage when it's put
in the hands
of lowly trash like you.
[CANA]
I failed again.
[BLUENOTE]
I'll take the spell now.
And the good news is I don't
need you alive to do so.
[CANA]
My last chance and I blew it!
[NATSU]
Cana!
[LUCY]
Run away!
[WENDY]
Leave her alone!
[BLUENOTE] Another day passes
and I still didn't get to fly.
Maybe sending you to hell
will lift my spirits.
I don't believe it!
-- [CARLA] We're saved.
-- [HAPPY] Gildarts is here!
[CANA]
Dad.
♪
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu. Did you know
that huge tree that covers
the island is called
the Tenrou Tree?
[NATSU]
Yeah, and Master Mavis
is buried somewhere at
the bottom or something.
Wait, does that make it
a "Fairy Tree"?
[HAPPY] Whoa, maybe
that means that a fairy
will grow out of it!
[NATSU] That would rule!
I wanna fight it!
[HAPPY] Sometimes I think
eating, sleeping, and fighting
are the only things
you care about.
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next Episode: Tenrou Tree
[NATSU] That isn't true! I care
about messing with Lucy;
sneaking into Lucy's house;
Making Lucy do stuff
[HAPPY] Sounds like this
might take a while.
Could you write it down
for me instead?