[NARRATOR]
Previously, Natsu and Gray
gave everything they had to
free the Village of the Sun.
At last, the frozen
Eternal Flame
was restored to its full glory,
and turned out to be the fiery
dragon, Atlas Flame.
In order to give
the weakened dragon
a tangible form, Wendy
used the Milky Way spell
that had been passed down
to her from Grandeenah.
With his strength returned,
Atlas Flame melted
the mysterious ice that
had covered the village,
and its people, for so long.
[WENDY] There's no trace
left of Atlas Flame.
He gave everything
to save the village.
[LUCY] To think that just a
fragment of his spirit could
be so powerful. He even created
a brand new Eternal Flame.
[NARRATOR] Before his passing,
the dragon told Natsu
of Igneel's failed attempt
to slay E.N.D.,
the strongest of Zeref's
demons, four hundred years ago.
[NATSU] So Igneel was tryin' to
take out a demon called E.N.D.?
Never heard of it.
I wonder what made
Atlas Flame think of that?
[HAPPY]
Who knows?
[NARRATOR] With this
latest job behind them,
the group prepares to head home.
But elsewhere, a mysterious
force begins to take action.
[MESSENGER 232A]
Excuse me, sir.
You've been ordered to
return to Headquarters
as soon as possible.
[SILVER]
You go and tell headquarters
that I'm busy paying
my respects.
[MESSENGER 232A]
My deepest apologies, Sir.
But each of the Nine Demon Gates
have been summoned
to this meeting.
Forgive my insubordinance,
but, Sir, I...
...I'm begging you!
Obey the order, please!
[SILVER] What's with
the trembling, friend?
Scared I'm gonna eat your soul?
[MESSENGER 232A stammers]
[SILVER]
Heh.
You can put your fears to rest.
I only feast on the
souls of demons.
[laughs]
[NATSU, HAPPY, GIANTS laugh]
[LUCY]
They're getting along well.
[GIANT 233A] We owe you
little people big time!
[GRAY] We're just happy
that we could help out.
[WENDY]
Little people?
[CARLA]
I guess that would put you
in an even smaller
category, Wendy.
[GIANTS laughing]
[HAPPY, NATSU laugh]
'Scuse me.
But what exactly
happened to you?
[GIANT 233A] Honestly,
I can't really remember
much of anything.
We were told that some
demon slaying ice wizard
raided the village.
Yeah! I remember grabbing my
weapon to help fend him off.
Everything's a blur after that.
[GIANT 233F]
Mm.
According to Atlas Flame,
the ice wizard confused him
for a raging fire demon,
and came to take him out.
So the whole village
suffered because of
a case of mistaken identity?
That's far from uplifting.
No doubt. And I got
a feeling we've only
scratched the surface
of this thing.
The Succubus Eye creep
told me somethin'.
The netherworld gate
just busted wide open.
All thanks to you.
[GRAY]
Uh.
You'll realize the
consequences soon enough.
There's no turning back.
The netherworld gate?
That's Tartaros!
[LUCY whimpers]
I think someone from Tartaros
was behind this from the get-go.
The fact that Succubus Eye
came here proves that.
They were sent
to keep it frozen.
So freezing the whole village
wasn't about extinguishing
Atlas Flame?
It's possible, but it's all just
speculation at this point.
Who cares? We finished
the job, so let's party!
Party hardy!
Has anyone seen Flare?
[ERZA grunts]
[LUCY]
Uh...
Uh! So, uh, what's with
the hide and seek?
[LUCY]
Hello? Earthland to Flare!
[GIANT 233A growls]
--Did someone say "Flare"?
--[HAPPY, NATSU scream]
Did she really come back?
Hey, come on.
They're waitin' on ya.
You're finally home.
You should be happy!
Listen. I abandoned the village.
I ran and never looked back.
They hate me.
[LUCY] That's not true!
Just look at those smiles!
Never mind.
[FLARE]
Uh.
[GIANT 233A]
It's been a long time.
I hardly recognize you.
[GIANT 233B]
You might still be tiny,
but it's obvious you've grown.
[FLARE]
U-Uh... Uh.
So, what was it like
in the outside world?
[FLARE]
Uh...
I-It, was a lot of fun.
But, it was also
full of hardships.
[GIANTS chuckle]
[HAPPY, NATSU laugh]
You'll find that's the
same wherever you go.
It's one thing we
have in common.
[FLARE]
U-Uh..
[GIANT 232G] You can come
and go as you please.
Just remember, that
wherever you end up...
[GIANT 233E] ...You'll
always have a home here.
[GIANT 232H]
That's right.
Now then. There's
one thing left.
Something we've all been
waiting to say to you.
[FLARE]
Uh...
Daughter. you've
finally come home.
[FLARE cries]
I...
I'm home.
[HAPPY, NATSU laugh]
[GRAY]
Hm.
[ERZA]
[WENDY laughs]
[GIANTS laugh]
[FLARE laughs]
[LUCY] I'd never seen Flare
smile like that before!
Her joy was so boundless,
I couldn't help but share in it.
[ALL laughing]
[LUCY] That night,
we partied with the big people.
Our songs and laughter
filled the village
until the sun came up.
It was enough to make us forget
all the doom and
gloom from before.
[LUCY]
Succubus Eye.
Minerva.
Demon Slayers.
The Books of Zeref.
And... Tartaros.
[MINERVA] This is not
how I left the place.
I don't see any bodies.
Perhaps everyone
left the guildhall?
So strange.
What are these things?
[KYOKA]
Your Guild mates.
[MINERVA gasps]
Who's there?
[KYOKA] I tried to enhance
them with my curses.
Who are you?
[KYOKA] Sadly, most of them
were too weak to be enhanced.
Those are all that's
left of them.
I am called Kyoka.
One of the Nine Demon
Gates of Tartaros.
Why would you do this?
Tartaros must know we lost
the Village of the Sun.
That's the only explanation.
I had expected punishment
for our failure,
but I don't think we deserved
this kind of butchery.
I don't know what you mean.
Your jobs are your own business.
[MINERVA] Uh?! Tartaros didn't
order us to the village?
Was it a private
request from Silver?
My only concern
is enhancement.
I seek out anyone
that is worthy.
War is coming.
My master needs all
the troops he can find.
That is where I come in.
I'm something of a recruiter.
It must be difficult
to form an army
when you massacre your troops.
You're not much of
a recruiter, are you?
I have no need for those
unfit for enhancement.
[MINERVA gasps]
Let's see if you fare
otherwise, shall we?
[MINERVA]
No. Stay back!
[MINERVA screams]
[glug]
[GROUP sighs]
Getting to the village
was a total breeze.
Going home is a different story.
Warrod's magic was much
better than walking.
I didn't think anything could
move that quickly.
Consider this training.
Besides, we get to
enjoy the scenery.
We should hurry though.
I can't wait to see
Warrod's face when he hears
we saved the village.
Uh-huh.
The thought of a huge reward
completely slipped your mind.
[LUCY laughs]
[NATSU]
Huh?
[GIANT 233A]
See you later!
[GIANT 232G]
Visit again anytime!
[LUCY]
Uh?
Thanks, Blondie. For everything.
[LUCY laughs]
Somethin' funny? Or are you
just going crazy over there?
[HAPPY]
I can't see her face,
but I think she finally
lost her mind.
[ERZA] Okay, that's
enough rest. Let's go!
[ALL BUT ERZA groan]
Hold on. Something's fishy here.
What do you mean?
Smell somethin'?
I just can't remember what
we're getting paid for this job.
Huh. That's weird,
neither can I.
Don't worry.
Warrod's a Wizard Saint,
he must be rollin' in Jewel,
and I'd be happy
to lighten the load.
I don't care about the money.
The sense of pride
in our accomplishment
is reward enough for me.
[NATSU] Someone's feelin'
self-righteous.
[HAPPY]
Holier than thou, much?
[ERZA] I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
[HAPPY]
It was Lucy!
[LUCY]
Don't drag me into this!
[WARROD laughs]
There wasn't a doubt in my bark
that you kids would
be up to the task!
Well done, everyone!
Well done, indeed!
We hardly broke a sweat.
It was our privilege to help the
villagers and to serve you,
Sir Warrod. You honor all of us.
Oh yeah, what happened to
the treasure hunting creeps?
I sent them off in grand style.
[WENDY]
We also found out Tartaros
may have frozen the village.
[WARROD] Is that so?
Well, we can let the Council
worry about investigating
that sorry lot. For now,
there are more important
matters. Like your reward.
We are getting paid!
Well, we did complete
the task. Why wouldn't we?
[WARROD]
Enjoy.
Thank you. Uh...
Remember, small potatoes
are better than none!
[laughs]
Don't worry, I wouldn't
do that to you!
[NATSU chuckles]
I hope not.
[GRAY chuckles]
Before I forget. The potato
set me back a few jewel,
so I took it out
of your pay.
[GRAY, NATSU growl]
[NATSU]
You think you're funny old man?
[GRAY]
I've got a joke for ya!
[LUCY]
This feels amazing.
[ERZA]
And so is the view.
[WENDY]
What a reward.
Oh, yeah. This is
everything I needed.
[ERZA] I have to hand
it to Sir Warrod,
this hidden hot
spring is top notch.
[CARLA]
I'll say.
By the time we're done here,
we should all be glowing.
[WENDY]
Awesome!
It's hard to beat a good
soak after a long journey,
that's for sure.
I would have to agree.
Whole-heartedly.
It's the perfect way to soothe
our bodies and focus our minds.
[ALL sigh]
[LUCY]
I'm getting hungry.
[WENDY]
Yeah. Should we go?
[CARLA]
Yes, and soon.
Before the tomcat
and the meathead
eat everything in sight.
[WARROD]
I don't like to brag,
but I know my way
around a bar-b-q.
[NATSU, GRAY] No kidding,
old man. This is amazing!
[HAPPY]
Thanks for the noms!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I knew you were
eating without us!
Now that I smell the food,
I don't blame them.
What a delectable aroma!
[WARROD]
I'm happy you could join us!
I have some drinks here,
if you're thirsty.
[ERZA] My apologies, Sir!
I'm so embarrassed.
I should have done that for you.
[WARROD]
Nonsense! You're my guests.
I'm happy to do it myself!
Please, have as much
as you can drink!
Thank you! I bet it's delicious.
It smells like a forest.
These little trees are
actually growing out of it!
So, question...
Why I am the only one
with a mushroom
coming out of their cup?
Do you have something
against mushrooms, Happy?
[NATSU]
What's in this stuff?
No offense, but it smells
like dead leaves.
It's a special blend of
medicinal herb tea.
It's great for relieving stress,
and even helps you stay regular.
It took me a long
time to perfect,
and it's my great pleasure
to share it with you.
[ERZA]
Down the hatch.
[glug]
You kids'll believe
anything, won't you?
[GROUP groaning]
[WARROD] Well, the part
about relieving stress
was true, at least.
[LUCY gulp]
Gross. I've tasted better
brew from a sewer.
That's quite some tea.
It's delicious. Thanks.
You've been real
stressed out lately,
you can take the rest
of mine. Drink up!
What are you talkin' about?
You're the one that
needs to chill, dude.
Don't be shy, drink it all.
Knock it off!
You're being impolite!
Then you can have it.
[ERZA]
Mm!
[WARROD chuckles]
[GROUP]
Mm?
[WARROD]
Spending time with guild mates
can be such a
wonderful experience.
I must admit,
I'm feeling nostalgic.
[LUCY]
Uh.
That's sweet, but since
when are we guild mates?
--[WARROD] Ha!
--[LUCY] Uh...
So sorry about that. I was sure
Mahkarov already told you.
[GROUP]
Uh...
I was a part of Fairy Tail
from the very beginning.
Right alongside Mavis, and
the other founding members.
You could even say I'm
your senior's senior.
[LUCY]
U-Uh...
[WENDY]
Uh.
No.
What?
[NATSU gasps]
Really?
[HAPPY] That makes you
as old as the first master!
[CARLA]
That is what he just said.
I see. So that's why...
You'll go.
And while you're out
there, you'll behave
to the best that your feeble
little minds are able.
[LUCY] I was wondering why
gramps was so uptight
when he's a Wizard Saint, too.
Now it makes sense!
I was just--
No! Don't say it!
Telling you the truth.
[GRAY groans]
[ERZA]
I see.
That's why you asked for
Natsu and Gray by name.
[WARROD]
Mm-hmm. Exactly!
You have the smell of the
guild's old trees on you.
As soon as you walked
into my home,
I knew you were my companions.
[ERZA, GRAY, NATSU chuckle]
Actually, that one was a joke.
[LUCY]
Heh.
We're not making
much progress here.
Meeting a new generation of
fairies has been inspiring.
You truly embody the
spirit of harmony.
The kind of harmony
Mavis talked about.
[GROUP]
Hm.
[WARROD] She dreamed of a
wizard guild bound not by blood,
but by the souls of its members.
That is Fairy Tail.
The foundation she laid
for our guild is so strong,
her spirit lives
on in your hearts.
I'm not saying this because
you completed the job.
I could feel it the moment
you walked into my home.
[WARROD chuckles]
Mavis told me something once.
"A comrade is much
more than just a word.
A comrade lives in your heart!
Someone you can trust
unconditionally."
[NATSU sighs]
I want you to feel like
you can rely on me.
Because, one day, I'll need you.
And our trust in each other
will see us through.
[MAVIS] Whenever you're
suffering, whenever you're sad,
I'll be there to make
sure you remember
that you never have
to face it alone.
[MAVIS]
We have as many hopes and dreams
as there are stars
in the sky. If we walk
toward the future together,
I know we'll reach them.
Now, let us move forward.
Forever in tune with
the song of the fairies.
[LUCY] I never thought I'd hear
Fairy Tail's founding words.
Mavis was truly incredible.
So, let me get
one thing straight.
You're more gramps
than gramps aren't ya?
Can you be polite
for two seconds?
Look, I'm not tryin'
to be rude here.
I was just thinking that,
since you're really old.
You might know something
about this demon.
It's called E.N.D.
[WARROD]
E.N.D.? Tell me more.
[NATSU] He's from the Book of
Zeref. Apparently, my old man,
Igneel, tried to take
him down way back when.
Zeref, you say?
I haven't heard that
name in a tree's age.
I've been trying to find Igneel
ever since he disappeared.
I thought if I found out
more about E.N.D.,
it might lead me to him.
Atlas Flame told us
there was history
between Igneel
and the demon.
[WARROD] Hmm. Sorry,
but I don't know anything.
However, there might
be a connection
between this E.N.D.
character and Tartaros.
They're an eerie group of
wizards, shrouded in secrecy.
No one knows how many
members they have,
or where their guild is located.
But I've heard
stories from people
claiming to have stumbled
upon their gatherings.
And all of them came to
the exact same conclusion.
The Tartaros rituals are
for worshipping demons.
[GRAY grunts]
[WARROD] Now we don't
know for certain,
but the Four Emperors of
Ishgar have a grim suspicion.
We believe Tartaros
may be in possession
of a demon from
the Book of Zeref.
You're kidding!
A guild with a demon?
Creepy!
If that's true,
it could be the one
we're lookin' for!
[GRAY]
So tusk face was involved.
I knew I was onto something.
[NATSU growls]
This sucks! Ah!
We can't do anything about it!
We don't even know
where they are!
If I get my hands on
one of those freaks,
I'll thrash 'em around till
they tell me everything!
--[HAPPY, CARLA scream]
--[NATSU] Like this! And this!
[WARROD]
Uh...
[NATSU] Tartaros won't
know what hit 'em!
Natsu. Look down.
Huh?
[ERZA growls]
[NATSU whimpers]
[NATSU screams]
[LUCY] Our group returns to the
guild after a job well done.
For the first time in awhile,
things are actually
pretty peaceful.
But the shadow of Tartaros,
the demon worshipping dark
guild, looms overhead.
And threatens to
ruin that peace.
Then, in a shocking
turn of events,
we find out that
Tartaros might be
even closer to home
than we realized.
Next time!
Tartaros Chapter, Prologue -
The Nine Demon Gates!
The netherworld gate has opened.