- Narrator: IN A
LAND FAR, FAR AWAY,
LIES THE KINGDOM OF FIORE.
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF SEVENTEEN MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME, BOUGHT
AND SOLD IN EVERY MARKETPLACE,
FOR MOST, MAGIC
IS MERELY A TOOL.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED THEIR
LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE WIZARDS BAND TOGETHER
TO FORM MAGICAL GUILDS
WHICH DOT THE
LANDSCAPE OF FIORE,
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN
GUILD IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS
LEGENDS HAVE BEEN BORN.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: IT'S CHERRY BLOSSOM
SEASON HERE IN MAGNOLIA.
AND WITH IT, COMES A SPECIAL
EVENT FOR THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
- Makarov: HEED MY WORDS,
DEAR FRIENDS!
IF YOU FANCY YOURSELF
A MEMBER OF THIS GUILD,
YOU MUST HONE YOUR SKILLS
BOTH DAY AND NIGHT.
DO SO AND FORTUNE
WILL ALWAYS BE YOURS.
NEVER FORGET YOU ARE
RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR OWN KEEP.
WHILE MANY OF YOUR
DAYS WILL BE SUNNY,
OTHERS WILL BE CLOUDED
IN HARDSHIP.
PEACE AND PROSPERITY, TEMPERED
BY TRAGEDY AND HEARTBREAK.
HOWEVER, I HAVE FAITH
WE CAN FIGHT THROUGH
EVEN THE DARKEST OF DAYS AS
LONG AS WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
YOU ARE SURROUNDED,
NOT BY CO-WORKERS,
BUT BY AN ENDURING
AND LOVING FAMILY!
TOGETHER WE ARE ONE!
THAT'S WHAT BEING A
FAIRY TAIL WIZARD IS ABOUT!
- ( crowd cheering )
- I COULDN'T BE MORE
PROUD OF WHAT YOU KIDS
HAVE ACCOMPLISHED
IN THE LAST YEAR.
SO TO COMMEMORATE YOUR
HARD WORK AND DILIGENCE,
TOMORROW WE WILL BE HOLDING,
THE HIGHLY ANTICIPATED
FLOWER VIEWING PARTY!
- ( crowd cheering )
- Makarov: THAT MAKES TODAY
THE PRE-CELEBRATION! SO DRINK!
- BUNCH OF MORONS.
- Happy: RAINBOW
CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- TAKE IT EASY.
SAVE THE DRINKING FOR THE
CELEBRATION TOMORROW.
- YEAH, NO JOKE.
I'LL NEVER GET THIS WHOLE
"FLOWER PARTY" THING.
YOU GUYS ARE JUST LOOKING
FOR AN EXCUSE TO BOOZE IT UP.
- WHOA, THE POT'S CALLING
THE KETTLE BLACK.
- NO KIDDING, SHE DRINKS AS
IF EVERY DAY'S A CELEBRATION.
- FLOWER PARTIES
ARE FREAKING MANLY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU GONNA TAKE HOME THE GRAND
PRIZE FROM THE BINGO GAME, DAD?
- YOU BET. THIS IS MY YEAR.
SO YOU BETTER BE THERE
TO ROOT FOR YOUR POP.
- I DIDN'T GET A SINGLE NUMBER
DURING LAST YEAR'S BINGO GAME.
BUT THAT JUST MEANS I'LL GET ALL
OF THE NUMBERS THIS YEAR, BABY.
- IT DOESN'T REALLY
WORK THAT WAY.
- LET HER HAVE HER
MOMENT, MAN.
- YOU PEOPLE MAKE
NO SENSE AT ALL.
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL ABOUT
SOME SISSY FLOWERS?
THEY GOT HIDDEN POWERS
OR SOMETHING?
- Nab: IT'S A BIG DEAL
AROUND HERE.
I MEAN, EVEN OUR CLIENTS
KNOW THE SCORE.
- Gajeel: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Nab: THE BOARD GETS PRETTY
BARREN THIS TIME OF YEAR
BECAUSE EVERYBODY KNOWS NONE
OF US WANT TO WORK
DURING THE CELEBRATION.
- Gajeel: RIDICULOUS.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
DO YOU EVER WORK?
- ( siren wails)
- YOU'RE BLUER THAN NORMAL.
- IT'S MY DEAR GRAY!
HE MUST HAVE FORGOTTEN ABOUT
THE PARTY AND LEFT ON A JOB.
IF MY BELOVED ISN'T HERE,
THEN I WON'T HAVE ANYONE
TO CUDDLE AND LOOK AT
THE FLOWERS WITH.
- I'M SORRY, BUT YOU KNOW
THAT A WIZARD
HAS TO EARN HIS
DAILY KEEP SOMEHOW.
- THAT'S FUNNY COMING FROM YOU!
- LAY OFF!
- HE'S GONE. WHY?
I COULD HAVE
HELPED HIM OUT!
- IT WOULD'VE BEEN OVERKILL.
HE'S ALREADY TEAMED
UP WITH NATSU,
AND THEY DON'T NEED
ANOTHER PERSON!
- HANG ON.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
WHY DID WENDY AND CARLA
GET TO TAG ALONG WITH THEM?
- BECAUSE THEY'RE BOTH NEW TO
THE GUILD FROM CAIT SHELTER.
THEY NEED TO GET THEIR FEET WET
SOONER OR LATER, DON'T THEY?
- YES, I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE FACT,
THAT HE ABANDONED ME!
- OPEN, GATE OF THE
CLOCK CONSTELLATION.
HOROLOGIUM!
- Narrator: THE FRIGID
PEAKS OF MT. HAKOBE.
- Horologium:
"I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE,
"YOU'D THINK I'D KNOW TO
WEAR SOMETHING WARMER.
"I'M FREEZING MY RUMP OFF!"
SHE EXCLAIMS WITH
GREAT DISCOMFORT.
- I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS!
- YOU HAVE TO GET USED
TO THE ELEMENTS
IF YOU'RE GOING TO
DO WORK LIKE THIS.
- "GET IN HERE WITH ME, WENDY.
"YOU DON'T WANNA
CATCH A COLD."
SHE CHATTERS WITH
NURTURING CONCERN.
- MMM. OKAY, THEN!
AS LONG AS YOU'RE SURE
IT WON'T BE ANY TROUBLE.
COMING, CARLA?
- NO THANK YOU, I'LL BE FINE.
YOU SHOULD BE TRYING TO OVERCOME
THESE CONDITIONS AS WELL.
FOCUS YOUR MIND AND
ADAPT TO DISCOMFORT.
- OUR SEARCH SHOULD BE EASIER
NOW THAT THE STORM HAS CALMED.
- I'M STARVING. I COULD
EAT AN ENTIRE VOLCANO.
- IT'S SO WARM IN HERE.
- YEAH? THEN WHY AM
I GETTING FROSTBITE?
- WHOA! IT'S SO COLD THAT EVEN
I'M STARTING TO GET CHILLY.
- HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
PUTTING ON A SHIRT?
- ( grunts )
- HEY, NATSU.
I'M NOT CONVINCED
THAT THIS HERB WE'RE
LOOKING FOR EVEN EXISTS.
- IT'S GOTTA.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE
POST A JOB TO FIND IT
IF IT DIDN'T EXIST?
- IT SOUNDS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
A WIZARD CAN BOOST
THEIR MAGIC POWER
JUST BY PUTTING THIS
STUFF IN TEA OR CAKE?
I BET IT'S GOT SOME
WICKED SIDE EFFECTS.
LIKE YOU GROW A SECOND HEAD
OR IT GIVES YOU SERIOUS GAS.
IT'S LIKE THEY SAY,
"THERE'S ALWAYS POISON
TO EVERY GOOD FISH!"
- I THINK YOU MIGHT MEAN,
"THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A FREE LUNCH."
- I'VE BEEN SAYING IT
WRONG ALL THIS TIME?
- Erza: "SIDE-EFFECTS"
ARE NOT OUR CONCERN.
THE JOB FLIER SAID TO
COLLECT AND DELIVER,
SO THAT'S WHAT
WE'LL DO.
BUT IF WE FIND AN EXCESS,
THERE'S NO REASON WE CAN'T
TAKE SOME TO USE FOR BINGO
PRIZES TOMORROW. SOUND GOOD?
- YEAH. HEY, HERBS,
COME OUT AND FIGHT ME!
- HEY NATSU. SHUT UP.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- HOW'S A PLANT SUPPOSED
TO ANSWER YOU,
LET ALONE COME DOWN
HERE AND DUKE IT OUT?
THEN AGAIN, IF IT COULD,
I BET IT'D WIPE THE FLOOR
WITH YOUR FACE.
- WATCH IT, FROSTY.
IF YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY,
WHY DON'T YOU SAY
IT TO MY FACE?
- NEXT TIME YOU GET THE BRIGHT
IDEA TO TALK TO A PLANT,
KEEP IT TO YOURSELF.
- WOULD YOU SHUT UP?
- Both: AYE!
- MAN, I CAN'T WAIT TO GET THIS
JOB DONE SO WE CAN GO BACK HOME.
- THERE'S SO MUCH TO DO
BEFORE TOMORROW'S PARTY.
- YEAH, I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO IT.
- Lucy: JUST WAIT 'TIL YOU SEE
MAGNOLIA'S CHERRY BLOSSOMS!
NOT ONLY ARE THEY GORGEOUS
IN THE DAYLIGHT,
BUT THEY'RE
RAINBOW-COLORED AT NIGHT.
IT'S LIKE A DREAM.
TOMORROW'S GONNA ROCK.
- RAINBOW BLOSSOMS? WOW.
JUST THE THOUGHT OF
IT IS SUPER PRETTY.
- NO JOKE, SISTER.
- Horologium: THEY
PRATTLE, ON AND ON.
- Lucy: YOU'RE GONNA
LOVE IT, WENDY.
EVERYBODY BRINGS A
BOXED LUNCH WITH THEM
AND WE SPEND THE DAY
BENEATH THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
WE'LL PLAY GAMES AND PARTY,
SURROUNDED BY FLOWERS.
CAN YOU IMAGINE A
MORE PERFECT DAY?
( exclaims ) IT'S GONNA BE EPIC.
THAT'S WHY I WANNA WRAP THIS
UP AND GET BACK TO MAGNOLIA.
I'VE GOT MAJOR PREP TO DO.
FIRST, I NEED TO BAKE COOKIES,
THEN I'LL DECIDE WHETHER I
WANNA WEAR ONE OUTFIT
OR CHANGE IT UP AT NIGHT. THEN
I'LL FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO
WITH MY HAIR. THEN,
I'LL PROBABLY GO TO BED
WITHOUT WORKING ON MY NOVEL.
OH WELL, PROCRASTINATION IS
NOTHING NEW FOR ME AND THEN...
- WAIT
- HMM?
- I TAKE IT YOU WENT TO THE
FLOWER VIEWING PARTY LAST YEAR?
- HUH? WELL, ACTUALLY...
- THAT'S WEIRD.
IS ANYONE ALLOWED TO GO?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT YOU'VE BEEN
WITH FAIRY TAIL
FOR LESS THAN A YEAR.
- OKAY. TRUTH IS, THIS'LL
BE MY FIRST TIME, TOO.
- REALLY?
( laughs )
- Lucy: I GUESS I'VE JUST
HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT IT
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN
BEFORE, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH AND WE'LL GET
TO EXPERIENCE IT TOGETHER.
IF IT'S HALF AS GOOD
AS IT SOUNDS,
IT SHOULD BE A TON OF FUN.
ESPECIALLY SINCE
WE'LL BE CELEBRATING
WITH ALL OF OUR FRIENDS
IN FAIRY TAIL.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
LET'S HURRY AND GET OUT
OF THIS FROZEN WASTELAND.
- ( alarm ringing ) - ON THAT
NOTE, I BID YOU FOND FAREWELL.
- ( both exclaiming )
- GET A GRIP.
- WE'LL GET HOME FASTER
IF YOU HELP FIND THE HERBS.
- Lucy: GIVE ME A BREAK.
- ( sniffing )
I FOUND YOU.
I KNEW YOU COULDN'T HIDE
FOREVER, YOU STUPID PLANT.
- BEHOLD THE POWER OF A
DRAGON SLAYER'S SCHNOZ.
- WAIT, HOW CAN YOU BE SURE
YOU'VE FOUND THE RIGHT HERBS,
HAVE YOU SMELLED THEM BEFORE?
- NU-UH. DOESN'T MATTER.
I KNOW THIS IS THEM.
- LET'S GO, HAPPY.
- AYE, SIR.
- WAIT FOR US, JERK.
- SO, WHO ELSE SAW
THAT ONE COMING?
- STOP GAWKING AND
START FOLLOWING HIM.
HIS WITS MAY BE DULL,
BUT HIS NOSE IS SHARP.
- AM I THE ONLY ONE,
WHO'S SUDDENLY FEELING A
SENSE OF IMPENDING CALAMITY?
- I HOPE YOUR HUNCH TURNS
OUT TO BE WRONG THIS TIME.
- ( yelling )
- ( whooping )
- YAY. - HE STARTS BRAGGING,
WE BURY HIM IN SNOW.
- WELL I'M IMPRESSED.
- SO YOUR HUNCH WAS WRONG.
- THAT REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
- OKAY. LET'S PICK THESE
THINGS AND GET BACK HOME.
- AYE, SIR.
- ( growls )
- Narrator: THE
DECEPTIVE BLIZZARD-VERN,
ALSO KNOWN AS THE WHITE WYVERN,
A DRAGON-LIKE BEAST THAT MAKES
IT HOME IN HIGH ALTITUDES.
ALTHOUGH FEROCIOUS,
THESE CREATURES ARE HERBIVORES,
AND THE HERBS NATSU JUST
FOUND ARE ITS FAVORITE FOOD.
- YOU'RE KIDDING. - I DON'T
THINK IT WANTS TO SHARE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE WE'LL
GET TO FINISH THE JOB
AND TAKE HOME A JUICY BONUS
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
WHITE WYVERN SCALES
GO FOR A LOT OF MONEY
AND THIS GUY'S GOT
PLENTY TO GO AROUND.
- SURE DOES.
YOU HEAR THAT, STINGY?
WE'RE GONNA TAKE YOUR FOOD AND
STRIP YOU FOR GOOD MEASURE.
- I SUGGEST THE FOUR
OF YOU STAND BACK.
LET US TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- WHAT?
- WE WANT IN ON THE ACTION, TOO.
- REQUIP.
VERY WELL THEN,
YOU MUST LISTEN CLOSELY.
ONCE WE'VE GOT
THE BEAST DISTRACTED,
GRAB AS MANY OF THE
HERBS AS YOU CAN.
- YES, MA'AM.
- I BEG YOUR PARDON?
- WAIT. WHY ARE YOU GIVING US
THE MOST
DANGEROUS PART OF THE JOB?
- IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- NO, MA'AM.
WE'RE ALL OVER IT.
- YOU READY?
LET'S DO THIS.
- Both: HERE GOES.
- ( growling )
- ( whimpering )
- WE GOTTA PICK UP THE PACE.
- PLEASE REFRAIN
FROM SPEAKING TO ME.
- FIRE DRAGON,
BRILLIANT FLAME!
- WHOA, HE DEFLECTED IT.
- AND NOW IT'S HEADED
IN OUR DIRECTION.
- ( all screaming )
- ICE-MAKE SAUCER!
- ( screaming )
- TRY DEFLECTING THIS.
- UH-OH.
- WHAT IN THE HECK?
- ( screaming )
- IDIOTS. DON'T YOU
KNOW HOW TO DODGE?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- BUT IT CAME AT US SO FAST.
- HOW IS THIS THING
SO POWERFUL?
- NO CLUE.
SORRY ERZA, BUT I AM NOT JUST
GONNA SIT ON THE SIDELINES.
- ( grunts )
DON'T GET COLD FEET!
NATSU, ERZA, LITTLE HELP?
- RIGHT.
- CONSIDER IT DONE.
- ( screams )
- FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- SCORE. LUCY, YOU ROCK.
IT'S NO WONDER YOU'RE
SUCH A VALUABLE MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL'S STRONGEST TEAM.
- ( rumbling )
- AVALANCHE!
- IS EVERYONE OKAY?
- ( retches )
- YOU'RE SICK? AN AVALANCHE
DOESN'T COUNT AS A VEHICLE.
- IT APPEARS MY
HUNCH WAS RIGHT.
- HEY! WHERE DID LUCY GO?
- LUCY, WHERE ARE YOU?
- I'M HERE. BARELY.
- Narrator: THE DAY OF THE
FLOWER VIEWING PARTY
HAS FINALLY ARRIVED.
- ( sneezes )
- Natsu: HOLD UP.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- TRUST ME, YOU DON'T WANNA
MISS MAGNOLIA'S FLOWERS.
- IT'S NOT BY CHOICE.
( moaning )
I WANTED TO GO SO BADLY.
- Happy: WELL, WHAT'S
KEEPING YOU FROM GOING?
- ARE YOU BOTH
BLIND OR SOMETHING?
I CAUGHT A NASTY COLD.
THANKS FOR STOPPING BY.
I'M GOING BACK TO BED.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
- HOPE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- Natsu: TALK ABOUT
A MAJOR DOWNER. THIS SUCKS.
- Happy: IT'S REALLY
BAD TIMING.
SHE'S BEEN SUPER EXCITED
ABOUT IT FOR A LONG TIME.
- MMM-HMM.
- A FLOWER PARTY?
YEAH, I'LL GO.
YOU JUST MADE MY DAY.
YAY! OH, I'M GONNA
BUY A NEW DRESS.
AND THEN I'LL BAKE
COOKIES FOR EVERYBODY.
- THIS'LL BE A BLAST.
- SHE'S SO CUTE.
I KEEP FORGETTING SHE WASN'T
AROUND FOR
LAST YEAR'S FESTIVITIES.
- THIS'LL BE FUN.
- A PARTY?
- YEAH, WE ALL GET
TOGETHER TO EAT, DRINK,
AND GO WILD UNDER THE
BEAUTIFUL CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- WHY'RE YOU ALL FIRED UP?
- BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS
DREAMED OF SEEING THEM.
THE RAINBOW CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
NOW I WILL. I'M GONNA COUNT THE
DAYS UNTIL THE VIEWING PARTY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET TO
CELEBRATE WITH EVERYONE.
- THAT'S GOT TO
BE DISAPPOINTING.
- YEAH, I FEEL BAD FOR HER.
- ( people chattering )
- EAT UP, YOU GUYS.
THERE'S MORE WHERE
THAT CAME FROM.
- THIS ONE'S MINE,
SO KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF.
- SURPRISED YOU
ONLY BROUGHT ONE.
- AND NO ONE WOULD BE
STUPID ENOUGH TO TAKE IT.
- FLOWERS ARE MANLY!
- WHATEVER YOU SAY, BIG GUY.
- CAN I GET YOU
SOMETHING TO EAT?
- OR ANYTHING TO DRINK?
- WHAT? WHY ISN'T
LUCY COMING?
- DID SHE LOSE INTEREST?
- SHE'S GOT A COLD. I'VE NEVER
SEEN HER LOOK SO ROUGH.
- HOW DID SHE CATCH A COLD?
- HAVE YOU ALREADY FORGOTTEN?
- POOR LUCY, SHE WAS REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS.
- HEY, WAIT.
WHY DON'T WE GO TO HER PLACE,
AND YOU CAN HEAL HER?
- I ALREADY DID THAT
EARLIER TODAY.
BUT SHE BE WON'T FULLY
RECOVERED 'TIL TOMORROW.
- THIS ISN'T HER DAY.
- ( moaning )
RAINBOW CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
I BET EVERYBODY'S HAVING THE
TIME OF THEIR LIVES RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M STUCK HERE IN BED.
- EVERYONE HAVE A CARD NOW?
LET THE ANNUAL FLOWER VIEWING
BINGO TOURNAMENT BEGIN.
- Crowd: BINGO!
- ( Makraov laughs )
WE'VE GOT SOME GREAT PRIZES
FOR THE TOURNAMENT THIS YEAR.
I HOPE YOU'RE ALL
READY TO PLAY.
- All: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT!
EVERYONE READY?
- All: AYE, SIR!
- OKAY, THEN. YOU MAY NOW
POKE THE CENTER HOLE OPEN.
- THE GRAND PRIZE
IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
- KICK THEIR BUTTS, DAD.
- LET'S PLAY BINGO.
- THE FIRST NUMBER'S COMING UP.
- NUMBER TWENTY-FOUR.
- AWESOME. I GOT ONE ALREADY.
- MAN, I'M ALREADY BEHIND.
- Both: YOU'VE GOT THIS, LEVY!
- ( coughing )
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S BEEN
LESS THAN A YEAR SINCE I JOINED.
IT SEEMS LIKE FOREVER AGO
THAT I RAN AWAY FROM HOME,
DREAMING OF BECOMING
PART OF FAIRY TAIL.
I RAN INTO NATSU
PRETTY SOON AFTER THAT.
AND MY DREAM BECAME A REALITY.
IT ALL HAPPENED SO QUICKLY.
- Mirajane: NUMBER FIVE.
- I'VE GOT THAT ONE.
I'M A MAN!
- THAT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
- I HAVEN'T GOTTEN
A SINGLE NUMBER.
- C'MON NATSU,
AREN'T YOU GONNA PLAY?
- Lucy: SO MUCH HAS
CHANGED IN MY LIFE,
AND IT ALL HAPPENED
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE.
- NUMBER SIXTY-EIGHT.
- I GOT BINGO!
- SERIOUSLY?
- SHE'S REALLY INTO THIS.
- I'VE ALMOST GOT ONE AS WELL.
- ERZA GETS THE FIRST BINGO.
- I HAVE ONLY MY
TRAINING TO THANK.
SO, DO I WIN A SPECIAL PRIZE?
- UH-HUH. HERE.
AN AMAZING HERB RUMORED TO
TEMPORARILY INCREASE
A WIZARD'S MAGIC POWER.
- WHAT?
- Crowd: WOW!
- BUT THAT'S ONE OF THE PLANTS
THAT WE PICKED YESTERDAY.
AND IT'S ALREADY WILTING.
- YEAH, THAT'S BOUND TO HAPPEN
WHEN YOU BRING IT
INTO A WARMER CLIMATE.
- SO THAT'S IT.
MY PRECIOUS BINGO?
- I'M SORRY.
- Lucy: IT'S CRAZY.
SO MANY ADVENTURES IN SUCH
A SMALL AMOUNT OF TIME.
WOW.
( laughs )
WOW. NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S A MIRACLE I'M STILL ALIVE.
- BINGO!
- BUT HOW?
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN ONE NUMBER.
- FACE THE FACTS,
THIS AIN'T YOUR GAME.
- IT'S NOT OVER YET.
- I'VE GOT A HUNCH IT'S
OVER FOR THIS FELINE.
- WELL, MAYBE YOUR
HUNCH'LL BE WRONG THIS TIME.
- ( sighs )
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF PRIZES
AND I DON'T EVEN HAVE ONE ROW.
I WAS HOPING I COULD
WIN SOMETHING FOR LUCY,
SO SHE'D HAVE A SOUVENIR.
- NUMBER ONE-FIFTEEN!
- All: BINGO! HUH?
- ALL THREE OF YOU?
- WELL, THIS IS A FIRST.
SO, LET'S HAVE A TIE-BREAKER,
WHERE THE BEST SHORT PERFORMANCE
WINS THE GRAND PRIZE.
- All: SHORT PERFORMANCE?
- THIS IS WHAT YOU
ARE COMPETING FOR.
TWO TICKETS FOR THREE DAYS AND
TWO NIGHTS OF LUXURY
AT AKANE RESORT.
- WOW!
- Both: TICKETS FOR TWO?
- THE AKANE RESORT?
SOUNDS LIKE A PERFECT
GIFT FOR MY SISTER.
- THREE-DAYS AND TWO-NIGHTS
WITH GRAY?
IT'S TOO MUCH TO TAKE.
MY THOUGHTS ARE SO
HOT I MIGHT EVAPORATE.
- SHORT PERFORMANCE.
WHERE THERE'S FOUR IN THE RING,
AND THREE FEEL THE STING.
TRY NOT TO CRY WHEN I TAKE
HOME THE PRIZE. YOU DIG IT?
- All: YOU'RE NOT COMPETING.
- OFF THE STAGE! LAST I CHECKED,
YOU WEREN'T EVEN NEAR BINGO!
- YOU OKAY?
- HMM.
- ( sneezes )
THERE WERE SO MANY TIMES
I NEARLY LOST ALL HOPE.
SO MANY DESPERATE SITUATIONS.
AND COUNTLESS ENEMIES
WITH UNBELIEVABLE STRENGTH.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT KIND
OF OBSTACLE WE FACED,
I KNEW THE GUILD WOULD
ALWAYS BE THERE FOR ME.
WE LAUGHED TOGETHER.
SHARED OUR TEARS.
AND SO MUCH MORE.
THROUGH IT ALL, WE'VE SHARED
IN EACH OTHER'S PAIN.
BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT FAMILY DOES.
EVERYONE HAS THEIR
OWN PROBLEMS,
BUT THEY NEVER HAVE
TO FACE THEM ALONE.
NO MATTER WHAT,
THROUGH THE GOOD TIMES,
AND THE BAD, WE GROW TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHAT FAIRY TAIL
IS ALL ABOUT.
ALL IN ALL, I'VE JOINED A PRETTY
INCREDIBLE GUILD, HAVEN'T I?
( sneezes )
TIME TO CRASH.
- ( people chattering )
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
AND WHY IS IT SO LOUD OUTSIDE?
- ( crowd gasping )
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL. INCREDIBLE.
- ( gasps )
IS THIS A DREAM?
BEAUTIFUL.
- Natsu: SO, YOU'RE
ALREADY OVER YOUR COLD?
- YEP! I'M AS GOOD AS NEW.
- WE'RE GLAD TO
HAVE YOU BACK, LUCY.
- ALL RIGHT, WHICH ONE
OF YOU NUMBSKULLS
UPROOTED THE CITY'S
PRIZED CHERRY TREE?
THE MAYOR'S BEEN BREATHING
DOWN MY NECK ALL MORNING!
YOU'RE GONNA WISH I'D
KICKED YOU OUT OF THE GUILD
WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOUR
SORRY HIDES. NOW WHO DID IT?
- GEE. I WONDER.
- GRAY, DARLING. CLOTHES.
- BUNCH OF MORONS.
- THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- UH, WHAT ARE YOU
THANKING US FOR?
- YEAH. WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL. WE SWEAR.
- ( Lucy laughs )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
- Happy: WHERE THE HECK
DID THAT COME FROM?
- Natsu: I DON'T KNOW, IT
JUST POPPED INTO MY HEAD.
I'M FEELING LIKE,
OH, WHAT'S THE WORD?
- Happy: GETTING LIGHT-HEADED?
- Natsu: NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S MORE LIKE,
I DON'T KNOW.
A GUT FEELING?
- Happy: WELL, MAYBE
YOU'RE HUNGRY OR SOMETHING.
- Natsu: IT'S ON THE
TIP OF MY TONGUE.
SOMETHING LIKE DAY JOB FU?
- Both: NEXT TIME,
WENDY'S FIRST BIG JOB?
- Natsu: NOW I'M HUNGRY. WHAT DO
YOU SAY WE GO GRAB SOME GRUB?
- Happy: THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
- Natsu: OH NO. NOT YOU, TOO.