Princess. The wizards
can handle things
from this point on,
so we should leave.
I can escort you.
For now, it is my
duty to remain here.
I cannot desert my people
in a time of crisis.
[YUKINO]
But Princess. It's dangerous.
[LUCY]
Hey, I've got something!
You need to look at this! Now!
[HISUI]
What do you want to show us?
[LUCY]
It's my future self's diary!
[YUKINO]
What does it say?
[LUCY huffs]
Read it!
[YUKINO] "Our one hope,
is that the Eclipse gate
in this time period
gets destroyed.
If that happens, the one
that exists in the future
will disappear, as well.
And none of the horrible
things will ever happen."
But can that be true?
Yes, it can't still
be around in the future
if we destroy
the gate in our time.
[LUCY] There will be an
entirely new future where
the eclipse was
destroyed in the past.
It'll be gone forever.
Just a part of ancient history.
And if it's not around,
Rogue won't have a way
to travel back in time.
But that's already
happened in our time,
so is it still
possible to change it?
[HAPPY]
Yeah, and if we're lucky,
Rogue and the dragons will
get out of our time for good.
Well, it's certainly
worth a try!
[ARCADIOS] You're right. But it
is a rather daunting task.
How can we destroy
that massive structure
when our resources
are spread so thin?
It won't be an easy
job, that's for sure.
[LUCY] Easy or not
we have to find a way!
The future of the entire
world is at stake here.
Let's take it down.
I made a promise to myself
and there's no way
I'm gonna break it.
We've gotta hit it
with all the magic power
we can muster!
Let's go.
Now open.
The Gates of all Twelve Signs!
[LUCY] Zodiac!
[YUKINO] The Zodiac!
Go! Take it down!
[YUKINO, LUCY gasp]
[ARCADIOS, HISUI gasp]
Not a scratch?
I don't believe it!
[ARCADIOS] That's because
it was created from
an extremely magic-resistant
maginanium alloy.
Destroying it
will not be easy.
We can do it!
[HAPPY]
Fields of Gold!
[NATSU grunts]
Be safe, Gajeel.
[KINANA gasps]
[FUTURE ROGUE grunts]
I'll knock you outta here!
[FUTURE ROGUE groaning]
[NATSU]
Back to your own time!
[FUTURE ROGUE] I won't leave
until I'm finished here!
Oh yeah? Then what'll happen
to the Rogue from now?
[FUTURE ROGUE] He and I will
eventually merge into one.
Like two shadows
overlapping in darkness.
[NATSU]
That's not gonna happen!
I won't let you
take away his future!
[FUTURE ROGUE] If Acnologia
lives, there is no future!
[NATSU grunting]
[FUTURE ROGUE]
That's why I came here!
To take back our world!
[NATSU yelling]
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU growls]
[FUTURE ROGUE cackling]
[NATSU grunting]
[FUTURE ROGUE grunts]
[NATSU groans]
[FUTURE ROGUE cackling]
[NATSU panting]
What about Frosch?
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Frosch is dead!
[NATSU] Not today!
And, like everybody else,
I'm sure your
friend is terrified.
All because of
what you're doing.
[FROSCH whimpers]
Aw, cut the cryin'!
Your buddy Lector's
here to protect ya.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
One year from now, Frosch dies.
[NATSU] And you couldn't
do anything about it?
[FUTURE ROGUE]
No. It was unavoidable.
So what? Frosch is alive now!
That doesn't matter to me!
Because the Rogue
that used to waste time
playing around with
his cat is dead as well.
[NATSU growls]
You can change that!
You don't understand that I'm
going to change everything.
After all the pain
and suffering I've seen
I know our only hope
is through total destruction!
That doesn't sound
like hope to me!
All you're gonna do
is cause more pain!
And that's the price that must
be paid to secure my future!
You want happiness for everyone,
but it will never happen!
I will never stop trying!
[NATSU] I will never stop
fighting for my future
and everyone else's!
The world that
we all live in
is what we make of it!
It's not just up to you!
[ATLAS FLAME]
Natsu!
[FUTURE ROGUE gasps]
And no matter what's
gonna happen tomorrow...
[NATSU] I'm gonna keep
fighting to live today!
[FUTURE ROGUE groaning]
[NATSU growling]
[FUTURE ROGUE screaming]
[NATSU growling, yelling]
[LUCY] I can't believe it.
They're all gone.
[LUCY gasps]
[NATSU]
Sorry to keep you waiting, Lucy.
Cocky lizards.
Listen up, ugly!
You just picked a fight
with the wrong guy!
I'm Natsu Dragneel
of the Fairy Tail guild.
I'm a Dragon Slayer!
And I'm here
to do just that.
[NATSU yelling] Fire Dragon
Brilliant Flame! Roar!
Fire Dragon Crushing Fang!
[LUCY sobbing]
Natsu! It's no use!
Please stop!
[NATSU]
I ain't givin' up that easily!
[NATSU yelling]
[NATSU groaning]
[LUCY]
Natsu!
[NATSU]
I ain't quittin'. I refuse!
I won't run,
and I won't turn back.
Do you hear me?
You're dead meat!
Natsu!
[NATSU yelling]
I can't keep this up...
[LUCY]
...for much longer.
[LUCY grunts]
How the heck did that
not do anything to it?
All that and we couldn't
even move it an inch.
[YUKINO, LIBRA gasp]
[HAPPY gasps] We need to
get away from the gate,
you guys! Something's coming!
[LUCY screaming]
[ALL screaming, grunting]
[ALL grunting, screaming]
[LUCY screaming]
[LUCY groaning]
[ALL groaning]
[HISUI grunts]
[NATSU panting]
Natsu totally
destroyed the gate!
Nice work!
[NATSU grunting, panting]
I don't believe it.
The gate was designed
to be indestructible.
[HISUI] What do you think
is going to happen now?
If we were correct,
the Eclipse should
cease to exist
in the future as well.
Which means Rogue can't use it
to travel back to our time.
And everything should
go back to normal.
[NATSU gasps]
The dragon is starting to glow!
[LUCY]
What's happening?
[ATLAS FLAME]
We're returning to our own time.
[COBRA] Hm. So you're finally
turnin' tail and runnin'.
Get lost.
[ZIRCONIS groans]
This can't be!
Well ain't that something.
It's disappearing.
[ZIRCONIS] No! You're just
a bunch of stupid humans!
There's no way you can beat me!
Please forgive me.
Don't get near him!
[ARCADIOS]
Princess!
[LAXUS]
Bad idea.
The gateway between
our times was created
as the result of my decree.
[HISUI] Which means,
I am solely to blame
for throwing your
time into disarray.
[HISUI] Your kind live
400 years in the past,
and humans live
in the present day.
Therefore, we were never fated
to have conflict
with each other.
But I foolishly interfered.
And I apologize for that.
[ZIRCONIS]
Who are you?
Hisui E. Fiore.
[ZIRCONIS]
Hisui?
[HISUI]
In the language of my ancestors,
it means "jade."
Same as your color.
[ZIRCONIS]
Same as me, eh?
Yes, that's right.
[ZIRCONIS]
Hm.
[HISUI] I shall call you
the Jade Dragon.
[ZIRCONIS] Jade Dragon, huh?
Does got a nice ring to it.
[ZIRCONIS gasps]
Hey! Wait! What's happening?
I got tricked by
a stupid human! No!
[WENDY, LAXUS gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[FRIED gasps]
[COBRA grunts]
So uh. Was that us?
I think they must've finally
beaten those dragons!
Yeah, I think they did too.
[BETH gasps]
[MILLIANNA gasps]
[ATLAS FLAME]
I will never forget you.
Natsu Dragneel.
Couldn't've done it without ya.
Thanks, Uncle.
[LUCY sighs]
They're all gone.
All the little
guys disappeared!
Did we beat 'em, guys?
I don't know what just
happened, but I like it!
[ROMEO]
I bet it was Natsu!
I just knew he could do it!
[GAJEEL]
Did the thing just vanish?
I can't believe
we pulled it off!
Yeah. Kinda.
This doesn't sit
right with me.
[MAVIS] All those Dragon Slayers
gave it their all.
But not a single one
could slay a dragon.
[STING]
Man, that was totally pathetic.
[ROGUE] And we call ourselves
"Dragon Slayers"? What a joke.
[STING]
Just goes to show ya
how tough those
things really are.
[STING] And Acnologia's
even more powerful than them.
[ROGUE] Honestly, I'd rather not
think about that right now.
[STING]
No doubt.
It's weird, we fought
all those dragons,
and now they're gone,
but it sure as hell
doesn't feel like a victory.
[JUVIA, MELDY laughing]
It is a victory.
We protected our
friends, didn't we?
I may not know
Rogue very well,
but he'll never become you.
[FUTURE ROGUE] The shadow.
[NATSU] Huh?
[FUTURE ROGUE] The shadow
will continue to follow me.
He's relentless.
And he won't be satisfied
until he's swallowed me whole.
And then on that
fateful day that
I lose Frosch,
it will finally happen.
I will be swallowed
by the darkness forever.
[NATSU]
That's not gonna happen.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
It most certainly will.
One year from now.
You must warn
the Rogue from your time,
to protect Frosch
one year from now.
[inaudible]
[NATSU gasps]
[FUTURE ROGUE]
They will kill Frosch.
[FUTURE LUCY grunting]
What was that? A dream?
[FUTURE NATSU]
Hey! Lucy!
[FUTURE LUCY]
Huh?
[FUTURE NATSU]
Would ya get over here already?
[FUTURE HAPPY]
Everybody's waiting on you!
[FUTURE LUCY gasps]
[FUTURE NATSU laughing]
Come on, we still have
adventures to go on!
Yeah!
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY whimpering]
I'm crying.
[NATSU]
Hey, is something wrong?
[LUCY]
No, it's nothing. I'm okay.
Thank you.
[HAPPY] Oh man, Natsu,
did you hear the news?
[NATSU] I hear a lot of things,
little buddy, what's up?
[HAPPY] Well, as a thank you
for saving everybody,
the king invited us to
a huge party at the castle!
[NATSU]
Whoa! Seriously?
[HAPPY] Oh yeah,
and you know the king
is gonna have the most
awesome food ever!
[NATSU] Ooh! I wonder
if they're gonna serve
some broiled fire,
or steamed fire?
[HAPPY] Uh, I don't know
about that, Natsu.
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next Time: The Grand Banquet!
[NATSU] I would love to scarf
down some roasted fire, too!
[HAPPY] How in the heck can you
cook fire? With more fire?