Can I get you some
water or anything?
I'm fine. Thanks.
[HOTEYE]
Hmm.
His eyes.
[HOTEYE]
His eye injuries aren't severe.
He should be able to
see again before long.
That said, many of his other
injuries are far more serious.
He fought four members
of the Oración Seis alone.
He can't have expected to
come out of that unscathed.
Yeah, I guess not.
Looks like it's
headin' straight for us.
I don't suppose you'd want to
hole up in there with Jellal.
[RACER]
Don't be stupid.
[ANGEL] Should we find
a different house then?
There are plenty around.
This place is a ghost town.
That's not what I'm gettin' at.
This storm's our chance
to make some distance.
It could very well be, but
where do you think we should go?
[RACER] Long as it ain't here?
I couldn't care less.
[RACER]
Come on!
What? Is freedom
too much for you?
Can't handle the idea
of not havin' a boss?
[ANGEL]
No, but--
"No but," what?
We just got outta jail.
And we got free of Brain.
Finally, no one
tells us what to do.
You already wanna give
that up? Cobra, talk to 'em.
We have no boss, remember?
You don't choose for her.
Fine. What about you, Midnight?
[RACER]
Hey.
[RACER] Hey! Somethin'
wrong with your ears?
Stop runnin' your
damn mouth, Racer.
It'll force you
to think for once,
and you might actually like it.
[RACER]
I'll shut up when I'm finished.
Now listen--
I've decided.
I'm joining Crime Sorciere.
You're swapping one
master for another?
At least give freedom
a try. We don't need him.
We've been imprisoned in
some way our whole lives.
We don't owe this world jack.
Think about what it did to us.
[ANGEL]
I've thought this through.
And I'll be going with Jellal.
[RACER]
Nothin' to say, boys?
Heh, I get it.
Well, suit yourselves.
As for me--
[MIDNIGHT]
Never again.
I'll never be a pawn in
someone else's game again.
I'll live and die just
as free as I am now.
There we go!
[MIDNIGHT]
But.
[RACER] Ever tell ya
how much I hate that word?
[COBRA laughing]
[RACER]
You laughin' at me?
Naw. I just heard a voice
from old times is all.
Hey, there. Thought
you'd kicked the bucket.
[RACER gasps]
[RUSTY]
Is that so?
I'd accuse you of faithlessness,
but I thought you'd
be in prison right now,
and for the rest of your
lives, for that matter.
So, what brings the
Oración Seis here?
[RACER]
Rusty?
[ANGEL] You were with
Grimoire Heart's Seven Kin.
Rustyrose! Is that really you?
[RUSTY]
You're here, Meldy?
Where have you been?
Why are you with them?
It's hard to explain. You look
terrible, what happened?
Trust is like iron,
for if it's neglected,
it corrodes over time.
I'm leaving.
[MELDY]
No, wait! Stay a while, please!
I no longer have
business with you.
I know.
But could you talk to me,
for old times sake?
[RUSTY]
Hmph.
The past is dead. Bury it.
Slow it down.
Your old friend's not the only
one who's got questions.
Somethin's got ya scared,
Rusty. It's in your voice.
And I never took you
for a pushover, so,
I'd like to know what that is.
Now talk.
[MELDY] Wait. Is this
what I think it is?
Doesn't feel like I have
much of a choice here.
Well, you have two options.
One just sucks.
[RUSTY]
I've been to Tartaros.
[COBRA] Tartaros?
With the Nine Demon Gates?
[RUSTY] Well, yes, but that
guild is more than it appears.
[JELLAL]
Hm?
Seven years ago, after we lost
to Fairy Tail on Tenrou Island,
Hades, Kain, and
I tried to escape.
That's when Zeref appeared.
The rest followed quickly.
Master Hades was killed
before my eyes.
I was knocked unconscious.
Woke up drifting in the sea.
Obviously, I managed to survive,
but I couldn't find
my old guildmates.
I wandered everywhere,
searching. Trying to heal.
So you never found Kain?
[RUSTY] No, I don't know
where he is or what he's doing.
Hell, I don't even know
if he survived that mess.
I see.
[RUSTY] The Baram Alliance
was the political spine
of the Dark Guilds.
Between our factions and
Tartaros, there was balance.
But Grimoire got
its heart cut out.
Its body scattered to the winds.
And your whole guild was
tossed into some dungeon.
Which left Tartaros, and a
power vacuum the size of Fiore.
What exactly are
you tryin' to say?
Everywhere I traveled,
I was followed by a rumor
I didn't want to believe.
The Dark Guilds that had
once followed Grimoire
were being annihilated,
one by one.
The fatality rate from these
attacks made one thing clear.
Tartaros was responsible.
[SOLDIER A]
At your stations!
[SOLDIER B]
Who are you people?
[RUSTY] No one. Just a few
messengers of darkness.
We came here in the hopes
we could meet with the leaders
of Tartaros, if they're free.
[SOLDIER C]
Messengers of darkness?
Identify yourselves at once!
We're men who don't take
questions from cowardly dogs
that turn on their allies the
moment they sense weakness.
[ZANCROW] Look, we've got no
interest in you minion types.
But we're in a pretty crap mood,
and you're in our way.
[SOLDIER D]
Kill 'em!
[SOLDIER E]
No one gets through!
Well, I suppose that this
gate is as good a place
for you to die as any.
Bleve.
I was hopin' I could save
all this rage for your bosses,
but screw it.
Flame God Bellow!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Ha! That was like
stompin' on maggots!
I can't even call
that a warm-up.
[SOLDIER F] You. Why are
you here? Who are you?
We're from Grimoire Heart.
Your former confederates.
Bleed quick now!
Forgive us, we're unaccustomed
to such churlish visits.
That this may be,
but it doesn't hold a candle
to the cannibalistic attacks
you've been launching
on the guilds beneath you.
[KYOKA]
Hm.
Let us introduce ourselves.
I am Kyoka, one of Nine
Demon Gates of Tartaros.
And I am called Rustyrose.
I am one of the Seven Kin.
We belong to a member guild
of the Baram Alliance.
Grimoire Heart.
My name is Azuma.
Mine's Zancrow.
[KYOKA] You're from Grimoire
Heart? Of the Baram Alliance?
Both the alliance and that guild
are long forgotten relics.
You having trouble
with your eyes?
I'll give ya the
"forgotten" bit,
but if we're a relic, then
what killed all your guards?
[KYOKA]
Three bitter failures.
The Baram Alliance is gone.
It dissolved when Tartaros
became the last guild standing.
What do you mean
"last guild standing"?
We're standin' right
in front of ya!
Tell me something. Do you
know what you've done?
Did you willfully violate
the most basic
principle of alliance?
Am I on trial, then?
The verdict is in.
You've assaulted our
subordinate guilds, one by one.
You killed most and
abducted the rest
for Zeref knows what purpose.
This treachery begs vengeance.
[KYOKA chuckles]
[KYOKA] I'm quite busy. If it's
appeasement you're after,
I suggest you look elsewhere.
I've neither the time
nor interest needed
to continue this little talk.
[chuckles]
We didn't come here to talk.
But you already knew that.
That takes some guts, stormin'
Tartaros just the three o' ya.
Guts or insanity,
I'm not sure which one.
I don't get it.
How could those two--?
So, could someone wake me up
once Rusty's finished bragging?
That sass needs an off
switch. Just ignore her.
Go on. What happened next?
I'm listening.
Your guild is at fault for
the broken peace between us.
To restore it, you must
first make reparations.
[KYOKA]
Really? Must I?
[RUSTY] Children fear no
flame till they get burned.
That's why you must pay
for what you've done
to prove you won't repeat it.
Hm. And what's your price?
You have me curious.
We want half of the dark guild
members you abducted returned.
As a show of our goodwill,
we ask nothing for the dead.
I was against offerin' your
guild a deal in the first place.
But the sooner we're out of here
the better, so just take it.
[KYOKA]
Hmm.
[RUSTY] All things considered,
this is a lenient offer.
Agree to our demand,
and the Baram Alliance
could live once more.
That's quite enough.
[KYOKA]
You pitiful fool.
How dare you.
[RUSTY groaning]
What did you do to him?
I hope you're ready
to fight a real war!
The art of enhancing human pain
grants such a sense
of exhilaration.
[yelps]
My comrades.
The Arc of Embodiment, correct?
What a desperate ploy.
Grimoire Heart's
a relic after all.
Rise from the underworld!
My Jet Black Sword that
cleaves through all!
[screaming]
Who is that man?
Disgusting. Begone.
[RUSTY screaming]
[KYOKA] Zeref's return
is quite close at hand.
And the beginning of his new era
shall mark the end of mankind's.
[KYOKA] Why so scared?
You've nothing to lose.
So utterly broken.
You're not worth torturing.
Scurry on home with
your imaginary friends.
[RUSTY] There's more in Tartaros
than the Nine Demon Gates.
I saw something there, in the
shadows. Something far worse.
[COBRA]
That's a strange story.
Wish I cared.
[JELLAL] She said Zeref
was coming, did she?
Said it with certainty.
Meaning that Tartaros is trying
to make contact with him?
You'll have to find
out for yourself.
I'd rather face the fires
of hell than that one again.
Good talk. Guess I'll
see you around.
Wish I'd known.
I'm heading out.
To find Tartaros.
No, you can't.
You're in no condition
to travel, or to fight.
That may be true.
Still, I must do this.
There's no choice.
[MIDNIGHT] We won't go with you.
Not to attack Tartaros.
[MIDNIGHT] They may have broken
their pact with Grimoire Heart,
but they haven't with us.
We gave our word that
we wouldn't attack them.
Even now, that word is binding.
[MELDY] That's where you
draw your "moral" line?
Our guild may
have been unlawful,
but for all our
many transgressions,
never once did we betray a pact.
We won't forsake the one
source of integrity we had.
[JELLAL] That's disappointing,
but I must go regardless.
Even if that means I go alone.
For now, I'll say farewell,
but I will come for you again.
I swear it.
Careful, there're lots
of roots to trip on.
Thank you.
[MELDY]
So, I was wondering.
[JELLAL]
Mm?
[MELDY] Why do you care so
much about the Oración Seis?
Is it because of something
Doranbolt said?
They're all prisoners.
They were captured as children.
Held against their will
in the Tower of Heaven.
Their circumstances are my own.
That's where the seeds
of our sins were planted.
That's where we lost
our childhoods together.
[JELLAL] No matter what,
there's some part of each of us
that will always be
locked in that tower.
That bond is irrevocable.
None of us who shed sweat
and blood in that place
would deny it.
No, not even Sawyer.
You share that pain,
that burden.
[JELLAL] Pain and prayers
were all we had there.
The Seis prayed for Nirvana to
take the darkness of their lives
and give them light.
Nirvana's spell has faded.
Their prayers remain.
[MELDY]
What prayers?
[JELLAL] Richard prays
to find the brother he lost
when he was first taken to
the Tower all those years ago.
Sawyer prays to be so fast
he can never be caught again.
Sorano prays to be free of this
earth, to vanish into the sky.
Erik, he prays to hear
the voice of the one friend
who might listen to his story.
And Macbeth, he prays
to sleep quietly,
in a world that rings
with screams and sobbing.
Their prayers granted
them great power.
Zero twisted that.
Turned the pain of
unrequited hope to anger.
He took advantage
of them. As did I.
[MELDY]
That wasn't you.
I'm done searching for excuses.
Regardless of what
Ultear believed,
darkness can only
engulf the ones
who let it inside their hearts.
Natsu told me something
in that Tower.
I still think
about it even now.
You'll never know what
it means to be free!
As long as you're
possessed by that spirit,
you'll always be a slave!
You can do it, Jellal.
Free yourself!
[JELLAL]
Helping them to free themselves,
like Natsu did for me,
it's part of my atonement.
[MELDY]
I understand.
Tch.
[MIDNIGHT] What'd you hear?
Anything to worry about?
[COBRA]
Naw, just Jellal.
I bet that I could
tune him out easy
if he'd stop sayin'
my real name.
[ANGEL]
He doesn't know how shy you are.
[COBRA]
Ugh. Shut it, Sorano.
[chuckles]
Look out!
[MELDY]
What is this?
How did the Tower
of Dingir get here?
[RUSTY]
Simply enough, my dear.
I summoned it using
my Arc of Embodiment.
[MELDY] Rusty? Were you planning
to attack us from the start?
[RUSTY] I'm not trying
to hurt you, Meldy,
I'm trying to rebuild!
Grimoire Heart can live
again through us! Together!
[MELDY]
What if I don't want it to?
[RUSTY]
Then I'll have to persuade you!
You'll join us if you
want him to live.
You'd be sparin' yourself
a lotta pain as well!
[screaming]
You aren't going to win
this, Meldy, so join us.
I don't want to hurt an old
friend any more than I have to.
What's the matter?
The girl I knew would've at
least tried to fight back!
You aren't even using
your Sensory Link!
[MELDY]
You're in so much pain already.
I refuse to cause you any more.
[RUSTY]
What do you mean?
You told me that the past is
dead, but you're trapped in it.
What does that make you?
Seven years I wandered!
Seven long years I never
gave up on finding you!
That hope was the only
thing I lived for.
But I've moved on, and you
can still do the same.
Don't let the past
constrain you.
Look to the future instead!
[growling]
[RUSTY]
Shut up!
[screaming]
Don't do this. Don't force me
to kill you. Join me and live.
There is no other path for you.
Come on back to us!
Just look! Everybody's waiting,
all we need is you!
I can't. That's not real,
Rusty. It's the past.
I haven't forgotten it.
[MELDY]
But I live now!
Every day, Jellal and I risk our
lives to atone for those times.
I found a guild that
strives to do better!
It's called Crime Sorciere!
Then that's what I must destroy.
You won't blow me off
once you have nothing else.
[JELLAL]
Leave her... alone.
[RUSTY] How're you gonna
fight me in that state?
You're holding Meldy back.
So begone from this world!
[thud]
[RUSTY yelps]
What's happened? Where is he?
[COBRA] How about you
ditch that scrap of cloth
and see for yourself?
[JELLAL]
Meldy.
Are your eyes back to normal?
What color's my hair?
I know that much blind.
[BOTH gasp]
[JELLAL]
You came.
Nothin' personal,
we just couldn't think
of anything better to do.
So, for now at least,
we've decided to tag
along with you two.
See how we like it.
To free the victim
in your heart,
you fight to build
a better world.
A world that victim can forgive.
I go my own way, but
I have respect for yours.
[JELLAL]
Right.
Rustyrose. You too will have
to find your own way forward.
However,
the isolation tormenting
you can finally cease.
When you find yourself
ready to make amends
for the sins of your past,
there's a place for you
in Crime Sorciere.
Until that day, farewell.
I gotta go fast!
Master Makarov needs to
know what's going on!
Hang in there, Natsu!
You too, Lucy!
Smell anything? Mira?
[NATSU sniffing]
Not yet. This place is
built like a friggin' maze.
Damn it!
Let's keep on
moving west for now.
Don't worry! We'll find
her, I can feel it!
Mira!
[LUCY]
Where are you?!
[MAN] The demons of
the Books of Zeref.
Also known as the "Etherious."
A human imitation doesn't stand
a chance against the real thing.
Isn't that right, Master?
This is naught
but the beginning.
So much darkness waits
to spill from our world.
Enough to smother the
waning light of this world
beneath a blanket
as black as night.
[LUCY] After casting
a Macro on herself,
Seilah unleashes the full
brunt of her power,
overwhelming Mirajane.
Faced with imminent death,
Mirajane recalls the most
important times of her life.
The times she got to
spend with her family.
The power of that
strong, gentle bond
summons the kind of miracle that
no demon can stand against.
Next Time:
"Tartaros Chapter Alegria."
She uses her strength
to protect her family.