HEY GUYS! READY FOR SOME
MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT WHEN
YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT TOO
CLOSE TO THE TV!
- PREVIOUSLY, ON FAIRY TAIL!
- WE GOT IN A HUGE FIGHT WITH
OUR RIVAL GUILD, PHANTOM LORD,
AND BOTH MASTER MAKAROV
AND ERZA WERE TAKEN OUT!
NOW THEIR MAGIC
GIANT'S ATTACKING US
AND THE ONLY WAY TO STOP IT
IS TO BEAT THEIR STRONGEST
TEAM, THE ELEMENT 4!
LUCY'S LAYING LOW
IN OUR HIDEOUT,
'CAUSE PHANTOM'S AFTER HER,
BUT IT MAY NOT BE SAFE
THERE EITHER.
- Loke: I GOT A BAD FEELIN'
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( bell tolls )
- Elfman: SEE, LOOK AT IT NOW!
- Gray: YEAH, IT'S DEFINITELY
DRAWING THE MAGIC CIRCLE
SLOWER THAN BEFORE.
- Mirajane: SO WE WERE RIGHT.
- Gray: FIRE, WATER,
AIR, AND EARTH.
- Elfman: JUST LIKE
WE WERE SAYING,
THE GIANT AND THE SPELL GET
THEIR POWER FROM THE ELEMENTS.
- THAT'S THE TRUE COMBINED
POWER OF THE ELEMENT FOUR.
THREE HAVE BEEN DEFEATED.
TOTOMARU OF THE GREAT FLAME,
WAS TAKEN OUT WITH JUPITER.
ELFMAN TOTALLY ANNIHILATED
SOL OF THE EARTH.
AND JUVIA OF THE GREAT SEA
WAS TAKEN OUT OF
THE EQUATION BY GRAY.
- SO THERE'S ONE LEFT.
- IF WE STOP HIM WE'LL STOP THE
GIANT FROM CASTING THE SPELL!
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHO
THE LAST ELEMENT IS?
- ARIA OF THE GREAT SKY. AND
HE'LL BE THE TOUGHEST TO BEAT.
HE'S THE STRONGEST MEMBER
OF THE ELEMENT 4.
HE'S ALSO THE ONE WHO
DRAINED THE MASTER
OF HIS MAGICAL ENERGY,
LEAVING HIM POWERLESS.
- Porlyusica: MUST BE
IMAGINING THINGS.
- Happy: WINGS OF FLAME!
- YOU'RE STILL STANDING AFTER
MY ATTACK. VERY IMPRESSIVE.
- I'M FIRED UP NOW.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT!
- CAREFUL.
- AIRSPACE SEVER!
( he screams in pain )
- HE'S THE STRONGEST WIZARD
IN THE ELEMENT 4.
HE MIGHT BE TOO
POWERFUL EVEN FOR NATSU!
- THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE BETTER
THAN YOU, YOUNG DRAGON SLAYER.
- WE'LL SEE 'BOUT THAT!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- HE'S GONE!
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- I SHALL END THIS WITH A GIFT.
I WILL ALLOW YOU TO JOIN YOUR
MASTER IN HIS SUFFERING.
AIRSPACE DRAIN!
( Natsu screams )
SO SAD! YES, BECAUSE ANY
WIZARD CAUGHT IN MY AIRSPACE
WILL BE COMPLETELY
DRAINED OF THEIR POWERS!
- I CAN FEEL IT! MY POWERS
ARE BEIN' SUCKED OUT!
- NATSU!
- NO. I CAN'T.
- ERZA!
- YOU'RE HERE. YOU SURE
IT'S OKAY FOR YOU TO MOVE?
YOU'RE INJURED!
- SHE IS P.O'D!
- Erza: SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO HARMED OUR MASTER.
- THE GREAT ERZA SCARLET.
HOW UNFORTUNATE.
SEEMS THE BRILLIANT
TITANIA WILL LOSE HER HEAD
ALONG SIDE HER
FRIEND SALAMANDER.
- OUR MASTER SUFFERED
GREATLY BY YOUR HANDS.
I WILL AVENGE HIM.
- YOU CAN'T!
- WELL, NOW THAT I'M FINALLY
FACED WITH A WORTHY OPPONENT.
I GUESS IT'S TIME I START TAKING
MY BATTLES MORE SERIOUSLY.
- Gray: HIS EYES?
- Mirajane: YES.
- Gray: WHAT'S SO
SPECIAL ABOUT 'EM?
- Mirajane: EVIDENTLY, ARIA
KEEPS HIS EYES COVERED
WITH BANDAGES. HE DOES
THIS BECAUSE IT HELPS
TO CONTROL HIS
OVERWHELMING MAGICAL POWER.
- Elfman: SO, IT'S
ALL IN HIS EYES?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SO WHEN WE FIND HIM,
WE HAVE TO BEAT HIM
BEFORE HE OPENS THEM
BECAUSE IF THAT HAPPENS,
WE DON'T STAND A
CHANCE AT VICTORY.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- THE MAGIC CIRCLE'S GLOWING!
- DOES THAT MEAN IT'S DONE?
- YEP! LOOKS LIKE OUR
GOOSE IS COOKED!
- Loke: COME ON, GUYS! DON'T
GIVE UP! WE CAN DO THIS!
- Aria: NOW TITANIA.
STEP INTO ZERO
AIRSPACE OF DEATH.
IT CONSUMES THE LIVES
OF ALL WHO DARE TO ENTER.
- I'M TOO CUTE TO DIE!
- Erza: A SPELL THAT
CONSUMES LIFE?
TELL ME! HOW CAN YOU DO THIS?
HOW CAN YOU JUST TAKE LIVES
SO EASILY? YOU SCOUNDREL!
- IT'D BE MORE FUN
TO SHOW YOU!
- ERZA!
- LET'S SEE JUST HOW WELL
YOU HANDLE THIS, TITANIA!
- BUT HOW...? SHE'S CUTTING
THROUGH MY AIRSPACE!
NO!
- Erza: HEAVEN'S WHEEL!
SCATTERED PETALS!
( Aria screams )
- SHE TOOK HIM OUT
WITH ONE HIT!
- MAN, SHE IS ONE SCARY LADY!
- Erza: SOMEONE LIKE YOU
COULD NEVER HOLD A CANDLE
TO THE STRENGTH OF OUR MASTER.
YOU'LL BE REMEMBERED
ONLY AS A SOBBING COWARD
WHO FELL BY MY HAND.
- THAT'S SO SAD.
- EVERYBODY GET DOWN!
- I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GONNA HELP US!
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- WHOA!
- ITS EYES AREN'T
GLOWING ANYMORE.
( Happy screaming )
- ERZA! WAKE UP!
- NOW WHAT?
- NATSU MUST'VE BEATEN
THE LAST ONE.
- YES! WE DID IT!
WE STOPPED THE ABYSS BREAK
SPELL FROM BEING CAST!
- Elfman: 'CAUSE WE'RE AWESOME!
- Gray: HA! YOU KNOW IT!
- Mirajane: ALL THE MEMBERS
OF THE ELEMENT 4
HAVE BEEN DEFEATED!
- ( fairy tail crew cheering )
- GUESS THEY TOOK OUT THE
ELEMENT 4! THAT'LL SHOW EM!
- OH NO, REEDUS,
ARE YOU OKAY?
- OUI. WELL AREN'T YOU
THE STUBBORN ONE.
- IT'S OVER, TUBBY.
MIGHT AS WELL GIVE UP.
SO JUST HAND OVER THE BRAT.
- OUR BOSS DOESN'T LIKE TO WAIT.
( he chuckles )
- LUCY, RUN WHILE YOU STILL CAN!
- AND LEAVE YOU?
I'LL STAY HERE AND FIGHT!
- PLEASE, FOR THE SAKE
OF THE GUILD, DO IT!
- BUT...
- STOP IT. I'LL CRY.
- OH, HOW TOUCHING.
- I LIKE WHERE THIS IS GOIN'.
- PICTO MAGIC! ROAR OF SILVER!
- WOW! VULCANS, HUH? JUST LIKE
THEY GOT ON MOUNT HAWKOBAY!
- MIRROR MAGIC. FORM MIRROR!
MY MIRRORS WILL REFLECT ANY
ATTACK RIGHT BACK AT YA!
YA SEE?
- Lucy: REEDUS.
I'M SO SORRY!
- YOU'RE GONNA LEAVE FATTY
HERE TO TAKE THE FALL?
THAT'S NOT NICE!
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH A SAD
EXCUSE FOR A GUILD.
THEY JUST LET ANYONE
JOIN FAIRY TAIL?
- Lucy: TAKE THAT BACK!
- Gajeel: YOU GONNA MAKE ME?
HEY, BIG GUY.
SOUND BLAST HOWLING!
( he screams )
- Lucy: REEDUS!
- Gajeel: WHAT A CREAM PUFF.
YOU ACTUALLY LIKE
HANGING OUT WITH GUYS
LIKE THAT, LITTLE PRINCESS?
- YOU. YOU MONSTER.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
- WHY'D THE GIANT STOP?
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
( she groans in pain )
( explosion )
- HECK OF A WAY TO SAY HELLO!
- Loke: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOIN' WITH LUCY?
IF YOU DON'T LET HER
GO RIGHT NOW, YOU'LL BE SORRY!
THAT IS, IF YOU LIVE
TO SEE TOMORROW!
- OH REALLY? WELL, I LIKE
A GOOD CHALLENGE!
SO LET'S DANCE, FAIRY!
- LOKE?
- WHAT'S UP WITH THIS GUY?
SOMETHIN' ABOUT HIM
SEEMS DIFFERENT.
HE'S NOT SOME ORDINARY
HOLDER TYPE WIZARD CHUMP.
SO JUST WHO ARE YOU ANYWAY?
AND WHY DON'T YOU SMELL RIGHT?
- I DUNNO WHAT YOU MEAN.
I NEVER GOT ANY COMPLAINTS
FROM THE LADIES.
NOT NOW!
- GUESS I WAS WRONG.
YOU WEREN'T MUCH OF A
CHALLENGE, AFTER ALL.
HEY, I'M HAULIN' BLONDIE
BACK TO THE BOSS.
YOU TWO TAKE CARE OF LOVER BOY.
- Bozu, Sue: GOT IT!
- LET HER GO.
- SOUND BLAST DISTURBED!
( metallic clink )
- ( Loke screams in pain )
- MIRROR MAGIC. KALEIDOSCOPE!
Sue: IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU LIKE LOOKIN'
AT YOUR OWN PATHETIC FACE,
'CAUSE IT'S THE ONLY THING
YOU'RE GONNA SEE FOR A WHILE.
- Jose: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
MY STRONGEST WIZARDS,
THE ELEMENT 4,
WERE COMPLETELY WIPED OUT BY
THAT WORTHLESS FAIRY TAIL SCUM?
- Gajeel: GUESS THAT MAKES 'EM
EVEN WORSE THAN SCUM, HUH?
- GAJEEL. SO YOU'VE RETURNED
BEARING A GIFT HAVE YOU?
- YEAH, I PICKED YOU UP A LITTLE
SOMETHIN' WHILE I WAS OUT.
- Jose: OH, VERY
IMPRESSIVE, MY BOY.
HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO TRACK
HER DOWN SO QUICKLY?
- Gajeel: YOU SHOULD
NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
THE NOSE OF A DRAGON SLAYER.
- SHE IS ALIVE, RIGHT?
WITHOUT A PULSE,
SHE'S WORTHLESS TO US.
- I WAS PRETTY ROUGH
WITH HER. LET'S SEE!
YEP! SHE'S STILL
ALIVE AND KICKIN'!
- EXCELLENTLY DONE, GAJEEL!
I KNEW I COULD COUNT ON YOU!
( announcement system tone )
- Jose: ATTENTION YOU
PATHETIC FAIRY TAIL WORMS!
LISTEN CAREFULLY BECAUSE
I'LL ONLY SAY THIS ONCE!
- WHAT THE...?
- IT'S MASTER JOSE!
( Lucy screams )
- I KNOW THAT SCREAM.
- LUCY?
- OH, NO!
- Jose: WE HAVE CAPTURED
YOUR PRECIOUS LUCY HEARTFILIA.
WHICH MEANS OUR FIRST ORDER OF
BUSINESS IS NOW OUT OF THE WAY.
AND THAT LEAVES US WITH JUST ONE
MORE THING. MY FAVORITE PART.
WIPING ALL OF YOU
MISERABLE BRATS
RIGHT OFF THE FACE OF THE EARTH!
- NO WAY.
- PLEASE. FORGIVE ME.
I COULDN'T PROTECT YOU.
SORRY, LUCY.
- I KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE WAITED.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE SOONER.
BUT I WAS AFRAID.
I WAS TOO SCARED TO BE
NEAR LUCY AND NOW SHE'S GONE.
( he weeps )
PATHETIC!
SHE'S RIGHT. I DO LOOK
ABSOLUTELY PATHETIC.
DON'T I, KAREN?
- OH NO!
- I THINK THERE'S MORE NOW!
- THERE'S A TON OF 'EM!
( chatter in the background )
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
THEY STILL WANNA FIGHT?
- KEEP AN EYE ON THE GIRL.
THERE ARE STILL SOME PESTS
SCUTTLING AROUND MY GUILD HALL.
- YOU TALKIN' ABOUT SALAMANDER?
- YES, HIM, AND HIS FRIENDS.
THEY'VE BEEN LUCKY THUS FAR
BUT THEIR LUCK IS ABOUT
TO COME TO AN END.
I'M GOING TO EXTERMINATE
THEM MYSELF!
- AW MAN. THEY GOT LUCY!
- NATSU.
- ERZA!
- LISTEN.
USE YOUR STRENGTH.
IT LIES DORMANT,
DEEP DOWN INSIDE OF YOU.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF. FIND IT.
FIND YOUR STRENGTH.
AND AWAKEN IT. FOR LUCY.
FOR OUR GUILD.
DO IT NOW, NATSU! SHOW ME.
SHOW ME YOU CAN SURPASS ME!
( roaring )
( he screams )
- IT'S NATSU.
- MAKAROV? HOW ARE
YOU FEELING?
NOT YET. YOU STILL NEED REST.
- SINCE WHEN
DO I LISTEN TO YOU?
- A REMARKABLY SPEEDY RECOVERY.
ESPECIALLY FOR SOMEONE
SO LONG IN THE TOOTH.
- IS THAT SO? WELL.
- DO YOU HASTEN TO YOUR DEATH?
- I WILL TAKE THE CHANCE.
MY CHILDREN NEED ME NOW.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
- I SWEAR. NOTHING
CHANGES WITH HIM.
- Mirajane: ERZA?
- SHE OKAY?
- MAN, IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMETHIN' BIG WENT DOWN.
- IT'S YOU.
- YOU'RE INJURED...
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE!
- YEAH, YOU'RE NOT REALLY
LOOKING TOO GOOD.
- WHOA.
- Mirajane: THAT'S ARIA!
- Elfman: YOU GOT
SHOT BY THAT CANNON
AND STILL FOUGHT THIS GUY?
- Gray: WHAT THE HECK WERE
YOU THINKIN'? HOLD ON.
- Mirajane: YOU BEAT
HIM ON YOUR OWN?
- I MUST ADMIT. I NEVER
WANTED ANYONE TO SEE ME
IN SUCH A WRETCHED STATE.
I GUESS I STILL HAVE
A LOT TO LEARN.
- WHAT THE...?
- WHAT IS IT?
- I SENSE DEATH!
- Gray: I DON'T LIKE
THIS FEELIN'.
- Elfman: I'M SUPER MANLY
AND IT GIVES ME CHILLS.
- Mirajane: WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'S PURE EVIL.
( slow clap )
- Jose: BRAVO. YOU ARE
ALL QUITE KEEN.
VERY IMPRESSIVE,
FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS.
I KNEW THIS WOULD BE FUN
BUT NEVER IN MY
WILDEST DREAMS DID I THINK
IT WOULD BE THIS ENTERTAINING.
YOU ANNIHILATED
THE JUPITER CANNON,
DISPOSED OF MY ELITE ELEMENT 4.
AND YOU EVEN MANAGED TO BRING
MY MAGIC GIANT TO ITS KNEES.
- MASTER JOSE!
- Elfman: THIS CREEP?
- Gray: HE'S PHANTOM'S MASTER?
- IT'S LIKE THERE'S A BLACK
CLOUD HANGING OVER HIM.
I FEEL SICK JUST
BEING NEAR HIM.
- THANK YOU. YOU'VE BEEN SO
KIND TO ENTERTAIN ME...
I SIMPLY MUST
RETURN THE FAVOR.
- YOU READY?
- YOU BET!
- I'LL RETURN IT IN FULL.
- ICE MAKE SAUCER.
- BEAST ARM.
- NO! DON'T DO IT!
- IRON BULL!
- HOW ABSURD!
( Gray and Elfman scream )
- ELFMAN! GRAY!
- Jose: FASCINATING.
YOU TOOK A SHOT FROM JUPITER
AT FULL FORCE, DID YOU NOT?
AND YET YOU'RE
STILL STANDING.
- ONLY BECAUSE MY FRIENDS HAVE
FILLED MY HEART WITH STRENGTH.
I WILL WITHSTAND
ANY PHYSICAL PAIN
TO PROTECT THE ONES THAT I LOVE!
- POWERFUL, COURAGEOUS,
AND EXQUISITELY BEAUTIFUL.
DESTROYING YOU WILL BRING ME
UNBELIEVABLE PLEASURE!
( Lucy grunts in pain )
- YOU GOTTA SING
BETTER THAN THAT.
TOO BAD. YOUR HEART'S
JUST NOT IN IT.
- GAJEEL. HEY.
HASN'T SHE HAD ENOUGH?
BESIDES THE MASTER
SAID HE DOESN'T WANT
HER GETTIN' HURT OR NOTHIN'.
- BUT WHAT ELSE AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S DOING THIS.
HE LEAVES ME TO WATCH
OVER BLONDIE HERE,
WHILE HE GETS TO
HAVE ALL THE FUN.
ANYWAY, I'M JUST PLAYING
WITH MY NEW TOY.
- YEAH, BUT IF THE MASTER
CATCHES YOU DOIN' THIS,
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE IN TROUBLE.
- SHUT UP. I KNOW MASTER
THINKS SHE'S IMPORTANT
BUT SHE'S JUST A PIECE
OF FAIRY SCUM TO ME.
HEH, EVEN THOUGH SHE'S
A GIRL, SHE'S STILL A WIZARD!
SHE SHOULDA KNOWN WHAT
SHE WAS GETTIN' INTO
WHEN SHE JOINED THE GUILD.
- YOU'RE TAKIN' THIS WAY
TOO FAR, MAN. LET IT GO!
- MASTER'S GONNA
LOSE IT, ISN'T HE?
- WELL, THEN I'LL TELL HIM
IT WAS ALL YOUR IDEA.
- Bozu, Sue: PLEASE
DON'T DO THAT.
- Gajeel: AW, I KINDA
FEEL SORRY FOR HER.
HER FELLOW GUILD MEMBERS
DIDN'T EVEN WANT HER BACK
'TIL THEY FOUND OUT
HER OLD MAN'S LOADED.
( she chuckles )
- GEEZ, YOU'RE DUMB. I CAN
BARELY EVEN BELIEVE IT.
IT'S JUST SAD.
I ACTUALLY FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
- Gajeel: OH?
- Bozu: WHAT? DID SHE
REALLY JUST SAY THAT?
- THIS CHICK'S TALKIN'
SMACK TO GAJEEL?
- PHANTOM LORD, HUH? RULER OF
THE SPIRITS? OH, PLEASE.
YOU DON'T SCARE ME AT ALL!
- Gajeel: YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID THAT.
IT TAKES SOME NERVE TO
GO RUNNIN' YOUR MOUTH
IN A SITUATION LIKE
THIS, PRINCESS.
I GOTTA ADMIT, YOU GOT GUTS.
MAKE SOME NOISE!
BUT NOT THIS TRASH TALKIN'
ACT YER PUTTIN' ON.
I WANT SCREAMS.
AND IF I DON'T START
GETTIN' WHAT I WANT,
YOU'RE GONNA BE SORRY.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GO AHEAD AND DO IT?
FINISH ME. THEN YOU'RE
GONNA BE SORRY. JUST YOU WAIT.
- YEAH? WHO'S GONNA
MAKE ME? I'M CURIOUS.
- Lucy: FAIRY TAIL.
THEY'D NEVER LET YOU GET AWAY
WITH THIS. THEY'D TAKE REVENGE.
THEY'LL NEVER STOP.
AND IF I WERE YOU,
I'D BE WATCHIN MY
BACK FROM NOW ON,
'CAUSE THE WORLD'S SCARIEST
GUILD'LL BE AFTER YOU...
AS LONG AS YOU LIVE!
- SO THEY'RE GONNA COME AFTER
ME, HUH? SOUNDS LIKE FUN!
- GAJEEL!
- STOP IT!
( sinister laugh )
( explosion )
- WHAT?
( Natsu screams )
- SO I WAS RIGHT! I KNEW
I SMELLED HIM HERE.
- IT'S NATSU!
- GAJEEL!
( singing in Japanese )
- SO D'YA THINK THIS IRON DRAGON
SLAYER GUY ACTUALLY EATS IRON?
- PROBABLY. ISN'T
THAT HOW IT WORKS?
I MEAN, THEY CALL YOU
THE FIRE DRAGON SLAYER
AND YOU EAT A LOT OF FIRE.
- HEY! WHATCHA THINK
ABOUT CALLING YOURSELF
THE FISH DRAGON SLAYER?
- FISH DRAGON, WHOA! THAT
WOULD BE TOTALLY AWESOME!
- NEXT TIME: THE TWO
DRAGON SLAYERS!
- SO DOES THAT MEAN I'D HAVE
A FISH DRAGON ROAR ATTACK?
- YEAH, YOU COULD SPIT
FISH OUTTA YOUR MOUTH!
- I DON'T THINK THAT'D
BE TOO EFFECTIVE.