My name is Mavis Vermillion.
And for the past seven years,
I've been studying strategies
for taking on wizard guilds.
Together, we can beat them.
No, Mavis. You've got
to be kidding me!
I humbly ask you
take me with you.
The Tenrou Orb is the
symbol of this island.
My people have protected this
sacred relic for generations.
I must fix this.
This treasure belongs
to the island,
and it's my duty to
see it's returned.
Please, don't.
Just to be clear,
we're treasure hunters.
Even if we do find the thing,
there's no guarantee we're just
gonna give it back to you.
Then you and I can have
another game of wits
whenever that time comes.
But right now, we share a
common goal of finding it.
Not to mention, you
still have to make good
on the promise you made.
I wanna meet a fairy!
[YURI]
Huh?!
Okay! Let our adventure begin!
[MAVIS]
Wow!
[MAVIS giggles]
[MAVIS]
It's beautiful!
I love the ocean.
There's no end to it!
And there's nothing like the
feel of salty air on my skin!
Hello there, seagulls!
I bet you're doing
your yearly migration.
You've lived on an island
in the middle of the
sea your entire life,
how is this exciting?
Seeing it from land
is way different.
Being out here on the
open water like this
gives me a whole
new perspective!
Whatever you say, Missy.
[MAVIS]
Really! This is incredible!
All right!
No stopping till Hargeon!
I know we'll find information
there that will lead us
right to Blue Skull
and the Tenrou Orb!
Yeah, we are definitely
gonna find that treasure,
but make no mistake,
once we do that, it's ours.
[MAVIS]
Interesting.
It looks like you're
adjusting the sail
to be at a right angle to
the wind, is that true?
You got it.
I know just how to tweak the
sail to get us there fast.
That's really fascinating to me.
I've never sailed,
but I've read a lot about it
in the library back home.
[MAVIS]
Although...
[YURI]
What?
[MAVIS] I think we should shift
the sail a bit farther forward.
Roughly five degrees if we wanna
maximize the power of the wind.
Oh, yeah?
[MAVIS] Hmm. Okay,
maybe one degree more.
[YURI]
Is that good?
[MAVIS]
Ah! Hold on!
The wind just started
blowing north-northwest!
[YURI]
Huh?
[MAVIS] Hurry! Bring it back
two, no, wait, four degrees!
[YURI]
Stop!
I'm kind of an expert at
this stuff, remember?
How about you stick
with what you know?
I'm sorry, I wasn't
trying to bother you.
I'll leave you be.
Let's go, Zera.
[ZERA]
But where else is there to go?
We can explore.
[ZERA] Seriously? I don't wanna
make anyone else mad at us.
Stop worrying!
Oh, great.
[MAVIS gasps]
Ugh, it's mustier
than our library.
I bet this is all treasure!
Hello, what are you
doing over there?
Just messin' around with
this fish-catching gun.
Do you mean you shoot them?
[WARROD] Yup. Bang!
One blast is all it takes.
Aww...
Ha! I was only screwin'
with you, kiddo.
It's got no bullets.
It shoots a net to catch fish.
Tell me more about it!
Are the nets really big,
or are they just little ones?
They're gigantic.
I caught an iceberg with one
of these back in the day.
That big? I wanna see!
[WARROD] Just kidding!
I'm jokin' with you again!
They're pretty big,
but not big enough to catch
an iceberg, that's for sure.
What's the rate of expulsion?
Do you have to aim it
at a specific angle?
Um, well, lemme think.
So you have to aim right
at the fish obviously--
Do you fire from a
standing position,
or kneel to brace it properly?
I always kneel, but I guess
you could stand, or--
[YURI] Hey, Warrod! Could you
come gimme a hand up here?
Be right there! Gladly.
Let's talk later.
Sure! Let me know when
you have some free time!
You've got to get a sense for
when you're bothering people.
Yeah, you're right.
I just get so excited!
Now what next? There's so
much on this ship to explore!
Yeah. Probably less
than you're thinking.
[MAVIS humming]
[gasps]
I can't believe the wind
died down so quickly.
I really hate this part.
[WARROD] There's no point
gripin' about things
you can't control.
Yeah, I know that.
This is one of those times
when it'd be best
to stay out of it.
That sounds like
excellent advice!
I don't find your
tone convincing.
That guy looks kind of
scary, don't you think?
What are you two
doing with the sail?
Well, the wind stopped,
so we're furling it.
There's no point having
it up with no breeze.
Supposedly the breezes
in this part of the ocean
come and go in two to
three-hour intervals
pretty consistently
this time of year.
It should pick up again in a
little while, if that's helpful.
You sure know a lot.
What, did ya get that
info from a book?
Yep! I read all about
ocean currents, too!
She's right. Let's rest
till the wind picks up.
I'm tired of working anyway.
Fine by me.
Is there anything
you'd like me to do
to help out around the ship
while you guys are relaxing?
[YURI] Nope, I think
we've got it covered.
Well, just let me know.
Hey, stay away from all
that stuff. Please.
Yes, sir.
What did I say earlier?
[YURI] Why don't you go back
to staring at the ocean?
Think I could talk
to you for a minute?
I told you to
stare at the ocean!
Then that's what I'll do!
What are the odds that
she'll do what I say?
I finished cleaning and
organizing all the gear.
[YURI]
Oh, that's great.
[WARROD]
But it doesn't really matter
if we can't afford
to use any of it.
Buying the boat and making
the journey to Tenrou Island
has put a major dent
in the old coin purse.
[YURI]
I know.
We'll just have to
earn some more Jewel
when we get to Hargeon.
[DOLPHIN A crying]
[MAVIS gasps]
What do you think
that sound was?
[DOLPHIN A crying]
[gasps]
Oh! Those are dolphins!
They're beautiful!
Did you know they're
mammals like us?
They might look like fish,
but they're very different!
They're friendly
and intelligent,
maybe even more so than humans,
and they're extremely
playful and gentle!
All right!
What are you doing?
How long have you
had that thing on?
[MAVIS]
I figured we'd have a chance
to do a little swimming
on this trip,
so I decided that
I'd wear my swimsuit!
Wait! Mavis!
[splash]
Hi, my name is Mavis,
and I'd like to be your friend!
Oh, wow, are you
saying hello, too?
[DOLPHIN A grunts]
[MAVIS laughing]
[MAVIS]
This is amazing.
I read that dolphins had
skin as opposed to scales,
but I never imagined
it would be this smooth
and silky to the touch!
You sure you're okay out there?
Yeah, I'll be back
in a bit! Woohoo!
[ZERA]
She has to be crazy.
[MAVIS laughing]
[MAVIS]
Oh! What now?
Wow!
[MAVIS]
Incredible!
[MAVIS] It's like a whole other
world. So vast and beautiful.
[MAVIS laughing]
[MAVIS]
Hm?
What is this?
[MAVIS]
Is it some kind of shrine?
[splash]
There you are!
You had me worried!
Don't be, I'm fine!
And you're not gonna
believe what I found!
Thank you, friend! Wait here
for me a moment, okay?
[ZERA]
What?
So what did you find?
Shh!
Just tell me!
Be quiet.
[ZERA]
Uhh...
'Kay, um, what is that?
It's magical diving gear!
With this, I can go
exploring underwater
for as long as I want.
It's perfect.
I heard Yuri and Warrod talking.
They said this expedition has
very nearly bankrupt them.
[ZERA] I don't really see how
that has anything to do
with this magical diving gear.
I found an underwater shrine
on the seafloor nearby.
[ZERA]
Are you kidding me?
[MAVIS] And shrines are
usually full of treasure,
so I'm going to
explore down there!
You're a lunatic.
People do that kind of thing
in fairy tales, Mavis.
This is real life.
If I can find any
treasure in the shrine,
I'll give it to them
and help relieve
some of their
financial difficulties.
[ZERA] Hey! Are you
even listening to me?
[MAVIS]
Hush!
If they wake up,
just tell 'em I'm playing
with the dolphins
and I'll be right back!
I really think this
is a terrible--!
[MAVIS]
See you in a bit!
Mavis, wait!
[MAVIS] I won't let myself
be a burden ever again!
Okay, friends, we made it!
I just need to figure
out how to get inside.
You really don't
wanna come with me?
That's all right. Just wait
right here until I get back.
[MAVIS] Wonder what kinda stuff
I'm gonna find down here.
[MAVIS]
This writing...
It looks like the language of
the ancient Kurill civilization.
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
Just some tiny fish.
[sighs]
[MAVIS] All of the
architecture seems sturdy,
like it's holding up well.
[MAVIS]
Oh!
I've reached a dead end.
[MAVIS]
This statue's a different color
than the stone around it.
Hmm.
[MAVIS]
Oh!
Wow!
[gasps]
Is that an altar
there in the center?
This must be a ritual chamber.
If there's any
treasure to be found,
I'm certain it would be in here!
[MAVIS]
What's this?
More ancient Kurilean script.
Maybe it'll give me some clues
about where the treasure
could be hidden.
"The sacred chamber
of the Kurilean gods
must remain undisturbed.
This holy place shall
never be desecrated.
Trespassers of mal intent will
meet with divine punishment."
What? Divine punishment?
Huh?
It looks like divine punishment
just means getting eaten by you!
[MAVIS]
I have to act quickly!
[SHRINE GUARDIAN roars]
[yelps]
[MAVIS screams]
[gasps]
[YURI]
Damn.
I'd hoped magic
bullets would work,
but it looks like they're
useless underwater.
Then it's a good thing
we've got a Plan B!
Wow, your timing couldn't
have been any better!
Save the thanks for later!
Find a safe place to hide!
[MAVIS]
Right!
Oh, you're hungry? Eat this!
Perfect, now fire the net!
You got it!
Looks like you caught him!
I thought this net was
supposed to be unbreakable.
[YURI]
Crap!
Now the exit's caved in!
What the heck were you thinking
coming here all by yourself?
I can explain.
Explain it when we're
back on board the ship.
Right now, we've gotta
find a way out of here!
[gasps]
What is this?
I'm sure the answer's
here somewhere.
You'd better know what
you're talkin' about.
But where?
Hey! Don't ignore me!
[MAVIS]
Sorry, I was thinking.
I'm deciphering the writing
to find a clue to
get us out of here.
Well, then keep
focusing on that.
We'll take care of the
giant sea beast over there.
Are you sure you'll be
okay without my help?
I think we can handle
this one on our own.
We are experienced
treasure hunters, after all.
And if we make it out alive,
we'll have a pretty good story.
[MAVIS]
"Seek repentance, O lost one,
and the path shall be revealed.
Humble thyself and you will
know true freedom at last."
"Turn all eyes to gaze as
one upon the single star,
for only then may the
door to the heavens
open to grant you passage."
A star?
But how could you
see a star in here?
And what does it mean by
the "door to the heavens"?
Hurry up!
"Turn all eyes." But whose eyes?
What is it talking about?
[WARROD]
Think faster, kid!
I've got it!
The statues' heads
are facing backwards!
Hey! What're you doing?!
I think I've figured
out the solution!
"Turn all eyes to gaze
upon the single star"!
It has to mean the one
in the center! Right?
These statues' heads
are turned backwards,
away from the center!
The text says to "turn all eyes
to gaze upon the single star,"
and there's one in the middle!
That's what it means?
[MAVIS] Help me turn
them all to face inward!
It says "for only then may the
door to the heavens open"!
I don't understand,
but I trust you. I guess.
I'm working on a hunch here,
but their heads are turning,
so I think I must be
onto something!
Okay! That's all of them.
Let's hope my gut is right!
It doesn't seem like
anything is happening.
Wait. Give it a second.
[WARROD, YURI gasp]
[MAVIS gasps]
So did your gut
tell ya about this?
[MAVIS] Um, it looks like
the altar is sinking!
[WARROD]
That's just great.
I really don't like
the way this is going.
Yeah, I'm with you.
That's not what I imagine
when I hear "door to heaven."
I'm sorry.
I guess I led us into an
underwater booby trap!
[YURI, WARROD]
Are you serious?!
[ALL screaming]
[YURI] Do you realize
how crazy that was?
Well, lesson learned.
You could've gotten the
three of us killed down there.
That's true, but at
the end of the day,
we would've never made
it out of that shrine
without her expertise, so...
...I guess in a way
she saved our lives.
That's one way to look at it.
Though a big treasure
would've been nice.
A crown, or at
least a fat Jewel.
[YURI]
I did snag these.
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah.
Look what I found!
Holy crap!
You kiddin' me?
[MAVIS]
Here ya go.
I thought that it could
go towards funding
the rest of the journey.
Hey. The wind's back!
You feel that? Anchors up!
[MAVIS] After a long
and eventful journey,
my new friends and I finally
arrive in Hargeon.
There, I get to experience
a few thrilling firsts.
My first port city, and my first
market, with its bustling crowd.
From there, I accompany the
quiet and mysterious Precht
on a quest for information about
the Blue Skull Wizard Guild,
and the possible location
of the Tenrou Orb!
Next Time:
"Dancing with Blades."
Skilled swordplay
takes center stage!