Now have at it.
The winner gets to live.
[GRAY] My mind... I feel
like it's fading away.
[JUVIA] No, I-I won't
hurt my darling Gray.
I don't want to, but...
[GRAY] I can't focus.
I'm losing control.
[yells]
[screams]
[INVEL] Gray will win this
fight, just as I predicted.
[screams]
[INVEL] Killing his dear friend
with his own two hands
will unleash the
darkness within him.
[INVEL] Creating the apex
warrior who shall defeat E.N.D.
[INVEL] Your Majesty, may I
inquire about that necklace?
I've not seen you without it.
Of course.
This pendant--it holds an image
of my younger brother, Natsu.
[INVEL] His Majesty will
vanquish Acnologia,
then the world
will truly be his.
But to fully realize this goal,
E.N.D. must be removed.
[JUVIA] Why? Why am I trying
to harm my love like this?
It goes against every
fiber of my being.
I would truly rather die
than see him suffer.
Please, my darling!
Hurry and kill me!
No, that wouldn't work.
He would blame himself.
His heart would be broken.
It's clear what I must do now.
I have no other choice.
Yes. I shall take my own life!
I'll do it. Before I lose
what control I still have.
I have to be brave.
This is for the best.
[INVEL]
Don't bother resisting.
My Ice Lock magic
imprisons your mind.
Its cold shackles
confine your free will.
To earn release, you must
kill the one before you.
My feelings will
never be confined,
but if my body is trying
to imprison them,
then I must destroy it!
[gasps]
You awakened the
best part of me.
Gray, my love.
That's absurd. Choosing
self-destruction?
Juvia. You didn't have to.
[gasps]
[INVEL] They'd both
rather end their lives?
I'm sorry. I thought...
My darling Gray.
You shouldn't have!
[GRAY]
There was no other choice.
I couldn't hurt you, Juvia.
You mean too much to me.
You're my friend.
[JUVIA]
I feel the same.
I just wanted... to protect you.
But now, I...
You're so kind. My very
last moment is a happy one.
[INVEL]
What the hell is going on here?
I never saw this coming.
[GRAY]
Damn it.
It wasn't supposed
to turn out this way.
[GRAY] Natsu. Please.
Don't let us die in vain.
Avenge us.
[INVEL] They couldn't live with
the guilt of killing a friend,
so instead they
killed themselves.
It's absolutely mind-boggling.
[INVEL] I'll have to think
of another strategy.
[INVEL]
But as things stand now,
it seems the only option left
is to deal with E.N.D. myself.
[WIZARD A gasps]
[WIZARD B]
Hey, the blizzard stopped!
[WIZARD C]
It's about time!
[GRAY]
What's goin' on?
I'm still alive. But how?
I mean, I know what I did.
[gasps]
[GRAY]
It's so strange.
The blood inside me...
...somehow it doesn't
feel like my own.
[JUVIA]
Water Make Blood.
I'd been worried that
something terrible
would happen to you, my love.
So I secretly mastered
a blood transfusion spell
that would let me care for you.
[JUVIA] I'll always be alive,
inside of you.
So don't cry.
We'll still be together.
No, you can't die.
Juvia.
[JUVIA]
My life is yours now.
We're inseparable.
[screaming]
[GRAY]
I need ya to focus!
[BOTH yelling]
Ice Make Geyser!
Water Nebula!
[GRAY]
Get down!
[JUVIA]
I can still feel the warmth
of Gray's hand on my tushie!
[GRAY]
Juvia, listen for a sec.
There's somethin' I've
been meanin' to tell ya
for a while now.
Um. Whatever "something" is,
I'm ready to hear it!
[GRAY] I mean, it's not
that big of a deal, but--
You never know, it might be
a really big deal for me!
[JUVIA] Could this be the moment
I've always dreamed of?
Will he confess his
love to me at last?
Oh my goodness. What will I say?
[JUVIA]
I was knitting in a rush,
so it didn't turn out very good.
But I'd be honored
if you wore it!
Here, please!
[GRAY] You should get home
before it starts storming.
[JUVIA]
Wait!
What the hell?
I knitted a scarf for
you, won't you wear it?
I don't do scarves.
Come on, it's a
cute accessory!
I don't accessorize either.
But it's gonna get cold out--
look at those clouds!
So what? I'm an ice
wizard, all right?
The cold doesn't even affect me.
[JUVIA]
Juvie!
I'm sorry.
[JUVIA]
I wanna make up for my mistake.
So I made you this body pillow!
Here, do whatever
you want with it!
[GRAY]
No way!
[JUVIA]
It's also in commemoration
of our 414th day anniversary,
so you know, it'd be pretty
rude not to take it!
[GRAY] Seriously! That thing's
creepy! Take it back!
[JUVIA]
Creepy?
Gray, my darling,
aren't you glad I brought
my special two-person sleeping
bag with me on this trip?
No way I'm gettin'
in that thing!
I have a surprise for
you, my darling Gray!
Something warm for
you to munch on!
[yelps]
[JUVIA]
I call them Graybuns!
Well, they do look pretty tasty,
but it would feel weird
to gnaw on my own face.
I thought you'd say that.
Guess I'll keep all the
Graybuns for myself.
Which means you get to enjoy
these hot Juvibuns!
[GRAY]
You set me up!
You went through
all the trouble...
I might as well eat one.
Oh, my darling! That's a--
Graybun.
[grunts]
It was you?
[GRAY crying]
You freed him.
[GRAY]
Thank you.
[JUVIA]
Gray.
[GRAY]
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, my love?
I'm fine. Care for a bite?
Wow! My darling Gray is
sharing his food with me?
His lips touched this!
I hope you know
I appreciate you.
I can always count on you
to be by my side, right?
[JUVIA] Oh, well, yes,
of course, my love.
If that's what you want!
I'll give you my answer
once the battle is over.
[GRAY] But for now,
let me focus on this.
Sure.
[GRAY] Oh, Juvia. I'm sorry
for the way I've treated you.
I promise I'll take your
feelings seriously.
Just please wake up.
Juvia.
I believe Brandish was
headed in this direction.
[ALL scream]
[HAPPY]
Jeez, Lucy. You weigh a ton!
[NATSU]
Man, that hurt!
Hey, monster lady!
What's your problem?
I'm sorry for what
happened earlier.
Brandish, I really don't think
we need to fight anymore!
Well, neither do I.
[BOTH gasp]
[BRANDISH] You guys helped me
out when you didn't have to,
so I've decided to spare you.
[HAPPY]
You'll spare us?
[BRANDISH]
Like I said before.
I've no intention
to betray Alvarez.
It's where I call
home, after all.
I'm going to slaughter
every last one
of your friends and guildmates.
But I promise that
I will not harm you.
Huh?
What the hell? Are you serious?
[DIMARIA]
Randi.
And to think I trusted you.
It's inevitable.
There's no doubt that
Alvarez will be victorious.
Our sheer numbers, the power
of the Spriggan Twelve,
and our heavyweights,
August and Irene.
And at this very moment,
His Majesty is reaping
the Fairy Heart.
Give up already.
Because you don't have
chance at winning.
No way. Fairy Tail will
never surrender.
[BRANDISH]
Doesn't matter.
All your friends
are going to die.
There's nothing you can do.
[AJEEL laughing]
I gotta say, you have a
lotta fight in ya, big guy!
But it won't help!
[LISANNA gasps]
Not more sand.
[AJEEL]
Shrivel up and die already!
Your bodies will blow
away with my sand.
I gotta think fast.
We can't lose!
You're weak!
I swear I'll protect Lisanna
and the rest of the guild
like a real man!
Well, your moves are
bloody brilliant, but...
...ya can't land 'em.
No!
My skill: Closing My Eyes.
[MIRAJANE]
How can I beat this guy?
It appears you've
already burned through
a lot of your magic power.
That'll make my job
a good bit easier.
Then bring it on!
--[MINERVA screaming]
--[WALL laughing]
I need to hurry this up and
exterminate all you pests.
Because the truth is,
I've got a major bone
to pick with that cocky
lighting bastard.
Am I supposed to be
afraid of a shadow?
I have returned from
beyond the grave.
And now the underworld
is waiting for you
to take your place within it!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ERZA growls]
[NATSU] So you think all our
friends are gonna die?
Not if we can help it.
We've been through more
tough battles than I can count
and we're still standing strong!
[HAPPY]
Aye! She's right!
This time is different.
You've never faced an enemy as
lethal as the Spriggan Twelve.
[INVEL] To think that
you actually survived.
[growling]
However, I imagine that
you're still too injured
for a proper fight.
[screams]
[growls]
[INVEL]
How?
He's forced my hand.
I've no choice but to
take a drastic measure.
[INVEL]
Absolute Ice Shroud!
[INVEL] This netherworld ice
freezes all that it touches.
You may think you're resistant,
but any contact with this armor
will freeze you to your core.
[groaning]
[INVEL] And then you'll
shatter into pieces.
[yelling]
[gasps]
[NATSU]
You're cocky.
But that's because you've never
faced an enemy like Fairy Tail!
How could this be?
[INVEL] This wizard is able to
duplicate the same properties
as my netherworld ice?
[GRAY] Juvia had a life
ahead of her, a future,
and you stole it from her!
I'll make you pay.
[GRAY] You're the one
who's gonna shatter!
[GRAY] Ice Demon...
Zero Destruction Fist!
[BRANDISH]
You remember what went down
on Caracol Island, don't you?
I could end your lives right now
with a snap of my fingers.
Like to see you try.
Natsu!
We're not lookin'
for some kinda mercy.
You guys came here for a fight,
and we'll give it to ya!
[NEINHART]
Erza! Lady Erza!
Come out wherever you are!
[BRANDISH]
Neinhart.
Wait. Your eyes.
[chuckles]
[NEINHART] An effect of my
lady's augmentation magic.
Right now I'm
practically bursting
at the seams with power.
You should step aside, Brandish.
These three are comrades
of Lady Erza.
That makes them enemies.
"Lady Erza"?
Leave us be. We're in the
middle of a negotiation here.
Is that so?
Sounds suspicious to me.
You would dare betray
Lady Irene and the Empire?
[BRANDISH screams]
Holy crap!
This wind is like a
million little razors!
[grunting]
[BRANDISH]
My magic can't even touch him!
How much did she power him up?
[NATSU]
All right, ya windbag!
[BRANDISH] No! You don't
have a chance against him!
[laughing]
I'll never know unless I try!
I am not gonna run away!
Because every single step
I take forward is a victory!
[NATSU] That's how we're
gonna get back to the guild!
[BRANDISH] Whoa. He's way
stronger than I thought.
Yes! Way to go, Natsu!
But why did he call
her "Lady Erza"?
Just hang on.
Don't get up until I've
completely healed you.
[JUVIA]
Wendy.
You're awfully lucky that she
was able to find you in time.
A moment later and
you'd've been gone.
Actually, the reason
we found her so quickly
was because of
your clairvoyance.
So I survived?
It's a miracle.
[JUVIA]
You ladies saved my life!
From the bottom of
my heart, thank you!
It's no problem!
We're all supposed to help
each other out, ya know!
I owe it to Shelia to
work twice as hard
to keep everybody safe!
I'm alive!
And I can still feel the kiss
that my spicy ice hunk gave
me as I lay unconscious.
I'm sure it was a dream.
[gasps]
Do either of you know
where Gray is right now?
He was hurt. Is he okay?
[WENDY] He wasn't here
when we showed up.
I could keep thrashing you, and
as good as that would feel...
...it still wouldn't
bring her back.
Like your long-lost mother,
your father, your master, right?
How do you know about all that?
[INVEL] Because it's your
fate in this life.
Unless you defeat E.N.D.,
misery will follow you
for the rest of your days.
[GRAY]
I am gonna take him down.
I don't need you to tell me!
[INVEL] The truth is,
you're the only in this world
one who can beat him.
However, you should
know his other name.
Etherious Natsu Dragneel.
He is the mightiest demon
of the Books of Zeref.
[INVEL] Which means
he's your ultimate foe.
[GRAY]
Huh?
[LUCY] Gray struggles
with the revelation
that his old friend
Natsu is really E.N.D.
as I begin my battle
against Brandish.
Although I don't
wanna fight someone
who has shown me kindness,
I'm forced to go head-to-head
with a super-sized version of
the powerful Spriggan Wizard.
With neither side finding
room to compromise,
our fight triggers
a brand-new crisis.
Next Time: "The Mightiest
Demon of the Book of Zeref."
Who is standing in our way now?
Friend, or foe?