- Hades: I WASN'T EXPECTING
TO REUNITE WITH MY OLD FRIEND
MAKAROV.
WHILE IT'S UNFORTUNATE,
IF WE WANT TO BE VICTORIOUS,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO ANNIHILATE
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
FOR ONCE THEY'RE
OUT OF THE WAY,
WE CAN PURSUE
OUR TRUE OBJECTIVE,
FINDING ZEREF.
GOD SPEED,
SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY.
I AWAIT YOUR GOOD NEWS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I HOPE YOU FOOLS ARE
PREPARED TO DO BATTLE WITH ME.
- Lucy: A GOAT?!
- THERE'S SOMETHING
WEIRD ABOUT THIS GUY,
BUT I CAN'T QUITE
PUT MY FINGER ON WHAT IT IS.
- I CAN TELL YOU
WHAT'S WEIRD ABOUT HIM.
HE'S A GOAT.
- STAY BACK, LUCY.
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
- ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M ONE OF THE SEVEN KIN,
CAPRICO.
- THE SEVEN WHAT NOW?
WHAT THE HECK DOES THAT MEAN?
- GRIMOIRE HEART'S GOT
SIX MORE WIZARDS
WHO ARE JUST AS STRONG
AS THIS GUY?
- CAPRICO.
- Hades: MAKAROV.
YOU'VE DONE AN EXCELLENT JOB
OF LEADING THE GUILD
FOR THE LAST
48 YEARS.
HOWEVER, I'M AFRAID
YOUR TIME IS UP, OLD FRIEND.
YOUR REIGN AS FAIRY TAIL'S
MASTER ENDS TODAY.
HISTORY IS COMING TO A CLOSE
FOR BOTH YOU AND YOUR GUILD.
- Happy:
"FIRE DRAGON VS. FLAME GOD"!
- ( growls )
- ( chuckles )
YOU LEFT YOURSELF
WIDE OPEN, DUMB ASS.
I WAS EXPECTING MORE POWER
FROM A DRAGON HUNTER LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE NOT
HOLDING BACK ON ME,
ARE YOU?
- YOU JUST WAIT.
NOW THAT MY BODY'S WARMED UP,
I'M READY TO FIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA WISH YOU
HADN'T ASKED THAT QUESTION.
- CAREFUL, NATSU.
- HE'LL BE FINE
BECAUSE THE ENEMY
DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
WHEN HE'S ALL FIRED UP
LIKE HE IS RIGHT NOW.
- BUT HIS ATTACKS
HAVEN'T HAD ANY EFFECT.
WHO IS THAT FIEND?
- HE JUST REFERRED TO HIMSELF
AS A GOD SLAYER.
BUT I'M NOT SURE
IF THAT'S REALLY HIS POWER
OR HE'S TRYING
TO TALK TOUGH.
- LET ME INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M ONE OF GRIMOIRE HEART'S
SEVEN KIN,
AND THE GUY WHO'S GONNA
KICK YOUR ASS.
I'M KNOWN AS THE GOD SLAYER
NAMED ZANCROW.
- WELL, I'M KNOWN AS
THE DRAGON SLAYER.
I'M NATSU OF FAIRY TAIL.
( laughs ) I KNOW
WHO YOU ARE, DRAGON BREATH.
YOU'RE FAMOUS
IN THE BARAM ALLIANCE
BECAUSE OF ALL THE DESTRUCTION
YOU LEAVE IN YOUR WAKE.
- SAY WHAT?!
- THE BARAM ALLIANCE?
CARE TO EXPLAIN?
- AYE, SIR, THEY'RE BAD GUYS
WHO BANDED TOGETHER
TO WREAK HAVOC.
- YES, GRIMOIRE HEART,
THE ORACION SEIS,
AND TARTAROS
JOINED FORCES TO CREATE
A COALITION OF DARK GUILDS.
- OUR COALITION
OF LIGHT GUILDS
WAS ABLE TO BEAT
THE ORACION SEIS,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT BEATING GRIMOIRE HEART.
I MEAN, THEY'RE
THE STRONGEST MEMBER
OF THE BARAM ALLIANCE.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- YOU ANNIHILATED LULLABY.
YOU STOPPED US FROM
BEING BACK DELIORA.
AND THEN YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
REALLY SCREWED UP OUR PLANS
WHEN YOU WIPED OUT
THE R-SYSTEM AND NIRVANA!
YOU TOOK DOWN JELLAL,
AS WELL AS MASTER ZERO.
IF YOU THINK THAT
MAKES YOU HOT STUFF,
LET ME TELL YOU, THOSE GUYS
AIN'T NOTHING COMPARED TO ME.
- I CAN TAKE YOU.
- YOU'RE JUST A LOWLY DRAGON
HUNTER. DON'T BE SO COCKY.
- KNOW WHAT'S COCKY?
CALLING YOURSELF A GOD SLAYER!
WHAT'S THAT EVEN MEAN?
YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
A GOD TRAINED YOU?!
- I GUESS IF YOU CALL
MASTER HADES A GOD,
THEN YEAH, 'CAUSE HE'S
THE ONE WHO TRAINED ME
TO USE THIS AWESOME
LOST MAGIC.
- GIVE ME A BREAK!
YOUR MASTER AIN'T A GOD!
HE'S JUST
A REGULAR OLD PERSON.
UNLIKE YOU, EVERYTHING I KNOW
ABOUT DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
I LEARNED FROM
AN ACTUAL DRAGON!
- YOU REALLY THINK
I GIVE A CRAP?
DRAGONS ARE JUST
FLYING LIZARDS.
WANT TO ASK THIS LITTLE GUY
IF HE'S GOT ANY MAGIC?
- HEY, MAN, IGNEEL'S NOT
A FRICKIN' LIZARD!
- YEAH, YOU TELL HIM.
GRANDINE IS NOT A LIZARD EITHER,
YOU BIG MEANY.
- DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM, WENDY.
- I'D SHUT UP AND SIT PRETTY
IF I WERE YOU.
I GOT MY HANDS FULL
WITH PINKY,
BUT AS SOON AS
I'M THROUGH WITH HIM,
YOU'RE GONNA BE UP NEXT.
( cackles )
- ( whimpering )
HE'S NOT MESSING AROUND.
- I WON'T LET YOU
LAY A FINGER ON THIS CHILD.
- HEY, YOU!
DON'T GO GETTING DISTRACTED!
YOU BETTER GET
OUT OF HERE, GUYS.
- ( snickers )
BRINGING OUT THE BIG GUNS, HUH?
- THE FLAMES OF MY RIGHT HAND
AND THE FLAMES OF LEFT!
PUT THEM TOGETHER
AND YOU GET...
- I ASK YOU TO SCORCH ALL
FROM THE FAR WEST
TO THE FAR EAST,
OH, BREATH OF GOD.
- FIRE DRAGON...
- FLAME GOD...
- BRILLIANT FLAME!
- KAGUTSCHI!
- ( screams )
- Pantherlily:
WHAT INCREDIBLE POWER.
- Carla: AND SUCH
TREMENDOUS HEAT!
- Wendy: THE POWERS
OF A DRAGON AND A GOD
ARE COLLIDING.
- ( growls )
- ( chuckles )
- ( strains )
OH, NO YOU DON'T!
( struggling grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- NATSU!
- NO WAY.
- THAT GUY OVERPOWERED HIM.
- ENOUGH WITH
THE PLAY-BY-PLAY.
GET LOST, CATS.
- ( all screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( cackles )
UH-OH, IT WASN'T
JUST CATS.
THAT PUNY LITTLE BRAT'S
A DRAGON HUNTER TOO.
OH, WELL, THAT'LL TEACH HER
NOT TO MESS WITH ME.
( laughs )
- WENDY,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- TO THINK THIS BARBARIAN
COULD EASILY OUTCLASS
A DRAGON SLAYER
WHO IS AS
STRONG AS GAJEEL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
THIS MUST BE THE POWER
OF LOST MAGIC.
- ( frustrated growl )
I'LL SHOW YOU!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- NICE TRY, PAL.
BUT DON'T YOU KNOW
IT WAS THE DIVINE
WHO GRANTED HUMANS
THE KNOWLEDGE OF FIRE.
IT WASN'T CREATED
BY MANKIND OR DRAGONS.
IT WAS THE GODS!
- ( sighs )
I GOT HIM.
( gasps )
- ( slurps )
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO WAY!
- ( burps )
- HE HAS NO MANNERS.
- HE ATE ALL
OF NATSU'S FLAMES.
DID YOU SEE THAT, CARLA?
- THAT'S SOME TASTY FIRE
YOU GOT THERE.
NOTHING I LIKE MORE
THAN THE FLAVOR
OF VIOLENT,
NEVER-ENDING FLAMES.
EVEN THOUGH YOU MAY
HAVE ENOUGH POWER
TO SLAY A DRAGON,
YOU COULD NEVER SLAY A GOD.
PREPARE TO WITNESS THE POWER
OF GRIMOIRE HEART'S MAGIC.
FLAME GOD BELLOW!
( screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
- NATSU, NO!
NATSU!
- WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
THOSE TWO DRAGON HUNTERS
HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
( laughs )
( cackles )
( laughter echoes )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HOW COME WE
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO LAND A SINGLE HIT
ON THIS GOAT FREAK?
- COME ON, LOKE.
- GOTCHA!
- NOT AGAIN!
SOMETHING FEELS OFF.
I'M SENSING THIS
STRANGE PRESENCE.
WHAT COULD IT BE?
- THIS GUY IS STRONG.
HE'S ABLE TO FEND OFF
ALL FOUR OF US.
WHO IS HE?
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
I'M NOT ABOUT
TO WASTE MY TIME
GETTING ALL WORKED UP
OVER A STUPID GOAT!
WHAT THE--?
HOW'D I MISS HIM AGAIN?
- WHAT'S HIS SECRET?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S USING
SOME SORT OF MAGIC
TO DODGE US.
AND FROM WHAT I CAN TELL,
HE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
READING OUR MOVES
LIKE COBRA.
- I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT,
BUT I GOT THIS FEELING.
I JUST KNOW THAT NONE OF
OUR ATTACKS ARE GONNA HIT HIM.
I KEEP THINKING
WHAT'S THE USE OF FIGHTING
IF YOU CAN'T WIN.
WE'RE SCREWED!
- VERY PERCEPTIVE OF YOU.
YOU ARE POWERLESS
AGAINST ME IN BATTLE.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
YOU TRY TO ATTACK,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO HIT ME.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GIVE UP.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO,
BUT REVERE AND WORSHIP ME.
- THERE IT IS AGAIN.
I KEEP FEELING
THIS STRANGE PRESSURE.
- MAN, I WISH I KNEW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHERE'S THIS SENSE
OF HOPELESSNESS COMING FROM?
- CAPRICO.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IT'S DEFINITELY HIM.
THIS COULD BE BAD,
ESPECIALLY FOR LUCY.
- ( Natsu groans )
AH, MAN.
THAT GUY'S HARDCORE.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE FIRE'S
ACTUALLY FELT HOT TO ME.
WAIT, WHERE
IN THE HECK AM I?
HUH?
( sniffs )
I KNOW THAT SMELL.
( panting )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
( gasps )
OH.
WHOA, GRAMPS.
NO WAY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- NATSU, IT'S YOU.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
HAPPENED TO YOU?
OH, CRAP, YOU'RE HURT
REAL BAD, AREN'T YOU?
I'M KIND OF SCARED
TO MOVE YOU,
BUT WE GOT TO
GET YOU TO WENDY.
OF COURSE THAT'S A LOT EASIER
SAID THAN DONE
BECAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW!
- NATSU.
- HOW'D YOU GET
SO BEAT UP?
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
- NATSU, LISTEN.
THE CHANCES OF US
DEFEATING GRIMOIRE HEART
ARE NIL.
- YOU MUST BE OUT OF
YOUR MIND RIGHT NOW!
THE GRAMPS I KNOW WOULD NEVER
SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- YOU'RE INJURED, MY BOY.
WHO DID THAT TO YOU?
- THIS AIN'T NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT I'M GONNA DO TO HIM.
THE NEXT TIME I SEE
THAT CHUMP, IT'S ON.
- I BEG YOU, NATSU.
- HUH?
- GATHER ALL THE OTHERS
AND LEAVE WHILE YOU CAN.
- WOULD YOU QUIT
TALKING LIKE THAT?
WE'RE NOT THROUGH
WITH THE S-CLASS TRIAL.
AS FAIRY TAIL'S MASTER,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SUPPORT US.
NOT TELL US WE CAN'T WIN.
- WHILE THAT'S TRUE,
THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN THE BEST THING TO DO
IS RETREAT.
MASTER.
- ( Zancrow laughs )
WELL, WELL, WELL.
IT LOOKS LIKE MASTER HADES
DID A NUMBER ON YOU,
EH, MAKAROV?
( laughs )
- HE'S THE ONE
WHO DID THIS?
- LET IT GO, MY BOY.
REMEMBER WHAT
I JUST TOLD YOU.
- I AIN'T BACKING DOWN.
( shaky breathing )
- HMM?
NATSU.
HE'S TREMBLING IN FEAR.
- Makarov: NATSU.
- YOU HAVING A HARD TIME,
DRAGON HUNTER?
LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE FREAKING OUT
'CAUSE THERE'S SWEAT DRIPPING
FROM EVERY PORE.
- I...
ACCEPT DEFEAT.
- Gildarts:
REMEMBER, NATSU,
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH FEELING FEAR.
AFTER ALL,
HOW ELSE WOULD WE
COME TO KNOW
OUR OWN WEAKNESSES?
- ( shivering )
THIS FEELING,
THIS IS FEAR.
- NATSU.
- ( laughs )
YUP, YOU GOT IT.
I CAN'T SAY
I BLAME YOU.
IT'S GOT TO BE TERRIFYING
FOR A RUNT LIKE YOU
TO FACE MY ULTIMATE POWER.
IF I WERE YOU, I'D STAND
THERE TREMBLING IN FEAR TOO.
- ( shivering )
- YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( laughing )
- HE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS FEAR
I'M FEELING.
BU IT'S NOT THE SAME
KIND OF FEAR
THAT GILDARTS
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- HUH?
- ( fire crackles )
- I AIN'T TREMBLING
BECAUSE OF YOU.
THE ONLY THING
I'M AFRAID OF RIGHT NOW
IS THAT SOMEONE ELSE'LL DO IN
THE JERK WHO BEAT UP GRAMPS
BEFORE I GET THE CHANCE
TO GET A FEW GOOD LICKS IN.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY.
I WON'T LET YOU GUYS
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
I'LL TAKE DOWN
MASTER HADES.
AND I'LL DO IT
WITH MY OWN TWO HANDS!
- UNFORTUNATELY,
IT WOULD APPEAR
I GOT THE SHORT END
OF THE STICK
WHEN IT COMES TO OPPONENTS.
- Mirajane:
THE SHORT END OF THE STICK?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WELL, I DON'T
MEAN TO OFFEND YOU,
BUT AFTER BEING FORCED
TO FIGHT CATS AND CHILDREN,
I'D HOPED TO FACE A MORE
CHALLENGING ADVERSARY
THAN A COUPLE
OF YOUNG LADIES.
- IF HE WAS FIGHTING CATS
AND CHILDREN,
THEN THAT MEANS...
- HE MUST HAVE FOUGHT
HAPPY AND WENDY'S TEAMS.
- I DON'T SEE WHY WHO I FOUGHT
MAKES ANY DIFFERENCE TO YOU.
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW
IS I DEFEATED THEM
AND I'LL DO THE SAME HERE.
- ( gasps )
- ( rumbling )
- HIS MAGIC IS SO STRONG.
- LISANNA,
YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
- NO, I'M OKAY.
- THIS WIZARD, HE'S POWERFUL.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING,
BUT I KNOW WE CAN BEAT HIM.
NOW TAKE OVER!
ANIMAL SOUL!
- SO TAKE OVER MAGIC, HUH?
I CERTAINLY WASN'T
EXPECTING THAT FROM YOU.
- FOLLOWED BY...
- HMM?
- PENGUIN!
- SHE INSTANTLY SWITCHED
TO A DIFFERENT TAKE OVER.
WHEN DID SHE LEARN
SUCH AN ADVANCED MOVE?
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME.
I'M YOUNG, BUT I'M AS TOUGH
AS THE OTHER FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS.
- BLEVE!
- GOTCHA!
( meows )
- LISANNA!
- JUST STAY BACK.
I GOT THIS.
- I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU'RE A MUCH BETTER
FIGHTER THAN I EXPECTED.
THAT'S SAID,
ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU
WHY I'M CONFIDENT
YOU'LL NEVER DEFEAT ME.
YOU CAN'T WIN A BATTLE
WITH SPIRIT AND SENTIMENT ALONE.
IT TAKES SKILL.
AND MINE GREATLY
SURPASSES YOURS.
ARE YOU REALLY WILLING
TO RISK YOUR LIFE
IN AN ATTEMPT TO PROVE
YOUR STRENGTH TO ME?
- WHAT DO YOU
MEAN BY THAT?
THIS ISN'T ABOUT
A DIFFERENCE IN POWER.
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN ME.
WHO CARES?!
WE JUST WANT TO
PROTECT OUR CAMP
SO OUR FRIENDS KNOW
WHERE TO FIND US.
- FRANKLY,
I COULDN'T CARE LESS.
I WAS SENT HERE TO FIGHT YOU,
SO THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
- YOU OKAY?
- I WANT YOU TO GO
AND LOOK FOR THE OTHERS.
MEANWHILE, I'LL STAY HERE
AND KEEP THIS GUY BUSY.
- I CAN'T LEAVE
YOU ALONE WITH HIM.
- WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
I BARELY SENSED ANY MAGIC POWER
FROM HER BEFORE,
BUT THEN SHE SUDDENLY
GAVE OFF
A TREMENDOUS
SENSE OF PRESSURE.
- I'M GONNA FIGHT WITH YOU.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER,
WE'VE GOT
A BETTER CHANCE
OF BEATING HIM.
- YOU'RE JUST AS
STUBBORN AS BEFORE.
VERY WELL THEN.
- TWO AGAINST ONE
MEANS I DON'T HAVE TO HOLD BACK.
- Mirajane:
MESS WITH OUR GUILD--
NO, OUR FAMILY--
AND YOU'RE IN
A FOR A WORLD OF HURT!
- Zancrow: YOU THINK
YOU CAN TAKE DOWN MASTER HADES?
( laughs )
THERE AIN'T NO WAY IN HELL
THAT'S EVER GONNA HAPPEN
IF YOU CAN'T EVEN BEAT ME,
YOU PUNK.
- I TOLD YOU.  YOUR FLAMES
HAVE NO EFFECT ON ME.
- OH, NO, IT CAN'T BE.
HE USES FIRE MAGIC TOO?
- YOUR DRAGON FIRE'S GOT
NOTHING ON MY DIVINE FLAMES.
THEY'RE ON A COMPLETELY...
- ( grunts )
- DIFFERENT LEVEL.
MY FLAMES DO MORE
THAN JUST BURN STUFF.
THEY BECOME
A WEAPON OF FIRE
THAT CAN DEFEAT ANY ENEMY.
( laughs )
( cackles )
- ( grunting )
- GOT YA'!
- ( gasps )
- MY FLAMES LOVE
TO CONSUME
PUNY WIZARDS LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
FLAME GOD...
SUPPER!
- ( screams )
- YOU SHOULD QUIT FIGHTING
'CAUSE ONCE MY BLAZE
HAS GOT YOU,
THERE'S NO GETTING OUT!
NOT TILL YOU'VE BEEN
TURNED TO ASH.
- ( screams )
- NATSU, NO.
- OH, YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
I CAN STILL EAT
MY WAY OF HERE, YOU KNOW?
- GO AHEAD AND TRY IT,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY A WIZARD
WITH DRAGON'S POWER
COULD EVER EAT
A DIVINE FLAME.
- ( slurps )
( screams )
- DON'T SAY THAT
I DIDN'T WARN YOU!
( groans )
( grunting )
A GIANT, HUH?
- GRAMPS!
- HOW DARE YOU.
WHAT KIND OF
HEARTLESS MONSTER
WOULD HARM ONE OF MY CHILDREN
RIGHT BEFORE MY VERY EYES?!
STOP OR I'LL CRUSH YOU
LIKE AN INSECT.
- ( gags )
- AND WHEN I'M DONE,
THERE WON'T BE
ANY TRACE OF YOU!
- HOW CAN YOU BE SURE
YOU'VE GOT ENOUGH
STRENGTH LEFT, OLD MAN?
- ( strains )
- AWW, COME ON,
YOU BETTER LET GO OF ME SOON.
OTHERWISE, THE ONLY THING
THAT'S GONNA VANISH
WITHOUT A TRACE
IS YOUR ARM.
- ( strains )
( screams )
- YOU CRAZY? LET GO.
DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO LOSE THAT ARM?
- IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES,
SO BE IT.
- PLEASE, JUST LET GO
OF HIM, GRAMPS.
- ( growls )
LET ME GO!
- Natsu:
I'M BEGGING YOU, LET GO.
- I PITY YOU, YOUNG MAN,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
THE POWER OF FAMILY!
- ( hisses )
( grunts )
( growls )
- IS IT GONNA BE
THE DRAGON HUNTER,
MAKAROV, OR ME?
WHICH ONE OF US
WILL KICK THE BUCKET FIRST?
- ( screams )
- ( power sizzles )
- NATSU'S MAGIC POWER,
IT'S GONE.
- ( laughs )
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE DRAGON HUNTER'S
THE FIRST TO GO.
( laughs )
- ( slurps )
- ( burbles )
- ( gasps )
- ( slurping )
- NO, IMPOSSIBLE!
A DRAGON HUNTER SHOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO EAT MY FLAMES!
- Makarov: AMAZING.
BY USING EVERY LAST DROP
OF HIS OWN MAGIC POWER,
HE BECAME A VESSEL CAPABLE
OF CONSUMING INEDIBLE FIRE.
- I GET IT NOW.
I HAD NO CLUE
THERE WAS SPECIAL TRICK
TO EATING CERTAIN
TYPES OF FIRE.
- Makarov: NO WAY!
I WOULDN'T CALL
THAT LEVEL OF MAGIC
"A SPECIAL TRICK."
HE EMPTIED HIS BODY
OF MAGIC POWER
WHILE THE ENEMY'S BEGAN
TO BUILD UP INSIDE.
HOW COULD YOU
BE SO FOOLISH, NATSU?!
DO YOU WANT TO DIE?!
- OF COURSE I DON'T, GRAMPS.
AND I WON'T LET
ANYONE ELSE, EITHER.
NO ONE'S DYING.
AT LEAST NOT ON MY WATCH,
ANYWAY.
WE'RE ALL GONNA MAKE IT
BACK HOME TO FAIRY TAIL.
( growls )
DRAGON AND DIVINE FLAMES,
COME TOGETHER
TO BECOME ONE!
DRAGON GOD...
BRILLIANT FLAME!
- ( cackles )
- ( gasps )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE ACTUALLY WON.
HE'S GROWN SO MUCH...
- ( pants slowly )
- INTO AN AMAZING WIZARD.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( panting )
I DID IT.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: YOU SEE THAT?
I TOTALLY WON.
- Happy: THAT'S GREAT, BUT YOU
SHOULDN'T USE YOUR MAGIC
SO RECKLESSLY.
THAT WAS SUCH A HUGE GAMBLE.
I MEAN, USING UP
ALL OF YOUR POWER
AND THEN ABSORBING
YOUR OPPONENT'S.
- Natsu: GIVE ME A BREAK.
THERE'S NO WRONG WAY
TO USE MAGIC.
BESIDES, ARE YOU
REALLY SURPRISED?
KICKING BUTT IS WHAT I DO.
- Happy: YOU KNOW,
YOU WOULD HAVE SOUNDED
A LOT COOLER
IF YOU HADN'T SAID
THAT LAST PART.
- Happy and Natsu:
NEXT TIME, "GRAND MAGIC WORLD"!
- Happy: YOU KNOW, IT TAKES A
LOT OF GUTS TO BRAG LIKE THAT
AFTER YOU BARELY
BEAT THE GUY.
- Natsu: SAYS THE CAT WHO'S
NEVER WON A FIGHT ON HIS OWN.
- Happy: GEEZ, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO REMINDING ME!