It's, uh...
It's almost unthinkable.
Yes. These ideas... You wrote
this treatise yourself?
Yes.
[OLD TEACHER A]
I see.
The work is quite impressive,
but I cannot condone
the content.
It's not appropriate for a child
to discuss matters
such as these.
[OLD TEACHER C]
Your age notwithstanding,
magic pertaining
to life and death
is dangerous and
forbidden territory.
You must not delve
further into it.
It would surely be looked
upon as an act of hubris.
[OLD TEACHER A]
Mh-hm.
Such thinking would
risk drawing the ire
of the god of life
and death, Ankhselam.
Thus, we will not allow you
to continue pursuing this magic.
[OLD TEACHER A]
Well, Zeref, is that clear?
Yes, sir.
All I want is to understand
why people live.
And why it is we die.
There has to be a reason.
A dream?
[ZEREF]
Must've been a dream.
[ZEREF] Can't remember
the last time I had one.
Natsu.
It's been ages since my
younger brother was with us.
At the time he was taken,
his life was just beginning.
I could never understand
why he had to die.
And so... that became
my life's mission.
There's still much
work to be done.
But if we find a way to amass
the 2.7 billion units
of magic power needed,
the Revive System
will become reality.
It's unbelievable.
[TEACHER D] The theoretical
magic is flawless.
The Revive System...
could bring back the dead?
In the academy's history, we've
never witnessed such a mind.
[OLD TEACHER A grumbles]
[OLD TEACHER A] How many times
must I repeat myself, Zeref?
The type of magic that you're
exploring is strictly forbidden.
Have you not
considered the toll?
The sheer number of lives
that must be sacrificed
for your design to work?
Life and death are both
bound by nature.
And they fall under the rules
of gods, not mere mortals.
[ZEREF]
Consider life.
There exists an element of
human choice in its creation,
does there not?
So, then, why should death
be fully exempt from that?
[OLD TEACHER A]
Uh!
Ankhselam! I beseech you to
have mercy on this boy's soul!
[grumbles]
[OLD TEACHER A]
Zeref.
Yes, sir?
Are you ignoring my commands?
I told you to stop working
on this Eclipse Project.
[ZEREF] But the design
is almost complete.
And I figured out how to
avoid the ethical dilemma.
A door that takes us
through time. Backwards.
But why return to the past?
Well, I...
It's all part of a recurring
focus of your work.
I can only assume
your ultimate goal
is to bring your late
brother back to life?
Despite our repeated
warnings over the years,
you remain obsessed with
the dangerous idea
of reviving the dead.
And because of this, the board
has decided to expel you.
[gasps]
[OLD TEACHER A]
This was not an easy decision.
We all had such high
hopes for you.
Not now! Please, sir!
Your brother is
never coming back!
And nothing you can
do will change that!
[gasps]
[OLD TEACHER A]
Huh?
What's happening?
Teacher... Help me.
[OLD TEACHER A]
Oh, no!
This must be the
wrath of Ankhselam!
[chokes]
[gasps]
[ZEREF screams]
[ZEREF]
Before I knew it,
the lives of every teacher
and student at the academy
had been snuffed out.
[gasps]
[ZEREF] I had indeed drawn
the wrath of Ankhselam.
This curse is one
of contradiction.
The deeper my
concern for life...
...the more I'm
surrounded by death.
[ZEREF]
Please forgive me.
The only way to suppress it
is to have no concern for life.
[ZEREF] This curse also
stopped my process of aging,
dooming me to live forever.
[ZEREF] After the school,
I was plagued by conflict.
Unfathomable guilt for
taking so many lives.
Yet, the fact that I could
continue my studies forever
pleased me greatly.
And in turn,
that joy disgusted me.
After wandering through that
existential labyrinth for years,
I came to a conclusion.
My death will bring
all this to an end.
[ZEREF] So I began to undertake
the most taboo magic of all.
That which creates life.
I brought into existence
demons that could kill me.
Known today as Demons
of the Books of Zeref.
Because they were made of ether,
the building blocks of magic,
I originally called
them "Etherious."
If only those demons
were powerful enough
to finish me off.
[ZEREF] Eventually,
I created my magnum opus
that could bring
all this to an end.
In fact, I called it E.N.D.
Etherious Natsu Dragneel.
[ZEREF] But this was not
some object or tool
to be used as a means to an end.
He was human from the
beginning, flesh and blood.
I had cared for my beloved
brother's body all those years.
Waiting for this day.
At last.
My brother's returned as
the ultimate Etherious.
[ZEREF] My deepest desires
have both been made flesh.
Nastu, do you remember me?
I am your older brother, Zeref.
[ZEREF]
Etherious Natsu Dragneel.
I'm sure you'd like to know how
you were paired with Igneel,
as well as my
connection to Mavis.
But those tales will
be told later.
At the moment, there's
a very important man
that I need to meet with.
[ZEREF]
Can I even call him a man?
[ZEREF] It's rather
surprising that you agreed
to have this discussion.
I can assume this is
how you normally look?
How's your arm healing up?
[ZEREF]
Well, Acnologia?
Black Wizard.
What is it you want?
[ZEREF]
You crave destruction.
Yet you hardly indulge yourself.
If you so desired,
you could use your power
to bring the entire
world to its knees.
But for some reason you haven't.
Whether it's a
matter of principle
or ambition is unclear.
[ACNOLOGIA]
The same could be said of you.
[ZEREF]
To be quite honest,
my indecision is what has
kept me out of the fray.
Should I side with humans
and do battle with you?
Or would the opposite
better suit my needs?
But I've come to the conclusion
that the question
itself is flawed.
After weighing my interests,
I am on neither side.
Both you and mankind
should be wiped out.
What do you think?
You have been waiting for a
serious challenge, correct?
I am the one who will
bring that to you.
The world will bear witness.
A human, a dragon,
and an immortal..
...will constitute
this final battle.
[chuckles]
[bell tolls]
[LUCY] In my opinion, Magnolia
is the jewel of eastern Fiore.
But it shone much brighter
when the Fairy Tail guild
hall was part of the skyline.
Strange to think
it's been a year
since we've walked
these streets.
Does this bring back
some memories or what?
Hey, look! They fixed up
Kardia Cathedral!
[LUCY] The members
we'd been able to find
were all in favor of getting
the guild back together.
It's so good to see
everything's back to normal.
The town's always
been resilient.
Yeah.
[LUCY]
After the fight with Avatar,
our group needed to
split up for a while,
but we agreed to reconvene
here in Magnolia.
[ERZA]
I won't be long,
but I need to report
back to Jellal first.
[GRAY]
Hey, Gajeel.
Could you not tell
the council about us?
Keep it hush-hush.
They wouldn't approve
of us shacking up!
[GRAY] Gimme a break!
I mean me and Erza's mission!
Shack up?
We need to report back as well,
but we'll meet you
there A.S.A.P.
Kinda thought workin' for the
Council was my true calling.
That is supposed to
be a joke, right?
[GAJEEL] I bet ol' wood
face'll be sad to see me go.
Now, that one's
definitely a joke!
I should arrest you for that!
No crime in being funny!
[BOTH chuckle]
[LUCY] It's a shame,
but I seriously doubt
we're gonna get any
information about Zeref
from those Avatar members.
They worshipped him, but they
didn't actually know him.
[WENDY]
Hm?
Is something wrong?
You look sad.
Aren't you glad to be back here?
Uh-huh, of course I am!
I just kinda got lost in my
memories for a second.
[LUCY]
Yeah.
So many memories were
made in this town.
Some are sad...
Some are happy...
Most of them still
make me smile.
I formed them with
my Fairy Tail family.
I was afraid after what
happened last year,
those memories would
be all we had left.
Master, are you outta your mind?
What's wrong with you?
[JET] I can't believe you
wouldn't talk to us first!
[DROY] How will we put
food on the table?
[FAIRY TAIL A]
Yeah, we need money!
[FAIRY TAIL B]
Tell us you're joking!
I am disbanding
the Fairy Tail guild.
Which means, from this point on,
you must forge your
own way forward.
That's final.
I just can't accept
this, Master!
You gotta realize that you're
messin' with our lives here!
[FAIRY TAIL C]
If you wanna quit so bad,
why don't you just
leave by yourself?
[FAIRY TAIL D]
Yeah!
A real man never quits!
Fairy Tail ain't goin' away!
[MAKAROV] I've made my decision,
and Fairy Tail is no more!
Hear me?
You are never to speak its name
again! Leave it in the past!
Tch.
[gasps]
[LUCY] Makarov was gone before
the shock could wear off.
We were all in a daze.
Eventually, everyone did have to
start forging their own paths,
as he'd said.
Just like that,
Fairy Tail was over.
We were left clutching
those memories we'd shared.
Come on, Lucy,
we're just about there.
Yeah, we're practically
at the old guild hall.
I know.
But honestly, I'm kinda too
scared to get any closer.
[NATSU]
Why? 'Cause the building's gone?
That's the least important
part of the guild.
It's what's inside
us that counts.
We all feel the
same way about it.
But everyone else?
I mean, it was exciting when
you showed up out of nowhere
and talked about
reviving the guild.
So I let myself
get fired up too.
And right away, I sent
out messages to everybody
that had been in the guild.
At least, those I could find.
No word from me
for an entire year...
Then suddenly, I ask them
to drop everything,
come to Magnolia,
and rebuild Fairy Tail.
Maybe they've done
exactly what master said
and started making their
own way through life.
Maybe they've moved on.
Are we the only ones
who feel this way?
What if they have
put it in the past?
What if they've forgotten
about it altogether?
I...
I know my memory's
not that great,
but it's only been a year.
[NATSU]
Cana?
[WENDY]
You're here!
[CANA]
Hm?
What's up?
It's so good to see
you guys again!
Wendy, I think you've grown
a bit since last time!
[WENDY]
No. Not really.
And you're just as
bouncy as always, Lucy!
Cana.
[CANA] Not gonna lie,
with all that happened,
this has been an
eye-opening year for me.
I decided I'd try to
track down my old man,
so I was gonna take a trip.
Can hardly believe I got your
letter. What a lucky break!
I imagine everyone
else feels the same.
[LUCY gasps]
The guild's family.
I've been a member ever
since I was a little kid.
So when Makarov decided to
break it up all of a sudden,
I was pretty lost.
I had no idea how I was
gonna make a living
or who I could turn to.
In a weird way, it helped put
things into perspective.
[CANA] The whole situation was
such a shock to all of us.
It seemed like nobody had
the stones to reach out.
Or I should say, nobody
but you, Lucy. Good call.
[gasps]
[NATSU chuckles]
[CANA]
So come on!
Everyone's waiting!
Yeah?
[gasps]
Lookin' good, Lucy! You are
rockin' that long hair!
[DROY, JET] It's so
awesome to see you guys!
When I got your letter,
it made me really happy!
Oui.
Heard Natsu caused a
scene at the capital!
Hey, Wendy. We missed you
and Carla around here!
[WAKABA] Lookin' like a
scrapper there, Happy!
Certainly took you long enough.
Back in Magnolia.
It feels good.
[LUCY]
Warren.
You like the portable
communication lacrima I built?
[LUCY]
Nab.
He read your Sorcerer Weekly
articles! And so did I!
[LUCY]
Reedus. Max.
Oui, oui.
Here in the flesh!
[LUCY]
Alzack, Bisca, and lil' Asca!
[ERZA] Still such a beautiful
and happy family.
[LUCY]
Jet! Droy!
[BOTH] Team Shadow Gear
is together again!
I had to leave the council
for that to happen!
[ALL] You were working
for the Magic Council?!
[LUCY]
Macao, Wakaba, and Romeo!
Gonna have to lock you
guys up for bein' chumps.
[LUCY]
Laki!
Diggin' the new hairstyle.
[LUCY]
Vijeeter!
I'm guessing that's some
kind of reunion dance?
[LUCY]
Kinana!
She actually
learned some magic!
[ELFMAN] I wasn't gonna
miss this for the world!
[gasps]
[LUCY]
Lisanna! Elfman!
A reunion fit for a real man!
[MIRAJANE]
Lucy.
Mira, it's you.
[giggles]
Welcome back home.
I am home.
[LUCY] It felt so natural
for us to be together again,
like a real family.
I was so happy, but
the tears wouldn't stop.
I missed you all.
[LUCY]
Mira!
Guess what I found!
A little ragged, but who cares?
[NATSU]
Our guild is back in action!
Fairy Tail still rules!
[LUCY] The Fairy Tail reunion
kicks off in Magnolia.
But so does the hard work
we'll need to put in
to build the guild up
to our former glory!
Although, we're all worried that
no one has heard from master
since that fateful day.
The first order of business
is to rebuild our
wrecked guild hall.
Then one day, as we start
to get back on our feet,
a man bearing the
Fairy Tail emblem
shows up with a message for us.
Next Time: "The Seventh
Guild Master."
The secret door will
soon be opened.