[girl crying]
[MICHELLE]
Why are you crying?
[YOUNG LUCY]
I can't help it.
I'm sad 'cause
everyone's gone.
Mommy, Daddy, and
even my little sister.
[MICHELLE] So you
remember me now?
[YOUNG LUCY] Yeah.
I'm sorry I forgot.
[MICHELLE] You don't
have to apologize.
I'm just happy you
remembered me, Big Sister.
Michelle.
[panting]
Aw, c'mon!
How many more of these
do we have to destroy
before this works?
[ERZA] Warren!
What's the situation?
[WARREN] More than half of
the chains are still intact!
You guys, please hurry!
It's no use.
It's taking
us too long.
I'm afraid
we've no other choice
but to go through
and cut them one-by-one.
[CARLA] Come child,
we have to keep going!
[MIDNIGHT] It won't
be long now.
Once I fulfill
my father's wish,
everything will
cease to exist!
[COCO] No!
Please Lucy!
You have to wake up!
Natsu, we're
gonna lose her
if we don't hurry!
[NATSU] No way!
I'm not gonna let
you just disappear!
You've gotta hang
in there, Lucy!
Can you stand up?
[ROMEO] Michelle's gone.
Yeah, she is.
Just let it go.
We got more
important things
to worry about right now.
Yeah, you're right.
Can you hear me?
I know they're
cutting the chains
but it doesn't seem
to be doing
anything to help her!
[ROMEO] We're not
gonna make it in time!
We've gotta
defeat their final member!
Alright, we'll help
you take him down, Natsu!
Yeah!
[MIDNIGHT] Klodoa.
[KLODOA] Allow me to
handle them, Master.
I won't let you fools
interfere with our plans!
[NATSU] You guys focus on
snappin' that twig in two!
Meanwhile, I'm gonna
punch the make-up
right offa this punk's face!
Let's do this, Romeo!
Yeah!
I'm fired up now!
[HAPPY] Lucy and Michelle!
[COBRA] Damn you, Titania.
You should've
just killed me
when you
had the chance.
Someone's coming.
Who's there?
Reveal yourself!
I'm not scared
of your flames.
You can attack
all you want
but they will
never burn me.
[MIDNIGHT] Eventually...
You'll run out
of magic power.
[NATSU] Yeah,
that's what you think!
If you ain't afraid of me
how come you keep
avoiding my attacks?
You're a coward!
[MIDNIGHT] And now all
you can do is hurl insults?
It's quite telling.
Obviously I hold
the power here.
[MIDNIGHT] I've always
dreamed of having magic power
equal to that of my father.
And after my sacrifice,
I finally do.
[NATSU] What kinda sacrifice?
[MIDNIGHT] Now you will become
a traveler of the void.
Salamander.
Genesis Zero!
Open Gate
of Restless Wailing!
Go forth,
travelers of the void!
I want you to consume
his soul, his memory.
Consume his very existence!
Devour him!
For the sake of your master!
[ELFMAN] Natsu!
[ROMEO] Natsu!
[MIDNIGHT] That should be
the last of you.
You're forever
trapped within the darkness.
Much like your friend
who is trapped
within perpetual time.
[JUDE] Lucy.
[LAYLA] What do
you think, dear?
Do you like her?
[YOUNG LUCY] Oh yeah!
She's the best
birthday present ever!
[YOUNG LUCY] And she's gonna
be my new, little sister!
[LAYLA] That's wonderful.
Take good care of her, okay?
[YOUNG LUCY] I need to
think up a nice name for her.
Like Gonzales!
Yeah!
[LAYLA] Um.
Why don't you go with
something more feminine?
[MICHELLE] Do you
remember how much fun we had?
The mansion was so big
that it felt like
a castle to us.
[MICHELLE] You made me so
many beautiful outfits
out of nothing but
paper and flowers.
[MICHELLE] We went
everywhere together
and wherever we went,
you were all smiles.
But then...
[LUCY] My mom died.
Every day I would go
to her grave and cry.
[LUCY] I lashed out
at everyone around me.
I can't imagine
how worried my
father must've been.
[MICHELLE] I felt so helpless
because all I could do
was watch you go through it.
I wish I had been
able to help you somehow.
[LUCY] Every time
I looked at you,
it reminded me of my mom
and how much I missed her.
[MICHELLE] I know.
[MICHELLE] I assumed that's
why you stopped talking to me.
[LUCY] Sorry.
Time passed and I eventually
forgot all about you.
[LUCY] For years and years,
you sat patiently,
waiting for the day
I would come
back to you again.
[JUDE] I'm sorry.
She hasn't
necessarily abandoned you.
It's just that the sorrow
of losing her mother
has overwhelmed her.
She's so distracted
she's lost sight of what
was once important to her.
[JUDE] I wish
there was something
I could do to
ease her heartache.
[JUDE] Someday,
when she's grown up
and she's gotten
over her mother's death,
it is my hope that
you'll get the chance
to be her
little sister again.
[MICHELLE] For years
I waited patiently,
hoping you'd come back.
Over time, the once-lively
mansion grew quiet.
[MICHELLE] Eventually,
it was deserted.
[MICHELLE] When someone
finally came looking for me
it wasn't my big sister.
[MICHELLE] I was so
thankful to be given life
as Imitatia that I did
exactly as I was told.
I took the name
Michelle Lobster
and set out to obtain
the Infinity Clock.
[LUCY] So when you told me
you had helped
my father with his work.
[MICHELLE] It was
the absolute truth.
[MICHELLE] It broke
my heart to use him
but it had to be done.
I wanted the good
old days back.
[MICHELLE] Lucy,
all I wanted
was to be your
sister again.
I know you
and your father
have had your ups
and downs over the years.
But that's normal.
It's all
part of being a family.
No matter
what happens
the bond you share
will bring you together.
[JUDE] I haven't
heard from her
but I know Lucy's still
alive out there somewhere.
Will you go find her and
give her the clock hand?
Please, Michelle.
Of course I will.
You know,
I'm always amazed
by the power of magic.
This time
I'm sure of it.
You will be her little
sister once again.
I'm so sorry, Michelle.
That must've been
really hard for you.
[MICHELLE] Please
stop crying, Big Sister.
It's okay.
You're loved by
so many people.
Listen closely
and you'll hear
them calling out to you.
I do!
I can hear everyone
and I can see them!
My friends!
[ERZA] Hang in
there, Lucy!
[WENDY] We're too slow!
Hurry! We've gotta
work faster!
[CARLA] Okay!
On to the next one!
[GRAY] What's up?
Have we beat 'em yet?
[CARLA] Warren!
How's Natsu's team?
[WARREN] Aw, crap!
I dunno what happened
but I've lost my
telepathic link with him!
[ROMEO] Natsu's in
serious trouble!
[ELFMAN] He just
vanished into thin air!
[KLODOA] There's no
saving your friend
now that he's been
consumed by the darkness,
so you might as well
give up the fight.
[NATSU] Please, just wait
a little longer, Lucy.
I'm comin' to save you!
[LUCY] Natsu.
The longer I'm here.
The more I lose
sight of who I am.
I can't!
I've gotta do something!
[MIDNIGHT] No matter
how much you struggle,
you will never
escape the darkness.
[MIDNIGHT] Your time is up.
Goodbye, great
dragon wizard.
[NATSU] No!
I ain't done yet!
[NATSU] You hurt
Lucy and Michelle!
Now I'm gonna hurt you!
[LUCY] I can't
keep crying forever.
No!
Apologize to Michelle!
And bring Natsu back!
[COCO] What's
happening now?
[HAPPY] It's so bright!
[ROMEO] Did you hear that?
[ELFMAN] Yeah, it
sounded like Lucy!
[MIDNIGHT]
What happened to me?
The Tower of Heaven?
No!
This is it!
[MIDNIGHT] This is
the Real Nightmare!
[MIDNIGHT]
How did this happen?
It must've been the girl!
My seal is
all that's left.
It's not strong enough
to hold her back!
[MIDNIGHT] I'm such a fool!
[NATSU] I heard you, Lucy!
[COCO] How'd he come back?
[HAPPY] Lucy did it!
She used
the Infinity Clock
to cast the Real Nightmare
spell on that creep!
[NATSU] So, You
made a sacrifice?
Gimme a break!
[MIDNIGHT] As they say,
magic comes from the heart.
And the greater the feelings
that you're willing to abandon,
the greater
the power you'll gain!
[KLODOA] I don't like
the looks of this!
Those two are about
to throw down!
[KLODOA] Now, now,
there's no need
to resort to violence!
The girl's taken control
of the Infinity Castle,
so as far as I'm concerned,
you guys win.  See ya!
[ROMEO] He's runnin'.
[ELFMAN] And you
call yourself a man?
[ROMEO] No, he's a stick.
[MIDNIGHT] When you
care for someone,
your deepest wish
is to see them again!
[MIDNIGHT] There's nothing
more excruciating
than knowing
you will never have
the chance because
of your own actions!
[NATSU] Whatever you say.
So tell me,
what did you sacrifice
to gain the power
that you have now?
[MIDNIGHT] My future.
At least one in which
I'll ever get
to see my father again.
[COCO] So he
took a possibility
and then made
it an impossibility
in order to gain power?
My head hurts.
[HAPPY] A backward view
using forward thinkin'.
That's pretty
impressive, huh?
[NATSU] I don't
get it, man.
You're not
makin' any sense.
If you wanna see
your dad so badly,
then why dontcha
just go see him?
[MIDNIGHT] You're the
reason my father and I
were torn apart
all those years ago.
Don't tell me
that you've forgotten.
[NATSU] That's what
you're pissed off about?
Don't you dare try to act
like the innocent
victim, buddy.
You're the scumbag
who made Lucy cry.
[NATSU] So you "sacrificed"
your future.
If you ask me,
givin' up somethin'
that hasn't happened yet
ain't that big a deal.
Quit your whining
and fight me!
[LEVY] Warren!
[WARREN] What's up?
[LEVY] I've got news.
We've been double-checking
our notes and, well.
[JEAN-LUC] Now
Listen carefully!
You see, we've actually
discovered something
very important
that we thought
you and the others
should know!
[WARREN] Say what?
Run that by me again!
[MIDNIGHT] Impossible!
How am I being overpowered?
[NATSU] I know
what it's like
to miss havin'
your dad around,
so I can definitely
sympathize with you.
But you're wrong.
[NATSU] That whole
thing about having
to abandon your feelings
to gain power
is a huge crock.
'Cause you only gain it
by holding 'em
close to your heart.
[MIDNIGHT] Liar!
That can't be true!
I was taught that
sacrifice is the only way!
[NATSU
'Fraid not!
[NATSU] You don't know what
to think anymore, do ya?
You've been twistin'
everything around so much
your perception's
all screwed up now.
If you keep it up,
you can't be true to your past!
Much less your future!
[NATSU] You can't even
be true to your own heart!
[MIDNIGHT] Are you implying
that I'm not being
true to my father?
[NATSU] Lucy opened
up to her dad
and Michelle
opened up to her.
Don't punish them just
'cause you got it wrong!
[NATSU] You think
you're so smart
but you've got
a lot to learn.
[NATSU] Feelings
are one thing.
[NATSU] You obviously
don't know anything about!
[ROMEO] Yeah!
[laughing]
[MIDNIGHT] Father.
[ROMEO] We beat the last
of the Six Demons!
[ELFMAN] How's Lucy?
[COCO] Oh, no.
[HAPPY] We're too late.
What'll we do now?
[HAPPY] Lucy's
completely disappeared.
[NATSU] How'd that happen?
I mean, we got rid of
all six of the seals!
Where the heck did she go?
We ain't leavin'
'til we get her back!
[LUCY] Huh?
What're they talking about?
I didn't go anywhere,
I'm right here!
[LUCY] Whoa, wait a sec!
Don't tell me that I'm...
You gotta be kiddin' me!
[ELFMAN] What was that?
[ROMEO] Is Lucy
here somewhere?
[NATSU] That's weird.
I can smell
her all around us!
[GRAY] Whoa.
That wasn't telepathy.
[ERZA] We can't
give up hope.
Not yet.
[WENDY] Oh no.
We were too late.
[CARLA] Yes, It
appears as though
she's merged with
the Infinity Castle.
[HAPPY] Lemme
get this straight,
you're sayin'
that Lucy's
turned into this
humongous fish?
[NATSU] So, in a way,
this is her body now, huh?
[LUCY] No!
[LUCY] I can't believe
this is happening to me.
One minute I'm normal
and the next I'm Happy food?
[HAPPY] Don't worry,
I won't eat ya!
[WARREN] It's gonna be okay!
Unfortunately, you sped
up the merging process
whenever you used the Real
Nightmare spell to save Natsu.
[NATSU] Don't blame
me for this!
[WARREN] Look, I'm just glad
I finally got through to you!
Listen up, everyone!
I've got some news
from the team back
at the guildhall.
[WARREN] Jean-Luc
and the others
have figured out a way
for us to save Lucy!
[NATSU] Who is Jean-Luc?
[HAPPY] He's the guy who
always says "actually".
[JEAN-LUC] If the
seals aren't removed
from the Infinity Clock
before the merging
process is complete,
the person who has been
merged can only be freed
if they focus their mind
and actually control
the Real Nightmare spell.
[LEVY] According to
what it says here,
the clock is
remaining in this world
because of the magic
power it's absorbing
from the Celestial wizards
who are serving as body links.
[WARREN] They're stuck
in chrysalis form,
so we need to lift the curse
that's been placed on 'em.
Luckily, it should
be pretty simple.
[COCO] Lucy's gotta alter
their perception of time
to one hundred years
in the future.
[WARREN] Yep, you got it.
If she does that,
then the clock
will break apart
and all the pieces
will scatter themselves.
[WENDY]
Are you sure?
[GRAY] Wait.
But what about Lucy?
[ERZA] How is this
going to affect her?
[JEAN-LUC] I wish
I could tell you.
All we know for sure is
this will undo the merging.
[ELFMAN] Yeah, but
it could also send her
flyin' along with
the clock pieces!
[ROMEO] What'll we do?
[NATSU] C'mon, there's
gotta be another way!
[LUCY] I'll give it a shot!
[LUCY] The other
Celestial Wizards need me.
If I don't pull it off
they'll sleep
for a hundred years.
[LUCY] So what if I get
sent flying off somewhere?
I think that
it's worth the risk!
I'm not scared
'cause I'm a
Fairy Tail wizard.
Jude and Layla
Heartfilia's daughter.
Lucy... Michelle's
big sister!
I can do this!
[MICHELLE] I believe
in you, Lucy.
[LUCY] This is tough!
[MICHELLE] Don't be afraid.
I'll stay right
by your side.
[LUCY] Thank you!
[KINANA] You've
been badly injured.
Is there anything
I can do to help you?
[COBRA] You can get
your dirty hands off of me.
[KINANA] So the person calling
out to me, was that you?
[COBRA] I can hear it.
[COBRA] It's you!
[KINANA] Tell me.
[KINANA] What
happened to your eye?
[COBRA] I sacrificed
it to gain power.
It's no big deal.
All I need is
my hearing anyway.
[KINANA] What's your name?
[COBRA] It's Erik.
[KINANA] Hello, Erik.
[LAHAR] You're Cobra of
the Neo-Oración Seis?
[DORANBOLT] The others
are already in our custody.
We ask that you
surrender peacefully.
[COBRA] And
what if I don't?
[KINANA] No, wait!
He's not a bad guy.
He's not!
[DORANBOLT] What the?
[LAHAR] Are you
resisting arrest?
[LAHAR] That's odd.
The girl doesn't
appear to be a wizard.
[DORANBOLT] If she's
an accomplice to
the Neo-Oración Seis,
we're gonna have
to take her in, too.
[COBRA] Relax, I'm coming.
Get outta here.
[KINANA] What?
Erik.
[KINANA] Wait!
You never answered!
Were you the one
calling out to me?
[KINANA] Were you?
[COBRA] I don't know
what you're talking about.
[LAHAR] What about the girl?
[DORANBOLT] Is she
an accomplice of yours?
[COBRA] Nope.
I don't know her.
Apparently she's
been wandering around
looking for an
old friend of hers.
[LAHAR] Very well then.
Let's go.
[DORANBOLT] You're givin'
up a lot easier
than I thought you would.
[COBRA] Yeah, well.
Change of heart.
I envy that girl.
Knowing you have a friend.
[COBRA] It must be
a comforting thing.
Maybe I'll find
one some day.
[KINANA] Erik.
I know that was your
voice calling out to me.
[KINANA] I can't
help but wonder
if you could
hear me too.
[COBRA] I finally
got to hear it.
The sound of your voice.
[ICHIYA] Man!
I'm glad you're okay!
[NATSU] Are we on
top of an octopus?
[ICHIYA] There's
no need to panic.
Kanaloa and I are now bound
by the parfum of
eternal friendship.
[NATSU] So you guys
are buddies now?
[HAPPY] Hey Natsu, listen.
[NATSU] Where's Lucy?
We gotta get out
there and find her!
[ERZA] We're already
working on it.
[GRAY] Yeah, Warren's
team is lookin' for her.
[NATSU] Well, that
ain't good enough!
[sniffing]
[NATSU] Guys,
I've picked up her scent!
It's gotta be her.
Take us thataway, octopus!
[ICHIYA] Very well then.
If you would, Kanaloa.
[KLODOA] We were so close
but we still
failed miserably.
I should've known better
than to leave those
Fairy Tail brats
to the "Neo-Oración Seis."
[KLODOA] I guess I'll just
have to become Brain the Third
and find six more idiots
who are willing
to sacrifice-- Wha?
[BOOK GIRL]
There's no escape.
You, too, shall
sleep for a century.
[LUCY] By the time I came to,
both the Infinity Castle
and the Neo-Oración Seis
were long gone.
[LUCY] And so,
the journey that began
with the hand of a clock
and all of the
confusion and chaos
caused by "Key of
the Starry Heavens"
finally came to an end.
[LUCY] I'm not sure why,
but ever since I've
been back in my apartment,
it's felt kinda
cold and empty to me.
[LUCY] But even so,
I never feel lonely.
[LUCY] Don't worry about me.
I'm gonna be okay.
Oh, and one more thing.
[LUCY] Mom.
Dad.
Thanks for giving me
such a great little sister.
[NATSU] We did it!
We actually defeated
Brain the Second!
[HAPPY] And everybody
got to play a part in it!
[NATSU] Fairy Tail's
definitely
the strongest
guild around!
[HAPPY] I'm not
so sure about that.
I heard that while we
were stuck on Tenrou Island,
another guild took our place
as the strongest in Fiore!
It sucks but we were
gone for seven years.
[NATSU] Another guild?
No way!
Who?
[HAPPY] Next time: Sabertooth!
[NATSU] Next time: Sabertooth!
[NATSU] I say we kick their
butts and take our title back!
[HAPPY] Geez, what's with you?
I'm startin' to wonder if
fighting is all you think about.