- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE.
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST, MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WOULD NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
TEAMING UP WITH YOU IS
THE WORST IDEA EVER!
- YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- Erza: THE TWO OF YOU ARE THE
STRONGEST WIZARDS HERE.
- Gray: EISENWALD?
- Erza: WE HAVE TO STOP THEM
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
- Lucy: NATSU!
- ( grunts, screams )
- Lucy:
KAGEYAMA HAS THE LULLABY.
- Erza:
THE MASTER IS IN DANGER!
- Lucy:
THAT'S LULLABY'S TRUE FORM?!
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- Lucy:
THEY WENT OVERBOARD.
- THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THESE ARE DEFINITELY
THEIR FOOTPRINTS.
FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
IT'S BEEN TWO DAYS
SINCE THEY WERE HERE.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN THEY SHOULD HAVE
REACHED MAGNOLIA
A LONG TIME AGO.
COULD MEAN TROUBLE.
NOW WHAT?
- ( sighs )
IT'S PROBABLY BEST
IF WE GIVE OUR REPORT
TO THE GUILD.
- WE'RE GOING BACK?
- ( squawking )
- Narrator:
SHE IS BISCA MULAN.
HE IS ALZACK CONNELL.
AS THEY RETURN TO FAIRY TAIL
FROM THEIR SCOUTING MISSION,
BOTH CARRY HEARTS
FULL OF UNCERTAINTY.
- OHH.
THIS IS NO GOOD AT ALL.
I NEED TO GIVE THEM A MESSAGE
FROM THE COUNCIL RIGHT AWAY.
- DON'T BLAME ME.
I WANTED TO GO AFTER THEM.
- BUT THERE'D BE NO POINT.
I KNOW YOU'RE WORRIED,
BUT CLOVER CANYON
IS A DEATH TRAP.
EVEN WITH SOMEONE
FROM A HUNTER'S GUILD
TO GUIDE YOU,
IT WOULD SWALLOW YOU UP
AND NEVER SPIT YOU OUT.
- BUT IF IT'S A DANGEROUS
MAZE OF CANYONS,
WHY WOULD THEY EVEN
WANT TO GO IN THERE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT MUST BE IMPORTANT.
I'M SURE THE MASTER
CAN HANDLE THINGS,
BUT I'M STILL
A LITTLE WORRIED.
- ( Happy speaking )
- AWW, JEEZ!
COME ON, HAPPY.
DON'T TELL ME THAT
YOU GOT US LOST AGAIN.
WE'VE BEEN WALKING FOR
FOREVER AND A HALF,
AND WE STILL HAVEN'T
FOUND MAGNOLIA YET.
WHY ARE WE FOLLOWING
A CAT ANYWAY?!
- Narrator:
THIS IS WEB VALLEY,
HIDDEN DEEP WITHIN
CLOVER CANYON.
HERE, COUNTLESS FISSURES
PRODUCED BY ANCIENT EARTHQUAKES
FORM A FEARSOME MAZE.
MANY ADVENTURERS,
EITHER BRAVE OR FOOLISH,
HAVE ENTERED THIS PLACE
ONLY TO DECORATE ITS LANDSCAPE
WITH THEIR BONES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AGAIN"?
HOW RUDE!
I WASN'T LOST LAST TIME,
SO THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE GOTTEN US LOST.
- FIRST TIME OR NOT,
LET'S JUST TRY TO MAKE IT
OUR LAST, OKAY?
( groans )
- MAN, I WANT SOME FOOD.
- WE ALL DO.  TALKING ABOUT IT
JUST MAKES US HUNGRIER.
- I CAN'T HELP IT
IF I'M HUNGRY, JERK.
- NO, BUT YOU CAN STOP
RUNNING YOUR MOUTH, CAN'T YOU?
- LISTEN UP!
WE NEED SOME FOOD.
- Both: YEAH, WE KNOW!
- ENOUGH.
( stomach growls )
- YOUR STOMACH'S TRYING TO TELL
YOU SOMETHING, ISN'T IT?
- NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU'RE HEARING THINGS.
- UH, YEAH.
REAL CONVINCING, ERZA.
- ( gasps, squeals )
- WHAT ARE YOU
EXCITED ABOUT?
- DOWN THERE!
LOOK, NATSU, LOOK!
- HUH?
- I CAN FLY!
- YOU CAN FLY!
- CAN YOU FLY!
- Happy:
THOSE ARE WINGFISH.
THEY'RE A LEGENDARY
DELICACY.
AND THEY'RE SUPER YUMMY,
FROM WHAT I HEAR.
YUM YUM YUM
YUM YUM YUM!
- A LEGENDARY DELICACY?
- WINGFISH, HUH?
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- WELL DONE, HAPPY.
YOU MAKE THIS
OLD MAN VERY PROUD.
- GUYS, ENOUGH WITH
THE GROWLING STOMACHS.
- ( growls )
- YOU WERE SAYING?
- SHUT UP.
- NOW, TIME TO FISH.
- ( wingfish chattering )
- AW, COME ON,
YOU STUPID FISH.
JUST SHUT UP
AND LET ME EAT YOU.
- WE GOTTA FISH HARDER,
GUYS.
- I DON'T KNOW.
ARE YOU SURE THESE THINGS
REALLY TASTE THAT GOOD?
- BE QUIET AND FISH.
ANYTHING EDIBLE WILL DO.
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE THAT HUNGRY.
- YOU'RE GOING IN MY BELLY!
RIGHT NOW, YOU HEAR?
HAPPY'S GONNA
EAT YOU, FISH.
WHATEVER.  I GIVE UP.
- THAT WAS FAST.
- WELL, I COULDN'T CATCH
A SINGLE FISH.
- YOU REALLY WANT TO
EAT ONE, DON'T YOU?
YOU SHOULDN'T GIVE UP
SO EASILY.
YOU CAN DO IT,
LITTLE GUY.
- ( murmurs )
I CAN'T HELP
THAT I'M LITTLE!
- WHAT?!
I THOUGHT I WAS CHEERING YOU UP.
- Erza: THAT WAS HARDER
THAN YOU'D THINK.
ALL THAT TROUBLE
FOR ONE FISH.
- GO AHEAD AND EAT IT,
HAPPY.
- BUT THAT WOULDN'T BE FAIR
TO YOU GUYS, WOULD IT?
- IT'S WAY TOO SMALL
TO SPLIT UP.
IF WE HAD A BITE,
WE'D JUST WANT MORE.
- HURRY UP AND EAT IT
BEFORE WE CHANGE OUR MINDS.
- OKAY!
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
- ( all grumbling )
- ( chewing )
- WHO KNEW THAT ONE FISH
COULD BRING SO MUCH JOY?
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D
BE JEALOUS OF A CAT.
- GROSS!
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
- I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT...
- ALL THAT FISHING...
- MADE ME HUNGRIER.
- ( all gasp )
- A VILLAGE.
- HOUSES.
- AND THAT MEANS
THERE MUST BE...
- FOOD!
- ( laughing )
- THERE'S NO ONE HERE.
- Lucy: IT DOES SEEM
AWFULLY QUIET, DOESN'T IT?
- Natsu: MAYBE THEY'RE TAKING
AN AFTERNOON NAP OR SOMETHING.
HEY, ANYBODY HERE?!
- Happy: WE'RE STARVING
LIKE CRAZY OUT HERE.
SOMEBODY COOK US SOME DINNER!
- Lucy: WOW, HAPPY,
EVER HEAR OF THE WORD "PLEASE"?
- Gray: YOU REALLY THINK
THE WHOLE TOWN'S TAKING A NAP?
- Makarov:
WELL, IT'S EITHER THAT
OR THEY ALL GOT DRUNK
AND PASSED OUT.
- Lucy: I THINK THAT ONLY
HAPPENS BACK AT THE GUILD.
- ( Makarov chuckles ) WE DO
LOVE OUR SPIRITS, DON'T WE?
- YOU GUYS CAN HANG OUT HERE
ALL DAY IF YOU WANT,
BUT I'M GONNA FIND
A KITCHEN TO RAID!
- SHAME ON YOU FOR EVEN THINKING
ABOUT ROBBING THIS PLACE, NATSU.
- YOU'RE JUST MAD
I THOUGHT OF IT FIRST.
( grunting )
HEY!
ANYONE HOME?
( grunts ) COME ON,
GIVE US SOMETHING TO EAT.
WE'RE DYING!
- LOOKS LIKE NOBODY'S HERE.
- WHO CARES?
THERE'S FOOD.
( sniffs )
GOOD,
IT STILL SMELLS FRESH.
OPEN WIDE.
- NOT SO FAST.
- WHAT IS IT NOW?
- THERE'S SOMETHING
STRANGE HERE.
- SHE'S RIGHT.  WHO WOULD LEAVE
A TABLE FULL OF FOOD
JUST SITTING THERE LIKE THAT?
AND IF SOMEBODY COOKED THIS,
THEN WHERE THE HECK
ARE THEY NOW?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
ANYWAY,
READY TO DIG IN, HAPPY?
- AYE.
- AHH--
- NATSU.
- YES, MA'AM?
- WE NEED TO INVESTIGATE
THE VILLAGE FIRST.
WE'VE HELD OUT THIS LONG.
WE CAN HOLD ON A LITTLE--
- ( stomach growls )
- I THINK YOUR STOMACH
MIGHT HAVE DIFFERENT PLANS.
- HMM.  YES.
BUT WHICH ONE
DO WE LISTEN TO?
- SEARCH THE AREA FOR MUSHROOMS
OR ANYTHING THAT LOOKS EDIBLE.
AND DON'T EAT THE FOOD
IN THE VILLAGE, OKAY?
WHILE YOU'RE ALL DOING THAT,
MASTER AND I
WILL TRY TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- YEAH YEAH.
I HEAR YOU.
LET'S GO, HAPPY.
- AYE.
- WAIT.  WHY MUSHROOMS?
( sighs )
- STUPID ERZA.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET
FULL ON A BUNCH OF MUSHROOMS?
THAT FOOD BACK THERE
LOOKED REALLY GOOD TOO.
- HEY, MUSHROOMS.
- I TAKE IT BACK.
THESE LOOK TASTY!
- BUT WHY MUSHROOMS?
- IT'S SO OBVIOUS, LUCY.
- OH, YEAH?
- NATSU'S GONNA EAT
A POISONOUS MUSHROOM
THEN SOMETHING WEIRD
WILL HAPPEN TO HIM.
YOU KNOW THE CLICHE,
RIGHT?
- GIVE ME SOME CREDIT,
HAPPY.
YOU REALLY THINK I'D FALL FOR
SOME LAME GAG LIKE THAT?
NO WAY.
- ( sighs )
( gulps )
- MASTER?
- I WAS JUST INVESTIGATING,
ERZA.
- THESE MUSHROOMS
AREN'T VERY BIG,
BUT IF I KEEP EATING
A TON OF THEM,
I'M BOUND TO GET FULL
SOONER OR LATER.
- AND HERE COMES THE SETUP.
- BETTER START PICKING FASTER.
- ( giggles )
- ( winces )
( choking )
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
NATSU?
- AND HERE'S THE GAG!
- THAT WAS SCARY.
- YOUR HEAD IS SCARY!
- I WAS HOPING THEY'D
TURN HIM PURPLE.
- OH, THAT'S WHAT
YOU WERE HOPING FOR?
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
ALL WORKED UP ABOUT?
- JUST TAKE A LOOK AT
ONE ANOTHER, OKAY?
- Both: WHY?
( both scream )
- ( laughs )
THERE'S A MUSHROOM ON YOUR HEAD.
- OH, YEAH?  WELL I BET YOURS
IS BIGGER THAN MINE.
- THIS COULD BE REALLY BAD.
WHO CARES HOW YOU LOOK?
GUYS...
- HEY, DROOPY EYES,
WHAT THE HECK
YOU LAUGHING ABOUT, HUH?
- ME?  WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING ABOUT, SHROOM HEAD?
- ( both grunting )
- YOU CAN FIGHT LATER.
WORRY ABOUT
THE MUSHROOMS FIRST!
- DID YOU FIND ANYBODY?
- NOPE.
NOT A SINGLE SOUL.
THE WHOLE PLACE
HAS BEEN DESERTED.
- BUT IF THAT'S THE CASE,
WHY DO ALL THE HOUSES
HAVE FRESHLY COOKED FOOD
ON THEIR TABLES?
HOLD ON.
WHAT IS THAT?
THIS ISN'T AN ORDINARY
CRACK IN THE GROUND.
IT MUST SERVE
SOME KIND OF PURPOSE.
- ( both panting )
- COME ON, GUYS.
TURN OFF THE STUPID, WOULD YOU?
- LUCY!
LOOKIE, I FOUND A BIG ONE.
- HOLY COW, THAT'S BIG!
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THAT WOULD DO TO YOU.
- OH, MAN. WOW.
IT'S HUGE.
- YEAH, IT'S SO BIG
WE COULD EAT OFF IT FOR DAYS.
- HOW ABOUT WE HOLD OFF ON
EATING ANYMORE OF
THESE THINGS TODAY?
AFTER ALL THIS, YOU STILL
SHOVE ONE OF THOSE THINGS
IN YOUR MOUTH LIKE
IT'S NO BIG DEAL?
SPIT IT OUT RIGHT NOW!
- BUT IT'S YUMMY.
( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( screams )
- WELL, I GUESS THAT
HAPPENS TO EVERYONE
WHO EATS THESE THINGS, HUH?
- I WONDER IF THE VILLAGERS
KNEW SOME WAY
AROUND THIS PROBLEM.
- WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE THEY LIKE
THE WAY IT LOOKS.
- YEAH.  MAYBE WE'LL BE IN STYLE
WHEN WE GET BACK TO TOWN.
- ( Natsu and Gray chuckle )
- IT'S NOT AS FUNNY
THIS TIME!
- WERE YOU TRYING
TO BE FUNNY?
UH, NATSU, IS IT JUST ME,
OR IS YOUR MUSHROOM GROWING?
- UHH...
- ( crying )
HOW COME HE ALWAYS
GETS THE GOOD GAGS?
- THIS LOOKS JUST LIKE
THE OTHER SEAM.
- HMM.
- ( growling, murmuring )
- WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- YOU HEAR THAT?
- WHAT IS IT?
( gasps )
- YAY!  THE MUSHROOMS
ARE GONE NOW.
- NOT QUITE. LOOKS LIKE YOURS
IS STILL GOING STRONG.
- AAH!
- ERZA!  GRAMPS!
- GET THIS THING
OFF OF MY HEAD.
IT'S NOT FUNNY WHEN
THE JOKE'S ON ME.
- ( gasps )
- ERZA.
BE CAREFUL, HAPPY.
- AYE.
- ( gasps )
- WHOA.
WHAT'S WITH THIS PLACE?
- WHY IS EVERYTHING MOVING?
- IT LOOKS LIKE THE HOUSES
ARE HAVING A DANCE PARTY, HUH?
- I THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- IT'S TIME TO RUMBLE,
GRAMPS.
- NO, WAIT!
- WHAT?  WHY?
- WE NEED TO GET
TO HIGHER GROUND.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO CHECK.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
LET'S GO.
TRY TO STAY CLOSE.
- ( roars )
- OH, MAN.
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT OUT
JUST IN TIME.
- NOW I SEE.
IT WAS A MAGIC CIRCLE.
- Makarov: THAT'S RIGHT. THOSE
LINES WE SAW IN THE VILLAGE
WERE CARVED INTO THE GROUND
TO FORM A MASSIVE MAGIC CIRCLE--
A CIRCLE USED FOR
A TYPE OF MAGIC
THAT WAS BANNED
MANY YEARS AGO.
A FORM OF SEALING MAGIC
THAT IS KNOWN AS "ALIVE."
- WHAT DOES IT DO?
- SEE FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
IT HAS THE ABILITY
TO TURN INANIMATE OBJECTS
INTO LIVING CREATURES.
IT APPEARS THE VILLAGERS
CAST THE FORBIDDEN SPELL
ONLY TO END UP BEING EATEN
BY THE VERY MONSTERS
THEY BROUGHT TO LIFE.
- BUT WHY WOULD THEY USE
MAGIC THAT'S BEEN BANNED?
- THIS VILLAGE WAS HOME
TO A DARK GUILD.
- NO WAY.
- WHILE INVESTIGATING,
I CAME ACROSS A COLLECTION
OF MAGIC TOOLS
TUCKED AWAY IN A SHED.
UPON CLOSER INSPECTION,
I REALIZED THEY WERE TOOLS
USED TO PRACTICE BLACK MAGIC.
- KNOWING HOW RECKLESS
DARK GUILDS CAN BE,
THEY PROBABLY THOUGHT UP
SOME CRAZY PLAN
AND WOUND UP GETTING
BURNED IN THE PROCESS.
BUT!
- ( all gasp )
- THERE'S ONE THING
WE SHOULD BE GRATEFUL FOR.
- OH, YEAH?
AND WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
- THE DARK GUILD'S MISCHIEF
BROUGHT THESE CREATURES TO LIFE.
AND MOST LIVING CREATURES
CAN BE TURNED INTO...
FOOD!
- ( screams )
- ( both chuckle )
- THAT SMIRK MAKES YOUR
NAKEDNESS CREEPIER, GRAY.
- HUH?
- ( stomachs growling )
- NOW TIME TO CHOW!
- YEAH!
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU, NATSU.
- AT THIS POINT,
I DON'T EVEN CARE
WHAT THEY TASTE LIKE.
- ( gasps ) EVEN ERZA'S
GONNA EAT THOSE THINGS?
- TIME TO GET
MY GRUB ON.
- WAIT!  YOU'RE CRAZY!
- SAVE SOME FOR ME,
YOU TWO.
- LISTEN UP, DINNER.
BEFORE I EAT YOU,
LET ME TELL YOU A LITTLE SECRET.
I'M AN AWESOME CHEF,
AND I LOVE TO FLAMBE.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- ( roars )
- SORRY, PAL.
BUT YOU'RE TOAST.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
NOW THAT HE'S COOKED...
( grunts )
WE'LL COVER HIM UP
AND LET HIM STEAM FOR A BIT.
- NORMALLY I'D SAVE DESSERT
FOR AFTER THE MEAL,
BUT NOT TODAY.
- ( roars )
- ICE MAKE FISHNET.
( grunts )
ANYONE WANT TO TRY
A MONSTER POPSICLE?
- ( grunting )
EVEN IF YOU'RE A CHAIR,
YOU CAN'T TASTE WORSE
THAN A WINGFISH.
( grunting )
- HIYAH!
- AAH!
( whimpers )
( screams )
- ( hisses )
- ERZA!
- NOW STAND BACK.
IT'S TIME TO START COOKING.
- UH, COOKING WITH WHAT?
- REQUIP!
( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- THE TRICK IS TO CUT THEM INTO
PERFECTLY BITE-SIZED PIECES
THAT ARE FIVE CENTIMETERS LONG
AND FOUR MILLIMETERS WIDE.
- I THINK YOU GOT
A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY.
AND WHAT'S WITH THE WEIRD
OUTFIT YOU'RE WEARING?
- Natsu:
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- Gray:
ICE MAKE KNUCKLE!
- Happy: WHOA!
- ( Erza grunts )
- I WISH THEY WOULD HURRY.
I'M STARVING HERE.
- ( grunts )
TIME TO DIG IN.
- WHOA!
- WHAT THE HECK'S
GOING ON WITH HAPPY?
I DON'T CARE HOW HUNGRY HE IS.
HE CAN'T EAT A CHAIR.
- LUCY...
GO AHEAD.
YOU TRY IT FIRST.
- NOT A CHANCE.
- FINE.  I'LL DO IT.
- THAT'S COLD, ERZA!
YOU WERE TRYING TO USE ME
AS YOUR PERSONAL GUINEA PIG,
WEREN'T YOU?
- WHOA!
- UH, DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD HELP HIM?
- I'M SURE HE'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
HERE GOES.
- SO, HOW IS IT?
UH... ALL RIGHT, YOU WIN.
- WELL, IT AIN'T PRETTY.
HOPE IT TASTES
BETTER THAN IT LOOKS.
- ( all chewing )
- UHH...
- WHOA!
- All: GROSS!
- HUH? - WHAT WERE
YOU THINKING, GRAMPS?
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN
EAT THIS NASTY STUFF.
- YOU TRYING TO KILL US,
YOU OLD GEEZER?
- TRUE.  I WOULD HARDLY
CALL THIS EDIBLE.
- IF YOU KNEW IT
WAS HARDLY EDIBLE,
WHY'D YOU FORCE ME TO EAT IT?!
- WHOA!
( groans )
( gasps )
- YOUR MUSHROOM
FINALLY FELL OFF.  LOOK.
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE STUPID MUSHROOM.
I WANT TO KNOW WHY
YOU GUYS DIDN'T HELP ME!
HOW COULD YOU BE SO MEAN?
I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS.
- WE ARE. - YOU WERE JUST
GOOFING OFF, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO NOW?
I WOULD RATHER STARVE
THAN EAT MORE OF THAT STUFF.
- GUESS THAT'S WHAT WE GET
FOR TRYING TO COOK UP
A BUNCH OF MONSTERS.
- MAN, THIS SUCKS.
ALL THAT BARBEQUING
MADE ME EVEN
HUNGRIER THAN BEFORE.
- I SEE HOW IT IS.
EVEN AFTER ALL
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
YOU'RE READY TO THROW ME OUT
LIKE YESTERDAY'S GARBAGE.
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
- LOOK OUT!
- NATSU!
- MAN, THESE THINGS ARE NASTY.
- IN MORE WAYS THAN ONE.
- I'M GONNA BLOW YOU TO PIECES.
FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
- ICE WALL!
- ( grunts )
- I WANT TO HELP.
OPEN, GATE OF THE GOLDEN BULL.
TAURUS!
- MOO!
YOU'RE LOOKING SMOOTH
AS USUAL, MISS LUCY.
- LESS PASSION, MORE BASHING.
- SHE LOVES MY MOO-VES.
( shouts )
- THEY JUST KEEP COMING.
- GREAT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
- THE MAGIC CIRCLE.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- OH, WOW.
IT'S SO PRETTY.
- YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT AGAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THAT
MIXED UP LITTLE HEAD OF YOURS?
- THIS IS BAD.
RUN FOR IT!
- ( all shout )
- ( sighs )
I'M STARVING.
LIKE FOR REAL.
- I CAN'T WALK
ANOTHER STEP, YOU GUYS.
- WELL, GOOD THING
YOU HAVE WINGS,
UNLIKE THE REST OF US,
YOU SHOW OFF.
- I STILL DON'T GET
WHAT HAPPENED.
- UM, MASTER?
- YES?
- I'M NOT SATISFIED WITH
YOUR EXPLANATION, SIR.
- THAT SO?
- NOW SPILL IT.
WHAT WERE YOU TRYING TO PULL?
- WE WERE USING
THE MAGIC CIRCLE
TO CAST FORBIDDEN SPELLS.
BUT THOSE MONSTERS APPEARED
AND TOOK OVER EVERYONE IN TOWN.
- SO THE MONSTERS WE FOUGHT,
YOU WERE ALL TRAPPED
INSIDE OF THEM?
- OH, YOU MADE ME
TASTE ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
- WHEN YOU STEPPED
INTO THE CIRCLE,
IT ACTIVATED THE SPELL
AND WE NO LONGER HAD
ANY CONTROL OF OURSELVES.
- WELL, YOU WON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT
THAT HAPPENING AGAIN.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT,
GRAMPS?
- THERE'S NO NEED TO SWEAT
THE DETAILS, MY BOY.
NOW AS FOR ALL
YOU VILLAGERS,
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
THAT SOMEONE CAME ALONG
TO FREE YOU
FROM YOUR POSSESSION.
I ASSUME YOU'VE LEARNED
YOUR LESSON FROM THIS
GROSS MISUSE OF MAGIC.
AND AS LONG AS
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN AGAIN,
I WON'T REPORT YOU
TO THE COUNCIL.
IS THAT A DEAL?
- YES, OF COURSE.
WE NEVER WANT TO
GO THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- YOU HAVE OUR WORD.
- ( chuckles )
- WHEN WE FINALLY
DEFEATED THE MONSTERS,
IT SEEMED TO ACTIVATE SOME
KIND OF SELF-DESTRUCTION SPELL
WITHIN THE MAGIC CIRCLE.
THAT'S WHEN YOU CAME IN.
RUN FOR IT!
- ( all scream )
- IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
YOU SAVED US,
FREED THE DARK GUILD
FROM THE TAKEOVER SPELL
AND DESTROYED
THE MAGIC CIRCLE
BEFORE IT FLATTENED THE VILLAGE
AND EVERYONE IN IT.
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
- I'LL TELL YOU SOME DAY.
( sighs )
BUT WHAT MATTERS NOW IS...
- All: WE'RE STILL HUNGRY!
- ( stomachs growling )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NO WAY!
NATSU AND ERZA
ARE GONNA FIGHT?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
- 'FRAID NOT.
EVIDENTLY, NATSU'S FINALLY
READY TO GET REVENGE.
- BUT SHOULDN'T WE STOP THEM?
- NO.  GUILD MEMBERS
CHALLENGE EACH OTHER
TO FIGHTS ALL THE TIME.
SO WHO DO YOU
THINK WILL WIN?
- WELL, I'M THINKING
IT'LL BE ERZA,
BUT I HATE TO UNDERESTIMATE
NATSU'S POWER, YOU KNOW?
- ( Mirajane and Lucy speaking )
- Mirajane: HEY, WHY DON'T
YOU CHALLENGE ERZA
FOR THE TITLE OF "STRONGEST
FEMALE WIZARD IN FAIRY TAIL"?
- Lucy: YEAH, RIGHT!  MAYBE I
COULD BEAT HAPPY, THOUGH.