- Pantherlily: PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- Mest: I MUST KNOW!
TELL ME OF THE MAGIC
OF PLOT SYNOPSES.
- Pantherlily: SUSPICIOUS.
- Carla: LILY AND I
HAD A SINKING
FEELING ABOUT MEST.
SO WE HEADED TO
TENROU ISLAND.
WE HOPED TO
CATCH HIM OFF GUARD
SINCE THE S-CLASS TRIAL
WAS ALREADY UNDERWAY.
- Pantherlily:
VERY SUSPICIOUS.
- Carla: NOW THAT WE'RE HERE,
IT SEEMS
AN EVEN BIGGER CRISIS
LOOMS OVER THE ISLAND.
- Mest: PLEASE TELL ME!
WHAT IS IT LIKE
TO BE IN CRISIS?!
- Pantherlily: SERIOUSLY!
YOU'RE WAY TOO SUSPICIOUS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Erza: UNBELIEVABLE.
I NEVER IMAGINED THAT ZEREF
WOULD STILL BE ALIVE.
- AS MUCH AS THAT
TERRIFIES ME,
I'M MORE CONCERNED
THAT GRIMOIRE HEART'S
FIGHTING FORCE
IS ON THEIR WAY.
- I BELIEVE THEY'RE CALLED
THE SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY,
RIGHT?
- YES.
AND APPARENTLY ONE OF THEM
IS ALREADY LURKING
AROUND THE ISLAND.
- COME ON, JUVIA,
LET'S HURRY.
WE NEED TO FIND
WENDY AND MEST
AND REGROUP AT THE CAMP
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- STOP IT.  WHAT'S
GOTTEN INTO THE TWO OF YOU?
- STAY BACK AND
KEEP QUIET, CHILD!
- TELL ME WHO YOU
REALLY ARE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IT'S MY BELIEF
THE MAGIC YOU WIELD
ALLOWS YOU TO MANIPULATE
PEOPLE'S MEMORIES.
IF I'M CORRECT,
YOU'VE BEEN USING
THAT MAGIC TO MASQUERADE
AS A MEMBER OF FAIRY TAIL
SINCE BEFORE THE TRIAL.
TOO MANY THINGS
DON'T ADD UP
INCLUDING YOUR STORY
ABOUT BEING MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL.
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
NO ONE HAS ANY
REAL CONNECTION WITH YOU.
AND JUST NOW
YOU HAD NO IDEA
WHAT THE GUILD'S
EMERGENCY FLARE SIGNIFIED.
THERE'S NO TALKING
YOUR WAY OUT OF THAT.
( gasps )
- HE DISAPPEARED!
- NO! TELEPORTATION MAGIC?
WENDY!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
( screams )
- WENDY, NO!
- ( Happy speaking )
- Mest: GET DOWN NOW!
- ( screams )
- AN ATTACK?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- HE PROTECTED HER?
BUT WHY?
- WHO ARE YOU?!
SHOW YOURSELF!
- IMPRESSIVE.
YOUR SENSES ARE QUITE SHARP.
- THE TREE ATTACKED US?
- OUT! COME AND FACE US!
- I'M FROM GRIMOIRE HEART.
NAME'S AZUMA.
I'M ONE OF
THE SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY.
- GRIMOIRE HEART?
- A DARK GUILD.
- SO THAT'S WHAT
THE FLARE WAS.
SOMEONE MUST HAVE RUN INTO
MORE OF THESE FREAKS.
- ( chuckles ) A BIT LATE TO BE
WORRYING ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS.
- HOW DARE YOU!
WHAT EXACTLY
IS GOING ON HERE?!
- I THOUGHT IF I WAS GOING
TO FIND ANY DIRT
ON THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD,
THE MOST LOGICAL PLACE
TO START WOULD BE HERE,
ITS SACRED BURIAL GROUND.
- ( growls )
- BUT TO FIND ZEREF
AND GRIMOIRE HEART AS WELL,
TALK ABOUT
HITTING THE JACKPOT.
MUST BE MY LUCKY DAY.
- ZEREF?
- JUST WHO ARE YOU?
- COME ON,
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I WORK FOR
THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
I INFILTRATED YOUR RANKS
TO GATHER INTEL
THAT'LL BRING YOU DOWN
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- YOU'RE A SPY?!
- BUT, MEST...
- VERY INTERESTING.
- BUT I'VE CAUGHT
A MUCH BIGGER FISH NOW.
TO THINK THE EVER ILLUSIVE
GRIMOIRE HEART
WOULD JUST FALL INTO MY LAP
OUT OF NOWHERE.
( chuckles )
IF I TAKE THEM OUT,
MY CAREER IS AS GOOD AS MADE.
I EVEN HAVE THE COUNCIL'S
CUSTODY ENFORCEMENT UNIT'S
BATTLESHIPS ON STANDBY.
ONCE THE DARK GUILD
MAKES LANDFALL,
IT'LL BE GAME OVER
FOR THEM.
THIS IS A CRACKDOWN!
TODAY, THE DEVIL'S HEART
STOPS BEATING FOR GOOD.
- THOSE BATTLESHIPS,
THEY LOOK SO FRAGILE
FROM HERE.
- NO.  ALL OF THOSE PEOPLE...
- THE SHIPS!
- BUT HOW?
- IF YOU'RE DONE TALKING,
I'D LIKE TO GET TO WORK
DESTROYING EVERYONE HERE,
RIGHT NOW.
- EVERYONE STAND BACK.
- Makarov: A RED FLARE,
THE SIGNAL OF AN ENEMY RAID.
I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD HAPPEN HERE
AND ON MY WATCH NO LESS.
MAVIS,
DID YOU EVER
FIND YOURSELF
IN THIS SITUATION?
BECAUSE I WONDER
HOW YOU WOULD HAVE HANDLED IT.
I'LL BET YOU'RE
SO ANGRY WITH ME
YOU'RE SPINNING
IN YOUR GRAVE RIGHT NOW.
I'VE ALLOWED THE ENEMY TO TREAD
UPON OUR GUILD'S SACRED GROUND.
I ASSUME FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
AND I WILL PAY THE PRICE
REST ASSURED OF THAT.
HOWEVER...
I ASK THIS OF YOU.
KEEP THEM SAFE.
- IS IT JUST ME
OR DID THAT SOUND
LIKE SOME TROUBLE WENT DOWN
OVER THERE?
- YEAH.  DO YOU THINK
THE ENEMY'S ALREADY HERE?
- ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
- AYE.
- NO, HOW COULD
YOU DO THAT?
- THOSE SHIPS WERE FULL
OF INNOCENT PEOPLE!
- HOW COULD ONE MAN
HAVE SUCH POWER?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( growls )
- LILY!
- BLEVE.
- OOH.
( screams )
- ( both screaming )
- IF ONLY I HAD A SWORD.
- DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE NOT IN THIS ALONE.
OH, SWIFT WINDS
THAT SPEED THROUGH
THE HEAVENS...
- WHOA.
- VERNIER!
- MY BODY SUDDENLY
FEELS LIGHTER.
- I CALL UPON THEE,
THE STALWART MIGHT
TO CLEAVE THE HEAVENS!
- AMAZING.
SO THIS IS THE POWER
SUPPORT MAGIC HOLDS.
- ARMS!
- IN THIS STATE...
DODGING THESE
EXPLOSION SPELLS
IS CHILD'S PLAY.
- LISTEN UP, MEST.
I THINK I KNOW HOW
TO TAKE THIS GUY DOWN,
BUT I'LL NEED
YOUR HELP TO DO IT.
- NO, WEREN'T YOU
LISTENING BEFORE?
- I'M NOT YOUR ALLY.
I'M WITH THE COUNCIL.
- DO YOU THINK WHO YOU
WORK FOR MATTERS TO ME?
ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS PROTECTING FAIRY TAIL.
PLEASE HELP ME DO THAT.
- I ONLY CAME TO THIS ISLAND
SO I COULD DESTROY FAIRY TAIL
AND FURTHER MY CAREER.
- AND YOU'LL FAIL.
THERE'S NO ONE IN EXISTENCE
WHO COULD TAKE US DOWN.
- ( gasps )
- LILY, GO UP!
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHERE YOU RUN.
MY EXPLOSIONS
ALWAYS HIT THEIR MARK.
- DIRECT LINE.
- I'VE GOT
ONE SHOT AT THIS.
- ELIMINATING THIS GUY
TAKES PRIORITY FOR NOW.
- GOTCHA.
- SKY DRAGON ROAR.
- YOU PATHETIC FOOLS.
- ( gasping )
- GO, TOWER BURST!
- ( screams )
- ( screaming )
- ( Natsu pants )
WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S A TOWER OF FIRE.
THERE'S NO ONE IN FAIRY TAIL
WHO USES MAGIC LIKE THAT.
- GUESS WE KNOW
WHERE THE ENEMY IS THEN.
- ( ragged breathing )
- TIME'S UP.
- I NEVER IMAGINED...
THE SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY
WOULD POSSESS SUCH POWER.
- THIS GUILD,
ARE CATS AND CHILDREN
ITS ONLY DEFENSE?
- THERE ARE SIX MORE
OF THESE GUYS?
WE'RE ALL DOOMED.
FAIRY TAIL DOESN'T
STAND A CHANCE.
- ( Lucy pants )
COME ON, WHERE THE HECK IS
THIS STUPID MEETING PLACE?
- Gray: IT'S BACK
AT THE BASE CAMP.
DIDN'T ANYBODY TELL YOU?
- Loke: WE'LL GET THERE QUICKER
IF WE PASS THROUGH
THESE RUINS.
JUST KEEP RUNNING.
- ( Lucy pants )
HOW DID A SEARCH
FOR A GRAVE
TURN INTO AN ORDEAL
LIKE THIS?
- I DON'T GET IT.
CAN YOU THINK OF ANY REASON
THEY'D ATTACK NOW?
- NO.
- DON'T GIVE UP ON ME, OKAY?
WE HAVE TO FIND THE OTHERS
BEFORE THE ISLAND'S OVERRUN.
WE'RE AT
A MAJOR DISADVANTAGE.
THEY ATTACKED
WHILE WE'RE SPLIT UP.
I DON'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN.
- NICE OUTFIT.
GETS ME FIRED UP
AND READY TO CUT LOOSE.
- ZANCROW,
YOU SHOULD BE TAKING
THIS BATTLE SERIOUSLY.
- TONIGHT
THE SOULS OF OUR FOES
DINE IN THE CITY OF WOE.
- POETRY AND STUFF.
I'M ALSO READY TO FIGHT
AND, UH--
FILLED WITH...
- UR, LOOK.
- NEVER REFER TO ME
BY THAT NAME.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- AWW, COME ON, DON'T BE
SO NERVOUS ALL THE TIME.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT'S UP?
- IT'S IN VIEW NOW.
THE FAIRY ISLAND.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT IN THE HELL
IS THAT?
- ( groaning )
- Ultear: A GIANT.
- OH, WOW.
- THAT SUCKS.
- WHO IS THAT?
- MAKAROV.
- BE GONE.
- Narrator: LET'S GO BACK
TO THE YEAR 736,
48 YEARS BEFORE
THE PRESENT DAY.
- WAIT.
EITHER I'M GOING SENILE
OR YOU JUST SAID
I'M FAIRY TAIL'S NEXT MASTER.
- THAT'S CORRECT.
- FIND SOMEONE ELSE.
I CAN'T.
- YOU CAN
AND YOU WILL, BOY.
- WHO YOU CALLING BOY?
I'M 40 YEARS OLD, YOU KNOW?
- I REALIZE YOU HAVE
DOUBTS AT THE MOMENT.
BUT YOU HAVE THE ABILITY
TO LOVE AND TRUST
YOUR FELLOW MAN.
I'M CERTAIN YOU WILL LEAD
FAIRY TAIL TO GREATNESS.
( echoes )
JUST AS MAVIS,
OUR FIRST MASTER,
PASSED THIS HEAVY MANTLE
ONTO MY SHOULDERS,
I NOW PASS FAIRY TAIL'S
SPIRIT ONTO YOU.
PLEASE HANDLE IT
WITH CARE.
- TURN BACK
OR SUFFER THE WRATH
OF FAIRY TAIL.
- ( chuckles )
- ( growls )
- ( screaming )
- WHOOPSIE!
- HEAVY DAMAGE SUSTAINED.
- HE PUNCHED THROUGH LAYERS
OF REINFORCED ARMOR!
- GAME OVER, MAN.
- ( growls )
- Hades: EVASIVE MANEUVERS.
- ( grunting )
- PREPARE THE FOCUSED
MAGIC CANNON JUPITER.
- ( growls )
- ( laughs )
- ( screaming )
- THE SHIP!
HE'S TEARING US APART!
- CAN'T WE DO ANYTHING?
- NOW ULTEAR!
- SIR!
ARC OF TIME, RESTORE!
- CAPRICO, GET ALL OF OUR FORCES
ONTO THE ISLAND.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, SIR?
- I'LL REMAIN HERE
AND DEAL WITH MAKAROV MYSELF.
- AS YOU WISH.
- RUN IF YOU LIKE,
BUT THERE IS NO ESCAPE!
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
UNTIL THE COUNT OF THREE
TO GET OUT OF MY SIGHT.
OTHERWISE,
YOU AND YOUR COMRADES
WILL SEE THE OTHER SIDE
OF OBLIVION.
- THE ULTIMATE MAGIC SPELL
THAT VANQUISHES EVERYONE
WHOM THE CASTER DEEMS
TO BE A FOE.
- ONE.
- LET'S SEE YOUR
FAIRY LAW IN ACTION.
- TWO.
- Natsu: WHAT THE HECK
HAPPENED HERE?
WENDY, PLEASE SAY SOMETHING.
COME ON.
WENDY!
- LILY! CARLA!
I THINK THEY TOOK THE FULL FORCE
OF THAT SPELL WE SAW.
OH, PLEASE BE OKAY.
- DAMN IT!
SOMEONE'S GONNA
PAY FOR THIS.
WAS IT YOU?!
HEY, ANSWER ME.
( growls )
- THE MEMORY MANIPULATION
SPELL'S WORN OFF.
- Narrator:
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
A USER OF MEMORY
MANIPULATION MAGIC
HAS THE ABILITY TO ADD
HIS OR HER PRESENCE
INTO THE MEMORY OF OTHERS.
HOWEVER, JUST LIKE
WITH CHARM MAGIC,
MEMORY MANIPULATION
IS BROKEN
THE MOMENT THOSE AFFECTED
BECOME AWARE
IT'S BEEN USED ON THEM.
- DON'T.  MEST IS A MEMBER
OF THE MAGIC COUNCIL, NATSU.
- ( screeches )
WOW, NICE COAT.
LET ME FIX IT FOR YOU.
( gasps )
THE MAGIC COUNCIL
IS OUR ENEMY NOW?!
- ( whimpers )
- YOU'RE WRONG.
THE ENEMY IS GRIMOIRE HEART,
A DARK GUILD.
- FROM THE BARAM ALLIANCE?!
- YOU MEAN THEY'RE
ON THE ISLAND?!
HOW'RE WE SUPPOSED
TO FEND OFF
THEIR ENTIRE GUILD
ON OUR OWN?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?!
- Natsu: WHY ARE
YOU ASKING ME?!
- WHAT'S THAT UP THERE?
- ( Lucy screams )
- IT'S RAINING MASKED MEN.
- I'D SAY HALLELUJAH,
BUT THEY DON'T LOOK FRIENDLY.
- CRAP.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
THERE'S TONS OF THEM.
ALL THOSE ORBS
ARE ENEMY SOLDIERS.
- ( soldiers shouting )
- ( soldiers chattering )
- ( boots clinking )
- UH-OH.
WE'RE TOO LATE.
- ( indistinct shouting )
- I'LL TAKE ALL OF YOU ON!
WHO'S GONNA ARM WRESTLE
ME FIRST?
- DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S MORE ANNOYING.
YOU OR THE GOON SQUAD.
- HOW DID THEY OVERRUN US
SO QUICKLY?
- I'M NOT SURE AND I'M AFRAID
MORE ARE COMING.
- ( growls )
- WELL, WELL.
THE ROWDY ONES WILL FINALLY
BE JOINING ME IN BATTLE.
- ( cackles )
YAHOO!
- THE UNDERWORLD
WILL RUN RED
WITH OUR SACRIFICES TONIGHT.
- OPERATION IS UNDERWAY.
- ( groaning )
- AT LAST, I AM NEAR HIM.
LORD ZEREF.
- SO MUCH CONFLICT.
WILL IT EVER END?
- AND THAT'S THREE.
TIME'S UP.
FAIRY LAW.
- DON'T BE SO HASTY.
- OH.
- GRIMOIRE LAW.
- ( gasps )
- THESE SPELLS SERVE
THEIR INTENDED PURPOSE.
LESSER MEN WOULD
BE DETERRED BY THEM.
BUT UNLESS ONE OF US
BACKS DOWN FROM THIS DUEL,
THE DESTRUCTION THAT FOLLOWS
WILL LEAVE
A SCAR ON THIS WORLD
OF CATACLYSMIC PROPORTIONS.
- UH! IMPOSSIBLE!
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
- I'M GOING ON A JOURNEY, BOY.
I KNOW YOU'LL MAKE
THIS GUILD A GREAT ONE.
- MASTER, WAIT.
DON'T GO.
- MASTER?
I'M NO LONGER
THE GUILD'S MASTER.
( echoes )
IT'S YOU.
HELLO, BOY.
YOU'RE LOOKING WELL.
- IT IS YOU.
MASTER PRECHT!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: NATSU, HAVE YOU HEARD
OF LOST MAGIC BEFORE?
- ROAST MAGIC? WHAT? YOU MEAN
LIKE A CHICKEN OR SOMETHING?
- NOT ROAST, LOST.
IT'S ANCIENT MAGIC
THAT'S BEEN LOST AND
COMPLETELY FORGOTTEN
BY WIZARDS LIKE US,
YOU DOOFUS.
SERIOUSLY, HOW'D YOU GET
CHICKEN FROM THAT?
- WELL, HOW CAN YOU
JUST LOSE MAGIC?
THAT'S PRETTY IRRESPONSIBLE.
- ( frustrated groan )
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO LOST IT.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
UGH, MAN, NOW I'M BEAT.
- WHY ARE YOU TIRED?
ALL YOU'VE DONE
IS SIT HERE AND TALK WITH ME.
- EXACTLY.
THAT'S ENOUGH TO
MAKE ANYONE EXHAUSTED.