[NARRATOR]
The Eclipse Gate was opened,
and through it
stormed seven dragons,
each hell-bent on
mayhem and destruction.
The seven Dragon Slayers
are leading a desperate fight
against these giant beasts,
hoping to save humanity
from total annihilation.
[ATLAS FLAME roaring]
I will usher in a new age.
The era of dragons!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[HAPPY] People and People,
Dragons and Dragons,
People and Dragons!
[ATLAS FLAME growling]
[LAXUS grunts]
I never imagined that
you dragons were
such foolhardy creatures.
Engaging the Thunder
Legion in battle is
a painful experience for
all who dare to do so.
[FRIED]
Dark Écriture Absolute Shadow!
Fairy Machine Gun Leprechaun!
[BIXLOW] Let's rock,
babies! Baryon Formation!
[TOMMENS]
Let's rock!
Lightning Dragon Roar!
I think a billion
volts to the face
oughtta shut you up for a while.
[ATLAS FLAME cackling]
[LAXUS gasps]
[ATLAS FLAME]
That didn't hurt one bit.
My hellfire burns magic away!
Damn, that hit didn't
even touch him.
It appears lightning
is useless against fire.
You're just not a
good match for this one.
Is there such thing as
a water Dragon Slayer?
If there is, I've
never heard of it.
Looks like there's a fire
one floating overhead.
[HAPPY]
We're almost right above him!
Drop me on him like a bomb!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
Ha!
Natsu?
[NATSU yelling]
A real fire dragon!
This one's all mine!
[ATLAS FLAME]
Who are you, pest?
I'm Natsu Dragneel!
And I'm the guy
who's gonna eat ya!
What?
[ALL]
That's crazy!
I suppose that's
the kind of strategy
you should expect
from a guy who's always
thinking with his tummy.
[ATLAS FLAME]
You, eat me?
You can't be serious!
[NATSU] Oh I'm dead serious,
and your fire tastes delicious!
[ATLAS FLAME roaring]
Get off me!
[NATSU]
No way!
Natsu! What in the hell
do you think you're doing?
[NATSU]
What does it look like?
Gettin' this tasty old
dragon into my belly!
[LAXUS]
Okay...
You and your guys should get
over to the castle right now!
[NATSU]
Wendy needs some backup!
[LAXUS grunts]
Even though she is
a Dragon Slayer,
she's rather young
and inexperienced.
Yeah, and if she's
all on her own,
it could be pretty
tough for her.
I agree that we
should go help.
Besides, who better
to fight a fire dragon
than a fire Dragon Slayer?
Don't you think?
Hey! You sure you
can handle this one?
[NATSU] Yeah!
And after I eat him,
I should have tons of power!
Well, let's get going.
[EVERGREEN, BIXLOW, and FRIED]
Roger!
[NATSU munching]
[NATSU]
You should go too, Happy!
Aye!
[ATLAS FLAME] This will be
your final meal, you brat!
[NATSU munching]
[ATLAS FLAME]
You'll taste my fury!
[ATLAS FLAME growling]
[NATSU munching]
[ATLAS FLAME roaring]
[ATLAS FLAME] How dare you
lay your hands on me!
[ATLAS FLAME roaring]
[NATSU munching]
[ATLAS FLAME gasps]
[ATLAS FLAME]
It's so strange.
Is it even possible?
No, that's ridiculous.
But why does this
human remind me
so much of him?
[ATLAS FLAME]
The Fire Dragon King, Igneel!
Boy!
[NATSU]
Huh?
[ATLAS FLAME] You have
some connection to Igneel,
do you not?
Hold on just a second.
Are you seriously trying
to tell me you know Igneel?
[ATLAS FLAME]
He's King of the fire Dragons,
and my friend.
No way! I know him
pretty well too.
He's actually my dad!
[ATLAS FLAME grunts]
[VIRGO] What are you
looking at, Princess?
[LUCY] It's the diary that
belonged to my future self.
[VIRGO] But I thought
reading someone else's diary
is considered poor taste.
[LUCY]
Well, technically it is mine.
Seriously?
So then. You're free to
read my punishment diary
if you're interested.
I guess I'll take your
silence as a "no."
[FUTURE ROGUE]
The raw, destructive force
of the dragons is
amazing to behold.
Their power will make
my dreams a reality.
Acnologia doesn't have
a prayer against us.
We will kill him for sure.
Once he's taken his last breath,
the world will be mine
to rule as I see fit.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
May the land be ripped apart,
may the skies burn,
and may the light of life
be snuffed out.
[FUTURE ROGUE] I am the
true king of the dragons.
I will claim my crown at
the Dragon King Festival!
The shadows will become
a cleansing light!
The world will be reborn
with its divine illumination!
[NATSU] We got no use
for your crappy light!
[FUTURE ROGUE sighs]
Again?
[NATSU]
Because we got our own!
Shinin' right out of our hearts!
And I guarantee it's a
million times brighter
than whatever you've got!
[ATLAS FLAME growling]
How can he be riding
a dragon like that?
Atlas Flame, why have
you betrayed me?
[ATLAS FLAME]
I merely listened to my heart.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
What?
[ATLAS FLAME]
This boy is the son of Igneel.
My dear friend.
I appreciate the help.
Thanks, Uncle!
[ATLAS FLAME]
U-Uncle?
[FUTURE ROGUE] Atlas Flame,
why have you betrayed me?
[ATLAS FLAME]
I merely listened to my heart.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
What?
[ATLAS FLAME]
This boy is the son of Igneel.
My dear friend.
But this dragon should
be under my control!
What have you done, Natsu?
[ATLAS FLAME] Your magic
that clouded my mind is gone.
[NATSU] It's simple, I just
became friends with him.
Right?
[ATLAS FLAME]
Mm-hm.
You and that dragon...
are friends?
Come on, Uncle!
Let's get him!
[ATLAS FLAME roaring]
Awesome. Get behind
'em like that!
Don't turn your back to them!
Move, Mother Glare!
[MOTHER GLARE roaring]
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU gasps]
[FUTURE ROGUE grunts]
[NATSU] Hey are you
feelin' okay after that?
[ATLAS FLAME]
My body is pure flame.
Breath attacks can't hurt me!
[FUTURE ROGUE grunts]
[MOTHER GLARE]
And no flame could ever
burn my adamantine body.
[ATLAS FLAME] You've never
felt my Hellfire, have you?
[ATLAS FLAME] It burns
as intensely as flames
from the pits of hell.
[ATLAS FLAME] And this young
man whom I call my friend
has consumed it.
He has it raging
inside his belly.
[NATSU yelling]
[FUTURE ROGUE]
He ate the fire of Atlas Flame?
How?
[NATSU yelling]
[MOTHER GLARE roaring]
[MALE SOLDIER 195A]
Your Majesty! Do you see that?
[MALE SOLDIER 195B] It looks
like a couple of the dragons
are starting
to fight each other!
[MALE SOLDIER 195C]
Yes. Those two are definitely
going at it up there.
My beautiful city
of flowers has been
stained red with blood.
Trampled over by total chaos.
[TOMA] A frenzy of people,
dragons, and magic.
People fighting people.
Dragon fighting dragon.
People struggling
against dragons.
It's just as the
legends spoke of.
This is the
Dragon King Festival.
[MALE SOLDIER 195A]
Your highness!
[MALE SOLDIER 195B]
Something wrong, your majesty?
[MALE SOLDIER 195D]
Do you need assistance?
No. This is a catastrophe.
It's too late.
The world as we once knew it
has been irrevocably changed.
[RUFUS]
I know what to do. Memory Make.
Sword of Frozen Black Lightning!
Shrine of the Stormy Wind Fang!
[RUFUS panting]
Is there no end to
these foul creatures?
Their sheer number.
Their raw power.
Like nothing in my memory.
Here comes my Ice Bringer!
[GRAY grunts]
Magnificent.
[GRAY] Why are you
just standing there?
I used that exact same
technique to beat you,
don't you remember it?
[RUFUS] Then I suppose
you wouldn't mind me
incorporating it
into my repertoire.
[RUFUS]
Hm.
[GRAY]
We can take on
these things, pal!
[DROY] Yeah! We may
not have Levy,
but we still gotta
represent Team Shadow Gear!
Now! Falcon Soar!
Have a taste of
my Knuckle Plant!
See? We still
got it, right bud?
Ha! We never lost it, man!
Purple Flare!
Take this!
[WAKABA]
Father and son teamwork!
But I've got more than
a couple of tricks
of my own up my sleeve.
Fooled ya! That was just
my smoke you're chasin'.
Thanks for the
setup, ol' buddy!
That was awesome, Dad!
You're actually pretty
quick on your feet
for an old geezer!
Like you're one to talk.
[OLGA] Lightning God
Charged Particle Cannon!
Right. So how many of these
critters do I have left?
[OLGA gasps]
How'd I not notice
them all around me?
[OLGA grunts]
Arise. Iron Rock Wall!
It's Jura!
[JURA]
Hm! Rock Tor!
I never thought I'd say this,
but man, I'm glad to see you.
And even though
you beat me earlier,
it rocks having you on my team!
Power up White Drive!
Now feel my
White Dragon Roar!
[STING]
Ya like that? Take this!
[STING yelling]
Let's see how scary you are
when you can't even move!
[SCISSOR RUNNER]
You stupid human.
That's just pitiful.
I don't feel a thing.
Is that really
the best you can do?
[STING grunts]
[ROGUE]
Shadow Dragon Roar!
[LEVIA cackles]
[ROGUE panting]
[LEVIA] Rogue. You're much
too weak to defeat a dragon.
Why exhaust yourself
any further?
[ROGUE]
How do you know my name?
[LEVIA] I was specifically
instructed to spare your life.
[SHADOW ROGUE]
It's true, you know.
[ROGUE]
What are you?
I am you. At least, I am
another version of your future.
I am the darkness
that always follows you.
Born form the darkness
inside your heart.
[ROGUE]
Shut up!
[SHADOW ROGUE cackling]
Shut up! You're
lying! You're lying!
[LEVIA cackling]
[LEVIA]
You should stop fighting
if you know what's
good for you.
For you are the only human that
will survive this onslaught.
And in due time become
ruler of the world.
What are you talking about?
I have no desire
to rule the world!
Who told you to spare me?
[LEVIA]
Who? Why you did, Rogue.
[ROGUE gasps]
[LEVIA] You were the
one who summoned us.
We will destroy the
world at your request,
so you can rule
over the wreckage.
In seven years you
will hatch this plan,
and travel back to this time.
[ROGUE] Heh. I don't
believe all of this nonsense.
[SHADOW ROGUE]
But it's the truth.
[ROGUE gasps]
[ROGUE panting]
[LEVIA]
Look inside your heart.
You cannot deny it has
been stained by darkness.
[ROGUE]
What?
[LEVIA] Or rather, your heart
will be stained by darkness.
You have no choice
in the matter.
You must accept your fate.
It is your destiny
to live on and rule.
[ROGUE groaning]
It's not true. It can't
be true! You're lying!
There you are.
[NARRATOR] Let us travel
back in time to one hour ago.
[MELDY]
Natsu, are you okay?
You shouldn't try
to move just yet!
[NATSU]
She's gone isn't she?
[ULTEAR gasps]
[NATSU]
Lucy...
[NATSU panting]
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU sobbing]
[NATSU]
No!
[ULTEAR]
Tell me who did this.
[NATSU] Rogue. He came from
seven years in the future.
So there was another
time traveler after all.
What does he want?
[NATSU]
I don't know.
He's our enemy?
[NATSU] He is mine.
Because he murdered Lucy.
Rogue is strong now,
but it seems like
he's gonna get
way more powerful
in the next few years.
Yes. But coming from the
future betrays a weakness.
[MELDY gasps]
If we were to kill the Rogue
that lives in our time,
then his future self
would cease to exist.
Are you sure?
Because it seems like
a major paradox to me.
There is already a
Rogue from the future.
So doesn't that mean the
one from now can't die?
I just don't think it'll work.
You would be right.
But time is not flowing
as it should right now.
It is in a state of flux.
There have been far
too many disturbances
in its natural flow,
people crossing from
one time to another.
We can use this
to our advantage.
[MELDY]
How?
Exactly as I
had said earlier.
We eliminate the
present day Rogue,
and the one from the future
will vanish completely.
And if that version of
him is out of the picture.
He can't come back
and wreak havoc.
Lucy won't die like this!
[NATSU]
No.
I'm gonna defeat that
future Rogue myself.
[ULTEAR] You're too emotional
to think clearly right now.
You don't understand!
[ULTEAR, MEDLY gasp]
[NATSU] The one from the
future is not the same
as the one from our time.
Something happened
and he lost his way.
We would be killing a
completely innocent person.
It's wrong. So, no.
Think of our futures.
Just who would we
be if we did this?
Good point. You're
absolutely right.
We cannot harm the
present day Rogue.
I won't touch him.
[ROGUE] I'd never do that.
It's all a lie. It has to be.
[ULTEAR]
I'm sorry. I made a promise.
But there's no other way.
[ULTEAR]
Rogue may be innocent now,
but he will fall from grace.
He will become the agent
of our destruction.
We just can't risk
letting this happen.
If he can't come
from the future,
he can't open the gate,
and the dragons
will never attack.
The only way to save the
world from this nightmare,
is to end his life
before it's too late.
[NATSU] Man, that has
got to be the tastiest fire
I've ever had!
[HAPPY] Really? So does dragon
fire taste all that different
than regular fire?
[NATSU]
Oh yeah, totally!
It's got a completely
different flavor profile.
There's a kind of richness
that normal fire
just can't compete with.
[HAPPY] Uh. This is gonna
take a while isn't it?
[NATSU] Ah, it's like
it's aged for super long,
it gives it such a
deep, smoky quality.
[HAPPY]
Well, he's sure fired up now.
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next Time: Sin and Sacrifice!
[NATSU] But what really makes
my uncle's fire so special is--
[HAPPY] Yeah. It's all right.
Save it for another time.