- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE,
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WILL NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: THIS IS THE
PORT TOWN OF HARGEON.
- ( muttering )
- EXCUSE ME, SIR?
- NATSU, WE MADE IT TO HARGEON.
COME ON, GET UP ALREADY.
- IS HE ALL RIGHT?
- HE'S FINE.
THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS
WHEN HE TRAVELS.
- NEVER-- I'M NEVER RIDING
A STUPID TRAIN AGAIN.
- IF OUR INFORMATION'S CORRECT,
THAN WE SHOULD FIND
THAT SALAMANDER SOMEWHERE
IN THIS TOWN.
LET'S GO. - JUST GIVE ME
A SECOND, WOULD YOU?
- ( train whistles )
- NO!
NO!
- ( train whistles )
- UH-OH, THERE HE GOES.
- ( guitar plays )
- Happy: "THE FAIRY TAIL."
- ( crowd mutters )
- LUCY: WHAT?!
YOU MEAN TO TELL ME THERE'S
ONLY ONE MAGIC SHOP
IN THIS WHOLE TOWN?
- 'FRAID SO. THE PEOPLE AROUND
HERE ARE MORE FISHING FOLK
THAN THEY ARE MAGIC FOLK.
I RECKON
MOST PEOPLE IN TOWN
DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO USE MAGIC.
I BUILT THIS SHOP
TO SELL TO THE WIZARDS
WHO HAPPEN TO BE
PASSING THROUGH.
- OH, MAN. I CAME OUT ALL
THIS WAY FOR NOTHING.
- NOW, NOW, DON'T SAY THAT,
LITTLE LADY.
I HAVE ALL THE LATEST GOODS.
LET ME SHOW YOU A FEW.
THIS COLORS MAGIC
IS POPULAR.
ALL THE YOUNG GIRLS
REALLY SEEM TO LIKE IT.
IT LETS YOU CHANGE THE COLOR OF
YOUR CLOTHES ANYTIME YOU WANT.
PURPLE.
- I ALREADY HAVE ONE OF THOSE.
WHAT I REALLY WANT ARE SOME
POWERFUL GATEKEYS. - NOW GREEN.
- ( gasps ) - GATEKEYS, HUH?
THAT'S A RARE REQUEST.
- OW, WOW, IT'S THE
LITTLE DOGGIE! - ( barking )
- YES, BUT THAT ONE'S
NOT VERY POWERFUL, YOU KNOW.
- I KNOW, BUT I REALLY,
REALLY WANT IT.
SO HOW MUCH?
- 20,000 JEWEL.
- I'M SORRY, BUT HOW MUCH
WAS THAT AGAIN?
- I SAID 20,000 JEWEL.
- ( coin drops )
- AW, COME ON.
HOW MUCH IS IT REALLY WORTH?
SURELY, YOU CAN
CUT ME A DEAL.
- ( muttering )
- ( huffs )
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE ONLY
KNOCKED OFF A THOUSAND JEWEL.
THAT STUBBORN OLD GEEZER
MUST BE BLIND.
THAT TRICK USUALLY WORKS.
SO MUCH FOR USING
MY FEMININE WILES.
( girls chattering )
- Girl #1: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
HE'S REALLY HERE?
- Girl #2: IT'S SALAMANDER!
- SALAMANDER?
( gasps )
AS IN THE WIZARD
WHO USES FIRE MAGIC
YOU CAN'T EVEN
BUY IN STORES?  WOW!
- ( cheering )
- HE'S IN THIS DEAD-END TOWN?
- ( groans )
MAN.
I WOUND UP RIDING
THE TRAIN TWICE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO GET OVER
THAT MOTION SICKNESS.
- NOW I'M SO HUNGRY
I COULD EAT MY HAND.
-  IT'S TOO BAD WE DON'T
HAVE ANY MONEY FOR FOOD.
- HEY, HAPPY.
THIS SALAMANDER
WE'RE LOOKING FOR
HAS GOT TO BE IGNEEL, RIGHT?
- AYE, IT HAS TO BE
BECAUSE THE ONLY FIRE DRAGON
I'VE EVER HEARD OF
IS IGNEEL.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- ( girls cheering )
- SALAMANDER!
- YOU'RE SO DREAMY!
- AND SO HOT!
- Both: SALAMANDER?
- HA! WELL, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
WE'RE IN LUCK TODAY, HAPPY.
- AYE!
- ( laughs )
- ( chuckles )
- ( screaming )
- ISN'T HE HANDSOME?
- HE'S SO COOL!
- ( heart beats )
- ( chattering )
- Lucy: WHY IS MY HEART
BEATING SO FAST?
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO ME
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- YOU LADIES
ARE ALL SO SWEET.
- ( gasps )
HE LOOKED AT ME!
IS IT 'CAUSE
HE'S A FAMOUS WIZARD?
IS THAT WHY MY HEART'S
THROBBING OUT OF CONTROL?
( gasps )
COULD IT BE?  AM I IN LOVE?
- IGNEEL!  IGNEEL!
- IS HE THE ONE?
- IGNEEL, IT'S ME!
- ( gasps )
- Natsu:
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
- WHO AM I?!
I'M SALAMANDER.
SURELY YOU'VE
HEARD OF ME BEFORE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
- Girl #9: YOU'RE SO RUDE!
- Girl #10: SALAMANDER'S
A GREAT WIZARD.
YOU BETTER APOLOGIZE TO HIM
OR WE'RE GONNA RIP
YOU TO SHREDS.
- WHAT IS IT
WITH YOU GIRLS?
- NOW, NOW, THAT'S ENOUGH,
MY LOVELIES.  LET HIM GO.
I'M SURE THE POOR BOY DIDN'T
MEAN ANYTHING MALICIOUS BY IT.
- ( girls coo )
- SALAMANDER!
- AND HERE'S MY AUTOGRAPH, KID.
NOW YOU CAN BRAG TO ALL
YOUR FRIENDS. - NO, THANKS.
- ( growling )
- ( groaning )
- GUESS IT WASN'T HIM AFTER ALL.
- DEFINITELY NOT HIM.
- WELL, I'M AFRAID
I MUST BE GOING, LADIES.
I HAVE BUSINESS TO ATTEND TO.
- All: YOU'RE LEAVING ALREADY?!
- TIME FOR THE RED CARPET.
HA!
- ( girls cheer )
- I'M HAVING A SOIREE
ON MY YACHT TONIGHT.
AND YOU'RE ALL INVITED.
- ( girls chattering )
- WHO THE HECK
WAS THAT GUY?
- Lucy: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT HE WAS A REAL CREEP.
- HUH?
- HMM?
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
- UH...
- ( cuckoo clock chirps )
- AND THEN...
- MY NAME IS LUCY.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
- Happy: HI.
- ( slurping )
( gulping )
( chewing loudly )
- UH...
UM, NATSU AND HAPPY, WAS IT?
- HM-HMM, YOU'RE SO NICE.
- THANKS.  YOU CAN SLOW DOWN.
WE'RE NOT IN A HURRY.
AND FOOD IS KINDA
FLYING EVERYWHERE.
THERE GOES THE MONEY I SAVED
AT THAT OLD GEEZER'S SHOP.
EVIDENTLY, THAT SALAMANDER GUY
WAS USING MAGIC, A CHARM SPELL,
TO HYPNOTIZE THE LADIES
IN TOWN INTO THINKING
THEY WERE IN LOVE WITH HIM.
CHARM SPELLS HAVE THE POWER
TO ATTRACT PEOPLE TO YOU
AGAINST THEIR OWN WILL,
BUT THEY'VE BEEN
BANNED FOR YEARS.
NOBODY EVEN SELLS THEM
ANYMORE.
HE MUST HAVE GONE THROUGH
A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO GET HIS HANDS ON IT.
WHAT A CREEP.
I TOTALLY FELL VICTIM
TO HIS SPELL,
BUT I SNAPPED OUT IF IT
THANKS TO YOU
BARGING IN WHEN YOU DID.
I REALLY CAN'T
THANK YOU GUYS ENOUGH.
- NO PROBLEM.
- I KNOW I MAY NOT LOOK LIKE IT,
BUT I'M A WIZARD TOO.
- IS THAT SO?
- YEAH, BUT I HAVEN'T JOINED
A GUILD YET OR ANYTHING.
OH, I SHOULD
PROBABLY EXPLAIN, HUH?
SEE, GUILDS ARE
THESE ORGANIZATIONS
WHERE WIZARDS COME TOGETHER
TO SHARE INFORMATION,
AND FIND WORK,
AND THINGS LIKE THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU AREN'T
CONSIDERED A FULL-FLEDGED WIZARD
UNTIL YOU BECOME
A MEMBER OF A GUILD.
BUT THERE ARE TONS OF THEM
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
I'VE HEARD IT'S REALLY TOUGH TO
GET INTO THE MORE POPULAR ONES.
AND THE GUILD I WANT TO JOIN IS
THE MOST POPULAR ONE THERE IS.
( sighs ) YEAH...
THEY'RE THE GREATEST AND
THEY'RE ALWAYS FEATURED
IN "SORCERER WEEKLY."
OH, IF I COULD ACTUALLY
CONVINCE THEM TO LET ME IN,
I THINK I'D JUST ABOUT DIE.
- YEAH?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS ALL THIS WIZARDING TALK
MUST SOUND LIKE A BUNCH
OF GIBBERISH TO YOU, HUH?
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
I'M DEFINITELY GONNA JOIN
THAT GUILD SOMEDAY.
AND THEN I'M GONNA TAKE
ALL KINDS OF EXCITING JOBS
AND MAKE TONS OF MONEY.
- OH, YEAH?
- YOU TALK A LOT.
- UH...
OH, MAN, I ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU GUYS CAME HERE TRYING
TO FIND SOMEBODY, DIDN'T YOU?
- WE'RE LOOKING FOR IGNEEL.
- WE HEARD A RUMOR
THAT A SALAMANDER
WAS GONNA BE COMING
THROUGH THIS TOWN,
SO WE CAME HERE TO SEE HIM.
TURNS OUT, IT WAS SOMEBODY ELSE.
- YEAH, THAT GUY DIDN'T LOOK
LIKE A SALAMANDER AT ALL.
- NO KIDDING.  I BET THAT POSER
CAN'T EVEN BREATHE FIRE
LIKE A REAL DRAGON.
- UH, I DON'T GET IT.
YOUR FRIEND IGNEEL
LOOKS LIKE A DRAGON?
- NO, YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
HE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE A DRAGON.
HE IS ONE.
- ( roars )
- HUH?
- AYE, IGNEEL...
IS A REAL-LIFE FIRE DRAGON.
- HUH?!
- Narrator: EVEN IN THIS
MAGNIFICENT WORLD OF MAGIC,
DRAGONS ARE CONSIDERED
EXTRAORDINARY,
MYSTICAL CREATURES.
THEY ARE RARELY SEEN
BY THE HUMAN EYE.
- WHY WOULD A FIRE DRAGON
SHOW UP IN THE MIDDLE OF TOWN?!
- Both: UH...
- IT'S TOTALLY RIDICULOUS!
WELL, I SHOULD GET GOING.
ENJOY THE REST OF YOUR LUNCH.
AND MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
- THANK YOU, MA'AM.
PLEASE COME AGAIN.
OH!
- ( awkward laugh )
- THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
- THANK YOU!
- CUT IT OUT!
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME!
LOOK, IT'S COOL.
YOU GUYS HELPED
ME OUT EARLIER.
SO LET'S JUST CALL IT EVEN.
- I FEEL BAD, THOUGH,
'CAUSE WE WEREN'T EVEN
TRYING TO HELP HER.
- AYE, WE OWE HER SOMETHING.
- OH, I KNOW!
HERE, THIS IS FOR YOU.
- NO WAY!
- ( cawing )
- Narrator:
THIS IS THE WIZARDING MAGAZINE,
"SORCERER WEEKLY."
- OH MY.
LOOKS LIKE THE FAIRY TAIL
GUILD'S OUT THERE
CAUSING TROUBLE AGAIN.
"DEMON BANDIT CLAN
WIPED OUT,
BUT SEVEN HOMES DESTROYED."
( laughs )
TALK ABOUT GOING OVERBOARD.
THE CENTERFOLD'S MIRAJANE.
SHE'S SO PRETTY.
I WISH I KNEW HOW
TO GET TO BE A MEMBER.
DO YOU HAVE TO APPLY
OR MAYBE INTERVIEW WITH THEM?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'M SO GONNA
JOIN FAIRY TAIL!
THEY'RE TOTALLY
THE COOLEST GUILD EVER!
- ( giggles )
- Salamander: WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU WANT TO JOIN FAIRY TAIL?
- SALAMANDER! - I'VE BEEN
LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I WANTED TO PERSONALLY
INVITE YOU TO THE PARTY
I'M HAVING ON
MY YACHT TONIGHT.
- YOUR CHARM SPELL
WON'T WORK ON ME.
THAT MAGIC'S WEAKNESS
IS AWARENESS.
IT DOESN'T WORK ON PEOPLE
IF THEY KNOW YOU'RE USING IT.
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
I GUESSED YOU WERE A WIZARD
THE MOMENT
I LAID EYES ON YOU.
NO MATTER.  THE INVITATION
STILL STANDS.
- WELL, YOU CAN FORGET IT.
I WOULDN'T BE CAUGHT
DEAD AT A PARTY
BEING THROWN
BY A CREEP LIKE YOU.
- A CREEP?  WHY WOULD
YOU CALL ME A THAT?
- YOUR SPELL. USING IT TO
MAKE YOURSELF POPULAR.
- DON'T BE MAD, MY DEAR.
IT'S ALL IN GOOD FUN.
I JUST WANTED TO
FEEL LIKE A CELEBRITY
AT MY OWN PARTY.
CAN YOU BLAME ME?
- THIS JUST PROVES THAT
EVEN FAMOUS WIZARDS
CAN BE BIG IDIOTS.
- YOU WISH TO JOIN
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
ABOUT SALAMANDER,
ONE OF FAIRY TAIL'S WIZARDS?
- WELL, YEAH.
YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU'RE HIM?
YOU'RE THAT SALAMANDER?!
- THAT'S CORRECT.
AND IF YOU WANT TO JOIN,
I COULD PROBABLY PUT IN
A GOOD WORD FOR YOU.
- ( gasping )
- I WOULD LOVE TO GO
TO YOUR PARTY TONIGHT.
( giggles )
- WOW, THAT WAS EVEN EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
- SO, YOU REALLY THINK
YOU COULD GET ME INTO
FAIRY TAIL? NO KIDDING?
- I DON'T SEE WHY NOT,
BUT YOU CAN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THE CHARM SPELL.
- I WON'T SAY A WORD.
- GOOD.
THEN I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE PARTY TONIGHT.
- YOU GOT IT,
MR. SALAMANDER, SIR.
HE GOT ME.
I WAS PSEUDO-CHARMED.
BUT...
HOORAY!
HE'S GONNA GET ME
INTO FAIRY TAIL!
I JUST HAVE TO KEEP
MY MOUTH SHUT
AND TRY TO BE NICE
TO THAT SLEAZEBAG UNTIL THEN.
( giggles )
- THAT WAS QUITE A MEAL,
HEY, HAPPY?
- AYE.
HEY, LOOK, DO YOU THINK
THAT'S THE BOAT
WHERE THAT SALAMANDER GUY
IS HAVING HIS PARTY?
- ( gags )
I'M GONNA HURL.
- OH, COME ON.
IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE GOING ABOARD OR ANYTHING.
- Girl #11: OH MY GOSH!
THAT'S SALAMANDER'S YACHT,
ISN'T IT?
- I WISH I COULD HAVE
GONE TO HIS PARTY.
- WHO'S SALAMANDER? - WHOA,
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD OF HIM?
HE'S A SUPER FAMOUS WIZARD
WHO'S IN TOWN RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH, AND HE'S A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL.
- HUH?
FAIRY TAIL?
( gags )
OH, NO.
SO HE'S IN FAIRY TAIL, IS HE?
- Salamander:
IT'S LUCY, RIGHT?
THAT'S A LOVELY NAME.
- YEAH, THANKS.
- I'D LIKE TO
TOAST YOUR BEAUTY.
NOW, OPEN UP WIDE, LUCY.
SAVOR THE TASTE
OF EACH FLAVORFUL DROP
AS IT ENTERS YOUR MOUTH.
- CREEPY!
I'M STRONG.
I CAN GET THROUGH THIS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE UP TO.
YOU'RE TRYING TO USE
SLEEP MAGIC.
- ( chuckles )
VERY IMPRESSIVE, MY DEAR.
- LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO
GIVE YOU THE WRONG IDEA.
YES, I REALLY WANT TO JOIN
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA DATE YOU
TO MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
- ( chuckles ) YOU'RE
QUITE A HANDFUL, AREN'T YOU?
- ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- WELCOME ABOARD MY SHIP.
AND YOU'D BE WISE
TO BEHAVE YOURSELF
UNTIL WE MAKE IT TO BOSCO.
DON'T MAKE ME ANGRY.
- WE'RE GOING TO BOSCO?!
YOU SAID YOU'D GET ME
INTO FAIRY TAIL!
- FORGET IT.
I JUST SAID THAT
SO I COULD LURE YOU HERE
AND MAKE YOU ONE OF OUR SLAVES.
- HOW COULD YOU?!
YOU'RE GONNA KIDNAP
ALL OF THESE GIRLS?
- Minion #1: THAT'S OUR
SALAMANDER, ALL RIGHT.
- Minion #2: WE GOT
A BIG HAUL THIS TIME.
- WHY YOU!
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- HMM.
THESE ARE GATEKEYS.
SO YOU'RE A CELESTIAL WIZARD.
ONLY THE WIZARD WHO IS
CONTRACTED CAN USE THIS MAGIC.
SO THESE ARE ABSOLUTELY
USELESS TO ME.
WHOOPS.
- ( whimpers )
- ( chuckling )
- YOU USED MAGIC TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF OTHERS.
YOU'RE THE WORST
WIZARD ALIVE.
- ( groaning )
- HEY, I KNOW YOU.
- ( gags ) I KNEW
THIS WAS A BAD IDEA.
- YOU ARE SO LAME.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, LUCY?
- OH, HAPPY,
THIS JERK TRICKED ME.
HE SAID HE WAS GONNA
GET ME INTO FAIRY TAIL.
HOLD UP, SINCE WHEN
DO YOU HAVE WINGS?
- Happy: I'LL EXPLAIN
THAT LATER, OKAY?
HOLD ON.
- ( screams )
- AFTER THEM.
WE CAN'T LET THEM
REPORT THIS TO
THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
- WAIT, WHAT ABOUT NATSU?
- I CAN'T CARRY TWO PEOPLE.
- ( shivers )
- PROMINENCE WHIP!
- ( screams )
- ( awed muttering )
- THAT CAT'S QUICKER
THAN HE LOOKS.
- Natsu: HEY, GUYS.
- Lucy: WHAT ABOUT NATSU
AND THE OTHER GIRLS?
- WE GOT A PROBLEM, LUCY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT PROBLEM?
- MY TRANSFORMATION'S UP.
- ( both scream )
- STUPID CAT.
- ( grunts )
- Lucy: MY GATEKEYS.
- ( men grunting )
- FORGET ABOUT THEM.
LET'S CONTINUE ON
TOWARDS BOSCO.
- ( grunting )
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD...
YOU'RE A MEMBER?
- ( gasps )
HERE WE GO.
OPEN, GATE OF THE WATER BEARER.
- ( doorbell rings )
- AQUARIUS!
- A FISH!
- NOT FOR YOU.
- THAT WAS AWESOME.
- THAT'S THE POWER
OF A CELESTIAL WIZARD.
WHENEVER I USE MY GATEKEYS,
I CAN SUMMON SPIRITS FROM
OTHER WORLDS TO HELP ME.
LISTEN UP, AQUARIUS,
I WANT YOU TO USE YOUR POWER
TO PUSH THAT SHIP
BACK INTO THE PORT.
- ( scoffs )
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO COME
FROM THE SPIRIT WORLD TO HELP,
NOT TO GIVE ME ATTITUDE.
- I WOULDN'T MAKE HER
ANY ANGRIER, LUCY.
- LET'S GET SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
THE NEXT TIME
YOU SO MUCH AS THINK
ABOUT DROPPING MY KEY,
YOU'RE DEAD.
- IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- ( screams )
- WHY IS THE SEA SO ANGRY?
- HEY, DON'T WASH
ME AWAY WITH IT!
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU THINK YOU COULD HAVE TRIED
NOT TO SWEEP ME
UP WITH THE SHIP?!
- OH, THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET THE SHIP.
- WAIT, THAT MEANS
YOU WERE AIMING FOR ME?!
- DON'T CALL ME FOR A WHILE.
I'M GOING ON A WEEK-LONG
VACATION WITH MY BOYFRIEND.
AND HE'S HOT.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO RUB IT IN.
- I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
IF THE FISH LADY
GIVES YOU ANY MORE TROUBLE,
YOU CAN CALL ME
TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
- I DON'T THINK I CAN HANDLE
MUCH MORE OF THIS STUPID CAT.
- ( muttering )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- THAT SHIP WAS
THROWN INTO PORT.
- THAT HURT.
WHAT IN THE--
- ( gasping )
- Lucy: NATSU!
- SO YOU CLAIM TO BE A MEMBER
OF THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD?
- SO WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
GO GET HIM, MEN.
- SIR.
- LET ME GET A CLOSER
LOOK AT YOUR FACE.
- Lucy: WATCH OUT!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU THIS EARLIER,
BUT HE'S A WIZARD TOO.
- ( gasps )
- MY NAME IS NATSU.
I'M A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD.
AND I'VE NEVER
SEEN YOU BEFORE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
SO NATSU IS
A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD?
- Man: THAT MARK ON HIS ARM,
THIS GUYS IS
THE REAL DEAL, BORA.
- DON'T CALL ME THAT,
YOU FOOL.
- I KNOW HIM.
THAT'S BORA THE PROMINENCE.
RUMOR HAS IT, HE WAS KICKED OUT
OF THE TITAN NOSE WIZARD GUILD
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO
BECAUSE OF BAD BEHAVIOR.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO HERE, BUDDY,
AND I DON'T CARE IF YOU'RE
A GOOD GUY, BAD GUY, OR WHAT.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU DIRTY
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD'S NAME.
- AND WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
STOP ME?
PROMINENCE TYPHOON!
- NATSU!
- ( screaming )
- THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES.
THE BIGGER THE TALK,
THE WEAKER THE MAN.
- AW, THIS IS SO GROSS.
ARE YOU SURE THAT
YOU'RE REALLY A FIRE WIZARD?
BECAUSE THESE ARE THE NASTIEST
FLAMES I'VE EVER TASTED.
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
- THANKS FOR THE GRUB, POSER.
- Man: WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHO IS THIS KID?
- FIRE MAGIC DOESN'T WORK
ON NATSU.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- NOW, I'VE GOT
A FIRE IN MY BELLY
THAT'S RAGING TO GET OUT.
HERE IT GOES.
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- Minion #3: HEY, BORA,
I SWEAR I'VE SEEN
THIS GUY BEFORE.
THE PINK HAIR AND
THE SCALY-LOOKING SCARF,
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
HE'S GOT TO BE THE REAL ONE.
- SALAMANDER?!
- I HOPE YOU GUYS
ARE PAYING ATTENTION.
THIS IS WHAT
A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD CAN DO.
HERE I COME!
- RED SHOWER!
- ( grunting )
- SO HE EATS FIRE
AND THEN ATTACKS WITH IT?
BUT HOW DOES HE DO IT?
IS IT SOME KIND OF SPELL?
- HE HAS DRAGON LUNGS THAT
ALLOW HIM TO BREATHE FIRE,
DRAGON SCALES TO HELP HIM
TO DISSOLVE THE FIRE,
AND DRAGON CLAWS FOR
ATTACKING WITH FIRE.
HIS BRAND OF FIRE MAGIC
IS ONE THAT ALLOWS HIS BODY
TO TAKE ON
ALL THE QUALITIES
OF A DRAGON.
IT'S AN ANCIENT SPELL
THAT'S RARELY USED ANYMORE.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THIS PARTICULAR MAGIC
WAS ORIGINALLY USED
TO DEAL WITH DRAGONS.
- WHOA.
- HELL PROMINENCE!
- Happy: IT'S CALLED
DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC.
IGNEEL WAS THE ONE
WHO TAUGHT IT TO HIM.
- ( screams )
- NOW, THAT WAS A HEFTY MEAL.
YOU'RE NOT DOING TOO BAD.
BUT I'M ABOUT TO COOK YOU
LIKE A SMOKED FISH.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO WHAT TO ME?
- GET READY.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
( grunts )
- ( screams )
OWW, OWW, OWW!
- ( bell rings )
- DON'T BE SILLY, NATSU.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU
SMOKE FOOD WITH SMOKE,
NOT FIRE.
- OH, WOW.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
BUT HE OVERDID IT.
- AYE.
- OH, SHUT IT, CAT.
- THE ARMY?!
( screams ) - OH, CRAP,
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- WHERE THE HECK
ARE YOU TAKING ME?
- JUST COME ON.
YOU SAID THAT YOU WANTED
TO JOIN THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD,
DIDN'T YOU?
SO LET'S GO.
- ALL RIGHT!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Lucy: I'M SURE THAT
BEFORE I JOIN FAIRY TAIL,
THEY'RE GONNA MAKE ME
INTERVIEW WITH THEM.
FIRST IMPRESSIONS ARE IMPORTANT
WITH THINGS LIKE THIS.
SO I'M GONNA PRACTICE.
( clears throat )
GREETINGS, MY NAME IS LUCY.
NO, THAT'S PROBABLY
WAY TOO FORMAL FOR THEM.
HIYA', I'M LUCY.
WHAT'S UP?
UGH, TOO TEENAGE GIRL.
NEXT TIME...
I'VE GOT TO BE MORE ENERGETIC
AND SAY SOMETHING
THEY'LL REMEMBER ME BY.
I AM LUCY!
WHOA, THAT WAS JUST SCARY.