How much longer do we have to
walk before we get to Magnolia?
[PRECHT] We should be there
in about three more days.
Wha--?!
I guess we're gonna be campin'
out in the forest tonight.
Is this guy crazy?
I can't sleep outside!
[MAVIS] Come on, Zera.
It'll be an adventure!
We'll have fun!
Don't you get that this isn't
like the woods back home?
This is like one of
those haunted forests
from the stories
we used to read!
[screams]
You see! This place is
crawling with creepy bugs!
And I'm sure there
are snakes, too!
[MAVIS] They're more afraid
of you than you are of them.
[ZERA]
That's impossible!
We're sleeping under the stars!
Time to camp out!
I'm gonna find some wood to
build the best damn camp fire
you guys have ever seen!
[PRECHT] I'm going to hunt
down fresh meat for dinner.
And I'll go see if I can find
some mushrooms and herbs
to have with it!
I think I'm gonna stay
right here and keep watch.
Meat, side dish,
guard duty, what's left?
Oh, right, I'll go try
and catch some fish!
[ZERA screams]
[gasps]
Uh-oh.
Zera! What happened?
Is everything okay over here?
Yeah, I just took
a little spill.
These fish are a
lot harder to catch
than the ones we
have back home.
I'm glad it was just that.
You had me worried!
Sorry, I didn't mean to!
[chuckles]
Perhaps it would
be a better idea
to look for nuts or
berries instead.
What is this place?
I have no idea. I've never
seen anything like this.
We should show the others
and see what they think.
[YURI] What the heck
happened to the trees?
It's as if a poisonous
wind swept through
and killed all the living
things in the area.
I'm beginning to get the feeling
that it would be too dangerous
to camp out in the forest
and maybe we should
get out of here.
No, the sun's already
starting to set.
I think it's worse to travel
an unknown path in the dark.
Yeah.
Where we're camped is
far enough from here
that we should be
out of harm's way.
That makes sense.
Being seasoned treasure hunters,
you clearly have a whole
lot more experience
with phenomena like
this than I do.
Right? Don't you think?
Well, if you think
so, then yeah.
Speaking of experience,
this seems oddly
similar to something
that went down on another gig.
Do you remember?
I do.
Feels a lot like our adventure
at the ruins in
Hell's Valley, right?
Did you say "Hell's Valley"?
[PRECHT] That was
definitely more dangerous
than taking a straight path
through a dark forest, though.
Yeah, the particulars are
startin' to come back to me now.
Yuri put us through
a special kind of hell
on that one, didn't he?
[YURI grunts]
Yuri caused trouble?
What? How? I wanna hear
all the juicy details!
[YURI growls]
Will you ever let me
live that one down?!
We got the treasure in the end,
isn't that the only
part that matters?
You'll never live it down!
It's a miracle we even lived to
see the light of another day!
Well, we're standing here
fighting now, aren't we?
You're exaggerating the story
to make me look bad!
With the mistakes you
make on a daily basis,
you do a fine job making
yourself look bad!
[MAVIS] So "Mister Perfect"
isn't perfect?
Oh, I really wanna know what
kind of mistakes he makes!
I'm gettin' really
tired of saying it.
You're reckless and impulsive
and you had better get
that crap under control.
If not, we're all heading
towards an early grave.
[YURI] What? It's not like
you're perfect or something!
You've almost gotten us killed
a few times, too, as I recall,
so don't lecture me
about my mistakes, bud!
I'm saying this stuff
for your own damn good!
So don't come crying
to me if you get hurt!
Why don't you just
mind your own business?!
Who do you think
you are anyway?!
[BOTH growl]
[YURI]
Tch!
Wait, you're just gonna
walk away after that?
I'm sleeping by myself tonight.
I don't wanna be
anywhere near this jerk.
Well, good, with you gone
my odds of surviving the night
just got better!
Come on, you guys!
It's not worth it!
Those two are
acting like children.
[MAVIS] Precht, you're not gonna
do anything to stop them?
[PRECHT] What they do
is up to them, not me.
But splitting up is dangerous.
[PRECHT] Yes, but there's
not much I can do about it.
If something happens
to them, it happens.
Is he serious?
Why don't you and I
split up and go after them?
I'll track down Yuri;
you follow Warrod.
If that's what you want.
[MAVIS]
Yuri, where are you?
This part is dead, too?
What is going on here?
[PRECHT]
Hm?
I guess they really do mean
to sleep on their own tonight.
[PRECHT sighs]
[PRECHT]
Here's the whole story.
We made the trek
through Hell's Valley
in search of a legendary
magical plant
by the name of the Wild Rainbow.
It only bloomed in
one part of a cave
deep in the mountains
around Hell's Valley.
It was known for its brilliant,
rainbow-colored petals.
Because of its rarity, the plant
was worth millions of Jewel.
That sounds like an
amazing treasure.
[PRECHT]
If we found it,
our reputation
would be unmatched
among treasure hunters.
Legends say that it was
protected by an ancient curse.
To reach the treasure,
we had to travel through
a barren wasteland
where poisonous
gases spewed forth
from deep within the ground.
[WARROD] I've never seen
such a desolate place.
[PRECHT] This used to be
the center of a civilization,
despite how barren it seems now.
Its citizens were
plant worshippers,
and believe it or not,
there used to be an
abundance of vegetation.
The state it's in
now is the result
of environmental destruction
and climate change.
[WARROD]
Time spares no man or land.
[YURI]
Whatever. Who cares?
Let's just get inside
and grab that treasure.
[YURI sighs]
We can finally breathe again.
Stay on your toes, Yuri,
and pay attention.
Legend has it no one
who's entered these ruins
made it back out alive.
[YURI]
Don't be a scaredy-cat.
We're gonna make it out,
and when we do,
we'll be rich beyond
our wildest dreams.
I wish you'd slow down.
We need to be extra cautious
inside these caves.
I wanna chase down that thing
before it pulls up its roots
and runs away to make some other
treasure hunters millions.
[sighs]
[YURI]
Dammit, we're lost!
What did I tell you
about being cautious?
[PRECHT] Calm down, you two.
I brought a map with me.
How convenient! I knew
we could count on Precht!
Then why were you
freaking out just now?
[PRECHT] We definitely came
in from that direction.
Uh.
The lantern's out of oil.
Not to worry, I've got
some extra fuel right here.
[YURI] Man, it's too dark
to see what I'm doing.
If only we knew
how to use magic.
I bet we could light up this
entire cave in no time at all!
Uh?
Well, that was perfect timing!
Uhh...
Something weird is going on.
[PRECHT]
Automatic ignition lamps.
They must be
designed to activate
in response to intruders.
That seems like bad news.
[rumbling]
What an astute observation.
We'd better make
a run for it, boys!
Which way, genius?
Oh, I don't know, maybe away
from the falling rocks!
Look! Over there!
[WARROD, YURI yelling]
Where do you think
this thing goes?
Why don't you ask the
guy with the map?
[ALL screaming]
[ALL]
Huh?
What a perfect place to stop.
[PRECHT]
So now what?
[YURI]
We get out and walk, obviously.
[WARROD]
Okay... Then what?
[YURI] I'm sure we'll
figure something out.
Do you ever think ahead
or do you always fly by
the seat of your pants?
[YURI]
Hey! Look at that!
I believe we found our
first treasure, boys!
Are you kidding? That thing has
booby trap written all over it!
Nah, there's no writing. And
look at the size of that jewel!
[YURI]
Uh...
[YURI screams]
What did I tell you?!
Shut your mouth
and move your feet!
Keep going! We're almost there!
[ALL screaming]
[YURI] Ouch. We're all
still alive, aren't we?
[PRECHT]
By some miracle, yes.
Hey, look. What is this?
How is it so bright?
[PRECHT]
Hm.
This moss is luminescent.
That must be what's
lighting up the place.
Doesn't seem like it
should be here naturally.
[PRECHT] Maybe in the days
of the civilization
this used to be a sacred site.
Look!
[YURI]
It's the Wild Rainbow!
[YURI lauging]
Something has been bothering me
about this entire expedition.
Oh, you mean besides Yuri?
[PRECHT] I've seen a lot of
traps in other places like this.
They're usually designed
to kill intruders.
The ones here are different.
They seem engineered
to lead anyone
who sets foot in
these caves here.
Doesn't that seem odd to you?
What do you think
that means for us?
The people here worship plants.
This part of the cave
is full of them,
and unusual ones at that.
I suppose what I'm
getting at is this:
What if the traps
we've encountered so far
are set up to lead
intruders to this spot
so that they can become
food for some monster
that lives down here?
[gasps]
Yuri, hold on! Stay
away from that flower!
Why?
[WARROD]
What the--?!
[growling]
[WARROD gasps]
[roars]
[YURI yelping]
Yuri, no!
I knew it wasn't a flower.
It's bait to lure people into
this cave so it can eat them.
Now I understand why
the Wild Rainbow
has never been brought
outta this cave!
Hang on!
Try not to move around
for a second, Yuri!
Couldn't you have gotten me down
without shattering my tailbone?!
Gratitude would be
appropriate here!
[roars]
So what are we gonna do
about this monster?
We simply have to
wait for an opening!
At the first opportunity,
grab the flower and
put it in the pod!
You make it sound so easy.
What are you doing now?!
I'm gonna distract this thing
to get you an opening!
You guys go for the flower!
I thought I was the Wild Card!
He's just taking a page
from your book, I guess.
Let's not let him
forget that he did!
[yelling]
[BOTH]
Warrod, no!
Grab the flower while
you have the chance!
No way! Are you crazy?
Hang in there, and
we'll come save you!
I'm a treasure hunter.
I'm capable of saving myself!
We're this close.
Now get it or the
whole expedition
will have been for nothing!
Hurry! I can't keep his
mouth open much longer!
You better not get
eaten, you dummy!
The Wild Rainbow
would be worth nothing
if we didn't all make it
out of this cave alive!
[WARROD]
Not good!
[YURI]
Precht, help!
Hold on just a little longer!
[YURI]
For real?
[WARROD]
We're gonna die!
Now's our chance!
How did you pull that one off?
[PRECHT]
Well, the thing is a plant,
so I figured the best
course of action
would be to take out the roots.
I'm just lucky it worked.
At least somebody's thinkin'.
I wish you would have come up
with it a little bit sooner.
[PRECHT]
Did you get the Wild Rainbow?
[chuckles]
Of course I did.
See for yourself.
Hey!
[rumbling]
Now what the heck is happening?
[PRECHT] All of that activity is
causing the ruins to cave in.
Well that's just great!
So we got out alive
with the treasure,
and we're still working
together to this day.
Oh, wow.
I guess going through something
like that builds unity.
You know, Precht, I learned
something from that story.
And that's: We can count on you!
[PRECHT]
That wasn't my intention.
I was simply relaying the
facts as they occurred.
And you're so modest, too!
[WARROD]
Oh-ho!
You've already got a
nice campfire going!
Perfect timing! Take a look!
We caught this big ol' beast
in a lake we found nearby!
You two weren't even
speaking earlier
and now you're going
fishing together?
[YURI]
Hm?
Oh. That's right,
we don't like each other.
[WARROD] I was so focused
on catching our dinner,
I forgot I was mad.
Yeah, whatever,
I'm too hungry to care.
Let's grill this tasty monster!
Precht, would you do the honors?
I guess when you're friends,
you let go of the things
that don't matter.
Right, Zera?
[WARROD, YURI chuckle]
You know, being
a treasure hunter
certainly seems like a
challenging way of life!
[YURI]
It is,
but the rewards always make
the hardships worthwhile.
The Tenrou Orb is
an S-class treasure.
Once we get it, we can sell it.
And then we'll never
have to work again
for the rest of our lives!
[MAVIS] Judging by the way
you talk about treasure,
I get the feeling you guys are
only going to be our friends
until we find that orb.
This girl's a smart one, huh?
I guess it makes sense.
But we'll see what
actually happens
after we find what
we're looking for.
I'll say this.
You've led a very sheltered
life on that island,
and you shouldn't trust people
that you've only known
for a little while.
You could easily
end up getting hurt.
But you guys wouldn't do that.
Because your eyes tell
me you're trustworthy.
Zera?
Did you see which way she went?
I hope she's not embarrassed
that she wasn't able
to catch any fish.
She can be so
sensitive sometimes.
I'll be back in a bit.
I'm gonna try to find her.
[YURI sighs]
[PRECHT]
That girl is incredibly strange.
I really enjoy having
her around, though.
I've been thinking,
maybe we should let her have
the Tenrou Orb back after all.
[PRECHT] To be honest,
I've lost interest in it.
What?!
Did you forget the entire point
of being a treasure hunter
is taking things that
other people want?
I won't give in to some kid.
When we find the Tenrou Orb,
we're taking it for ourselves.
That little girl isn't
getting anything.
You're despicable.
[MAVIS] Oh, there you are, Zera.
I was worried about you!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is something bothering you?
Are you upset that you weren't
able to catch any fish?
[ZERA]
Mh-hm.
I'm just a little worn out.
Well, we did live by ourselves
on an island for seven years.
Yeah.
It's been a long time
since I've had to be
around people this much.
It's only three others, though.
You saved me.
I know I would've died that
night if you hadn't been there.
[MAVIS]
Zera!
[coughing]
Zera, you're alive!
[ZERA] I made a vow to myself
and to you seven years ago.
I swore that from then on,
I would always protect you.
But out here, in the world
away from the island,
I feel like there's so much
I don't understand.
So much I've never seen.
I feel useless.
In the end, all I ask is
that you stay by my side.
That's what best
friends are for, right?
No, that's not enough anymore!
I can't stand feeling
this way, Mavis!
The only way I'm gonna
be of any help
is if you teach me to use magic!
I wanna learn the kind of magic
spells that can beat Blue Skull,
and even those treasure
hunters if we need to!
Teach me the strongest
spells you know!
I am always gonna
protect you! I swear it!
Okay! I'll teach you
all the magic I can!
This is so exciting!
So let's not waste any time.
We can start my
training tonight!
[ZERA screams]
I've got to stop doing that!
[laughs]
[gasps]
Get in the water!
This journey's
been so stressful;
we deserve to relax
for a minute or two.
Wait, you mean right now?
Yeah, it feels incredible!
It brings back so many memories
of when we were little girls!
I'm not gonna let you
have all the fun!
[ZERA laughs]
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[gasps]
Look, Mavis, a fairy!
Do you see it?
What? No, where is it?
I was talking about the one
we keep in our hearts.
I do.
[WARROD] There it is.
The city of Magnolia!
Whoa!
We finally made it!
So this is the home of the guild
who killed all of our people
and stole the Tenrou Orb.
[PRECHT] Our first task
is to locate Blue Skull.
Oh, wow!
I really can't wait to visit
the Kardia Cathedral!
Is that the enormous old church
you were telling me about?
[PRECHT] Kardia Cathedral
is one of Fiore's
three largest churches.
The legends say that long ago,
the angel known
as St. Mikardia--
Hey, look! See that?
What the heck?
[PRECHT]
What is that?
[YURI] It's gotta be
Kardia cathedral, but--
Why's there a
blue-skulled dragon?
[MAVIS] My friends and I finally
arrive in the city of Magnolia,
only to find that a giant,
blue-skulled dragon
keeps watch over
the Kardia Cathedral,
the symbol of the city.
We wander the streets,
looking for answers
about the Blue Skull guild and
the location of the Tenrou Orb.
What we find instead is
a hapless, dying city
and a people devoid of
joy or hope of any kind.
Next Time: "Blue Skull."
An evil magic power
rules over the city.