[NATSU] Hey, Lucy!
Listen up!
I know that you
can hear me right now!
Just hang on!
I promise
I will save you!
Warning.
Another of the seals
has disappeared.
If the remaining
three vanish,
The holders of the clock
will lose possession.
[NATSU] C'mon Lucy!
Please snap out of it!
[Midnight giggles]
[MIDNIGHT] No matter
how much you plead,
it's useless.
Very soon, Lucy Heartfilia
and the Infinity Clock
will become one.
[KLODOA] And once they
are completely merged,
we will finally
have absolute control
over Real Nightmare!
Not happenin'!
I won't let anybody
touch my big sister.
She and I will
stay together
for the rest of time.
For all of eternity.
[NATSU] Previously,
on Fairy Tail!
[HAPPY]
We were fighting
against the
Legion Platoon
over the clock hand
that Lucy's dad
gave to her.
When all of a sudden
the Neo- Oración Seis
just came outta nowhere!
[CARLA] They stole
the clock, abducted Lucy,
and activated the spell
known as Real Nightmare.
We chose our
strongest wizards
to rescue her,
and put an end to this
once and for all.
[PANTHERLILY] If we can defeat
all of their remaining members,
we'll be able to
stop the Real Nightmare.
There are only
three of them left.
[LAYLA] Happy
birthday, darling!
We love you.
[YOUNG LUCY] Thanks mommy!
And daddy!
And everybody else!
[LUCY] Wait a second.
Michelle's not here.
[LUCY] No, of
course she's not.
Because it
was all just a lie.
[WARREN] Natsu!
What's goin' on over there?
How's Lucy?
Not so good.
If we don't hurry,
she's gonna be
absorbed by the Clock!
Are you serious?
[HAPPY] I Hear the
Voice of My Friend!
[LAKI] Lucy's
going to become
part of the Infinity Clock?
That must be why
telepathy can't reach her.
There's gotta be
some way that
we can help her.
[CARLA] You won't be helping
anyone, without rest!
Hey! Listen up
everybody!
[WARREN] We gotta
finish beating
the Oración Seis right now!
Because once Lucy merges
with the Infinity Clock,
it's game over!
We can't let that happen!
I heard that.
If you defeat me,
my seal will be
taken off the clock.
But you don't have
much time left to do that.
So just give up
and save yourself!
Ridiculous.
I would never
surrender to you.
[COBRA] You think
that even if you fall,
your friends will still
be around to help you?
There's no
way you can win
believing in
something so naïve.
[ERZA] Requip!
[COBRA] True power
requires true sacrifice!
And what we gave up
can never be replaced!
Erigor's memory.
Racer's humanity.
Angel gave away years
from her life!
But you
and your friends
don't have the strength
to make sacrifices!
We gave up everything
to get the kind of power
that you will never have!
[WARREN] Hey! Who is this?
Romeo?
What are you doing here?
You weren't supposed
to come along with us!
[ROMEO] I hitched
a ride on the Christina
without anyone knowing.
Did you really expect me
to stay behind
at a time like this?
I can't believe you!
I understand
why you did it.
But still, kid.
Hey Romeo,
can you hear me?
[ROMEO] Yeah.
Try to find another
member of Fairy Tail, okay?
[WARREN] But do it quickly!
Lucy's in trouble
and the only
way to save her
is to beat
the Neo-Oración Seis!
[ROMEO]
Which way should I go?
[CARLA] Natsu's the
closest person to you.
I'll tell you
where to find him!
[ROMEO] Thank you!
[WARREN] Happy! Lily!
[HAPPY] We just
heard all of that!
[PANTHERLILY]
We'll go and meet
them there at once!
[WARREN] We're
counting on you!
You're the only ones
who can stop Samuel!
[PANTHERLILY] Roger!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[BYRO] What is the
Archbishop's condition?
[WARREN] It's you!
[LAKI] Oh no!
What happened to Gildarts?
[BYRO] Both he
and another one
of your
comrades took a fall.
But, I'm sure
they're unharmed.
Now, can you tell me
what's become of
Samuel and the others?
[LAKI] There's
no reason for you
to go after
Lucy anymore!
[CARLA] If all
Six Demons are defeated,
their seals will
vanish from the clock.
They'll lose control.
[BYRO] True.
But it will
all be for naught
once Lucy Heartfilia
completely merges
with the device.
Correct?
[WENDY] Yeah, but.
[ARCHBISHOP]
There is yet another way.
[BYRO] Your Excellency!
[ARCHBISHOP] Finally.
My nightmare has now ended.
It was such a
helpless feeling
being controlled
like a puppet.
Forced into actions that
brought about this situation.
However, these kind souls
put their very
lives on the line
in order to rescue me.
Although I didn't
intend for it,
I was forced into the
position of their enemy.
Amid the chaos,
they came to my aid.
[LAKI] Sir?
[WARREN] Can you please
explain something to us?
[WENDY] Yes, please sir.
You know a lot
about the clock.
Isn't that right?
[ARCHBISHOP] I assume
you want to know
how you can free the
captured celestial wizard?
[NATSU] You say you wanna
be with Lucy forever, huh?
Have you ever
thought about
what she might want?
I can tell you,
she just wants to
believe in you again.
You betrayed her,
but I know she
can forgive you.
Why can't you
understand that?
[MIDNIGHT]
Don't confuse the issue.
Imitatia is
simply attempting
to reclaim that
which she once lost.
Aren't you?
[NATSU] Listen!
I know my
sister and I
want the same thing!
After all.
We were always
together before!
What?
[ROMEO] You liar!
[NATSU] Romeo!
Nobody believes a
single word you say anymore!
It's over.
You lied when you
said you were Michelle!
So why in the hell
should we believe you now?
It's the truth.
I was there!
Do you know
how happy
Lucy was to meet you?
She'd just lost her
last family member
when you came along!
Her heart was broken!
And you took advantage
of the pain she was in!
She put her
trust in you.
So did I,
but then, you lied!
Romeo, look.
[KLODOA] Don't let this
brat's childish words
weaken your
resolve, Imitatia.
Remember,
anyone who stands
in your way is the enemy.
[ROMEO] So what
do you have to say
for yourself, huh?
[MIDNIGHT] Kill him.
[NATSU] Romeo!
[ROMEO] Michelle...
How could you?
All right, that's it, lady.
I don't give
a crap who you are.
You're gonna pay
for what you've done.
I gotta save Lucy,
and you're in my way.
[IMITATIA] I see.
[KLODOA] Oh yes!
It looks like these two are
about to put on a show!
[MIDNIGHT] Do not
fail me Imitatia.
And be sure that
you don't forget
who's in charge here.
If you wish for me
to breathe life
into your prayer,
Show your loyalty.
[LUCY] Please, Michelle.
Please, stop.
You're gonna
regret that!
[KLODOA] Yes! That's my girl.
Keep your eyes focused
squarely on the prize.
Your deepest,
most heartfelt wish
an eternity to spend
with your dear big sister.
[MIDNIGHT]
Now, snuff him out.
Extinguish his fire
and realize your dream.
I can make it
come to fruition.
Entangle him.
Rip this fool
to shreds!
[LUCY] I'm begging you.
Please.
[LUCY] Warning.
A blood-thirsty enemy
is quickly approaching.
[COCO] Who is it?
No, Samuel!
What are
you doing here?
The only thing I can do!
Killing Lucy Heartfilia,
so we can put an end
to this madness!
[IMITATIA] No!
[SAMUEL]
Move aside, Coco!
No, never!
We don't have
time to argue about this!
Then go ahead.
If you wanna
get to Lucy,
you're gonna have to
tear through me first!
[SAMUEL] Look, I've put
aside church doctrine for now.
I'm doing this solely
for the greater good!
Even when you
know in your heart
that it's wrong?
Is it?
I don't even
need to calculate
the outcome this time.
We trade one life
for the sake
of our entire civilization!
[HAPPY] No you don't!
[COCO] It's you.
[PANTHERLILY]
I'll take care of him.
[NATSU] Just in time!
So your
answer is more bloodshed?
You need to learn
the value of life!
I guess I'll have to
school you some more.
Come and
get me brother.
[PANTHERLILY] Sammy!
[HAPPY]
Come on, wake up!
Lucy?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
I'm talkin' to you!
[LUCY] Yes.
I can hear you,
but I can't move.
I can't do anything!
[LUCY] I see my
friends being beaten
right in front of me.
But there's nothing
I can do to help!
It breaks my heart.
I can't stand to see
my friends in such pain.
[COCO] She's crying.
[HAPPY] Yeah!
I bet that means
she can hear us!
Lucy's fightin' even
harder than we are!
There's no way in
hell we're givin' up now!
[KLODOA] Ugh! What
a stubborn fool!
This is why I said
we should
exterminate him
instead of taking
him hostage!
[MIDNIGHT] You can fight,
but it's far too late.
You have zero
chance of victory.
[ERZA] Tell me!
Why do you go to such
lengths for power?
Causing all this
chaos and pain.
Dragging the whole
world into your sorrow.
Is your desire for
vengeance that strong?
[COBRA] Yes.
And that's not
all, Titania.
I'm doing this so
I can face Cubellios!
Don't you
understand?
Not that I've given up
all that I had.
I have no fear of
losing everything!
[COBRA] And without
that kind of fear.
I have true power!
[WARREN]
Listen up, everyone!
There's still hope!
We've found a way to slow down
Lucy's merging
with the Infinity Clock!
I'll go ahead and let the
Archbishop explain it to you.
[COCO] The
Archbishop's with him?
[ARCHBISHOP] For
the clock to fully merge
with a sacrificial
celestial wizard,
It must slowly
become integrated
with that
individual's mind
as well as their
sense of time.
[ARCHBISHOP]
To put it another way,
it must combine
with her memory.
[ARCHBISHOP]
The chains extending
from the Infinity Castle
serve two purposes.
Not only do they spread
the Real Nightmare
spell into the Earth,
but they also absorb
all of the magic power
and memories of
those who dwell on it.
[WARREN] So we
can buy some time!
But we're gonna have
to start breakin'
those chains!
[WARREN] Byro and his men
have already started the job!
We have to help
them finish it!
[GAJEEL] Okay.
Looks like I'm gonna need
an appetite for this job.
[PANTHERLILY]
Didja hear that?
[SAMUEL] Yes.
Very clearly.
It seems
I was wrong.
[PANTHERLILY]
Forget it.
Everybody makes
mistakes sometimes.
I know
I certainly have.
The real test...
Is how you make
things right.
Isn't it?
[PANTHERLILY] Let's go
cut some chains, Sammy!
[SAMUEL] Yes!
And whoever severs
the most is the victor.
Sound good?
[PANTHERLILY]
You're on!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Talon!
[IMITATIA]
You're not giving up?
Do you really think
you have a chance?
[NATSU] I heard
what the old guy said,
so you bet I do!
[MIDNIGHT]
Such a feeble hope.
Go ahead and waste
all your power!
[COBRA ] It's time
I finish you,
once and for all!
[COBRA] Cubellios.
You gave me one
final breath before
you departed.
[COBRA] Now I'll
put it to use.
[ERZA]
So he's one
of the Second Generation
Dragon Slayers.
[COBRA] I'll rot the
flesh off your bones!
[COBRA] Poison Dragon Roar!
[COBRA] What happened?
[ERZA] This
ancient weapon
was created to
ward away evil!
As you see,
It proves quite
useful in battle.
[COBRA] I can't
hear your thoughts
if you don't know them yourself.
[COBRA] You grabbed
that weapon
completely
out of instinct.
You should
try listening to my heart!
[COBRA]
So, you're willing
to make a big
sacrifice after all?
You'll cut these chains
and risk killing us both!
Here's one!
Two!
It's too late for this!
[GAJEEL] Man, this
stuff is disgusting!
[GAJEEL] Whoa.
It looks like they're
goin' all out up there!
Can't let 'em
show me up.
Can I?
[BYRO] We must
sever the next chain!
Hurry!
[GUTMAN] I heard
the Archbishop
talking to
little ol' me!
Forget about the
stupid Legion Platoon!
We gotta turn some
frowns upside down
and fix what
we did wrong!
So let's do it!
[SAMUEL]
That's five for me!
[PANTHERLILY]
I got seven!
[KINANA] I can hear it!
It's calling me!
[KINANA]
It's so close now.
The voice is
getting stronger.
The voice of my friend!
[ERZA] Cobra.
You told me
your power
comes from the
things you've lost.
Your sacrifices.
[ERZA] Having
nothing to lose
isn't the same
as being strong!
[COBRA] If you have a point,
then go ahead
and make it!
[ERZA] Fighting to protect
what you hold dear.
Not giving
it all away.
That's true power.
You can't live
only for yourself!
Not caring
about anything else.
If you ask me,
that's the very
definition of cowardice!
[COBRA] What?
If this
friend of yours
was to come back,
how could you even
look them in the eye?
Shut up!
You lasted longer
than I expected!
But it's over now!
Time to die, Titania!
[COBRA] Cubellios?
It can't be!
No way.
But still.
I hear her!
[COBRA] She has
a different body,
but I can still
hear her mind!
It's hard to believe,
but I know it's her!
[ERZA] It seems
you've also sacrificed
your focus in battle.
[COBRA] Damn you!
[ERZA] Having
friends to care for
doesn't make you weak.
It's the opposite.
You realize that
now, don't you Cobra?
I know you hear it.
The voice of your friend
calling out to you.
Telling you that
you still care.
[KINANA] That's him!
Yes!
I can hear his voice!
And there's
the shooting star!
It's true!
That is him!
[KINANA] He's
come back to me!
[LUCY] Warning.
Another seal has
been erased.
Now only two remain.
[KLODOA]
Cobra's been defeated?
This is terrible.
[NATSU] Aw, yeah!
Now all I gotta do
is kick your butts
and it's over!
[IMITATIA]
How can you be
so stubborn
and single-minded?
At this point,
all you can do
is delay
the inevitable.
It's far too late
to change anything.
[MIDNIGHT]
I will complete
what my
father could not.
To wipe out all that
has form in this world,
and to usher in a new
age of pure chaos.
You got in
our way seven years ago,
but history will
not repeat itself.
I will destroy you.
[HAPPY] Natsu!
[COCO] Natsu!
[MIDNIGHT] And just
so you understand,
this celestial wizard,
whose life you're
desperately trying to save,
She's already gone.
A lost cause.
She could survive
a century-long slumber.
But she will
actually become
one with the Clock
and lose herself entirely.
Her mind and body merging
with the clock itself.
At that point,
she will fade
from the memories
of those who claimed
to love her so dearly.
Her very existence
will be completely
erased from this world.
[IMITATIA] No, what
are you saying?
Is that true?
She can't.
She's supposed to
stay with me forever.
[MIDNIGHT] But you
don't understand,
that can still happen.
She is simply
going to change her form
to one that's more
suited to our needs.
You can
still be with her.
[MIDNIGHT] In fact,
she'll be the perfect companion
for someone
as empty as you.
No.
No!
My deepest wish.
My one true prayer.
This isn't
what I wanted!
Sister!
What are you doing?
Stay away!
Move!
Sister! Please!
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
Please!
[LUCY]
Michelle.
All of your tears.
Your appetite.
Your clumsiness.
You're so cool.
Living your dream.
I'm jealous.
That's just a strategy
to avoid feeling guilty.
Harden your heart
to suffering
and you can
justify any decision.
[LUCY]
Poor Michelle.
You were suffering
all along, weren't you?
[KLODOA] Well, this is an
unfortunate turn of events.
[MIDNIGHT] How pathetic.
Imitatia.
You are no longer
useful to me.
Back to the trash heap.
Sister.
[MICHELLE]
Big Sister.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
[LUCY] Yes.
It makes sense now.
That's why
she wanted things
to go back to the way
they were before.
Really?
Do you mean it?
[LUCY] Yeah!
She wasn't lying to me.
She really believed it.
And at one point...
I did, too.
She was my little sister.
[MIDNIGHT] Filthy,
little piece of garbage.
[KLODOA] Now, now.
You don't wanna soil
your shoes, do you Master?
[NATSU] You monster.
[ROMEO] Natsu! Catch!
[MIDNIGHT] Yes! That's it!
Do you really think that
other people's suffering
is something to laugh at?
That it's a joke?
Get ready.
'Cause things're
about to get
really funny for you, pal!
[NATSU] No, that thing's
gonna swallow up Lucy!
[HAPPY] Taking out
the new Brain
is the only
chance we've got!
[NATSU] Yeah, I know.
But it's gonna be tough.
He's got a bigger
chip on his shoulder
than anyone else in
the Neo-Oración Seis.
[HAPPY] Come on, Natsu!
There's no way
that we can lose!
We've got a lot more
heart than that big jerk!
And we've got all our
friends in Fairy Tail
to back us up!
[NATSU] Next time:
Lucy and Michelle!
[HAPPY] [NATSU]
Next time: Lucy and Michelle!
[NATSU] Yeah, but
you and I both know
that I'm the only one
who's actually
gonna fight him, right?
[HAPPY] Hey, we're
all with you in spirit!
[NATSU] Thanks,
but don't go tryin'
to steal my
thunder after I win!