[CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] It's the final day
of the Grand Magic Games
and the competition's
really heating up!
The ladies of Mermaid Heel
have been pushed back
to fourth place with
forty-three points.
Well, that's what
happens when you lose
three team members
right off the bat.
Geez, way to point out
the obvious, Grandpa.
I can't believe I
went down so easily.
Well, it's not like
we did any better.
[CHAPATI] And neck and
neck in second place,
with forty-nine points each,
are Lamia Scale and Sabertooth!
Our kids have their work
cut out for them, don't they?
Only the most powerful
competitors remain.
And in first place,
with fifty points and every
single member still standing.
Give it up for Fairy Tail!
[CROWD cheers]
Gotta say, their initial
strategy threw me off.
I thought they were
goners, didn't you?
I figured it was
part of their plan.
[YAJIMA] Once they
sprang into action,
they dominated the competition.
But a Fairy Tail
push like that
is always gonna cause quite
a bit of damage to the city.
[CHAPATI] I'm told it'll
be restored using magic.
[CHAPATI] Well spank my butt
and call me Quatro Puppy!
We've got an exciting new
development on our hands!
It looks like we're
about to witness
an incredible three-way battle
between Fairy Tail's Erza,
Mermaid Heel's Kagura,
and Sabertooth's Minerva!
[YAJIMA] These fierce
ladies might just bring
this tournament to an
earthshaking climax!
[JELLAL]
Reveal your identity.
I have already revealed mine.
A woman?
[JELLAL gasps]
There's no way!
[HAPPY]
Erza vs. Kagura!
What the...?!
Is that me?!
Wow, she looks
just like Lucy!
Does that mean they're
the same person?
There's no way.
That has to be Gemini, right?
I still say that's
the one from Edolas.
[FUTURE LUCY] I know that
you've heard of Eclipse by now.
I was able to use its powers
to meet with you today.
[GROUP gasps]
You used the Eclipse?
But that would mean...
...you've come from
another time, haven't you?
Yes, from the future.
[GROUP yells]
What's going on?
Why'd you decide to
come back to our time?
[FUTURE LUCY whimpers]
[FUTURE LUCY]
I came to warn you.
This kingdom is doomed.
[NATSU gasps]
[LUCY gasps]
[NATSU] Hey!
[WENDY]
Is she gonna be okay?
[CARLA] She fainted but
she's still breathing.
I think she'll be alright.
What in the heck is
goin' on around here?
I don't have any idea.
[CARLA] A Lucy
from the future...
But what could
this mean...?
Could my vision
be coming true?
You holding up okay?
I just don't understand
why I would do this.
Unless I was desperate.
At any rate, we'd
better take her with us.
We can work the rest out later.
Then, once we're
outside the castle,
we'll launch
the signal flare.
Right.
The rest of the guild
will be happy to know
that we've rescued Lucy.
[NATSU] Not to brag, but we
even got ourselves a spare.
Princess, there's something
I don't understand.
You need a Celestial wizard
to open the Eclipse door,
and yet you threw
the two you had
into the Palace of Perdition.
Why would you hinder
your own plans like that?
It doesn't make sense.
[HISUI] It does
and it doesn't...
I only needed the
twelve zodiac keys,
not the wizards
themselves, but...
I acted cruelly.
[DARTON] If it
then why did you return
them to their wizards?
It seems rather
foolish to toss aside
keys to a door you
wish to pass through.
[HISUI] The keys are
no longer needed.
[DARTON] Hm?
Why is that, Princess?
[HISUI] Because I've
already used them...
The doorway through
space and time
is now unlocked.
All that's left is for
someone to open the door
and walk through it.
And is this
someone prepared
to accept responsibility
for the lives
which they may ruin
by changing history?
[HISUI] I can't shoulder
this burden alone...
That's why I wanted
Arcadios by my side.
And why I sought your approval.
[DARTON] Hm...
Whether we open
Eclipse or not
depends on the outcome
of the games...
For now...
we must wait
and see how it unfolds.
[MINERVA] Hm.
[KAGURA]
Release her at once!
[MINERVA]
Perhaps in a bit,
but first I plan to show you
how a queen wages war.
This is your
last chance.
release my comrade and
I will allow you to live.
[MILLIANNA sobs]
If you want to save her,
come and take her.
[KAGURA grunts]
She's so fast!
You'll be the second
tiger I feast upon!
Careful, Mermaid, this one's
rather tough to swallow.
[BOTH] Uh!
[CROWD murmurs]
Ah! That's unbelievable!
What did she do?
I didn't see a thing!
Neither did I,
it was too fast!
Another dirty trick!
[KAGURA]
They switched places?!
[ERZA]
What kind of magic is this?!
Heh, heh. You ladies can go
ahead and battle it out.
I'll wait and take on the
victor once she's weakened.
[ERZA] You're running from
a fight you interrupted?!
And you call yourself a queen?
[MINERVA] A true queen arranges
the pawns to suit her strategy.
[BOTH grunt]
If anything you
should be flattered.
I must admit, I underestimated
your combined power.
I now realize that I
wouldn't stand a chance
against the two of you.
But in the end,
it's irrelevant.
A queen does not
yield to power alone.
[ERZA]
Let Millianna go!
[KAGURA]
I'm warning you...
Don't you dare...
[ERZA] Ugh!
Don't pretend
to be my ally!
[MINERVA] My, my.
It seems you ladies have
some catching up to do.
I'll just be on my way.
I accept your terms; just
leave Millianna out of this!
[MINERVA chuckles]
[ERZA] She's got us
in quite a bind.
[KAGURA] Be quiet...!
I don't speak to my enemies...
I destroy them.
[CHAPATI clears throat]
[CHAPATI] Well this is certainly
a complicated situation.
Tell me, Yajima,
what do you make of it?
[YAJIMA] Hm. There isn't any
rule against taking hostages
during the Battle Royale.
Therefore we have no choice
but to look at this kidnapping
as a tactical play.
You kiddin' me?!
She's gonna hurt Millia
unless somebody stops her!
I feel so helpless,
just standing here
watching from
the sidelines.
There's nothing we
can do about it...
C'mon Kagura.
Millia's life is
in your hands now.
[GAJEEL] This sucks...
The first master's plan's
gone right off the rails.
Some "fairy tactician" she is.
[MAVIS whimpers]
It's okay First Master,
we all make mistakes.
I keep adjusting
my calculations
but no matter how
I look at them,
that three-way fight just
shouldn't be possible!
Are you feelin'
okay, Levy?
Uh, yeah,
I'm fine...
Just kinda worried, I guess.
D'ya think he'll be all right?
[LISANNA] Of course he will,
he's a Dragon Slayer.
It takes a lot to
keep them down.
Yeah, you're right.
Good luck, Gajeel.
We're rooting for you.
[GAJEEL]
Well, well...
You're a pesky little bugger.
I ain't nowhere near
as nice as Salamander
so start saying your prayers.
[CHAPATI] Whoa!
Looks like a couple of dragons
are about to duke it out!
[FROSCH]
Be careful, Rogue...
[YAJIMA] Ahhh.
I think this matchup may prove
to be even more exciting.
[LAXUS]
How's it goin?
So you and I finally
get to square off.
[LAXUS] So, what's with
the black lightning?
Surely you've realized by now.
I'm no ordinary wizard;
I'm a Lightning God Slayer.
That's gonna make
it embarrassing
when ya get your butt
kicked by a fairy.
[CHAPATI] Hold me, Yajima,
I think I'm gonna faint!
The matchups just
keep on coming!
[YAJIMA] We haven't
seen Sting in a while.
I wonder if he'll
make an appearance.
[CHAPATI] That's odd...
The Lacrima-tron cameras
can't seem to find him
anywhere in the city.
[FROSCH whimpers]
[FROSCH]
Come on, guys!
You gotta fight extra hard
so we can get Lector back!
[DARTON] Hm.
It would be incredible
for the games to end
in such a way...
But I have my doubts
as to whether
it will actually come to pass.
It seems all but impossible.
I have the same doubts
as you, Minister...
We can only hope that
my contact is mistaken.
[STING] You fight
real dirty, m'lady.
Heh, heh. But it
ain't gonna matter.
Least, not after I'm finished.
With the plan
I got in mind,
there's nothing anyone can do
to keep me from winning.
I'm gonna make
you proud, Lector.
[JELLAL] I'm afraid
that we gravely mistook
the gravity of the situation.
If there is a joke in this,
it's that our fate
was already sealed.
[MELDY] What do we do
if this future Lucy
is telling the truth?
There's gotta be
something, right?
If we can't think of a plan,
the kingdom will be destroyed.
[JELLAL sighs]
Any ideas, Jellal?
[MELDY] But how?
How is this possible?!
[ULTEAR sighs]
[ULTEAR] I guess it's
still following me...
Even after all this time.
What?
The price of all my sins...
destruction.
[YOUNG MILLIANNA grunts]
[BUDI]
Move faster, scum!
[GALI] We will finish the
R-System as quickly as possible!
You can work to be part of it,
or you can be buried underneath.
You hear me?!
[YOUNG MILLIANNA sobs]
[YOUNG MILLIANNA]
I can't take it!
My hands hurt so bad.
[YOUNG ERZA]
Please don't cry anymore;
here, you can have my food too.
[YOUNG SIMON] You eat it, Erza;
she can have mine instead.
[YOUNG ERZA]
I'll be fine, Simon.
You need it more than I do.
[YOUNG SIMON] But you've
gotta be starving...
[YOUNG JELLAL] I had no idea
you were so strong, Erza.
[YOUNG ERZA] Huh?
[YOUNG JELLAL]
I haven't told you guys
my full name yet, have I?
It's Jellal Fernandes.
Cool name, but it sounds
hard to remember.
[YOUNG JELLAL]
And what about you?
You mean me?
It's just plain old Erza.
That's the only name I've got.
Well, you gotta
have a last name.
What are you doing?
Sorry, but I just think
your red hair's pretty...
I've got it!
What do you think about
Scarlet being your last name?
You can't just go and make up
whatever name you want!
It's not your choice
to make, it's hers.
So now I'll be
Erza Scarlet.
Y'sure, Erzy?
She actually
likes it?
Now I know I'll never
forget your name.
I just have to think
about your pretty hair.
[BUDI] Stupid brat.
Bet he thought
we'd go easy on him
'cause he's covering
for his friends.
[GALI] Who cares?
We've got a slave
revolt to deal with;
we can torture this one later.
[BUDI]
Brace yourself kid,
'cause you ain't gettin' outta
here till you worship our god!
[YOUNG JELLAL weakly]
There is no god...
If there were, then he would
kill you both and save us.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
So much hatred...
You've got plenty
to share, don't you?
I feed off of the
suffering of others...
and I have gained
much power from you.
You're such a
fortunate boy
to have the honor of
speaking with a god, yes?
[YOUNG ULTEAR] The most
nefarious wizard in history...
I am Zeref.
I am hatred incarnate.
[YOUNG JELLAL] We need
to stay here, Erza...
[YOUNG ERZA] But we're slaves!
We'll be free once we escape!
[YOUNG JELLAL] There is
no freedom in this world.
Those that think they
have it are deceived.
But we can make
a new world...
A world that's
ruled by Zeref.
[YOUNG ERZA]
Don't be stupid!
This place is evil, we can
still get out of here, Jellal--
Ahh!
[YOUNG JELLAL] Fine then,
I'll let you leave.
Go on, have a good time
pretending to be free.
However...
I'll kill everyone you care for
if you ever come back here.
That's the price
of your freedom!
So go on!
That is, if you can stand
with the weight of their lives
on your shoulders.
[JELLAL laughs]
[JELLAL] In my darkest hour,
Lord Zeref called to me.
We are destined to create
a land of true freedom!
Please stop, Jellal.
You can never be free
as long as you're possessed
by that stupid spirit!
Stop letting him manipulate you!
Free yourself!
[ULTEAR] It was me at
the Tower of Heaven.
I was controlling Jellal...
Don't blame him for
what he was forced to do.
Besides...
I think he's been through
enough as it is.
[ERZA gasps]
The three of us have formed
an independent guild...
Crime Sorcière,
or "witch's crime."
[WENDY]
An independent guild?
[ULTEAR] Unfortunately, our one
true goal still eludes us.
Zeref, the dark guilds,
and any evil force in the world
that seeks to destroy
the lives of innocents.
We'll purge every one
of them so no wizard
will be possessed
by his darkness again.
I've committed a ridiculous
number of sins in my life...
Far too many.
[ULTEAR] I will never
find redemption.
No matter how hard I may try.
So what now?
Seems like at the very least
we should get the
citizens to evacuate.
That would only
cause panic.
It'd save their lives!
[JELLAL]
That's enough!
[ULTEAR and MELDY] Huh?
There's no guarantee that what
she said will come to pass.
[ULTEAR] What?
Why do you
say that?
I'm not quite
sure just yet.
But all is not as it seems.
Something isn't right.
[NATSU] Hm...
Somethin' doesn't
feel right...
Would you care
to elaborate?
This Lucy that I'm carryin'...
She's a lot lighter than you.
Not in the mood for
your snarky comments!
[HAPPY] She pro'lly lost weight
from all of her hardships.
[NATSU] Hear that, Lucy?
In the future, you're gonna find
a diet that actually works!
[LUCY]
You're on thin ice, pal!
Looks like it's time for
us to put an end to this.
I'm not going
to hold back.
I'd be insulted
if you did.
[ERZA] Uh!
Heaven's wheel!
Pentagram sword!
Grudge Sword.
Archenemy!
[KAGURA] Blast form!
[ERZA yells]
[KAGURA] Slicing form!
[ERZA] Adamantine Armor!
[ERZA yells]
That's crazy!
The Jupiter cannon couldn't
even break through that armor!
Plus she hasn't even
drawn her sword yet!
So powerful...
How did she--
Strange you survived.
[ERZA] Flight Armor!
Sonic Claw!
[ERZA yells]
I didn't even
see her attack!
Me either!
[ERZA coughs]
Erza's being beaten
in a swordfight?
That's impossible!
I have to admit, I never
saw this coming either.
[ERZA whimpers]
[CHAPATI] Incredible!
Kagura has struck down Erza,
the woman who wiped out all one
hundred monsters of Pandemonium!
[ERZA] I'm surprised.
To think that such
power exists...
I suppose that
your strength
is fueled by your
hatred for Jellal.
[KAGURA grunts]
[thud]
[ERZA groans]
[ERZA] If you want to
hold onto the hatred,
it makes no difference to me...
Go right ahead...
But please don't force Millianna
to go down that road with you.
She's moving on!
This was his will.
[ERZA yells]
And now it is
mine as well...
I will kill Jellal.
[ERZA coughs]
[ERZA]
What happened?
What drove you
to these extremes?
[KAGURA] The man whose
will I speak of?
It turns out you
knew him very well.
His name was Simon
and Jellal killed him.
He was my brother.
[ERZA gasps]
[ERZA] Simon...
You're his sister?!
Our family was
poor, but happy.
[inaudible]
[KAGURA] Until that happiness
was stolen from us...
[KAGURA] One night,
these strange men showed up
in our village...
[CHILDREN scream]
[KAGURA]
It was a child hunt.
I alone managed
to escape.
I vowed to find
my brother...
I spent years searching for him.
That is...
until I met Millianna.
I'm sorry...
I don't know how to say this...
[KAGURA] That's when I found out
my brother had been killed,
and how much he had suffered.
[ERZA whimpers]
[KAGURA] He was
imprisoned, tortured,
and enslaved for years.
Then he was brutally murdered.
I was plunged
into darkness.
That's when I took a new vow,
to avenge his death.
Until the time comes for
me to fulfill that vow.
Archenemy shall
remain in its sheath.
[ERZA] There's something
that you need to know...
Millianna didn't see
your brother die.
[KAGURA gasps]
[ERZA]
She wasn't there...
It was only Jellal,
Simon, Natsu, and me.
[JELLAL] I'm going to
obliterate both of you!
[NATSU] Watch out!
What're you doin'?!
It's my fault that you were
involved in this mess,
so the least I can
do is protect you!
[NATSU]
Get outta the way!
Heavenly body magic: Altairis!
Erza!
[gasps]
[ERZA]
Oh, Simon...?!
[SIMON groans]
[thud]
[JELLAL laughs]
[ERZA]
My Simon...?
[SIMON] Don't cry.
It's okay.
I'm happy to
give my life...
...for you.
Don't talk!
Just try to stay with me!
[SIMON]
Please don't cry...
You were the
only person...
...who made me smile.
I've always...
loved you...
[ERZA gasps]
[ERZA] Nooo!
[ERZA] I can see why
you thought Jellal
was responsible for
your brother's death...
It would be easy to let you
go on believing that, but...
I'm the one to blame.
[KAGURA gasps]
[KAGURA]
You'd resort to lies
just to be that
killer's scapegoat?
I'm sorry, but
it's the truth...
If I hadn't been
so incredibly weak,
your brother would still
be alive and well today.
[KAGURA seethes]
Kagura, no!
Think about what
you're doing!
Don't let your anger
get the best of you!
[KAGURA seethes]
[SIMON] Kagura...
[KAGURA gasps]
[KAGURA screams]
I'm so sorry.
[gasps]
[HAPPY] How come Erza hasn't
beaten that mermaid girl yet?
She can requip and stuff!
[NATSU]
Yeah, but I'm pretty sure
Kagura's the toughest
wizard in her guild.
[HAPPY]
Maybe it's just me,
but Erza seemed like
she was kinda sad.
Do ya think we should
be worried about her?
[NATSU]
You gotta be kiddin' me!
There's no way she'd ever
give up during a fight.
If anything, you should be
worried about the other chick.
[HAPPY] You know what, Natsu?
You're right!
[BOTH] Next time: A Future
Racing Toward Despair!
[NATSU]
C'mon, 'lil buddy!
We gotta make it back to
the others, for Erza's sake!
[HAPPY] Yeah!
Let's go and put
her mind at ease!