- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- Lucy: WHEN WE WERE ATTACKED
BY THE ORACION SEIS
ERZA WAS BITTEN
BY A GIANT SNAKE
AND NOW SHE'S BARELY
HANGING ON TO LIFE.
- Gray: WE ALSO LOST
MY OLD FRIEND, LYON.
- Happy: BUT THINGS ARE
STARTING TO LOOK UP
WHEN NATSU RUSHED IN
TO SAVE ME AND WENDY
FROM THAT CREEPY BRAIN GUY
AND HIS PALS.
- Natsu: UNTIL WE FOUND
OURSELVES FACE TO FACE
WITH JELLAL.
- (theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT'S THAT RUMBLING?
HEY, DO YOU HEAR THAT?
- ( yawns sleepily )
- ( chuckles )
- ( rumbling )
- ( Happy speaking )
- LYON.
- NO! IS HE--
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
- HE WOULD NEVER
GIVE UP THAT EASILY.
LET'S FIND HIM.
COME ON.
- ( whimpers )
LYON...
HE'S GONE FOREVER.
SOMEBODY'S GOTTA PAY.
- YOU DON'T HONESTLY
THINK YOU CAN HIDE FROM ME?
SHOW YOURSELF.
- HOW SILLY OF ME TO TRY
AND OUTFOX A WIZARD SAINT.
OH YEAH!
WE BOTH USE EARTH MAGIC AND YET
OUR POWERS ARE SO DIFFERENT.
MINE HEATS UP AND
SOFTENS THE SOIL,
WHILE YOURS SOLIDIFIES IT.
OH YEAH!
I WONDER WHOSE POWER
IS THE STRONGEST?
DON'T YOU?
- NO.
MAGICAL ABILITY
IS IRRELEVANT.
THE STRONGER
IDEOLOGY ALWAYS WINS.
- I'M AFRAID
THAT YOU'RE WRONG.
NO MATTER THE ERA,
THE ONES WHO TRIUMPH
ARE THE RICH.
OH YEAH!
- YOU MISS ME?
- NATSU!
- HOW'D YOU DO THAT, ANYWAY?
ALL OF A SUDDEN, YOUR MAP
POPPED RIGHT INTO MY HEAD.
- I'LL EXPLAIN IT TO YOU LATER.
IS WENDY ALL RIGHT?
- SHE'S FINE.
- TIME FOR YOU TO WAKE UP, KID.
I SAVED YOU.
NOW YOU GOT TO SAVE ERZA.
- DON'T BE SO ROUGH WITH HER!
- COME ON, RISE AND SHINE.
WAKEY, WAKEY.
- ( screams )
I HAD TO DO IT.  SORRY.
- I'M WILLING TO
OVERLOOK THAT RIGHT NOW.
ERZA WAS BITTEN BY
A POISONOUS SNAKE.
SHE'S IN BAD SHAPE.
PLEASE SAVE HER!
- SHE'S HURT?
- WE NEED ERZA TO DEFEAT
THE ORACION SEIS.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THEM WITHOUT HER HELP.
- PLEASE, WENDY, WE NEED
HER MORE THAN EVER.
- WE'RE BEGGING YOU.
- YEAH! I'LL TRY TO SAVE HER.
NO, I WILL.
- HURRAY.
- SNAP OUT OF IT ALREADY.
YOU'RE SO PATHETIC.
- AYE.
- I'VE HEARD THAT
JELLAL DID TERRIBLE THINGS
TO HURT ERZA IN THE PAST.
THAT'S HARD
FOR ME TO BELIEVE.
- Cobra: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS ABOUT THIS GUY,
BUT I CAN'T HEAR
HIS INNER VOICE.
IF I COULD, I WOULDN'T
HAVE TO FOLLOW HIM AROUND
AND SPY ON HIM LIKE THIS.
WHY'D HE STOP?
I KNOW THE WOODSEA WELL,
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS PLACE BEFORE.
LOOKS LIKE BRAIN
WAS ONTO SOMETHING.
COULD THIS BE WHERE
NIRVANA IS SEALED?
( laughing )
AT LAST, WE FOUND IT,
OUR FUTURE!
- WELL, THAT SHOULD DO IT.
I GOT RID OF ALL THE VENOM.
NOW ALL WE HAVE
TO DO IS WAIT.
- WAIT?!
( groans )
SHE'S OKAY!
- HEY, GIVE ME SOME SKIN, LUCY.
- I'M SO HAPPY.
( cries )
- DON'T LEAVE ME HANGING.
- FINE, JUST THIS ONCE.
- AYE.
- THANKS, WENDY.
I GUESS I OWE YOU ONE.
- SHE'S PROBABLY NOT GONNA
WAKE UP FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
BUT SHE'LL BE BACK TO
NORMAL WHEN SHE DOES.
- THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
WHO KNEW SKY MAGIC
WAS SO STRONG?
SHE'S ALREADY
LOOKING MUCH BETTER.
- NO, YOU DON'T!
- EXCUSE ME.
NOW THAT YOUR
FRIEND IS HEALED,
PLEASE DON'T MAKE WENDY
USE HER SKY MAGIC AGAIN.
SHE'LL INSIST THAT SHE'S FINE,
BUT I CAN TELL
THAT SHE'S EXHAUSTED
BY THE LOOK ON HER FACE.
- NO, YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
I'M JUST WORRIED IS ALL.
- WE'RE GONNA STRIKE BACK
AS SOON AS ERZA WAKES UP.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY, OKAY?
- YEAH, WATCH OUT,
ORACION SEIS.
- AYE! WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU GET NIRVANA.
- WHAT IS THAT?!
- A GIANT PILLAR
OF BLACK LIGHT.
- NO WAY!
- Hibiki: IT'S BEEN UNSEALED.
- IT'S BEEN UNSEALED.
THAT'S NIRVANA!
- ALL OUR HARD WORK,
IT'S FINALLY PAID OFF.
WE DID IT!
NIRVANA BELONGS TO US!
- THAT BEAM OF LIGHT
JUST SHOT UP OUT OF NOWHERE.
OH, NO, DON'T TELL ME
THEY'VE ALREADY FOUND NIRVANA.
- SO IT HAPPENED.
- YES, NIRVANA IS OURS.
- CONGRATULATIONS ARE IN ORDER.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
THERE'RE SOME PESKY
GUILD WIZARDS
I NEED TO ELIMINATE.
DON'T WAIT UP FOR ME.
YOU SHOULD GO TO
THE LIGHT, FATHER.
- YEAH, THAT'S GOT TO BE IT.
- SERIOUSLY?
BUT HOW'D THE ORACION SEIS
BEAT US TO THE PUNCH?
- THAT PILLAR OF LIGHT...
I KNOW JELLAL'S THERE!
- JELLAL?
HOLD ON!
WAIT, DON'T JUST RUN OFF
WITHOUT TELLING US
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
- ( cries )
NO, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
THIS IS ALL BECAUSE OF ME.
- ( pants )
I CAN'T RISK HIM
RUNNING INTO ERZA.
I GOT TO STOP HIM.
NO, I GOT TO DESTROY HIM.
THAT WAY, HE'LL NEVER
HURT HER AGAIN.
- JELLAL.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THAT'S ABOUT?
- NO CLUE.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
SOME KIND OF BLACK
STUFF IS FLOWING
OUT OF THAT TREE OVER THERE.
IT'S LIKE IT'S BEING
SUCKED OUT BY THAT LIGHT.
- I WONDER WHAT COULD DO THAT?
- YOU DON'T THINK
THAT LIGHT
COULD BE COMING FROM
WHEREVER NIRVANA IS, DO YOU?
- BUT IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THAT MEANS SOMEONE'S ALREADY
GOT THEIR HANDS ON IT.
- WAS IT THE ALLIED FORCES
OR THE ORACION SEIS?
HIBIKI, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CAN YOU READ ME? HEY!
- THIS MAGIC ENERGY MUST
BE BLOCKING OUR TELEPATHY.
- NOW WHAT?
- I THINK WE SHOULD SPLIT UP.
I'LL CONTINUE
THE SEARCH FOR WENDY.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL GO FIND OUT
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT LIGHT.
BE CAREFUL.
- I KNOW HE'S GOT TO
BE HERE SOMEWHERE.
- SOMEONE'S GOT TO PAY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO MY LOVE.
- WHERE ARE YOU?!
ANSWER ME, LYON! HEY!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?! LYON!
- HE'S THE ONE.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
- IT'S NIRVANA! OH YEAH!
- ( gasps )
- THERE'S NO REASON FOR
YOU TO GET ALL WORKED UP.
ITS MAIN OPERATION HASN'T
BEEN ACTIVATED YET.
THE LIGHT SIMPLY MEANS
ITS SEAL HAS BEEN BROKEN.
IT'S ALSO A SIGN
WE'RE ABOUT TO BE
ROLLING IN DOUGH.
OH YEAH!
( giggles )
- FIGHTING THIS BUFFOON
WOULD BE A WASTE
OF MY PRECIOUS TIME.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
DEFEATING THE ORACION SEIS
IS THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF OUR MISSION.
SHOULD I STAY HERE AND FIGHT?
OR SHOULD I GO
STOP NIRVANA?
- ( giggling continues )
MONEY!  MONEY!
WE'RE ABOUT TO BECOME
INCREDIBLY WEALTHY!
( gasps )
( whimpers )
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO HIM?
- COME ON, WE HAVE
TO GO AFTER NATSU.
- WHY? WHY WOULD HE MENTION
JELLAL OUT OF NOWHERE?
- I CAN EXPLAIN LATER.
RIGHT NOW, WE'VE
GOT TO GO FIND HIM.
- Carla: ( shrieks )
ERZA HAS GONE MISSING.
I SWEAR, WHERE
ARE HER MANNERS?
SHE DIDN'T EVEN THANK WENDY
FOR SAVING HER LIFE.
- UH-OH, DO YOU THINK
SHE MIGHT HAVE HEARD
US MENTION JELLAL'S NAME?
- HOW COULD I BE SO STUPID?
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
WHAT DID I DO?
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE HEALED HIM.
IT'S MY FAULT THAT
NIRVANA WAS FOUND,
ERZA DISAPPEARED,
AND NATSU RAN OFF.
- WENDY!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, STRIKING A GIRL?
- I GOT TO FIND JELLAL.
- IF YOU THINK YOU'RE
GONNA GET PAST
MEMBERS OF RACER'S
HARPYIA GUILD,
YOU'RE JUST AS
DUMB AS YOU LOOK.
- LET'S GET HIM, GUYS!
- ( cheering )
- GET OUT OF MY WAY,
SPEED FREAKS!
- ( screams )
- I'M NOT LETTING THAT JERK
GET NEAR ERZA.
I'LL BURN HIM
TO A CRISP!
- I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T
MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
BUT SHE'S GONNA BE FINE.
I JUST KNOCKED HER OUT.
- WHY'D YOU DO IT? AND WHY ARE
WE SUDDENLY IN A HURRY?
- WE'VE GOT TO CATCH UP
WITH NATSU AND ERZA.
JUST KEEP RUNNING TILL
YOU REACH THE LIGHT.
- WHY SHOULD WE TAKE ORDERS
FROM A BRUTE LIKE YOU?
I REALIZE WENDY CAN
BE A BIT OF WHINER.
THAT'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO STRIKE HER.
- NOT COOL, DUDE.
- I DID IT
BECAUSE I HAD TO.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
COMPLETELY HONEST.
I KNOW A LOT MORE
ABOUT NIRVANA
THAN I ORIGINALLY LET ON.
- WHAT?  WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US?
- I COULDN'T.
BECAUSE OF THE NATURE THE MAGIC,
I COULDN'T SAY A WORD.
EVEN JUST MENTIONING IT NOW,
IS RISKY AND MIGHT
PUT US IN DANGER.
THAT'S WHY GUILD MASTER BOB
ONLY TOLD ME ABOUT IT.
MR. ICHIYA, REN, AND EVE
HAVE NO CLUE.
- SO WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
- NIRVANA IS A TERRIFYING MAGIC
LIKE NO OTHER.
IT ALONE HAS THE ABILITY...
TO TURN LIGHT
INTO DARKNESS.
- ARE YOU FOR REAL?
- MY WORD.
- IT CAN SWITCH THEM?
- BUT THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN
UNTIL ITS FINAL STAGE.
THE FIRST THING IT DOES
WHEN IT'S BEEN UNSEALED
IS SHOOT OFF A BLACK BEAM JUST
LIKE THE ONE IN FRONT OF US.
THEN IT GOES IN SEARCH
OF THOSE WHO ARE WEAK.
IT'LL SWITCH ANYONE WAVERING
BETWEEN LIGHT AND DARK
TO THE OPPOSITE ALIGNMENT.
IN OTHER WORDS, A GOOD GUY
WHO'S FEELING DOWN AND OUT...
WILL LIKELY FALL
TO THE DARK SIDE.
- SO THAT'S WHY.
YOU KNOCKED WENDY UNCONSCIOUS
TO PROTECT HER.
- HOW COULD I BE SO STUPID?
WHAT DID I DO?
I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE HEALED HIM.
- SHE WAS AT HIGH RISK
OF BECOMING A TARGET
BECAUSE OF HER GUILT.
IF I HADN'T STEPPED IN
WHEN I DID,
SHE EASILY COULD
HAVE SWITCHED OVER
TO THE DARK SIDE.
- NOW YOU'VE GOT ME WORRIED?
IS ANGER A NEGATIVE EMOTION?
IF SO, NATSU'S IN DANGER.
- Hibiki: THAT'S A TOUGH CALL.
NORMALLY IT WOULD BE,
BUT BECAUSE HIS ANGER
IS FOR SOMEONE ELSE'S SAKE,
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU COULD
CLASSIFY IT THAT WAY.
- I FEEL LIKE A DUMMY.
NOTHING YOU'RE SAYING
MAKES ANY SENSE TO ME.
- BECAUSE YOU ARE A DUMMY.
ALLOW ME TO
SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU.
NOW THAT NIRVANA'S SEAL
HAS BEEN BROKEN,
IT HAS THE POWER TO TURN
THOSE WITH GOOD HEARTS EVIL
AND THOSE
WITH EVIL HEARTS GOOD.
DO YOU GET IT NOW, BLOCKHEAD?
- I KEPT QUIET
ABOUT IT AT FIRST
BECAUSE IF I TOLD YOU WHAT
I KNEW, YOU'D BE AT RISK.
THINKING IN TERMS
OF GOOD AND EVIL
CAN BRING NEGATIVE EMOTIONS
TO THE SURFACE.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
THEY'VE TAKEN HOLD OF YOU.
"IF ONLY THAT PERSON
DIDN'T EXIST..."
"WHOSE FAULT IS IT
THAT I'M IN PAIN?"
"WHY DOES THIS
ALWAYS HAPPEN TO ME?"
THESE PESSIMISTIC THOUGHTS
ATTRACT NIRVANA
AND ALLOW IT TO TAKE CONTROL.
- WHAT THE--
( groans )
- I HAVE AVENGED YOU,
MY BELOVED SWEET LYON.
WHO SHALL BE
MY NEXT VICTIM?
PERHAPS ONE OF HIS FRIENDS,
ANOTHER MEMBER OF
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD?
- ( screaming )
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY!
- IT'S AS IF HE'S
BEEN POSSESSED!
- MONEY...
IS THE ROOT OF ALL EVIL.
OH YEAH.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU SAID
JUST A MINUTE AGO.
- YOU SEE, I'VE BEEN
DESPERATELY SEARCHING
FOR MY LONG-LOST
YOUNGER BROTHER.
AND I THOUGHT THAT IF
I ACCUMULATED ENOUGH MONEY,
I WOULD BE ABLE TO FIND HIM.
OH YEAH.
HOWEVER, NOW I REALIZE
HOW FOOLISH IT WAS OF ME
TO THINK THAT WAY.
I WAS WRONG.
- HUH?!
- JURA, WHY DON'T WE BURY
THE HATCHET AND BECOME FRIENDS?
OH YEAH.
THE WORLD AROUND US
IS OVERFLOWING WITH LOVE,
OH, YEAH, FULL TO BURSTING WITH
SUCH SWEETNESS AND COMPASSION.
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE
WHEN YOU HAVE
THE POWER OF LOVE
ON YOUR SIDE.
OH YEAH!
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE WORK TOGETHER
TO PUT AN END TO
MY FORMER COMRADES' PLANS?
WE MUST TEACH THEM THE WONDERS
OF PEACE, LOVE, AND HARMONY.
ARE YOU WITH ME?
- YEAH.
SURE.
- WHITE FURY!
( screams )
( grunts )
- ONE DOWN AND SEVEN TO GO.
MAN, HE'S SO MUCH
STRONGER THAN ME.
MY MAGIC'S
USELESS AGAINST HIM.
- HEY, YOU STILL ALIVE
DOWN THERE?
- ( groans )
( screams )
- I LOVE WATCHING
MY PREY SUFFER.
- SO WHENEVER NIRVANA
IS FULLY ACTIVATED,
EVERYBODY IN THE ALLIANCE
COULD SUDDENLY TURN EVIL?
- ONE QUESTION.
I UNDERSTAND THE PART ABOUT
IT TURNING US EVIL,
BUT DOES THAT MEAN
IT'LL TURN
THE DARK GUILD GUYS GOOD?
- IT'S POSSIBLE, BUT THERE'S
NO WAY OF KNOWING FOR SURE.
WHAT MAKES NIRVANA
TRULY TERRIFYING
IS THE FACT THAT
IT CAN BE CONTROLLED
TO DO WHATEVER
ITS CASTER SEES FIT.
- WHAT?
- I'LL EXPLAIN.
LET'S SAY THAT A WIZARD WAS
TO USE NIRVANA AGAINST A GUILD.
THEY COULD HAVE THE MEMBERS
START KILLING EACH OTHER
OR MAKE THEM GO TO WAR WITH
ANOTHER GUILD FOR NO REASON.
AND THEY'D BARELY HAVE
TO LIFT A FINGER.
- SERIOUSLY?!
- WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP IT AND FAST...
OTHERWISE THE LIGHT GUILDS
WILL BE WIPED OUT.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: I'M THINKING YOUR COLOR
WOULD BE RED, NATSU.
- HUH?  WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- WHAT COLOR DO YOU THINK
REPRESENTS YOU THE BEST?
I'D SAY RED 'CAUSE
YOU USE FIRE MAGIC.
AND GRAY SHOULD BE BLUE
BECAUSE HE USES ICE MAGIC.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I THOUGHT BLUE WAS YOUR COLOR,
LITTLE BUDDY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT!
BOTH OF US CAN'T BE BLUE!
( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: WHAT IF I SWITCH
TO SOMETHING COOL LIKE BLACK?
- NO, I THINK
THAT'S LUCY'S COLOR.
- YEAH, YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
SHE'S GOT THE BLACKEST HEART
OF ANYONE IN FAIRY TAIL.