[NATSU]
Previously, on Fairy Tail.
[CANA] We were in the middle
of the S-Class Wizard
Promotion trial,
held on Tenrou Island.
[LUCY] When Cana confessed
a major secret to me,
I swore that I'll do everything
I can to help her make S-Class!
[HAPPY] But then we found
Zeref on the island
and we were attacked by the
scary Grimoire Heart guild!
What kinda horrible thing
is gonna happen next?
♪
[NARRATOR] Equipped with the
potent Fairy Glitter spell,
Cana arrived with
seconds to spare.
She fought valiantly,
but was no match for
Grimoire Heart's sub-commander,
Bluenote Stinger.
The Fairy Tail members
found themselves at the verge
of utter defeat.
But hope arrived
in the form of Gildarts.
Cana's father and Fairy Tail's
strongest wizard.
[BLUENOTE] So this is
the legendary Gildarts.
[CANA]
Dad.
The old man came back!
[GILDARTS] You need
to get outta here.
What for?
[HAPPY]
Tenrou Tree!
That look on Gildarts
face is one of the most intense
things I've ever seen.
Yes.
I can definitely
agree with that.
Now go!
That's crazy!
Gildarts is so cool!
That hurt.
I think we should all
try to stay out of their way.
[HAPPY]
You okay, Carla?
I can barely hear you
with that rock on your face.
Unbelievable.
He pushed me back?
--[HAPPY] It's stuck!
--[CARLA] Ridiculous!
I'm getting scared.
I think we probably should
get away from here,
like he asked us to.
Yeah.
You're right.
Hey, Cana?
Let's go.
Gildarts can handle it.
We'd only get in his way
if we hung around.
Let's fly.
Awesome!
I wanna see 'em fight so bad.
No.
We gotta go Natsu.
Now!
[CANA]
Please.
Be careful, Dad.
[HAPPY]
Cana!
Hurry up!
[GILDARTS] You've interrupted
something very important.
These kids were
pushing themselves to the limit
working to make the world
a better place than what
we've left them.
They put absolutely
everything on the line
to salvage the future,
and then you came along
and trampled all over it.
Man, I can't believe
we're missing out on the fight
of the century right now!
Sorry, but making
sure our friends are okay
is more important!
Yeah, I guess.
Hopefully, the others
have found their way
back to base camp.
We need to regroup and
figure out our exit strategy.
Don't forget Mest...
I mean Doranbolt...
promised that he'd do his best
to help us get off the island.
Talk about a leaky vessel.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm alright.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, back at
what's left of the Fairy Tail
base camp, a few able-bodied
members have been attending
to those wounded in battle.
However,
a problem has arisen.
The Seven Kin of Purgatory
have come calling.
My name is Rustyrose.
I spy a feast of
dreams waiting to be devoured.
We need to
protect our friends with
everything we've got left.
There's no way
I'm gonna let another one of
these creeps hurt
my sister without a fight.
I'm afraid I can't stay
in my battle form
for that much longer.
We'll need to put
an end to this quickly.
[RUSTYROSE] Two young girls and
a cat guarding the infirmary?
Oh dear.
And here I was,
hoping to be involved in
a more epic battle.
Well, no matter.
This is the hand fate
has chosen for me.
So I shall play it.
Unencumbered by mercy!
I don't understand it.
How can you people
just be so cold-hearted?
Did you get to be the
strongest dark guild
by preying on the defenseless?
How is that supposed
to show your strength?
It must be done.
Those poor feeble souls would
never have a prayer of surviving
the Grand Magic World.
So we're simply helping
nature run its course
by speeding along
the inevitable.
You'll never
create an ideal world
by killing whoever you
think doesn't deserve it.
That's exactly what
the king was trying to do
in Edolas, and it didn't
work out for him.
Then you should use
your righteous convictions
to try and stop me!
For the most effective weapon
against darkness is the light
that you claim to wield!
What sounds!
Cries and Screams!
They provide such
a perfect soundtrack!
To the end of your dreams!
Who dares silence
my symphony?
It's Fried!
And Bixlow!
But how?
I thought both of you had left!
[BIXLOW] We saw the
red flare in the sky.
[FRIED] So we returned
with Gildarts.
He really came back
to the island with you guys?
Ha!
Though your ranks may swell
you'll still get swept away
by my Arc of Embodiment.
And all that will
remain of you will be
the ephemeral fragments
of tragically fading memories.
[BIXLOW] You're gonna
realize pretty quickly that
we don't always like to play
by the rules in our guild.
We'll do whatever
it takes to beat you.
[FRIED] Simply put, since
you've harmed a member of
the Thunder Legion the
rules no longer apply.
[BIXLOW]
Baryon Formation!
In my left hand,
appears a golden shield
through which no single
attack shall ever pass.
[RUSTYROSE] On my feet,
appear Pegasus' wings!
You cannot defeat
my rich imagination!
An eternal wellspring
of limitless power!
Come forth,
my Guardian Saint Beast:
Belfast the Windstorm!
May your mighty gusts sing
through their bones!
Where did that come from?
Summoning magic.
But like nothing
I've ever seen before!
Hey guys watch out!
He's really dangerous!
Oh, we know how
to handle this fool!
Seid Magic!
Possession!
[BIXLOW]
Shatter!
Impossible!
Dark Écriture.
Absolute Shadow!
Incredible!
They sure are!
That's our Thunder Legion.
Thanks, you guys.
[BIXLOW]
Get up!
[FRIED] There's nowhere
for you to run.
[RUSTYROSE] My very being is
wracked with erratic trembles.
Is this fear?
[NARRATOR] The Great
Tenrou Tree provides shelter
for this sacred island.
And among its twisted roots,
the warriors Erza and Azuma
are soon to entangle.
You're telling me
you've eliminated Wendy?
But she hasn't
fallen on her own.
Several of your comrades have
joined her and the rest are
all being dispensed
with as we speak.
[ERZA]
What nonsense!
There's no way you could
overpower Natsu, Mirajane,
and the others!
[AZUMA] I can't vouch for
this "Natsu" friend of yours.
But as for the She-Devil.
I sent her back to hell
with my own hands.
Do you doubt my words?
[ERZA]
Not entirely sure.
I'll have to test your abilities
myself to believe you.
Well, I can't
believe my luck.
First I faced the She-Devil.
And now the mighty Titania.
It's amazing.
What lovely trophies
for this day's hunt!
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere, Gray
is having a strange moment
with Grimoire Heart's Ultear,
who is revealing something
quite extraordinary.
This doesn't
make any sense.
You actually wanted to meet me
'cause you're really on my side?
[ULTEAR]
That's right.
I have been searching for
you for such a long time.
You are the beloved
pupil of the Ice Wizard, Ur.
And I am her
long lost daughter.
That means you and I are
practically siblings.
What, like brother and sister?
Give me a second
to process here.
I never knew I had a sister
just roaming around!
[ULTEAR] Well, I did
say "practically."
But, with that being the case,
I bear no grudge against you.
Seriously?
I'm having a hard time wrapping
my brain around all this.
You do realize our guilds
are sworn enemies!
It's true.
I've sworn allegiance
to Grimoire Heart.
But there's more
to life than guilds.
Perhaps we can get past
our differences.
We both share her guidance.
She lives on inside of us.
[LUCY] All of this fighting
on Tenrou Island was finally
nearing its conclusion.
We never lost faith.
We believed
wholeheartedly in our victory.
We still had hope.
[RUSTYROSE]
Fear pulsing through my veins.
Flooding my mind with
thoughts of impending doom.
Still.
It is I who has the advantage.
These racing
thoughts of fear
are like my fuel.
They serve to spur
my imagination.
Go forth, spirits of Brittia!
Dine on the souls of Fairies!
His summoning
power's insane.
Don't let those
things touch you!
[FRIED]
They're sticking to me!
[PANTHERLILY] He can make
anything in his imagination
come to life?
How can we fight against
someone like that?
This has gotta be
the most messed up magic
I've ever seen!
[RUSTYROSE]
Fried and Bixlow, was it?
Ah, yes.
Two members of the Thunder
Legion, if I'm not mistaken!
Or should I say two
underlings of Master Mahkarov's
disgraced grandson who was
ejected after a failed
overthrow attempt.
What was his name again?
Oh yes, Loxus, the fallen star.
[BIXLOW]
Shut your mouth!
[FRIED] How dare you even
speak his name, you scum.
You know nothing about him!
You bastard!
At last!
A true challenge appears!
[AZUMA]
Bleve!
[ERZA]
Morning Star!
Photon Slicer!
Does something amuse you?
[AZUMA]
Not quite 'amused'.
But I must admit I'm intrigued.
I've heard many tales
of your skill and valor.
I believe that you and I
are cut from the same cloth.
We seek warriors,
because fighting means
everything to us.
[ERZA] I'm afraid
that's not true.
I don't go looking
for warriors to fight.
[AZUMA]
No?
The only way you could reach
your level of strength
is fighting powerful foes.
All I have ever wanted is
the strength to protect those
I hold close to my heart.
I would give up all
of my strength if I could
still guarantee their safety.
It's strange, but true.
[AZUMA]
What a shame.
You're quite interesting.
I had hoped we'd
have a fair fight.
[ERZA] What do
you mean by that?
We've reached a
different stage in our battle.
What's happening?
I am connected with nature.
The forest.
My Lost magic
is the Arc of Trees.
I can take the
explosive power from the land
and channel it into
the heart of the wood.
But, where my magic's
true power lies is it gives me
the ability to become one
with the land and control
its magic energy.
You can control the
energy of the land itself?
[AZUMA] That is the reason I was
first to arrive on this island.
To harness the magic energy
contained in your sacred ground!
[ERZA]
No.
That's impossible!
This was not my choice.
But I must follow
the orders I was given.
[ERZA]
What?
What are you going to do?
Answer me!
[DORANBOLT]
No.
The Tenrou Tree.
It's falling!
Look!
It's coming down.
The whole island is collapsing!
It's that huge tree!
It's starting to topple over!
[DORANBOLT]
This can't be happening.
I should've forced them to
leave when I had the chance.
Wendy.
Natsu.
[DORANBOLT]
I wish you good luck.
[NATSU] What in
the heck is goin' on?
[HAPPY]
Please hurry, Carla!
[CARLA]
You're behind me!
We all gotta hurry
and get back to camp ASAP!
What the-?
[LUCY]
What's happening?
I feel like I just
ran outta juice.
My legs just quit working.
What's wrong with me?
So weak.
Hey.
What in the world is happening?
It's Azuma.
My power,
it's completely run out!
All at once.
What is it?
Oh no, Fried and Bixlow!
[RUSTYROSE laughing]
What a dramatic
reversal of fortunes.
The tide has turned again.
And The last
laugh will belong to me!
No.
I don't understand this.
What happened to our power?
[GILDARTS]
Damnit.
I'm totally out of energy.
What is this?
What the hell's going on here?
Old man.
What sort of insane mission
are you having Azuma
carry out for you?
[HADES] Quite the impressive
pawn Makarov has in Gildarts.
To think, someone other
than me could stop Bluenote
in his tracks.
if only for a moment.
Although it did take
a bit longer than I had
originally hoped.
Tenrou Island's magic power
is now under our control.
And with that, Fairy
Tail's chance of surviving
this battle disappears.
[AZUMA] Master Hades holds
a vast amount of knowledge
about this island.
Does he?
[AZUMA] At the center,
stands the great Tenrou Tree.
It blesses all who bear
the guild's emblem
with divine protection
from harm and death.
While at the same time, it
amplifies their magic power,
and gives them
extraordinary abilities.
[ERZA] So that's why master
chooses to hold the trial
on this island.
And you've
just felled the tree!
[AZUMA]
That is correct.
And as a result, not only has
this protective spell over
every Fairy Tail
wizard been nullified.
All of your magic
power will rapidly drain
from your bodies.
[RUSTYROSE] I must say this
is a vision of loveliness
before my very eyes.
If that's the case,
tell me this.
Why do I still stand?
[AZUMA] This may be
the end for your guild.
It will die,
along with that tree.
However.
Since I control all the
magic power on this island.
I've kept yours intact.
Now, Titania.
All of your friends
are at death's door.
And you are the only one
who can save them.
You strive for the power
to protect those close to you.
Show me what that means!
♪
[NATSU] Man, that's gotta be
the biggest freakin' tree
I've ever seen in my life!
What kind is it?
[HAPPY] It's called the
Tenrou Tree and I'm pretty sure
that it's the only one.
[NATSU] I bet it's probably the
strongest tree in the world,
dontcha think?
[HAPPY] I dunno, but it
looks pretty solid to me.
[NATSU] Yeah, well I wonder
if it would move if
I punched it really hard.
[HAPPY]
Please don't do that!
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: Erza vs. Azuma!
[HAPPY] Besides, if the tree
started moving and fell on you,
you'd be squashed
flat as a pancake!
[NATSU] Now why would
a tree just start movin'?
[HAPPY]
It was your idea, Natsu!