[ARCADIOS groaning]
No! Don't do it!
Are You tryin' to
get yourself killed?!
[ARCADIOS] I have no choice!
Well, I'll be.
I ain't never seen
someone that crazy.
[ARCADIOS] Climb up! Quickly!
But what about you?!
Don't worry
about me. Just go!
The two of you must survive!
Quit yapping!
We're safe, so get out!
[ARCADIOS] Please listen to me!
If you do manage to
leave this place alive.
You have to...
meet with Princess Hisui...
Seek her out.
[YUKINO] Take our hands! Please!
[LUCY] You have to
reach for us! Hurry!
You don't have to die like this!
Lucy...
He's willing to
throw away his life
so Lucy and Yukino can live?
It doesn't make
sense... My premonition...
can't come true if he dies!
The two of you
can decide...
if the Eclipse project
is what we need...
Please, don't!
Arcadios! Noooo!
[HAPPY] Scorching Earth!
But why...?
It's not fair...
I really am bad luck!
You should get away from me.
Don't say that...
[HOROLOGIUM] Saved
in the nick of time!
[BOTH gasp]
[HOROLOGIUM] Although.
I'm not sure how long
I can keep him in here.
It's a bit of a tight fit.
[LUCY] Horologium!
But how in the heck
did you get down here?
I'm not familiar with
this celestial spirit.
[HOROLOGIUM] Lady Lucy.
Would this be a case of
"out of the frying pan
and into the fire"?
[LOKE] It's about to
be for this sorry hick.
[UOSUKE] Hick?!
How's it goin', Lucy?
I thought you might
want your keys.
Loke!
Isn't that
Leo the Lion?
I see.
Those is spirits!
Huh.
Here. I have yours too.
Wow. I can't
thank you enough.
I'm sorry. It won't
happen again. I swear.
[LUCY giggles]
Aw yeah!
Now that they have their spirits
we can turn things around!
[UOSUKE] Them
keys is for spirits?
I think I get it now...
So ya'll two gotta be--
[LUCY] Your worst nightmare!
Both of them
have some really
powerful spirits
at their disposal!
That sorry fish thief's
in a heap o' trouble!
Hooo-wee!
Really?
I couldn't
help it, alright?
You ready?
All the Zodiac keys
are gathered as one.
You're in hot water.
Oh, fish-sticks!
[LEADER] You're a truly
light-footed lawbreaker.
A stark contrast to
the weight of your crimes.
[NATSU] Enough fancy
talk... By the way.
Those big swipes
of yours mean jack
if you can't hit
anything with 'em.
[LEADER] You can run
from your sins all you like,
but you can never escape them!
[LEADER] They are a part of you.
etched into the very fabric of
your soul and memories!
Hey! What the
heck are these?
Some sort of gropey magic?
[LEADER] They are
proof of your offenses!
You can never
wash clean of them!
Does your heart not ache
from such destruction?
[NATSU] Huh? So
what you're saying.
is that all those times I
crumpled cities on jobs
and got the Council's
undies in a wad.
Those were the
wrong things to do?
[LEADER] Of course they were!
Wha--? Get outta here!
[LEADER] Such impiety!
You are beyond forgiveness!
I shall behead
you where you stand!
Execution Technique:
Guillotine Justice!
Now what?
Too slow, jerk!
[LEADER] I told you before.
You can run from sin,
but you can never escape it.
It will relentlessly pursue
the marks on your flesh.
until justice has been served.
Reflect upon your
sins and despair.
[UOSUKE] Well. This
sitchi-ation's gone
haul-a crazy...
Thanks for the
save, Horologium!
Any time.
It was an exceptionally
close call, though.
[HAPPY] It's okay!
Looks like he's still breathing.
[CARLA] I'm impressed
that he even survived.
Let's serve up
some vengeance.
Prepare yourself!
Fish in a barrel!
Terrain Effect:
Gravity Zone!
[YUKINO] Open!
Gate of the Balance!
[YUKINO] Libra!
[LIBRA] Gravity Change!
Counter-balance!
What?!
[LIBRA] Counterbalance complete.
All right!
I like where
this is going!
[UOSUKE] You can't
just change the gravity!
Question: Why are humans
always such hypocrites?
[UOSUKE] Terrain Effect...
Gale Force Zone!
[ALL grunting]
Yeah! Gotta nice
view back here!
Stop looking!
[CARLA] Hold on!
[HAPPY] I hope his
belt is on tight!
[LUCY] Open! Gate
of the Maiden! Virgo!
[UOSUKE] Why can't I
catch a girl like that?!
Rough winds and a
burning pit just for me?
This punishment is
really a dream come true.
Thank you.
[LUCY] Yeah, I'm not
gonna touch that one.
And It's good to see
you again, Big Brother.
Why are you still
making her call you that?
I had no idea
they were related!
Trust me, they're not...
But it's way too
weird to explain.
Enough with the
yappin', y'all!
[LUCY] Do your thing, Virgo!
Then dig, I shall.
[LUCY] Get him!
[LOKE] Say no more!
[UOSUKE] The haul?!
[HAPPY] That's right, wind!
You stay up there!
It's much
safer down here.
[VIRGO] Princess, the
enemy seems to be dodging
Big Brother's attacks
without much effort.
Mr. "Hook and Rod" is
more nimble than he looks.
I suppose you
can't judge someone
by their appearance alone.
But I totally win
in that category.
I had enough of you
and your fish hole!
You're making me mad!
Then do something about it.
[UOSUKE] Terrain Effect:
Chill Zone!
[BOTH whimpering]
I'm freezing!
I'm so not
dressed for cold.
I got a feelin' you
misjudged the gravity
of the sitchi-ation.
[ALL gasp]
[LUCY] Oh no!
[LIBRA] Gravity Change!
Counter-balance!
[LUCY squeals]
[LOKE] Lucy!
[UOSUKE] Cod nugget!
[LUCY] Get me down
before I lose my cool!
[WENDY whimpers]
So sour...
[COSMOS giggles]
[COSMOS] That anguished
expression is simply precious.
I'll be kind and give you
a lovely demise, my sweet.
[COSMOS] Buried beneath
your most hated food,
you'll drift off to sleep
amid pain and suffering.
Let death's
warm embrace
gently lull you
into eternal slumber.
What?! No, please!
[COSMOS] Now, close your eyes.
Makura, kamura...
This is a
spell of death.
Once these spores
have put you to sleep.
The waking world is
forever lost to you.
Sweet dreams, darling.
Savor your final nightmare.
[COSMOS laughs]
[CROWD cheering]
[JET] Man...
The first master sure
knows her strategy.
[DROY] Yeah!
Taking first place
was easy as pie!
How'd we go from a girl
like her to an angry old man?
You talkin'
about yourself?
I think you guys have
some issues to work out.
I sense something.
[MAKAROV] What is it,
First Master?
Trouble?
I'm not quite sure,
but it's coming from deep
beneath the city of Crocus.
It's faint,
but I sense tremors.
and the clashing of magic power.
Do you think...
it's the rescue team?
[MAVIS] Most likely.
And they seem to be
fighting separately.
[LUCY] So cold!
[UOSUKE] Ha-ha!
What's the matter?
Those arms and legs
goin' numb on ya?
[LOKE] Don't worry!
I know just what to do!
A little
flesh-on-flesh contact
will keep your limbs toasty.
[LUCY] Go away!
Please, leave everything
to me, Princess.
An amusing dance
will raise your spirits
and chase away the shivers!
How's that gonna
solve anything?!
They're such lively
celestial spirits.
It's obvious how much
they care for you, Lucy.
You know they're
crazy, right?
All this dancing
has exhausted me,
so I'll be going now.
[LUCY] Oh. Thanks, I guess?
[YUKINO] My body is
almost completely numb...
and I'm getting sleepy.
We need to lift this spell
before we're popsicles.
I might regret this, but...
Open... Gate
of the Golden Bull!
[LUCY] Taurus!
[TAURUS] Moo...
[LUCY] Huh? What's
with the gloom, Taurus?
Did your milk go sour?
[TAURUS] I was primed and ready
to get a peek at that nice-bod
all hot and flushed
from the lava,
but now all I get
is a meat locker.
[LUCY] Ah. Geez!
But watching you hug
those udders to survive
is moooving in its own right!
[LUCY] Shut up!
Why don't you and your
new friend cuddle for warmth
while I send this
tool out to pasture?
[UOSUKE] You got some
interestin' spirits.
Is it because
you're so borin'?
[LUCY] That does it!
Alright, big guy, give
this loud mouth the horns!
Yes, ma'am!
When I'm done with him, I've
got a whole stampede's worth
of smooooches for you!
Watch your step!
[TAURUS grunts]
Runnin' on ice is just
askin' for an accident.
[TAURUS] My tenderloin...
[LUCY] That was
totally pathetic!
[UOSUKE] The jig's up!
Now, be good little minnows
and accept your punish--Wait.
Weren't there more of ya before?
[LOKE] Heads up!
[UOSUKE screams]
[LUCY] Yukino!
[YUKINO] Right! Now, Libra!
Use the ice chunks!
[LIBRA] As you wish.
Altering gravity
around the enemy.
[UOSUKE grunting]
[UOSUKE] I feel like a mackerel.
[CARLA] Way to go!
Nice combination!
[YUKINO] It's back to normal!
I wonder if he thinks
I'm "boring" after that!
Another baddy put down by
the sweet power of our love.
Let's take this "love"
thing down a notch, okay...?
[UOSUKE] Crim'nals.
Ya'll never know
when to quit, do ya?
[ALL gasp]
[UOSUKE] Now I'm mad...
And believe you me,
this is one pole slinger
ya'll don't wanna
be gettin' riled up.
[LUCY] Uh, weren't you
already mad to begin with?
[CROWD cheering]
[MALE SOLDIER A] Fairy
Tail's in the lead?!
[MALE SOLDIER B] Yeah,
but Sabertooth still has the
Twin Dragons out there,
so there's no telling
what'll happen.
Don't forget about
the Wizard Saint!
[MALE SOLDIER D] Or
that babe, Kagura!
It doesn't make
sense, though.
Why in the heck would Fairy Tail
try to force a prison break
when all they had to do
was win the tournament?
Who cares? Low-lifes
will do as low-lifes please.
[MALE SOLDIER C] What
about the Colonel?
[MALE SOLDIER D] No matter how
you look at it, he's a traitor.
Plain and simple.
[IRIKI] Princess. I've just
been handed an update...
The Hungry Wolf Knights have
begun Operation Fifteen Hundred
in the Palace of Perdition.
The lawbreakers
are resisting,
and combat is
ongoing at present.
I'm told they've moved
to five separate locations
on the lower level.
[MALE SOLDIER B] What
about their telepathy?
[MALE SOLDIER C] Already
taken care of.
All telepathy from
outside has been blocked.
I know His Majesty
is a fan of Fairy Tail,
but that doesn't mean
they're above the law.
[MALE SOLDIER C] Meanwhile,
that same guild is about
to win the tournament!
It's unreal!
What is... this thing?!
[PLUE squeaks]
[UOSUKE] Hello?
[UOSUKE] Fish, fish-fish!
Fish, fish-fish!
[HAPPY] He's
actually fallin' for it!
I guess silver keys
have their uses too, huh?
It's ust as I planned! Kind of.
Of course it is.
Fish! Fish! Fish! Fish!
Gravity Zone!
[LUCY screams]
You want seafood, huh?!
I'll just open the
Gate of the Giant Crab!
Cancer!
--Ca-rab!
--Baby!
Those pinchers are a little
on the small side though.
Unlike your hair.
You could use a trim, baby.
What's this?
A wild new do, baby.
So long!
And hunky
to boot, baby.
No.
But I think it
looks cute, baby.
[UOSUKE] Execution!
[CANCER] And I'm out!
Cancer!
Ya'll must think I was
born on the boat yesterday.
I know you're tryin' to buy
time for your injured friend.
It was worth
a shot, at least.
Aw man, he saw
right through that!
Who knew he'd
be so smart?
You're dealin'
with the
sharpest dang hook
in the tackle box!
Execution! Torment Zone!
[CARLA &amp; HAPPY scream]
What are these?!
Torture devices!
Help me, I'm stuck!
I'm a little
tied up here!
[LOKE] Hang in there!
[UOSUKE] Don't you
move a muscle!
You're more trouble
than a hole in a net...
Simmer down or
I'll give Beardy there
the closest shave of his life.
[LOKE] What do we do?
[LUCY] Whatever he says.
Aw. What's the matter?
You ain't got no more
magic critters to call up?
I guess he's got
us on the ropes.
Indeed, it's
quite annoying.
So, let's change that.
Open. Gate of the Scorpion!
Open. Gate of the Two Fish!
[LUCY] Scorpio!
[SCORPIO] Wicked!
Come, Pisces!
It's fishies!
Fresh eel!
I could eat for a
month on this puppy!
What an incredible haul!
Now, Scorpio!
[SCORPIO] Sand Buster!
Careful!
Easy!
Way to go! Nice work!
[SCORPIO] Wicked. I'll... just
be over here if you need me.
Yeah...
Huh?
Lucy! We're
A-OK over here!
[LUCY] Huh?
Oh, right! Thanks a lot!
[UOSUKE] I'm still here!
I done sailed currents
that'd give you nightmares!
Ya'll ain't never
gonna shake me off!
Ready?
Let's do it!
--Scorpio!
--Pisces!
[UOSUKE shouts]
[UOSUKE] Yee-haw!
[SCORPIO] Wicked!
[UOSUKE] I think I'm gonna hurl!
You must
strike quickly!
I'll hold him.
Loke!
Give him everything you've got,
but try not to hit Pisces, okay!
That's a tall
order. But for you?
I think I can whip up
a real crowd pleaser.
Here goes!
Regulus Impact!
Oh yeah! Right on target!
With a beautiful
attack, to boot!
That isn't
from my attack.
It's his doing!
[UOSUKE] Terrain Effect Plus:
Midnight Sun Zone!
I fought light with light!
I betcha didn't see that comin'!
[LUCY] Wait, you can do that?!
If that's the case, then
I'll use my own trump card.
[COSMOS] Having sour
dreams yet, sweetie?
You know,
out of all my
execution techniques,
this is my favorite by far.
And you're my
favorite... victim.
It's been a while
since I've executed
a lovely lawbreaker like you.
[WARREN grunts]
[MAKAROV] Any luck?
Judging by your face, I'd
guess the answer would be no.
That right?
[WARREN] Sorry about
this, Master...
But I don't understand
what's wrong.
Natsu's team was
going to Mercurius,
which isn't far from here.
So communicating with them by
telepathy should be a breeze.
This clashing magic
power that you sensed,
is it possible it's
beneath the castle?
It is.
So, why can't we
reach the team?
Maybe it's because
of that Eclipse thing!
It absorbs nearby
magic power, doesn't it?
[ALZACK] No.
If that was it, she
wouldn't sense them
fighting down there...
There must be another cause.
Who're they gonna fight
with that far underground?
The Sacred Blossom Cherry
Knights or whatever?
Don't forget, there's
also that Magic Unit...
Council dogs.
I can't imagine Natsu's team
having a hard time with them.
And if it was the Council, there
would've been a huge uproar
the moment they were spotted.
[ALZACK] Assuming they did
rescue Lucy and Yukino,
there's only one
possibility I can think of.
Though It's never
been made public.
There have been rumors
of an independent squad.
Hold on, you're
talking about
the executioners, aren't you?
You actually believe that?
No.
But many legends are
somewhat steeped in fact.
I don't know, after
finding out about
that Eclipse Project and all...
Anything could
be plausible, right?
For real?
So all this weird
telepathic interference...
could be coming from a
group of psycho knights?
It's a vexing situation.
but we can't afford to make any
rash decisions at the moment.
No, we can't.
All we can do is
wait and have faith.
[NATSU] How do ya like that?
Didn't even hit me once!
[LEADER] Such
mental fortitude...
You refuse to atone.
You refuse punishment.
Never before has there
been such a lawbreaker.
Ain't I a stinker?
So. Why don't you just
let me pass? Okay?
[LEADER] Like your comrades,
you will learn there is
no deliverance.
Surrender and join them
in the afterlife.
Yeah, right. Get real.
Nobody in Fairy Tail would ever
kick the bucket that easily...
So I know you're lyin.'
[LEADER] A lowly guild wizard
would dare defy the will
of the kingdom?!
After everything
you've done to my friends?
Yeah. I "dare to defy"!
And I'll do
it with gusto!
[LUCY &amp; YUKINO scream]
[YUKINO] Pisces!
[UOSUKE] The fish!
They vanished!
What the heck?!
What happened to them?
This is the
true form of Pisces...
A mother and her son.
There can be only one reason
that we'd be summoned like this.
Wiping out the enemy.
with style.
For a gal that's had a kid,
she's never lost that body.
I'm counting on you.
Right mama! We're on it!
[YUKINO] I'm not your mother,
you know that!
Amazing!
I kinda liked 'em better when
they were fish though...
Get serious.
Let's make quick work of him.
Okay?
Yes, ma'am. gladly.
[UOSUKE] Terrain Effect.
Hot Lava Zone!
[PISCES BOY] Be careful, mom!
Spicy eel stew,
comin' up!
No! Don't eat 'em!
[YUKINO] Are you sure
that you've got him?!
[LUCY] Careful!
[LOKE] Don't worry!
He's fine, just a little
on the heavy side.
Although...
I wouldn't mind holding the two
of you this close to my chest.
[LUCY] Just get going.
Why don't we cool
things off a little bit?
Beating the heat
sounds like a plan to me!
[UOSUKE] Ya'll done
put out my fire!
But how in the heck did
a little water do all that?
[PISCES MOM] Our magic power
is much stronger than yours.
[PISCES BOY]
Totally! By a long shot!
Am I still alive?
Question. Couldn't you
have just flown away?
Oh yeah...
Man...
This is really taking a
lot of power out of me...
[YUKINO] Let's give it one
final push; that should do it!
Yeah!
It's time to filet
this fishy freak!
Taurus!
[TAURUS] One moore time!
[UOSUKE yelling]
[TAURUS] Boom!
Did you see how udderly
cool I was, Miss Lucy?
[HAPPY] You go, cow!
May I ask what
you're doing?
[HAPPY] My butt feels amazing.
Seriously Carla, the
ground is so toasty and warm;
you should give it a try!
Uh-huh...
[UOSUKE] I've had it up to
here with those critters!
Terrain Effect Magic:
Whirlpool Zone!
Oh... yeah.
Do you hear something?
[BOTH screaming]
[UOSUKE] I'll flush ya'll
out like my chili gumbo!
The current
is too strong!
Stay tough
and fight it!
[BOTH scream]
[TAURUS] I was made
for dry land.
Water rides make me
feel like yakkin'!
[HAPPY] They're fish again!
How could he possibly
know that Pisces
has a weakness to water?
That doesn't
make any sense!
[LOKE] Lucy! Are you
okay down there?!
[LUCY] I think so!
I dunno what you're up to.
I didn't take any damage,
and the water's too
shallow to drown in.
Are you just
trying to soak us?
[UOSUKE] Take a gander
at them whirlpools!
If ya let 'em suck
you in, you'll be sent
to another place entirely!
What kind of "place"
are we talking about?
Uhhh...
[LUCY] You mean you don't even
know what your attack does?!
[UOSUKE laughs]
[UOSUKE] This is it, Crim'nals!
You'll be sleepin'
with the fishies
'till the cows come home!
[LUCY] What the--?
Oh yeah! Water!
That's all I need!
Oh no!
Lucy's about to summon
the fish-lady spirit!
I thought
you liked fish!
[LUCY] Open...
Gate of the Water Bearer!
Huh?
[LUCY] Aquarius!
[AQUARIUS growls]
[HAPPY] We're unstoppable
now that Lucy and Yukino
have their zodiac keys back!
[NATSU] All right!
Now, we just gotta
thrash these guys!
[HAPPY] Aye!
But don't forget, we need one
of 'em to tell us the way out!
[NATSU] Oh yeah, we can't
afford to be stuck here forever!
[HAPPY] That's it, Natsu!
Get to roastin'!
[NATSU] Boy, did these
suckers pick the wrong guild
to mess with!
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
Our Place!
[NATSU] We'll take on
the kingdom, the world,
or anyone else to
help our friends!
That's the Fairy Tail way!
[HAPPY] You can do it, Natsu!