Ugh, my stomach wants
to jump right out of my body.
So, you're sure
Natsu will be okay?
Why wouldn't he?
It's just motion sickness.
Stop worrying and
let him get some rest.
[LUCY] What about Wendy?
[PORLYUSICA]
She's coming along nicely.
At least you're
up now, Carla.
How're you feeling?
[CARLA] Fine.
I'm so glad to hear that.
The others are waiting,
so I'll check back later 'kay?
You're not going
to say anything to her?
I just don't think it
would do any good.
They'd never believe me.
Not about a future
like that, anyway.
[CARLA] I saw Mercurius
come crashing down.
And, as it happened, I thought
I heard someone singing.
Lucy.
♪
[NARRATOR] Natsu
and friends have entered
Fiore's annual
Grand Magic Games.
They barely made it
out of the Sky Labyrinth
to finish eighth in
the qualifying round.
But it was enough to secure
their spot in the tournament!
[NARRATOR] Now the
real contest is underway!
Day one began with "Hidden",
followed by
one-on-one matchups.
But Natsu's team met with
total defeat in both rounds,
netting them zero
points for the day.
[NATSU] Zero points?
Sounds great to me.
This is our chance to
make an epic comeback.
Yeah.
I'm fired up now.
[NARRATOR] They got on
the scoreboard on day two,
collecting two points on the
fast and furious
game "Chariots."
After that, it was time
for another round of battles.
Ultra-Poison Nails!
Mega-Mega Jellyfish!
He just vanished!
[BLACKSNAKE] Sand Rebellion!
[Toby howls]
You're stronger than
I thought you were!
[BLACKSNAKE]
You're not so bad yourself.
[TOBY] I wish I had a cool
name like Blacksnake!
[BLACKSNAKE]
It's just my wizard name.
[TOBY] You mean you lied to me?
[BLACKSNAKE]
What are you talking about?
[TOBY] Alright!
Then, if I beat you, you gotta
tell me what your real name is!
Deal?
[BLACKSNAKE] I'm fine with that.
But what if I win?
[TOBY] Then I'll tell
you my super-special
secret that nobody knows!
[BLACKSNAKE] Sounds intriguing.
It's a deal!
Our competitors seem to
have struck a friendly wager.
I wouldn't consider
their secrets a prize.
Cool!
A little gambling? This
could make things interesting.
[TOBY] Nails! Nails! Fangs!
Psyche! Nails!
Come on dog, I've got a hundred
jewel ridin' on this one!
[CHAPATI]
The dust has settled, and we
can clearly see
Toby on the ground!
That's it folks!
[CHAPATI] Blacksnake
slides away with
another win for Raven Tail!
[ERZA] Very impressive.
[GRAY] No doubt.
And I got the feelin'
that he was holdin' back.
Not only will those
guys cheat to win,
they have real
power on their team.
[CHAPATI] Look at
the scoreboard and you'll
see Raven Tail fiercely
climbing to the top.
Now at thirty-six points.
And Lamia Scale at twenty.
[JASON] Cool!
[BLACKSNAKE] Now.
You owe me a secret.
[TOBY] It's my sock.
It just disappeared, man.
It's driving me
crazy cause I
feel like it's just
right under my nose.
But I just can't seem
to find it anywhere.
[TOBY] I'm so ashamed.
[TOBY] I've been keeping
it to myself for months now.
Has it really
been right here all along?
[TOBY] I don't know
how to thank you.
[TOBY] I'm just so
happy to see it again.
[CHAPATI] Have you ever seen
anything like this before?
[YAJIMA] Thankfully, no.
[JASON] Such emotion!
What an ending!
What a good boy.
I'm so happy for him.
This is way too
stupid to cry about!
Uh. Wha--?
I'll spin you.
[CHAPATI] What is this?
After fighting fang and claw,
are these two gonna shake hands?
[CHAPATI] Guess not!
[TOBY] No!
[CHAPATI]
Adding insult to injury,
Blacksnake rips up
the prized possession!
[BLACKSNAKE]
You should never have told me
how much that
stinking rag meant to you.
Dumb move.
You there!
Spin for me!
[LAMIA SCALE MEMBER 162A]
Why me!
[EVERGREEN] What is his problem?
That was completely
uncalled for!
Once again Raven Tail
is showing their true colors.
Well, what else
would you expect?
These are the kind
of people that would
work for a creep like Ivan.
The poor dog
guy was already beat.
That was just mean.
[CHAPATI]
Let's move on to round two
of today's head-to-head battles!
First, from Quatro Cerberus,
it's the god of wine, Bacchus!
[BACCHUS] Yeah!
[CHAPATI] Fighting a member
of Team Fairy Tail A!
So it's one of us.
But what if they call
out Natsu's name?
Then we wake him up.
I've heard stories
about this guy.
He's supposed to be
as strong as Erza isn't he?
Fight!
Someone avenge me!
I don't care who it is!
Oh my.
Relax Cana.
I'm sure that Gray
could get the job done!
[MATO] Very nice.
You've done precisely
as I'd requested.
Yes, my lord.
[MATO] Such an exquisite
pairing. Bacchus's wild spirit
against the graceful
power of Erza Scarlet.
[MATO] Problem?
[ARCADIOS]
Forgive me your majesty,
but did you say Erza?
I'm sorry, but I arranged
for a different fighter.
[CHAPATI] Elfman Strauss!
[ELFMAN] Me?
That's not her!
It's Elfman's turn?
Is he even ready?
Well we're screwed!
Hey, don't be mean to him!
You've got this one.
Believe in your heart
that you can win and
victory will be all yours.
Uh, yeah.
[HAPPY] Elfman vs. Bacchus!
[MATO] You incompetent fool!
I had wanted to see Bacchus
do battle with Erza!
[ARCADIOS]
My deepest apologies, my lord.
[MATO] How about
that Fairy Tail member?
The one that can transform!
Darn it, what was the name?
El--
I've failed.
[MATO] This will not be
a match, but a slaughter.
Bacchus will make
easy work of this novice!
[ARCADIOS] Yes, indeed he will.
[MALE SPECTATOR 162B]
You can do it, Fairy Tail!
Yeah?
Because I'm not
too sure about that.
[BACCHUS] Hey, whaddaya
say we make our own bet?
Like those last guys did.
[ELFMAN] What?
Your sisters are a couple
of smokin' hot little numbers.
[ELFMAN] So what's your point?
[BACCHUS] Come on man,
I know you can't be that dense.
If I win the match, they
keep me company tonight.
Both at the same time.
Scumbag.
[HAPPY] Both of them?
That is seriously messed up.
What nerve!
[BACCHUS] Now it's your turn.
If you win.
[ELFMAN] Listen pal.
A real man doesn't tolerate
that kind of disrespect.
So get ready.
To get schooled.
So I reckon that means you
accept this little wager, do ya?
I'm so excited I got the shakes.
I slept like a log!
[NATSU] What's the deal?
Hello?
That's weird.
Did they all take
off or something?
[NATSU] Somebody
else was in here.
I can smell 'em.
[NATSU] This way!
[NATSU] Hey, you!
[MALE BANDIT 162A] Oh crap!
It's that guy from Fairy Tail!
[MALE BANDIT 162C]
We must've woken him up!
[NATSU] Stop right there!
You're not taking
them anywhere, ya hear?
[MALE BANDIT 162A] Run!
[MALE BANDIT 162B] Hurry!
I told you to stop!
[MALE BANDIT 162B]
He's crazy fast!
[MALE BANDIT 162C] What?
After seeing him
in that last game,
I didn't think
he could run at all!
[MALE BANDIT 162D]
I got this!
Let's see if he
can outrun a bullet!
Get outta my way!
Come back here!
I won't let you take Wendy!
[MALE BANDIT 162A]
He's catching up!
[MALE BANDIT 162B]
This guy is insane!
We need to get the lead out!
[MALE BANDIT 162C]
What do we do?
[MALE BANDIT 162A]
We gotta dump these other two!
[MALE BANDIT 162B] You idiot!
We're supposed to grab
the girl in the infirmary!
[MALE BANDIT 162A] But this old
broad and the cat ain't girls!
[MALE BANDIT 162B]
Then why did we grab 'em?
[MALE BANDIT 162C] Well,
they're all technically females.
[MALE BANDIT 162B]
They ain't no girls though!
Who hired you to do this?
[MALE BANDIT 162B]
We're doomed!
[CHAPATI] I've seen
plenty of one-sided matches
in my day but this
is just embarrassing.
Did Elfman come to lose?
I am gonna have
a wild time tonight.
Oh yeah.
No.
This is horrible!
This guy is way
more on your level, Erza.
Yes.
And unfortunately,
he's just getting started.
Get up Elfman.
Don't worry.
Your brother never fails
to come through in a pinch.
Yeah.
You're right.
Woo!
Get him, big guy!
Beast Soul; Weretiger!
This take over should
increase his speed.
But he still hasn't
landed a single attack.
What are we boys?
[ALL] Wild!
[GRAY] Elfman may be faster.
But that speed doesn't
do him any good if
he can't hit his target.
It's all because of
the weird way that guy moves.
Surprisingly enough.
It's a part of an
extremely rigorous technique.
One that focuses
magic into his palms.
[ERZA] He's very methodical.
He uses this power in
conjunction with
a specific style of
martial art he's mastered
known as "Chop-Hanging Palm."
This particular
style specializes
in devastating palm strikes.
All delivered from that
unique stance he's taking.
[GRAY] I see what you mean.
[ERZA] But Bacchus has
taken this all a step further.
He's modified it to create
his own method of fighting.
One that he calls
"drunken chop hanging palm."
He's. Drunk?
This dude get hammered
when he fights?
[ERZA] That's right.
The "drunken hawk's"
moves are unpredictable.
The alcohol also
increases his destructive
power and dulls
his sensitivity to pain.
[ERZA] But that's not
the issue Elfman's facing now.
[ERZA] The problem.
Is that he hasn't had
a drop to drink yet.
A rare technique.
The chop-hanging
palm is quite obscure.
And now all our
fans watching can say
they've seen it with
their very own eyes!
What a great moment
in the history of cool!
I think I've already seen it!
So that explains the craziness
that went down at the bar.
Man.
Do ya think Elfman's
gonna pull this one out?
I think he's got it in him.
He's got way more than
size working in his favor.
Yeah, you're right.
All of us need to
keep on believing in him.
What are we boys?
[ALL] Wild!
Elfman get up!
Bacchus relies
on his liquor to keep
his moves erratic
and super powerful.
But he hasn't even
touched the bottle
that he's got down in the arena.
[LUCY] He's sober?
[GRAY] Which means
he's hardly even trying.
[CHAPATI] Whoa!
His takeover has worn off!
Looks like he's back to
being just a beast of a man.
That'll cost him a tremendous
amount of magic power.
Not a good combination with
all the damage he's taken.
[JASON] What an awesome fight!
Oh man.
I can't wait.
[CHAPATI] Is that it?
Is Elfman down for the count?
Sorry folks, but I forgot
to mention something earlier.
Mato, beloved mascot
and referee of the
Grand Magic Games, could
not attend today's events.
So I will be serving
as day two's honorary referee!
Oh?
Cool!
The plot twists are
totally unstoppable today!
Couldn't make it?
What?
Couldn't they've just thrown
some other schmuck in the suit?
It's not a suit, he's a
real-live talking pumpkin!
[BACCHUS] Ah.
Back on your feet.
All your howling about being
a man ain't just for show.
[ELFMAN] Listen up, you dog.
I never told you what I wanted.
[BACCHUS] Huh?
Our bet.
What I want you to do if I win.
[BACCHUS] This is
gonna be the only time
this comes up, so go ahead.
Tell me what happens if you win.
I want you.
And the rest of your Guild bros.
To go by the
name "Quatro Puppy."
[ALL] What?
Funny.
But do you think
he'll agree to that?
It is pretty silly.
It's hilarious!
And I think it suits
them way better!
[BACCHUS] Okay, okay.
You got yourself a deal!
[BACCHUS] Last call!
He's guzzling now!
That's right.
So he's serious.
No way!
[CHAPATI] Here we go!
It's happening folks.
Bacchus downs
some "fighting fuel!"
Drunken Style.
Eh?
Wow,
I wanna try some too!
Cool brew!
[BACCHUS] Hit me
with your best shot.
Should be easy to knock down
a wobbly ol'
drunk like me, right?
Take over beast soul!
[BACCHUS] It's pointless!
So many hits!
And they all happened so fast.
Oh wow.
It's like he turned himself
into a gigantic blur.
[ERZA THINKS] Seven strikes
in the blink of eye!
That's unreal.
All those hits must have
caused quite a bit of damage.
Yes.
But look.
[Bacchus laughs]
Feel that?
[BACCHUS] What in the hell?
He got me?
[CHAPATI] Uh oh!
Bacchus may
have double vision,
but he didn't
see that one coming!
What are you?
Lizardman.
I can't hit you, but go
on and hit me all you want.
[ERZA THINKS] It's his
own version of armor.
Hold on...
that's crazy.
I don't know if that
strategy is gonna work.
He's like a
scaly punching bag.
He's making a big gamble.
And there's nothing we can do.
Just sit back
and watch it happen.
[ELFMAN] All right, bring it on!
Go nuts and hit me
with everything you've got!
I wanna see you rip those puny
little arms of yours to shreds!
Man.
This guy is wild.
I sure hope Elfman
knows what he's doing.
It's so reckless.
I know that thick,
scaly, lizardman skin
and all those spikes
would be tough for a barehanded
fighter to get through.
But still.
[JUVIA] Bacchus is much stronger
than your everyday opponent.
What, are ya scared?
I like your style, man!
You know how to
get my blood pumpin'!
Be a man!
[CHAPATI] And the
blows come raining down!
This is more
than a simple fight,
but an ultimate
showdown of wills!
[CHAPATI] Will Bacchus
wear himself out?
Or will the barrage prove
too much for Elfman?
[CHAPATI] It's too close!
I just can't call it!
Who will be left standing!
[BACCHUS]
Your name's Elfman?
[Bacchus laughs]
That's right I'm wild!
[ALL] Wild!
No.
He lost?
[CHAPATI] He may be shaky,
but Bacchus has
risen to his feet!
[BACCHUS] I gotta tell ya, pal.
You--
Are a real man.
[CHAPATI] And Bacchus is down
like a sack of drunken potatoes!
[CHAPATI] The winner is Elfman!
From this victory, Team Fairy
Tail A scores ten points.
Which brings their total into
the double digits with twelve!
[ALL] Aw man!
[Elfman roars]
[CHAPATI] Is this manly roar,
the sound of
Fairy Tail's resurrection?
What an upset!
Elfman beats the odds
and snatches victory
from the jaws of defeat!
Yeah!
Hear that?
It's amazing!
Yay Elfman!
Now child.
Shouldn't you
get back in bed?
I'm fine.
And it's all thanks
to Grandeena.
Didn't I tell you not
to call me by that name?
So, Natsu.
About these hoodlums.
[MALE BANDIT 162D]
We were just doing a job!
That's all!
[MALE BANDIT 162B] Yeah,
for somebody in Raven Tail!
[MALE BANDIT 162C] We
were supposed to bring 'em
the girl that was
in the infirmary!
[IRIKI] Sure you were.
They can tell us all
about it at headquarters.
Raven Tail is gonna pay.
Who was there.
Past tense.
That seems weird.
[PORLYUSICA]
There was one before you.
Natsu brought her in.
[WENDY]
They're going after her?
Lucy?
There are more rounds to go.
But this win may give us the
momentum that
we've been looking for!
[IRIKI] I'm afraid the
operation was a failure.
[ARCADIOS] You idiot!
Did you not tell them
what their target looks like?
How else could they
have taken the wrong girl?
[IRIKI] My apologies, sir.
[ARCADIOS] No matter.
We do have a plan B
to fall back on.
What has become
of the kidnappers?
[IRIKI] We've taken
them all into custody, sir.
[ARCADIOS] Ignorant
to the truth, I hope.
[IRIKI] Yes sir.
They still believe
that they were
hired by the Raven Tail guild.
[ARCADIOS] Luckily, we can
use the rivalry between
Raven Tail and
Fairy Tail to our advantage.
And when the opportunity arises,
we will have a celestial
wizard in our possession.
To use in the Eclipse project.
[PORLYUSICA] What's wrong?
Why that ghastly expression?
[NATSU] Raven Tail's dirty
tricks are really making me mad.
Me too.
Isn't their master
a relative of Makarov?
Yeah.
His son.
Laxus's dad.
[PORLYUSICA] What does
that have to do with this?
[NATSU] I don't know.
But it is definitely personal.
♪
[HAPPY] Whoa!
The next round is gonna be a
beauty contest between
Mirajane and Jenny!
[NATSU] Can anyone else compete?
[HAPPY] I don't know,
but there is a swimsuit round.
Seeing girls in
swimsuits really doesn't
do anything for me
because I'm a cat!
[NATSU] Is that so?
Hold on,
Carla's in her swimsuit!
That does not leave
much to the imagination!
[HAPPY] What?
For real?
I gotta see this!
[NATSU AND HAPPY]
Next time: Mirajane vs. Jenny!
[HAPPY] Work it kitty!
Shake that fluffy tail for me!
[NATSU] I'm kidding, it's just
Mira. And we've all seen that.