[ALZACK] Oh,
here you are.
Hey, hon...
So what book is
she readin' today?
"Key of the
Starry Heavens".
Yeah... She was
telling me she wanted
to help the guild...
so I let her borrow it
from the cathedral's library.
Momma?
[ASCA] Is that really how
the book is s'posed to end?
[BISCA] Yeah, that's it.
[ALZACK] Is there
something wrong?
♪
[KINANA] Master...
What's wrong?
You seem a little down.
Nothin'. Just thinkin',
that's all.
Yeah right, you're worried
about Romeo- admit it!
Alright, I am!
But I'm his dad--
what do you expect?!
There's no need
to worry, man.
The kid's got Natsu with him.
Yeah that's what
scares me. I mean...
I don't want my boy
ending up like him.
[nervous laugh]
[NATSU] Check it out, Romeo!
He's tryin' to act all high
and mighty while
sittin' on an octopus!
[giggles]
I wouldn't laugh...
He held his own against
Gildarts, remember?
[NATSU] Yeah, yeah,
he's powerful. Who cares?!
He's ridin' a giant
freakin' octopus!
[laughs]
[HAPPY] Natsu's turned into
a jerk of a role model.
That makes me worry
about Romeo's future!
[NATSU] Wait, that means
if I beat this guy...
Then it's kinda like
I'm beatin' Gildarts, too!
I'll destroy you.
[HAPPY] The Course
of the Holy War!
[NATSU] Aw man, that
is some dangerous ink!
[HAPPY] Be careful, Natsu!
[MICHELLE] Ooh I want
squid ink risotto...
[LUCY] Let's save
the cravings for later!
[NATSU] Get back I got an
idea! Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
What now...?
I dunno... what I should do...
[LUCY] Coco!
[OCTOPUS growls]
[LUCY] Look out!
Ow. Are you
all right?
I think that'd
be seven points.
[gasps]
Is Dan okay?!
Yeah... See?
[NATSU] Hey, Octo-punk!
Are you so stupid
that you don't even know
who's on your side?!
[LUCY] Seriously! Coco and Dan
are supposed to be your allies!
I realize that
but, as proud members
of the Legion Platoon,
they are prepared to sacrifice
their very lives
to win this holy war.
"Holy war" my butt!
You don't have any right
to speak for her;
she's not your slave!
She doesn't belong
to you, or Zentopia,
or anyone else! She can
make her own decisions!
[BYRO] You're in no position
to chastise my actions.
You fail to grasp the
severity of the situation.
There are many more
lives at stake in this war
than you realize.
[MARY] It's like, resonating.
I better take off with it
before things get crazy.
[ELFMAN] No, I won't let you!
Come fight me like a man!
No thanks...
but I'll watch some
brother-sister rivalry.
That's not what
it's called, genius.
[MARY] 'Scuse me?
A rivalry between
brothers and sisters
is actually referred to
as a "sibling rivalry".
[ALL] Oooh!
Wait!
I'm not gonna let you,
like, distract me.
I'm takin' that freakin'
clock piece right now!
Tell me, why are
you doing this?
Why? I have,
like, no idea, lady.
All I know is that everything's
gonna work out as long as we
do what the archbishop says!
Huh?
If you're only doing
what you're told...
...then you're nothing
more than a puppet!
[MARY] Ya don't say.
Well, then...
In that case I'll totally
make you a puppet, too!
[desperate, demonic scream]
[ELFMAN] What's
she doing to you?!
[LISANNA] Mira!
[MARY] Conducting Art:
Second Movement!
I'm not supposed to
use this technique
but I'll totes make
an exception for you!
[pained scream]
[LISANNA] Something's
coming out of her body!
[ELFMAN] It's
her Satan Soul!
Mira, no!
What'll we do?!
[laughs]
Let's see how far you can
take this "sibling rivalry"!
[demonic breathing]
[LISANNA]
No, not us!
[ELFMAN growls]
[ELFMAN] Beast Soul!
[MARY] This is so
freakin' awesome!
Oh no?! How're we
gonna get out of this?!
[MARY] This is, like,
the greatest thing ever!
Anyone who dares to defy
the archbishop is totes bad!
And all bad people have,
like, gotta be punished!
[DROY] That fight
between you and Sammy
was somethin' else, Lily!
[JET] Yeah, I've never seen
two Exceeds go at it before.
It was nuts.
There's so few
of you guys around,
it's a shame you
can't all be friends.
[PANTHERLILY] He's a rather
impertinent fellow, I'm afraid.
While we're
on the subject...
Yeah, what's
the big deal?
Why has Sammy
been following us?
Because he's a
stubborn fool.
I am not a fool and
I am not following you...
I am merely observing you.
Just so we're clear,
you're not getting'
your hands on
this clock face!
The truth is, according
to my calculations,
it makes no difference
whether or not I'm the one
who retrieves it.
[PANTHERLILY] What's
that supposed to mean?!
I can't say with
utter certainty but...
"Brother"...
May I have a moment?
[ERZA] Oh, look...!
There's a table up ahead
that's practically begging
us to take a break!
[WENDY] Sounds good to me!
Wanna go ahead and have
lunch while we're stopped?
[CANA] Yeah, that's fine
with me, I guess...
But why're we wearing
these ridiculous
Butt Jiggle Gang uniforms?!
More importantly,
why do we happen to have
one in my size?!
"Preparation is salvation!"
[CARLA] What in the world could
we possibly be preparing for?!
I think this might
help you overcome the trauma
you've experienced, Carla.
[WENDY] I dunno how this'll
help but it is kinda fun!
[CANA] I'm a little
disturbed that you guys
are so into this...
Listen up!
If we're going to make
a second attempt at the
first picnic of our lives...
then both our minds and our
bodies need to be as one!
Yeah whatever
you say...
I'm scared to have
another picnic!
I don't blame you after
what happened on our
last attempt. Things didn't
really work out in our favor.
Now... let's dig in, ladies!
[BOSS] Don't even
think about it, hussy!
Get lost! This place
is our picnic spot!
Hey anyone
want some mayo?
[surprised gasps]
Kay, Lackey A and Lackey B!
Let's teach these twerps
a lesson and smother 'em
with our jiggly jumblies!
[BOTH] We're ready
to rumble, Boss!
[BOSS] Your itty bitty
titty committee...
[LACKEY B] ...Can't handle
our boobiferous brawn!
[BOSS] Y'know, your
bazongas would be bigger
if you'd quit
dieting the fat away!
[LACKEYS] Yeah,
just look at us!
Our mantra is,
"You gonna eat that?"
[BOSS] We know a thing or two
about fun bags 'cause...
[ALL]
We're the Jugs Jiggle Gang!
No way! They've
got bigger boobs
than me and
they're men?!
[shocked gasps]
[BOSS] You can't just
barge into our territory;
there are rules, y'know!
[LACKEY A] Rule number one: is
skinny girls can't picnic here!
[LACKEY B] But I'd be happy
to share my mayo with you!
[CANA] Look out you guys, I
think Erza's about to explode...
[ERZA] I even put another
flower in my hair!
[BOSS] You broke the rules
so give up the food!
[LACKEY A] There's
too many veggies!
Where's the meat and cheese?!
[LACKEY B] Hey,
anyone want mayo?
[CARLA] Don't blame us for
what's about to happen.
How dare you do this
to me? I'm going to make
you pay for ruining our second
attempt at my first picnic!
Huh?
I said I'd share
my mayo with you!
Prepare yourselves!
Come forth...
Spectral Sword:
Crimson Blossom!
You three are
about to learn
a very important lesson.
Just because you're bigger
than someone doesn't mean
they can't destroy you!
[LACKEY B] No!
I'll give you my mayo!
[JUGS JIGGLE GANG
yell and groan]
Can't say I didn't
try to warn them...
[MIRAJANE] Elfman...? Lisanna?
[gasps]
[LISANNA cries out]
Let me go!
[gasping]
Lisanna!
[MARY laughs]
[MARY] That was fun...!
But I don't wanna play
with you guys anymore...
I'll like totally put you
out of your misery
before I go, though.
Tell me...
do you enjoy it?
Hurting others like this?
[smirks]
Honestly, I do
'cause it proves I'm not
the helpless loser I used to be.
[MIRAJANE]
Huh?
[MARY] Now that I'm powerful,
the only thing I gotta worry
about is wiping out anyone
who opposes the archbishop.
It's a shame you're
defying Zentopia
'cause it's like, a major sin...
and all sinners must die!
Just try it!
Whatcha gonna do? You're
helpless now that
my Sacred Baton has
control of your powers.
This is the end of the line!
Bye-bye Fairy Tail wizard!
[MARY] Who knew
she was so strong?
I think I might've
overdone it a little bit.
[gasps]
Uh-oh. We've got
trouble now.
Calm down, Mira!
Don't let it take over!
Stay in control!
No way, that's
impossible!
No one told me she has
another Satan Soul!
You'd think they would've,
like, warned me!
I don't understand,
what's happened to her?!
This is bad... We've
gotta get outta here
while we can.
[ELFMAN] That form is
different from a Satan Soul.
The reason you've never seen it
before is because our master
forbade her from using it.
It's known as...
the Demon God Halphas!
[NATSU screams]
Your tentacles
are so heavy!
[NATSU cries]
[NATSU] No! Don't shoot,
Octo-scum!
You're lucky I got
here when I did
or your loud-mouth friend
would be a goner!
I knew I could
count on you!
Hey, what in the heck
do you think you're doing?!
You summoned me from a puddle?!
Sorry! But that's
all I could find!
Thank you, Lucy and...
uh... Aquarium?
[AQUARIUS] It's Aquarius!
[HAPPY] Cool! It's
like Natsu fishing!
I'm willing to let
you off the hook for
the puddle thing if you'll
do me a little favor...
Would you please hurry up and
figure out how to summon two
Celestial Spirits at once?!
I might be nicer to you
if I had my man Scorpio's
around... Well...?!
Whoa... I thought
she was called here
to help Lucy, not
threaten to hurt her.
[NATSU] Hey Romeo...! ya think
ya can get his mouth open?
[ROMEO] Yeah, just leave
it to me! Purple Net!
[NATSU] Alright!
Fire Dragon...
It looks like he's
gonna blast fire
down the
octopus' mouth!
But isn't that
kinda cruel?!
Oh I bet it's
going to taste
delicious freshly-grilled!
Well, She doesn't
seem to think so.
How terribly naïve...
Kanaloa is a veteran warrior
just like me.
[BYRO] Such childish tactics
aren't going to work.
He's got Natsu!
We've gotta save him!
[LUCY] Oh no, he's getting sick!
[BYRO] It would appear
that victory is ours...
Let's go, Kanaloa.
We have what we need.
[LUCY] Hold it right there!
My father left that clock hand
to me which makes it mine!
It's the only thing I
have to remember him by!
You don't have any
right to take it!
What's so important
about these clock pieces
that you would go to such
lengths to steal them?
[BYRO] We are not
stealing them...
We are taking them
into our care.
[LUCY] What's that
supposed to mean?
We're gathering these
pieces because they belong
to the Infinity Clock.
The Archbishop of Zentopia
has demanded that
we retrieve them... We're
simply following his orders.
The Infinity Clock...?
What could the
Archbishop possibly want
with such a thing?
[ARCHBISHOP's voice]
"Time ticks forward...
on toward inevitable chaos."
[ARCHBISHOP] I don't
suppose you have any idea
what that means, Byro?
[BYRO] That's the phrase
you hear in your dreams,
is it not? Forgive
me my lord,
but I haven't
the slightest.
[ARCHBISHOP] Once every
one hundred years,
the Infinity Clock
releases the magic power
it has accumulated
and becomes active...
It is said that if all six
of the scattered clock pieces
are gathered together
when it is activated...
[BYRO] What will happen?
[ARCHBISHOP] Then the clock
will begin to tick...
and it will usher in
the end of the world.
[BYRO] That cannot be...
[ARCHBISHOP] According to the
cardinals, a wizard guild is
looking to gather the pieces
of the Infinity Clock.
We are the only ones
who can stop them.
In other words...
We now have a
purpose given to us
by a higher power.
Byro... Prepare
yourself for a holy war.
[LUCY] If all the clock pieces
are gathered together...
...then the world
will come to an end.
So that's the
"inevitable chaos".
Yeah...
Sounds like it.
Things just got way
more serious around here!
I cannot give
this back to you.
A meager wizard guild doesn't
have the power to protect
the world from destruction.
He's got a point.
If we make one mistake
it could spell disaster!
Then maybe... we
should just let him
take it after all.
No way!
That story sounds
like a bunch of baloney,
if you ask me!
[BYRO] What?
[NATSU] If gatherin'
the clock parts is gonna
make somethin' bad happen,
then I gotta wonder what you
and your buddies are up to!
Natsu's right, the answer
is to not gather them!
Besides, do we really want
Zentopia holding the fate
of the world in their hands?
Yeah, you don't know
what to do with 'em
any more than we do!
Who says that you guys
won't make a
dangerous mistake?!
Oh no! We're
all gonna die!
I can assure you our
teachings are not mistaken.
How dare you even
question the archbishop?!
He is infallible!
[MICHELLE] That's not true.
Nobody is perfect;
we all make mistakes.
That's why we can't find
world peace. I thought
everyone knew that.
[NATSU] I don't buy it!
You're tryin' to play the hero
but I can tell
you're up to somethin'!
You can't
fool me, man...
Someone's a jerk; either
you or that "Archbishop"
you keep talkin' about.
He might think he's calling
the shots right now but...
[BYRO] Such blasphemy!
Kanaloa!
Don't get sick!
Funny how fast he can go
from kick butt to butt face.
[WAKABA] What's the
matter, Kinana?!
[KINANA trembles]
Are you feeling
all right?
[KINANA] It's close...
So very close...
[KINANA] I sense it... The
end... is within our grasp...
I can hear it now...
I hear--!
There's no
need to panic.
It's just another
of her fits.
Hey Wakaba... Know
where Makarov is?
In the East Forest,
gettin' healed up.
Man, I hope he
gets back soon...
I could really use
his help about now.
Run faster, Lisanna!
[LISANNA] That's kinda hard to
do when you're carrying me!
This is no fair;
she's totally cheating!
I had no idea she was,
like, an actual demon!
How'm I supposed
to fight her?!
She's so sinful and wicked!
[MIRAJANE] To be
honest with you...
I like Zentopia's teachings...
Acknowledging and
baring the malevolence
within you... Devoting every
ounce of your love to others...
However...
I've lost all respect
for them now that I know
they embrace people
like you. Such a shame.
That's it! I've had
enough of you!
[MARY] I'm sorry, Archbishop!
I know that
I'm committing a sin.
Forgive me! I'm
doing it all for you!
[ELFMAN] What the
heck is happening?!
[LISANNA] Look!
Inside the blast!
[MARY, demonically] Merging
with someone you control...
Conducting Art,
Third Movement!
Using this forbidden
technique I will defeat you,
with your own power!
[demonic scream]
[MIRAJANE] So this...
...is what you
call a sin?!
[ELFMAN] They're moving so
fast I can barely see 'em!
[LISANNA] Wow...
Mira's... kinda... scary...
[MARY] Begone!
No way!
That attack didn't
even scratch her!
As far as I'm
concerned,
you've committed
a greater sin.
You've had your
fun. Now...
you'll pay for
taking my power,
and using it against me.
But most of all,
you'll pay for hurting
my brother and sister!
[MARY groans]
[MIRAJANE] You used my magic
to threaten my loved ones!
That's unforgiveable!
[MARY] Stay away...!
Here it comes!
Just thinkin' about it
makes me wanna pass out!
What's Mira
gonna do to her?!
[MARY] Please... don't...!
Bad!
[confused whimpers]
[MIRAJANE] Bad!
It's so terrifying...
This one time...
she was so desperate to catch
her enemy and discipline 'em
that she wiped out
an entire town.
Well, no wonder Master
forbade her from using it.
[BYRO] I have thoroughly
explained the purpose
of this holy war... Yet you
still insist on opposing us.
[LUCY] Honestly, I don't know
if I believe all that stuff
you said about the
end of the world.
I just care about keeping
my dad's memento safe!
So that's why
we're takin' that hand,
and the other clock pieces!
We're gonna do our
best to gather them all!
Enough of
your sinful drivel.
[LUCY] Run, Michelle! Hurry!
[MICHELLE] Okay!
Alright, Open, Gate of
the Golden Bull Taurus!
[TAURUS] Fierce... Mooove!
And here's another one!
[TAURUS] Look at you
with that tentacle!
This is my wildest
fantasy come truuuue!
Geez, would you
quit bein' a perv
and help me out here?!
Such indecent behavior.
I'm free!
[HAPPY] It's about time!
It's time to show this
jerk he can't mess with us!!
[ALL THREE]
Aye, aye, sir! Let's do this!
--[ROMEO] Purple Wire!
--[LUCY] Fleuve d'étoiles!
[BYRO] No!
[ROMEO] Now, Natsu!
[LUCY] This is your chance!
[NATSU] Here goes!
[HAPPY] Max Speed!
[NATSU] Plus...
Fire Dragon... Sword Horn!
[LUCY] I can't
hold on much longer-
By working together
to restrain Kanaloa,
they can now focus on me.
Quite an impressive attack.
Apparently there's more
to these Fairy Tail wizards
than we'd originally thought.
I'm losin'
my patience...
You'd better give Lucy that
clock hand or I'm gonna hurt ya.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
As we speak, members of
your guild are collecting
the scattered clock pieces
and are most likely
bringing them here.
I'm prepared to do
whatever it takes to stop you
from gathering them.
Well, I'm prepared
to beat your face in!
[PANTHERLILY] So what did you
want to talk to me about?
I consider myself
a proud member
of the Legion Platoon.
However, I have not
forgotten my roots.
I cannot deny
that I am an Exceed.
I've come to realize
that our sense of time
is vastly different than
that of the humans.
Surely even a muscle-brained
goon like you has noticed that.
Are you trying to pick
a fight with me?!
Please, just
hear me out...
Something has bothered me
since I deciphered that book.
It may sound odd... but,
as someone who shares
my sense of time, you
will likely understand.
I noticed something
inside of it
that I feel the need
to share with you.
Inside what book?
You mean "Key of
the Starry Heavens"?
Nu-uh! I don't
like this book at all!
[ALZACK and BISCA] Huh?
[ASCA] It's got a weird
story... and it's scary.
[gasps]
What are you doing,
Archbishop?!
You shouldn't be up, sir!
[ARCHBISHOP, excitedly]
It's close... So very close...
"Time ticks forward...
on toward inevitable chaos... "
It won't be long
before the end is upon us...
So very close...
[laughs]
[PANTHERLILY] Let me
get this straight...
there's still something
hidden in the book?
[SAMUEL] Don't think that
by sharing this with you
I am denouncing Zentopia.
I will fulfill my duty
as a member of
the Legion Platoon.
However, just as in Edolas,
no one knows what course
this holy war in the
human world will take.
♪
[HAPPY] Wait a minute,
that's not fair!
Nullifying magic
is totally cheating!
[NATSU] Chill out! We don't even
need magic to beat this guy!
[HAPPY] He seems to be
beating you pretty bad...
In fact, you've been
completely helpless
against him in this fight!
[NATSU] Don't be stupid!
Everyone knows a real hero
doesn't save the day until
things are at their worst!
[HAPPY] Uh-huh, sure.
Whatever you say "hero".
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
Time Begins to Tick!
[HAPPY] I think you're more
of an underdog than a hero.
[NATSU] Hey, now! I'm
obviously a classic hero!
[HAPPY] I dunno. You'd
have to be a lot more
sophisticated to
pull off "classic".