[NATSU] Let's rumble.
What? The clock hand...
It's started to resonate!
[ARCHBISHOP] It's
finally happening...
time is ticking forward!
[crazed laugh]
The chaos...
the everlasting midnight...
it's coming!
[gasps]
[MALE VOICE] Your voice...
Let me hear it...
Who are you?
Tell me!
I have to know!
♪
You've done
very well, Kanaloa.
I'll handle things
from here on.
[LUCY] Whoa!
It's pocket sized!
How'd that happen?!
[MICHELLE] Great for a
snack! Or side dish!
He's a warrior,
not an entrée!
[HAPPY] Time Begins to Tick!
Fire Dragon Roar!
He neutralized it!
Magic is useless
against him.
[NATSU] That was just an ember!
Try stoppin' an inferno!
Get away from him! Open...
Gate of the Sea-Goat, Capricorn!
[BYRO] It won't work!
What the--?!
My power nullifies
all other forms of magic.
You might as
well surrender now.
Quit playin' dirty,
Octo-freak!
This Byro's way worse then
the one we met in Edolas!
[NATSU] You're really
startin' to get on my nerves!
Natsu!
You okay?!
No need to worry,
you guys, I can take it.
That was nothin'; I've
had tougher fistfights
with Gray before breakfast!
[NATSU being punched
over and over again]
This is so barbaric.
Sorry, sir, I
overslept again! Oh...
it was just a dream...
shame cause Titania
and I were gonna try some
one-on-one sparring--
Happy!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
Pathetic.
[HAPPY] My Aera
magic went poof.
I figured it
wouldn't work.
You coulda told me!
I clearly said that I can
nullify all types of magic.
You should pay attention...
if you want to live.
[MICHELLE] Without magic
we're completely helpless!
[LUCY] No... There's gotta
be something we can do!
Okay. What's the
plan, Natsu?
If I can't use
magic I'll use force!
Huh?
Ol' Gildarts used
magic when he fought him,
but taking that approach
got him nothin' but a draw.
So I'm gonna throw
down with good ol' fashioned
elbow grease. I'll
get Lucy's clock part
and show-up Gildarts
at the same time!
Yeah! I'm all
fired up now!
For better or worse,
at least he's got
a positive outlook.
[BYRO] The fate of the entire
world hangs in the balance...
yet you care only for
personal affairs?
[NATSU] You got
a problem, pal?
[BYRO] Such shortsightedness...
You couldn't possibly understand
the weight of the
burden we carry.
We are prepared to
sacrifice our lives
for this mission.
You gonna fight or
talk me to death?
Don't avert your
eyes, Coco...
He may be our enemy.
But he's also got serious guts.
The real battle
is just beginning.
[JACKPOT] Things are finally
starting to heat up, huh?!
[laughs]
Good luck,
Salamander and friends!
I hope you manage to get
a little thrill out of this
ultra-hot battle before
Lord Byro takes you down.
[laughs]
[KINANA] Master...
What happened to me?
You just passed
out from anemia.
You need to rest for a while.
No... You don't have to
lie, I know this has
something to do with
the spell I was under.
It's all
just a blur now.
I don't remember
being a snake.
I'm afraid.
What'll happen
if I do remember?
I don't think it'd
be a good thing.
[KINANA] Should I
really be here?
[WAKABA] What?! You were
changed into a snake?!
Yep! My memories from back
then are pretty hazy,
except for one thing...
Someone I hold very
dear made a special
promise to me.
Isn't that wonderful?!
A promise, huh?
He promised that even
if we were torn apart,
one day he'd come back on a
shooting star to take me away
from all of my worries!
That's crazy talk.
Hey Master...
Who is that girl?
Believe it or not, she was
a snake a moment ago.
While we were out and about,
we spotted a snake
that appeared to be
afflicted by a curse.
[WAKABA] And when you lifted
the curse it changed into
that little girl?
[MAKAROV] It was no easy task
lifting it, that's for sure...
and I don't know
why it was placed.
I tried my damnedest
but I'm afraid
she's still unstable.
[MACAO] Explains
her memory loss.
[MAKAROV] I think it would
be best if we kept an eye
on her for the time being.
[WAKABA] You're a
helpful old fart.
Ain't no denyin' that!
I'm concerned
about the voice
she keeps hearing. It
pains me to say this, but...
If her memories
as a snake resurface,
she may not have the
brightest future ahead of her.
Poor kid has
got it rough.
[WAKABA] Shame to think
her future could be ruined
by her own memories.
[MAKAROV] Well then,
we'll just have to make sure
that doesn't happen.
C'mon kiddo, try to
keep your chin up...
There's no reason to worry
about the curse, okay?
[MACAO] I promise
no matter what happens...
we'll be here
to keep you safe.
Try to get some
sleep while you can.
[BOOK GIRL] Don't...
Did you hear that,
or am I goin' crazy?
No...?
[NATSU] So you and your buddies
are prepared to sacrifice
your lives for
your mission, huh?
What a load of crap!
Life ain't somethin' you just
toss aside like garbage...
You should protect it!
We fight for the lives
of the people
who we call friends.
The bonds we share
are what drive us!
And push us to be better!
Don't you know that friends
aren't "things" or "tools"?
You can't just use
'em however you please!
They're more
important than that!
It looks like he's
already broken several bones,
but you couldn't tell
by lookin' at his face.
That ain't the look of
defeat he's wearing right now.
[NATSU] Listen... I want you
guys to stay outta this.
I'm takin' him
down on my own...
That's a promise from a wizard
of the Fairy Tail guild.
Time to rearrange
your face Octo--
C'mon, get up!
Sheesh... Poor Natsu can
barely stand anymore.
But he'll find a way!
Nothin' can keep him down!
Get up... I know
you've got it in you.
He is a worthy
adversary. Respect.
But, Dan...
I don't get it.
How could someone
as brave as he is...
really be an enemy
of Zentopia?
[DAN] Well, he sure
is acting like one.
[BYRO] What?!
[punch]
Bulls-eye!
That won't
be enough.
[BYRO] Strange sensation...
Looking upon you fills me
with emotions I forgot
a long time ago.
Anger is at the forefront.
You yammer on about
the sanctity of life,
about the nobility
behind your own vendetta,
but you are nothing more
than guild rats chasing coin.
That you would
compare your avarice
to our holy mission
belittles not only us,
but the Archbishop and
the ideals he represents.
That's not true!
We're not in this
for the money, okay?!
Yeah, 'cause
we've got plenty!
Enough to pay rent?
And buy food?
[MICHELLE] What are you
waiting for?! Say something!
[LUCY] Well... Uh...
[HAPPY] I really didn't expect
him to throw that out there.
That's big talk
coming from a thief.
You're the one who stole Lucy's
clock hand in the first pla--
This world is already
saturated with chaos.
The Infinity Clock's addition
may not even be noticed.
However...
Zentopia's doctrine
is to minimize that chaos,
and to instead, show
the people of this world
the righteous course of action.
The privilege of
putting those ideals
into practice falls
on the Legion Platoon.
[NATSU] Blah, blah! Add 'thou
shall shut-up' to your ideals.
Natsu isn't
hurt anymore!
How'd he do that?
Look! That's how!
[LUCY] The tomb's candles!
[HAPPY] Yeah, and
there's tons of 'em!
You dare to desecrate
these flames?
Does your blasphemy
know no bounds?!
What, you gonna
start lecturing me
about my diet now?
Don't bother; I already
forgot most of the crap you
were yammering on about.
I heard some of it,
though...
like "friends"...
and "lives"...
Then you insulted
Fairy Tail.
Now my fists are
gonna lecture your face.
He's provoking him?
As if the guy wasn't
mad enough already.
That's Natsu for ya!
Awesome!
[COBRA] I can hear it...
It's close, now...
The end is finally
within our grasp!
[ARCHBISHOP] The end is
finally within our grasp!
The end is finally within
our grasp! [crazed laugh]
[deep, resonating clock ticks]
[PRIEST A] What is the
Archbishop's condition?!
[PRIEST B] It hasn't
improved at all.
[PRIEST C] But the
Founding Festival is just
around the corner.
[PRIEST D]
It can't be helped.
The cardinals have convened.
They're selecting the next
archbishop as we speak.
[LAPOINTE] Don't be ridiculous.
[PRIEST E]
Cardinal Lapointe!
[PRIEST D]
When did you get back?
[LAPOINTE] Replacing the
archbishop is utter nonsense.
I'm afraid that
we are faced with
a far greater
problem right now.
[PRIEST F]
What do you mean, Sir?
[LAPOINTE] There are traitors
to Zentopia in our midst.
[gasps, murmurs]
Unfortunately,
the Infinity Clock
has recently become
public knowledge.
As if that
weren't enough,
there are also the
attacks on our churches.
I am told these acts are
the work of an insider.
My word...
Is there any
proof of this?
[LAPOINTE] Do you think I
have cause to deceive you?
[PRIEST D] No...
[PRIEST G]
Of course not, sir!
[LAPOINTE] I am suspicious
of the priest who survived
one of these attacks. I wish
to question him personally.
Bring him to me at once.
[PRIESTS AND NUNS]
Yes, your eminence!
[LAPOINTE] I'll tend to
the Archbishop myself...
From this point on, no one is to
enter his chambers except me.
[BYRO] This is a holy war!
[NATSU screams]
[BYRO] The retrieval
of the Infinity Clock...
That sacred mission is the sole
purpose of the Legion Platoon.
The misguided principles
of a measly guild
can't even compare.
[NATSU groans]
[BYRO] If consuming fire
is another manner of magic,
then I will
neutralize it as well.
Yeah? Try it!
That's cheating!
Why dontcha fight him
fair and square, old man?!
Or just give up!
I can't believe
Lord Byro hasn't used
a single offensive
spell yet.
Don't act so
surprised...
I mean, the man's
strength is legendary.
Only four others in all of
Fiore can even stand up to him.
A weak and helpless fool
like you is unfit to lead
this world out of darkness.
What did you call me?!
A weak and
helpless fool...
A coin-chasing wretch
couldn't possibly understand
what we fight for.
In this world of misery,
people will cling to anything
that provides hope. And if
that happens to be Zentopia,
then cling to it they shall!
As do we... So if
the Archbishop orders us
to find the clock...
Then that's what we'll do!
If that order requires
us to sacrifice ourselves
or others to succeed...
then so be it.
It's our duty... The
greater good must be served.
That doesn't
make any sense!
I didn't
understand it...
But whatever you said,
I know you're dead wrong!
No kidding!
Don't you care that
people are suffering because
of you and your mission?!
Are you that heartless?!
[BYRO] It is foolish to act on
emotion. It solves nothing.
To reveal the
course of righteousness,
and to walk its
path unfettered...
[BYRO] We are faced
with difficult decisions
and we are forced
to make sacrifices.
The world is filled to
the brim with contradictions...
I believe we are all
painfully aware of that fact.
Therefore, it is
only logical that
the path I've chosen
will end in sacrifice.
Aw, man...
The cryptex in my head
is all kinds of jumbled
up after that speech.
[MICHELLE] Making
difficult choices...
That must be
rather easy for you.
[BYRO] What?
[MICHELLE] You said
you follow your "cause",
to make choices instead of
listening to your "emotions."
That's just a strategy
to avoid feeling guilty.
Harden your heart to suffering
and you can
justify any decision.
Michelle?
I'm a little lost on
all this philosophy jargon,
so why don't we just
make out? Sound good?
You dare dispute
the principles
of righteousness with me?!
[DAN] Get down, Loopy!
Stop it, now!
This is righteous?
If you ask me, you're all
just a bunch of bullies!
This is just like
what we saw in Edolas...
those in power making everyone
else suffer and give up their
freedom in the name of
some fake righteousness.
Any path that hurts
innocent people will never lead
to the greater good...
In fact, it's nothing
but a dead end!
If you're willing
to follow that path,
then what does it
say about you, huh?!
Even fish are born
free to swim along
any current that
they choose!
It's the same for
'guild-rats' like us!
We decided to use our magic
to help people who need it.
Yes, it is our job and
we get paid for it,
but, in return,
they get happiness!
That's how we got
to where we are!
That's how a
guild works!
Fairy Tail will never
lose to somebody like you!
'Cause fake righteousness
won't help anyone!
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
You dare to ridicule
the followers--
no, all of Zentopia
to that extent?!
[HAPPY] You bet I do!
'Cause you should be ashamed!
Wow, Happy...
Way to tell him!
That's right! Fairy Tail
members listen to
what's in our hearts!
Our guild is about helping
anybody who needs it!
[BYRO] Enough of this nonsense!
Time for your
divine punishment!
[ROMEO] That's what you think!
[HAPPY] Take him down!
Get back here!
Romeo!
Lord Byro...
Are you mad?!
You can't use
Divine Arrow on people!
You'll kill them!
I shall turn you to dust.
Now, burn and be
purified in the fire...
of your own sins!
Divine... Arrow!
He missed?!
Coco... What are
you doing?!
[COCO] Zero points,
Lord Byro!
Please, you have
to stop!
All the suffering...
All of the chaos we've
caused on our mission...
That isn't what the Legion
Platoon or Zentopia stands for!
We should be using our
strength to protect the weak.
Instead of just breaking them
down we should be building them
up and showing them the way.
[COCO] What's righteous about
slaughtering our flock...?
Don't you see?
It is hypocrisy...
and I simply can't
abide it any longer.
[BYRO] Blasphemy... How
dare you turn your back
on our doctrine!
[COCO] I'm fully aware of
the penalty for betraying
the Legion Platoon.
But, I can no longer see
the righteousness at
the end of this path, sir!
[BYRO] "Righteousness
is like an arrow...
It pierces through all
in an unwavering line
to arrive at
one thing: truth!"
Are you telling me that
teaching has been lost on you?
If the arrow must pierce
through the hearts of lost lambs
in order to find what is
right, then it's wrong!
And it should be
snapped in pieces!
What?!
[COCO] Lord Byro, I still
believe we can do good...
but I've realized there's more
to me than just doctrine.
After seeing the
way these people act--
how they see the world--
I can't help but be filled
with warmth and happiness.
And I'm sure if you
opened your heart to them,
you might start to feel
the same way that I do.
[BYRO] Coco...
You've been corrupted!
You wretched traitor!
Don't do it.
You will not be
allowed a tribunal.
The only thing that
awaits you... is justice!
Coco!
Goodbye...
Princess Lucy... Thanks...
I really wish... you
and I could've become friends.
[crash]
[COCO gasps]
[BYRO] You!
[ERZA] The chance
to cross swords didn't
present itself before,
but at last we meet.
Prepare for battle!
[BYRO] Titania.
Do not speak my name!
It disgusts me to hear it
said by someone who would
turn on their allies...
You're Despicable!
[NATSU and LUCY] Erza!
[GRAY] We're not in the
habit of putting up with
bullies like you, old man!
[HAPPY] Gray! And Juvia!
[HAPPY] Wait...
Why's Lyon here?
Come on... Is this
old timer really giving you
that much trouble,
Charcoal-breath?
[NATSU] Chill, Frostbite...!
I'm just playin' around with him
before I kick his butt,
so keep yours outta this!
[LUCY] Everyone made
it... and they found
the other clock pieces!
[NATSU] Even Gajeel's here!
[HAPPY] Carla's group
hit pay dirt, too!
And with our piece...
we've almost got the whole set!
[ERZA] As you can see... we've
obtained all five clock pieces,
save one.
Hand over what
you stole from Lucy
and we'll leave in peace.
I'll only ask once.
Then you'll have to take
it from me... Titania.
[ERZA] You're
outnumbered, Byro.
We'll take them
alright, and seal them.
Now... be smart.
It's over...
Surrender it!
[BYRO] I'm afraid
I can't do that.
The Infinity Clock was
originally Zentopian property.
Destiny demands
that we watch over it.
What?
Is that true?!
Well... To be honest,
I'm not so sure.
[clock piece resonates]
[BYRO] You guild rats have
become too involved in this...
You've glimpsed into a
darkness that the world
should never know...
Because of that,
I cannot allow you
to leave here alive.
[ERZA] Enough!
Prepare yourself!
No, don't attack!
Magic won't work!
What the heck
are you doing?!
Such fools...
What happened?! Did he
just block all of them?!
Even with our
numbers?!
Magic attacks
don't work on him!
This'll be
interesting.
I think you
mean 'annoying'.
Right...? Now I'm just a lame
ol' average talking cat!
[BYRO] One spell or a thousand;
it makes no difference...
In my presence, wizards cease
to be wizards entirely.
[HAPPY] What about cats?
There's still
one option left.
If we can't use magic,
we'll use our fists.
How arrogant.
I've been trained to fight
barehanded against fifty
opponents at once,
you won't even warm me up.
Well, well...
Sounds like Octo-geezer's
fired up, too!
Please stay focused. He's a
very proficient fighter.
Sounds like
a challenge.
[clock piece resonates]
[ding]
[LUCY] Huh?
[LUCY] Dad?
[BOOK GIRL] Don't...
[BOOK GIRL] I told you...
don't do it...
[BOOK GIRL] Time has ticked...
And now Chaos has come.
[LUCY] No... This is the
beginning of the end?
[crazed laugh]
No... What horrible power!
[MICHELLE] Big Sis!
Look...! The clock!
[LUCY] I see it... But,
what's happening?!
[deep, resonating clock ticks]
[PILGRIM A] What's that
sound?! It feels like
it's inside me!
[PILGRIM B]
My head's splitting!
[PILGRIM C] Someone!
Help us! Please!
[PILGRIM D] Archbishop!
[PRIEST H] There
are Pilgrims out there!
[PRIEST I]
They're suffering!
[PRIEST J] We can't
open the gates yet!
[PRIEST I, knocking]
What do we do?!
[PRIEST J]
How should I know?!
I can hear it... Everlasting
midnight has come...!
At last! [cackles]
[screams, chaos from the
other side of the door]
[PRIEST K, knocking]
Archbishop, please!
Those mindless fools...
Swarming like insects.
[deep, resonating clock ticks]
[NATSU] My ears are bleeding!
[HAPPY] That's
some alarm clock.
[ERZA] The tomb
is collapsing!
It can't be...
Why now?
This ain't the
time to space out!
Let's scram!
That smell... But how...?
Keep your guard up!
We're in
real hot water now.
[deep, resonating clock ticks]
♪
[HAPPY] Oh no! I think
the Infinity Clock
has started ticking...
and is that the Oración Seis?!
[NATSU] Sure looks like 'em...
but where's the blocky face guy?
[HAPPY] You mean the one
who always goes, "Oh yeah!"
[NATSU] Yeah, that's him!
Wow, that was a really
bad impersonation, 'lil buddy.
[HAPPY] Whatever, I sound
just like him! "Oh yeah!"
[NATSU] Uh huh...
Don't quit your day-job.
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
Enter the Neo-Oración Seis!
[HAPPY] Happy rules, "Oh yeah!"
Natsu drools, "Oh yeah!"
[NATSU] Okay, you're right.
You totally sound like him.
[HAPPY] Aw, c'mon!
You're giving up already?!