What the? Is there
something stuck to my head?
Uh, what the heck is going on?
[CAPRICORN] We're
about to begin our contest.
What contest?
A quiz! Worthy of
a Zodiac Spirit!
A game show?
[CAPRICORN] I suppose.
Each contestant
will be presented
with a series of questions
they must answer.
There are ten in all.
Once the final score is tallied,
the winner will then be
granted complete freedom.
And the loser will suffer
a truly horrible fate.
Oh. I don't like
the sound of that.
But why are we playing
a trivia game?
Well, because I'm rather
fond of them, that's why.
Now then.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Fairy Tail
Cult Quiz, Question Number One!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Guess I have no choice
but to play.
Fine then.
Excellent, let's proceed.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] This doll
was a gift to Lucy Heartfilia
from her mother.
What'd she name it?
--[LEVY] Ha!
--[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Miss Levy!
[CAPRICORN] Hmm...
You're swift on the buzzer,
but are you accurate?
It seems like I was nervous
about this for no reason,
because this
game's super easy!
That doll's name was "Michelle"!
[buzzer sounds]
Uh. That sounds bad.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Mr. Capricorn!
[CAPRICORN]
Lucy named her doll "Gonzales."
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
That is correct!
While the doll did eventually
come to be called Michelle,
this was not the name
it got from Lucy.
Upon receiving the doll
as a birthday present,
young Lucy could think
of no better name
--for it than Gonzales!
--[AUDIENCE cheers]
[LEVY] Wait, don't
you have amnesia?
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Incorrect
answers must be penalized!
What? Hey!
Can someone fix this thing?!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
For each incorrect answer,
our contestant's odds of falling
into the "Fun Zone"
will increase!
[LEVY yells]
[CAPRICORN] Look at us.
Two perfect examples of what
to do and what not to do
when engaged
in a match of wits.
The fun zone isn't
fun at all, is it?!
[HAPPY] Guild Deck
vs. Celestial Deck!
[CANA] What did those
brats just do to me?!
[GEMI &amp; MINI]
Piri, piri!
--Check it out.
--Her life has gone down!
[SCORPIO] I'm not
the only rule in this game.
Allow me to explain:
the lit symbols to your left
indicate your
current life total.
You've just lost one
out of four life points.
Now, should you lose
the remaining three,
you will lose this match
and pay the price.
What price?
The real fun of this game
is in devising varied,
unexpected strategies to
keep one's life points safe.
But, you'll agree that a game of
cards is most entertaining
when the stakes are high.
So... If you do lose, you'll be
added to my card collection.
[CANA] Fat chance, nerd!
I'll win your stupid game,
then you'll let me close your
gate like a good little spirit.
If you play as shrewdly
as you hand out insults
then I'd say the two of us are
in for a game to remember.
Now that our bets are placed,
I'll end my turn.
You may begin yours when ready.
I'd love to, but
where do I start?
I still don't get what
"I am the rules" means.
Plus these cards are blank.
Wait.
The game board we're standing on
is clearly magical.
When you placed your cards,
it looked like the Gemini
twins appeared in the flesh.
So you filled
your deck with friends.
then summoned them on the board.
Seems easy enough.
If you're going to play
with your friends,
then I'll stack the
deck with my own.
[CANA] So that's what you meant.
You aren't the rules
after all: I am!
I can make whatever
cards I want,
based on the people
that matter to me.
You catch on quickly,
don't you?
Card master indeed.
The game lets you combine
cards to form different attacks.
Well, that I'm
pretty much used to.
Let's get things moving.
First, my draw sequence.
Next up, my standby phase.
I summon my friends
Happy and Carla!
Aye, Sir!
Would you like us to rough
somebody up for you then?
Piri, piri.
Both of her friends
are kitty cats!
I think they're
called "Exceeds".
[CARLA] So you're the
ones we're fighting.
[HAPPY] Tough break for you,
cause I'm super strong!
[CANA] Those figures
aren't real, are they?
[SCORPIO]
They're illusions.
To give the game
some extra flavor.
Well, they're
extremely convincing.
I appreciate that.
[CANA] I deploy two Field Cards!
Face down!
[SCORPIO] You've never
even seen a field card flipped,
and yet you're deploying
your own! Amazing!
[GEMI &amp; MINI]
She's not bad.
[HAPPY] Uh, why's he shaking?
[CARLA] How would I know?
I love the tactics of
strategy card games
more than life itself.
So doing battle with a
player as masterful as you
gives me a thrill like no other.
[CANA] What a creeper.
All right! I'll start
my Battle sequence!
Get them, Happy!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[SCORPIO] I'll block
that attack with Gemi.
Sure hope he
doesn't beat me!
Happy Attack!
[GEMI grunts]
[CANA] Good work, Happy!
That's one down!
[SCORPIO] Destroyed cards
are sent to the spirit realm:
a trash zone, which generally
renders them unusable.
However...
Both of my Gemini
possess a special ability.
Whenever an allied
monster is destroyed,
I may replace it
with a field card!
I reveal "Celestial Punishment",
which summons Virgo the Maiden.
Summoning Virgo during
an opponents turn
triggers her ability to
resurrect a monster
from the spirit realm.
Are you glad to
be back, Gemi?
Of course I am!
No way! You can
actually do that?
And by the way,
summoning me also allows him to
draw five cards from his deck.
You're playing a lot of
cards on not your turn!
You seem flustered.
Which is precisely how
I like my opponents.
[CANA] Screw it. I end my turn.
[PISCES BOY screams]
[PISCES MOM]
Sweetie-pie, no!
You should teach him to speak
to his mother with respect.
Just who are you
to criticize?!
If I wanted parenting
advice from a demon,
I would've asked for it!
[MIRAJANE] If you keep indulging
him, he'll treat you worse!
We are the perfect picture
of what a family should be!
This one doubts
our bond, munchkin!
Let's show her what a
loving family can do!
[PISCES BOY]
Yeah, Whatever hag.
I guess I'll help you.
Why do you let him
talk like that?!
--[PISCES MOM] A mother.
--[PISCES BOY] And son's.
[BOTH] Forbidden embrace!
--Work it, sweet-pea!
--I love you, ma!
--[MIRAJANE] On second thought.
--[PISCES BOY grunts]]
[PISCES MOM gasps]
[MIRAJANE] It seems that
your indulgence is mutual.
[PISCES MOM] Unhand us!
[PISCES BOY screams]
[PISCES MOM screams]
That looked painful.
I'm sorry.
If I were you... I'd run.
[MIRAJANE] Look.
There's more to family
than indulgence.
You're meant to help
each other grow.
[PISCES BOY]
Take it back....
[PISCES MOM] Snookums...
[SCORPIO]
Finished already?
Then I'll start
my draw sequence!
Entering standby phase!
I'll send Mini to the spirit
realm in order to summon
Taurus, the golden bull!
[MINI] Bye, bye, brother.
[TAURUS]
Apologies, good Gemi.
Your partner's sacrifice
was a noble one.
I will strive to ensure
she did not fall in vain.
Aw! This bites!
[CANA] Sounds like there's
some dissension in the ranks!
I'm not too worried about it.
Entering battle phase!
Taurus! I want you to
Launch an attack!
[TAURUS] As you command.
Carla, block his attack!
He'll squish me!
Before damage resolves,
I'll flip a field card.
Activating, Maiden's Bond!
This card allows me to
special-summon a female friend
to give Carla some backup!
Look at that, I've got Carla's
best friend right here.
I summon Wendy!
The Dragon Slayer!
[TAURUS] Moo?
[WENDY] Sorry
that I took so long!
[CARLA] Glad you're here!
[CANA] Know what happens when a
Dragon Slayer and her Exceed
use Maiden's
bond together?
They get a bonus 100,000 attack!
Did you say 100,000?!
Oh, and I get to draw
three cards on top of that.
[SCORPIO growls]
[SCORPIO] Fine!
Then I'll sacrifice Gemi
in order to increase
Taurus' attack by 200,000!
[GEMI screams]
[TAURUS]
Now this is power!
How can you
sacrifice your friends?!
[SCORPIO]
Don't be so sentimental.
He was nothing but a pawn.
[CANA] Wendy! Carla!
[WENDY] We're on it!
[CARLA] We'll barbeque him!
[WENDY] We weep for Gemi.
He was too kind a spirit to
be sent to the spirit realm.
[CARLA] For every tear shed,
we'll gain 10,000 attack points.
Keep crying!
[TAURUS] What an
"offal" predicament!
How can I call
myself a gentleman
if I bring harm to a
maiden while she weeps?!
Wait? 500,000 attack?!
[WENDY] Sorry in advance.
[CANA] Take him out.
[BOTH] Tearful Maiden
Counter-blow!
[WENDY] Tearful Maiden
[CANA] Having fun yet?
[SCORPIO] I wouldn't pour
a victory drink if I were you!
Taurus' death was
a part of my plan.
[CANA] Yeah, right!
With him gone,
the field tilts in your favor.
That makes this the perfect time
for me to summon Libra,
the balance!
There must be balance
in all things.
[SCORPIO] Libra
makes for a fine equalizer.
When summoned, she
weighs her own attack
against that of an opponent's.
Whoever's weakest gets
sent to the spirit realm!
[LIBRA] I choose the cat!
[CARLA] Why's it always me?
[SCORPIO] When the scale
tips, the weakest one will rise.
[CARLA] That's just my luck!
--[CARLA screams]
--[LIBRA] I banish you!
Carla, no!
[CANA growls]
[LUCY screams]
[LUCY] Is that a
fricking spike pit?!
Not having it!
[LUCY grunts]
[LUCY] Way too close...
[VIRGO]
That was impressive.
But tell me, what'll
you do about...
...this.
--[rumbling]
--What?! Wait! Not the--!
[LUCY screams]
Please don't
crush me, Virgo!
I want to live,
can't we talk this out?
[WENDY sobs]
[CANA] Your tears
can't bring her back.
Nonetheless,
I'm grateful for them.
They give us a shot at revenge.
I Figured he'd
go after Carla.
Flipping the field card:
"Wendy's Tears!" Activate!
[SCORPIO moans]
To predict plays
that far in advance
you must've read me
like a street sign!
You weren't half this
good in my dreams!
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear that
and use this card to
kick your creepy butt!
Activating Wendy's Tears
allows me to dual-summon
Gray Fullbuster
and Juvia Loxar!
Atta-girl.
I bet she summoned
the two of us together
because she knows that
we're an item, darling!
I'm going to need
you focused.
Sir!
[CANA] By the way,
it's still your turn.
Got anything else for me?
[SCORPIO] Nah, I think
I'll leave things as they are.
I end my turn.
[CANA] 'Bout time, too!
Cool, so first I draw a card.
And then I start
my standby phase.
I summon Lucy the
celestial wizard
and Erza Titania!
Just tell me
what to stab.
We're here to help!
Time for my
battle sequence!
Juvia, I need you
to take out Virgo.
[JUVIA] Right!
[CANA] She and
Gray're dual-summons.
So as long as he's on the field,
her attack will be
five times its usual.
Not good...
We're even more connected
than before, Gray!
I can feel your power
surging inside me!
[SCORPIO] By the way.
Virgo has one other ability.
She can temporarily
summon an ally at any point
during one of my
opponent's attacks.
[CANA] Sounds pretty
frigging cheap to me!
[SCORPIO]
I special summon Capricorn!
Take the hit!
This should be refreshing!
[JUVIA yells]
I've taken the hit, sir.
You make a fine shield
and I appreciate your efforts.
Let's see you
pull it off twice.
You're up next, Erza,
run them through!
As you wish.
[CANA] Erza's ability allows me
to take any requip field card
that I have in hand and
put it directly on her
when she attacks.
Requip!
Heaven's Wheel Armor!
[CANA] She has 60,000 Attack!
I'll just block with Virgo.
[CANA] Got something
up your sleeve,
or do you just suck at math?
Why bother stuffing my sleeves
when I have a field card?
I activate: "Cruel Punishment"
[ERZA] What's this?!
Erza, no!
It's my worst nightmare!
I wasn't any help at all!
[SCORPIO] Cards
sent to the spirit realm
via punishment effects,
are completely untouchable.
So there's no point
in trying to save her.
[CANA] There's some
smug on your face.
Don't worry though.
it wipes right off.
Could you help him
out with that, Lucy?
Leave it to me!
[CANA] Take a life point!
You've got this!
[LUCY] I won't let you down!
[SCORPIO]
I'll block with Libra!
[LIBRA] Where we lack
balance, there is chaos.
Attacking triggers
Lucy's best ability!
If I have a celestial spirit
card in my hand,
then I can play it!
Leo the Lion! I summon you!
Intriguing. You've summoned
a spirit of your own.
But as he was a
special summon,
I can weigh his strength
against Libra's.
You better not be making
up crap as you go!
[SCORPIO]
Responding to such an accusation
would be beneath me.
Now then, let's see if your Leo
can match the strength
of an Eclipse Spirit.
[LIBRA] Uh-oh.
[LOKE] Sorry, babe!
Rules of the game!
Symmetry lost!
Correct me if
I'm wrong here,
but it looks like
you're out of blockers.
You are correct, indeed.
I'll just have to take
the damage, then.
--[LUCY] This one's for Erza!
--[SCORPIO yells]
[SCORPIO sighs]
[CANA] Why do you look
so damn pleased?
[SCORPIO] You're amazing.
In all the time I've played,
you're the very first player
to take one of my life points.
[CANA] You're welcome?
[SCORPIO] Thank you.
This card can only be
played when I lose life.
You'll be the first to see it.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
[SCORPIO] I flash-deploy
and activate a field card:
"Twelve Constellations"!
Don't bother asking
what it does,
you'll have to wait and see.
Fine, then go ahead
and show me.
[SCORPIO]
All in good time.
Entering Draw Sequence.
Begin standby sequence.
I summon Sagittarius!
The Archer!
[SCORPIO] Now
for the battle sequence.
[CANA] That weird
field card you played.
Going to use it or not?
[SCORPIO]
Give her the whip, Virgo.
[VIRGO]
She has been naughty.
[CANA] And here I thought
it was annoying
when you only wanted
to talk to me.
Lucy, block the attack!
[LUCY] No problem!
Uh, yeah I take that back.
[CANA] What's wrong?
[SCORPIO] Just another
one of Virgo's abilities.
When she attacks, she can
also root an opposing monster
to the ground.
Which makes it a bit
tough for them to block.
[CANA] Dammit!
[VIRGO] Spare the rod,
spoil the human!
He's got me
halfway down already.
[SCORPIO]
What's on your mind?
Were you thinking about
how suddenly I took what
small advantage you'd gained?
You can tell me. C'mon.
[CANA] Can it, weirdo!
Once you're in
a tough position,
it's quite hard
to bounce back.
You get stressed,
start making mistakes.
That tight spot will
get even tighter
and you'll lose your
mind to panic.
This has been a great
talk, but could you shut up
and play something?
Now my "Twelve Constellations"
can take effect.
This card will hit you with no
less than twelve blasts of magic
before my turn can end.
[CANA] Twelve?!
Did I hear that right?
[SCORPIO] Yeah, but...
Look, I know twelve seems
like more attacks
than anyone needs,
but if you keep in
mind they don't stop
even once you're beat, you can't
quite call the effort wasted.
[CANA] Geez! Overkill much?
Hey, why take a risk
if I don't have to?
You ready for the first one?
[CANA] Block it, Juvia!
[JUVIA] Sure, I'm all over it!
[JUVIA screams]
And here comes
number two.
Lucy, please!
[LUCY] I'll do my best.
[LUCY screams]
Well, that sucks.
I'm sorry, girls...
It's on now!
[CANCER] Shake me down,
I want to prance!
I got to move.
It's time to dance!
Oh yeah!
[GRAY] The heck have I done?
Anything but this
I could've dealt with.
[CANCER]
Don't just stand there!
Show me your moves, man!
Say what? What do
you mean by "my moves"?
[CANCER]
You know what I mean.
Your hot boogie moves!
You've got them inside!
So let them come play!
[GRAY] That isn't helpful!
Twelve Constellations.
Attack three inbound.
[CANA]
Just two life points left...
Hey, wait! I forgot about that.
Let it come. I don't
plan to block it.
You hatch some
desperate plan?
I'm down to my last life.
And as a result of that,
I can now play the Field Card:
Mavis' Patience!
[SCORPIO] Ooh.
After sitting through a
countless number
of bathroom emergencies,
the first master of Fairy Tail
became the poster
child for endurance.
Not only can
she block you,
she ends your turn
when summoned!
[SCORPIO] A much better
plan than I expected.
I'll pass my turn then.
Lucky thing that I
remembered.
It's not that
uncommon to lose track
of the effects your
deck can have.
But it certainly seemed
to have worked out well
for you this time.
You've turned a game of cat
and mouse into a dogfight!
And you did it
with a single move!
[CANA] I told you that
you're weird, right?
Beginning my
standby sequence.
I'll summon a pair of Happys!
[BOTH] Aye, Sir!
Why are there more of me?
[SCORPIO] Goodness.
Triple stacks are pretty rare.
[CANA] Happy's special ability
triggers.
If there are three Happys
on the field at once,
then they all get sent
to the spirit realm.
Wait! I want to get
to know myself!
[SCORPIO] What ability?
You're sacrificing them.
[HAPPYS] But I thought
we were friends!
[CANA] Now that I've sacrificed
all three of my Happys...
I can summon Natsu,
the dragon slayer!
I'm all fired up!
After that, I'll flip one
of my field cards.
Activating:
"Gray gets half-naked."
[GRAY] Hell yeah!
Now that's a good card!
[CANA] A shirtless Gray
gains 60,000 attack!
I place one field card
face down.
And then I'll start
my battle sequence.
Since Natsu and Gray
both have the same target,
they can combine their attacks!
--[GRAY] Sounds good.
--[NATSU] Oh yeah!
Break the Twelve
Constellations!
[GRAY &amp; NATSU yell]
[CANA] You know, that
card really wasn't so bad.
[SCORPIO] It's rather
funny you should say so.
Because by destroying my
"Twelve Constellations"
you've triggered
its final ability.
I need only discard two cards.
And then I can perform
a Golden Summons.
Leo the Lion!
Women are just the worst.
Well, damn. Never thought
I'd hear myself say that.
Beat him down, will you?
This "Loke" looks frail.
I'll block with Leo.
I'll destroy him.
[CANA] C'mon, Loke!
Make me proud!
[LOKE grunts]
[SCORPIO] It seems that
my Leo is the superior warrior.
[NATSU &amp; GRAY] Loke!
[LOKE] Astounding.
Was I really that weak?!
I'm sorry, Loke...
I'll try to give your
sacrifice some meaning.
Come to think of it, one of my
field cards needs a death.
I'll flip and activate:
"Call from the Spirit Realm"
as Loke passes through the gate!
[SCORPIO] A resurrection?
[CANA] One soul in
and one soul out!
I special summon Happy
from the spirit realm!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
I'm back in business!
[CANA] There's more. With Happy
and Natsu on the same field,
I can fuse the
two fairies into one!
This brings forth my one
and only ultra-combo Wizard.
Winged Nappy Dragneel!
[NATSU] Aye, Sir!
[LOKE] It's so awkward.
[SAGITTARIUS]
It's Dragneel as a flying cat,
what'd you expect?
[SCORPIO]
Pretty much anything but that.
Okay, Winged Nappy Dragneel,
show them how you fight!
I'll block him
with Sagittarius.
[SAGITTARIUS] Targeting!
[NATSU] Woo-hoo!
Screw getting' carried,
I can fly on my own!
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU] No thanks!
He dodged it?
Course he did! Why else would
I combine Natsu and Happy?
An unblockable pyro
hits his mark!
--[NATSU] Aye, Sir!
--[SCORPIO grunts]
[CANA] Either find
a way to stop him,
or enjoy your last two turns.
How'd I let
this happen?
I'll end my turn.
But the clock's ticking.
[SCORPIO] That was
good. But I can still do better.
I'll summon a spirit:
Aries the ram!
[ARIES] 'Bout time you
got me in on some action!
I've been bored as hell!
Say you're sorry!
[NATSU] And what if I don't?!
To start my battle sequence,
I'll attack with Sagittarius!
I shan't miss!
[CANA] Block him
with your ice, Gray!
[GRAY] Let's see him
shoot through this!
[GRAY grunts]
Gray, no!
Next, I'll activate
this field card.
Flames of Darkness.
[LOKE]
Such unthinkable power!
[SCORPIO] Put on Leo,
it grants five million attack.
Did you say million?!
Nappy Dragneel!
You have to try and block him!
[NATSU growls]
[NATSU grunts]
[HAPPY screams]
Look, I'm back
to four lives.
[CANA] What?! How?!
[SCORPIO]
It's a lesser-known effect
of my dark flame combo.
If the augmented spirit
can split a fused wizard,
then I get my lives back.
--[CANA growls]
--There, there.
You played the game well.
It just didn't matter.
Go on, Aries, put her down.
Sure thing!
I'll make her cry too!
I can still win this.
When my last life point
is attacked head on,
I can use an
extra-special summon!
The only catch is that
he be an S-Class wizard.
[CANA]
I special-summon my father,
Gildarts Clive:
the Ace of Fairy Tail!
Hey, darling.
Too cool! She just baited me
into rescuing her!
[GILDARTS] It's a rough
situation. But even so.
I just wanted to say how
glad I am that you called,
and how much I love to
hear you call me "Father".
I mean, "Daddy" would trump
that, but still, I'm very happy!
I'd call you "Daddy" if you
hadn't ditched Mom, you jerk.
Try to take this seriously.
[GILDARTS] Hey.
If it's serious for you,
then I will do
whatever it takes.
Come on, we need
to get moving!
Yes, but where to?
It's pretty clear what
we need to do next.
[NATSU] Yup. We've
got to stop Loke
And guess what? He's got
a whole world to himself.
First, we're going
to sneak in there.
Then we're going to find him
and beat him senseless!
[HAPPY] ♪ Ba-da-ba-ba, hey! ♪
So. What do you
think of my moves?
[NATSU] Never seen
someone flail like that.
Did it hurt?
[HAPPY] Of course not!
And that was not flailing,
it was a dance, you got it?
[NATSU] So... like
a seizure-dance?
[HAPPY] My talents
are wasted on you...
[NATSU] One more time!
[HAPPY] Fine, but focus!
Back spin! Half turn!
Double-axel!
So?
[NATSU] Still just flailing.
[NATSU &amp; HAPPY] Next time:
Gray vs. Cancer!
Dance Battle!
[NATSU] Your legs are too
stubby for dancing, come on.
[HAPPY] You're so rude!