[yells]
[BRANDISH] To think you
live in that dump.
Still, I'm glad I found you.
Who are you?
And what connection do
you have to my mother?
[BRANDISH] It's too much
of a hassle to explain.
[CANA] Get the hell away
from Lucy, you weirdo!
Magnolia isn't your personal
playground, ya know!
So you need to get outta here!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[NATSU]
Erza!
[GAJEEL gasps]
Go with Natsu. She's
gonna need your help.
We can handle all
the riff-raff here.
Better back her up, Blue!
Aye!
[yelling]
I got ya!
[NATSU]
Erza! You okay? Wake up!
Oh, thank goodness!
I think Wendy's on her way.
The sandstorm's finally over.
Good, but I'm sure
there's more trouble.
Hang on, where'd she go?
[sneezes]
[BRANDISH] What is the deal
with all the crazy pollen
in this town?
Allergies?
I guess the wind from
that sandstorm
whipped up all the pollen
and crap in the air.
[BRANDISH] Ugh!
This is freakin' annoying!
[sneezing]
Owie!
Sucker punch?
She left herself
wide open, so...
[BRANDISH groans]
[LUCY]
Looks like she's down.
[CANA] Jeez, is that really
all it takes to knock out
one of the Twelve?
[LUCY]
What should we do with her?
[CANA] She's our prisoner.
We'll hold her in the guild.
I can see!
The sand's beginning to clear.
There's five?
Works for me.
They have a strange
magic energy.
Yeah, they do! Be careful!
Get ready!
Physical attack?
That just won't work on me!
[gasps]
[JUVIA screams]
[GRAY]
Juvia!
A steam attack?
All right.
Get ready to freeze!
They got fire, too?
[JUVIA] And the one
fighting me has steam.
What the hell's with
this guy? He's so fast!
Now! Manly punch!
[LISANNA yelling]
[LISANNA screams]
Oh, no! I can't hurt him!
[GRAY] They're using
fire against my ice,
steam against Juvia's water,
speed against Elfman's power,
and power against
Lisanna's speed.
I see what's goin' on here.
They're using our
weaknesses against us.
Lucky for us, Mira doesn't
have any weaknesses.
[gasps]
No. Please don't!
Cut it out, Elfman,
you're hurting me!
Hey! You're arguing
with a fake, ya know!
You! You did this!
How the heck did you know
which ways to attack us?
My Weakness magic
can generate soldiers.
They home in and take advantage
of my foe's weaknesses.
My power is a
unique one, indeed.
I can accurately
detect any fighter's
strong points and shortcomings.
Well, that explains it.
[WALL] My Weakness Soldiers
can deal with your lot,
I'm sure of that.
As for me, I shall dispatch with
that loathsome enchantment user
and nullify the
barrier for good.
[GRAY]
What?
He's gone.
And he's after Fried!
[EVERGREEN] It's working,
just hang in there!
A bunch of ships
coming in from the west
have been taken out!
That's good!
Apparently, Erza and Bisca
put one of the Twelve
outta commission!
Ha. More reassuring news.
[WALL]
It's a disgrace.
That failure brings shame
to the Twelve, indeed.
[FRIED gasps]
[BIXLOW]
Who's that?
[EVERGREEN]
It's one of the enemies!
[FRIED] I can't move
while maintaining
a high-level enchantment.
Sorry, you two. He's yours.
[BIXLOW]
No problem!
[EVERGREEN]
We can handle him.
We're Laxus's personal
bodyguards after all.
Part of the Thunder
Legion's duty
is to maintain our
fearsome reputation.
I can see it clearly.
What you're best at
and where you will fail.
Just like reading
a children's book.
Making it easy for
me to crush you.
Huh?
Say what?
Weakness Generation!
Take them down.
Line Formation, babies!
[BIXLOW gasps]
[WEAKNESS SOLDIER A]
Purification.
He's using white magic?
Fairy Bomb Gremlin!
[WEAKNESS SOLDIER B]
Mist.
What's going on?
My Fairy Dust won't work?
Man, this sucks!
My black magic keeps
getting canceled out
by his white magic!
Then try looking
them in the eye!
[BIXLOW]
Come on!
[EVERGREEN]
That doesn't work either?
Use it on the main one!
This will stop you!
Now turn to stone!
Won't work on me.
[gasps]
Bixlow! Evergreen!
Nothing's landing
on this guy!
Indeed, none of
your attacks will.
[gasps]
[WALL]
Because I'm not human.
I'm a mechanical being.
A Machias.
[gasps] He's a machine that
can wield magic power?
[ICHIYA]
Ahh...
[gasps] Is that lightning?
Laxus!
Zap, zap! Man!
[BOTH gasp]
I believe what the
doctor ordered here
is some shock treatment!
With a blast of
my Thunder Parfum!
Man!
[gasps]
[EVERGREEN]
Ichiya?!
[BIXLOW]
What are you doing here?
[ICHIYA]
Ha!
Don't tell me you've forgotten
your previous indignity!
No matter!
We'll chat after I
eliminate this bastard!
Indignity? What does
he mean by that?
No clue.
[FRIED] How could I have
confused this half-pint troll
for one so great as Laxus?
That's weird.
Just got the chills.
Is something wrong with you?
Nah.
[WALL]
Indeed, It makes no difference
how many are in your number.
I can determine all your
weaknesses with minimal effort.
All I need to do
is a quick scan.
Then my method of attack
is made clear to me.
Huh?
[ICHIYA]
Mmm...
[WALL]
This must be a mistake!
How can he be this flawed?
Man.
Ichiya's in a class all his own.
The dude's got so
many weaknesses,
the enemy doesn't even
know where to begin.
Although our time spent
together was brief,
you three were members of my
beloved Blue Pegasus guild!
In other words, you
and I are like family!
As a rule, no one harms my
family and gets away with it!
I know Fairy Tail shares
those feelings!
Now, quake in fear before me;
there is no escape!
[chuckles] The thick aroma
of death surrounds you.
Ha! That's my poison parfum.
[WALL] Alas, I lack the
ability to perceive smell.
Ah! You don't have a nose!
[WALL]
Besides that, I'm a Machias.
Your countless weaknesses had
me a bit flummoxed, indeed.
But it's quite simple.
You're just a weak...
pitiful... fool!
Ichiya!
[EVERGREEN growls]
This is so annoying!
I have my own problems here!
Hold on.
[ICHIYA]
Leave it to me.
Every last machine has the
same undeniable weakness.
Thunder Parfum with...
...massive Point-Blank Suction!
[gasping]
[ICHIYA]
Yes, that's right!
You're no match for
the power of lightning!
Justice... Thunder... Man!
[WALL] It's true Machias
made from organic metal
are vulnerable to
lightning strikes.
But do you honestly believe
that I would be allowed
to join the ranks of
the Spriggan Twelve
without first conquering
my own deficiencies?
What did you say?
[WALL] Since my magic
exploits weaknesses,
I learned a while ago
to eliminate any
that I found within myself.
So, I proceeded to address
my own failings,
and can now convert lightning
into a usable energy source!
Is he serious?
[WALL]
Vortex Charge!
[BOTH scream]
Man!
I'd heard of the Machias' power,
that they'd mastered
alchemy of some sort,
but I never knew they used it
to continually alter themselves.
[WALL] Indeed, the
more lightning of yours
that I absorb,
the easier it will be
for me to smite you all!
Ugh... I can't believe
the lightning helped him.
It never occurred to me.
[EVERGREEN] This means Laxus'
magic wouldn't have worked!
[BIXLOW] I was disappointed
when I realized Ichiya was here,
but now I'm glad Laxus
didn't show up.
[FRIED] Nobody here has
a chance against him!
I have no other option.
The enchantment's
getting weaker!
What's happening?
[MAKAROV]
And why now?
Listen, Fried! Don't let
your enchantment fall!
The guild hall's under
attack from the west!
[gasps]
[WALL]
Oh? What's this?
It looked as though you were
dropping your enchantment
for a moment.
So will you let it fall
in order to defend yourself...
...or will you die in vain
while trying to protect
the entire town?
A tough decision, indeed.
[LAXUS]
Hey!
What's goin' on?
I'm comin' to help you!
Stop yelling.
It's telepathy, you know,
so he can hear you just fine!
[FRIED]
No! Stay away!
Huh?
[FRIED]
We're the Thunder Legion.
We're your personal guard.
Our sole purpose has been
to protect you. However...
At this moment,
we must protect the guild!
So, you are still alive.
If you knew us, that wouldn't
be any kinda surprise!
We're not the types to go
down without a real fight!
I see. Then my Weakness
Soldiers shall give you one!
[BIXLOW, EVERGREEN groaning]
[BIXLOW]
More of these guys?
[EVERGREEN] Jeez! Will
these things just stop?
If you guys are fighting
more than one,
switch up your targets!
You hear me?
Is that Elfman?
[GRAY]
This one's a piece of cake!
Go, Gray! I'll take out
the fire one with water!
I'll go against the
more powerful machine!
The fast one is kind
of a joke to me!
I guess that means I gotta
beat up creepy robot me!
[ROBOT ELFMAN]
...help me. Manly.
So the Weakness Soldiers
have flaws. How ironic!
[ICHIYA]
It was this simple?
Well, if that's the case...
Let's wreck 'em!
[EVERGREEN] White magic doesn't
cancel out my spells!
[BIXLOW] And my trusty little
babies don't give a crap
about some stupid mist!
[WALL] I'm afraid it's too
late to turn the tide.
[gasps] Don't hurt him!
[NATSU]
We took... the western forces!
[BIXLOW gasps]
You there? Hey!
We took down the western forces!
Aye, Sir!
[GAJEEL chuckles]
What you've done is inspiring.
Now I can give my all
to the fight at hand.
[FRIED] Dark Écriture...
Absolute Shadow!
Smell the Power
Parfum... of Max Man!
[FRIED, ICHIYA yell]
Can you go one second without
stealing the spotlight, Ichiya?
Yeah, come on!
Guess we handled them, huh?
Sure did!
What happened to your clothes?!
Hey, Ever. You okay?
[EVERGREEN] As if you would
truly have to worry about me.
How's Erza? Is she okay?
[WARREN]
Yeah, she's fine!
I'm happy to report we've
captured one of the Twelve.
Lucky us!
And we're bringin' her
back to the guild hall.
Aw, yeah! This is awesome!
D'ya hear that, Zeref?
Don't mess with Fairy Tail!
That's my Thunder Legion for ya!
Seems we've somehow
managed to weather
the first wave of the
storm, First Master.
[EVERGREEN]
Wait. Ichiya.
How long have you
been in Magnolia?
[ICHIYA]
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
Just answer the question, man.
Honestly. This is the problem
with you Fairy Tail people.
You seriously don't remember
what happened a few days ago?
Man.
We've come for the
Lightning Dragon Slayer!
Hand over the
Thunder Legion, too!
Now wait a moment.
We're gonna need to borrow
your ship, Ichiya!
I've always wanted to
take a ride on that thing!
Hold your horses, ladies.
Alvarez, we're comin' for ya!
Let's get 'em!
Hang on a minute, please.
My amazing family
came to rescue me!
Gramps!
Yeah!
Master!
They had a bit of
help, you know.
[NATSU]
We're back! Ha!
[GRAY]
I missed ya, Magnolia!
[LUCY]
Woo-hoo!
I'm standing right here.
And that happened
about a week ago!
Well, then perhaps you
should've gone home?
[ICHIYA]
What?!
Do you appreciate everything
that goes into a long
flight such as that?
It entails massive amounts of
preparation and maintenance,
not to mention
all the fuel costs!
And then, lo and behold,
Alvarez has the gall
to come attack Fiore?
It really pisses me off! A lot!
Sorry about that, buddy.
But you truly saved the
day, so we're grateful.
Hmph! I'll never
speak to you again!
[FRIED]
How petty can you be, old man?
[ICHIYA]
I'm not old! Just experienced!
[gasps]
Ichiya! Get away!
[ICHIYA]
Hm?
[gasps] Wha--?
[laughing]
[ALL gasp]
[GRAY]
What was that?
[LISANNA]
It came from Kardia Cathedral!
Evergreen!
Guys! You okay? Please,
just say something!
Hey! Fried! Evergreen! Bixlow!
[BIXLOW] I guess...
we had it comin', huh?
[EVERGREEN]
I'm just glad you're okay.
[FRIED]
We were in the same guild.
That bond can be
stronger than blood.
You mean that... I--?
Hey! What just happened?
Dunno. It's really hard to tell.
[ICHIYA wails]
[ICHIYA]
Man!
[WALL laughing]
[DIMARIA] Enough with the
creepy cackling, okay?
Knock it off for once.
I'd rather be hearing
the sound of the waves.
[laughs]
This little excursion is turning
out to be way more thrilling
than I'd ever
imagined, indeed!
[laughs]
Oh, yeah. I'm done with
the "indeed" thing.
I was almost certain my puppet
would be enough to handle them.
[DIMARIA]
Oh?
So the fairy brats broke
your plaything, did they?
[WALL] Honestly, I did
consider that a possibility.
But most surprising
is the fact the enemy
was able to defeat Ajeel
and take Brandish into
custody this quickly.
[laughs]
Hilarious! They captured her?
Talk about a "hassle."
It's almost too
pitiful to joke about.
[WALL laughs]
Well, I for one,
am quite amused.
These Fairy Tail meat bags
really know how to play tough.
I suppose Emperor Spriggan
deployed the whole army
for good reason.
Even so, I'll be damned
if we don't get
to have the last laugh today.
That would be a real tragedy!
[DIMARIA]
Cool it, okay?
We're almost to the port.
And our first order
was to take it out.
[DIMARIA] You really think
you can do it from here?
It's still like 30
kilometers away.
[WALL]
No.
I'm actually gunning for
the Fairy Tail guild hall!
That's gotta be ten
times farther!
You don't have a chance!
How dare you
underestimate me!
I'm Wall, the great Machias!
Now, watch me!
Ultra-long distance
anti-material magic cannon,
fire!
Hey! Bixlow! Ever! Fried!
Are you there? Please respond!
[alarm blaring]
Hey! There's something
huge coming our way!
Whoa! It's magic power!
Whatever that is, its super-fast
and headed right for us!
[LAXUS]
What? Their army?
No.
I'd bet they're firing some
kind of long-range attack.
Can they seriously hit
us from that far away?
[MAKAROV]
Fried, we need you!
Put your enchantment back up!
Fried!
[WARREN]
Nothing!
There's no response
from the Thunder Legion!
[LAXUS]
Tch! Damnit!
The thing is getting
closer! And fast!
It's gonna be a direct hit!
Evacuate the guild, now!
Oh, no! Is our guild hall
gonna get flattened again?
[ICHIYA]
Not if I can help it!
Who was that?
The Christina!
That was Ichiya?
[ICHIYA]
Man!
What the--?
Looks like you missed.
He just used his ship
as a shield!
Why would he do that?
[ICHIYA]
This is a battle!
But it is not yours
to fight alone!
Calling all of Fiore! Now!
[ICHIYA]
Listen up, everyone!
This battle...
belongs to all of us!
[LUCY] The first wave of attacks
has been pushed back for now.
But there's still
a war going on,
and things will
only get tougher.
Our fellow wizard guilds
across Fiore rise up
and join the battle to
defend our homeland,
while "Fairy Tactician" Mavis
initiates her new plan.
Out to the west, Natsu and
Happy speed across the sky,
ready to fight!
Next time: "Natsu vs. Zeref."
The black wizard sees
death approaching
and greets it with
a quiet smile.