[NEINHART]
These souls, that never had
the pleasure of meeting before,
now interact as old friends.
Ahh. It's such a
marvelous thing.
Now, spread forth,
Historia of Corpses.
[KAGURA]
Live!
So, you ready for more training?
[GRAY, LYON]
Ur?
Yo. If it ain't ol' Meldy.
Zancrow?
What is this? They're dead!
[KEYES]
Not wandering corpses
but memories of fallen
rivals given form.
Whoa! Who is that?
[WENDY]
Shelia, take Carla and run.
Right now!
This has gotta be
some kinda joke.
[KYOKA]
Oh.
The pain you'll experience
will be absolutely exquisite.
How pathetic! That's it
after all these years?
Dear boys.
It's obvious that you're
never gonna surpass me.
[LYON]
Ur.
[GRAY]
Don't fall for it, man!
That's not Ur!
I realize that. It's just
a spell to throw us off.
But still...
[UR]
Rose Garden!
[LYON yells]
She has the same skills
and power level?
[GRAY] Maybe, but you
and I both have more
than we did back then, remember?
Oh?
You have to get over it, Lyon!
She's just an enemy
that looks like Ur!
But, Gray...
[GRAY] We can't let her defile
our master's memory like this!
But you're dead! You never
made it off of that island!
Oh, yeah! I died on Tenrou!
That's why seeing you...
[MELDY screaming]
...and finding out you
made it when I didn't
totally pisses me off!
[KEYES]
The voices of the dead
once again reverberate
across the battlefield.
Now I find myself as
the puppet in this scene.
How fascinating!
The dead shouldn't be
playthings for anyone.
[KEYES] Those alive once again
plagued by the memories
of their past struggles.
[WENDY screams]
[KEYES laughs]
[KEYES] This is a joyous
occasion indeed.
Oh, no! I can't walk!
[LAXUS]
Tch.
I mean, I get it.
Course the founding
members of Fairy Tail
wouldn't just stay in
their graves, but damn!
[ERZA yells]
[NEINHART]
I can't believe the pitiful show
Dimaria and Wall put on.
Overpowering these
buffoons is an easy task.
That is, for me at least.
[ERZA yelling]
[ERZA gasps]
Isn't this fun?
[ERZA screams]
[NEINHART] That rage in
your eyes is delicious.
I've no doubt you'll make
someone a lovely Historia.
Once we're finally
done with you.
Pull her up, would you, dear?
[ERZA grunting]
Well, this takes me back, Erza.
To our time in my
torture chamber.
You remember my loving
caresses, don't you? Hmm?
[ERZA screams]
[KYOKA] I've amplified
your sensitivity to pain.
[KYOKA chuckles]
[KYOKA] Now, I wonder if
I should raise it more.
Or should I introduce a
hint of pleasure instead?
I'm starting to believe I may
have actually missed you, Erza.
[ERZA]
That so?
Because I've grown quite
weary of this little reunion.
[gasps]
[ERZA] It's true all of you
were once powerful foes,
and obstacles to my
progress, however...
...each of you...
also fell by my hand!
[gasps]
[KYOKA]
Shut your mouth!
[gasps]
Get out of my sight,
you damned ghosts.
Before you feel the bite
of my blade again!
Such ferocity...
Erza!
[gasps]
What's happening?
I can't believe this!
Damn you, Erza!
[NEINHART] She was able
to defeat my Historias
with mere intimidation?
Who is she?
[JELLAL, KAGURA]
Erza!
[NEINHART]
Wait a second.
[KAGURA]
She's badly injured.
Erza! Talk to me!
[gasps]
[JELLAL growls]
[NEINHART] Her name. Her scarlet
hair. Her immense power.
It all adds up.
But could she really
be Irene's...?
[KAGURA]
Please! Erza! Open your eyes!
It seems there's one final
sin I need to commit.
What do you mean?
[gasps]
[NEINHART]
No! What happened to the sky?
Has night fallen?
[growling]
[KEYES] The stars, harbingers
of blessings... or misfortune?
What's going on?
This is Jellal's magic!
Really?
Who in the hell
even gives a crap
about the stars and the sky?
Juvia. Link with me again!
If that'll help, but how?
[MELDY] When people who trust
each other share their senses,
their power is multiplied, too.
So now it's something good?
[MELDY] This is how the spell
was intended to be used.
[KEYES]
What you call mutual trust
is nothing more than
pitiful dependency.
And that means you'll
both feel more pain
when I roast you alive!
[BOTH yell]
[WIZARD B] Does anybody
else feel a little chilly?
[WIZARD G] It's 'cause Gray
and Lyon are doin' their thing!
[WIZARD C] The enemy is on its
last legs! We've almost won!
Ice Make Geyser!
Ice Make Volcano!
[gasps]
[GRAY, LYON scream]
[LYON]
There's no way we can win.
Not against Ur.
I told you that thing isn't Ur!
Ur's dead, you hear me?
She's dead, and it's my
fault! You know that, Lyon!
[LYON]
You've had to walk a long road
to get where you are now, Gray.
That road took you to place
where you could heal yourself.
Where you could get over
all that happened with Ur.
That journey...
...I never had the
chance to take it.
Well, you have a chance now.
Don't let it go to waste.
Listen, man. My journey
didn't just happen to me.
I only made it this far
because I never stopped.
I kept on pushing forward.
Get moving. Right now!
Why even bother? You might
as well just give up.
[WENDY]
This is bad.
How am I gonna fight like this?
[CARLA]
Wendy!
[gasps]
[WENDY]
It's Carla! And Shelia!
Get back!
No way! We'll help you!
Wendy! I could never leave you!
I'll help you fly!
Friends stay together forever
and always, don't they?
[WENDY]
Yeah!
Now, Wendy, let's go!
Right!
You belong in the past,
you old geezer!
So apologize to the First Master
and then go back to hell!
Ready?
Let's do it!
Here's the first step!
Oh, yeah! And we're
gonna take it all the way!
[GRAY]
Ice Demon... Zero Long Sword!
[LYON]
Ice Blade... Swan Wings!
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Crushing Fang!
[BOTH]
Maguilty Water!
[LAXUS]
Lightning Dragon Jaw!
[JELLAL] May the seven stars
bring judgment upon you.
[NEINHART]
Oh, Jellal,
we've already seen
your Historia today!
Simon! Your old friend!
The one you murdered after
all he'd done for you!
[gasps]
[NEINHART] You can't do
it again! How could you?
The guilt... Could you
live with that burden?
This thing is not my brother!
[gasping]
Jellal! Strike him down!
[JELLAL]
Grand Chariot!
[screaming]
[BOTH chuckle]
[BOTH laughing]
[ALL laughing]
[ALL cheering]
It was just the middle of the
night and now it's sunset?
The sky... Scarlet and lovely.
[NATSU]
That guy in the east?
I'm gonna meet him
halfway and kick his butt!
Are you talking about August?
You can't take him
on by yourself.
I'll go with you!
Aye, me, too!
[MAKAROV]
Hmm... I don't know.
[NATSU] You want me to just
sit around and wait for him?!
What's the point if we're gonna
end up fighting anyway?!
If we're fighting the
strongest of the Twelve,
we have to be ready!
[BRANDISH]
He's not the strongest.
Huh?
The enemy--?
[BRANDISH]
To be more accurate,
he's only one of the strongest.
[ROMEO] Whoa! She's in
the Spriggan Twelve!
[MEST]
Why is she out of her cell?
Because I let her out.
Say what?!
She's actually been
pretty cool, ya know?
So you're saying there's
another one as strong as he is?
Yes, exactly.
August is powerful.
Hardly anyone else in the
Twelve can compare to him.
But there is another
that rivals,
or maybe even exceeds
his magic power.
--[LUCY, HAPPY gasp]
--[MAKAROV] Hm...
[BRANDISH] You could say,
if he's the strongest man,
then she's the strongest woman.
Irene Belserion.
A wizard also known as
the "Scarlet Despair."
You're finally awake.
[ERZA]
Kagura. Uh!
[KAGURA]
Don't exert yourself.
[WENDY]
Your wounds were pretty bad,
so it's gonna take a little time
before you're
completely healed up.
But don't worry, there
shouldn't be any scarring.
It looks like you guys went
through the wringer yourselves.
[JUVIA]
Gray! Your clothes!
[CARLA]
Yours, too.
Thank you.
[gasps]
What's going on now
with the battle?
[chuckles]
[GRAY] We were able
to liberate Hargeon
and take back
control of the port.
There are still a few soldiers
left hangin' around,
but Jellal and his team
are takin' care of 'em.
That's great.
We're gonna head back
to the guild hall soon.
They probably still need
our help back home.
Luckily, our friends from
Mermaid and Lamia
will look after everything
here after we leave.
I should return, too.
[KAGURA] You need to stay
put until you're well.
You know I can't just lie here.
What's the matter with Laxus?
[KAGURA] He had two big
fights back to back,
so he'll be out for a while.
[gasps]
[KAGURA]
Erza.
Huh?
[KAGURA]
Uh... this is awkward.
I hope you'll forgive me.
What are you talking about?
[ALL scream]
That was my apology.
[ERZA]
Uh.
[LYON]
Hey. Are you okay?
[SHELIA]
Yeah. I'll be fine.
[LYON]
Quite a reckless move.
[SHELIA]
It was pretty stupid, wasn't it?
'Cause now...
I've lost my magic.
That may be, but you traded it
for something far greater:
A future for all of us.
[DIMARIA]
They captured her?
Talk about a hassle.
It's almost too pitiful
to joke about.
[DIMARIA]
Randi.
[MAKAROV]
So, you're finally willing
to divulge some information?
[BRANDISH]
Just this once.
Don't let me give
you the wrong idea.
I don't intend to completely
betray my homeland.
I'm not going to start
fighting for your side.
But I do owe a debt to Lucy.
Huh?
What in the world
did you do for her?
Uh, I--
Here's the deal.
I'm willing to negotiate
with August on your behalf.
What?
But you're allies!
What do you mean by that?
Tell us.
[BRANDISH]
There isn't a wizard alive
who'd have a snowball's
chance in hell
against August in battle.
Except Irene, that is.
Back in Alvarez, August is
known as "the Calamity,"
while Irene is called
"the Scarlet Despair."
I don't have a
relationship with Irene,
so I wouldn't be
much help there.
But August and I have been close
ever since I was a little girl.
No promises, but I may be able
to talk him out of an attack.
Oh, wow!
For real?
Uh, thank you. That's an
incredible thing to offer.
No way! It's just a ploy.
She is not trustworthy!
She's trying to escape!
[BRANDISH] You can believe me or
not, that's totally your call.
[NATSU]
Hm...
I think we should
trust her, guys.
Lucy!
[chuckles]
That settles it for me!
I'm gonna kick that
old dude's butt!
Pay attention for once
in your life, would ya?
[HAPPY]
Classic Natsu move right there.
[NATSU] I got him and Lucy
can take on the other one!
[LUCY]
Me? Why?
So this is Zonia,
the sacred mountain,
where the heavenly black and
white maidens fought long ago.
As the white maiden
claimed victory,
snow began to blanket the peak
and still falls to this day.
Wow, Lady Irene,
I'm impressed you know
so much about this
country's old legends.
Idiot, she's actually
from Ishgar, remember?
I think you may be an idiot
for bringing that up.
Huh? Uh, please, forgive me!
[IRENE chuckles]
The heavenly white maiden
and black maiden
reminds me of the two of you.
I call dibs on black!
I'm obviously the
black one, dummy!
If you two were to
do battle, I wonder,
which one of you would
emerge the victor?
[BOTH whimpering]
[IRENE]
I'm joking.
[BOTH sigh]
[IRENE] The initial conflict
between those maidens
began because the two girls
were fighting over a man.
A darling little tale.
But as lovely as it may be,
I can't stand the chill.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LISANNA yells]
Come on, Sting. Wake up!
All the others...
are they still alive?
[GAJEEL]
Safe and sound. Don't worry.
What a disgrace.
We didn't stand a
chance. We're weak.
Don't beat yourself up.
We'll get revenge for you.
They'll be pickin' their
teeth up off the ground.
What's happening?
Hey, Gajeel!
[GAJEEL gasps]
Something's not right.
You can say that again.
[LEVY] It's so weird.
The snow's melting.
[JULIET]
Yay! Lady Irene, you're amazing!
[HEINE]
It's warm now.
It appears we have some
more guests joining us.
Has everything been prepared?
Bloodman. Larcade.
[STING crying]
[STING]
Damn it. What're we gonna do?
They've got those three
monsters on their side!
[chuckles]
Yeah, well, we got six
monsters on our side!
Whoa. You're counting me?
[LUCY]
As the Wizard King, August,
approaches from the east,
we set out with Brandish in tow,
hoping to convince him
to call off his attack.
Meanwhile, on the sacred
mountain of Zonia,
Sabertooth and Blue Pegasus
spring back into action
thanks to Gajeel's team.
They may have their sprits back,
but the foes they'll
face will send them
spiraling into a
world of terror.
Next time: "The Third Seal."
Death looms all around
and threatens to drag everyone
down to the underworld.