[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Fairy Tail's
Gray Fullbuster has won
the impromptu Maker
magic showdown!
Rufus snatched the
top spot from Gray
during our first game, Hidden.
I guess revenge really
is a dish best served cold!
[MATO stuttering]
[MATO] I'm too
shocked for words!
Yeah, it was a real
doozy of a battle!
Gray toughed it out
and came out on top.
That's Fairy Tail!
[CHAPATI] And, as a result,
Fairy Tail gains
another valuable point!
Beautiful! Way to
sock it to him, Gray!
It would have been quicker
if he'd gone all out first.
He fought wonderfully!
Looks like you were right
all along, First Master.
Sometimes emotions can
exceed all calculation.
[MAVIS] Firm belief
in certain victory.
Without that, all the
calculations in the world
won't help you win.
I simply bet everything
on his emotions.
When push came to shove,
I think Gray's inner strength
was far superior to Rufus's.
[MAKAROV] All of their
inner strengths will have
to be superior.
For Natsu and the rest
of his team as well.
This battle has
only just begun!
Now, let's show the
world that Fairy Tail
is the most powerful guild...
in all of Fiore!
[CHAPATI] Now, then!
Let's have a look at
the current scoreboard!
[CHAPATI] In first place
is the Fairy Tail guild,
with fifty points!
Five members remain: one leader
and four normal members!
[MATO] Sabertooth is in second
place with forty-nine points!
Fairy Tail only got one point
for defeating Rufus which
means that the
team's leader must
be one of their three
remaining members!
[YAJIMA] Interestingly
enough, Lamia Scale
is also in second place.
They have their leader
and two regular members
left on the field.
[CHAPATI] And in fourth
place we have Mermaid Heel,
with forty-three points.
Only their leader and
one normal member remain.
It's a close game,
but Fairy Tail's
really dominating out there.
[YAJIMA] They're the
only group that still has
all its members.
[MATO] Sure, Fairy Tail
has a serious advantage,
but can they
utilize it?
[HAPPY] The Hungry Wolf Knights!
[OLGA] So Rufus went
and got himself beat.
That's fine by me.
With him out
of the way,
I'll get more prey
all to myself.
[ROGUE] Fairy Tail
is truly formidable...
But I don't care.
Gajeel... Until I
beat you on my own,
I refuse to be
defeated by anyone else.
[CROWD cheering]
[FROSCH] Poor Rufus...
So, will Sabertooth crumble,
consigned to the
pages of history?
Or will we survive?
It's up to you, Sting.
Only your strength can
carry us through the day.
Whatever you choose,
I'm sure it'll be interesting.
[STING] Lector...
[MALE SABERTOOTH A] No way...
[MALE SABERTOOTH B]
He took down Master Jiemma!
[MALE SABERTOOTH A]
What are we supposed to do?!
Stay close to me...
Mark my words, Sting.
You will pay. I swear it!
[MINERVA] I doubt that...
Your reign of terror
ends here, Father.
And not a moment too soon.
Don't worry
about your seat;
it will be filled
by someone worthy.
Since he's beaten you, I believe
Sting should have the honor.
She thinks Sting
should be our new Master?
--[STING] I can't!
--[JIEMMA] Minerva!
You insolent wench!
How dare you--!
What's your mantra?
"Sabertooth has
no room for losers."
Or is there suddenly an
exception to that rule?
[JIEMMA growls]
Look, Sting. This is your power.
The power of raging emotions!
It's the very advantage
Natsu had over you.
I'm not sure
that I understand.
It seems you
were influenced by
my father's dogmatic
views on power.
"Friends are unnecessary.
Strength is everything."
But, deep down,
you're different.
Your feelings for Lector
are what give you strength.
His power lies...
in his emotions?
What does she mean?
[MINERVA] Rejoice.
That strength is yours
to cultivate,
however you see fit.
You can even surpass Natsu now.
I'm sorry. But, I
don't think I can.
Don't worry, Sting.
Your Lector's alive and well.
[STING] What?
[MINERVA] It may have
looked like my father's magic
disintegrated him, but
he was just teleported.
He's probably shaken,
but he's safe nonetheless.
You mean it, M'lady?!
He's still alive?
Lector didn't
really go bye-bye?
That's right.
[STING] Thank you!.
Thank you for keeping
him safe, M'lady!.
You can bring him
back now. Thank you.
[MINERVA] Don't be naïve.
You'll see your
dear Lector again,
but only after we've won
the Grand Magic Games.
[STING] What are
you saying, M'lady?!
Please, stop! Bring
Lector back now!
Why are you doing this to me?!
You should be thankful
I'm not like my father.
The Sabertooth guild is
still destined for greatness,
and I won't let
our status as the
best in Fiore
be taken from us.
Yes, you and Rogue
were defeated...
However, losing Lector seems
to have given you new strength.
In that respect, you could
say you've been reborn.
Surely you can
feel the difference.
Your sense of loss
turned into power...
One strong enough
to leave my father in
a helpless heap
on the floor.
But If we're to survive,
you must show the world
your new-found strength.
Only then will our
guild's reign be secure.
[MINERVA] Oh, and before
you get it in your head
to blow a hole through me...
Remember that
Lector's life can still
come to an end if I will it.
[STING] M'lady...
If I win. you'll return
Lector unharmed?
[MINERVA chuckles]
That's right. Just
win the games.
Use those feelings to crush
our enemies for good.
[STING] All right.
I'll win this for Lector.
Count on it.
Awesome! We're
back in first place!
If they can keep this up,
we'll win for sure!
[MACAO] Cool it.
We're not out of the woods yet.
[WAKABA] Sabertooth still has
four members in peak condition.
Plus, Lyon and Jura
are out there.
[MACAO] Yup We're just
gettin' to the hard part.
I'm starting to
get worried about
Natsu and the others.
Yes, they do seem to be
taking awhile, don't they?
[MAVIS] Unfortunately...
I think it's safe to assume
that something's gone wrong...
[LUCY] Get up! Natsu!
Pull yourself together!
[WENDY] He's not moving!
[MIRAJANE] Can you do
anything for him, Wendy?
I've tried everything.
Whatever's wrong with him,
I don't think I can help.
I'm so sorry!
If only I knew more healing
magic he wouldn't
be suffering like this!
Aw, come on,
don't blame yourself.
You hear that, Natsu?
You made Wendy cry.
I hope you're happy!
[NATSU] I can't help it...
If I don't get some food
in me, I might keel over.
Somehow I doubt we'll find
anything worth munching on.
It won't be long before
we're part of the scenery.
Thanks for the
optimism, fur ball!
We're back!
[NATSU] Any luck, Happy?
[HAPPY] No, the ceiling's
completely blocked, too.
[CARLA] There doesn't seem
to be any way out of here.
[NATSU] Man, this sucks!
And after we've made it so far.
We came in as jail breakers
and now we're inmates.
[WENDY] It's kind of pathetic.
[LUCY] Geez, my feet are killing
me. How big is this place?
Well, I've only heard
rumors from the guards, but,
I believe it's centered
below the castle,
and is roughly ten times
larger than all of Crocus.
[LUCY] I just had to ask...
I wish we had the
foresight to draw a map
of the place while we
were looking around.
By the way, Natsu,
weren't you supposed to be
in the tournament today?
I had to come
rescue you, dummy.
[HAPPY] He was so gung-ho
about saving you,
he wouldn't listen to reason.
An-y-way...
Aw, how sweet, I didn't
know you cared so much.
You know,
it's kinda funny.
Even though we're in
a hopeless situation,
I feel at ease when
I'm around you all.
That's what happens
when you're with friends.
Neat, huh?
Yes, it is...
[NATSU] Oh, uh.
just so you know.
I totally haven't forgotten
your name or anything.
[YUKINO] It's Yukino.
Please, don't worry about it...
But, if you don't mind...
There is something that I've
been meaning to thank you for.
What's that?
The way you
stood up for me.
Lucy told me all about it.
[YUKINO] She said that
when you heard why
I was kicked out of Sabertooth.
You stormed Crocus
Gardens and took on
the guild all by yourself.
Oh, that? It was
nothin'! No biggie!
That's Natsu-ese for
"I don't remember squat!"
You forget way too fast.
[NATSU] Get off my case!
By the way, I'm
sorry for draggin'
your pal into this mess.
Have you known
Arm-crazy-ohs long?
His name is "Arcadios"!
[YUKINO] Until now, my entire
world revolved around being
a member of Sabertooth; I had
nothing after I was kicked out.
Even now, I'm only
working for the royal army
on a temporary basis.
[LUCY] She doesn't
have anywhere to go,
not even a place to call home.
Her parents are gone,
and her sister went missing
when she was little.
[MIRAJANE] Oh...
That's rough.
Still, when I heard
that you fought for me,
I felt happiness that
I can't even describe...
It really meant the world
to me. Thank you so much.
[NATSU yells]
There's really no
need to be so formal.
For real; he'll just forget
about it all over again.
Yukino's
a decent girl.
Loyalty and gratitude
are hard to come by.
Next thing you know,
Lily's gonna
be popping the que-stion!
Do you and I need to have
another private talk, Happy?
Sorry, I was just kidding!
Stop with the angry face!
[MIRAJANE] This is nuts!
Is it just me, or does she
look a lot like Lisanna?
[LUCY] Well, now
that you mention it...
Lisanna? Who's that?
[MIRAJANE giggles]
She's my little sister.
[YUKINO gasps]
[far-off rumbling]
[NATSU sniffs]
Smell that?
It feels like there's
a new flow of air in here.
It could mean
there's an exit!
We'll go and
take a look!
Do you think that shaking
caused a cave-in somewhere?
We can only hope.
Why is this scent so familiar?
[CARLA] Hey guys, there's
an opening over here
that I think we can
squeeze through!
[HAPPY] Good job!
Freedom, here we come!
[PANTHERLILY] This seems
less like a passageway
and more like melted rock.
[WENDY] It's certainly
a tight fit.
Yeah, you're not kidding.
Think you can
manage it, Yukino?
Yes, but it'll
take a second.
[HAPPY] You can do it, Natsu!
[WENDY grunting]
[NATSU yells]
[WENDY yells]
Can I get a
little help here?
What? Too many
late night snacks?
[LUCY] If you're
gonna be a jerk,
at least be a useful
one and help me!
[NATSU grunting]
--[LUCY stuttering]
--[YUKINO] Oh my...
I swear It's not
what it looks like!
Someone's here!
I think they might be hurt!
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKINO] Colonel Arcadios?!
[NATSU] Ah-ha! So
that smell was Crazy-toes!
[PANTHERLILY] She
just said his name.
[NATSU] Hey, you
alright? Helloooo?
The white knight...
He sure picked a strange
place to take a cat-nap.
But how'd he get here?
Was he tossed in
with the rest of us?
[YUKINO] A fall wouldn't
explain these injuries.
[ARCADIOS groans]
Run away...
[ALL gasp]
[YUKINO] Colonel Arcadios!
What happened to you?!
[WENDY] Hold still,
I'll heal you.
No, forget about me.
You have to get out of here!
Pop go... the crim'nals!
[ALL scream]
What is that?
It's acid!
It's eating the
ground away!
Is that what made
the opening for us?
[MAN 2] My first
catch of the day!
And she's a beaut!
What a haul!
[ALL screaming]
[HAPPY grunting]
[LUCY] So much ow...
[NATSU] Who are these guys?!
[MIRAJANE] What is that?
[YUKINO] Confetti?
[YUKINO] I think they
attacked Arcadios!
[ARCADIOS] Get out
of here! You're in danger!
Why, old man? Do you
know who they are?
[ARCADIOS] They're an
independent squad that
serves the Fiore Kingdom
from the shadows...
Ruthless, blood-thirsty
executioners
[LEADER] Hungry Wolf Knights.
Commence Operation
Fifteen-hundred.
They're Executioners?
They don't exactly
look the part.
Trust me, they're very
good at their jobs.
If the rumors are true,
then we're facing some
relentless hunters.
A group of royal
execution machines.
The Hungry Wolf Knights!
They're the reason
it's impossible
to leave this cursed
place... Alive, anyway.
[LEADER] By the authority
granted to us by the
Kingdom of Fiore,
we, The Hungry Wolf Knights,
will now carry out
your sentence.
[NATSU snickering]
Natsu?
[NATSU laughing]
This really isn't a good
time to go cuckoo.
[NATSU] Oh, sorry, my bad!
But, can you blame me?
I mean, just look at these guys!
[LUCY] Yeah, I get
what you're saying...
[WENDY] None of their outfits
really say "Knight" to me.
[NATSU] Especially, him!
Shucks...
That's a good point.
Usually you'd expect a group
of knights to dress in
the same uniforms.
Where are your helmets
and suits of armor?
Haulin' armor
ain't our style.
We're a secret squad, so we
gottta stay under cover.
If we gussied up in armor,
we wouldn't be secret no more.
Not that your fashion
lessons aren't interesting,
but I've got a real achin'
to punch your teeth in.
What the hell?!
If you're fishin'
for trouble...
You hooked yourself a whopper.
[ARCADIOS] Don't let their
appearances fool you!
Be very cautious
of their magic.
Make one wrong move
and you're as good as dead.
[NATSU] That's just the kind of
challenge I live for, old man.
This is awesome!
One epic brawl and our ticket
out of this dump is secure!
Lucky us.
Let's try to leave one conscious
so we can ask for directions.
The two of you
should get back
since you don't have
your keys with you.
We'll take care
of these guys.
Can't say I'm
a fan of this
"sitting on the
sidelines" garbage.
Careful, Arcadios.
Don't move too fast.
You two give Lucy
and Yukino a hand.
Aw c'mon, I can
help you fight!
Not such a good idea.
[PANTHERLILY] It's been
a while since I last fought.
I've sure missed it!
[PANTHERLILY giggles]
You must stop them.
Fighting the Wolf Knights isn't
just reckless, it's suicide.
[YUKINO] Please, everyone.
Be careful...
I'm all fired up now.
[LEADER] There are
plenty of miscreants
who did not fear
The Hungry Wolf Knights.
But they're all dead.
Your bones will join
theirs soon enough.
[GIRL 1] We'll start things
off. I hope you're ready.
What?! Just
the two of you?
In that case, I'll
take you on myself!
Guess they beat us
to the punch again.
That ain't fair!
I wanted to brawl!
Let's do it, Cosmos.
We'll dazzle them with
our beautiful dance, Kamika.
Now.
[KAMIKA] Paper Blizzard:
Red Dance!
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Paper Magic won't work!
Not when I can
roast the lot of 'em!
[NATSU] Hey! What gives?!
How are they
not burning?!
My red paper is infused
with fire spirits.
Touch them if you dare!
Oh, I'm gonna
touch 'em alright!
Get in my belly, you beauti--
[NATSU screaming]
I'll make sure you
have your fill, then.
[NATSU screaming]
Hold on! I'm
coming to help you!
Sky Dragon Roar!
Nicely done, Wendy!
Way to huff and puff!
[NATSU] Alright then,
we'll go two-on-two.
I'll follow your
lead, Natsu.
[COSMOS] Beautiful...
Don't forget about us.
Hold on.
We should just keep our eyes on
the enemy's movements for now.
Let Wendy and Natsu handle this.
Pop!
Ready for this, Wendy?!
Let's go!
Fire Dragon Wing Attack!
Ohh... A couple of
Dragon Slayers?
Sky Dragon Crushing Fang!
And such lovely long hair.
You might wanna
pay attention!
You're the least
beautiful thing here!
Say what?
Shoot, this is boring.
They're just
toying with them.
--[NATSU] Fire Dragon... Roar!
--[WENDY] Sky Dragon... Roar!
Way to go!
Their teamwork is
truly spectacular.
[PANTHERLILY] I don't
sense them anymore.
Did we get 'em?!
[MIRAJANE] No. Not yet.
They're concealing
their magic power!
A plant bud with
red paper on it?
[NATSU &amp; WENDY grunt]
We are the truly
spectacular team.
Be good little
law-breakers
and take your punishment.
I think Miss "Poofy Pink Hat"
is using plant magic!
I don't get it.
How are they giving
us so much trouble?
Paper and plants
should be easy pickings
for wind and fire users.
[COSMOS giggles]
Think so,
pretty kitty?
We can put your theory
to the test, if you like.
What do you say, love?
Of course!
I still have plenty
of colors to show them.
[NATSU &amp; WENDY grunt]
[MIRAJANE] I can't see anything!
I didn't know paper
could be used like this!
[WENDY screams]
[COSMOS] I've got you now.
Wendy!
[NATSU yells]
Take a moment and cool off
and you'll feel much better!
[NATSU] I've spent a
life-time fighting off
colder ice
attacks than this!.
I don't even feel it!
[NATSU yells]
[NATSU &amp; WENDY grunting]
[WENDY] Oh no!
[COSMOS] Your magic complements
mine beautifully, as always.
Darn it! I can't
move a muscle!
[WENDY] All of these
thorns are pricking me!
[KAMIKA] Two
lawbreakers captured.
I guess all that's
left is to execute them.
[NATSU &amp; WENDY scream]
Gross! What are
those things?!
Carnivorous plants?!
[WENDY screaming]
This is so nasty!
They'll be killed!
Don't worry, we're gonna
get you out of there!
[NATSU] The hell you will!
Things are starting to get good!
Wait your turn!
[PANTHERLILY] Get over it!
This isn't the time for that!
I'll pull out
your whiskers!
Don't test me!
He puts on the tough
guy act pretty thick.
I wonder if he'll keep
it up as he's eaten alive.
Let's turn these
freaks into compost!
[WENDY] I'm ready when you are!
Sky Dragon...
Wing Attack!
That's awesome!
Dragon Slayer teams
are unstoppable!
And here I thought
Natsu and Gajeel
worked well together.
It just goes to show ya
how close he and Wendy are.
Wait. When did Natsu
and Wendy start dating?!
And once again,
you don't get it.
All right. You ready?
Ohh yeah. I've got
a fire in my belly.
[WENDY shouts]
[NATSU shouts]
[CARLA] Must they
be so dramatic?
[HAPPY] Wow! They're
in perfect sync!
The Hungry Wolf Knights
are being pushed back?
Just how powerful are they?
After all the battles
they've had to fight together,
they're super powerful.
I wouldn't be
surprised if they knew
what each other was thinking.
He trusts her.
She trusts him...
What a powerful bond.
That must be why
Fairy Tail's so strong.
[ARCADIOS] Don't
drop your guard.
This fight's far from over.
The executioners' true
terror is yet to come.
[LEADER] Neppa. Uosuke...
Alright, Freshwater,
let's splash this party.
Let's haul'em in!
There's two more!
It's our turn, Lily!
I'm right behind you!
Hook, line, and sinker!
[NATSU &amp; WENDY shout]
[MIRAJANE &amp; PANTHERLILY yell]
Ka-pop!
Sploosh!
Cheaters!
It was two-on-two!
Where's your sense of honor?
We never accepted
any formal challenge.
Our only goal is to
execute you lawbreakers.
We was just testin'
the waters, is all.
[PANTHERLILY] That's
some powerful stuff!
[MIRAJANE] Keep your
distance around chubby.
[NEPPA chuckles]
What's the matter?
Can't take the heat, hot stuff?
Keep your
balance, Wendy!
I'm trying!
[COSMOS] Even if it was just for
a moment, you made a complete
disarray of our
beautiful handiwork.
And you'll suffer
the punishment.
I promise it won't
be pleasant...
Especially...
for the loud and ugly one!
[NATSU] Shut your fly-trap!
[NATSU yells]
Natsu! You okay?
[WENDY yells]
This isn't the
time to be worrying
about others, my dear.
Illusion magic!
No problem! I should be
able to break through!
Sky Dragon... Roar!
[COSMOS giggles]
Simply beautiful...
What in the
heck is this?!
Soon you'll dance
with the grim reaper...
As my Corpse Flower
blooms from your blood!
Wendy!
[NATSU] I honestly didn't think
those goofy lookin' knights
would be that strong!
[HAPPY] If looks
gave you strength,
I'd be the strongest
member of the guild!
[NATSU] You keep thinkin' that!
Do you realize how
frustrating it is to lose
to a bunch of circus freaks?!
[HAPPY] I thought their
outfits were pretty snazzy.
[NATSU] I'll rephrase; if
Miss "Rose and Thorns"
took your fish, would you still
think she dresses well?
[HAPPY] No Flower Lady's
taking this cat's supper!
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
Fairy Tail vs. Executioners!
[NATSU] I refuse to lose to such
a dumb lookin' group of jerks!
[HAPPY] Just try
and take my fish!
My claws will be
happy to meet ya!