- Narrator: HARGEON HAS
MANY FINE RESTAURANTS,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING MAGICAL
ABOUT THIS NEWEST ADDITION,
"8 ISLAND."
- Lucy: WELCOME.
I'D BE SO HAPPY
TO TAKE YOUR ORDER.
- THANKS.  I'D LIKE
THE BLUE SKY MEAT SAUCE
AND SOME HOLY SODA WITH ICE.
- BEASTMAN CURRY FOR ME,
PLEASE.
- SURE, BOTH GREAT CHOICES.
CAN I INTEREST YOU
IN SOME DESSERT AS WELL?
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YEAH, I THINK
I'M GONNA TRY
THE RUBY PARFAIT.
- MAKE THAT TWO.
- COMING RIGHT UP.
- CAN I GET SOME
SERVICE TOO, MISS?
- YES, SIR.
AHH! WAIT!
WHAT AM I DOING
WAITRESSING?!
- Natsu: LUCY.
- YEAH, WHAT?
- YOU'RE WORKING A JOB
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
- SINCE WHEN DOES
WAITING TABLES
QUALIFY AS
LEGITIMATE WIZARD WORK?
AND WHY DO I HAVE
TO WEAR THIS HORRIBLE OUTFIT?
- NOT MY IDEA.
- I MEAN, I KNOW
I CAN ROCK THIS UNIFORM,
BUT STILL.
- WHATEVER.
- THE CHEF HERE AT "8 ISLAND"
USES MAGIC TO COOK ALL
OF HIS TASTY DISHES.
SO HE THOUGHT IT'D
BE KIND OF COOL
IF THE WAIT STAFF WERE
MAGIC USERS AS WELL.
- Natsu: ( chewing )
GEEZ, LUCY.
WE AGREED TO TAKE THIS
JOB FOR YOU, REMEMBER?
- ( gasping )
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE EATING
THE CUSTOMER'S FOOD.
- BUT THROWING TRAYS IS OKAY?
- Gray: LIGHTEN UP.
THE UNIFORMS
AREN'T ALL THAT BAD
IF YOU ASK ME.
- YOU'RE BARELY
EVEN WEARING ONE.
- WATCH IT.  DON'T YOU FORGET
THAT WE'RE DOING THIS
TO PAY YOUR RENT.
- UGH, YEAH, I KNOW.
- EH, IT'S COOL.
LOOK THERE.
- HUH?
- I KNOW YOU WANT SOMETHING.
ISN'T THAT TRUE?
NOW TELL ME.
- YEAH, I-- UH...
- WE'LL HAVE A...
- JUST GIVE US...
- YES, WE'LL TAKE
ONE OF EVERYTHING.
- WELL NOW,
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
I AM TRULY GRATEFUL.
- OUR PLEASURE, MA'AM.
- THAT'S ONE WAY TO DO IT,
I GUESS.
- SEEMS TO WORK PRETTY WELL.
- AH, YES, THE THRILL
OF A NEW CHALLENGE.
- ( Happy speaking )
- Yajima:
TOP-NOTCH JOB TODAY, KIDS.
GOT TO SAY, I'M MOST
PLEASANTLY SURPRISED
BY ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
YOU'RE WELCOME HERE ANY TIME.
- THANK YOU.
WE'VE LEARNED MUCH
FROM THIS EXPERIENCE.
- AND WHAT WAS THAT?
"YOU LOVE CLOTHES"?
- Gray: NOW I KNOW HOW TIRED
MIRA MUST BE AFTER WORK.
- Natsu: AND HOW STUFFED
HER BELLY MUST BE.
- SHE SERVES THE FOOD
INSTEAD OF EATING IT ALL.
- WELL, THAT'S HER LOSS.
- AND YOUR WEIGHT GAIN.
- IF I MAY ASK YOU, SIR,
WHAT IS THE STATE OF
THE MAGIC COUNCIL THESE DAYS?
- WELL, OF COURSE I STEPPED DOWN
SOME TIME AGO.
- THE MAGIC COUNCIL?!
- WHAT THE HECK'S
GOTTEN INTO YOU TWO?
DID YOU DUNCES FORGET
MR. YAJIMA WAS A MEMBER?
- ( gasps )
- AFTER ZIEG-- OR WAIT,
WAS HIS NAME ZELLAL?
- YOU MEAN JELLAL?
- AH, YES.
AFTER HE AND THAT OTHER
INTERLOPER ULTEAR
THREW EVERYTHING INTO DISARRAY,
I PARTED WAYS WITH
THE ORGANIZATION.
I'M NOT USUALLY
ONE FOR GOSSIP,
BUT THERE HAVE BEEN RUMORS
GOING AROUND LATELY
THAT A PLAN TO REESTABLISH
THE MAGIC COUNCIL
IS IN THE WORKS.
OUR IGNORANCE AND
MISGUIDED ACTIONS
CAUSED YOU
A GREAT DEAL OF TROUBLE.
I AM TRULY SORRY.
- IT'S FINE.
THEY SAY YOU STOOD YOUR GROUND
IN OPPOSITION TO FIRING
THE ETHERION
RIGHT UNTIL THE VERY END.
YOUR CONVICTION IS ADMIRABLE.
- POLITICS JUST ISN'T MY THING.
BUT COOKING...
WHOO! HOO!
OH BOY! HA HA!
THAT WAS WHAT
I WAS BORN TO DO.
BY THE WAY, YOU BOYS
LISTEN VERY CAREFULLY.
NOW I EXPECT THIS NEW COUNCIL
TO BE QUITE DIFFERENT.
I WILL NO LONGER BE THERE.
I TOOK A LAX ATTITUDE TOWARD
FAIRY TAIL'S HIJINKS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?!
DON'T TEST THEIR PATIENCE
WITH YOUR CARELESS DESTRUCTION!
- NO, WE PROMISE
WE WON'T, SIR.
- HMM.
SAY HELLO TO MAKI FOR ME,
WILL YOU, HUH?
- AYE.
- WE CERTAINLY WILL, SIR.
AND THANKS AGAIN
FOR THE WORK.
- ULTEAR...
WHO KNOWS WHERE
SHE MAY BE HIDING?
- Narrator:
THIS OMINOUS AIRSHIP
BELONGS TO THE DARK GUILD,
"GRIMOIRE HEART."
- ORACION SEIS, HUH?
THEY'RE MAKING THEIR MOVE.
- Narrator: AND THIS WOMAN
IS THE FORMER COUNCIL MEMBER
IN QUESTION, ULTEAR.
IT TURNS OUT,
SHE WAS ACTUALLY A MEMBER
OF THE AFOREMENTIONED
DARK GUILD ALL ALONG.
- SO, MASTER HADES,
HOW SHALL WE RESPOND?
- WE SHALL ALLOW THEM
TO DO AS THEY PLEASE FOR NOW.
SURELY THOSE ON THE OTHER SIDE
WILL NOT STAND IDLY BY.
AND IN THE CONFUSION THAT
WILL ENSUE FROM THEIR CLASH,
WE WILL TAKE
THE OPPORTUNITY TO LOCATE
THE REMAINING KEYS
TO ZEREF'S SEAL.
AND IF FORTUNE
SHOULD TRULY SMILE ON US,
PERHAPS SOME OF OUR RIVALS
MAY BE ELIMINATED
IN THE PROCESS AS WELL.
- SUCH AS FAIRY TAIL PERHAPS?
- ( chuckles )
- Lucy: WHAT'S ALL THIS?
- Mirajane: IT'S A CHART
LISTING OUT THE DARK GUILDS.
- OUI. SHE HAD ME
DRAW IT UP FOR HER.
- A TROUBLING SIGHT.
THERE ARE FAR MORE
THAN I'D REALIZED.
- WHAT BROUGHT THIS ON?
- UNFORTUNATELY, THEY'VE BEEN
NOTICEABLY MORE
ACTIVE AS OF LATE.
- THAT MEANS WE NEED TO
STRENGTHEN RELATIONSHIPS
WITH OUR FELLOW GUILDS.
- OH.
- WHAT'S THE BIG CIRCLE
IN THE MIDDLE SUPPOSED TO BE?
- Juvia: I KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
IT'S THE BARAM ALLIANCE
OF DARK GUILDS.
- ( gasps )
- Juvia: THE THREE MAJOR PLAYERS
IN THAT ALLIANCE
ARE ORACION SEIS,
TARTAROS, AND GRIMOIRE HEART.
ALL POWERFUL
IN THEIR OWN RIGHT,
BUT COMBINED,
THEY'RE THE STRONGEST FORCE
IN THE SHADOWY GUILD UNDERWORLD.
EACH CONTROLS LESSER GUILDS
THAT CARRY OUT THE DIRTY WORK
THEY DON'T WISH
TO DO THEMSELVES.
HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE ON THIS
CHART WHO REMAINS INDEPENDENT.
RAVEN TAIL.
- OH, MAN...
I RECOGNIZE
THE NAME EISENWALD.
- I'M SURE.
THAT'S THE GUILD
ERIGOR BELONGED TO.
- ( silent )
- SO EISENWALD WAS ACTUALLY
JUST A KIND OF SUB-GUILD
THAT WORKED UNDER
THIS ORACION SEIS?
- Wakaba: I'VE SEEN A LOT
OF THESE NAMES BEFORE.
- Macao: I THINK SOME OF THEM
EVEN USED TO BE LEGIT.
- Mirajane: THERE WAS ONE MORE,
GHOUL SPIRIT,
WHICH THE THUNDER LEGION
TOOK OUT.
- Lucy: YEAH?
- MOST OF THE GUILDS
THAT GAJEEL AND I DESTROYED
WHEN THE TWO OF US
WERE MEMBERS OF PHANTOM LORD
WERE UNDER ORACION SEIS,
EXCEPT FOR FAIRY TAIL
OF COURSE.
BUT WE'RE ALL
GREAT FRIENDS NOW, RIGHT?
- I WOULDN'T REMIND 'EM OF THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
- CREEPY.
HEY, YOU GUYS,
DO YOU THINK THEY'LL
TAKE IT OUT ON US?
- AH, RELAX.
DON'T WORRY YOUR PRETTY
LITTLE HEAD ABOUT THEM.
FROM WHAT I HEAR,
THEY'VE ONLY GOT SIX MEMBERS
IN THE GUILD ANYWAY.
- YEAH, THEY SOUND LIKE
SMALL POTATOES IF YOU ASK ME.
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE THEM.
THOSE SIX WIZARDS MAKE UP
ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL GUILDS OUT THERE.
- SPEAKING OF
THE ORACION SEIS...
WORD HAS COME DOWN.
WE MUST DESTROY THEM.
- HUH?
- All: WHAT?!
- Mirajane:
WELCOME BACK, MASTER.
- ( groans )
- I HOPE THAT YOU HAD
A GOOD TIME AT THE CONFERENCE.
- ( gasps )
I'M SURE.
- BUT, MASTER,
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- ORACION SEIS' RECENT ACTIVITY
WAS THE FOCUS OF MUCH DISCUSSION
AT THE CONFERENCE.
THEY POSE AN URGENT THREAT
THAT CAN NO LONGER BE IGNORED.
THEREFORE, THEY MUST BE
DEALT WITH IMMEDIATELY.
WE WILL TAKE THEM DOWN
BEFORE THEY CAN HARM
ANY OF OUR FELLOW GUILDS
WE ARE SWORN TO PROTECT.
- AND WE GOT TO DO
ALL THE HEAVY LIFTING, RIGHT?
- TYPICAL.
- FAIRY TAIL WILL BE
TAKING THEM ON BY OURSELVES?
- THIS ENEMY
IS FAR MORE POWERFUL
THAN ANY OTHER WE
HAVE FACED BEFORE.
TO FIGHT THEM ALONE
WOULD BE TOO DANGEROUS.
OUR ATTACK WOULD SURELY
INCUR THE WRATH
OF THE ENTIRE
BARAM ALLIANCE IN NO TIME.
WHICH IS WHY FAIRY TAIL
WILL JOIN A COALITION
OF MAGICAL GUILDS.
- All: A COALITION?
- Makarov: FAIRY TAIL...
BLUE PEGASUS...
LAMIA SCALE...
AND CAIT SHELTER.
THESE FOUR GUILDS
WILL SELECT MEMBERS
TO REPRESENT THEM
IN THE ALLIED FORCE.
TOGETHER, WE WILL WORK
TO BRING DOWN THE ENEMY!
- BUT WE CAN HANDLE IT
OURSELVES, GRAMPS.
IN FACT, I COULD
PROBABLY EVEN DO IT ALONE.
( grunts )
- DON'T BE A FOOL.
THE MASTER IS WISE
TO CONSIDER
THE LONG-TERM CONSEQUENCES.
- WHOA, JUST HOLD ON A SECOND,
YOU GUYS.
WE'RE ONLY TALKING ABOUT
SIX PEOPLE AREN'T WE?
I MEAN, ARE THEY SERIOUSLY
ALL THAT SCARY?
- Cobra: I CAN HEAR IT.
- THAT SWEET SOUND OF LIGHT
CRASHING TO THE GROUND.
- Racer: DON'T JUMP TO
CONCLUSIONS SO QUICKLY, COBRA.
THOUGH, SPEED CAN
BE A WONDERFUL THING.
- RACER, THE MAGIC WE SEEK
IS RIGHT UNDER OUR NOSES.
I'M SURE OF IT.
- THAT ANCIENT
AND HIDDEN MAGIC
WITH THE POWER
TO TURN LIGHT INTO COMPLETE
AND TOTAL DARKNESS,
OH YEAH!
- NIRVANA.
- ( snoring )
- ( staff clangs )
- A LEGENDARY POWER,
ONE THAT WILL SOON BE OURS.
- ARE YOU SURE WE SHOULD
PUT ALL OUR BETS ON NIRVANA?
IT SOUNDS
TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
- LOOK THERE.
THE DARKNESS THAT
SPREADS THROUGH THE TREES
MEANS NIRVANA
IS CLOSE AT HAND.
THE FOREST
IS BEGINNING TO DIE.
- ( snorting )
- Lucy: I KNOW
I'VE SAID THIS BEFORE,
BUT I'VE GOT A REALLY
BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS MISSION.
AND WHY AM I HERE?
I'M NOT ALL THAT STRONG.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO HELP YOU GUYS, ANYWAY.
- LOOK, THIS AIN'T
NO PICNIC FOR ME, EITHER.
SO QUIT POUTING, WOULD YOU?
- HMPH.
- ( pouts )
- ( moans )
- WE'RE HERE FOR ONE REASON.
BECAUSE MASTER
PUT HIS FAITH IN US,
SO LET'S NOT DISAPPOINT HIM.
- I KNOW.  YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT GAJEEL AND JUVIA
ARE BETTER FIGHTERS.
- THEY CAN'T GO 'CAUSE MASTER
SENT THE TWO OF THEM
ON ANOTHER MISSION.
- ( groans )
I DON'T CARE.
I JUST...
WANNA...
GET... THERE.
- IT JUST SEEMS LIKE WE'RE
ALWAYS PICKED FOR THIS STUFF.
- YOU SHOULD
CONSIDER IT AN HONOR.
AND TODAY WILL BE OUR
FIRST JOINT OPERATION
INVOLVING THE OTHER
ALLIED GUILDS.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT WE ALL
FOCUS OUR EFFORTS
ON STARTING TO BUILD
A POSITIVE RAPPORT.
- Happy: THERE IT IS.
THE RENDEZVOUS SPOT.
- Lucy: GREAT,
ANOTHER CREEPY OLD MANSION.
- Erza: IT'S THE SECOND HOME
OF BLUE PEGASUS MASTER, BOB.
- OH, HIM.
- Narrator:
TO JOG YOUR MEMORY A BIT,
MASTER BOB
IS A SKILLED WIZARD
AND, ALSO, A MAN.
- HE MAKES ME FEEL FUNNY.
- GRAY, BE NICE.
MASTER BOB MAY BE
A LITTLE ECCENTRIC,
BUT HE DOES DESERVE
OUR UTMOST RESPECT.
- YEAH, ECCENTRIC.
- ( moans ) JUST TELL ME
WHEN WE'RE THERE, GUYS.
- OKAY, WE'RE THERE.
- Young man: YES!
THEY'RE HERE AT LAST!
- Two young men: AT LAST!
- Young man:
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
HELLO.
- Both: HELLO.
- Young man: FAIRY...
- Both: FAIRY...
- Young man: TAIL...
- Both: TAIL...
- All: WIZARDS!
- HUH?
- All:
WE'RE SO GLAD YOU CAME.
( echoes )
- WE ARE...
- THE BLUE PEGASUS...
- ELITE CREW.
- All: THE TRIMENS.
- "HUNDRED NIGHTS" HIBIKI.
- "HOLY NIGHT" EVE.
- "STILL NIGHT" REN.
- Lucy:
THE TRIMENS FROM BLUE PEGASUS.
WOW, THAT IS SO COOL.
THOSE GUYS ARE LIKE
THE HOTTEST WIZARDS AROUND NOW.
HIBIKI LAYTIS
IS ALWAYS NEAR THE TOP
OF "SORCERER WEEKLY'S" MOST
ELIGIBLE WIZARD BACHELOR'S LIST.
HE'S BEEN IN THE TOP-THREE
FOR THE LAST FEW MONTHS.
- WOULD YOU
LOOK AT THOSE GUYS?
I FEEL TOTALLY
UNDERDRESSED!
- ( sighs ) AND THEY
ARE NOT ON THE LIST.
- I'VE HEARD TALES
OF YOUR BEAUTY...
AND THEY'RE TRUE.
- IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU,
MISS TITANIA.
- PLEASE COME WITH ME.
- UH...
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO FRESHEN UP?
- OR MAYBE SOMETHING TO EAT?
- NO.
- AH, BUT THERE'S CAKE.
WANT SOME?
- NO, THANK YOU.
- GEEZ, WHAT IS THE DEAL
WITH THESE GUYS?
- PLEASE, HAVE A SEAT.
- ( gasps )
- OH WOW.
YOU'RE ALMOST TOO CUTE.
- I AM?
- NO JOKE, WHAT IS THE DEAL
WITH THESE CORNBALLS?
- I MISSED SOMETHING.
WHO ARE THEY?
- IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET A FUTURE ALLY.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO WORKING TOGETHER.
- YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S ALMOST UNREAL.
IS THIS A DREAM?
- UH...
- I HOPE NOT BECAUSE
I'VE ALWAYS ADMIRED YOU.
- HERE.
YOU CAN HAVE IT
IF YOU WANT,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
I MADE IF FOR YOU.
- NOW HE'S BEING COY?!
- WELL, YOU LADIES
MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
FEEL FREE
TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
- All: WE DON'T MIND.
- Both: UH...
- Ichiya: CALM DOWN, MEN.
GIVE THESE LADIES
SOME BREATHING ROOM.
- WHOA, THAT VOICE,
IT'S SILKY SMOOTH.
- YES, ICHIYA, SIR.
- HIM? OH DEAR.
- IT'S BEEN FAR TOO LONG,
MISS SCARLET.
- A LONG TIME, YES.
I NEVER EXPECTED
TO SEE YOU HERE.
- OH, HOW I'VE MISSED YOU,
MY SWEET HONEY.
BUT DON'T CRY.
I'M HERE.
OOH.
- Both: MY SWEET HONEY?!
- ( gasping )
- WHOA, SHE'S SHAKING.
- A SURPRISE.
- Trimens: A SURPRISE!
- A REUNION.
- Trimens: A REUNION!
- All: OH, YES!
OH, YES! OH, YES!
- Trimens: WE DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
MR. ICHIYA.
PLEASE FORGIVE
OUR RUDENESS.
- YOU KNOW
THAT IS NOT TRUE!
- YOU IDIOTS!
WE HAVE WORK TO DO!
- RIGHT, BOSS.
RIGHT, BOSS.
- "BOSS," HUH?
I THINK THAT'S LIKE
THE THIRD THING
THEY'VE CALLED HIM.
- THEY'RE A BUNCH
OF MIXED NUTS.
- IT SEEMS THAT DESTINY
HAS BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
MISS ERZA, MISS LUCY...
YOU TWO NOT SO MUCH.
SNIFF, SNIFF, SNIFF, SNIFF.
SWEET PARFUM!
- Narrator: PARFUM IS JUST
A FANCY WAY OF SAYING "SCENT."
- HE'S CREEPING ME OUT.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
I'D NEVER CHOOSE TO
BE IN HIS COMPANY.
HOWEVER, HE IS
A GIFTED WIZARD.
- LISTEN UP, YOU BLUE PEGASUS
PLAYBOY WANNABES,
YOU'D BE WISE TO KEEP
YOUR HANDS OFF THESE LADIES.
WE CLEAR?
- CLEAR AS CRYSTAL.
NOW TAKE YOUR LEAVE.
- THANKS FOR DROPPING BY.
- Both: THANKS FOR DROPPING BY.
- WE'RE HERE ON SOME
SERIOUS BUSINESS, YOU KNOW?
CAN YOU PRETTY BOYS
EVEN FIGHT?
- YOU WANT TO FIND OUT?
- YEAH, WE'RE REAL TOUGH, PAL.
- FIGHT?!
WELL, COUNT ME IN!
- EVERYBODY NEEDS
TO CALM DOWN THIS INSTANT.
- MY HONEY.
- ( gasps )
- YOUR SWEET PARFUM,
IT STILL DRIVES ME CRAZY.
( moans )
- YOU STAY FAR AWAY FROM ME!
- MAN.
- NICE RIGHT HOOK.
- ( gasps )
- MAN!
- YOU DARE TO GREET US
WITH THIS FLYING BUFFOON?
LAMIA SCALE DESERVES
MORE RESPECT.
WE INSIST ON IT.
- Narrator:
THIS MAN IS LYON BASTIA.
HE AND GRAY
SHARE A LONG HISTORY TOGETHER.
AND BOTH TRAINED UNDER
THE SAME MASTER.
- IT'S YOU!
- IT'S YOU.
- HEY, SO YOU WENT
AND JOINED A GUILD AFTER ALL.
- ( muffled ) MAN!
MAN!
OH NO!
DON'T HURT THE FACE!
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- HE WAS THE ONE
WHO ATTACKED ME, GRAY.
- WATCH IT, THAT'S OUR LEADER
YOU'RE MESSING WITH, PAL.
- HOW DARE YOU.
- YOU AND YOUR MEN
SHOULD JUST TURN AROUND
AND GO HOME.
- Sherry: I SUPPOSE
THAT MEANS WOMEN
CAN STAY AND FIGHT?
MARIONETTE ATTACK!
CARPET DOLL!
- WHAT DID I DO?
HOLD ON,
I RECOGNIZE THAT MAGIC.
- ( laughing )
SHERRY?! NO WAY!
YOU JOINED THE GUILD TOO?
- Narrator:
THIS GIRL IS SHERRY BLENDI.
SHE IS A COMRADE OF LYON'S
AND IS ALSO
MADLY IN LOVE WITH HIM.
- ( laughs )
I WAS HOPING YOU FAIRIES
HADN'T FORGOTTEN WHO I AM.
BUT, PLEASE, DO TRY
TO FORGET WHO I WAS, OKAY?
- STILL CRAZY.
- I HAVE BEEN BORN ANEW
BY THE POWER OF LOVE.
- MORE! I MUST BREATH IN
MORE OF YOUR PARFUM!
- OH NO! STAY BACK!
- LET'S GO, LYON!
- MY PLEASURE!
- I'M READY TO PARTY.
- I COULD NEVER LOVE YOU.
- WELL, THE FEELING'S MUTUAL.
- ENOUGH!
WE'RE HERE TO WORK
TOGETHER AS A GROUP
TO DESTROY
THE ORACION SEIS.
THIS IS NOT THE TIME FOR US
TO FIGHT AMONG OURSELVES.
- YES, JURA.
- THAT'S JURA?
- SO THAT'S REALLY HIM?
- LAMIA SCALE'S TOP-MAN,
IRON ROCK JURA.
- WHO?
- THAT GUY
IS ONE OF
THE TEN WIZARD SAINTS.
- YEAH, WHICH MEANS
HE'S KIND OF A BIG DEAL.
- SO FOUR FROM FAIRY TAIL
AND FOUR FROM BLUE PEGASUS?
HA! FUNNY, OUR GUILD ONLY NEEDED
TO SEND THREE MEMBERS.
- AWW MAN, WHY DO THEY ALWAYS
FORGET ABOUT ME?
- IT SEEMS WE
HAVE REPRESENTATIVES
FROM THREE GUILDS.
THE MEMBERS FROM CAIT SHELTER
HAVE YET TO ARRIVE.
- YES, AND ABOUT THAT GUILD,
I HEAR THEY'RE
ONLY SENDING ONE.
- JUST ONE MEMBER?
- Gray: THAT'S INSANE!
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE UP AGAINST
A POWERFUL GROUP HERE.
- ONE? IF THAT'S TRUE,
HOW CRAZY INTENSE
IS THIS GUY GONNA BE?
- AHH!
OWW.
HI, I, UH--
I'M SORRY
I GOT HERE SO LATE.
I'VE COME FROM
THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD.
MY NAME'S WENDY.
IT'S NICE TO MEET ALL OF YOU.
- ( gasps )
- SHE'S A KID?!
- A LITTLE GIRL?
- WENDY, HUH?
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: MAN, THAT'S
AN INTERESTING GROUP
WE GOT HOOKED UP WITH.
- Happy: CAN YOU BELIEVE
LYON AND SHERRY CAME BACK?
- I KNOW!
AND THEY BROUGHT
A WIZARD SAINT WITH THEM.
- WE'RE GONNA NEED HIM
'CAUSE THEY SAY THE GUYS
WE'RE UP AGAINST
ARE SUPER STRONG.
THEY CAN TAKE OUT WHOLE GUILDS
BY THEMSELVES.
- WHOA! SERIOUSLY?!
I MEAN, I COULD DO THAT
IF I REALLY WANTED TO.
- YEAH, SURE YOU COULD.
( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU STILL CAN'T
EVEN BEAT ERZA.
- HEY, I COULD
IF I SET MY MIND TO IT.
- IF YOU THINK THAT'S
GONNA WORK OUT FOR YOU,
YOU'VE LOST YOUR MIND.