HEY GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV!
- Makarov:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy: OH, NO!
LAXUS AND THE THUNDER LEGION
SHOWED UP
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE HARVEST FESTIVAL
AND STORMED
THE MISS FAIRY TAIL CONTEST!
NOW THEY'VE TAKEN ALL THE GIRLS
FROM THE GUILD HOSTAGE
AND THEY'RE FORCING THE GUYS
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER!
I GOTTA DO SOMETHING!
ONLY I CAN'T
'CAUSE THEY TURNED ME TO STONE!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I HEARD THERE'S BEEN
SOME TROUBLE WITH FAIRY TAIL.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NOPE, I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
I DID HEAR SOMEONE SAY
THE MEMBERS
WEREN'T GETTING ALONG
TOO WELL.
- WELL, IT SEEMS THINGS
HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
'CAUSE I JUST SAW
A COUPLE OF THOSE BOYS
FIGHTING EACH OTHER
OUT IN THE STREET!
- YOU DON'T THINK
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE TO CANCEL
THE FANTASIA PARADE, DO YA?
- WHO KNOWS?
- WHAT A SHAME.
- All: AH!
- HEY, LOOK,
THERE'S ONE OF 'EM NOW!
- YOU PUNKS BETTER QUIT
TEARIN' UP OUR TOWN!
- Vijeeter: TOWNSPEOPLE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DOESN'T
THE ENCHANTMENT AFFECT THEM?
I GUESS FRIED MADE IT
SO THE BARRIER'S RULES
ONLY APPLY TO WIZARDS
FROM THE GUILD.
- Nab: VIJEETER!
- NAB!
- SIT STILL
SO I CAN FINISH YOU OFF!
I HATE TO DO THIS TO YA, PAL,
BUT RULES ARE RULES
AND I CAN'T FIGHT LAXUS
TILL I BEAT YOU!
- I WAS HOPING I WOULDN'T
HAVE TO HURT ONE OF MY FRIENDS.
PITY.
BUT YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE!
- AH!
- YAAH!
- JUST GIVE UP!
YOU KNOW I CAN SEE
THROUGH YOUR PLANS, MAX!
IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN SURPRISE ME
WITH YOUR SAND MAGIC,
YOU'RE WRONG!
- YOUR FAMOUS TELEPATHY, HUH?
JUST 'CAUSE YOU
CAN READ MY ATTACKS
DOESN'T MEAN YOU'RE FAST ENOUGH
TO DODGE, WISE GUY!
- AHH!
- BETTER NOT BLINK!
- SAW THAT COMING A MILE AWAY!
- HEY, IS THIS PART
OF THE FESTIVAL?
- WITH THEM,
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- I JUST HOPE THEY CLEAN UP
AFTER THEMSELVES.
- ( Happy speaking )
- I'M GONNA SAVE MIRA,
EVEN IF IT MEANS
I GOTTA FIGHT YOU.
- I TAKE IT YOUR WIFE
DOESN'T KNOW
ABOUT YOUR LITTLE CRUSH, HUH?
- YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
'CAUSE YOUR WIFE LEFT YOU.
- YOU CROSSED THE LINE, BUD.
- LAKI, ARE YOU TRYING
TO ONE-UP US WITH YOUR NEW LOOK?
- HOPING MORE PEOPLE
WILL NOTICE YOU?
- WELL, I THINK
YOU LOOK LIKE TRASH!
- YOU WEREN'T GONNA ENTER
THE PAGEANT, WERE YOU?
- WHO KNEW I COULD CAUSE SUCH A
FUSS OVER A LITTLE HAIR CHOP?
I FEEL LIKE A SUPERSTAR!
- OH, SHUT UP!
WE'RE GONNA TEACH YOU
A LESSON!
- MUD SHOT!
- HMM.
- AHH!
- "MAX VERSUS WARREN. THE WINNER
IS WARREN."
"VIJEETER VERSUS NAB.
THE WINNER IS NAB."
"LAKI DEFEATS FOUR OTHERS. MACAO
VERSUS WAKABA, IN PROGRESS."
- FOOLISH CHILDREN!
WHAT DO THEY THINK
THEY'RE DOING?
- THEY REALLY DON'T HAVE ANY
CHOICE BUT TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
THOSE ENCHANTMENTS
ARE HIDDEN ALL OVER TOWN
SO THEY'RE IMPOSSIBLE
TO AVOID.
IT'S JUST LIKE LAXUS SAID--
THIS IS
THE BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL.
- BUT WHY?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE!
( grunts )
- NATSU.
- I WANNA FIGHT TOO!
- Both: IS THAT ALL?
- OH MAN, YOU SUCK!
GO AWAY, INVISIBLE WALL!
- WHY DO YOU WANT TO FIGHT
YOUR FRIENDS?
'CAUSE IT'S A TOURNAMENT
TO SEE WHO'S THE STRONGEST!
- THIS IS NOT A TOURNAMENT!
IT'S NOTHING BUT A TRAP.
LAXUS IS PLAYING YOU
LIKE A BUNCH OF PAWNS.
IF WE CAN'T BEAT
THE THUNDER LEGION IN TIME,
THE GIRLS ARE GOING
TO BE SMASHED TO PIECES.
I KNOW THAT EVERYONE'S TRYING
TO KEEP THAT FROM HAPPENING,
BUT THEY'RE GOING ABOUT IT
IN THE WRONG WAY.
IF WE KEEP
FIGHTING AMONGST OURSELVES
THEN THE GIRLS ARE AS GOOD
AS FINISHED.
WE CAN'T LET LAXUS WIN.
- Natsu: C'MON, GRAMPS,
YOU DON'T SERIOUSLY THINK
HE'D HURT EM, DO YOU?
I KNOW HE CAN BE A REAL PAIN
SOMETIMES,
BUT HE'S STILL ONE OF US.
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY A BLUFF.
- YOU THINK SO?
- THERE'S A FIGHTING FESTIVAL
GOIN' ON OUT THERE!
WHY DO I GOTTA BE STUCK
IN THIS DUMP?
- BEATS ME.
I CAN GO THROUGH JUST FINE.
- DOES THIS MEAN I'M OVER 80
AND NO ONE EVER TOLD ME?
'CAUSE I'D KNOW
IF I WAS A STONE STATUE, RIGHT?
- AND HERE I THOUGHT
WE KNEW EACH OTHER, NATSU.
- YOU STILL THINK OF LAXUS
AS PART OF THE GUILD?
EVEN AFTER ALL THIS,
YOU DON'T BELIEVE
HE'D HARM HIS FELLOW MEMBERS?
"TIME REMAINING:
TWO HOURS AND 18 MINUTES.
PARTICIPANTS REMAINING: 42."
- THAT CAN'T BE
ALL THAT'S LEFT.
THAT MEANS
MORE THAN HALF THE GUILD
HAS WIPED ITSELF OUT
IN LESS THAN AN HOUR.
- HERE GOES!
PURPLE RAIN!
- AHHH!
- OH, CRAP!
THAT WAS MY SMOKE FAKE.
YOU'RE LOSING
YOUR EDGE, MAN.
BUT YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN TOO SOFT
FOR YOU OWN GOOD, RIGHT, BUDDY?
- ( men screaming )
- Reedus: I'M TIRED
BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP.
I GOTTA MAKE IT
TO THE EAST FOREST.
THE MASTER'S COUNTING ON ME TO
GET THAT REMEDY FROM PORLYUSICA!
I GOTTA DO IT
FOR THE GIRLS!
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
DON'T TELL ME FRIED SET UP
AN ENCHANTMENT
AROUND THE ENTIRE TOWN!
- YOU'RE NOT ATTEMPTING TO
BREAK THE RULES OF THE GAME,
ARE YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- AS LAXUS SAID,
THE ENTIRE TOWN OF MAGNOLIA
IS YOUR BATTLEFIELD
AND YOUR GUILD ALLIES
ARE NOW YOUR OPPONENTS.
IF YOU ARE A WIZARD,
THEN YOU MUST FIGHT!
SORRY, THAT'S THE RULE.
- LET'S CHECK ON GRAY.
- THIS SUCKS! WHERE'S THE
THUNDER LEGION HIDING?
- IT'S GRAY!
- 'SUP, GRAY?
- THOSE ARE
BIXLOW'S SIDEKICKS!
- YO!
WHAT D'YA SAY
WE HAVE SOME FUN, HUH?
- Elfman: EVERGREEN!
A REAL MAN WOULD NEVER NEED
TO TAKE HOSTAGES!
IF YOU HAVE ANY PRIDE,
YOU'LL TURN MY SISTER BACK!
WELL, I'M NOT A MAN,
YOU KNOW.
OH, ARE THOSE BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS
FOR ME?
HOW KIND OF YOU.
THEY SUIT ME SO WELL.
- ( townspeople reacting )
- IT'S A SHAME THE ONLY THING
THAT'S CUTE ABOUT YOU
IS YOUR NAME, ELFMAN.
- YOU'D BETTER
TURN MY SISTER BACK OR ELSE.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN
DEFEAT ME WHILE BLINDFOLDED?
- AHH!
THERE YOU ARE!
- HOW RESOURCEFUL.
SO YOU CAN TELL WHERE I AM
BY FOLLOWING MY SCENT!
UNFORTUNATELY IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU'RE ALREADY COVERED
IN MY FAIRY DUST!
FAIRY BOMB ATTACK!
GREMLIN!
- AHHH!
- STATUES ARE WONDERFUL,
AREN'T THEY?
NO MATTER HOW UGLY A BEAST
MAY BE,
ONCE HE IS CAPTURED IN STONE,
HE BECOMES A BEAUTIFUL WORK
OF ART.
NOW GAZE INTO MY EYES
AND SUBMIT TO THE ETERNAL BEAUTY
OF STONE.
- "EVERGREEN VERSUS ELFMAN.
THE WINNER IS EVERGREEN."
- "ELFMAN K.O.-ED."
- I THOUGHT HE'D HAVE
NO PROBLEM BEATING HER.
- AH!  NOW IT SAYS THAT GRAY'S
FIGHTING AGAINST BIXLOW?
WHY'S HE GOTTA HOG
ALL THE FUN?
- IT ALSO SAYS FRIED
IS FIGHTING AGAINST REEDUS.
THE THUNDER LEGION
IS REALLY MAKING THEIR MOVE.
- THIS IS THE END OF THE LINE.
- Lucy: HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
WE'RE GONNA SETTLE
THIS FIGHT MAN TO MAN!
UH, MAN TO GIRL!
- I THOUGHT YOU HAD BEEN TURNED
TO STONE?
- THE MAGIC WORE OFF
SO I CAME AFTER YOU.
HMM! YOU CAN'T KEEP A
GOOD MAN-- I MEAN, WOMAN--
YOU SHOULD KNOW YOU CAN'T KEEP
A GOOD WOMAN DOWN!
THIS MAN-- I MEAN, THIS GIRL IS
A LOT STRONGER THAN YOU THINK!
- AHA HA HA HA HA!
- UH-OH!
AHHH!
- ( Lucy laughing )
- THOUGHT YOU COULD TRICK ME
WITH ONE OF YOUR
CREATIONS, DID YOU?
I KNOW THAT YOUR MAGIC
GIVES YOU THE ABILITY
TO BRING YOUR DRAWINGS
TO LIFE.
IT'S RATHER UNFORTUNATE
REALLY.
THINGS COULD'VE
GOTTEN INTERESTING
IF I'D BEEN SURPRISED.
- FRIED, STOP.
I'M BEGGING YOU,
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS
TO YOUR FRIENDS.
YOU'RE HURTING THEM.
I KNOW DEEP DOWN YOU'RE NOT THE
KIND OF GUY WHO'D DO THIS.
- NOW ONLY 40 WIZARDS REMAIN.
VICTORY WILL SOON BE OURS.
- OH NO. THEY TOOK OUT REEDUS.
- I KNEW IT! HE NEVER
COULDA BEAT FRIED.
THAT GUY IS GOOD.
- I KNOW HE'S COOL AND ALL,
BUT YOU'RE CHEERING
FOR THE WRONG SIDE!
NOW WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET PORLYUSICA'S HELP!
- WE DON'T NEED IT.
LAXUS IS JUST BLUFFING
ABOUT TURNIN' THE GIRLS TO DUST.
- I'M JUST BLUFFING, AM I?
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- WHERE'D YOU COME FROM?
- IT'S A THOUGHT PROJECTION!
- NATSU, WHAT'RE YOU DOING
HOLED UP IN THIS DUMP?
ARE YOU SCARED?
- I'M NOT SCARED, I'M STUCK!
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- HOW'S IT FEEL, HUH?
YOU THINK OF THE GUILD MEMBERS
AS YOUR CHILDREN, RIGHT?
MUST BE TOUGH WATCHING
YOUR LITTLE KIDDIES
TEAR EACH OTHER APART.
IT'S TOO BAD NATSU AND ERZA
CAN'T JOIN THE GAME
'CAUSE YOU
DON'T HAVE ANYONE LEFT
WHO'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO TAKE ON THE THUNDER LEGION.
YOU READY
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL?
- NO, IT'S NOT OVER YET.
DON'T FORGET THAT GRAY'S
STILL IN THE GAME!
AND HE'S JUST AS STRONG
OF A WIZARD AS NATSU!
- HE'S AS STRONG AS ME?
NO WAY, MAN!
- SORRY, BUT YOU'RE IN DENIAL!
- GRAY, HUH?
YOU'RE GONNA PUT
ALL OF YOUR HOPES ON THAT LOSER?
- I WOULDN'T UNDERESTIMATE
THE BOY'S POWER IF I WERE YOU!
- LINE FORMATION, BABIES!
- All: AW, YEAH!
- AW, YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT TOO SHABBY.
NOW GIMME A VICTORY FORMATION,
BABIES!
HEY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CRAP!
THEY'RE FROZEN SOLID!
- ICE MAKE HAMMER!
- X-FORMATION, BABIES!
- WHAT THE--
- I GUESS YOU'VE NEVER HEARD
ABOUT MY SEIDHR MAGIC, HUH?
I CONTROL MY BABIES' SOULS.
FREEZE 'EM AND I'LL JUST MOVE
THEIR SOULS TO ANOTHER DOLL.
I GOT AN IMMORTAL ARMY
ON MY SIDE!
- All ( echoing ): ON HIS SIDE.
- MAN, THIS IS GONNA BE
A REAL PAIN, ISN'T IT?
- DO YOU GET IT NOW?
YOU CAN ATTACK MY BABIES
ALL DAY
AND IT WON'T DO YOU
A LICK OF GOOD!
- WELL, SINCE IT WON'T WORK
ON THEM,
I'LL JUST FREEZE YOU INSTEAD.
- GO AHEAD AND TRY,
IF YOU CAN CATCH ME!
- DON'T RUN AWAY!
COME BACK HERE!
- ( laughing )
- FIGHT ME LIKE A MAN!
CRAZY FREAK.
WHERE'D HE RUN OFF TO NOW?
- GETTING WARMER.
PEEK-A-BOO.
- REAL FUNNY. WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO PULL HERE, ANYWAY?
- I JUST WANNA FIGHT SOMEONE
ON MY LEVEL.
A SHAME
YOU DON'T MAKE THE CUT.
MY BABIES ARE GETTIN' BORED.
IT'S TIME TO SPICE THINGS UP
A BIT.
- ANOTHER ENCHANTMENT?
- GUESS YOU'RE OUTTA LUCK.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO USE MAGIC
AS LONG AS YOU'RE INSIDE
THAT BARRIER.
- ONE OF FRIED'S TRAPS, HUH?
- SUCKS TO BE YOU.
YOU'RE STUCK IN THERE
ALL BY YOURSELF,
BUT IT'S A PARTY OUT HERE.
BABIES!
- All: TIME TO PARTY?
- AHA HA HA HA!
I DON'T THINK I'D BOTHER
GETTING UP AGAIN IF I WERE YOU.
YOU CAN'T WIN
WITHOUT YOUR MAGIC.
- OH, YA THINK SO?
YOU WANT SOME?
AHHH!
- AHA HA HA HA!  DON'T TELL ME
THAT'S ALL YA GOT?
- AHH!
- Mother:
C'MON, SWEETIE, LET'S GO.
IT'S TIME TO EAT LUNCH.
- BUT--
- LISTEN, YA JERK!
WHEN MY BABIES
HIT YA LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE S'POSED TO STAY DOWN!
I'M GLAD
I WORE MY HELMET TODAY.
THAT PUNCH
COULD'VE CAUSED MAJOR DAMAGE
TO MY HANDSOME FACE,
AND NOBODY WANTS THAT.
'COURSE WE'RE JUST LUCKY IF GRAY
HERE DECIDES TO WEAR ANYTHING.
( chuckling )
- Laxus: "ONE MORE DOWN,
ONLY 28 CONTENDERS REMAIN."
- ( laughs )
AND THAT CHUMP
WAS GONNA SAVE YA?
- YOU CHEATER!
I KNOW YOU AND YOUR PALS
USED SOME DIRTY TRICK
TO BEAT HIM!
- ALL RIGHT, WHO'S GONNA BEAT
THE THUNDER LEGION NOW, OLD MAN?
- GAJEEL WILL!
- I DON'T THINK SO.
HE'S MADE IT CLEAR
THAT HE DOESN'T WANNA PLAY.
WHICH DOESN'T SURPRISE ME.
THAT GUY COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT HAPPENS TO THE GUILD.
- WHAT?
AM I INVISIBLE?
- YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE IF YOU
CAN'T GET PAST THE BARRIER.
- ENOUGH.
IT ISN'T WORTH IT.
I SURRENDER, ALL RIGHT?
- WAIT A SEC!
- YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN.
NOW STOP THIS.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE THE MASTER OF
THE ALMIGHTY FAIRY TAIL GUILD?
YOU CAN'T JUST GIVE UP
AT THE DROP OF A HAT.
BUT IF YOU INSIST ON QUITTING,
THEN BY ALL MEANS,
HAND THE GUILD OVER TO ME
AND TAKE AN EARLY RETIREMENT.
- WHY YOU GOTTA PLAY DIRTY?
WHY DON'TCHA COME HERE
AND FACE US?  HUH?
- I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
THIS WAS YOUR GOAL ALL ALONG,
WASN'T IT?
- YOU'VE ONLY GOT AN HOUR
AND A HALF
UNTIL THE STATUES CRUMBLE.
IF YOU REALLY WANNA PUT AN END
TO THIS,
THEN ANNOUNCE YOUR RETIREMENT
TO THE WHOLE TOWN
OVER THE GUILD'S LOUDSPEAKER.
I WANT YOU TO TELL EVERYONE
YOU'RE RELINQUISHING FAIRY TAIL
OVER TO ME!
- WHAT MEANS MORE TO YOU?
YOUR CHILDREN OR YOUR TITLE?
CHOOSE CAREFULLY.
- YOU'RE ASKIN' FOR IT!
AHHH!
- IF HE WANTS TO BE MASTER,
HE SHOULD HAVE THE GUTS
TO FACE ME IN PERSON!
HOW COME HE WON'T FIGHT ME?
- IT WAS NEVER
THE TITLE I VALUED.
- THEN YOU'RE
JUST GONNA GIVE UP?
- NO, HE MAY BE STRONG,
BUT HE'S NOT TRUSTWORTHY.
I'D NEVER LEAVE HIM
IN CHARGE.
IT TAKES MORE THAN JUST
MAGICAL STRENGTH TO RUN A GUILD.
HE HAS NEITHER THE CONVICTION
NOR THE HEART.
- Happy: WE GOTTA HURRY
AND DO SOMETHING
BEFORE HE TURNS THE GIRLS
INTO DUST!
THERE MUST BE SOMEONE
WHO CAN BEAT LAXUS AND HIS PALS.
- NO WAY! YOU WERE HERE
THIS WHOLE TIME?
- HE'S EATING THE DISHES TOO!
- GAJEEL!
WILL YOU FIGHT FOR THE GUILD?
- MIGHT AS WELL.
I GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
WITH THAT GUY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL HANDLE HIM.
- AH!
- AHHHH!
- DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE OVER 80 TOO?
- DO I LOOK 80 TO YOU?
- LET'S SEE HOW THE
GUILD'S DOING.
- GREMLIN!
- AHH!
- MY, WHAT A SHAME.
- STOP IT, BIXLOW!
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE, RIGHT?
- FRIENDS?  YOU WEAKLINGS
AIN'T NO FRIENDS OF MINE!
RIGHT, BABIES?
AHA HA HA!
- FRIED.
- HELLO, ALZACK.
- THANKS TO THOSE ENCHANTMENTS
OF YOURS,
I'VE HAD TO FIGHT
AGAINST ALL MY FRIENDS.
I TOLD MYSELF
I HAD TO FOR BISCA,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE IT OKAY.
GUNS MAGIC TORNADO SHOT!
HE SLICED
THROUGH MY WIND MAGIC?
( grunts )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CAN'T BREATHE.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
WHAT KINDA WEIRD MAGIC
IS THIS? BISCA.
- THOSE WHO USE MAGIC
WITHIN THIS BARRIER
WILL BE ROBBED OF OXYGEN.
OF COURSE, IF YOU HAD BOTHERED
TO READ THE ENCHANTMENT
YOU WOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT.
- HOW DO THEY EXPECT
TO DEFEAT ME
WHEN I'M THE ONE WHO WRITES
THE RULES?
NOW ONLY TWO REMAIN
IN THE BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL.
SUCH A PITIFUL DISPLAY.
- ONLY TWO LEFT IN THE GUILD?
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
FAKIN' BEING STUCK IN HERE?
YOU TRYIN' TO COPY ME?
- IN YOUR DREAMS!
- NOW I'M HUNGRY
AND IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT, JERK!
- QUIT BLAMIN' EVERYTHING
ON ME!
- IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA FIGHT,
THEN AT LEAST GO
GET ME SOME FOOD!
- NO WAY.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONES LEFT?
- BUT WHAT ABOUT ME, MASTER?
I'M A MEMBER TOO, AREN'T I?
- THERE'S NOBODY LEFT
WHO COULD TAKE DOWN LAXUS.
IT'S ALL OVER.
- I'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
GUESS I'LL BRING ERZA BACK.
- DO WHAT?
- AW, THIS SUCKS.
I THOUGHT I WAS FINALLY GONNA
HAVE A CHANCE TO SHOW HER UP.
- NOW HOLD ON A SECOND!
WHAT ARE YOU ABOUT TO DO?
- I'M GONNA USE MY FIRE ON HER.
YA KNOW,
TO MELT THE STONE OFF.
- SAY WHAT?
- SHE'S NOT COVERED IN STONE,
SHE IS STONE,
SO IT'S NOT GONNA MELT
OFF OF HER!
- WON'T KNOW 'TIL WE TRY,
RIGHT GUYS?
- THIS IS MADNESS!
YOU'RE GOING
TO ROAST HER ALIVE!
- HA HA!
IT'S TOASTY TIME!
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL!
- NO JOKE.
WATCH WHERE YOU PUT
THOSE FIRE HANDS, BRO.
- ( all screaming )
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO BREAK HER,
SOMEONE GET ME THE GLUE!
QUICK!  HAPPY!  GLUE!
- DO WE HAVE GLUE?
- THAT'S NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING,
YOU IDIOT!
WE GOTTA USE YOUR FIRE AND MY
IRON TO WELD HER BACK TOGETHER!
- ERZA, NO!
- I'M SORRY!
I'M SORRY!
I'M SORRY!  I'M SORRY!
I SO SORRY!  I'M SORRY!
- I FEEL HOT.
IT WAS YOU, WASN'T IT?
WERE YOU TRYING TO COOK ME?
- ERZA'S BACK IN BUSINESS,
GUYS!
- THANK GOODNESS.
BUT HOW
WAS THE SPELL BROKEN?
- HONESTLY, I'M NOT QUITE SURE.
BUT IF I HAD TO GUESS,
I'D SAY IT HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH MY RIGHT EYE.
- THAT'S IT!
HER ARTIFICIAL EYE MUST'VE
WEAKENED THE EFFECTS
OF THE SPELL.
- ERZA, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON RIGHT NOW?
- I THINK SO.
EVEN THOUGH I WAS STONE,
I WAS STILL ABLE TO HEAR
MOST OF WHAT WAS SAID.
- ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME TO STRIKE BACK.
- Happy:
LOOK, THERE'S THREE NOW!
- THE RUNES HAVE
ALREADY ADDED ME TO THE FRAY.
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
IT UPDATES AUTOMATICALLY.
BUT THERE'S ONLY THREE LEFT.
- ACTUALLY, IT'S JUST YOU.
NATSU AND GAJEEL ARE STUCK HERE
'CAUSE OF THE ENCHANTMENT.
WAIT, NOW IT SAYS THERE'S FOUR.
- IT WENT UP.
- WHO COULD IT BE?
- Makarov: THE GIRLS
ARE STILL STONE,
SO IT CAN'T BE ANY OF THEM.
- ( giggles ) AREN'T YOU GUYS
FORGETTING ABOUT SOMEONE?
A MEMBER WHO'S FREQUENTLY
OUT OF TOWN?
- HOLD ON.
YOU DON'T MEAN HIM?
- AND HE'S BACK
JUST WHEN WE NEED HIM THE MOST!
- HE'S ALWAYS BEEN ONE
TO MAKE A GRAND ENTRANCE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE REAL BATTLE
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- SOMEONE WANNA FILL ME
IN OVER HERE?
- Erza: WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A
MAN WHO MAY VERY WELL BE
THE STRONGEST WIZARD
IN FAIRY TAIL.
MYSTOGAN.
- SO ERZA HAS RECOVERED AND NOW
MYSTOGAN IS JOINING US.
INCLUDING ME, THAT'S THREE OF
FAIRY TAIL'S ELITE
COMING HEAD-TO-HEAD.
- YOU CAN'T HAVE A PROPER
FESTIVAL WITHOUT A MAIN EVENT.
- THEN.
- THANKS FOR HELPIN' REEDUS!
- THAT WASN'T REALLY ME.
- HEY THERE, ERZA.
THAT'S A PRETTY CRAZY
GETUP YOU GOT ON.
- WE SAW A BUNCH OF GUYS FROM
YOUR GUILD FIGHTING EARLIER.
YOU THINK YOU COULD ASK THEM
TO STOP WRECKING THE TOWN?
- PLEASE FORGIVE THEM.
THEY'RE JUST PREPARING
FOR THE BIG PARADE.
- I DON'T SEE WHAT THAT
HAS TO DO WITH FIGHTING.
- I PROMISE
IT'LL BE A GOOD SHOW.
- I'LL TAKE YOUR WORD FOR IT
THEN.
- TRY TO CLEAN UP
AFTER YOURSELVES, OKAY?
- MY MY, NOW THAT'S ODD.
I SEEM TO RECALL
TURNING YOU INTO A STATUE.
WELL, NO MATTER.
THIS GIVES ME AN EXCUSE
TO TORMENT YOU FURTHER.
- YOU WANT TO FIGHT ME?
- YOU'RE QUITE THE IRKSOME ONE.
THEY CALL YOU TITANIA,
QUEEN OF THE FAIRIES?
WHAT A FARCE.
I'M THE TRUE FAIRY QUEEN.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NATSU, YOU'D BETTER KEEP
YOUR TUMMY COVERED
OR YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
YOUR BELLY BUTTON!
- HUH?  C'MON, THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
- I KNOW, BUT THAT'S
WHAT LUCY TOLD ME.
SHE SAID IF I DON'T KEEP MY
BELLY BUTTON COVERED
DURING A STORM, A
BOLT OF LIGHTNING
WILL SHOOT DOWN FROM THE SKY
AND TAKE IT AWAY!
- LUCY'S FULL OF IT.
BESIDES, YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE A BELLY BUTTON.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- CAN LAXUS' LIGHTNING
STEAL BELLY BUTTONS?
- I DUNNO.  I'M MORE WORRIED
ABOUT HIM STEALING MY THUNDER.
- WOW, NATSU.
YOU SHOULD BE A COMEDIAN.