- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY,
ON FAIRY TAIL!
- Lucy: WITH CARLA
LEADING THE WAY,
WE INFILTRATED THE TUNNELS
UNDER THE KING OF
EDOLAS' CASTLE,
BUT IT WASN'T LONG 'TIL WE WERE
AMBUSHED AND CAPTURED
BY ERZA KNIGHTWALKER.
WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
I'M NOT GONNA GET MUCH
SCREEN TIME THIS EPISODE?
- Happy: IT'S TIME TO LET
SOMEONE ELSE SHINE.
- Lucy: BUT I'M THE ONE WITH
THE MAGIC. SOMEBODY HELP ME.
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( both grunting )
- Natsu: WHY, YOU...
HEY, WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
- OTHERS?
- YEAH, WHERE'RE OUR FRIENDS
LUCY, CARLA, AND HAPPY?
- WHO'S LUCY?
OH, YOU MEAN
THE BLONDE BIMBO?
PRETTY LITTLE THING.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'VE
GOT NO USE FOR HER.
SO SHE'S GONNA BE EXECUTED.
- IF YOU JERKS SO MUCH AS
LAY A FINGER ON LUCY,
I SWEAR, YOU'RE GONNA PAY.
I'LL BURN YOU DOWN
TO A PILE OF ASHES!
- Happy: EXTALIA.
- WHOA. WELL, AREN'T YOU
A SCARY ONE?
SO TELL ME SOMETHIN',
ARE ALL EARTH LAND WIZARDS
JUST AS FEROCIOUS AS YOU ARE?
- YOU'RE GONNA EXECUTE LUCY?
WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO
CARLA AND HAPPY?
- NO NEED TO WORRY
ABOUT THE EXCEEDS.
- HIS NAME IS HAPPY.
GET IT STRAIGHT!
- THE EXCEEDS ACCOMPLISHED
THEIR MISSION,
SO WE TOOK 'EM BACK TO
THEIR HOMELAND.
IN FACT, I BET THE LITTLE GUYS
HAVE CLAIMED THEIR REWARD
AND ARE HAVING A FEAST
AS WE SPEAK.
- WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT MISSION?
- BY RETURNING TO EDOLAS,
I WILL BE ABANDONING MY MISSION.
ONE HANDED DOWN BY
THE KINGDOM ITSELF.
- NO WAY, THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF
MISSION YOU GUYS SENT HER ON,
BUT I KNOW CARLA
ABANDONED IT.
- ( laughing ) OH, YEAH?
SHE ACTUALLY
COMPLETED IT LIKE A PRO.
- THAT CAN'T BE. WHAT ARE
YOU MAKING THEM DO FOR YOU?
- ( chuckles )
YOU MEAN, YOU STILL HAVEN'T
FIGURED IT OUT YET?
- ( people chattering )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THANKS FOR ALL YOUR HARD WORK!
- WHO ARE YOU?
- OH, I'M JUST YOUR
AVERAGE JOURNALIST.
I'M COVERING THE CEREMONY.
I'D LOVE TO ASK YOU
A FEW QUESTIONS,
THAT IS, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND.
- I GOT NO COMMENT.
NOW BEAT IT.
- I SEE THE KING HAS TROOPS
STATIONED ALONG
THE NORTHERN SIDE OF THE PLAZA.
IS IT THEREFORE
SAFE TO ASSUME
THERE ARE SOLDIERS STATIONED
ON THE SOUTHERN SIDE
OF IT AS WELL?
- GET OUTTA HERE!
- ( chuckles ) SORRY, GENTLEMEN,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DISTURB YOU.
( laughs )
- JUST GREAT. CAN'T RUSH IN
WITH THOSE PEOPLE DOWN THERE.
THEY COULD WIND UP GETTING HURT
IN THE SOLDIERS' ATTACK.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO NOW?
- WHAT THE...
WHERE ARE WE?
HEY, CARLA, WAKE UP.
- TOMCAT, WHAT IS THIS?
- ( gasps )
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
HAPPENED TO US?
- ALL I KNOW IS WE WERE KNOCKED
OUT AND WOKE UP HERE.
THIS WEIRD PLACE,
I KNOW I'VE NEVER
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- IT SEEMS MY INFORMATION
WAS ACTUALLY A TRAP.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE. I'M SURE
IT WAS JUST A COINCIDENCE
THEY FOUND US.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT, CARLA.
- I'VE BETRAYED DEAR WENDY.
I SWORE THAT I WOULD
PROTECT HER NO MATTER WHAT.
I MUST PROTECT HER. SHE'S THE
ONLY THING THAT MATTERS TO ME.
( crying )
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
- ( both gasp )
- GLIMMEOW. GLIMMEOW.
I BEG YOUR PARDON...
ARE YOU THE ONES WHO
RECENTLY COMPLETED
AN EARTH LAND MISSION, GLIMMEOW?
- IT'S NICHIYA?
- MEOW. NICE PARFUM.
- WAIT A SECOND, YOU'RE A CAT?
- DON'T BE SILLY,
I'M NO MERE CAT.
I'M AN EXCEED,
JUST LIKE YOU.
- MR. NICHIYA, SIR.
I'VE BEEN TOLD THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME THEY'VE BEEN TO EDOLAS.
IN FACT, I DOUBT THEY'VE EVER
SEEN ANOTHER EXCEED BEFORE.
- REALLY? WELL, I HAD NO IDEA.
- WELCOME. I AM NICHIYA,
THE CAPTAIN OF EXTALIA'S
ROYAL GUARD.
MEOW. MEOW.
- AND MY NAME IS NADI.
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS
EXTALIA'S MINISTER OF STATE.
CONGRATS ON YOUR MISSION.
- OUR MISSION?
- ( sighs )
- IT'LL BE OKAY, CARLA.
- I KNOW THIS IS RATHER SUDDEN
BUT THE QUEEN WOULD
LIKE TO SEE YOU.
- FOLLOW ME.
- THE QUEEN? SERIOUSLY?
DON'T WORRY, JUST LEAVE
EVERYTHING TO ME.
THE FIRST THING WE NEED TO DO
IS GET THE LAY OF THE LAND.
I PROMISE I'M GONNA
PROTECT YOU, CARLA.
- EXCELLENT WORK, MEN.
- Guards: MEOW, SIR!
- THERE'RE CATS EVERYWHERE.
- I BET YOU'RE EXCITED,
AREN'T YOU?
- I MIGHT BE IF I KNEW
WHAT IN THE HECK WAS GOIN' ON.
( exclaims )
- HEY, BABY, WANNA GO SHARE
SOME MILK WITH ME?
- ( gasping )
- HELLO THERE, MA'AM,
MAY I INTEREST YOU IN
SOME FRESHLY CAUGHT FISH TODAY?
- YES, I'LL TAKE THOSE.
AND ONE OF THE MACKEREL OVER
THERE, PLEASE.
- SURE THING. TELL YOU WHAT,
SINCE YOU'VE GOT SO MANY
YOUNG'UNS AT HOME TO FEED,
I'LL THROW IN
SOME EXTRA FOR FREE!
- THANK YOU. THAT IS SO
INCREDIBLY KIND OF YOU, SIR!
- ( chuckles ) I FIGURE I SHOULD
SPREAD THE WEALTH
SINCE THE QUEEN'S GENEROSITY
IS THE ONLY REASON
I MAKE A LIVING EACH DAY.
- WELL, MY KITTENS
AND I THANK YOU.
- NO PROBLEM.
- I SWEAR I'M NOT LYIN'.
I WENT DOWN TO THE SURFACE
THE OTHER DAY TO GATHER
INFO AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW IT.
- YOU GONNA TELL US WHAT
YOU SAW DOWN THERE OR WHAT?
- I CAME FACE TO FACE WITH A
CATERPILLAR THAT WAS THIS BIG.
- QUIT PULLIN' MY LEG, KID.
YOU DON'T REALLY EXPECT ME TO
BELIEVE THAT CATERPILLARS
GROW THAT BIG, DO YOU?
- IN OTHER WORDS, WHETHER
THE KING KNOWS IT OR NOT,
HE IS UNDER THE EXCEEDS' CONTROL
JUST LIKE ANY OTHER HUMAN.
- ( laughing )
- LET'S GO GET SOME
TREATS, YOU GUYS.
- WAIT FOR ME!
- IT'S A LAND OF CATS.
- LOOK, IT'S SIR NICHIYA.
- MEOW.
- SIR NADI, HOW'RE YOU
DOIN' TODAY?
- I'M GREAT,
THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
- HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
IS THAT THEM?
- YES, THEY'RE THE
ONES WHO COMPLETED
THEIR EARTH LAND MISSION.
- YOU GUYS ROCK.
YOU'RE HEROES.
- THAT CHICK'S PRETTY HOT, I
WONDER IF SHE'S WITH THAT GUY?
- EVERYBODY'S A CAT HERE.
- I'M AFRAID THAT YOU'RE WRONG,
MY FRIEND, WE'RE EXCEEDS, HERE.
WE STAND ABOVE THE HUMANS.
IT'S OUR DUTY TO GUIDE THEM
EACH AND EVERY DAY.
- I'VE NEVER HEARD OF YOU.
- AND THAT BEAUTIFUL
SIGHT BEFORE YOU
IS THE EXCEED KINGDOM, EXTALIA.
- ( drums beating )
- LOOK, HERE THEY COME.
- IT'S ALMOST TIME.
- I SEE THINGS ARE
FINALLY GETTING UNDERWAY.
- MMM-HMM. THE KINGDOM WILL BE
MUCH MORE STABLE AFTER THIS.
- WE'RE ON THE SOUTHERN SIDE
OF THE PLAZA.
LET ME ASK, IS SECURITY AS TIGHT
ON THE EASTERN AND WESTERN SIDES
AS IT IS HERE?
- NO, BUT ONLY BECAUSE
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH ROOM
FOR ANYBODY TO HIDE THERE.
- OH REALLY, IS THAT SO?
- PLEASE DON'T WRITE THAT
IN THE ARTICLE.
IT'LL GET ME IN TROUBLE.
- I'D NEVER DO SUCH A THING.
I ASSURE YOU, I'M COMPLETELY
AWARE OF WHAT'S APPROPRIATE
TO WRITE AND WHAT ISN'T.
I STRIVE TO BE
A FAIR JOURNALIST.
- YEAH.
- THERE ARE TROOPS STATIONED
ON THE NORTH AND SOUTH SIDES.
HOWEVER, JUST NORTH OF
THE SOUTH SIDE IS UNDERMANNED.
ACCORDING TO MY SOURCES,
THE CEREMONY WILL BE HELD
SOUTH OF THE LACRIMA.
HMM.
- HUH?
I SEE. WELL, HERE GOES NOTHIN'.
( laughing )
- YOU SEE, IN OUR WORLD, HUMANS
ARE A FOOLISH, INFERIOR SPECIES.
SO, IT IS OUR DUTY AS EXCEEDS
TO KEEP THEM UNDER CONTROL.
- IN CASE YOU DIDN'T NOTICE,
THEY HAVE A NASTY PARFUM.
BY THE
WAY, PARFUM MEANS SMELL. MEOW.
- OUR BELOVED QUEEN
WATCHES OVER THE HUMANS
AND GOVERNS THEM
FROM THIS CASTLE.
- SHE HAS AN ABSOLUTELY
DELIGHTFUL PARFUM.
- IT'D BE DANGEROUS IF THE
HUMANS' NUMBERS
WERE TO GET OUT OF HAND, SO
THE QUEEN DETERMINES
WHICH HUMANS ARE UNNECESSARY
AND HAS THEM EXECUTED.
- BUT WHY WOULD SHE
WANNA DO THAT?
- TO HELP RESTORE THE MAGIC
POWER THAT'S DWINDLING
FROM OUR WORLD.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT
THE QUEEN SAID.
YOU SEE, NOT ONLY DOES SHE
GOVERN THE HUMANS OF THIS WORLD,
BUT SHE CONTROLS THE HUMANS
OF EARTH LAND AS WELL.
- AND SHE DECIDES
WHICH PEOPLE LIVE OR DIE?
- YES, OUR BENEVOLENT QUEEN
HAS THAT AUTHORITY.
AFTER ALL, SHE IS
A GODDESS, MEOW!
- A GODDESS?
- THIS MISSION YOUR QUEEN
SENT US ON, I REMEMBER.
IT'S COMING BACK TO ME.
THIS MISSION HAS BEEN IMPRINTED
ON ME SINCE I WAS BORN.
THE QUEEN CHOSE ME TO HELP HER
CONTROL THE HUMAN POPULATION.
I WAS ORDERED TO ELIMINATE
THE DRAGON SLAYER WENDY.
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN, CARLA?
- PLEASE DON'T ASK.
- TELL ME WHAT YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAY YOU WERE
ORDERED TO ELIMINATE WENDY?
NO WAY.
THEN, DOES THAT MEAN...
MY MISSION WAS TO...
NO, THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
- I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT THAT
YOU WERE BETTER OFF
NOT KNOWING THE TRUTH.
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MY MISSION WAS TO
ELIMINATE NATSU?
- THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
- NO WAY.
- ( cheering )
- ( drums beating )
- I'M SUPPOSED TO
ELIMINATE NATSU?
- WOULD YOU JUST
CALM DOWN, TOMCAT?
LET ME MAKE ONE THING CLEAR,
WE DIDN'T ACCOMPLISH
OUR MISSIONS,
NOR DID WE EVER INTEND TO DO SO.
WHY IS EVERYBODY TALKING
TO US AS IF WE HAVE?
- DO YOU THINK IT'S AMNESIA?
- PERHAPS. YOU SEE THERE ARE
COUNTLESS SIDE-EFFECTS
OF OVERWRITING THAT
ARE STILL WIDELY UNKNOWN.
- ANSWER ME!
- OF COURSE, PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO EXPLAIN.
SIX YEARS AGO, OUR BELOVED QUEEN
SENT ONE HUNDRED EXCEEDS
TO EARTH LAND, IN
THE HOPES OF BETTER
CONTROLLING THE
HUMAN POPULATION.
AFTER THEY HATCHED,
THE INFORMATION THEY
HAD BEEN GIVEN
WOULD LEAD THEM TO
SEEK OUT AND ELIMINATE
THE DRAGON SLAYERS.
- ( growling )
- THEN, ONE DAY,
THE SITUATION CHANGED.
YOU SEE, WHEN THE HUMANS
CREATED ANIMA
WE WERE PRESENTED WITH
A NEW AND EXCITING POSSIBILITY.
WITH ITS INVENTION WE REALIZED
RATHER THAN SIMPLY
KILLING EARTH LAND HUMANS,
WE COULD CONVERT THEM
INTO MAGIC POWER.
AND IT'S WELL KNOWN THAT
THE DRAGON SLAYERS
ARE THE MOST POWERFUL OF
THE HUMAN WIZARDS.
THEREFORE, INSTEAD OF
ELIMINATING THEM,
YOU WERE ORDERED TO
BRING THEM INTO CUSTODY.
- Hughes: THIS IS SO COOL.
WE FINALLY GOT OUR HANDS ON YOU.
YOU BOTH HAVE SO MUCH
OF THAT AWESOME DRAGON SLAYER
MAGIC INSIDE YOU.
ALL WE GOTTA DO NOW
IS SUCK IT OUT.
( laughing )
- ( crying )
- I GOTTA HURRY. BUT IT'S SO
CROWDED I CAN BARELY MOVE.
- HEY. WHAT THE HECK'S
THAT THING?
- OH THIS? WELL, UH, FIREWORKS
FOR THE MAGIC POWER EXTRACTION.
COOL, HUH? WATCH THIS.
- FIREWORKS!
- THAT'S AWESOME.
I HOPE THEY SHOOT SOME MORE.
- WHAT THE...
- NO ONE SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT FIREWORKS!
- GUESS ONE LETTER'S NOT ENOUGH.
LET'S GO ALL OUT!
- THE NORTH?
- AND THE REST IS
UP TO YOU, MY FRIEND.
- SOLDIERS, THAT MUST BE
SOME KIND OF WARNING.
WE MUST PROTECT THE LACRIMA.
I SUSPECT THAT THERE'S
SOMEONE SUSPICIOUS
ON THE NORTH SIDE OF THE PLAZA.
- WHAT?
- WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING. THAT'S
THE REAR SIDE OF THE LACRIMA.
WE DON'T HAVE MANY MEN
POSITIONED THERE.
- KEEP YOUR FORCES HERE
AND I'LL TAKE THE OTHERS NORTH.
PUSH THE CROWD BACK
FOR THEIR SAFETY.
- YES, SIR.
YOU HEARD THE MAN!
EVERYONE, PLEASE MOVE BACK.
- ALL RIGHT. IT'S ABOUT TIME FOR
ME TO MAKE MY MOVE. HERE GOES.
- HEY, DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
I SAID MOVE BACK.
- THAT MYSTOGAN GUY MAY BE
ONE FREAKY WEIRDO,
BUT I GOT NO OTHER CHOICE BUT
TO TRUST HIM FOR RIGHT NOW.
- ( clamoring )
- IRON DRAGON CLUB!
- IT'S GOING PRECISELY
AS PLANNED.
- IRON DRAGON SWORD!
AIN'T NO STOPPIN' ME.
( yelling )
( grunting ) WHOA.
WHAT THE...
- JUDGING BY YOUR REACTIONS,
IT WOULD APPEAR OVERWRITING
YOUR ORDERS REMOTELY
MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
THE BEST IDEA.
- HOWEVER, EVERYTHING
WORKED OUT IN THE END.
YOU WERE STILL ABLE TO BRING
THE DRAGON SLAYERS TO US
DESPITE THE ERRONEOUS ORDERS.
- ( crying )
- Nichiya: THE HUMANS HAVE BEEN
TASKED WITH MAGICALIZATION,
WHICH IS THEIR CONVERSION
TO MAGIC POWER.
AFTER ALL, THEY'RE
MUCH MORE PROFICIENT
AT THAT SORT OF THING.
MEOW. MEOW.
- ( crying ) NO, IT CAN'T BE.
I CAME TO EDOLAS...
I CAME HERE
OF MY OWN FREE WILL.
- 'FRAID NOT. YOU WERE ACTING ON
THE WILL OF OUR FAIR QUEEN.
- BUT I LED EVERYONE TO THE
TUNNEL TO TRY AND SAVE THEM.
- IT MAY HAVE APPEARED
THAT WAY TO YOU
BUT ACTUALLY WE WERE THE ONES
WHO GUIDED YOU THERE.
- WHO ARE YOU,
HAPPY AND CARLA?
I THOUGHT THAT YOU
WERE OUR FRIENDS.
- ( crying ) NO, IT CAN'T BE.
ALL I EVER WANTED...
ALL I WANTED WAS TO
PROTECT WENDY.
SHE'S ALL THAT
MATTERS TO ME.
- WHAT YOU EXPERIENCED WAS
ACTUALLY A SELF-DELUSION.
WHEN YOUR ORDERS CHANGED
FROM ELIMINATE TO CAPTURE,
YOUR DUTY BECAME PROTECTING
THE DRAGON SLAYERS
TO ENSURE THEY WERE NOT KILLED.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE!
- WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOUR EVERY MOVE UP TO THIS POINT
HAS BEEN COMPLETELY
CONTROLLED BY US.
- ( sobbing loudly )
- LET'S GET ONE THING STRAIGHT,
WE'RE NOT YOUR PUPPETS.
- ( gasping )
- TOMCAT...
- YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
WE'RE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS,
WE DON'T WORK FOR YOU.
( breathing heavily )
- OH, HAPPY...
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO GET
EVERYONE AND BUST OUTTA HERE.
- Happy: AYE, SIR. WON'T TAKE
LONG WITH ME ON THE JOB.
IT'S JUST ONE QUICK FLIGHT
AND WE'RE THERE.
WAIT, I FORGOT I CAN'T
USE MY MAGIC.
- Natsu: GEEZ,
GET YOUR ACT TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU CAN'T
FLY, YOU'RE NOTHIN'
BUT A TALKIN' CAT, LIL' BUDDY.
- Happy: WOW, THAT WAS MEAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU THREW
THAT OUT THERE SO CASUALLY.
- Both: NEXT TIME,
FLY, TO OUR FRIENDS!
ALL RIGHT, IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WHAT DOES THAT MAKE YOU
WHEN YOU CAN'T BREATHE FIRE?
- Natsu: A DRAGON THAT
CAN'T BREATHE FIRE? WHOA.
- Happy: JUST A BIG,
UGLY LIZARD, HUH?