- HEY, GUYS! READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT TOO
CLOSE TO THE TV!
- Narrator: OUR STORY BEGINS
WEST OF MAGNOLIA AT FORT TERM,
WHERE AN UNSAVORY
BUNCH OF BANDITS
HAVE MADE THEIR HIDEOUT.
- THAT WAS GREAT!
JUST LOOK AT YOU GO!
- YOU'VE GOT SOME MOVES
OF YOUR OWN!
- ( theme song playing )
MAN, THESE GUYS DON'T PUT UP
MUCH OF A FIGHT.
- SO WHO DID YOU LOSERS
STEAL FROM?
OLD LADIES AND LITTLE KIDS?
- DON'T ACT LIKE THIS IS OVER!
YOU'LL BE SORRY! JUST YOU WAIT!
- YEAH, LORD DEBON IS
GONNA MAKE YOU PAY!
- WE BEAT UP THAT JERK
A LONG TIME AGO!
- I'M ALL FINISHED UPSTAIRS.
- SWEET! NICE WORK, ERZA!
- ( exclaims )
- GET BACK HERE!
UNFORTUNATELY, IT SEEMS
YOU STILL HAVEN'T
LEARNED YOUR LESSON.
- ( groans ) I'VE BEEN BAD!
PLEASE TEACH ME A LESSON,
TOO, MISTRESS ERZA!
- AND AWAY YOU GO! BYE!
- ( all groaning )
- WELL, THAT WAS A WASTE.
I WAS HOPING THEY MIGHT
BE A CHALLENGE.
- ( grunts ) I WANNA
FIGHT SOME MORE!
- I KNOW HOW YA FEEL,
BUT SAVE IT FOR THE NEXT JOB.
- CHECK OUT THIS GEM I GOT!
PRETTY COOL DON'T YA THINK?
- STEALING FROM THIEVES
IS STILL STEALING!
- HEY! ISN'T THAT LOKE
OVER THERE?
- WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
- JUST BEATING BAD GUYS
AND BEING AWESOME.
- SAME OLD SAME OLD.
- I'M GLAD WE RAN INTO YOU!
THANKS FOR MUCH
FOR FINDING MY...
- SORRY, BUT I'D BETTER
HIT THE ROAD. SO LONG!
- WHAT IS THAT GUY'S PROBLEM?
- I DUNNO WHAT YOU DID,
BUT YOU REALLY FREAK HIM OUT.
- YEAH, HE AVOIDS YOU
LIKE THE PLAGUE.
- IT'S NOT MY FAULT HE'S CRAZY!
- Happy: A STAR
REMOVED FROM THE SKY!
- GUESS WE MIGHT AS WELL
HEAD HOME!
- I DUNNO. I WAS THINKING,
SINCE WE FINISHED OUR
JOB EARLY FOR ONCE,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE STOP BY
A SPA AND TAKE IT EASY?
- LUCY.
- YES MA'AM?
- I THINK THAT'S A FINE IDEA.
- SO.
- Narrator: HOSENKA VILLAGE,
THE MOST POPULAR RESORT IN
ALL OF MAGNOLIA.
FAMOUS FOR ITS SPAS,
THIS FLAMBOYANT,
IF SOMEWHAT DODGY
TOURIST ATTRACTION,
WAS DESIGNED BY A DUKE WHO WAS
FASCINATED WITH THE ORIENT
AND ITS ARCHITECTURE.
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHY IS LOKE SO AFRAID OF ME?
- NICE MOON TONIGHT.
THE BATH'S NICE, TOO.
- YOU'RE BATHING IN YOUR ARMOR?
- I'M MORE RELAXED WITH IT ON.
- REALLY? DOESN'T IT FEEL
KINDA WEIRD?
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
IT DOES.
I MAY NEED TO RECONSIDER
MY DEFINITION OF "RELAXATION".
- YEAH. I DON'T THINK "TAKING IT
EASY" IS YOUR STRONG POINT.
WOW. YOU LOOK JUST AS AWESOME
WITHOUT YOUR ARMOR!
- IS THAT SO?
THEN PERHAPS I SHOULD WALK
AROUND THE GUILD LIKE THIS.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
- RIGHT.
- LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
- AYE!
- C'MON, MAN,
I'M TRYING TO SLEEP HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE YOUR
"PARTY" OUTSIDE?
- IT'S A SLEEPOVER! YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS, RIGHT?
YOU GOTTA BUST OUT
YOUR PILLOW-FU!
OR ARE YOU TOO SCARED?
- OF YOU? YEAH, RIGHT.
- MY ARSENAL IS EQUIPPED WITH
ONLY THE MOST POWERFUL PILLOWS!
- MOST POWERFUL?
- WHATEVER, ERZA!
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN!
- GROW UP, YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE IN FOR IT NOW!
OH, WOULD YA LOOK AT
ALL THESE PILLOWS?
- GO GET 'EM, MY PRINCE!
I'M HERE FOR YOU!
- YOU'RE NEXT, ERZA!
- NOT TOO SHABBY.
- OKAY, I GUESS
I'LL JOIN IN, TOO.
YOU KNOW, ON SECOND THOUGHT,
I THINK I'LL PASS.
DON'T REALLY FEEL LIKE
DYIN' TONIGHT.
- ( all shouting )
- ( sighs ) SOMETIMES I THINK
THOSE GUYS AREN'T EVEN HUMAN!
OH. HAPPY DOESN'T COUNT,
'CAUSE HE'S A CAT.
AND YOU'RE A DOG,
RIGHT, PLUE?
- ACTUALLY, I'M A HUMAN
JUST LIKE YOU!
- YEAH?
HUMAN? I NEVER EVEN KNEW
YOU COULD TALK!
- AYE!
- AYE?
- I COME FROM A FARAWAY LAND IN
SEARCH OF THE SACRED STONES!
- VERY FUNNY. NOW STOP
FOOLIN' AROUND
AND GET YOUR BLUE BUTT
OVER HERE, HAPPY.
- DARN. I WAS REALLY HOPIN'
I COULD KEEP IT UP
FOR AT LEAST A WEEK OR TWO,
YOU KNOW, SINCE YOU'RE
SO DUMB AND ALL.
- WOW, GLAD YOU THINK
SO HIGHLY OF ME.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOIN'
OUT HERE ANYWAY?
- GOIN' FOR A LITTLE WALK.
I'M WAITING FOR THE PILLOW FIGHT
APOCALYPSE TO BE OVER.
- YO! WHAT UP, GIRL?
- THAT OUTFIT LOOKS GREAT
ON YOU. ARE YOU A TOURIST?
- WE'RE HERE ON VACATION
FROM OSHIBANA, YO!
LET'S HAVE A FUNKY
GOOD TIME, YO!
- YOU GUYS CAN'T BE FOR REAL!
SORRY, BUT I'M HANGIN' OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS TONIGHT.
- AW. NOW DON'T PLAY ME
LIKE THAT, YO!
- I'D BETTER GO.
- BY "FRIENDS" YOU MEAN
THAT CAT AND UH--
- YO, I GOTTA ADMIT,
YOUR FRIENDS ARE PRETTY FUNKY.
THEY CAN TAG ALONG WITH US, YO.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO BE SHY!
- YOU'RE PUSHY, HUH?
COME ON, HAPPY, DO SOMETHIN'!
- MEOW!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "MEOW?"
- SHE THINKS HER KITTY CAN TALK!
HOW CUTE!
- YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG!
- COME PARTY WITH US!
- IT'S ABOUT TO GET FUNKY, YO!
- LOOK, I ALREADY TOLD YOU
I'M BUSY, SO KNOCK IT OFF!
- WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
I CAN'T MOVE!
- DON'T WORRY, BABY,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A GREAT TIME!
- IT'S GONNA BE
A FUNKY PARTY, YO!
- THESE GUYS ARE WIZARDS?
OH, NO!
- WHOA, THAT IS WHACK, YO!
YO!
( groans ) YO.
- YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
- LOKE.
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- FOR WHAT?
- THESE TWO
ARE RENEGADE WIZARDS.
THEY'VE BEEN TARGETING
FEMALE TOURISTS
THEY CATCH WALKING ALONE.
I WAS AFTER THEIR BOUNTY,
SO YOU ACTUALLY HELPED ME OUT.
ANYWAY, I BETTER TURN 'EM IN
BEFORE THEY DECIDE TO WAKE UP.
I'LL SEE YA LATER.
- HOLD ON A SEC.
- YEAH?
THANKS FOR RESCUING ME
FROM THOSE GUYS,
AND FOR GETTING MY GATE KEYS
BACK TO ME.
- NO PROB. IT'S NOTHIN', REALLY.
HEY, HOW ABOUT YOU AND I
GO OUT TOGETHER?
- UH-OH, THINGS ARE
ABOUT TO GET STEAMY!
- I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
- Narrator: THE WORLD-RENOWNED
RESTAURANT, "SUPER EXPRESS".
A POPULAR SPOT IN HOSENKA,
OFFERING ITS PATRONS A
CULINARY ADVENTURE.
WHILE ITS SILENT CHEF'S FOREHEAD
IS CERTAINLY CAPTIVATING,
ITS WIDE SELECTION OF
EXQUISITE DISHES
IS THE TRUE DRAW FOR
LOCALS AND TOURISTS ALIKE.
- YOU KNOW...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SIT SO FAR AWAY.
- OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
- I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK
YOU THIS FOR A WHILE.
IS IT TRUE THAT YOU HAVE A BAD
HISTORY WITH CELESTIAL WIZARDS?
IF YOU DON'T WANNA
TALK TO ME ABOUT IT,
THEN I CAN RESPECT THAT.
BUT I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR
FOR YOU TO JUDGE ME
JUST 'CAUSE I AM ONE.
- YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
SORRY. HONESTLY, I WASN'T TRYING
TO HURT YOUR FEELINGS.
I'M NO GOOD FOR YOU,
SO JUST FORGET ABOUT ME.
- UH, WHY'RE YOU GIVIN' ME
SOME LAME BREAKUP LINE?
- THAT CAME OUT FUNNY,
DIDN'T IT?
I DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY.
- YOU WEREN'T SERIOUS, WERE YOU?
- NO, I-- UH,
JUST THINKIN' ABOUT SOMETHIN'
THAT HAPPENED A WHILE BACK.
- CAN YOU TELL ME?
- ( snoring )
- ( sighs ) WELL, WHATEVER.
I FIGURED
IT COULDN'T HURT TO ASK.
THANKS AGAIN FOR SAVING ME
BACK THERE.
I FINALLY SEE WHY YOU'RE SO
POPULAR WITH THE LADIES.
THIS WAS NICE.
THINGS WERE STARTIN' TO GET
A LITTLE AWKWARD,
SO IT FELT GOOD TO JUST
SIT DOWN AND TALK TO YOU.
ANYWAY, I'D BETTER GET GOING.
- WAIT.
- UH, YEAH?
- LUCY.
- WHAT IS IT?
- THE TRUTH IS,
I DON'T HAVE LONG TO LIVE.
- YOU WHAT?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- ( laughs )
I SURE FOOLED YOU!
IT MAKES FOR A PRETTY GOOD
PICKUP LINE THOUGH, DOESN'T IT?
PULLS AT THE HEARTSTRINGS
EVERY TIME.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN YOUR FACE.
HA! CLASSIC!
- ( slaps )
- YOU JERK.
GEEZ. I TOTALLY BELIEVED YOU!
HAPPY, PLUE, WE'RE LEAVING!
- WHAT AM I DOING?
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I CAN'T LET MY FEELINGS
GET THE BEST OF ME.
AND I CAN'T DRAG LUCY INTO THIS.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME.
- WHAT'S WITH THE TWO OF THEM?
- EVIDENTLY THEY BOTH WERE
HURT DURING A PILLOW FIGHT
AFTER THEIR LAST JOB.
- IF THEY'RE THAT BANGED UP
THEN THOSE PILLOWS MUST'VE BEEN
FULL OF BRICKS.
- POOR GRAY.
I HOPE HE'S NOT IN PAIN.
- IT WAS JUST A PILLOW FIGHT.
WHAT WERE YOU GETTIN'
SO WORKED UP ABOUT?
- 'COURSE I GIVE EVERYTHING
ONE-HUNDRED PERCENT!
- OH, LIKE WHEN YOU
ONE-HUNDRED PERCENT LOST?
- I WAS AWESOME!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO LOST!
- MY PRINCE IS ALWAYS THE WINNER
IN MY HEART.
- LUCY! I WON
THE PILLOW FIGHT, RIGHT?
- PUT A SOCK IN IT.
- WE'RE SORRY!
WE'LL BE QUIET NOW!
- WOW, I THOUGHT ERZA
WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD KEEP THOSE
TWO IN CHECK.
- SHE'S A REAL MAN.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU SEEM LIKE
YOU'RE IN A BAD MOOD.
- DEAL WITH IT.
I'M ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
- YOU STILL MAD AT ME
ABOUT THAT PLUE THING?
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDIN' ME.
YOU THINK I'M PETTY ENOUGH TO
GET HUNG UP ON SOME PRANK?
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I JUST HAVE A LOT ON MY MIND
RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, YOU CAN ALWAYS
TALK TO ME!
- I'LL PASS.
THANKS ANYWAY, THOUGH.
- THIS IS MY FAULT.
MY TIME'S ALMOST UP.
- I'VE BEEN LOOKIN' ALL OVER
FOR LOKE! WHERE IS HE?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE RAN OUT ON ME!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, HUH?
- I COULD ASK YOU
THE SAME THING!
- LOKE, COME BACK!
- WHAT'S GOIN' ON OVER THERE?
- THEY'RE A BUNCH OF GIRLS
FROM AROUND TOWN.
FROM THE LOOKS OF THINGS,
THEY ALL THINK THEY'RE
LOKE'S GIRLFRIEND.
- LAST NIGHT, HE SAID HE WANTED
TO BREAK UP WITH ME!
- AND HE BROKE UP WITH ME, TOO!
- AND ME!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WHY DOESN'T HE WANT ME
ANYMORE? HUH? WHY?
- WELL-- UH.
IS HE GETTING MARRIED
TO SOME OTHER GIRL?
- UH, NO.
WHO IS SHE? IS IT SOMEONE
FROM THE GUILD?
LUCY! SAVE ME!
- SO, IS THIS THE GIRL?
- WELL, SHE DRESSES
LIKE A TRAMP.
- SHE THINKS SHE'S CUTE.
- DON'T TELL ME
LOKE'S GONNA MARRY HER!
- ( screams ) WHY'D YA
HAVE TO GO
AND DRAG ME INTO
THIS MESS, MIRA?
- SO.
- Narrator: THIS IS MAGNOLIA'S
ONE AND ONLY PUBLIC BATHHOUSE.
IN ADDITION TO
RELIEVING FATIGUE,
IT ALSO RESTORES THE MAGIC
ENERGY OF ALL WHO BATHE THERE.
- BATHHOUSES ARE MANLY!
- I LIKE MY BATH AT HOME,
BUT THIS PLACE TAKES THE CAKE!
NOTHIN' BEATS SOAKING
IN A BIG TUB!
LOKE?
- TRY THIS.
IT REALLY HITS THE SPOT
AFTER A BATH.
- OH, FLAVORED MILK? THANK YOU!
- THOUGHT I MIGHT HAVE ONE
WITH YA, IF YA DON'T MIND.
- JUST SO YOU KNOW, I HAD
A ROUGH DAY TODAY
THANKS TO YOU AND YOUR
STUPID FAN CLUB.
- LET'S PUT THAT BEHIND US.
HERE'S TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL EYES.
CHEERS!
- GOOD STUFF!
- NO KIDDIN'!
- THE SKY SURE IS PRETTY, HUH?
- YEAH.
- A SHOOTING STAR!
IT SOUNDS SILLY,
BUT I ALWAYS WONDERED WHERE
THOSE FALLEN STARS END UP.
- I KINDA FEEL SORRY FOR THEM.
JUST THINK, ONCE THEY
FALL FROM THE SKY,
THEY CAN NEVER RETURN TO HEAVEN.
DOESN'T THAT SEEM SAD?
- THAT'S ANOTHER ONE OF YOUR
SAPPY PICK-UP LINES, ISN'T IT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT YOU
ALMOST FOOLED ME TWICE!
- SAW RIGHT THROUGH ME.
C'MON. CAN'T YOU GO
LIKE FIVE MINUTES
WITHOUT TRYING TO
PICK UP A GIRL?
- I KNOW I CAN BE A REAL PAIN,
BUT I'M GLAD WE GOT
TO TALK AGAIN.
GOODBYE.
- OPEN GATE OF
THE SOUTHERN CROSS!
CRUX!
- WOW. SO THIS WEIRD
FLOATY GUY'S A SPIRIT, HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT! I LIKE TO
CALL HIM "GRANDPA CRUX".
I NEED YOU TO LOOK UP SOMETHING
FOR ME, PLEASE.
COULD YOU USE YOUR POWER TO FIND
OUT WHICH CELESTIAL WIZARDS
LOKE'S MET IN THE PAST?
- I DON'T THINK
HE HEARD YOU, LUCY!
- NAH, HE HEARD ME.
HE'S JUST DOING A SEARCH.
- WELL, HOW COME HE'S SNORING
LIKE THAT?
GRANDPA CRUX IS AN EXPERT
ON CELESTIAL WIZARDRY.
HE CAN TELL YOU ANYTHING
YOU WANNA KNOW ABOUT
THE DIFFERENT GATES THAT CONNECT
THE SPIRIT WORLD
TO THE HUMAN WORLD.
HE CAN EVEN TELL YOU ABOUT
PARTICULAR SPIRITS,
AND WHICH WIZARDS HAVE SUMMONED
THEM IN THE PAST.
SO DID YOU FIND ANY INFO?
INDEED. BUT REGRETTABLY,
I CANNOT PROVIDE ANY
EXTENSIVE DETAILS
AS PERSONAL PRIVACY LAWS DO
APPLY TO THE CELESTIAL WORLD.
HOWEVER, I CAN TELL YOU THAT
LOKE WAS ONCE CONNECTED TO
A CELESTIAL WIZARD
NAMED KAREN LILICA.
- KAREN LILICA?
- YOU KNOW HER? WHO IS SHE?
- SHE WAS SUPER FAMOUS
A FEW YEARS BACK.
I ACTUALLY HAD THE ISSUE FROM
WHEN SHE WAS PROFILED
IN SORCERER WEEKLY.
BUT, SHE DIED ON A JOB.
THEY SAY HER MASTER TOLD HER
NOT TO TAKE IT.
- SO SHE WAS A GUILD WIZARD
JUST LIKE US, HUH?
- MM-HMM.
SHE WAS A MEMBER OF BLUE PEGASUS
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY.
GRANDPA CRUX, WHAT WAS
THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN KAREN AND LOKE?
- SORRY, BUT I'M AFRAID I'VE
SAID ALL I CAN ON THE MATTER.
- AW, C'MON!
- HEY, IT LOOKS LIKE HE DECIDED
TO GO AHEAD AND SEARCH FOR YA!
- NO, HE'S ASLEEP THIS TIME.
SO KAREN AND LOKE.
- THE TRUTH IS
I DON'T HAVE LONG TO LIVE.
- HOLD ON.
- ONCE THEY FALL FROM THE SKY,
THEY CAN NEVER RETURN TO HEAVEN.
DOESN'T THAT SEEM SAD?
- FALLEN STAR? HE CAN'T BE.
- UH. IS SOMETHIN' WRONG?
- I GOT BAD NEWS, LUCY!
IT'S LOKE! HE QUIT FAIRY TAIL
AND THEN RAN AWAY!
- DID HE SAY WHY?
- NO, WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE!
EVERYONE'S OUT
LOOKING FOR HIM NOW.
HE'S BEEN ACTING WEIRD LATELY
BUT NOBODY EXPECTED THIS!
- MAYBE I'M RIGHT.
- Natsu: HEY, WHERE YA GOIN'?
LUCY! DO YOU KNOW SOMETHING
WE DON'T?
- HEY! LOKE!
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- COME ON OUT!
- LOKE!
- IS HE HIDIN' IN HERE?
- I'M GUESSIN' NO.
- LOKE!
- WHERE ARE YA, MAN?
- THERE YOU ARE!
- LUCY.
- THE WHOLE GUILD'S
LOOKING FOR YOU.
THAT'S KAREN'S GRAVE, ISN'T IT?
SHE WAS A GREAT CELESTIAL WIZARD
AND SHE HAD A CONTRACT
WITH YOU, RIGHT?
THE SPIRIT LOKE.
WAIT, THAT'S NOT REALLY
YOUR NAME.
YOUR NAME IS LEO.
LEO THE LION.
- WELL, I WON'T DENY IT,
BUT HOW DID YOU FIND OUT?
- DON'T FORGET,
I'M A CELESTIAL WIZARD, TOO,
AND I HAVE CONTRACTS
WITH A LOT OF SPIRITS.
IT WASN'T TOO HARD
TO DIG UP THE TRUTH.
STILL,
YOU SHOULD'VE COME TO
TALK TO ME ABOUT THIS!
NORMALLY, WHENEVER THE OWNER
OF A GATE KEY DIES,
THE CONTRACT BETWEEN SPIRIT
AND WIZARD IS TERMINATED.
THE SPIRIT IS THEN FORCED BACK
INTO THEIR WORLD,
UNTIL THE KEY FALLS INTO NEW
HANDS AND A CONTRACT IS MADE.
YOUR CONTRACT
WITH KAREN
SHOULD'VE ENDED ON
THE DAY SHE DIED.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE STILL HERE.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
THAT BEFORE. I MEAN,
THAT'S JUST NOT THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO WORK, RIGHT?
I KNOW YOUR KIND CAN'T SURVIVE
IN THE HUMAN WORLD FOR LONG.
JUST LIKE HUMANS CAN'T
SURVIVE IN YOUR WORLD.
IT'LL SLOWLY SAP AWAY
YOUR LIFE TILL, FINALLY,
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND IT'S BEEN
THREE YEARS NOW.
- THREE YEARS? I DIDN'T EVEN
THINK ONE WAS POSSIBLE!
- PRETTY AMAZING, HUH?
BUT I DON'T HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO KEEP IT UP.
- HOLD ON! THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME WAY THAT I CAN SAVE YOU!
WHY CAN'T I JUST OPEN A GATE
FOR YOU?
TELL ME WHY YOU CAN'T GO BACK
TO THE SPIRIT WORLD!
- YOU DON'T NEED TO SAVE ME.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IF YOU DON'T GET SOME HELP SOON,
YOU'RE AS GOOD AS DEAD!
- LOOK, THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN GO BACK.
- BUT WHY?
- I BROKE A FUNDAMENTAL LAW
THAT APPLIES TO BOTH
WIZARD AND SPIRIT.
AND AS A RESULT,
I WAS BANISHED FROM THE
CELESTIAL WORLD FOR ETERNITY.
- LOKE. JUST WHAT DID YOU DO?
- I CAN'T DENY MY CRIME
SO I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO FACE
THE PUNISHMENT.
I AM A TRAITOR TO MY OWN KIND.
I WAS CONTRACTED TO KAREN.
BUT SHE DIED,
BECAUSE I KILLED HER.
- ( closing theme song playing )
- SOMETIMES I WONDER WHAT
THE CELESTIAL WORLD IS LIKE.
- OH, YEAH? I THOUGH YOU ALREADY
KNEW WHAT IT WAS LIKE!
DIDN'T YOU SEE IT BACK AT
DUKE EVERLUE'S PLACE
WHEN YOU HITCHED
A RIDE ON VIRGO?
- NAH, THAT ONLY
LASTED A SECOND.
I COULD BARELY SEE ANYTHING.
BUT NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
I DO REMEMBER SOMETHING.
- OH! WHAT? TELL ME!
- A MUSTACHE.
- Natsu and Happy: NEXT TIME:
CELESTIAL SPIRIT KING!
- Happy: MUSTACHE?
WHAT ARE YA TALKIN' ABOUT?
- WELL, YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
TUNE IN NEXT TIME
IF YOU WANNA FIND OUT!
- NOW THAT'S A PREVIEW LINE!