[SOLDIER 144A] Message from
the Custody Enforcement Unit!
[SOLDIER 144B]
The Oración Seis is not out to
destroy churches as
we originally thought.
They're after the Celestial
wizards being sheltered inside!
[SOLDIER 144D] We must locate,
and protect these wizards!
[NATSU] Everything's happening
so fast all of a sudden.
♪
[WARREN] You gotta be kiddin'
me! Our Michelle is a phony?
Well, We're not absolutely
sure that's the case.
But it would certainly
appear that way.
We found who we believe to
be the real Michelle Lobster.
[WARREN] Seriously?
I'll let Master, Lucy,
and the others know right away!
[LAKI] Thanks!
We're gonna try to find
the closest hospital
and get this girl some help.
Man, I can't believe this.
What do you
think we should do?
We've gotta get a hold
of Natsu and his team!
Do they have
communication cards?
Yeah, each team
should have at least one.
I think Elfman
has one on him, too.
[VIJEETER] Bad news!
We just got word that
the Oración Seis
are attacking Kardia Cathedral!
[CANA] What?
Aw, crap!
And there's nobody
there to protect it.
[ALZACK] I'll go right now.
You comin'?
Of course. Please look
after Asca for us.
Hey! You guys
had better watch your back!
The Michelle who's
with you is a fake!
Be careful!
[WARREN] Hello?
Can anyone hear me?
Someone please respond!
[JACKPOT] Aw, yeah!
Hot payoff!
Rock Punch!
[JACKPOT] it looks like this
time the jackpot's hitting you!
[BYRO] If these two fools
defeat one another
it'll certainly make
my job easier.
However.
I don't understand.
Why are they ordering this now?
What is their reasoning?
Just stay back,
okay Michelle?
I'll do whatever it
takes to keep you safe!
[Jackpot laughs]
[JACKPOT] Oops, silly me!
I was having such a
good time playing with you
I completely forgot
about my mission!
Gotta run!
[NATSU] Hey!
[SOLDIER 144D] The Oración Seis!
[JACKPOT] Whaddya say
we get right to the action?
Here goes!
[JACKPOT] Sweet!
Three in a row!
That's a Triple
Bomb Bonus!
Kaboom!
Dammit.
Why's he attacking
the church?
[BYRO] This is reprehensible!
Curse you!
[HAPPY] Despair Unleashed!
Sand Slash!
It's pointless.
I hear you.
[MAX] Don't be so sure!
[COBRA] Don't you listen?
[MAX] The joke's on you, pal!
I got you in my Sand Trap.
Guess ya didn't hear
that one coming, did ya?
Now...
Erza...!
Go get 'im!
[COBRA] How idiotic.
I hear your attacks coming!
Now I'll destroy you!
[ERZA] Max!
Save you tears.
Do you honestly care
what happens to him?
[ERZA] Yes, he is my friend.
[COBRA] Ever since
I lost Cubellios.
I'm all alone.
I have no friends.
[Ezra chuckles]
I can hear it.
All the sadness in your voice.
Instead of
attempting to hide it,
you should aim to conquer it.
It'll make you a
stronger person.
[COBRA] Don't talk
as if you know.
You can't possibly
understand the
loneliness and
heartache that I feel.
[ERZA] We have all been there!
Everyone in this world
has experienced
heartache in some form.
Yes.
It's unavoidable.
[SOLDIER 144E]
Now then, come with us!
[SOLDIER 144F]
We've found a celestial wizard.
What should we do, sir?
[SOLDIER 144G] Good work!
Hurry and get her
to headquarters!
[COBRA] I'm wasting time.
I almost forgot
about my objective.
Titania.
We'll have to finish
this another day.
[ANGEL] Very good work!
[SHAMSIEL] I found him!
I caught the celestial
wizard for you!
Time for the Amplitude
Limiter Anti-Link.
This might hurt a bit.
No, please!
So beautiful.
[MAN 144A] Even if
you sever my body link,
the others will stop you--
[ANGEL] If what Father
Fabrizio told him is true,
then there are only two
celestial wizards left.
[SHAMSIEL] Yaaaaay!
This is so much fun!
[ANGEL] We've waited enough.
Now our prayers will
finally be answered.
[Angel laughs with
evil overtones]
[PANTHERLILY] Your doctrine
is being used for evil?
[HAPPY] I don't get it.
Can you explain?
[SAMUEL]
Yes, but before I do that.
[SAMUEL] I challenge you
to a rematch, "Brother."
[PANTHERLILY]
If that's what you want.
You're on, "Sammy."
Why now?
Perhaps Samuel has
got something to prove?
I've never understood
the thought
processes of the male species.
Better start explaining
before I knock you out!
[PANTHERLILY] I know
Zentopia's up to something!
Tell me!
That is precisely
what I'm trying to do!
Before we left,
Cardinal Lapointe gave
each of us very specific orders.
He's a bird, too?
No, not that
kind of "cardinal."
He's some sort of
big shot within the church.
[SAMUEL] Dan and Mary
were sent to stop you.
Sugarboy was put on standby
in case of an emergency.
And then there's Gutman--
[PANTHERLILY]
Wait, who is that?
[SAMUEL] A newcomer
to the Legion Platoon.
He's replacing Coco.
[PANTHERLILY] No way!
Where is she?
What did they do to her?
They put her where
traitors belong.
In prison!
[PANTHERLILY]
What'd she do?
[SAMUEL] She was supportive
of you and your colleagues.
[SAMUEL] Enough about her,
we've got more important things
to worry about right
now, like Gutman.
[SAMUEL]
I didn't hear his orders
but I've got a bad
feeling about him.
According to
my calculations,
when The Cleaner
steps into the limelight.
Zentopia will face a
threat from the inside.
[PANTHERLILY] Coco.
You know. She told
him that she hated cats.
Oh, so she rejected him?
He must be heartbroken!
How sad!
[PANTHERLILY]
There's enough drama in this
situation without you
making up stories!
[HAPPY] Sorry!
Please don't hurt me.
There's something
else you should know.
The orders given
to Lord Byro and me
were bizarre to say the least.
Bizarre how?
[SAMUEL] We were given
a task I don't understand.
But what's most
perplexing is we weren't
ordered to recover
the Infinity Clock.
[SAMUEL]
As far as I'm concerned,
stopping it should be
our top priority right now!
Oh, I see.
That is rather
bizarre, isn't it?
[HAPPY] In that case,
looks like we're gonna
have to work together
from here on out!
[PANTHERLILY]
So that's why you wanted
to know whether
Carla had any visions.
Even after all of this,
Lord Byro's loyalty
still remains intact.
But I however...
[PANTHERLILY]
You sure aren't putting up as
much of a fight
this time, Sammy!
[PANTHERLILY] There's a
hesitation behind your attacks.
You'll never be
able to defeat me
until you can fight
with utter certainty.
[PANTHERLILY]
We'll have to put an end to
whatever is causing your doubt.
[GUTMAN] You go boom now!
He's a monster.
[GAJEEL] I'm still
standin', ya blockhead!
[GUTMAN] Yeah, but not for long!
You ain't seen nothin' yet.
I'm just gettin' started.
[MARY] Just give up already!
You don't stand a
chance against this freak!
He's, like, way
stronger than all of us!
[GUTMAN]
Yep, listen to the lady.
Y'know, back when I was
with Phantom I might've turned
around and just walked away,
but unfortunately for you.
I'm a Fairy Tail wizard now.
[GAJEEL] So that means there
ain't no way I'm givin' up!
You can beat me to a pulp
and I'll still keep fightin'!
[GAJEEL] There's no stoppin' us.
Right Juvia?
[JUVIA] Thanks for buying
me some time, Gajeel.
[JUVIA] I'm feeling
much better now.
[GUTMAN] Oh no, it's a trap!
Are you kidding?
I can get outta this, easy!
[JUVIA] Go ahead and
give it your best shot.
[GUTMAN] Alright, fine!
You're goin' boom, lady!
[GUTMAN] What're you doing?
I don't wanna get hurt, too!
Let go of me!!
[JUVIA] That's not gonna happen!
Now Gajeel!
[GAJEEL] You got it!
Now it's your turn
to go boom scumbag!
[GAJEEL] Not bad but
our timin' could use some work.
It would've timed out perfectly
if Gray were my partner.
[GAJEEL] Oh ya don't say.
[MARY] They're so awesome.
They, like, totally beat
"Gutman the Cleaner."
I can't believe it!
[BIXLOW] Hey!
Wake up!
Open your eyes or else, Erigor!
Uh. You don't have
to be so rough with him.
I don't have to be nice,
he's the enemy!
C'mon, man!
Hurry up and tell me
what you guys are plannin'!
Where's the Infinity Clock?
Sorry I don't know...
Everything's hazy.
I have no idea
what I was even doing.
[WENDY] He just got
his memory back.
It might be a while before he's
able to think clearly again.
Do you even remember
anything at this point?
[ERIGOR]
I remember having a horrible
nightmare while I was in prison.
[ERIGOR]
It's hard to explain but it was
like someone snuck
into my dream.
After that, it was over.
[BIXLOW] So lemme guess,
when you woke up
you'd suddenly
become Grim Reaper?
[WENDY] I could be
wrong about this,
but it sounds like
someone cast a spell
to use your dreams
to control you.
[ERIGOR] I fear you're right.
[BIXLOW] Yep, that's it.
And I bet they're manipulating
their targets' brain waves.
That way, they can take control
slowly without being noticed.
If only I had
known before
I agreed to give
up my memory.
I was granted powerful
magic which allowed me
to control the weather,
but it wasn't worth it.
[ERIGOR] I forgot everything!
It was gone in a flash.
I can't imagine anything
more agonizing than that.
[ERIGOR] I never
understood why they say
"great power comes at
a price," but I do now.
I was lost.
Until I heard your
voice calling to me.
I've no intention
of being your friend,
but please allow
me to thank you.
Of course!
Wait a sec.
Cana!
Right before she
picked out all our teams.
She was talking about
how tired she felt.
[WENDY] Now that you mention it,
she did say she
had been sleeping a lot.
Do you think she's
being controlled through
her dreams and
she just doesn't realize it?
[BIXLOW] There's no
other way to explain it;
they manipulated her
into picking teams
that work best for them!
[WENDY] Oh, no!
[BIXLOW] Man, this sucks! We've
fallen right into their trap!
[MIDNIGHT]
I'd expect no less of the
renowned celestial
wizard Will Neville.
Even in death, you're protected
by intense magic power.
But it's not going to be
able to protect you forever.
[ALZACK] Hold it right there!
I don't know what
you're tryin' to do,
but we're not gonna
let you get away with it!
[MIDNIGHT] Well, well,
what do we have here?
This should be amusing.
[ALZACK] You must be Brain the
Second, of the Neo-Oración Seis.
[ALZACK] Let's go!
Alright, how 'bout this?
Omni-directional formation!
What a joke.
[BISCA] Okay, babe...
Just a little longer!
[MIDNIGHT] I applaud you for
trying, but no one can stop me.
Now!
[BISCA] One shot.
One down!
[Bisca screams]
[ALZACK] Bisca.
She has skill,
but lacks the resolve
needed to shoot another person.
You see, in order
to achieve greatness.
One must be willing to
pay an even greater price.
I can tell just by looking
at the two of you.
You're simply not willing
to make that kind of sacrifice.
[JACKPOT] Here goes!
Oh, we've got a match!
Anti-Link time!
What did you just do?
[Jackpot laughs]
[JACKPOT] Now don't
get your panties in a
wad over things that
don't concern you.
[JACKPOT] You just need
to focus on carrying out
the cardinal's orders
like a good little boy.
[BYRO] Say what?
[NATSU] Quit your blabbin'
and come fight me!
[JACKPOT]
Okay! Wow!
Another Lightning Bolt
Bonus--What the--?
How'd you hit me?
You will suffer the consequences
for this sinful destruction!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Talon!
[JACKPOT]
What have you done to me?
Now I can't use my Slot Magic!
I don't even know
who I am without it!
You're gonna give
me an identity crisis!
[NATSU] I knew I'd get
a hit in eventually!
But that was nothin'
compared to this!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Wing Attack!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Roar!
Something's wrong.
I've got this feeling.
I don't know what it is,
but it's bad.
[MICHELLE] Big Sister.
Don't worry.
I'll be here no matter what.
[MAX] I think the screaming
came from this way!
[ERZA] This is horrible!
What happened here?
[ERZA] So that's why
Cobra ran off.
Monster.
[MIDNIGHT] The celestial wizard
Anti-Links are now complete!
Huh? What does
that mean?
Their body links
have all been severed.
[MIDNIGHT] O, great Neville.
The Amplitude Limiters
have finally been released.
Now nothing stands
in the way of your nightmare.
[ARCHBISHOP] Soon It
shall blanket the entire world!
The chaos that was
sealed has been set free!
[ARCHBISHOP] It will be
unleashed upon the unsuspecting
world and the never-ending
nightmare will finally begin!
[Archbishop laughs maniacally]
[ARCHBISHOP] The end is near!
It is within our grasp!
Yes, The end is near!
It's within our grasp!
[Archbishop laughs maniacally]
[MAX] What the heck?
Aw C'mon, this has gotta
be some kinda joke!
[ERZA] Do you hear that sound?
[WENDY] The Infinity Clock
has been released.
[BIXLOW] What?
That can't be it!
It's way too big!
[ERIGOR] That is indeed
the Infinity Clock.
It was hidden above the
Grand Cathedral of Zentopia.
[BIXLOW] Now what happens?
[GUTMAN] You won't find
this version of Zentopia's
doctrine in your
widdle history books.
This is where good
and evil come together.
Where the beginning
meets the end.
[GUTMAN] We did exactly what
Cardinal Lapointe told us to do.
And the archbishop told him!
[GUTMAN] I don't know what
they wanna do with this,
but honestly,
it's not like I need to know.
[GUTMAN] For the doctrine!
For Zentopia!
Victory-wictory is all ours.
[HAPPY] Look, it's a giant fish!
I don't think it'd be very
tasty 'cause it's all bones!
[SAMUEL]
It appears we're too late!
If only I hadn't wasted so
much time by doubting myself!
I shudder to think about
what's going to happen next!
Where are you going, Sammy?
To see the truth
with my own eyes.
I'm going to the Grand
Cathedral of Zentopia!
[HAPPY] Hey, come back!
You never told us about
the weird orders the
cardinal gave you and Byro!
Be careful.
[PANTHERLILY] Coco.
What are those things?
[citizens talk in fear]
[NATSU] Aw man, now what?
It would appear that the
Infinity Clock has
been activated.
Oh no?
We have gotta find
a way to stop it!
I'm afraid. I cannot
help you with that.
I've been ordered to take
you to the cardinal,
Lucy Heartfilia.
[NATSU] What?
Why now all of a sudden?
What could he
possibly want with me?
I don't quite
understand it, either.
But it's my duty to follow
orders so please cooperate.
You're not takin'
her anywhere, got it?
I couldn't care
less about your orders!
Look at that thing in the sky!
We can't waste any time!
[LUCY] I know you're just
trying to do the right thing
but deep down you've
gotta know that's not it!
No, I don't.
[KLODOA] Byro.
You're only making this
harder on yourself by thinking.
Why are you hesitating?
Simply remain faithful
to the doctrine
and carry out your orders!
Not you again!
That creepy,
talking stick!
[KLODOA] My name is Klodoa.
I am the seventh member
of the Oración Seis.
Otherwise known as the
brains of the operation.
You remember, dontcha?
[LUCY] The seventh member?
Wait a minute.
Aren't you short a person?
[KLODOA] There's no need
to hide the truth any longer.
The time has come
for you to reveal yourself!
[KLODOA] Shed that disguise
you've been hiding behind
and show these "friends"
of yours who you really are!
Who, Michelle?
That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard!
If you're trying
to confuse me
it's not gonna work
this time, stick man!
That girl is Michelle Lobster!
And she's like family!
She's my sis!
She traveled
all over to find me
and give me dad's memento.
She's all the family
I've got now that he's gone.
Don't worry,
I won't fall for his tricks!
I know better than to believe
anything that creep has to say!
Hey, what's wrong?
Michelle.
Please tell me it's not true.
Please!
Careful.
I'm sorry I hurt
you. Big Sister.
Why...
Michelle?
[IMITATIA] You see?
I truly am a member
of the Neo-Oración Seis.
The mistress of deception.
They call me Imitatia.
[IMITATIA] We needed you
and your friends to gather the
parts of the Infinity Clock
and assemble it for us.
[IMITATIA] That's why I took
the form of Michelle Lobster.
It was the only way
I could earn your trust.
How could you be so cruel?
I treated you like family.
[IMITATIA]
We're willing to do whatever
it takes to emerge victorious.
We attacked the
churches in order
to sever all known body links.
Thereby releasing the
seal on the Infinity Clock.
[IMITATIA] Now that that
goal has been achieved.
You are the only
one who is still needed.
Big Sister Lucy.
What's gotten into you?
[LUCY]
Wait, I know!
They must be controlling
you with a spell!
Don't worry, I'll help you.
[NATSU] Stay away from her.
So you were lying to
us the whole time, Michelle?
[IMITATIA] That's not my name.
[NATSU] Answer me!
No, stop!
[KLODOA] A critical
hit right off the bat!
That's my girl!
[IMITATIA] Byro.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
the orders Lapointe gave you?
Take Lucy Heartfilia
back to him at once.
You are in no position
to tell me what to do!
My loyalty lies with
the church of Zentopia!
[BYRO] That belongs
to the Archbishop!
[KLODOA] Whoever
holds his gold seal wields
the same authority
as the archbishop himself.
[IMITATIA]
From this point forward,
my orders and the archbishop's
are one and the same.
[BYRO] Very well.
As you wish.
[KLODOA] If you ask me,
we should go ahead and
kill the Dragon Slayer
while we have the chance.
[IMITATIA] No.
I want to bring him with us.
I have a feeling he'll prove
quite useful as a hostage.
[KLODOA] Fine.
Guess I'll let him live for now.
But don't forget
that showing pity to
your enemies is
frowned upon, Imitatia.
Yes, I'm well aware.
Please.
Michelle.
Just talk to me!
[KLODOA] I thought
there was supposed
to be three of them here.
Did one get away?
We're in trouble!
[WARREN] What'd you say?
Can you speak up?
Seriously, I can
barely hear you!
[WARREN] You there?
Hey, Elfman!
♪
[NATSU] Aw man, I'm so sleepy.
[HAPPY] I don't know
how you could be.
I mean, you sleep
like a freakin' log.
[NATSU] Not lately.
I dunno what's up but I keep
havin' these creepy dreams.
[HAPPY] You have nightmares?
Seriously?
[NATSU] What?
Am I not allowed to
have 'em or somethin'?
[HAPPY] I'm just shocked to find
out you have a sensitive side.
Wow, you're not
a callous jerk after all!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Real Nightmare!
Hey, watch your mouth or I'm
gonna be your real nightmare!
[HAPPY] Now hold on a minute!
Just calm down!
Can't we talk this over?
[NATSU] The "callous jerk"
doesn't bother talkin'!