[FROGS scream]
[CROWD murmurs]
[MAGIC COUNCIL MEMBERS scream]
[DORANBOLT grunting]
My head. Hey,
what just happened?
[grunts] Get up.
This is serious!
Come on. I'm not
doin' this solo.
Wake up. Lahar!
My god. He's dead.
[grunting]
Uh!
[JACKAL]
You can't be alive.
Killing all of you
was the whole point.
Your pals played along, but I
guess you need some convincing.
Explosion.
Uh! Damn you!
[ORG]
Doranbolt! Run away.
[DORANBOLT grutning]
I can't do that!
There's no reason for you
to die with the rest of us.
Hate to burst your bubble,
but there's no running
from my explosions.
[ORG]
Leave! Do it now.
[DORANBOLT groaning]
The name's Jackal, by the way.
One of the Nine Demon
Gates of Tartaros.
Tell that to your
friends in hell.
They should know the name of
the man who slaughtered them.
Tell them I enjoyed it.
Live! Find what justice means
to you and defend till the end.
That's an order!
[chuckles]
[DORANBOLT]
Master Org!
[CROWD screams]
Strange. He left
some sort of mist.
It looks like it's spreading.
[TEMPESTER]
Mankind cannot escape disaster.
[LAXUS]
Tsch.
[TEMPESTER] This mist is
rife with Bane Particles.
As it spreads, they will destroy
any ether-nano they can find.
But ether-nano's inside
all living things! [coughs]
[TEMPESTER] Right you are.
Which is why this mist causes
Magic Deficiency Syndrome,
and bane sickness.
[BIXLOW choking]
[TEMPESTER] First you'll
be stripped of your powers,
and then you'll be
stripped of your lives.
[BIXLOW choking]
[LAXUS] No one else is gonna
die here! Not while I'm around!
[FRIED]
Laxus. Shield your mouth!
[LAXUS grunts, inhales]
[FRIED]
What are you doing?
[LAXUS inhales]
[LAXUS] That's twice you've
misjudged me, "Disaster".
First you underestimated
the strength of my magic.
Now you've done the
same with my lungs.
[FRIED] Please, stop.
You'll kill yourself!
[LAXUS inahles] No way're
you talkin' me outta this.
But you can make sure
they get home safe.
[FRIED gasps]
[FRIED]
Laxus!
[NARRATOR]
The dark, demonic, guild,
Tartaros, has come
out of the shadows,
and seeks to massacre the
members of the Magic Council,
both present and former.
Natsu and the gang sought out
former Council member, Michello,
hoping to save his life.
[CARLA] ...they're doing this
to achieve a goal.
[MICHELLO] I'm sorry, but I have
no idea what that might be.
No wait, there is something.
some awful thing, called Face!
Everyone down!
What is it?
That goes for you, too!
[MICHELIA, MICHELLO gasp]
Get ready.
For what?
[NATSU grunts]
No! Please, not my
beautiful house!
[LUCY whimpers]
I think we're under attack! Ah!
Is everybody okay?
--[LUCY, WENDY groan]
--[HAPPY] Aye.
That explosion was massive;
how are we alive?
[grunts] Haven't eaten
that fast since Tuesday.
[MICHELIA]
E-Eaten?
[belches]
Nice one!
[NARRATOR]
But Jackal,
the wizard who took the lives
of the current council,
appeared at Michello's house
in explosive fashion.
[JACKAL] ...that's how it was
with the Magic Council. Ha, ha.
[NARRATOR] For what
reason has Tartaros
set its eyes on the
Magic Council?
What diabolical purpose
are they trying to achieve?
And can Natsu and the gang
stop them before it's too late?
[NATSU] Brace yourself.
I'm gonna hurt ya.
[NARRATOR] The opening battle in
the war of Faeries and Demons
is about to explode into action!
The nerve of this guy!
Don't you have any
respect for your elders?
I don't think he does.
'Course not! He's with Tartaros!
He's already murdered your
colleagues back in Era!
[LUCY] We're not letting him
get you, too. It's time to run!
I don't need you
to tell me that!
[WENDY] Don't worry! Natsu will
stop this guy, no sweat!
Let's go!
[JACKAL chuckles]
[NATSU]
Uh...
[ALL scream]
--[CROWD screams]
--[MALE 236A] What's happening?
[MALE 236B]
The whole town's blowing up!
We gotta get outta here! Run!
[CROWD screams]
Why are you attacking
innocent people?
[NATSU growls]
Ahh! Explosion!
Natsu!
He's a goner!
He'll be all right!
Heat and explosion magic
are a light snack to
a Fire Dragon Slayer!
[NATSU grunts]
What's going on?
Is he eating my explosion?
[NATSU growls]
[NATSU yells]
[JACKAL groans]
Jeez, the guy's
a livin' fireball!
You're kidding me!
[JACKAL groans]
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
[NATSU yells]
[JACKAL groans]
That's the way! Roast 'em!
He's Amazing!
[MICHELLO stammers]
[MICHELLO] I've heard stories
about Fairy Tail wizards,
but this is the first time
I've seen one in action.
Didn't know they
were so strong!
[JACKAL yells]
You're good! Even better
than I thought you'd be!
But there's something you
should know about my power...
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
Hey!
[JACKAL groans]
I ain't through with you!
[NATSU grunts]
[JACKAL groans]
Incredible.
I don't believe it.
Natsu. You can stop!
You really are the
master of overkill.
Did you forget that we
needed him conscious?
[grunts] Oh, that's right,
he's supposed to tell us
where their hideout is.
And what they're
trying to accomplish.
[MICHELLO whimpers]
What if these monsters
really are after "Face"? All
of Fiore would be in danger!
The White Legacy is a secret.
Most Council members
didn't even know it existed.
How could these vile people
have found out about it?
No matter, I need to find
shelter and wait them out.
It looks like you've got this
handled, so I'll be leaving!
--[LUCY]  Huh?
--[MICHELIA] Uh...
[MICHELLO]
I'm going to, uh,
see if the other former Council
members are safe! Bye!
Grandpa! Wait!
You too, Michelia! Let's
get moving! Come on!
I don't think you
should be leaving us.
If you know something,
this is the time to share it!
I don't know anything! Nothing
at all! Just leave me alone!
I'm not buyin' it.
You better tell us,
if you know what's good
for you, old man.
[MICHELLO gasps]
I know nothing and that's final!
[JACKAL]
What a shame.
[MICHELLO]
Huh?!
[JACKAL grunts]
If you had some juicy
info to share,
I might've let you leave
with your body intact.
[LUCY]
He doesn't even seem injured!
[NATSU]
Ee!
What is this guy made of?
Do you have rocks for brains?
I told you, I don't
know anything!
Go ask somebody else!
I can't help you!
That's too bad. Guess I'll
stick to my first plan.
[MICHELLO groans]
U-Uh... Hey!
Don't just stand there
like a bunch of idiots!
Get him while he's down!
I order you!
You're kiddin' me.
[JACKAL grunts] You've got
skill, I'll give you that.
But you should learn
to pay attention
when someone's talkin'.
Huh?
Natsu! Look!
[NATSU]
Uh?! What the...?
My curses can change anyone
stupid enough to touch me
into a living bomb.
I wonder... How many
times did you touch me?
[NATSU growls]
Are you okay?
Keep away, Happy! That goes
for the rest of ya, too!
[LUCY]
But, Natsu...
[WENDY]
We can't!
Get outta here!
[WENDY, LUCY, HAPPY panting]
[CARLA screams]
--[HAPPY] Natsu!
--[LUCY] Get down!
[laughing]
[MICHELIA]
Oh no!
Is he...?
I can't really tell.
Weren't you going to protect me?
You're the most pathetic
bodyguard I've ever seen!
Grandpa, please!
Crazy! I can't believe
he's still in one piece
after all of that!
Not bad for a total loser.
[laughing]
[HAPPY] Come on,
Natsu! Please get up!
[CARLA]
He's out cold!
[LUCY growls]
Your knight in shining
armor is outta commission.
[MICHELLO whimpers]
I'm a goner. Please,
get up! I need you!
If you tell me what you know,
I promise I'll only
kill your grandkid.
[MICHELIA gasps]
Ya see, I can be a reasonable
guy. Aren't you lucky?
I can't believe this jerk!
No! Stay back!
[MICHELLO whimpering]
[LUCY]
Really?
[MICHELIA]
Grandpa!
[JACKAL]
Oh, no, you don't!
Wendy!
Let's go!
Whatever you do,
remember to not touch him!
We can handle this!
You won't get past us!
Sky Dragon Roar!
The explosion
canceled it out!
[JACKAL] Those weak
attacks won't hurt me!
Run away, Wendy!
If he touches you,
you'll end up like Natsu!
[WENDY gasps]
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
I told you, it's useless!
[WENDY gasps]
[JACKAL laughs]
Don't be shy, there are plenty
of explosions to go around.
[laughs]
[WENDY, LUCY grunt]
[MICHELLO panting]
[MICHELLO]
This is bad! Very bad!
If Face is really what they're
after, we're all done for!
The entire world
would be doomed!
Let's do this! Open,
Gate of the Scorpion!
Scorpio!
Long time, no see!
What the crap?
Did this chick just make
a guy out of thin air?
Stop askin' questions
and get ready for a dose
of my desert power!
Sand Buster!
Ha.
[LUCY, SCORPIO scream]
[CARLA]
There's sand in my eyes!
[WENDY coughs]
I think I swallowed some.
Don't you worry, there's plenty
more where that came from!
Sand Buster!
Three of 'em won't
make a difference.
Not again! I can't see a thing!
Sorry, this isn't working.
Good try, though!
Hey. S'cool.
[JACKAL laughs]
[JACKAL] Now do you
see how useless it is?
[WENDY, LUCY]
Mm.
He can block our attacks,
and hit us back harder
thanks to his explosions.
His magic's too powerful.
Magic?
[laughs]
You tools have no idea
what you're dealing with here.
We don't use magic in Tartaros,
we prefer a darker poison.
Curses!
What's that mean?
[JACKAL] A power that trumps
all the magic in the world.
I've killed stronger wizards
than you could hope to be!
[JACKAL grunts]
[HAPPY]
Uh!
[JACKAL]
Explosion Spiral!
[WENDY, LUCY scream]
[WENDY screams]
[LUCY groans]
[WENDY groans]
This is bad!
No, Wendy!
[WENDY groans]
[LUCY whimpers]
Later, losers.
I am so sorry. You're hurt,
and it's because of us.
[LUCY grunting]
No. This isn't your fault.
It's between our guild and his.
Hey Wendy!
Help Natsu!
[WENDY sighs]
[LUCY] I'm going after
the canine freak show.
Careful!
Where are all these
explosions comin' from?
[MALE 236A]
No idea... But I'm worried
it may have something to do
with what happened in Era!
[MALE 236B] They've caused
some serious damage.
We should probably go and help!
Gotta run! Gotta find shelter!
If I don't, I'm as good as dead!
Who is that? I've never
seen him around here before.
Yeah, neither have I. Maybe he's
connected to those explosions?
Hey, young man! Find me
somewhere to hide, and quickly!
[MALE 236B]
What's wrong with you?
My life is in danger,
you ignorant whelp!
Huh?!
Listen close. I'm a former
member of the Magic Council!
I've been protecting this town
and its people for years!
Now it's your turn
to protect me!
You didn't get
very far, old man.
[MICHELLO whimpers]
[JACKAL chuckles]
Stop this! I have nothing
to do with anything!
I don't have any secrets!
I just wanna live a peaceful
life with my grandchild!
That's all!
[JACKAL]
Is that the same grandchild
you straight up left alone
and at my mercy? Huh?
[JACKAL laughs]
[MICHELLO whimpering]
[LUCY panting]
Open, Gate of the--
Wouldn't do that. Unless
you wanna get blown up.
Huh?!
Uh...
What is this thing?
That's my landmine curse.
Make one wrong move, and boom.
[gasps]
What's with all the ruckus?
It looks like wizards
are fighting!
Get away from me, now!
You're all in danger here!
I feel like I've seen
this girl somewhere.
She was one of the wizards
in the Grand Magic
Games Bikini Contest!
Looks like we've
got an audience.
That could make things
more interesting.
[MICHELLO]
Ah! No! Stop!
--Ah! What's happening to me?
--[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD murmurs]
Say hello to my newest bombs!
[whimpers]
Let me go!
--[CROWD screams]
--They're bombs?
Run for your lives!
Aw. I wanted them to see the
true ugliness of humanity,
but I guess they're just
gonna have to miss the show.
[LUCY gasping]
Only one of these bombs is gonna
explode. So, who goes boom?
I'm leaving that
choice up to you.
[LUCY]
Huh?!
Which one of them lives
and which one of them dies?
Choose quickly,
patience ain't my thing.
[LUCY gasps]
Hurry and get up, Natsu.
We really need you!
[CARLA]
I've never seen him this bad.
Stand back, I'll
try to heal him.
Do you think you
can help him?
Don't push yourself
too hard, child.
If you use too much power,
you'll be in the same condition.
I don't have time
to worry about that.
Not when Lucy is fighting
all by herself!
[WENDY grunts]
Please Miss, you have to help
me! I'm carrying a baby!
You came to protect me, right?
Then what are you waiting for?
[LUCY] Stop it! What's the point
here? You were only after him!
This is a lot more fun! Humans
are playthings, nothing more.
[LUCY]
You creep!
You can at least face
me fair and square!
There's ten seconds left.
Better make your choice.
Seriously?
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm a former council
member, you dolt!
My life is far more
important than hers!
Stop wasting time and choose!
[LUCY grunts]
Careful! Any sudden movements
will set off the Mine,
and if you explode before
making your choice,
then both of these saps
will go sky-high!
[laughs]
It's okay. It'll be okay. Don't
be scared. Mommy's here.
Whose life is more useful, huh?
It should be obvious which one
of us the world needs more,
so stop thinking about it and
save me from this psycho!
[LUCY whimpers]
[JACKAL]
Time's up.
Whose life are you
gonna pick, Fairy Tail?
Who leaves in
a body bag?
[NATSU]
We choose...
[JACKAL]
Huh?!
[NATSU]
...yours, punk!
[NATSU grunts]
--[NATSU yells]
--[JACKAL screams]
[JACKAL groaning]
[JACKAL groans]
Natsu!
We got here as fast
as we could, Lucy!
And without a
moment to spare!
[gasps]
[stammering]
Looks like the bombs
are out of commission!
[PREGNANT LADY sobs]
[HAPPY]
You're gonna be okay.
[PREGNANT LADY]
Oh thank you...
[CARLA] We'll take you somewhere
safe, all right?
[MICHELLO groans]
Thank goodness. What kept you?
I thought I was done for!
[MICHELLO groans]
[WENDY]
Uh!
[HAPPY, CARLA gasp]
[LUCY sighs]
[MICHELLO groans]
[NATSU] Take a nap, old man.
I don't wanna deal with you.
[JACKAL growls]
You've either got a death wish,
or have the worst
memory of all time.
Anyone that touches me turns
into a bomb! Remember?
Stay away from him, Natsu!
He uses some kind of dark
power that's even stronger
than magic! They're
called 'Curses'!
[NATSU]
S'that right?
We're not entirely sure
what they are yet,
but we've seen what they can do.
Whaddya know?
The fools can learn.
But it won't help you now.
He's about to put on another
fireworks display,
and you're in the front row.
I hope you enjoy watching him
being ripped to shreds!
I've already gotten
the hang of it.
Say what?
Natsu!
Be careful!
[JACKAL gasps]
[laughing]
Uh?
[CARLA, HAPPY laugh]
[WENDY, LUCY laugh]
[LUCY] Natsu continues
the fight with Jackal,
and holds his own against
the horrific curses.
But, as bad as things already
are, the true terror of Tartaros
and its Nine Demon Gates
has yet to be seen.
Meanwhile, the other members of
Fairy Tail spread across Fiore
to try to prevent any
further casualties.
As they do, they bear witness
to a truly shocking situation.
Next Time! Tartaros Chapter,
Prologue - Natsu vs. Jackal
This is a fight
for all humanity!