[NATSU grunts]
[IGNEEL] Make sure you get
a good look at that guy.
See that book?
That's the Book of E.N.D!
Steal that book.
Because you're the only
one who can, Natsu.
Now listen, you are not to
open or destroy that book
under any circumstances.
Just take it. You understand?
For payment, I will tell you
everything you wish to know.
I'm'onna take that book
o'yours. Ya hear?
[MARD GEER]
Hmph.
[NATSU]
I promised my dad I would.
[NATSU] Come on!
Let's finish this!
[IGNEEL roars]
[MARD GEER] I find that
cocky attitude of yours
to be rather annoying,
"Dragon spawn."
[MARD GEER] I only consider the
actual dragons worth my worry.
Not pathetic humans.
Fire Dragon... Talon!
Face the facts,
you're no dragon,
you're just full of hot air.
[NATSU yelps]
[NATSU screams]
Natsu!
It would appear that the
dragons are still alive.
Unfortunate.
Well, you finally
decided to speak.
Any final words?
I thought I would "bid
farewell" to my enemy.
Prepare to be slain.
[NATSU screaming]
[MARD GEER]
It's over.
Time to put an end to all this.
Curse of Thorns.
[NATSU grunts]
[gasps]
Uh... Ha!
Sting! Rogue!
We thought you might
like some backup.
Hey! I knew I smelled you two!
It's cool that you guys
wanna help out and all,
but I got it covered.
Yeah, but Minerva told us--
[NATSU]
Yeah.
How about we save that story
for another time, 'kay?
[sighs]
[NATSU] What happened
to Lector and Frosch?
[ROGUE]
They're with Erza.
I knew she was gonna be okay!
[ROGUE] They were on their
way to the control room
to stop the Faces.
Happy was going with them, too.
[NATSU] Glad to hear it.
But, I mean, I wasn't
worried about 'em.
They can handle anything.
Let's go!
We can beat him faster
if we work together.
[ROGUE] With all three of us,
he won't stand a chance!
I gotta admit, you
make a good point.
But I gotta pass!
[STING, ROGUE]
What?!
My Dad gave me this job,
and I'm gonna make
him proud of me.
And I'm gonna do it alone.
Look Natsu, we don't
have time for this.
[grunts]
All right, have it your way.
But what do you think
about this plan?
Let's race to see who can
beat him first: you or us!
Wha...?!
[growling]
There's no way I'll ever
lose to you! It's on!
And that's how you get
what you want from Natsu.
He is rather simple.
[NATSU yells]
[STING yells]
[ROGUE yells]
[NATSU grunts]
[STING yells]
[MARD GEER groans]
[MARD GEER] With two dragons
in the sky above,
and three dragon
"spawn" at my feet,
I'm led to believe that
there are even more.
Seeing you fly about my
castle, disturbing my peace,
I am reminded of a feeling...
One that I had
forgotten so long ago.
Anger.
[BOTH grunt]
[NATSU]
Good for you, bro.
Guess that means you're
on par with humans, now.
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[IGNEEL roars]
[IGNEEL] I've waited for this
moment for so long, Acnologia!
Years ago, you slaughtered
dozens of dragons
and to this day,
you show no remorse.
I will take great joy
in making you pay.
Don't you see I've
already paid my price?
All I care about
is destroying you.
One more direct line and
we'll be in the thick of it.
Look there!
[WENDY, DORANBOLT gasp]
[DORANBOLT] Neither of them
seems to be wavering at all.
We have to do our part,
are you feeling up to it?
Of course.
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[CARLA] I never thought we'd
have to face Acnologia again.
[DORANBOLT]
But who is that red dragon?
[CARLA]
I wish I knew.
We've never seen
him before, either.
It's quite a mystery.
Well, we'd better get moving.
The rest of the guild
needs our help right now.
Let's go.
[LUMMYS laughing]
[LUMMY]
Blah!
[LUMMY sighs]
I wish I knew
what was happening.
But whatever it is,
it can't be good.
I really hope Natsu and
the others are okay.
Well, standing around worrying
ain't gonna help 'em!
A real man would put himself
right in the middle
of the action!
[LUMMYS laughing]
[gasp, scream]
[ELFMAN]
Like this!
It's time to take
out the trash!
[LUMMYS scream]
[LISANNA]
Right there with ya.
Ha!
[LUMMYS scream]
You know, you
should fear me,
'cause I can take care
of business, too!
Man, I only wish Levy were here
to watch us get 'er done.
Time for High Speed!
[LUMMYS yelp]
Here's my Knuckle Plant!
[LUMMYS groaning]
[LUMMY A grunts]
[LUMMY B grunts]
[LUMMY C] So where are all
the hot boys hiding?
[LUMMY D]
Yeah! Hook us up!
[LUMMY E]
But keep it on the DL,
we don't want the
others to know.
[WARREN]
What are you, blind?!
There's a good lookin' guy
right in front of you!
What? Hottie at Twelve O' Clock?
I don't see him.
Is he hiding from me?
Where is he? I can't
see anyone at all.
Where have all
the good men gone?
I need a hero, who's hot.
I'm talkin' about me!
Ya know, the guy standin'
in front of you?
[LUMMYS]
Huh?
[ALL laughing]
Ow, my ego.
[LUCY]
Juvia. You gotta hang in there.
Okay?
I have to see him.
She is seriously in need
of major medical attention.
So is Laxus.
Well the good news is
we have what Porlyusica
needs to make that antidote.
We just have to get that demon
blood to her, and quickly.
Gajeel.
[GAJEEL]
Yeah?
[LUCY]
We need you to take that blood
and get Laxus and Juvia
out of here asap.
Are you crazy? I'm not
gonna go anywhere.
I'm a Dragon Slayer, and it's
my job to protect you guys.
So that's what I'm gonna do.
Yeah, but these two
need you more now.
Besides, I think Natsu
and the others
can handle Acnologia
until you get back.
[LEVY]
I can do it!
[LUCY]
Uh?
Gajeel should stay here.
Don't worry, I can carry Laxus.
And then you can take
Juvia, okay, Lu?
Wait, are you sure about that?
This is nothing...
I can do this all day!
[LUCY] Uh! Levy!
You're gonna hurt yourself!
[LEVY]
I'm... good.
He isn't heavy at all.
I... swear. Ah!
[LEVY gasps]
[LEVY]
Uh?
Okay, you made your point.
But, Gajeel.
[gasps]
I'll take Laxus. Why don't
you just worry about Juvia?
Now we've got to hurry if we're
gonna get 'em to Porlyusica
so she can make that antidote.
[inaudible]
[GAJEEL]
I gotta purpose.
To protect the ones who've
always had my back.
Isn't that right?
[GAJEEL] Hey Lucy, give
Salamander a message for me.
[LUCY]
Sure, what is it?
Tell him to "get
started on that song."
He'll know what you mean.
You got it!
We're almost outta time, Erza!
She sped up the
countdown and now
we've got less than 20 minutes!
[ERZA grunts, yells]
You gave it your all,
but it's time you face
the facts Titania.
You don't stand a chance
against this form.
Her power just increased!
She wasn't nearly
this strong before!
Where's it coming from?
[HAPPY] You can do this!
Hang in there!
[ERZA]
Come on.
She's strong, but
she's not immortal.
There must be some way
for me to defeat her!
[LUMMY laughing]
[ALL laughing]
[ELFMAN yells]
[LUMMYS laughing]
[LUMMYS scream]
[LISANNA]
Nice work!
[DROY]
Now... eat... this!
[JET]
High Speed!
[LUMMYS scream]
You guys are doin'
a really great job!
You're supposed to be
fighting with us, Warren!
[WARREN]
Do I need to remind you
that my magic isn't exactly
useful in these situations?
Get it together
and do something!
[WARREN]
I'm still feeling the rejection.
Seriously?!
[LUMMY groans]
[LISANNA grunts]
[LUMMY gasping]
[ELFMAN]
Real men always...
let ladies finish first!
My only regret...
is that the one who beat me
was not more attractive.
[sighs]
Well. Looks like that's
one headache gone.
[LISANNA]
I won't be missing those voices.
[LUCY]
Uh? What happened here?
You're all safe! Oh,
I'm so glad you're okay!
--[LISANNA] Hi Lucy!
--[WARREN] Man. She is so hot!
Dude, just so you know,
your thoughts are leaking.
It's a long story, but yeah.
Now I'm... alone.
[inaudible]
What's the matter?
It's nothing, really.
I'm all good.
[ELFMAN]
How is everybody else doing?
Gajeel and Levy are on their
way to give Porlyusica
the demon blood.
She says she can make a potion
to help heal the others.
[JUVIA]
Where is Gray?
We'll see him soon, I promise.
Do you know which way
to go from here?
Yeah. I think it's
down this path.
We just have to
follow the markers.
Hey. That's really weird,
how did this get here?
[LUCY]
I haven't seen Gray,
but I heard he gained
this crazy strong power.
And Natsu's, well...
I guess you could say
he's sorting through
stuff with his Dad.
[ALL gasp]
[LISANNA]
Wait a second.
Could that red dragon
really be who I think it is?
[LUCY] The one Natsu
never gave up looking for.
His father, Igneel.
[ELFMAN] So where's he
been all this time?
[LUCY]
That's the weird part.
But if this dragon's
Natsu's dad,
then he's gotta be
on our side, right?
That would definitely explain
why he's takin' on Acnologia!
Guess this means our luck might
finally be turning around.
We still have the Faces
to worry about.
Wendy?
Carla! And you brought
that one Council guy!
[JET, DROY, WARREN]
Whoa!
What in the world have
you done to your hair?!
Never mind that!
What we need to focus on is
how to stop all the Faces.
[ALL]
Wait, "all the faces"?
Unfortunately, thousands of
Faces have been activated.
And unless we find
a way to stop them,
magic will vanish from
our world forever.
If that happens, the curse
power that Tartaros uses
will become the ruling
force on this planet.
[ALL gasp]
How could you even lift him?
This guy's freaking heavy.
And he's gonna owe
me a song, too,
after all this
saving his life BS.
[LEVY] Yeah, I wanted
to ask you something,
what are these songs
you keep talking about?
It's kind of an
inside joke we have.
Salamander's gonna write
one about how great I am.
And this dude?
Don't get me started.
He may as well write an album
of all the songs he owes me.
Well, if that's how it works,
then maybe you should
get to work on a song
about the person
who saved your life.
[GAJEEL]
Huh?
Don't try to act like
you don't remember.
It's time to pay up!
[GAJEEL]
Mm...
[LEVY] I never wanted
to make you mad.
I was just playin' around.
I was tryin' to be funny.
[GAJEEL]
♪ Shoo-bee-doo-ba! ♪
♪ Sha-la-la! ♪
♪ I once fought a demon,
deep under the sea. ♪
♪ Things were looking rough, ♪
♪ but he was never
gonna beat me! ♪
♪ I wasn't scared. Although
he turned into a shark. ♪
♪ 'Cause I knew that his bite ♪
♪ would be nothin'
like his bark. ♪
♪ But suddenly. ♪
♪ I couldn't breathe. ♪
♪ This was the end. ♪
♪ Oh Shoo-be-do- bah! ♪
♪ Then I looked up,
and who did I see? ♪
♪ Da be do be. ♪
♪ Super Levy! The girl
who came to rescue me. ♪
♪ She swam... ♪
Please! Make it stop!
I was just kidding;
I don't need a song!
I think, with a little work,
that could be a real hit.
[pants] I think your taste
in music is rather unique.
Something bad's about to happen.
I can feel it in the air.
I need to hurry up and find
the others before it's too late.
Feelings tend to dull
the mind, you know.
So a long time ago,
I decided I must find
a way to control them.
The time is nigh,
Master E.N.D.
Be patient a bit longer.
[NATSU growls]
[MARD GEER] Anger is an
especially powerful emotion.
For it has the potential to
transform a person entirely.
One must wonder,
who exactly would this
"transformed" me be?
I admit it's quite a terrifying
thought to be sure.
For who am I anyway?
Who is Mard Geer?
The Underworld King,
and leader of the masterless
cursed ones that are Tartaros.
That is who I must remain.
So I'll banish these
emotions forever.
And while I'm at it, I'll
banish you from existence.
What?! He can't do that!
He's giving off this
weirdly strong power!
I think he's beginning to
take this fight seriously.
We should, too.
[ROGUE, STING, NATSU grunting]
Dammit!
[NATSU yells]
[NATSU gasps, yells]
[NATSU grunting]
No! Natsu!
[ROGUE, STING]
Huh?
[ROGUE, STING groan]
This guy's strong.
For real.
[NATSU yells]
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Sword Horn!
That's not going to cut it.
Now... Roar!
[NATSU]
Sting! Rogue!
Hey, is Natsu askin'
for our help?
That means even he thinks
he's tough to beat.
[ROGUE, STING]
Holy...
Shadow...
Dragon...
Flash Fang!
[MARD GEER] Light and dark
in perfect harmony.
Isn't that just lovely?
But It can't last.
Vanish...
There's no way!
Did he absorb it?
[NATSU] Now, Lightning Flame
Dragon Firing Hammer!
[MARD GEER]
Heh.
[NATSU gasps]
If that's the best
you can muster,
I think you should give up now.
Spare yourself the agony
that my Etherious form will
surely inflict upon your bodies.
[NATSU whimpers]
[ROGUE, STING whimper]
[ELFMAN]
I've got a plan.
It's a long shot,
but it just might work.
We'll get Warren to use
his telepathy powers
to tell everyone to do whatever
they can to stop the Faces.
I wish I could help,
but it won't work.
I'm sorry guys.
My telepathy magic can only go
five kilometers out at the most.
There's no way I can reach
everybody on the planet.
It's just not possible.
Oh, no.
Well, there's gotta be
something we can do.
They could detonate
at any moment now.
We have to hurry and
think of something fast.
What do you think we're doing?!
Stupid! Why are me and
my powers so pathetic?!
[MAKAROV]
Enough!
[ALL gasp]
[MAKAROV] Now is not
the time to give up.
Master Makarov!
[MAKAROV] We've still got one
last trick up our sleeves.
[MAKAROV] We can use Fairy
Tail's ultimate weapon:
The Lumen Histoire.
[LUCY] Mard Geer continues to
fight Natsu, Sting, and Rogue
without even breaking a sweat.
Then, The Underworld King
shares a terrifying revelation
about the demons of
the Books of Zeref.
But just when Natsu and the
others think all is lost,
Fairy Tail gets some
serious back up
from the Ice Demon Slayer...
Gray Fullbuster.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Absolute Demon."
It's time we conquer despair
and reach the truth!