[NATSU] It's been too long!
Let's get back to work!
Whadda we got here?
[HAPPY] Hey, how about
we give this one a try?
So, all we gotta do is
capture this jail-breaker guy
called Velveno?
And they'll pay us
four million jewel?!
Alright, now we're talkin'!
I'm broke, and a huge
cash injection is just what
the doctor ordered!
♪
[LUCY] What're we waiting for?
We haven't decided
if we're taking it yet!
Well, we sure could
use the money, too.
so I say let's do it!
This job seems
kinda familiar.
Didn't Gray almost take a job
catching an escaped convict
a little while ago?
This is the same one,
but back then the reward
was only four hundred
thousand jewel!
For some reason,
he's way more valuable
than he used to be.
I wonder who
the client is.
Uh...
Some guy called
Count Balsamico?
That's a pretty
sour name, huh?
He'll go great on your salads!
[MACAO] Count Balsamico?
Ya know, rumor has it
that Velveno is gonna make
an appearance at the huge
magical ball that the Balsamico
family is throwin' this year.
What the heck are
you talkin' about?
They throw a big, fancy
party every seven years.
It's very exclusive; you
gotta be a wizard to even
get through the door.
[WAKABA] The next one's
happenin' this Saturday.
Alright, then let's
crash this rich guy's party
this weekend and walk out
four million jewel richer!
Sounds like a plan!
I'm fired up!
This is gonna
be great!
Wait, I just thought
of something, you guys!
If we're gonna go to
this high class ball,
we're all gonna need to work
on our dance moves first,
dontcha think?
Our dance moves?
[HAPPY] The Magic Ball!
[LUCY] Let me show you some
of the basic steps first.
Come here and hold my hands.
[NATSU] Ugh.
This is so embarrassing.
I don't understand
this at all.
What are they
doing again?
It's called
ballroom dancing.
It's super weird.
What's it for?
Ow!!!
Uh-oh, sorry
about that!
So it's some kind
of foot stomping game?
No, it's more like
the opposite of that.
If you know how
to dance like this,
you can meet a stranger
at a ball and move your body
in perfect rhythm with theirs.
[KINANA and ROMEO]
That sounds cool!
Hey!
What are you two
doing over here,
playing some kinda
game or somethin'?
It's not a game, doofus!
Let me play
a round with ya!
[LUCY] You just
got disqualified!
[JUVIA] How dare he?
Using his seductive
dance moves to flirt
with other girls behind my back.
If you have to strip down
to dance with Gray,
I am more than willing!
[ERZA] Well...
you may not be aware,
but in certain circles,
I was once known as
the "dancing demon."
You were?
[ERZA] Requip!
Ready?
Let's dance!
Nah, I don't think
I'm quite ready yet.
Don't be so foolish!
All you need
is spirit!
[NATSU] I'm gonna hurl!
Well, I guess Erza
was telling everybody
the truth about
her nickname.
Anyone who can make you
that sick has to be
some kind of demon.
[LISANNA] I can
teach Natsu.
He'll be cutting a rug
like a pro in no time.
If ya don't mind, I'm gonna
take a break for just a--
[LISANNA] Now let your
shoulders relax a bit
but keep your back straight!
[NATSU] This is the worst thing
that's ever happened to me!
How can Natsu be
such a big sissy?
Come on kid, man up!
All right, Elfman.
May I have this dance?
A real man doesn't
get spun around like this!
Ballroom dancing
looks amazing.
I wanna try it, too!
[WARREN] May I
have this dance?
That sounds
delightful.
Oh wow.
Wendy really knows how
to dance, doesn't she?
I don't like her prancing
around with a man
twice her age.
Uh.
May I have this dance?
Fine, but just this once.
Maybe we should
try it out, too.
Yeah, it
could be fun.
My lady, would you
grant me the pleasure?
But of course, sir.
Awesome!
Think you can just
waltz up and dance
with whoever ya want?
You're just jealous!
And you're crazy
if you believe--
Real cool, dad.
Hey!
Yeah?
What is it?
Just so you know, I
ain't the dancin' type!
Well that's perfect, because
nobody's asking you!
[JET and DROY] Oh Levy,
will you dance with me?
Back off, man.
I asked her first!
Nuh-uh, I did!
I did!
No, I did!
Okay, fine.
If you insist.
Whaddaya talkin' about?
I never asked you.
[JET and DROY]
That's so not fair!
I know all about
the magic of dance!
Yeah, that's true, but this
is a little different.
[ERZA] Everyone out of the way!
[LUCY] Wow, this private lesson
turned into a full on
dance party.
Wait.
Am I seriously the only one here
that doesn't have a partner?
You raaang, my lady?
Nope, I sure didn't!
[LUCY] I had no idea you were
such an excellent dancer.
[CAPRICORN] To honor your
late mother, I swore an oath
to ensure that you were
brought up to be a lady worthy
of the Heartfilia name.
Yeah. okay.
but this seems a bit much.
Let's start the
daaance from the top.
Do try to get it
right this time.
[NARRATOR] This ostentatious
palace is the home of
Count Balsamico.
[ALL] We're here!
[LUCY] This definitely looks
like the kinda place
that would have a magical ball.
[GRAY] I didn't realize
it was so far away.
[ERZA] a small price to pay
for the chance to dance.
You do remember that
we came all this way to catch
an escaped convict, right?
Um, you're a little early.
[WARREN, telepathic scream]
Whoa, what a fox!
Was it really
necessary to scream
that inside
of my head?
[GRAY] We're here
to see the count.
[GIRL] Yes,
of course you are.
My name is Aceto and my
father is Count Balsamico.
[WARREN] She's too pretty
to have such an ugly name.
[ALL] Everybody
can hear you, ya idiot!
My name is Natsu
and we're with Fairy Tail.
We've come here
concerning the job request
that your father posted
in our guild hall.
In that case, I'll
take you right to him.
Please, follow me.
Welcome, and thank
you for taking my request.
I am indeed Count Balsamico!
This guy is hilarious!
He's got a sour name!
And a sour
face to match!
Don't screw this
up for me, okay?
[BALSAMICO] Let me get
straight to the matter.
I want you to know
there is more to the story
than what was
written on the flyer.
Please, go on.
I am exceedingly
concerned for the well being
of my precious daughter, who
means more than the world to me.
Then why'd you give
her such a silly name?
It's a lovely name!
I apologize and
please, continue Sir.
[BALSAMICO] The ball being held
this evening is very special,
for it is tonight that her
future husband shall be chosen.
Yeah, that is
a pretty major deal!
[BALSAMICO] Once every seven
years, our family brings out
an extremely precious ring.
A ring that has
been passed down through
the Balsamico family line
for countless generations!
And you're afraid that
Velveno is gonna come here
and try to steal it from you?
[BALSAMICO] I'm
absolutely certain of it,
since he tried and
failed seven years ago.
But he did ruin
the ceremony to choose
my daughter's husband.
I see, but given his
"unique" appearance.
Wouldn't sneaking in
undetected prove to be
a bit difficult for him?
He is very skilled in
both transformation magic
and "Magical Drain."
"Magical Drain"?
What the heck's that?
[BALSAMICO] It allows him
to temporarily copy the type
of magic used by anyone
he comes into contact with.
It's very dangerous indeed.
Aw man, I wanna use magic
like that sometime!
I entrust full safety
of the ring to you.
Work together and make sure
he fails to snatch it again.
And what's more, I want
you to capture him
and put him back behind bars
where he rightfully belongs!
We'll catch this
clown for ya.
Yes. We will, Sir.
Uh, just one more thing.
The flyer mentioned a
certain reward if we were
to catch him for you?
That's correct,
four million jewel in
cash for his capture.
Oh yeah!
Cash is king!
Let's do this!
All done, baby.
Thank you.
But what'll happen if I'm
so beautiful that someone
proposes to me instead?
[ERZA] Ready to
get to work, Lucy?
Holy fashion
statement,
you are definitely
not playing around!
Although we've come here
strictly for business purposes,
we have to look the part
of elegant partygoers.
[WENDY] So, uh, do I look okay?
Okay?
You look absolutely adorable.
Thank you.
I never dress up like this.
Now then!
The curtain is rising
on the magical ball,
so let's take our places
on the dance floor!
I haven't seen her this
worked up since we were
in that weird
play together.
Okay, I'll try not
to mess this up.
[WENDY] I wonder if I should
cast a Troia spell on Natsu
before we get started.
[ERZA, telepathicly] Warren,
any sign of our man Velveno?
I've got surveillance lacrimas
floating all over the palace.
But so far, there's
been no sign of him.
If we see anyone
that looks creepy,
you'll be the
first to know!
Remember, you're at a party,
so try to act naturally.
What happened to the boys?
[WENDY] They're over there!
Looks like the
girls finally got here.
S'pose that means we
gotta start minglin'
and actin' like we
belong at a ball.
I'm pumped!
Balls are super manly!
C'mon, don't be
nervous, old buddy!
[ERZA] It's so glamorous.
I have to wonder if
Velveno will show up here
like the count's predicting.
[LUCY] All we can do
is investigate people
we find suspicious,
without being rude.
Whoa, I think a
red-headed angel
just walked
though the door!
You came way too far
from heaven to be frowning
like that, beautiful!
Dance with me and smile!
I don't think I've ever
seen anyone that suspicious
in my entire life!
[WARREN, telepathically]
Tail him, guys!
[NATSU, telepathically] Roger!
[ERZA] Very well.
[LUCY] That
poor, poor man.
[LUCY] Saw
that one comin'.
Tail that guy?
[MALE GUEST A] Whoa!
You've sent me
into circles baby!
I can't even see straight!
I've heard of a--
[ERZA] You lack the spirit!
I think she's got it.
He might need
help, though.
May I have this dance?
[LUCY] Yeah, sure!
Look, now Lucy's got
some guy talking to her!
Very suspicious, no
one's that handsome!
You guys know
what to do, right?
Let's go
check on Lucy.
Sure thing.
Oh, how could
I say no
to such a
handsome man?
You don't have
to be lonely
on the dance
floor tonight!
[NATSU] Gray, we're
being attacked!
[GRAY] I'd rather
be lonely, trust me!
I'm the
last man standing.
Is it too
forward of me
to ask you
to dance?
Oooh!
Yeah, I'll dance!
I'll dance like
a real man!
We are gonna set
this place on fire!
The fact that she's not
running away in terror
makes her super
suspicious!
If that woman truly is
Velveno he may be trying to
use his Magical Draining spell
to steal Elfman's Beast Arm!
Now Elfman may be
in trouble, check it out!
[GRAY and NATSU]
Loud and clear!
Off ya go!
[FEMALE GUESTS A &amp; B]
You make me dizzy!
[WARREN] Elfman!
You gotta switch out
with Gray right now!
Not happenin'.
What?
The world may try to get
between you and your woman,
but that just makes
the passion burn brighter.
It's the fire that
makes a man a man!
[NATSU] That's enough!
It's time to
switch partners.
My, what an enchanting
gentleman you are.
It's actually kind
of funny you would
put it that way, cause this
is a magic user's ball.
So what kind of
magic do you use?
That is a rather
personal question
don't you think?
A true gentleman would
reveal his type of magic first
before asking a lady.
Ha, I guess the whole
'being a gentleman' thing
ain't really my strong suit.
I see, well I suppose
I'll play along
and show you mine first.
Maker magic.
Ice Make Swan!
So you just happen to
use the same kinda magic I do?
Now, Ice Make
Kite!
Very impressive,
but not my style.
Ice Make Polar bear!
Ice Make Prison Cell!
You really know how to show
a lady a good time.
Ice Make Bazooka!
If you think
that's fun, try this.
Ice Make Cannon!
Now, if you'll
excuse me!
I've never
met a woman
like you before!
The two of you need
to cool it immediately!
And much to nobody's surprise,
this thing goes
completely off the rails.
Look, Miss Aceto's
up on the balcony.
It would appear that all
the men here are intimidated
by my daughter's beauty.
The way you sparkle
is so manly!
I am a girl,
you know.
Now then.
Would you grant me the
honor of the first dance?
Of course.
Why in the heck is
the Count's daughter
dancing with Erza?
I don't know!
[YOUNG MALE GUEST]
Excuse me, Miss.
May I have this dance?
Yes, thank you.
That smarmy, little
rugrat's got some nerve.
Wendy is way too young
to be dancing with boys!
What are you,
her dad?
They won't
be dancing long,
it's getting close
to midnight.
[clock chimes]
Now what's
goin' on?
The fateful
hour is upon us.
[ERZA] And what
happens at midnight?
The ring is presented.
The bells within that giant,
old clock only toll on one
night every seven years.
When the doors open,
out comes the ring.
[BALSAMICO] Whoever takes
the ring is thereby granted
the right to propose
to my beautiful daughter.
It is a Balsamico
family tradition!
Anybody that takes
the ring can propose?
[alarm rings]
Do you boys
see that?
I'll go check it out!
I'm coming with you!
Hear, hear!
Anyone who desires my
daughter's hand in marriage
must first possess the ring!
[ELFMAN] I bet she won't
say no to a real man!
Did you forget that
we're not here to hook up
with the client's daughter?
It's the boy who was
dancing with Wendy!
Whoa, Are you okay?
Some guy with a huge afro
tied me up before
the ball started!
It was Velveno!
Then that must mean...
the boy who's dancing
with Wendy right now...
[WARREN, telepathically] Wendy!
Watch out, that's Velveno!
Transform off, now!
I'm me again!
[VELVENO] Sky Dragon, Roar!
[VELVENO] And now the
Balsamico family's
precious ring is in the hands
of the one and only Velveno!
He did it.
Why you
rotten thief!
Give it back
this instant!
[NATSU] Alright!
This party's finally
gettin' started!
I wanna play too!
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
What?
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Roar!
[VELVENO] Fire Dragon Roar!
Ha!
I took the liberty
of helping myself
to some of your magic too,
while we had our little dance.
Then I shall have
to deal with you!
Now Gray, Elfman!
You two protect Aceto!
We're on it.
We're men!
Requip!
Purgatory Armor!
Requip.
It's pointless!
I've already copied the magic of
every single Fairy Tail member
that came to this
little shindig!
Oh yeah, copycat?
Then we'll have to kick your
butt the old fashioned way.
And we're pretty
good at it, ya know!
Aw, knock it off!
The last thing I wanna do
tonight is get in a brawl
with you and your buddies.
[NATSU] Say what?
I'm here 'cause
I screwed up last time.
I've waited seven long
years to try it out again.
Aceto.
I've got something
big to ask you.
No way!
We've known each other
ever since we were both
just little kids.
And this entire time, I've
been crazy in love with you.
You were the low-born
child of one of my
servants, yet I still permitted
you to play with my daughter!
Have you forgotten
your place?
Every time I came to
see Aceto, you'd remind me.
You'd say we were
from two different worlds
that shouldn't mix.
And then, you'd kick me back
out into the street again.
'Cause trash like me
doesn't belong in your palace.
Daddy!
You never told me
he tried to visit.
And you don't need to hear
about any of this now!
The sad thing is,
I started to believe him
and decided I was finally
gonna give up on you, Aceto.
I kinda gave up on
myself too, I drifted around
for a while, and eventually
turned to a life o' crime.
I got arrested.
Ended up in jail.
I'm not buyin' any
of this guy's crap.
Wait.
And while I was locked up.
I had all the time in
the world to sit around
and think about the thing that
I regretted most in my life.
How I never got the
chance to tell you how I felt.
So I took a risk and broke out
to come to the ball.
I even did it twice!
Miss Aceto, please
tell me you'll be my wife.
How sweet.
What?
No.
Never mind.
[BALSAMICO] Can't you see
this is a waste of time?
Her answer is no!
I will.
[ALL] Whaa!
Wow, are you serious?
Of course.
I've been waiting my whole life
for the day you'd come back!
[VELVENO] You were?
This is like my wildest
dream come true.
I can hardly
believe it!
There's just
one thing.
Turn yourself in.
You still need to
pay for your crimes.
You're right.
Isn't it wonderful?
That was so
beautiful!
He's the
sweetest guy ever.
Incredible.
Yeah.
That was so freakin' manly!
I don't know
about all this.
A round of applause
for the couple.
Well, they're
haulin' me off.
I'll wait for you.
I promise.
Thanks.
And I promise that
I'll come back for you.
So, about the four
million reward.
Do you think I'd
give you any money
after everything
that happened tonight?
[ERZA] Now!
To celebrate Lady Aceto's
new-found happiness.
Let's all dance the night away!
[cheers]
I never thought things
would turn out this way.
Ooooh wow.
I hope that someday a
special guy will propose to me
as sweetly.
[NATSU] Lucy?
Listen.
I ate so much food,
you'll have to roll me home.
Oh.
That's really great.
It's so nice here.
Can we stay for just
a little while longer?
Wait, stop.
[LUCY] One, two, three.
One, two, three.
Ow, quit stepping on my feet!
[NATSU] The Troia
spell is wearing off!
[LUCY] No!
Not on my dress!
♪
[HAPPY] Geez, are you
ever gonna grow out
of your motion sickness?
It's so annoying.
[HAPPY] You should've
listened to me,
I told you this would happen.
This whole job is
about riding on a train!
I knew that you wouldn't
be able to handle it.
[NATSU] Just make the world
stop spinning for a minute,
and then you can lecture me.
[HAPPY] The world
isn't spinning, Natsu.
It's just your brains.
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next Time:
True Scoundrels -
The Butt Jiggle Gang!
[NATSU] This is horrible!
[HAPPY] Wait, what's the
matter with you now?
[NATSU] I think my butt
is spinning, too!