[LUCY]
Lucy here!
I've been doing jobs
for the Fairy Tail guild
for a while now, and each one's
been more intense than the next.
I need to step up my
game to tackle them.
And the best way to do that
is add some spells
to my repertoire.
So, that's what I'm doing!
And not just new spells.
All new Magic!
Sweet!
So, there a reason for
the sudden interest?
[LUCY] Well, I can wreck shop
with the best of them,
but take away my celestial
keys and I'm helpless.
If I were to learn
transformation magic,
I should be able to
handle myself no problem!
Not to mention it sounds
totally wicked awesome.
Aye, sir!
Wait.
What possible use could you
have for transformation magic?
I'm always lookin'
for ways to step up
my prankin' game!
[HAPPY]
They'll never know what hit 'em!
I should've figured as much.
[HAPPY]
Transform!
Transformation magic can
get pretty complicated.
But I'm sure you can master the
basic level quickly enough!
You really think so?
Sign us up!
Let's do this!
[MIRAJANE] For safety's sake,
we should practice with
a bit more open space.
Why don't we all head
somewhere outside?
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Transformation magic.
Something like that
would help us get back
into the spotlight.
We're not getting any younger.
If we follow them,
we could learn to transform
and be back in our
primes by sundown.
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Sounds like a plan.
Indeed. The idea has merit.
[ERZA] Maybe I should
learn to transform.
[WENDY] Hey, Evergreen!
Are you about to head out?
What's the job?
Oh, there isn't a job.
A new boutique just opened
in Magnolia to rave reviews,
and I intend to
shop 'til I drop.
[giggles] I've been wanting
to get a new outfit or two.
Maybe I should tag along.
Not a bad idea!
It's important for girls to stay
in tune with the latest fashion.
Fashion isn't just for girls!
Men can be stylish, too!
Hell yeah!
I was thinkin' of addin' some
pyrotechnics and a zoot suit
to my stage outfit!
I've made my decision!
[ALL]
Uh...
[MIRAJANE] And those
are the basic principles
of transformation magic.
Any questions?
[LUCY]
Uh... Way too many to ask.
[NATSU, HAPPY snoring]
Are you two serious
about learning this stuff,
or did you just wanna
annoy me for the day?
[MIRAJANE] Now, there are
some important things
to keep in mind
when transforming.
Nap time's over.
Uh, sorry.
[LUCY]
Don't you dare sleep again.
[NATSU]
I can't help it.
It's because this is
so freakin' boring.
[HAPPY]
Aye.
I wouldn't mind
a little less theory
and more practice,
ya know. Whaddya say?
I suppose it can't be helped.
All right then, we can give
transformation a shot.
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY]
Awesome!
[LUCY] You're like my
favorite teacher ever, Mira!
[MACAO, WAKABA]
It's about time.
We'll start with
something simple.
A basic form transformation.
Like so.
[NATSU, LUCY gasp]
Okay.
Something's off here, but I
can't put my paws on it.
[MIRAJANE] At the basic level,
your clothes stay the same.
[HAPPY]
Ah! That was it!
[LUCY]
And the next level?
Intermediate will
change your clothes!
[NATSU, LUCY]
Whoa!
[LUCY]
Awesome!
[NATSU]
Even her armor is perfect!
[HAPPY]
Yup! That's Erza, all right!
[giggles] Memorizing even
the smallest details
will help you sell the illusion.
Are you sure about that?
'Cause, I'm not exactly shakin'
in my sandals over here.
--[ERZA] Natsu.
--[NATSU] Huh?
I trust you and Gray have
been behaving yourselves
like I've asked you to?
[whimpers]
You even sound just like her!
Being true to the
character is key.
If you wanna be a master.
That's cool!
No kiddin'!
For a second, I thought Erza
had appeared out of thin air!
[MIRAJANE] And, if you make
it to the advanced level.
You can alter your physical
form completely, at will.
[NATSU, LUCY gasp]
[HAPPY]
You look delicious!
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Whoa!
[MIRAJANE] And, if you
get even more advanced.
[LUCY gasps]
She's flyin'!
You can change your abilities!
[NATSU, LUCY]
Huh?
She's foxier than before!
Even your fighting strength
can be altered this way.
Did you hear that?
If we learn transformation
magic, we're set!
No more lounging around
the guild losing our hair.
[LUCY] I had no idea there
was so much to this!
[NATSU]
I wanna try next!
[MIRAJANE giggles]
Sounds good.
Mira, could you turn
into a fish again?
I'd really like to see it.
I think kitty's gone psycho.
That was a little too
advanced for you to try
right off the bat.
So, let's start
with a beginner
transformation.
Come on, we're not newbies!
Skip the kid stuff and
show us the goodies.
Yeah, we can do it!
[ERZA]
Enough of your insolence!
[HAPPY, NATSU yelp]
I'll have to try that.
[MIRAJANE] We're starting
with the basics for safety.
I won't tell you again,
so don't forget.
I had a feeling
I'd rock this.
[WENDY]
You're so pretty!
You're not looking
shabby either, Wendy.
[WENDY]
You really think so?
I was worried it might
be a bit "flashy".
[EVERGREEN]
Not at all!
This is your chance to be bold.
Show off your looks!
Is this bold enough for you?
[WENDY]
Wow, Carla!
You know how to
dress to impress!
[EVERGREEN]
Agreed.
Yes, you've certainly found
some keepers, ladies!
They're so you!
No.
It isn't bold enough to
clearly state my devotion
to the warrior's way of fashion.
[GAJEEL]
Now this is cool!
[PANTHERLILY]
Perhaps too cool.
[GAJEEL, PANTHERLILY laugh]
[gasps]
[WENDY, CARLA, EVERGREEN]
Uh...
Are we dynamic, or what?
We're the heroes
this city deserves!
[ERZA]
Heroes?
[GAJEEL, PANTHERLILY]
Justice!
Like a couple of
children at play.
No matter their age,
men are always children,.
Excuse me, sir, but
what are those outfits?
You truly have a keen eye
for fashion, Miss Erza.
Legend has it...
Long ago, people donned
those suits and defeated evil
in this town as
mighty superheroes!
At least, that's
what the label said.
I see.
Costumes for dispensing
justice. I'm deeply moved.
Is she serious about this?
Yeah. Definitely.
[CARLA] Just look at her face.
There's no stopping her now.
Hero! That's it!
Sir. I'm in your capable hands.
Just leave everything
to me, darling.
Am I good or am I good?
[ERZA]
Mm!
[ERZA] It's as comfortable
as I'd hoped.
Perhaps even more so.
I had it tailored to your
exact measurements.
I feel as if I'm
brimming with power!
The only explanation is destiny.
That suit has been waiting
for you to put it on!
Yes, that must be it!
From now on, I am Fairy Woman,
Defender of Magnolia! Woosh!
[WENDY]
So, uh...
Do you think we should
do something about this?
[EVERGREEN]
About what? I saw nothing.
Yes, child, it was
nothing but a breeze,
and should be forgotten
as soon as possible.
Natsu and Happy will
try turning into Lucy.
Lucy, you'll try Natsu.
--[NATSU, LUCY] Sure thing!
--[HAPPY] Aye, sir!
[WAKABA] 'Kay, what are
we supposed to try?
[MACAO]
What are you, brain dead?
If we pull this off,
we could turn into our young,
handsome selves again!
[WAKABA]
Oh, right! I forgot about that.
[MACAO] And then, maybe my
ex-wife will finally
come back to me.
[WAKABA] Maybe my wife will
finally stop henpecking me
and see me for the
gorgeous hunk I truly am.
And I can have my
hairdo back again!
[MIRAJANE] Start by looking
deep into each other's eyes.
[LUCY]
Yes, ma'am!
[NATSU grunts]
[LUCY grunts]
[HAPPY grunts]
Good, now really try
to picture your partner
inside your mind.
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY]
Picture it!
[WAKABA, MACAO]
Handsome stud!
[WAKABA]
Pompadour!
Look even closer. That's it!
Try to take in all
your partner's details.
Oh. A pimple.
[LUCY]
Shut up!
[MIRAJANE] The fact that you
two are friends should help,
but it goes even faster when
the pair is extra close.
Like this?
[LUCY] Uh! That's...
not what she meant.
[MIRAJANE]
Focus on the person. Very good.
Now, imagine that you
have their face and body.
Then, focus your magic power
on the picture of
them in your head.
[WAKABA, MACAO grunt]
Now unleash all of it!
[NATSU, LUCY, HAPPY]
Transformation!
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Ah... Aw.
Nothing happened.
It's fine!
You shouldn't expect
it to work right away.
You just started.
[NATSU cackles]
Man! What a lame-o!
[HAPPY laughs]
And you call yourself a wizard?
Hey, shut it, cat! It's not
like you did any better!
Yeah.
But I've already
figured out how to do it.
So did I!
[LUCY]
Huh?
[MACAO]
I'm still me. Damn.
[WAKABA] I guess everyone
overshadows us for a reason.
[MIRAJANE]
Okay, we've had our trial run.
Now let's give this next
try all you've got!
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY]
Yeah!
I won't give up when
my wife and good looks
are both within reach!
The power of the hunk
is calling my name!
[MACAO, WAKABA grunting]
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY]
Transformation!
[MACAO, WAKABA]
[LUCY, NATSU]
Huh?
Aye!
[NATSU]
Aw! Look, it's a Lucy cat!
You've passed the
beginner's level!
[LUCY]
This is creepin' me out a bit.
[NATSU grunts]
Okay, my turn!
Ha!
[NATSU laughs]
What the hell, dude?
If you're gonna do that then
change your clothes, too!
[MIRAJANE] Great work,
Natsu! Let's move on.
Man we suck.
Yeah.
[whines] I was the one who
wanted to learn to transform,
not those two clowns.
And would you put those away?
We're in public!
[MACAO sighs]
[MACAO]
Enno, my love.
Dammit. If I could only
learn to transform.
[sighs] Man, it'd be
nice to be in my prime.
[MACAO]
Screw it. One more try.
[WAKABA]
It's worth a shot.
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Transformation!
[MACAO]
Nope. It's useless.
[WAKABA] I guess you can't
get back what you've lost.
[WAKABA groans]
[MACAO grunts]
The hell? I'm burning up.
And my head is pounding!
I feel like I'm about
to split in half!
What's happening to me?
[MACAO yells]
[WAKABA grunting]
[yells]
[GIRL 222A sobbing]
I was playing
with my balloon,
but the wind took it away from
me and now it's too high
--for me to reach it!
--That's just terrible!
There must be
something we can do!
Are you kidding?
No one could reach
that kind of height!
[ERZA]
Ah! Ha-ha-ha!
Stealing from innocent children
is something I cannot abide,
you villainous tree!
[GIRL 222A]
Huh?
This is a job for Fairy Woman!
Woosh!
[gasps]
Take your balloon and know
that justice was served.
--[CROWD gasps]
--[GIRL 222A] You killed it!
Your thanks aren't
necessary, little one.
For I am a superhero.
Miss?
I lost the ring inside the
house, not in the garden.
This is a job for Fairy Woman!
I can't believe I forgot
about the bingo tournament.
Thanks for the lift, Missy.
This is a job for Fairy Woman!
--[MAN 222B] Yeah!
--[ERZA] Yes! Justice prevails!
Evil rears it's head.
I will be there to whack it!
[ERZA]
Hm!
I don't get it.
I've performed numerous good
deeds today, and yet...
It doesn't feel like I've dealt
a blow to the forces of evil.
What does it mean to be
a superhero, anyway?
Do they exist
because evil exists?
Or is there more to it?
[CROWD screams]
[ERZA]
The city cries out.
And Fairy Woman
will answer the call!
[screams]
[MONSTER cackles]
Now I understand what all
the commotion was about.
It smells familiar.
I know that mustache!
It's Macao!
You're wrong!
The Macao you once
knew is gone forever!
You can call me, Mr. Purple!
[LUCY]
What the heck is going on?
[NATSU] Don't know.
Was it somethin' he ate?
[HAPPY]
That's a serious food allergy.
[MR. PURPLE roars] I'm bursting
with so much youth and vigor.
I'm ready to blow!
[LUCY]
Whoa!
Watch it, pal,
you coulda hurt someone!
He's out of control.
What happened to him?
Isn't it obvious? He turned
into a big purple jerk.
[MIRAJANE]
That smoke...
[LUCY]
What do we do now?
[VILLAIN cackles]
Wait. Wakaba? Is that you?
Nope. Sorry, sweet-cheeks.
See, that wrinkled old has-been
you once turned down
for a date was tossed aside
like yesterday's stogie.
I've been reborn
as a hunky punk,
but you can call me
"The Smoker."
Right.
You could poke someone's
eye out with that hairdo!
[SMOKER] I'm finally
the in-your-face rebel
and handsome devil
I was always meant to be.
You're lookin' at
the studliest villains
in all Fiore,
so show some respect!
Not good.
They've both gone
completely mental.
[MR. PURPLE yells]
[SMOKER cackles]
Hey, knock it off! Are ya
tryin' to destroy the city?
What's with the bad attitudes?
I think Magnolia's on the
wrong end of a mid-life crisis!
Ah! I hear a voice deep inside
commanding me to brutally
destroy everything in my path!
That makes two of us.
I've never been one
to ignore my instincts,
especially when I get to
wreck everything in sight.
How in the world
did this happen?
I... think it's
transformation magic.
If that's the case.
Then the transformation magic
caused their constant stress
to take on physical
form. Maybe...
[HAPPY]
She doesn't know? Wait!
Now that I think about it.
They were upset about
being overshadowed lately.
Not to mention feeling insecure
over losing their hair
and wishing they
were more attractive!
[MIRAJANE]
That's horrible!
Whatever the case,
we have to stop them
before Magnolia's
nothing but rubble!
You're so dramatic.
At the very least,
our guild's rep will go
back down the crapper.
And we can't let that happen.
Besides, this'll give
us a chance to try
our new abilities in action.
Way to use your noggin!
[LUCY] I don't think this is
the time for playing around.
[MIRAJANE]
Remember! Picture and release!
Got it.
Ready when you are.
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Transformation!
[NATSU]
Huh?!
[HAPPY]
I don't think it worked!
What do you have to picture
to turn into construction paper
and a bamboo shoot?
How should we know?
We thought of it.
[ERZA] Ah! Ha-ha-ha!
This is a job for Fairy Woman!
[LUCY]
Erza?
Sorry, I've never heard
of Erza Scarlet.
I am Fairy Woman!
O... kay. We're screwed.
Even Erza's gone coo-coo.
Didn't you hear?
She's Fairy Woman, not Erza.
[HAPPY]
I don't think it matters.
[ERZA]
Fairy... Kick!
[MR. PURPLE groans]
Now, Fairy Punch!
The era of plain ol'
superheroes is over!
Dark and serious super villains
are what's hot, sweetheart.
Get with the times.
Dark and serious?
You scum!
Sorry, Fairy Woman,
but this turf is ours.
And you're not welcome!
Despicable cretins!
[SMOKER]
Well, yeah. We're bad guys!
Be careful!
Don't worry. I'll help ya!
[HAPPY]
Me too!
[LUCY]
Ugh.
The three of you
stay out of this!
I'm about to teach these
scoundrels a lesson
with my fairy fists of justice!
[MR. PURPLE]
Ha! Yeah, that'll be the day.
[SMOKER]
After we're through with you,
superheroes will be
a faded memory!
[GAJEEL]
Hold it!
[MR. PURPLE, SMOKER]
Huh?
[PANTHERLILY] No one cares
about superheroes anymore!
It's all about
the dark hero now!
[GAJEEL] I am the iron flower
that blooms in Magnolia.
The dark hero of
black steel. Fairy Man!
I have no weaknesses.
'Cept trains.
[PANTHERLILY] And I am
his trusted sidekick.
The ultimate warrior,
and seeker of justice.
You can call me Fairy Boy.
The stronger my foe,
the harder they'll crumble.
Who're these chumps?
[HAPPY]
A mysterious duo appears!
Are they friend or foe?
It's obviously
Gajeel and Lily, right?
Let them find out on
their own. It'll be fun.
Hey, Fairy Woman!
Leave these jerks to us!
Prepare for justice! Evildoers!
Do you idiots have no honor?
[GAJEEL, PANTHERLILY]
Wha?
How dare you steal my
climactic scene! Imbeciles!
[MR. PURPLE, SMOKER yelp]
This is the end!
Try to embrace your
fate with dignity!
Fairy... Fleuve!
[MR. PURPLE, SMOKER groan]
That's mine, Erza! Hold on,
when did she take it?
Erza's fighting without
using any Requips.
She must be totally
immersed in her role.
[HAPPY]
But she stole her role. Copycat!
I'm not copying,
but paying homage
in the most
respectful way possible!
We've come to the
part where I pull off
a spectacular finish.
I think I'll start with you:
"Old Smokey."
It's "The Smoker"!
It doesn't matter
who you are! Fairy Wind!
My smoke! My pompadour!
[LUCY, HAPPY, MIRAJANE]
Wakaba!
You'll pay for this,
Fairy Woman!
You are the one who will
pay for this, Mystery Pool!
My name is "Mister Purple"!
Get it right!
[yells]
[MACAO groans]
Looks like she did it.
I never doubted
her for a minute!
What gives?
We finally turned
back to normal!
Talk about lame.
I didn't even get to throw
a single punch at 'em.
Transformation magic's tougher
than you thought, huh?
[ERZA] Are you okay?
Was anyone injured?
[LUCY] We're good,
thanks to you, Erza!
[ERZA]
I am not Erza. I'm Fairy Woman!
[LUCY whimpers]
I'm scared.
That's unexpected.
What the--?!
[ERZA]
What's wrong with your faces?
You've gotta be kiddin'!
We should be asking you that!
Huh?
[HAPPY]
She's turned realistic!
[LUCY]
A few days later.
If I ever try that
crap again, shoot me.
I guess we'll just hafta
do our best as we are now.
The real question is "when will
I change back to normal"?
[HAPPY]
Hey, look!
Apparently Erza--
I mean, Fairy Woman--
saved Magnolia again today.
[laughs]
She did? Huh.
[HAPPY] Natsu, why are you
sitting in bed like that?
[NATSU] I found this
weird egg, so I'm warming it
to see what'll happen.
[HAPPY]
Whoa! Cool!
Do you think it's
gonna hatch soon?
[NATSU]
I'm not sure yet!
But, if it does, you'll have
a little brother to play with!
[HAPPY] Are you for real?
I'm so excited!
[NATSU]
We'll need a name, though.
[HAPPY] Right. If he's
my little brother, then...
[NATSU]
Happy Mark II!
[HAPPY]
Absolutely not!
[HAPPY, NATSU]
Next time: It's Kemo-Kemo!
[NATSU]
Okay, how 'bout this?
If Mark II is no good,
then Happy 2!
[HAPPY]
No! That's basically the same!