It's likely... you've not
heard of Fairy Heart.
For many years,
it's been our guild's most
closely guarded secret.
For good reason.
Because the world must never
learn exactly what it holds.
However, I believe it's
crucial that you know
why Zeref would go to
such lengths to get it.
And also, about my own sin.
It's time for my long-held
secrets to be revealed.
[MAVIS] This is a tale
of a boy and girl.
Of the awful curse they shared,
and the primordial magic...
that they sought together.
[MAVIS] My story takes
place over 100 years ago.
Not long before Fairy
Tail was founded.
We crossed paths in a
forest west of Magnolia,
where both our fates
were forever changed.
He was stricken by
the Curse of Ankhselam.
Against his will,
this horrible curse
killed every living
thing around him.
[MAVIS] I found him to be
completely fascinating.
He taught me so much
about the world of magic.
At the time,
Magnolia was controlled
by a dark guild
called Blue Skull.
They treated the citizens
with such cruelty.
So my friends and I learned
magic to win the city's freedom.
Just when things were at
their most desperate,
I cast an unperfected
black magic spell
that brought us victory.
Because I wasn't ready
to wield that spell,
there was an unintended
consequence.
My body would cease growing.
[MAVIS] A short time after,
in April of 686,
we founded Fairy Tail.
Trade disputes between feudal
lords had been escalating
at an alarming pace.
And later that year,
the bloody Second Trade War
began tearing the kingdom apart.
[explosions]
[MAVIS]
Hmm.
Have the left flank
pull back, please.
[SOLDIER A]
Uh. What?
Little girl, are you insane?
They're within striking distance
of the enemy's weakest point!
[SOLDIER A]
Now is the time to attack!
[SOLDIER B]
Look, you may be a wizard,
but you are out of your league
here on the battlefield!
[MAVIS]
If I were the enemy,
I would set up a small
ambush squad near this hill,
then lure in the opposition
and loose that squad upon them.
At the same time,
I'd send reinforcements west
to attack our main
battalion here.
[BOTH]
Huh?
I can formulate 49 effective
countermeasures at the moment,
but first, we need to pull
back that left flank.
They'll join the battalion
in an echelon formation,
and then we all watch for
the enemy's next maneuver.
Look at the princess
bossin' 'em around.
I'd argue she's more like
a general than a princess.
Seriously. You'd never guess
she was a military genius.
Are you ready?
[MAVIS]
This is Yuri Dreyar.
Master Makarov's father-to-be.
Precht Gaebolg.
My pick to be the
guild's second master.
But after he goes down
a path of black magic,
he becomes the leader
of Grimoire Heart.
And this is Warrod Sequen.
He'll one day be recognized
as the fourth-highest
ranked Wizard Saint.
So, is our wizard squad
gonna get the chance
to join in the action?
I'll need you to keep the
enemy's wizard squads at bay.
And it's very likely they'll be
getting back up from the west.
Be careful.
Let's go tear it up, you guys!
Ready to show 'em
what we can do?
[FAIRY TAIL yelling]
I have faith in you!
[SOLDIER A]
Hold on a second.
Is that Fairy Tail's
munchkin master?
[SOLDIER B]
I think she's a real fairy.
[thunder booms]
[WIZARD A]
Hm? Is there a storm coming?
[WIZARD B]
What the--?
[WIZARD C]
An enemy wizard!
[WIZARD D]
What guild is he from?
Fairy Tail says hello.
[SOLDIER A]
Whoa!
[SOLDIER B]
That's incredible!
Boom! And with that,
my score goes up to 27!
Still behind me, Yuri!
I've already taken out
34 and counting!
I'm at 100 and something!
Ha! I'm just kiddin'
with ya, fellas!
[SOLDIER A]
They came in way outnumbered,
but somehow, still
managed to win easily.
[SOLDIER B]
That girl is a fairy tactician.
[MEMBER B]
Woo! We did it, you guys!
[MEMBER C]
Look at all this gold!
[MEMBER D]
Now this calls for good wine!
[MEMBER A, WARROD]
Cheers!
[FAIRY TAIL]
You look kinda glum.
Something wrong?
[MAVIS] I was thinking
about the battle today.
It's mind boggling how many
lives must've been lost.
[gasps]
This war is brutal.
How long do you suppose
until it's all over?
I just wanna go on
another adventure.
[MAVIS] The Second Trade War
finally came to an end
in the year 690.
While the cease-fire was
a welcome development,
the resulting casualties
were over ten times
that of the First Trade War.
Most people believed
the high rate of mortality
was due to the wizard guilds'
involvement in the fighting.
As a result, the wizarding
world came together
and the Inter-Guild Conflict
Ban Treaty was signed.
This monumental agreement
brought about a brief period
of peace in the land.
[MAVIS]
A few years later, in 696...
[gasps]
[MAVIS] ...I had another
chance encounter with him
while walking
through the forest.
[ZEREF]
Hm?
Is that you, Mavis?
Oh my gosh! It's so
good to see you again!
Yay!
[ZEREF]
Wait! Stay back!
You shouldn't get close to me!
I-I'm cursed, remember?
[MAVIS]
I know!
What are you--?
I wanna thank you.
We were able to drive that
dark guild out of Magnolia.
And it's all because
of your help!
We saved the town with
what you taught us.
[MAVIS]
Hold on a minute!
You're actually the Black
Wizard Zeref? For real?
[ZEREF] That's why I
didn't want to tell you
my name back then.
[MAVIS] I've heard that you've
been alive for over 300 years.
Is that true?
It is.
Wow. I rarely think about
how long it's been.
I must say,
you're nothing like the
rumors paint you out to be.
Well, what do
they say about me?
The bad stuff's likely
true for the most part.
Why would you say
something like that?
I mean, your eyes have such a
kind and gentle quality to them.
I refuse to believe there's
a bad person in there.
You only say that
because you're so innocent.
[MAVIS gasps]
[MAVIS]
Do you remember Yuri?
That hot-blooded friend of mine?
Well, he and his wife are about
to have their first child.
[ZEREF] But he's practically
still a child himself.
[MAVIS] You do realize
it has been ten years
since you've seen him.
[chuckles]
I suppose I had forgotten,
considering how little
you've changed since then.
Oh, because I still
look the same.
You're right. I guess
that is confusing.
I should tell you
that to win the battle,
I cast an incomplete
black magic spell.
But it was the only way
I could save my friends,
so it was worth it in the end.
Don't tell me you
used the Law spell!
[gasps]
Whoa! What's this
about all the sudden?
[MAVIS whimpering]
[MAVIS gasps]
Uh, hey.
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
Hm?
Something wrong?
[ZEREF] You haven't just
stopped growing, Mavis.
[MAVIS gasps]
[ZEREF]
You've become like me.
You won't ever grow old or die!
[MAVIS]
What?
You made a judgement
on who lives and dies.
That's the purpose of the spell.
Now you have the
Curse of Ankhselam,
which means, the more value
that you place on life...
...the more death
will follow you.
[MAVIS]
That's not true!
'Cause... that hasn't happened.
Nobody just dies around
me, so it can't be.
I don't have that curse.
Perhaps that's the case
for the time being.
But think about this.
That war that went on
must've affected you.
War tends to dull
a person's feelings
concerning life and death.
I can imagine that your
thoughts on all of it
are still in a state of flux.
There's no way!
Because I...
I hate to say it,
but I'm afraid that
you've yet to realize
the true value of life.
[gasps]
[ZEREF] And the moment you
discover what that is,
the people closest to
you will start to die.
[gasps]
I don't get it.
Why are you saying
such things? It's cruel.
It would be much more
cruel to lie to you.
It's awful.
Don't you have feelings?
You said you didn't believe
the rumors about me,
but I'd wager you've
changed your mind.
[ZEREF] Well, it seems like you
might have it in you after all.
You may be able to walk
this path alongside me.
[MAVIS] He's a liar!
How dare he say that to me!
I do know the value of life!
It's more important
than anything!
[BABY crying]
[WARROD] Congrats, Yuri!
You're a father now!
[YURI]
Whoa!
[MAVIS]
What he said isn't true!
[MAVIS] In March of 696, Yuri's
only son, Makarov, was born.
Aww.
A healthy baby boy.
I'm so proud of you, Rita.
I love you!
Wow!
Cute!
You know, she didn't
have to deliver him
inside the guild hall.
What could I say?
Rita insisted on it.
There's love here.
I want my child to feel that
from everyone in the guild.
It's the most important
thing there is.
[YURI]
You're right about that.
Master Mavis, if you don't mind,
could you do the honor
of naming him for us?
[MAVIS]
What? Wait, you mean me?
That would be a priceless gift.
I think that you should
name the boy "Pippoko."
For the baby's sake,
I don't think you should
leave it up to us.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
Makarov.
I read a story about
a kind-hearted king,
and that was his name.
[RITA]
Makarov, huh?
It's nice. I like it.
Hey, Makarov!
Yeah. Okay.
It's awesome!
The kind-hearted boy, Makarov.
He's the first of
the next generation.
He's the future.
He is!
The bond we share is special.
Promise me... that we'll...
[gasps]
Rita?
Rita! Hey!
What's wrong?
[WARROD] Having the baby must've
taken too much out of her!
[ZEREF]
I hate to say it,
but I'm afraid that
you've yet to realize
the true value of life.
And the moment you
discover what that is...
[YURI]
My god! Rita!
Please, stay with me! Rita!
[ZEREF] The people closest
to you will start to die.
[MAVIS gasping]
[screaming]
[PRECHT]
Mavis!
Please, no. Stop this!
[wailing]
[MAVIS] Such is the
Curse of Contradiction.
The more love you have,
the more death surrounds you.
If you love no one...
...no one dies.
It's a powerful curse,
one that withers trees
and kills animals.
And of course, takes
the lives of people.
[MAVIS]
After that fateful day,
I never returned to
the guild hall again.
I aimlessly wandered the land,
leaving countless
corpses in my wake.
[MAVIS] And then, after
a year had passed...
There you are, Mavis.
I've searched for you.
Oh, it's you.
[ZEREF]
You're not looking too good.
[MAVIS] I haven't had
anything to eat or drink
in over half a year.
But here I am.
I want it all to be over.
That's one of the things
about the Curse of Ankhselam.
You could go so far as
to cut off your own head
and you still wouldn't die.
[MAVIS]
Please, Zeref,
I need your help!
I'm begging you to kill me.
Sorry, but what you're
asking is impossible.
There's nothing in the world
that can kill either one of us.
At first, I felt
exactly as you do now.
Honestly, I still think
about what a relief
death would bring all the time.
But regardless, you
need to try and change
your perspective on the matter.
We both have an eternity
here to do other things.
As for me, I've created
a new kind of beast
I call "Etherious."
My hope is that one day,
their inhuman strength
can end my life of suffering.
But of course,
it hasn't worked yet.
And I've spent some
time building a country.
[MAVIS]
A country?
It's a small place on the
western continent now,
but we're growing rapidly
because people will
do things for me.
It's a fun little challenge.
In fact, I'm known as
Emperor Spriggan over there.
I view my subjects
as mere pawns.
Don't judge.
It's safer that way.
With that attitude,
the Curse of Ankhselam
won't affect them at all.
It's like an intricate
simulation game.
What are you trying to do?
I guess I'm getting
ready for something.
A war?
But don't get the wrong
idea. I detest conflict.
In fact, I think it's
absolutely revolting.
Me building this empire is
just a way to pass the time,
but it disgusts me.
I wouldn't call it "fun."
Huh?
But you just said it
was a "fun challenge."
Did I? I don't remember.
[MAVIS] Are all his thoughts
contradictions too?
My entire life is wrapped
up in this game now.
I only live so I can die.
Or... to get my little
brother back... maybe...
...just so I can kill him.
Or... is it so my little
brother can kill me?
All this... it makes my head
feel like it's on fire.
[MAVIS]
Zeref.
[ZEREF]
The world... hates me.
It continually rejects me.
Everything hurts.
I won't reject you, Zeref.
I accept who you are.
[ZEREF gasps]
[MAVIS]
I may be the only one,
but I understand how you feel.
You can't give up.
I know we'll find a way to
lift the curse someday.
Together. Just you and I.
Do you mean that?
[MAVIS]
Yes!
[ZEREF]
Oh, Mavis.
This is the first time
anyone's ever been
truly kind to me.
[MAVIS]
Come on.
[ZEREF]
Huh?
You've probably forgotten
what it's like, that's all.
I know that I've never felt
this way about anybody before.
[MAVIS] The Abyss of Sorcery,
where everything begins.
[MAVIS] It contains the
primordial essence of magic:
Love.
Love brings about miracles.
And oftentimes, tragedies.
The two who carried the Curse of
Contradiction shared their love,
and the result was yet
another contradiction.
[MAVIS] The more love you have,
the more life this curse takes.
[MAVIS]
Such a bitter contradiction
is what took my immortal life.
[LUCY] Mavis and Zeref
created their own miracle.
It would evolve into
an incredibly powerful
form of magic that must
remain hidden to the world.
The family she built is
determined to cheer her up.
To help her let go of
the shame she feels,
we share our love with her.
Meanwhile, across
the deep blue ocean,
the Alvarez Empire
continues with their plan,
steadily preparing for
an assault on Ishgar.
Next time: "Fairy Heart."
The deep bond we
have with each other
is our constant
source of strength.