[LUFFY sighs]
[NARRATOR] Earthland has
been afflicted by a series
of strange phenomena.
These mysterious disruptions
to the natural flow of life
have done great harm not
only to the creatures
of Earthland, but
also to its people.
A region once
gorgeous and lush
with greenery now suffers
from unrelenting drought.
A once beautiful beach,
known for sunlit skies
and temperate weather,
lies blanketed in dark clouds.
A scorching desert that
once stretched as far
as the eye could see has
transformed into tundra.
[BIRDS screeching]
[NARRATOR] Disoriented by
these anomalies, a vast number
of creatures have
begun to migrate.
All have felt these
changes. However,
as of now, there is not a
single person in this world
who comprehends
their true significance.
[All gasp]
[LUCY]
The whole place is cleared out!
[HAPPY]
Weird, where'd everyone go?
[NATSU]
It's like a graveyard in here.
[HAPPY]
Signal of Rebellion
Is everybody else
out workin', or what?
Yeah. Between this weather
and the natural disasters,
folks have been
hurting out there.
[KINANA] So naturally,
the guild's been just about
buried in job requests.
Hey, I'm great at
disasters, let me at 'em!
Giddy up, man, I wanna
check out that request board!
This is perfect!
My celestial spirits
were pretty much
born to put nature in its
place. They'll rock this!
Just point me to a
town that's overheated
and I'll have Aquarius flood
the place with cool water!
There was a place like that,
but Juvia and Gray
beat you there.
[GRAY] This place is hotter
than I thought it'd be.
[JUVIA] We only just got
here and it feels like
I'm being cooked alive.
[GRAY]
Well, let's get to it.
I'll follow your lead,
darling. Go ahead.
Ice Make Geyser!
Water Slicer!
[FEMALE VILLAGER 205A]
It's so refreshing!
[MALE VILLAGER 205A]
I should've brought my coat!
[MALE VILLAGER 205B]
Finally, I can get...
[GRAY] Well, That should
last 'em for a while.
I'm cold now, warm
me with your body!
Gah, keep your
grabby hands off me!
[LUCY] Hm...
Okay, is there anywhere around
that needs to have repairs done?
'Cause I bet Taurus
could rebuild
a whole town singlehandedly!
Yeah there was, but Erza
has it covered by now.
[FOREMAN 205A]
Come on men, get a move on!
Work like you give a damn!
[FOREMAN 205A] And if you
need some inspiration,
take a good look at her.
[ERZA yells]
Dig for glory!
She's my hero!
[WORKERS]
Yeah, mine too!
[ERZA]
My work here is done.
I'll assist the others now.
I'm in your debt for
exposing me to such
an excellent workout routine.
[LUCY laughs]
Let's see here.
Oh yeah, Wendy and Carla
are off helping a ship
that got stuck in the
open sea for lack of wind.
[MIRAJANE] Laxus and
the Thunder Legion went
to protect this city with
a broken lightning rod.
[CROWD cheers]
[LUCY sighs] So are Elfman and
Lisanna helping out as well?
They're dealing with a
farmland pest problem.
My brother's probably
scaring the spots off
some leopard boars as we speak.
[LUCY] Gotcha. Wait,
is Nab out there too?
[KINANA] He read some
scary books and now
he's afraid to leave his room.
Sounds like him.
But, just about everybody
else was able to find
something that suited
their abilities.
That wall was covered in flyers.
But at this point,
the pickings are slim.
[HAPPY] Seriously. The only
ones left are all gross or lame!
[NATSU] Lawn work, book sorting.
Tricks at a birthday party?
Who do they think I am?
[LUCY] Don't knock those
till you see this side.
This is your fault Lucy.
If you hadn't spent half the day
in the bathtub, we'd be
wrapping up by now!
I have a morning routine.
You might not care how
you look or smell, but I do.
Don't you worry! I saw
a job that had "Lucy"
written all over it,
so I snagged it for ya.
[LUCY]
Did you really?
[HAPPY]
You're our savior, thank you!
[MIRAJANE]
Oh, stop it.
[KINANA]
Take a look!
There's a little coastal
village called Seabellus
that needs help with research.
There's a pretty
hefty reward, too.
[NATSU] Sounds legit.
Let's get a move on!
If we make it back before Gray
does, we can call him a slacker!
Aye!
Job after job.
You never see it coming.
[HAPPY]
Does it help to lay like that?
[NATSU]
I gotta get off this thing.
Just throw me out
the window. I'll walk.
[LUCY] Walking isn't an option.
It'd take us days to get there.
[HAPPY]
Wow, he turned a new color!
[NATSU groans]
How long till the pain ends?
[LUCY]
Around two hours or so.
[NATSU groans]
[HAPPY] This job is
perfect for ya Lucy,
I mean no one else
from Fairy Tail can do it.
[LUCY]
Mm-hm! celestial wizard wanted.
Assistance is required
investigating a disturbance
amongst the celestial spheres.
This is a possible cause
of recent changes seen
in the climate
throughout Earthland.
Maybe you can fix the weather!
Celestial wizards
really are super hard
to come by these days!
This job and I are a match
made in the heavens,
my feline friend.
[HAPPY] If your head
keeps growing it'll pop.
[LUCY] So I was thinking,
if the client can afford to do
this kind of research,
I'll bet they're like a scholar
with a royal grant or
a government agency.
[HAPPY] The flyer
doesn't say who they are.
But, I guess we'll find
out when we get there.
So, uh...
This is it. Or it should be.
[HAPPY] I don't know
how to it break to ya,
but there's nothin' here.
[LUCY]
Yeah, I noticed.
[NATSU]
"Just two hours left," she said.
Bull crap, it felt like days.
[NATSU sniffs]
That smell. What is it?
[LUCY, HAPPY gasp]
[LUCY, HAPPY scream]
[HAPPY]
What is that thing?
[LUCY] It's a sea slug!
A really frickin' big one too!
[HAPPY]
Is that a kind of fish?
'Cause if it is,
then we can eat it!
Crazy as this sounds, I think
he's hungrier than you are!
Okay fine, what's your plan?
I've got this!
It actually works out
that we're by the sea.
Open, Gate of the
Water Bearer! Aquarius!
[LUCY] Uh.
[HAPPY] Pop it open, now!
This is so not right.
Hey Aquarius.
What's the matter with you?
[LUCY] C'mon, Open,
Gate of the Water Bearer!
Aquarius!
[HAPPY]
What happened?
[LUCY]
Pretty please? I need your help!
[HAPPY, LUCY scream]
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
[LUCY screams]
It downed him
like a roast pepper!
I'll try this one.
Just hang in there, okay?
Open, Gate of the Golden Bull!
Come on!
Taurus!
[HAPPY]
What's the deal?
[LUCY] Why won't any of
my spirits come help me?
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon...
Roar!
[NATSU screams]
[HAPPY]
You're alive!
[LUCY] At least one
of 'em's gotta work!
Loke! Get your butt out here!
What's wrong with me?
I need some help!
Sagittarius! Please! Virgo?
Anybody out there?
Don't let me get eaten!
One, two three, heave!
I'm good! Lucy isn't
usin' her spirits?
What's the deal?
Uh...
[NATSU]
Hit the sand, Lucy! Fire...
Dragon Roar!
[LUCY screams]
Eat your fill.
Lucy, run! She's gonna blow!
[LUCY screams]
[NATSU] Yeah, I don't
think it's comin' back.
Hey Lucy, you okay?
[LUCY]
My celestial spirits won't come.
I say the words. Then, nothing.
[ERZA]
It's certainly strange.
[CARLA]
Yes. To say the very least.
Come on. Is nobody else
gonna be real with her?
As your friend,
I'm obliged to say it.
This ain't your look.
I find it ironic, getting
fashion advice from a nudist.
Cover yourself please
Excuse me. But what is it
that you said was strange?
The job that Natsu's
group just took.
Seabellus village
doesn't actually exist.
But, how could it not exist?
[ERZA] I've done a number
of jobs in that region
and it's quite deserted.
If there were a town there, it'd
be populated by giant sea slugs.
[GRAY] If the town isn't
real, we can assume
the job was faked too.
[MIRAJANE] But who would
do something like that?
And what are they after?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Unfortunately, it seems far
too elaborate to be a prank.
If they're heading for a trap,
then we should warn them!
[YUKINO]
I hope I'm not too late.
It's Yukino.
[GRAY]
You're soaking wet.
[WENDY]
You must be freezing!
I have to speak with
Lucy, where is she?
[ERZA] Tell us what's happening.
Why are you so flustered?
[MIRAJANE] Hold on a sec.
I'll go grab you a towel, okay?
There isn't any time.
I need to find Lucy
as soon as possible!
There's something important
I have to tell her!
Alright then.
Now Open, Gate of the Ram!
Come Aries!
[LUCY]
Open, Gate of the Twins!
Gemini!
[HAPPY] I'm sure they'd
come if they could, Lucy.
[NATSU]
All ten keys are broken?
[LUCY] I don't understand
what's wrong with them!
Maybe they're all
out doing some
important celestial
spirit stuff.
No. Even if that
were the case
they'd still give
some kind of response.
What could've happened?
I can kind of picture
Loke or Aquarius
blowin' you off, but Virgo and
Aries wouldn't do that to ya,
they take things too seriously.
[LUCY gasps]
There's one way to find out.
I still haven't tried
my silver keys!
Open, Gate of the
Southern Cross!
Crux!
It worked!
Wow, you did it!
[HAPPY]
Long time, no see, Grandpa Crux!
[CRUX groans]
[LUCY]
Grandpa Crux!
[NATSU]
Whoa man, you okay?
I'm afraid not.
You're badly hurt.
Talk to us, what
happened to you?
Just tell us what their name is.
I'll take care of the rest.
Something awful's happened.
In the celestial world.
Wait, what do you mean?
[CRUX]
Miss Lucy. Heed my words.
If that which has been set
in motion isn't stopped,
then both the celestial world
and the human world
will end up completely--
[NATSU]
Watch out!
[LUCY]
Who attacked us?
[HAPPY]
Maybe those moles had kids!
I know that scent.
Natsu? Where's Grandpa Crux?
[CRUX screams]
[NATSU, LUCY gasp]
[CRUX] Miss Lucy.
Please run while you can!
[WOMAN]
Shut your mouth.
The punishment for
chatting up humans is severe.
[LUCY]
Hey, who are you?
[NATSU]
Scent doesn't lie. We know her.
[LUCY]
No.
She would never hurt
a friend of mine--
[VIRGO]
I like to hurt things.
It's the best part
of being The Maiden.
Oh yeah!
[ERZA] Those are the
keys of the Balance
and the Two Fish, aren't they?
[YUKINO]
Yes.
I use these keys to
summon Libra and Pisces.
Unfortunately, the last several
times I attempted to use them,
my calls went unanswered.
You must be so worried.
Those spirits
are special, right?
Yeah, they're two of the
12 Zodiac celestial spirits.
There are many beings
in the celestial world,
but those 12 are
uniquely powerful.
[JUVIA]
I don't understand.
Are celestial spirits even
able to disregard a summons?
I thought they were
bound to obey the wizard
to whom they're contracted.
Is something interfering
with the keys?
[YUKINO] I've been looking
into it, but nothing's come up.
But, that's why I
must find Lucy,
to find out if
her zodiac spirits
have gone silent as well.
[CARLA] First we learn she's
taken a false job, and now this?
[WENDY] Without her spirits,
she could be in real trouble.
[GRAY]
Don't worry, she's with Natsu.
Did I just say that?
[MIRAJANE] We could try
to get in touch with her
telepathically, but Warren's
out on a job right now.
I hope she's okay.
Please. Help me!
Your cries of pain are giving
me the shivers, old boy.
Hey, let him go!
That can't be her. Can it?
[VIRGO] Go back where
you belong, traitor!
[CRUX screams]
She forced the gate to close!
[NATSU]
Tell me. Are you actually Virgo?
[VIRGO]
Who else would I be?
[HAPPY]
I don't know, but the real Virgo
wouldn't do this stuff!
[LUCY]
Mm-mm. No, I'm sure of it now.
You don't even look the same.
But you're her.
[LUCY] Whatever happened,
you're still Virgo.
There's no doubt about it.
I know my friends.
You've worked
that out, have you?
Well done, I'll reward
you with pain.
That's not how rewards work.
[VIRGO grunts]
[ALL scream]
You wanna fight me? Let's go!
Let's see what
your guts look like.
[NATSU yells]
[LUCY]
Stop fighting, please!
[NATSU]
How come?
[LUCY]
I have to deal with this myself.
I'm the one she made
her contract with,
so it should be me
that enforces that pact.
[VIRGO] In that case,
you must be Lucy Heartfillia.
I'm told that I used
to be a slave of yours.
[LUCY]
Slave? We were friends!
What do you mean "told?"
Don't you remember?
[VIRGO]
Sure don't.
The days I spent serving
you have gone dark.
That's crazy.
You forgot that much?
I'm bored talking, let's get
straight into the pain!
[LUCY]
I'll make you remember!
[HAPPY] Lucy's barely
keeping up with her!
[NATSU] Virgo was trouble
enough when she liked us.
[VIRGO gasps]
Take this!
Princess.
[LUCY whimpers]
You just showed
mercy to a sadist.
Bad move!
[LUCY screams]
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Lucy!
Stay back. It's my fight.
[HAPPY]
But why?
Something's taken her memories,
but that doesn't mean
she's not my friend.
I have to find
a way to help her.
Weakling! You coward!
Suffer, master!
Screw this.
[LUCY]
Natsu, stop!
If you really wanna help,
then stay out of this one, okay?
[LUCY screams]
The look on your face
is quite exquisite, Lucy.
But you can scream far louder
than that and we both know it.
[VIRGO cackles]
[LUCY screaming]
[VIRGO] And that means you've
been holding out on me!
How dare you!
You're a glutton for
punishment, aren't you?
I said louder! Cry for help!
You're pathetic!
I'm not gonna
watch this anymore!
[NATSU]
Lucy! Snap out of it, c'mon!
[VIRGO] Come back later, you
can have her once I'm through.
[NATSU]
You'll pay for this.
[HAPPY]
Why're you being so mean?
Can't see a thing!
What's goin' on?
It's burning through my eyelids!
Golden light.
[LUCY]
No way! Are they all here?
Aries?
Taurus!
Gemini.
Cancer?
Sagittarius!
Scorpio!
Capricorn?
Aquarius?
[NATSU]
Why do they look so different?
[HAPPY] I guess
whatever freakified Virgo
got ahold of them too.
Greetings, old master.
We thank you for
that introduction.
We also ask that you excuse us
for our ill-mannered entrance.
We weren't plannin'
to beat you up till later.
She's not right.
[NATSU] Okay spill it,
why do you all look so weird?
[LOKE] Perhaps we once
took on forms designed
to please you humans,
but no more.
Loke. Is that you?
[LOKE]
Loke?
Is that what you
used to call me back
when I was one of
your pet spirits?
Hear me well.
I am as through with that
name as I am with you.
[HAPPY] Did you really
just snub Lucy's love?
That's crazy, I mean you've
been hittin' on her for years!
[LOKE]
Silence, cat. I am Leo the Lion.
The Leo she tamed with a
key and a whip is no more.
In light of this new reality,
I'm free.
The contract I once
signed with you is void.
[LUCY gasps]
[LOKE] That goes for each
of us. We serve ourselves now.
[SAGITTARIUS] We lured you
here in order to inform you
of the termination
of our contracts.
[AQUARIUS] That fake job
flier we made tricked you
pretty good, huh?
[TAURUS] We decided to let
you see your utter inability
to control us for yourself.
[NATSU]
Wait.
So was that Sea Slug
attack a part of your plan?
[AQUARIUS]
Sure was!
We wanted to let you know
that you can't call us
to do your dirty work,
even with those golden keys.
Teehee!
Please. No.
It's so creepy when she
tries to act cute like that.
Can we talk about this?
Listen, please.
I understand that you
don't remember making
your contracts with me.
But you did, and it was
because you wanted to!
[LUCY]
I was never your master.
I was your partner, your friend!
I still am. it's just
that you've forgotten!
Crying. My, what a pitifully
human sight to behold.
[LUCY]
Aquarius!
You and I have been together
since I was just a little girl.
My whole life.
And now you're saying
that you don't remember
anything about me?
Honestly, you don't
look too familiar!
I've moved on, Lady, you should
probably try to do the same.
Times are changing.
[TAURUS] Any more questions
before we take our leave?
This can't be.
Please at least try to remember!
You've been with me for so long.
Good times and bad, I was
never alone because of you.
I just. Want my friends back.
[AQUARIUS]
Think she means it?
[TAURUS] It matters not.
We've delivered our message.
It's not our fault if she
refuses to understand.
[AQUARIUS] Yeah, humans
are dense like that.
[LOKE] Well if the girl won't
be convinced by our words.
Then let's give
her a demonstration.
Let's prove our bond is broken.
[LUCY gasps]
The hell?
[HAPPY] Good thing you
got her outta there.
That blast was huge!
[LOKE]
Aquarius!
[AQUARIUS]
Okay!
You three look awful thirsty!
[ALL grunting, screaming]
Sagittarius.
[SAGITTARIUS]
My aim is true.
[ALL screaming]
[LOKE]
Taurus.
[TAURUS] Yes. If you'd
be so kind as to leave.
[ALL screaming]
Virgo.
[VIRGO]
This'll be fun. Let's go!
[NATSU grunting]
[LUCY, HAPPY]
Natsu!
That'll do.
'Kay. I'm fired up now!
Wait, Natsu!
I know they're acting like
jerks, but it isn't their fault.
they're just not themselves.
If we could
somehow find a way
to bring their memories back.
They'd stop.
I've got an idea. Happy!
Keep an eye on Lucy!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
[SAGITTARIUS]
Where shall I stick them?
[HAPPY]
Oh no!!
[NATSU yells]
[HAPPY]
Natsu! Be careful, will ya?
Don't hurt them!
They're still our friends okay?!
Yeah. Don't worry 'bout it.
I'm just gonna pound on 'em
till they remember who I am!
Behold.
the raw power of a
celestial spirit unleashed!
Cool! Give me
everything ya got!
[NATSU] I'm kind of glad
this happened, Loke!
'Cause I still owe yo two
whacks from awhile back!
[LOKE] Are you saying
I've defeated you before?
[NATSU] No you sucker-punched
me, doesn't count!
[LOKE]
Ha! You'll have to hit harder
than that to put
a dent in my armor.
[NATSU] Look man.
I'm sure it's good armor,
but is it worth lookin'
that dumb, Loke?
That's not my name!
[AQUARIUS]
Points for hanging in there.
But Leo's gonna tear him apart.
[SAGITTARIUS]
Well, he's only human.
[LOKE] It's time to give up,
because you're beaten.
No mere mortal can defeat an
unshackled celestial spirit.
[NATSU]
Cut it out with the braggin'!
It ain't like you, Loke!
I told you not
to use that name!
[LOKE] This taste of freedom
has left us craving more.
Complete freedom will be ours.
[NATSU]
What?
[LOKE] There's no point
in explaining it to you.
It is something far
beyond your comprehension!
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU]
Let me down, Happy!
I had him right
where I wanted him.
Who's side are you on, cat?
[HAPPY]
You eat too much.
My little arms are
gonna pop right off.
He says they want
"complete freedom." But.
[LUCY] Weren't they free
already? What does he mean?
[HAPPY] You're like
two sacks of bricks.
[NARRATOR] The celestial
world's current state.
[AQUARIUS] Lame! I can't
believe we let 'em escape.
We totally had 'em too!
[TAURUS] Ignoring the
winged cat was a mistake
for they couldn't have
retreated without him.
[SAGITTARIUS] Their escape
does complicate things.
[LOKE]
We'll deal with them later.
In the meantime, there
are more pressing matters
that require our attention.
[LOKE] There are many tasks
and obsticles before us.
They'll forge the
path to freedom.
[HAPPY] Okay! Time to
buckle down and research
why the celestial
spirits got so weird!
[NATSU]
Perfect! That's my specialty!
[HAPPY] I said
"research," not "rampage."
[NATSU] Hey, for all you
know I could be a natural!
Ain't no tellin'
till I give it a try.
[HAPPY] This is how all your
great failures begin, Natsu.
[NATSU]
Just you wait!
I'll tear this book
apart in three sec--
[HAPPY]
Wow, knocked him right out.
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Next Time: Library Panic!
[NATSU] Ah, crap! Did I
just get KO'd by a book?
[HAPPY] Yup. Still
think you're a natural?