[OPHIUCHUS] The Celestial
Globe serves as a conduit.
It channels power from the
constellations of the zodiac
to my king.
The ritual we set out
to perform's sole purpose
is to grant him
the zodiac's strength.
It's called the "Liberam Verus".
Becoming an
Eclipse spirit did endow
the Celestial Spirit king,
who was already the
strongest being in his world,
with power greater
than he had ever known,
but it also gave him
an appetite to match.
Fearful of his mighty hunger,
the zodiac spirits attempted to
flee the celestial world.
They strove to be free of him.
But their celestial
bodies pulled them back
to the stars.
To resist was to suffer,
and to give in was to die.
The setup was perfect.
With the false hope
of the Liberam,
I set them and you
to work at granting my king
the power he craves.
The Celestial Spirit King
was that affected?
We thought we were
fighting to protect the spirits,
but we ended up putting
them right into harm's way.
To think we've been
banishing them to the very place
that they were so desperately
struggling to escape.
A world ruled by a
power-crazed monster.
How awful...
I can't believe this crap!
That isn't the
worst of it, either.
If this demented Celestial
Spirit King goes unchecked,
if his rampage can't be stopped,
then the celestial spirit world
will collapse in on itself.
Ya mean the whole damn place?
[OPHIUCHUS] Indeed.
Princess Hisui's prediction
may well come to pass.
[growling noise]
Didja hear that growling?
It sounded like a wild animal!
[laughing]
Time to move!
Yeah!
[OPHIUCHUS laughing maniacally]
Enough of your noise!
You and your king
seem pretty desperate
to get yourselves hurt.
Ya don't need to destroy
the whole world for that.
I got your pain right here!
[OPHIUCHUS] You're
completely out of options.
There is absolutely
nothing you can do
to save your precious zodiac.
I don't give a
crap about my options!
I'm gonna stop you
no matter what!
[HAPPY] When the Stars Fall!
Listen. I got this.
I can handle Ophiuchus.
Take out that globe!
[OPHIUCHUS] I've already
told you, human.
There's no stopping me now!
Wish I had a jewel
for every time
someone said that to me.
Right before
I kicked their butts!
[flute playing]
[HAPPY, NATSU yelling]
Natsu!
What happened?
[LUCY] No idea.
All she did was play
something on her flute.
I'm not sure,
but it looked like
The Serpent's Dance of Death.
[LUCY]
But what does that mean?
[HISUI] It allows her to
control any object or substance
in her sight,
merely by playing that flute.
[ERZA] This doesn't bode well.
[PANTHERLILY] Things must be
getting rough up there.
That's right.
Just one more reason
not to stand around waiting!
Let's get moving.
Natsu and Wendy are
gonna need some backup!
Yeah, but which
way should we go?
We can hear their voices,
but there's no telling
where they're comin' from!
Gray, darling!
I think we should
look for them over there.
just the two of us,
you and me, alone!
[GRAY] Drivin' that in
kinda hard, aren't ya?
[JUVIA] I don't know
how else to do it,
but I'm willing to learn.
This is hardly the time
for you two to get cozy!
We're not!
Let's just pick a
direction and start moving!
Can everyone please calm down?
Check it out!
Did you find something useful?
It has to do with
the term "Trinitas".
[CANA] Trinitas, huh?
Kay, what about it?
[LEVY] I had the entire passage
translated except for that word.
But I think I've got it now!
[flute playing]
[LEVY]
"Trinitas" means "trinity".
And in the context
of this ancient language,
a trinity is comprised
of parent, child and spirit.
Which spirit?
What are you saying?
The parent's Ophiuchus.
And the snake...
No, Astral Spiritus
itself must be the child.
Which means "spirit"...
...must refer
to the shining light
that's pouring out
of the Celestial Globe!
Yeah. That would
make sense to me.
So what does that
have to do with anything?
The three are much
stronger when they're united.
So it looks like the only way
to stop Liberam Verus now
is to destroy each
piece of the Trinitas at once!
Understood.
[flute playing]
[ERZA] We might not
be able to find Natsu,
but we can still assist him.
We'll leave the snake charmer
and the globe to his team
and deal with the serpent
of Astral Spiritus ourselves.
[CANA] You want us to fight
the thing we're standing in?
How would we even start?
[ERZA] I have a theory about
the source of all these tremors.
This might sound odd,
but I believe they're
caused by the serpent
shedding its skin in
order to alter its structure
as a kind of survival mechanism.
And if I'm correct,
then I say we
should help it along
until it's got
nothing left to shed.
So your plan is to tear
the monster apart from within.
[GAJEEL chuckles]
You tellin' me I can
smash whatever I want?
[PANTHERLILY]
That is the Fairy Tail way.
We'll teach the
snake girl a lesson.
If you sit on a
three legged throne,
it's far easier
for us to kick you off!
Let's do this!
[ALL] Yeah!
Look out! Sky Dragon...
...Crushing Fang!
[gasping]
Arcadios, are you hurt?
Fear not, princess.
He's all right,
but what about you?
I'm fine.
Never mind me, we need to fully
focus on destroying the globe!
Its defenses
are quite formidable.
Wendy, let's see what happens
if we attack it together,
all right?
Yeah, sure!
Fleuve d'étoiles!
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
How are we supposed
to deal with that?
[flute playing]
[HAPPY] Here it comes!
What do we do?
We can't back down!
Natsu!
[yelling]
A mere human,
soaring through the sky.
How arrogant.
[flute playing]
[NATSU] Damn you!
[HAPPY yelling]
[OPHIUCHUS laughs]
A lowly human can never
reach the level of the stars,
but if you really want to
fly, I'll help you.
[flute playing]
Cut it out! Crap...
Just hang in there, Happy!
Yeah. Don't worry abo--
--[flute playing]
--Whoa... whoa!
You okay?
We won't back down, right?
[HAPPY] Our heads are
thicker than she thinks!
That's right! Let's go!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[growls]
I've never seen
a wall fight back before.
Doesn't matter.
It can't take
both of us at once.
[ELFMAN] Whatever you do,
keep on attacking!
[MIRAJANE] Don't stop while you
still have magic left!
[JUVIA] What is this?
Looks like the
obligatory dungeon trap!
Well guess what?
There isn't a
trap in this world
that can put an end
to the two of us.
Finish it!
Right. Leave it to me.
Water... Cannon!
[PANTHERLILY] Get ready.
Iron Dragon Club!
There any metal here?
I'm sick of all
this friggin' rock.
Don't count my cards out yet.
They're sharper
than you'd think!
Solid Script Magic: Drill!
[LUCY] It's kicking back
everything we throw at it.
Still, there
has to be something.
Let me take a crack at it.
Go for it!
Hey there.
This is Deneb,
the White Swan!
[DENEB] Go on.
Stop staring and ask me
why my wings aren't white.
I know you want to.
Uhh...
Nice to meet you too, Deneb.
D'you see that globe?
Destroy it if you can.
[DENEB] All right, fine.
There's certainly
nothing better to do.
"If you can," she says.
Maybe I would try harder
if my wizard believed in me!
You've got this!
I believe in you!
If you must humor me,
don't wait until
I've screwed up first!
Come on!
Break, ya damn orb!
Can't something
work out my way for once?
[screaming]
[DENEB] You were right.
I'm just as useless
as you think I am.
Sorry I'm not better.
[YUKINO] Deneb, no!
[WENDY] Uhh...
[LUCY] He's actually
a pretty tough spirit.
But he's got some
insecurity issues.
He vented practically all
of his angst on it, though.
How did it survive?
Uhh, Yukino?
How does that surprise you?
Requip! Heaven's Wheel Armor!
Circle Sword!
Fire Dragon... Brilliant...
[flute playing]
You sound like crap--Agh!
[HAPPY]
Fight through it, Natsu!
[OPHIUCHUS laughs]
What a pitiful sight you are.
Be gone!
[HAPPY] C'mon, bud!
[WENDY] They haven't
given up and neither will I!
[CARLA]
That's the spirit, Wendy!
We can do this!
You can do this!
Give it everything you've got!
[WENDY] I will.
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Shattering Light: Sky Drill!
Good job, Wendy.
This should do it!
Wow. That just might work!
[OPHIUCHUS]
You're nothing more than ants
crawling in my sugar.
It's like you're
asking to be crushed.
[flute playing]
Princess!
Arcadios, you saved me!
You're still in danger.
Please run!
[HISUI]
Okay. Now you get out, too!
We have to help him!
What do we do?
[WENDY] Sky Dragon...
[WENDY] ...Roar!
Don't you worry,
I can heal you!
[ARCADIOS]
Are you all right, Princess?
I am, thanks to you.
But please stop throwing
yourself into danger!
[WENDY] It's okay, Princess.
He'll be fine.
You take care
of the globe! Hurry!
Thanks.
Okay, I'll do whatever I can.
But I'm...
[ALL scream]
I'm useless.
I've only made things worse.
No. Fight for today.
[HAPPY]
That light's getting stronger!
This doesn't look good.
We gotta stop it. Fast!
[OPHIUCHUS]
As you can see,
the Liberam Verus has entered
its final phase at last.
Soon its red light will
fill the Astral Spiritus,
draining the life force
of every member
of the Zodiac but me.
And when it does,
the Celestial Spirit King
shall acquire
more power than
you've ever imagined!
If you shoot that
much power into him,
he'll probably explode!
Lucy and the others...
They're bound to their spirits.
And I don't mean by contract.
They've put their
hearts into those bonds.
Natsu...
[HAPPY] He's right!
They're all connected!
Those bonds mean
everything to them.
And I won't let you cut 'em!
I'm bored with
the Dance of Death.
How's this?
It's The Death Penalty.
[NATSU grunting]
Natsu!
Didn't even feel it.
Stop worryin' about us!
Focus on the celestial globe!
We can take her!
But you gotta
break that thing, quick!
We haven't even
put a scratch on it yet!
There has to be a way.
We can't have come
this far for nothing!
The demolition's going well,
but what's our exit strategy?
Don't think anyone
thought that far ahead.
[PANTHERLILY]
Figured as much.
You did good, Juvia.
[JUVIA]
And it was worth the effort
to get alone with you
beneath this open sky.
Oh, darling!
Catch me if I faint!
You'd better not count on it.
Keep dodgin'!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
Don't give up.
I've got a plan!
Without that flute,
she can't do crap!
If we can take it out,
the rest should be easy!
[HAPPY] Who said
anything about givin' up?
Oh yeah! The flute!
Geez man, you sure did take
your time figuring that one out!
Less time than you!
Get us in closer, will ya?
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
It isn't working!
I think the light's
blocking my healing magic!
Be strong, Arcadios.
[ALL gasp]
Libra and Virgo
must've felt this pain.
Yet they kept on
fighting until the end.
To be free.
[HISUI]
First the Eclipse Project.
And then those keys.
I'm the reason
we're all suffering!
[LUCY] No one blames you.
There's no way
you could've known!
[HISUI] I deserve this pain.
A thousand fold.
I've earned it.
That isn't true.
You screwed up,
but you tried to make it right!
Listen. It's okay.
Everybody fails.
That's just part of being human.
Yes, but...
[LUCY]
We don't have time for regret.
We have to make a stand!
[HISUI] A stand for what?
A stand for our spirits!
That globe can take
the magic from the stars.
Now tell me what you are!
I am a... I'm a
celestial wizard, like you.
We have to stop this.
In fact, the three of us...
We are the only ones
who possibly can.
[HISUI] There is a way.
And it will hurt.
We must make the stars
in heaven rain down.
[LUCY] How is that possible?
There's a spell.
Long forgotten hyper-magic.
It was known as Gottfried.
There's no choice.
Start it.
[HISUI]
Hands of the welkin.
Clench thy mighty fists.
I bid the star's descent!
[CARLA] Wendy!
If he can last,
so can I!
Hurry, please!
[OPHIUCHUS]
Your efforts are futile.
The light of the Liberam
will fill this place soon.
Why can't you understand
that you came too late?
[NATSU]
Don't let them distract you!
You're fightin' me!
[HISUI] Shine down.
Break the land upon your light.
Cleanse it with
your hands divine.
Let there be no
place left for darkness.
Fall straight and true.
I bid thee.
Bring empyrean
crashing down upon us!
Shine down! Gottfried!
[screaming]
I can sense it.
One final blow and it's done.
[HISUI, YUKINO, LUCY
whimpering]
Black Fire Dragon mode!
What's that?
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Pitch-Black Phoenix Sword!
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu.
Whaddaya think this
evil Celestial Spirit King
is gonna be like?
[NATSU]
Maybe he talks super-fast now!
[HAPPY] Yeah!
A bunch of other spirits did
turn into their total opposites!
I mean, look at Loke!
He stopped likin' girls!
[NATSU]
I bet the king's gone bald!
[HAPPY] Seems likely to me!
[NATSU] And he was huge before,
so what if he's tiny now?
[HAPPY] Let's see then.
He must've turned into a bald,
fast-talkin, ant-man!
[NATSU]
Well I hope he can fight.
[HAPPY, NATSU] Next time:
Celestial Spirit Beast!
[HAPPY] What?
This is the
Celestial Spirit King?
[NATSU]
Man. We weren't even close!