[LYON] Their numbers
are too great for us.
At this point, we can't even
get anywhere close to the city.
I know, but we have to take it
back to stave off the invasion.
Because if we don't,
they're going to keep on
sending ships full
of reinforcements.
[SHELIA]
We have to get the upper hand.
Oh, I wish Wendy were here.
How lame!
You had a four-against-one
advantage,
and this is the best
you old farts can do?
My old friend.
Sadly, I'll never see
your smiling face again.
Huh?
[WARROD]
Yuri. Precht.
I'll be joining you very soon.
[GOD SERENA] I think
turning you into firewood
is going to be a lot
of fun, Warrod, no joke.
This does not bode well.
He took us down with
no help from the others.
I'm afraid going to Alvarez
has only made him stronger.
How can this be?
We've failed.
We've sullied the name of
the Four Emperors of Ishgar.
Time to say God-bye-bye.
[WARROD]
Sorry, Mavis, this is farewell.
However...
As one of the founders
of Fairy Tail,
it's not in my nature
to go down quietly.
I will fight to the end!
God Serena.
I'm taking you with me!
[WARROD] God Serena.
[grunting]
[WOLFHEIM roars]
I see. You're not as
weak as I thought.
[gasps]
[GOD SERENA]
Hyberion!
Nice.
Vampiric magic.
Without any contact. Seems
he's earned his stature.
[HYBERION]
As I suspected,
your bluster exceeds your
abilities, God Serena.
[AUGUST]
No need to get involved.
Just be content to
stand back and watch.
This will be a delight.
All right! Cavern Dragon!
Earth Collapse!
[gasps]
[WARROD groaning]
[WOLFHEIM yells]
What is this? Earth
Dragon Slayer magic?
There's more.
Purgatory Dragon:
Blazing Inferno!
Mighty Sea King Dragon:
Water Vortex!
Fire and water?
I've got Tempest
Dragon magic, too.
More elements?
[AUGUST]
You've done enough, God Serena.
[GOD SERENA] Whoops.
Seems I had too much fun.
Seeing him in action
was a delight indeed.
A Dragon Slayer with
eight dragon lacrimas.
Puts on a hell of a show.
The Hybrid Theory personified.
He is a man favored by
the god of dragons.
[chuckles]
There aren't any gods or kings
when it comes to dragons.
How could there be when none
can even compare to my power?
[AUGUST]
With those four bested,
let us continue
onward to Fairy Tail.
[WARROD]
They'll destroy everything,
leaving only death
in their wake.
But who can stop them?
[gasps]
[WARROD]
Wait. What is this presence?
This power?
Who is that approaching?
I smell the putrid
stench of a dragon.
[AUGUST]
Acnologia.
[grunts]
So you've come to me,
aren't I lucky?
I left Ishgar behind with the
dream of killing you, so--
[gasps]
[groaning]
[ACNOLOGIA] Only seven
more dragons remaining.
I will slay them all.
That's him. That's Acnologia.
[AUGUST]
Calm down.
You'd be dead before
you hit the ground.
[AUGUST] Perhaps His Majesty
could defeat him,
once he's acquired
the Fairy Heart.
[AUGUST]
Let us make haste to Fairy Tail.
So we may help secure
his extraordinary prize.
[footsteps]
How's his condition?
Can't tell. He hasn't
woken up yet.
Have you checked on
Bixlow and Evergreen?
Yes, they're feeling
much better.
[LUCY]
I'm happy to hear it.
If anyone's curious,
I should recover, too.
[FRIED] Do you happen
to know where Laxus is?
I think he left town
with Erza's team.
They're going to go
liberate Hargeon.
Gray and Wendy went with them.
I see. I hope he's not reckless.
[LUCY]
And how likely is that?
[FRIED]
Touché.
Caution? Not his style.
[ICHIYA] A man who dives
headlong into danger.
Man.
We'll reach Hargeon by morning.
So get all the rest
you can tonight.
Okay.
And you'd be wise to
take your own advice.
Wendy has better things
to do than play nurse.
Gray, my darling!
Aren't you glad I
brought my special
two-person sleeping bag
with me on this trip?
No way I'm gettin'
in that thing!
Juvie!
Feel like I haven't
seen Laxus in a while.
Earlier he said he was hungry
and he ambled towards the woods.
He's prob'ly off tryin'
to eat a bear or somethin'.
Think so?
Are bears tasty?
[WENDY]
Uh. You're drooling.
[LAXUS grunting]
[GRAY]
When did it start?
[LAXUS]
None of your damn business.
[GRAY]
Come on, man, we're guild mates.
I'm askin' as a friend.
[GRAY]
I'd guess a year ago?
Right when you got a double
lung full of Bane Particles?
That sound right?
[LAXUS sighs]
[gasps]
[LAXUS]
He's not human!
[TEMPESTER yelling]
I missed?
Stand still. Coward.
Is this still enough for ya?
Lightning Dragon Jaw!
[TEMPESTER] A great number
of people are about to die.
And we'll be the first.
[LAXUS]
No one else is gonna die here!
Not while I'm around!
[FRIED]
Laxus. Shield your mouth!
What are you doing?
[LAXUS] That's twice you've
misjudged me, "Disaster."
First you underestimated
the strength of my magic,
now you've done the
same with my lungs.
[FRIED] Please stop.
You'll kill yourself!
No way you're talkin'
me outta this.
But you can make sure
they get home safe.
Not one word.
Okay, this is between us.
Enough with the death glare.
[LAXUS sighs]
[LAXUS]
It's nothing.
Just bothers me every
once in a while.
Don't worry about it.
[GRAY]
Hm.
[LAXUS]
Tch.
I'm gonna protect the guild,
up until the battle is over.
Even if it kills me.
[LAXUS]
Get dressed, damn it!
Aw, man! Sorry about that!
[LEVY]
Hey, Gajeel.
Trouble sleeping?
Yeah. Guess I'm
not the only one.
I'm worried.
It feels like there's
a good chance
we're not gonna make
it back from this one.
We've said it before,
but there's something
different about this enemy.
I'm scared.
And I'm not nearly as
strong as everyone else.
Is this gonna be the end
of the story for us?
[gasping] What the--?
Gajeel!
You're under arrest
for self-doubt.
Sorry.
[GAJEEL] Ya know what
that means, don't ya?
I'm gonna throw your butt
in a guild hall cell
when we get back.
[WIZARDS yelling]
Today we will take back Hargeon!
Drive them out!
I rattled her yesterday,
but look at her now.
All fired up.
[WALL laughs]
Still though, I think I'll play
with someone else today.
Now Sky God... Boreas!
[SOLDIER A]
Who's that little shrimp?
[SOLDIER B]
She's pretty tough!
And Sky God--
I'm claiming this
little one for myself.
No please! Don't do this!
[DIMARIA] You're just
getting me more excited.
You want me to do to you
what I did to your friend?
[SHELIA growls]
[DIMARIA] Too bad, because
today is going to be different.
[gasps]
Let's see. You're
a healer, right?
Well, that means
I can't let you live.
[gasps]
[gasps] Wendy, it's you!
Sorry I got here late.
But the Sky Sisters
are back in action!
[DIMARIA] That brat...
kicked me in the face.
Ice Make Eagle.
If I can pull that off a couple
thousand more times, we're good.
[GRAY]
Lyon!
We're headed for the front line!
Let's send them back home!
Juvia? And Gray?
It's now or never, guys!
This is our chance!
[LYON] Whoa! She's
practically glowing!
[gasps]
What the hell are
you doing here?
[ERZA] This was our
battle from the start!
We never expected
another guild to butt in.
But here you are!
So thank you!
Erza!
Let's get moving!
Right.
[WALL]
Wow.
So Fairy Tail actually decided
to bring the fight to us.
Huh?
[growls]
You're the one who messed
with the Thunder Legion?
Never heard of 'em!
[WALL screams]
They're my friends, you freak!
Ah.
Alchemizing copper and zinc,
nine-millimeter rounds.
Fire!
That lightning?
We get that kinda weather
back in Magnolia.
Sunny with a chance of Laxus.
And plenty of ice
in the forecast!
Not bad, big guy!
What makes you tick?
A quick analysis.
[WALL]
Huh?
Your organs are
in quite a state.
Tch.
What's your secret?
I honestly wanna know
how you're alive.
I mean, are you actually human?
It's not about "how I'm alive."
It's "how I live"!
So profound.
You people really
enjoy showing off
your pithy wordplay, don't you?
And for your information,
lightning doesn't work on me.
[WALL laughing]
So the conversation needs to
shift to "how you'll die."
Erza, this way!
But what about all
the enemies here?
[KAGURA] My guild mates
can handle them.
We have to get to the port!
[ERZA]
What's the situation?
[KAGURA]
Two of the Twelve are in town.
The swordswoman and
the Machias alchemist.
But there's one more
who's not left their ship.
It's up to the two of
us to dispose of them.
Right!
[CARLA] You're underdressed
for the battlefield.
Here. Wendy's jacket
should fit you.
I appreciate it, thank you.
[SHELIA]
Wow, it's really tight.
I'm sorry, little girls.
But do you realize where we are?
Careful, Wendy.
I can't quite figure out what
kind of magic she uses.
[DIMARIA]
At least the one with the tail
knows it's a battlefield,
not a playground.
Hargeon used to be a place
where children could play.
Till you got here!
We're gonna make you leave!
So the people here
can live in peace!
[DIMARIA]
I don't care if you're kids,
I show mercy to no one.
The truth is, I could kill you
in the blink of an eye.
You wouldn't even
know what hit you!
Get ready, girls!
[DIMARIA] A split second
would last an eternity.
[WALL]
Analysis complete.
His innards are swimming
with Bane Particles,
but his magic power level
is one of the highest
in Fairy Tail.
I can't maintain
the upper hand
on my current "prankster"
personality setting.
So I'll set my program
to "coldhearted."
Enhanced exoskeleton
assault mode.
Designating Laxus
as sole target.
Locked on.
Magic fusion reactor ignited.
Estimated time to complete
target elimination, 90 seconds.
Huh?
[ERZA gasps]
What now?
The sky is on fire?
[WALL]
Re-calibrating.
[groans]
Attack mode: Now engaged.
[LAXUS] Damn it! Gotta
fight through the pain!
[gasps]
[LAXUS screams]
Enemy's survival: Confirmed.
Activating pursuit system.
Generating missiles. Fire!
[WALL]
Anti-matter laser!
[screaming]
[WALL]
Survival confirmed.
Generating high-voltage cannon.
[gasps]
Oh, no! Electrical attacks
only feed his magic power.
But they don't affect me at all!
[WALL]
System error.
Exceeded time for complete
elimination. System error.
Damn this pest!
[gasps]
[LAXUS groaning]
[LUCY] The Bane Particles
eating away at Laxus
threaten to stop him.
But can he pull off
one last ditch attack
that tears down Wall for good?
To the east of Magnolia,
Wendy and Shelia face
off against Dimaria,
the Warrior Queen, and the
odds are not in their favor.
But out of nowhere,
a familiar face appears,
a witch standing before them!
Next Time: "In a Silent Time."
Waiting somewhere
inside eternity,
the traveler of eras
smiles quietly.