[BYRO] You're certainly
restless tonight, Kanaloa.
I understand. But you won't
have to wait much longer.
It's coming
soon, our holy war.
And all who oppose
us will perish.
[OPENING CREDITS]
[PANTHERLILY] Who are you?
[PANTHERLILY] Coco?
But that's impossible!
Hold on Lily, you don't think
she could've come
to this world, do you?
Oh, I remember.
[HAPPY] Coco's the
girl who runs really fast
that we met in Edolas!
I know! She must've traveled
to Earth Land while we were
all stuck on Tenrou Island!
[CARLA] She doesn't look
that much older, though.
[PANTHERLILY] Why are you
here, Coco? Is there trouble?
Hey, quit talking
like you know me, pussy cat.
I've never met any
of you, so shut up.
Are you serious?
Oh no, she has amnesia!
I doubt that.
However.
They could be...
I'll beat that jerk next time!
I wonder how Gajeel
would've fared against him.
Maybe you can
ask him when he
comes crawling
out his hiding spot.
[MAX] We've got visitors.
[MIRAJANE] Oh, customers!
[WENDY] Isn't that
girl from Edolas?
Yeah. Queen Chagot, right?
No, she's a cat.
Coco? Long time no see!
[LUCY] But, how'd did you
get to Earth Land from Edolas?
Sugarboy, these tools
totes think we're like
"old chums" of theirs.
Mhm. Well, I'd have to
say that sounds like
their problem, Mary Hughes.
Let's finish this up before they
invite us to stay for dinner.
"Mary" Hughes?
And Sugarboy?
[NATSU] The
weirdoes we fought at
the Royal City's
Amusement Park?
[LUCY] Now that you mention
it, there is a resemblance.
[NATSU] What's with
the lady clothes, pervert?
You tryin' to fool
me or somethin'?
I just met him
and I wanna kill him.
Something's very wrong here.
If you're folks
aren't here to hire us--
Then you can march right
back where you came from!
[Mary chuckles]
[SUGARBOY] We ain't
takin' orders from slobs
with no style, darlin'.
Say wha--?
I'm only saying
this once, so listen.
I demand you give me
Lucy Heartfilia, like, now!
How forward! My
heart skipped a beat!
Oh wow. I've never seen
a real proposal in person!
[LUCY] It's not like that!
[MARY] Can it, fur ball!
[HAPPY] Target: Lucy!
[COCO] There's no
point hiding her from us!
[MARY] We, like, totes know
the spoiled little twerp's
a member of your guild.
[SUGARBOY] Why dontcha
make it easy on everyone
and shimmy on over here, baby?
What's going on here?
Why are these rude
people looking for you?
Believe me,
I wish I knew why.
You got some guts,
showing up outta the blue
and disrespectin' us like this.
I'm the Master of Fairy Tail.
Your request is denied, so
I suggest you get outta here.
We're not known for our patience
when it comes to cocky punks.
Especially when those
punks're shouting orders.
[MAX] Rubs us the
wrong way, y'know?
[MARY] Like we'd run from
kids, old men, and their cats.
All of those churches
that have been burned down
the past few weeks. It's you.
You're behind them.
Makes sense to me.
Even without proof, the
timing is too convenient.
They must be the culprits!
Spicy!
They're trying to serve
up some guilt, uh-huh!
Well I'm not bitin' it.
Keep on playing
the blame game if it'll
help ya sleep better at night.
Now hand over
Heartfilia before we decide
to get nasty with you!
[SUGARBOY] We're
gonna rock your world.
I'd like to start
with this little diddy.
Uh huh!
[SUGARBOY] C'mon!
♪ Little hound dogs,
don't be cruel. ♪
♪ Anyplace is paradise,
when I'm with you! ♪
[MACAO] Good grief.
[MAX] He needs to be put down.
Next up on the request line.
[SUGARBOY] ♪ A little
less conversation. ♪
♪ A little more
pain and screamin'! ♪
What the--?
My lunch is coming back up.
Looks tasty to me.
[LUCY] Ugh! Disgusting!
What is this stuff?
[LAKI] Slime?
[Elfman power yell]
[ELFMAN] Hey! Stupid sludge!
Why don't you fight
me like a real man?
[LISANNA] Let go of him now!
[MIRAJANE] Elfman, hold on!
No, stay back!
It'll grab you, too!
[Lisanna and Mirajane gasp]
[SUGARBOY] ♪ Yummy! ♪
Wizards taste so spicy!
I can't move.
I know we're in trouble but
I can't help remembering
when we used to snuggle
like this as little kids.
This isn't the
time to reminisce, sis!
[WENDY] What's
it doing to them?
[PANTHERLILY] It appears
to have a will of its own.
Well, whatever it is,
[CARLA] don't let
it touch you! Run away!
[COCO] You're the
guild master, correct?
Unless you want them to get
hurt, you'll hand over Lucy!
Beating up kids isn't my style!
Who the heck are
you calling a kid?
This ain't the time
to get soft on us, Macao.
These guys are the enemy!
I told you
to call me "Master"!
[COCO] Sorry, old timer.
But attacks like
that can't hit me.
Nimble little minx,
doncha think?
[MACAO] Don't act so impressed.
[ROMEO] Get back here!
[Romeo gasps]
Stop it!
Yeah, you're gonna
knock it down, kid!
Oh no, the slime
just got them, too!
Crap. They got us stuck
playing defense back here.
What's with that stuff?
It keeps getting bigger!
Natsu, get your butt over
here and roast this thing!
[Lucy gasps] Our
friends are being slimed
and you're takin'
a freakin' nap?
He's so pale!
Don't tell me
his fight with Laxus
is just now taking its toll?
That's some major time lag.
I'm, like ,totally gonna die
from laughing at these losers!
We got these boys
and girls all shook up.
[COCO] Guild wizards
are pushovers.
I don't see the appeal.
[PANTHERLILY] Coco.
No, it can't be her.
She absolutely hated violence.
The mere thought of harming
others made her physically ill.
But this girl...
[SUGARBOY] Alright,
little hound dogs.
Come home to papa!
[COCO] Game, set, and match!
Ya ready to give up yet?
[Laki and Max breathing heavily]
Damn.
I'm running low on magic.
[HAPPY] They weren't
this strong last time!
That's because these people
are completely different
from the ones
you met in Edolas.
They're the Coco,
Hughes, and Sugarboy
who have lived here in Earth
Land from the very beginning.
[WENDY] I see!
It's just like how Edolas had
its own crazy versions of us.
Guess we should
have expected to
run into someone
sooner or later.
You're wasting
too much time, Lucy.
Hurry up, or we'll
show your little friends
what we're really capable of.
[MARY] Sugarboy would
love to play another solo.
[Mary chuckling]
Don't listen to her, Lu!
[MICHELLE] You can't
give yourself up!
[NATSU] They still don't
know who Lucy is yet.
The three of you
go try to find gramps
and I'll deal
with them somehow.
Just don't keep
me waitin' long.
We can't.
We'll stay and fight with you!
Don't leave now.
Don't ya wanna
play with us too?
Natsu. Take this!
Thanks, Romeo.
[Natsu swallows and farts]
Aw, nasty!
Sorry 'bout that. Wrong flame.
[NATSU] Whatever.
It'll do the trick for now.
[SUGARBOY] Uh huh.
[NATSU] Feel the burn!
[SUGARBOY] Spicy!
[MARY] He's using Fire Magic?
Lame. Conducting Art!
[LAKI] Hey!
[MAX] Hey!
He attacked them!
But why?
Wait a minute, is she--?
[NATSU] Eat this!
Nope.
[screaming]
[Michelle and Lucy screaming]
Oh no!
[Mary laughing] Nothing like
a little "friendly fire".
Give us Lucy or the rest
of your guild gets cooked!
Sorry to break it
to you, sweetheart,
but things are
gonna get real cruel.
Totally. Get
ready, top heavy.
I'm about to make
you eat those rocks.
Run away, Kinana!
So the wittle
kitty wants to play.
[WENDY] Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
Bad move, kid.
[NATSU] Ahhhh!
Natsu!
It's 'cause of
that weird stick!
You may be right.
Perhaps it can take
control of people?
[Lucy wimpering]
[LUCY] I can't just
stand by and watch.
Maybe I should call
a Celestial Spirit.
I'd use the Fleuve
d'étoiles that Virgo gave me,
but I can't seem to
make it work anymore.
[HAPPY] How are you sick?
I'm sorry, it's all my fault!
That slime
really took it out of me.
You're crushing
me, I can't breathe.
Oh no! Everyone
else is drained, too!
That sucked.
Think I'll stay here a bit.
I can barely stand up!
All of our magic
was sapped away.
What do you
want with Lucy?
None of
your business, flea bag!
[MARY] Show yourself, Lucy.
We're, like, totes
getting bored!
[LUCY] Just stop it!
You have what you want now!
[LUCY] Okay.
I'm the Lucy Heartfilia
you're looking for!
[Lucy gasps]
Mhmmm. You, huh?
Be a good girl and
park it right here.
Don't do this!
I think there's been enough
violence for one day.
[MICHELLE] What exactly
do you want with me?
[SUGARBOY] That's her, mama.
You know a little darlin'
like this one grew up
playin' house at the
Heartfilia Mansion. Uh-huh.
[COCO] She certainly
looks the part.
[MARY] Well, this is,
like, disappointing.
I was expecting a total ditz.
[LUCY] What kind of messed
up plot twist is this?
[MARY] Lucy Heartfilia.
Once the daughter of
the Heartfilia Concern,
and now a Celestial Wizard
for the Fairy Tail guild.
That about right?
Indeed, that is correct.
I am the girl
of which you speak.
What is she doin'?
What if Michelle was
the real Lucy all along?
This is ridiculous;
I'm the real Lucy!
Huh?
[MICHELLE] Miss Michelle,
it means the world
that you're willing
to protect me from them.
But it's far too late for such
a deception to help us now.
Have you gone
completely crazy?
[MICHELLE] They're so
perceptive, I'm sure they'd
figure it out instantly!
And I'd hate for anything
to happen to you on my account.
Please, don't try to be a hero!
She's not bad,
but her performance
is a little over-the-top.
Yeah. She's really into it.
So beautiful! So manly!
I tell you, I'm
Lucy Heartfilia!
Don't listen
to her, I'm Lucy!
[COCO] Now what?
[SUGARBOY] Mhmmm.
The real Lucy
Heartfilia is supposed to
be over twenty years
old, ain't that right?
[SUGARBOY] Isn't Pigtails
a little on the young side?
That's because
we spent seven years
sealed away on an island!
[NATSU] Lucy, get back!
I'll make sure they
don't lay a finger on ya!
Right, because I'm Lucy!
Uhhh...
You mean her
name's Lucy, too?
You ready for
another round, Lucy?
[LAKI] Yep! Let's do this!
[COCO, MARY, AND SUGARBOY]
What's goin' on here?
Can you stand up
on your own, Lucy?
Yeah, I think so.
Just take it
easy for a bit.
There's another one?
Wow. I don't believe it.
How wonderful.
I can't tell which
is the real one!
What are we gonna do?
[COCO] Come on!
[MARY] This is so stupid!
Is your magic
back too, Lucy?
Yep, fresh as a daisy, Lucy!
The Devil in Disguise.
Game over, I'm Lucy!
No you're not!
They're totes annoying.
Why don't we just
capture the lot of 'em
and sort 'em out later?
[SUGARBOY] C'mon, hound dogs!
Your captive audience
wants an encore!
[NATSU] They're
not goin' anywhere!
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame!
Lucy! Leave now!
No.
Let's go! He's distracting them.
[MICHELLE] This is our
chance to slip away unnoticed!
[LUCY] Guys, I'm sorry!
And thank you.
Ya see that Coco?
We got runners.
Fetch 'em for me.
On it!
We're just gettin' started!
[power yells]
Free Run: Unlock!
[LEVY] She's airborne!
Eight, nine, nine,
and ten points!
[MACAO] What'd she do?
[LEVY] It looked like Free Run!
[WAKABA] It's a special
athletic magic.
It was banned 'cause so many
wizards got hurt usin' it.
I'll weigh her down.
Solid Script!
[LEVY] Iron!
[MARY] Nope.
Sand Slash!
Wood Make: Violent Approach!
[SUGARBOY] Uh-huh.
I gotta decline, baby.
Sand and wood aren't a
good match for my 'lil pups.
We didn't even faze it!
It's just too strong!
On the other hand, you
could walk a mile in my shoes.
What's your star sign?
It's no fun being lonely.
Huh?
[MICHELLE] They don't seem
to be following us, so I think
we should start trying to find
out where your master went.
[LUCY] Yeah, good idea.
But first, you wanna
tell me what that
crazy stunt
back there was about?
You were in danger. I was
only trying to help you out.
[LUCY] I'm a Celestial
Wizard, Michelle.
If they had caught me, I would
have been able to defend myself.
But what would
you have done if they
managed to take
you away instead?
[MICHELLE] I-- I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I didn't really
think that far ahead.
I just did what I thought
would be the most helpful.
I didn't mean to
cause you any trouble.
[LUCY] It's okay,
I'm not angry!
No need for the waterworks!
[LUCY] Actually,
it meant a lot.
Even if it was a bit dramatic.
Thanks for protecting me.
I owe you one.
You're welcome!
[LUCY] Dramatic's
an understatement.
But, then again, I'm pretty
sure I was the same way
when I first
joined Fairy Tail.
[LUCY] I did
some crazy things.
But everyone always went
with it and made it work out.
[LUCY] It'd be unfair if
I didn't do the same for her.
[LUCY] While we're here,
help me brainstorm.
What do these creeps want?
[MICHELLE] Do you think
they're the scoundrels
behind the church fires
like Kinana suspected?
[LUCY] Maybe but
I'm not a part of that.
It doesn't add up.
[LUCY AND MICHELLE] Huh?
I finally caught up with you!
You won't get away again!
[LUCY] Coco's gone coo-coo!
Follow my lead. We got this.
'Kay.
Just in time, I was
holding her for you!
I'm tired of running, so here's
the real Lucy Heartfilia.
No, wait.
Don't let her
fool you like that.
She's the honest to
goodness Lucy in the flesh.
What?
Real Lucy, you're so naughty!
I can't believe you'd
lie to save your own skin.
Oh, don't be silly!
You're the really real one!
[LUCY] Okay, you got me. I've
been lying this whole time.
I really am the
really real Lucy!
[MICHELLE] Or so you'd
think! But you're wrong!
'Cause in reality I'm
really the really real
Lucy Heartfilia, so there!
[COCO] I can't.
Brain not working.
Don't listen to them.
I'm the real Princess
you're searching for.
[Lucy squeal]
Hey, what are you doing
here, "Princess"?
Helping you get out of this
sticky situation, of course.
What's with all
the "Princess" talk?
Do you mean Lucy?
You're exactly right.
I'm the real Princess,
so take me away.
Then again, I might
be Lucy after all.
Or has it been me
from the very beginning?
[ALL THREE] The truth is you've
been Lucy this entire time!
I can't take this!
That should keep her
busy for a little while.
Let's hope so!
Yeah, but I can't help
feeling kinda guilty,
ya know what I mean?
[SUGARBOY] It's
now or never, baby!
Unless you want my hounds
to keep lovin' you tender,
you'll tell me where I
can find Lucy Heartfilia.
[Pantherlily power yell]
[SUGARBOY] Mhm. Your Mode Change
almost caught me off guard.
Lucky for me
I've seen it before.
What?
[NATSU] It's not me, I swear!
Beast Arm.
You're pissin' me off!
It's totes hard to fight with
all of these control spells!
Hey, "totes" is
my word, chump!
So, like, find your own slang!
Like, learn to
fight fair instead of
using live
boogers and a stick!
Let's get this
show on the road.
I gotta feelin' that
Coco's chasin' after
the real deal Lucy.
[MARY] Ya hear that, poser?
Your friend is
totes as good as ours.
We're not lettin'
you get away.
You're funny.
You aren't gonna have
any choice in the matter.
My Conducting Art
lets me control anyone!
There ain't no way I ain't
ever let you control me!
Natsu's in big trouble, Carla!
You should worry
about yourself, child!
[MARY] Bring it home, puppet!
[JET] Who'd have thought Gajeel
would be so good at hiding?
[DROY] Watch, he's gonna
be back at the guild
relaxing with everybody else.
I was hoping we'd
find him on our own
so we could impress
Levy with our skills.
Just have to
try again tomorrow.
[citizens gasping]
[JET] What was that?
[DROY] Hey!
That's the guild hall!
[both gasp]
[DROY] What in the
world happened here?
[JET] Looks like
all hell broke loose!
[WENDY] Lucy! Michelle!
Where are you?
[CARLA] Even if they went
looking for the master,
we have no way of
knowing which way they went.
Has your nose picked
up anything? Even faint?
I'm sniffing
like crazy, but I can't
sniff them out
for some reason.
That she-witch!
Nobody uses me like their
own personal firecracker!
Nobody!
[HAPPY] You'd better calm down
unless you want me drop you.
[LEVY] Then
they both took off.
Natsu and Wendy went
after them a while ago.
We're pathetic. I can't
believe we let those
clowns take control
of us like that.
Yeah, there were
only three of them
and we were all
completely at their mercy.
Somehow I doubt we've
seen the last of them.
Huh?
[COCO] Get back here!
[PANTHERLILY] Coco?
[CARLA] Wendy!
Nine, eight, ten points!
This isn't some
kinda game, Coco!
You could have killed her!
[COCO] I've lost track of Lucy
so tell me where she's hiding!
Unless you'd like
to eat my foot again.
Oh, and while we're at it,
[COCO] I hate cats!
So please quit talking
like we're best friends.
[Coco echoed] I hate cats!
I hate cats! I hate cats!
Hey, Natsu. Can't you find
Lucy just by sniffin' her out?
No, I tried.
There's a real funky smell
that keeps gettin' in the way.
[NATSU] It smells a lot
like that weird stick thing!
[NATSU] Woah!
Natsu, down there!
It's Sugarboy!
Mhmmm.
♪ If you're
lonesome tonight, ♪
my hound dogs would
love to keep you company!
[NATSU] Bring it on!
I owe you for earlier!
Hope you're in the mood for
deep fried loogies, ya jerk!
[SUGARBOY] Hm, you're
so sweetly naïve, hot boy!
But I happen to hate sweet
food and sweet people,
so I'm afraid
this convo's over.
How does he feel about
people that have sweet names?
[BYRO] Sugarboy, you
mustn't let short-term matters
distract you from
the task at hand.
Where did that come from?
No clue.
[LUCY] I'm sorry, Virgo.
I think I broke it somehow.
[VIRGO] Don't worry.
I'm sure it was just
affected by the magic
that sealed you
away for seven years.
I'll return to the celestial
spirit world and try to fix it.
Please excuse me.
Hope to see you soon!
That was a Celestial Spirit?
Yeah! Plue and Virgo
are just a couple of
the ones I'm contracted with.
They both seem very nice.
How're the mermaid
and the crab?
[LUCY] How do you
know about those two?
[MICHELLE] Huh?
You told me about them,
don't you remember?
[LUCY] No, I don't.
[MARY] Well looky here.
It's, like, exactly how Samuel
calculated this would go down.
Color me impressed.
[LUCY] Hughes!
Dance, monkey, dance.
Hey, where are you going?
[MICHELLE] My legs. They're
moving all by themselves!
Stop, Michelle!
You're gonna fall!
[MICHELLE] Believe me.
That's the last thing
I wanna do right now!
[LUCY] Wait a minute, Hughes!
What happened to
taking us with you?
[Mary chuckling]
I figure you two
bimbos won't be able to
run away from me
if I injure you first.
[MICHELLE] Let go, big sister.
I don't want you to
get hurt because of me!
[Lucy struggling]
[BYRO] Have you found
Lucy Heartfilia yet?
[SUGARBOY] I think the
little chickadee will be
ours momentarily, Lord Byro.
[NATSU] Byro?
He's the creepy
dwarf who tried to
drain me and Wendy's
magic in Edolas!
[HAPPY] He's an octopus?
[NATSU] Earth Land Byro is
nothing like the Edolas one.
Now don't be a fool, hot boy!
Lord Byro's the one standing
on top of the octopus!
Huh? On top of it?
[NATSU AND HAPPY] He's way
different than the other guy!
We're here to
obtain the Heartfilia girl,
not play with
this boy and his cat.
Eliminate them at once.
When you're done, return to
the mission at hand, or else.
[SUGARBOY] You
got it, boss man!
[MICHELLE] Lucy,
please! Save yourself!
[LUCY] That's not happening!
I'm gonna stick with you!
[MARY] I'm likin' this
friendship thing you got goin'.
It saves me the
trouble of having to
control you at the same time.
[Lucy and Michelle screaming]
[CLOSING CREDITS]
[HAPPY] Man, those
guys whooped us pretty hard.
[NATSU] Whatever, they'd
be a piece of cake
if I was takin'
things seriously.
[HAPPY] Huh? Then why
aren't you serious now?
[NATSU] Uh, 'cause it's
way cooler to beat 'em up
when everything
looks hopeless! Duh.
[HAPPY] You say that but
you're seriously having
a tough fight, aren't you?
[NATSU] No way!
I'm just holdin' back!
[HAPPY] Natsu. You're
starting to sweat.
[HAPPY AND NATSU] Next Time:
The Fury of Legion!
[NATSU] I'm tellin' you, I could
win this with my arms tied!
[HAPPY] You'll feel a
lot better if you just
admit the truth, Natsu.
[NATSU] Would you
quit talkin' to me
like you know everything?