[WENDY] Thanks.
I needed a haircut.
[LUCY] Well, I'm glad to help!
I don't have the scissor
skills of Cancer.
But it doesn't take much to
make you look super cute.
[WENDY]
Aw.
That's sweet of you to say.
You made an absolutely
perfect afternoon like this,
feel even better!
[LUCY] Yeah, today is
pretty darn perfect, isn't it?
So quiet and peaceful!
[CARLA] We'd better soak
it all in while we can,
because peace never
lasts long in this guild.
[LUCY] C'mon,
we're not that bad.
[NATSU]
Hey!
[CARLA] You see?
[LUCY] Now, things still are
peaceful around here, Carla.
At least for the moment.
[snoring]
Happy.
No slacking!
Fish?
No, it's just you.
What do you
mean it's "just me"?
Oh don't be
so sensitive.
I was just having
the most amazing dream
about a super
humongous fish buffet
that went on as far
as the eye could see.
I think I'm gonna
go back to it.
No way!
What's the big deal, man?
[NATSU "The big deal" is
you're supposed
to be my partner!
Yeah, so?
Well, don't you see
that I'm doing all this
yard work over here?
Not laying around?
It is your turn.
Why should I care?
Because your partner
is working his tail off,
while you're dreaming
about stuffing your face!
That is so not cool!
[LUCY] Those guys
are so immature.
My, don't you
catch on quickly?
We're partners on
missions and stuff.
But stupid yard work is
a completely different thing.
What in the heck is the
matter with you, Happy?
How could you be so cold?
Oh please,
I am not cold.
No way!
'Cause, it's way
too nice today!
It's so warm and
sunshiney out here!
[GRAY] So what are
you two idiots
flapping your gums
about this time?
The work would
go a lot faster
if you didn't stop to
complain about it.
Who asked you, frostbite?
And for the record, I'm not
complaining about cleaning up.
I'm just sayin' that
cat should help!
[HAPPY] Are you enjoying
this nice weather, Carla?
[CARLA] Indeed I am.
[NATSU] You can't just walk
away while I'm talkin' to you!
[MAX] Whaddaya know.
It's been seven whole years and
Natsu hasn't changed one bit.
Still a brat.
[HAPPY] What, are
you surprised?
He's been that way
practically his entire life!
[NATSU] Are you tryin' to
say that you've changed?
I mean, obviously besides
getting older and stuff.
[MAX] Yeah.
I've gotten older
on the outside,
but I still feel pretty
young on the inside.
[GRAY] So what you're
trying to tell us
is that you're basically
just an immature old fart?
[MAX] If you want me to show
you my new skills, you're on!
[NATSU] Ha!
Bring it, ya'
dusty ol' geezer!
Let's throw
down right here!
Thought you'd
never ask!
[LUCY] Hey, wait!
You two are gonna
fight right now?
[GRAY] Sounds
like a plan to me.
It's perfect weather
for a little outdoor sparring
match, dontcha think?
Yeah!
Now I've got a fire in my belly!
[HAPPY]
And So We Aim for the Top!
Let's rock!
What?
Are you kiddin' me?
Do you seriously think
that we just sat around
and did nothing the whole
time you guys were gone?
We've all been working
on our fighting chops.
[WENDY]
I don't believe it.
[LUCY] Natsu is getting
schooled by Max?
[NATSU] Well it
ain't over yet, pal!
Sand Rebellion!
Now you're just
pissing me off!
[CARLA]
Do you mind?
Teach him
a lesson, Natsu!
Weren't you just arguing
with him a minute ago?
This has nothing
to do with all that!
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
Sand Wall!
I'm a whole lot stronger
than I used to be!
[VIJEETER] Max is
beating Natsu.
That is so crazy.
[WARREN] I never
thought I'd see the day.
Maybe this means that
we could beat him, too!
[NATSU] Lightning Flame
Dragon mode!
Holy cow!
Whoa!
I don't think
I'm ready for this.
Lightning
Flame Dragon Roar!
Oh wow!
Aw man!
I thought that would be like
a hundred times stronger!
[LUCY] When did
you figure out
you could use
that technique?
[NATSU] Just now.
That's awesome.
[MAX] Well...
That's it for me.
I give up, man.
Really wasn't planning
on getting killed today.
Which one of you
is next in line?
[WARREN] I'm good,
thanks though!
[VIJEETER]
Yeah, you win!
It makes sense that
an attack like that
would use up a lot of power.
You should probably
practice a bit more
before you pull that
one out in a real fight.
I never knew you were
such a good fighter, Max.
Thanks, but obviously I
still have a long way to go.
If everybody in the guild has
gotten that much more powerful,
why is it that you
let Twilight Ogre
bully you around
for so long?
It's a little bit more
complicated than that.
It was more of
a problem with cash flow.
You don't expect
us to settle our debts
with brute force,
do you?
But that's kinda how
master settled them, right?
Oh yeah.
[GRAY] Listen up, guys.
I'm afraid the guild has got
a serious problem on our hands.
What do you mean by that?
Gildarts and Laxus
are still powerhouses,
but no one else has
kept up strength-wise.
A lot of us were
asleep for seven years
while everyone
here was training.
Yeah, you've
got a point.
I mean, Natsu
came really close
to getting shown up
by Max, of all people.
You're right, and
he's really weak.
At least she was nice
enough not to say it to my face.
I wonder if
anyone knows a way
for us to give our magic
power a super fast boost.
Huh.
[PORLYUSICA] Scram!
Sorry to bother you,
ma'am.
But we were wondering
if you had any potions
that could help us.
Like maybe something that
can make us all a
million times stronger?
There's probably no
way it'd be that easy.
What's the
matter, child?
You seem upset.
[PORLYUSICA] You know
I hate people, so get lost!
Shoo! Shoo!
I've had enough
brooms already!
Sorry to bother you!
Why does she hate us?
Is it 'cause she and
Gramps used to date?
We weren't a couple,
you fool!
[MAKAROV]
The time has come, kids!
I've done all I can in
service to this guild.
Allow me to introduce
Fairy Tail's next master.
[CANA] You're really
stepping down?
[MACAO]
I'm honored.
And I'll do
my absolute best.
[WAKABA] It ain't
you, ya dimwit.
[MAKAROV] Without further ado,
the fifth master of Fairy Tail
Gildarts Clive!
Where the hell is Gildarts?
[MIRAJANE] I'm not sure,
but he left us a note.
[GILDARTS] "To Makarov
and all of my Fairy Tail family.
I'm sorry. Being master of
the guild just ain't my style."
[MAKAROV]
What?
[GILDARTS] "But, since I
have the rare opportunity
to be in charge for a bit,
there are two things I
want to get done."
[GILDARTS] "First, I
hereby reinstate Laxus
as a member
of Fairy Tail."
[MAKAROV]
He's got some kinda nerve.
[LAXUS]
No way.
[BIXLOW] Welcome back
to the fold, old buddy!
[EVERGREEN]
This is wonderful!
The Thunder Legion is back!
[LAXUS]
Yeah, that's true.
I guess.
[FRIED] Thank you, Gildarts.
This is a blessed day!
[MAKAROV] Well, if that is the
master's wish, then so be it.
[GILDARTS]
"And second...
I hereby appoint Makarov Dreyar
as Fairy Tail's sixth master."
[MAKAROV] But I just retired!
[ALZACK] I guess you could say
things have come full circle.
[BISCA]
It works for me!
[ASCA] Old mustache
man's in charge!
[BISCA] And that's a very
good thing for us, sweetheart.
[GILDARTS] "It's time for
me to hit the road again.
But don't worry.
I'll come back around
when the mood strikes me.
Take care, everybody."
[MIRAJANE]
And this is for you.
[GILDARTS]
"To my dear Cana.
I'm sure you probably
think I'm being selfish.
And maybe you're right.
But if you ever need me, just
use this card to get in touch.
I'll come running back as
fast as I can, I promise."
[CANA] Are you
freakin' kidding me?
[ERZA] Cana!
[CANA] I told you I'm just
fine with the way things were.
Ya deadbeat dad!
[GILDARTS] "Fairy Tail will
always be my true home,
that will never change.
And I believe
with all my heart,
that we'll be the
number one guild in Fiore
by the time I return.
But getting us back on top
isn't my responsibility.
It's up to you guys.
Makarov. That will be
your final task as master.
I'm counting on you
to bring Fairy Tail
back to its former glory."
What does that lumbering
fool mean my "final task"?
After the stunt he pulled, I'll
never let anyone else be master!
I'll be this damn guild's
master til the day I die!
Somebody pour me a
drink! That's an order!
[MIRAJANE]
Of course, sir!
[WAKABA] He'll be in
a rotten mood for a while.
[MACAO] Well, at least
we got all that settled.
[ELFMAN]
What a man!
[MAX]
Wow, Elfman.
Who would've
guessed you'd say that?
[GILDARTS]
"And master...
I won't tell anyone about what's
down in the basement.
You have my word."
[MAKAROV] You'd
better not, bonehead.
[LUCY] Hey, whose
brilliant idea was it
to visit Porlyusica
in the first place?
[HAPPY]
Yours, genius.
[GRAY] And she's usually
so sweet and charming.
[CARLA] I'd always heard
she wasn't fond of people,
but I never expected all that.
[HAPPY] Apparently, she's
not too keen on cats either.
[GRAY] Why are
you crying, Wendy?
Did that old lady
scare you?
[LUCY] Hey!
It's gonna be okay.
[NATSU] That witch
made Wendy cry?
She'll pay for that!
[WENDY] It's not like that.
She's just so familiar.
[NATSU] What?
[CARLA] Have you two met before?
[WENDY] I don't really know
how to explain it, exactly.
It sounds strange
but it's the truth.
Her voice and her scent.
They're so much like Grandine's.
[WARREN] Gildarts
is out of his mind.
He thinks we can be
Fiore's number one guild?
[MAX] It's gonna
take a miracle
to make something
like that happen.
[ERZA] I don't
think it's impossible.
Besides, we should
rise to the challenge.
[WARREN] That's
a pretty tall order.
[MAX] Yeah.
Things are
different these days.
[ALZACK] Sabertooth
would be tough to beat.
[BISCA] Not to mention
that even the Lamia Scale
and Blue Pegasus
guilds have gotten
way more powerful in
the past seven years.
[ASCA] All of them
are super awesome!
[VIJEETER] We are a lot
better off now that
we have some of our major
players back in action.
[LAKI] But the fact of
the matter is you guys
are still seven years
behind everybody else.
[JET] [DROY]
Don't worry Levy,
you'll always be
number one in our book!
[MACAO]
You gotta admit,
that's a substantial
training gap.
[WAKABA] Whether you're talking
about individual strength,
or even the guild's
overall power,
we still have
a long way to go.
[ERZA] I see your point.
Seems it'll take a
good amount of time
and training to
reclaim our standing.
[ROMEO] I waited for you
guys for seven whole years!
I'm sick and tired of waiting
for something to happen!
[MACAO] Romeo!
[ROMEO] There's totally a way
for us to be number one again.
You all know what it is!
[WARREN] What?
[NAB] No way, kid.
[MAX] Come on.
[MACAO] No!
Didn't I tell
you we would never
take part in
that thing again?
[MAKAROV] And what might this
"thing" be, Fourth Master?
[MACAO] I'd appreciate it
if you didn't call
me that, Sixth Master.
[GRAY] Are you tryin' to
tell us she's Grandine?
[LUCY] How could
a regular person
have the same voice
and scent as a dragon?
Is that really
even possible?
I haven't the foggiest.
Yeah, Wendy.
Whaddaya mean?
I don't know.
But she's so familiar.
It's confusing.
She sounds and smells
exactly like my mother,
the Sky Dragon Grandine.
[NATSU] I say we go back there
and ask her what's goin' on.
[GRAY] Wait, Natsu.
If she's the human
version of Grandine,
there are a few things
that don't add up.
Just think about
it for a second.
[LUCY] Well, first of all,
both of your dragons
vanished without
a trace at the same time.
And don't forget, the dragon
that raised Gajeel
also disappeared
on the exact same day.
[LUCY] All in the year 777,
which was fourteen years ago.
But Master Makarov has known
Porlyusica way longer than that.
They were friends back when
they were both fairly young.
So that means she and Grandine
were around at the same time.
It just doesn't add up.
I wish it could be true,
but there's no way that
they could be one and the same.
[GRAY] I guess
that counts out
any kind of reincarnation
or transformation.
Yeah.
[WENDY] Y'know, when you stop
and explain it all like that,
it really doesn't
make any sense.
Besides her voice
and the way she smells,
her attitude is
completely different.
[CARLA] From all the stories
that you've told me,
your dragon was actually
quite kind to people.
Wait a second.
Ya think maybe it's
because she hates cats?
[WENDY] Grandine was nice.
She didn't hate anybody.
[GRAY] Sorry, but
it's kinda hard for me
to picture a nice dragon.
Especially after
our run-in with Acnologia.
Igneel was
usually pretty nice!
[PORLYUSICA] I'm sorry if
my attitude offends you!
[LUCY] Ms. Porlyusica!
[GRAY] You scared
the crap outta me.
[PORLYUSICA] There's really
no use in hiding it anymore,
so I might as well
tell you my big secret.
[PORLYUSICA] I know it's
not what you want to hear,
but I'm not the
dragon that you seek.
I'm just a human being,
same as you.
[NATSU] But why do you
hate humans so much?
[PORLYUSICA] Because they
ask too many stupid questions!
Sorry.
I'm afraid that I can't tell
you where your dragon is.
I simply don't know.
The fact of the matter is,
we have no direct
connection whatsoever.
[LUCY] Then how do you
explain your similarities?
[PORLYUSICA]
You're familiar with
the alternate world
of Edolas, are you not?
Rumor has it that
you've been there.
I've heard that you even
met your counterparts.
Saw how our worlds correlate.
[GRAY] How do you
know about Edolas?
[LUCY] I think I get it.
[NATSU] Wait. Hold on.
[CARLA] Oh my.
[PORLYUSICA] Every living
being in Earth Land
has a counterpart
there, including dragons.
So one could argue
that I am the Edolas version
of your friend Grandine.
I am not from this world.
But I found myself here
several decades ago.
[EVERYONE] What?
You're the Edolas Grandine?
[HAPPY] Like a human
version of a dragon?
[PORLYUSICA] I was
disoriented when I arrived
but Makarov
came to my aid.
The peacefulness and beauty
that I discovered here
quickly endeared me
to Earth Land.
So even though I had
several opportunities
to return to Edolas.
I had made the decision to
call your world my new home.
[NATSU] Does this mean
that Igneel and Metallicana
have human versions
back in Edolas, too?
Maybe they crossed over
just like you did!
[PORLYUSICA] I have no idea.
I've never encountered them.
However, I did have the chance
to speak with the Sky Dragon.
[WENDY] Huh?
[PORLYUSICA] Although we didn't
meet in a traditional sense.
It was more mysterious.
She spoke directly into my mind,
by way of telepathy.
You originally came here seeking
out a means to gain power.
I may be able to help
Wendy in that regard.
But only her.
The Sky Dragon dictated this
book of spells to me.
It contains, among other
things, the Sky Dragon spells
"Milky Way" and
"Shattering Light: Sky Drill".
Two Dragon Slayer secret arts
she never got a
chance to teach you.
[WENDY] I don't
know what to say.
Grandine really did this?
She asked me to give it to you
should you ever come to visit.
Those are powerful spells.
Extremely dangerous.
So be sure to
exercise great caution.
[WENDY] Thank you so
much, Ms. Porlyusica!
[WENDY] Ms. Grandine!
[ROMEO] We're gonna
do it this time.
You're not the
master anymore, dad!
[MACAO] Well neither are
you, you little rug-rat!
[MACAO] I absolutely
forbid it!
We're never gonna get involved
with that thing again, ya hear?
[NATSU] Yo guys,
we're home!
[MAX] Hey.
So how did it go?
Did you guys pick up
anything worthwhile?
[LUCY] Well, Wendy
sure did.
[ROMEO] You don't make the rules
anymore, so just get over it!
It's up to Makarov.
[MACAO] I'm expressing myself
as a member of the guild!
[GRAY] What's all the
fuss about this time?
[CARLA] Seems like typical
teenage rebellion to me.
Clothing, Gray!
[MACAO] Those of you
with me, say Aye!
[EVERYONE]
Aye!
I don't ever wanna go
through that crap again.
[BISCA] That has got to be
the most embarrassing
thing in the world.
[ROMEO] But we've got the
Tenrou Team with us this time!
Natsu and Erza and
all those guys!
There's no way we're gonna
lose with them on our side!
[WARREN] Haven't you
been paying attention?
They all missed out on
seven years of training!
[DROY] You're awesome Levy,
don't listen to those jerks.
[NATSU] So what exactly
are we talking
about doing or not doing
here anyway?
[ROMEO] While you guys were
all stuck on Tenrou Island,
a tournament started
to determine Fiore's
number one guild.
[HAPPY] Ooh!
[NATSU] Sounds like a
whole lotta fun to me!
[ROMEO] Guilds from all
over the country
face off against each
other in magic events.
[ROMEO] They call it.
The Grand Magic Games!
[NATSU] Oh yeah!
[LUCY] That sounds
totally amazing!
[WENDY] Yeah, I'd love
to play some games!
[GRAY] So it's more like
a kind of magic festival?
[ERZA] I understand.
Sabertooth is known as the
top guild in Fiore these days
because they won
the last go-round.
[ROMEO] That's right.
But if we can beat them and
win the games this time,
we'll be number
one instead!
[EVERYONE] Oh!
[MAKAROV] That would be nice.
But I'm not
entirely convinced
we could win given our
current state of disarray.
[MACAO] That's my
point exactly!
[ROMEO] Yeah, but if we do
win, the guild will get, like,
thirty million jewel
in prize money!
[MAKAROV] We're in!
[MACAO] Seriously?
[DROY] But master, it's
gonna be really hard!
[WARREN] There are tons
of powerful guilds
that compete each year.
[JET] And don't forget
that we've come in
dead freakin' last every single
time we've entered.
[ELFMAN] That is just pitiful.
[MAKAROV] Well this year
we'll just have to beat
all those other guilds to
a pulp!
[NATSU] Sabertooth thinks
they're hot stuff?
We'll just see about that!
[JET] Put a cork
in it!
[NATSU] So when does this
thing go down, anyway?
[ROMEO] It kicks off
in three months!
[NATSU] That's
plenty of time!
But we have to start
training ASAP.
We'll put Fairy Tail
back on top.
And nobody's gonna get
in our way!
[GRAY] Let's go!
[LUCY] Yeah!
And if all of us start
working together as a guild.
[ERZA] There will be no
stopping us.
[WENDY] I'd better start
studying these new spells
Grandine wanted me
to learn, huh?
[HAPPY] It's about time we
got a chance to cut loose!
[CARLA] It seems like this guild
is always looking to party.
[ELFMAN] Fight party!
This is gonna be
so freaking manly!
[CANA] Gildarts may
get his wish.
We could be the top dogs
in Fiore again very soon.
[DROY] This is gonna suck.
[JET] Please tell
me you're joking.
[LEVY] Come on guys,
where's your team spirit?
[ALZACK] Um.
This is really not a good idea.
[BISCA] I don't think
you guys understand;
the games are not your typical
kind of fighting tournament.
[NATSU] Huh?
What do you mean by that?
[WARREN] It's absolute hell.
[MAKAROV] Now the final
decision has been made,
there's no need for all
this moaning and groaning!
So let's get to work!
Let's win that thirty
million jewel,
and the title of Fiore's
number one guild!
Fairy Tail is entering the
Grand Magic Games
and aiming for the top!
[EVERYONE]
Yeah!
[NATSU] We are going on
a mega training vacation
at the beach, and the
Celestial Spirit World!
[HAPPY] This is
gonna be so awesome!
I can't believe we're actually
gettin' to go to a
party in the sky!
[NATSU] We'll get to
hang out with the cow,
the crab, and the fluffy
chick, on their own turf.
[HAPPY] I bet there'll
be some Spirits
we've never even met before.
And like, a ton of
Plues everywhere!
[NATSU] [HAPPY] Next time: Song
of the Stars!
Hey Natsu, can you help me?
There's a creepy plue stuck
to me and it won't let go!
[NATSU] Aw, is he
your new best buddy?