- HEY, GUYS.  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
LYON WAS SCHEMING
TO REVIVE DELIORA
AND HE SENT HIS LACKEYS
TO DESTROY THE VILLAGE.
BUT I TOOK 'EM ALL DOWN.
- Lucy: YOU DID WHAT?
- Happy: LUCY'S FIGHTING
IT OUT AGAINST SHERRY
AND HER MARIONETTE MAGIC,
BUT SHE'S HAVING A HARD TIME
'CAUSE I'M NOT
THERE TO HELP HER OUT.
AND SHERRY WON'T SHUT UP
ABOUT LOVE.
- Lucy: WORST RECAP EVER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU WERE ABLE
TO CLOSE THE GATE
EVEN THOUGH I WAS IN CONTROL.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS
I'M STRONGER THAN YOU.
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF I WOULD TAKE IT THAT FAR.
REMEMBER, MY POWERS
ALLOW ME TO TAKE CONTROL
OVER ANY CELESTIAL SPIRIT
THAT YOU MIGHT CALL FOR.
- DON'T BE SO SURE.
I'VE GOT A FEW POWERFUL
SPIRITS UP MY SLEEVE.
- ( circus music plays )
- OPEN, GATE OF CANIS MINOR.
COME, NICHOLA.
- ( doorbell rings )
- ISN'T HE THE CUTEST
LITTLE THING?
OH, I'M IN LOVE.
- WOULD YOU QUIT TALKING
ABOUT LOVE ALL THE TIME?
'CAUSE IT'S
GETTING PRETTY OLD.
- WELL, SOMEONE'S BITTER.
MARIONETTE ATTACK!
NOW, YOU'RE MY PUPPET.
- HEY, PLUE?
NO, NOT YOU TOO!
- ( grunts )
- Happy: JUST DO WHATEVER.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME?
- I KNEW YOU'D FALL FOR THAT.
( strains )
( grunts )
- YOU DELIBERATELY
SUMMONED A WEAK SPIRIT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I KNEW THAT IF I CALLED FORTH
LITTLE PLUE HERE,
IT WOULD MAKE YOUR SPELL
TOTALLY POINTLESS.
JEEZ, I RELEASE
YOU FROM COMMAND.
- ( gasps, whimpers )
- OH, I KNOW
YOU DIDN'T MEAN IT.
NOW GO BACK, OKAY?
- MARIONETTE ATTACK!
GET HER, ROCK DOLL.
- WE'RE GONNA KEEP GOING
ROUND AND ROUND AREN'T WE?
I'LL STOP YOUR DOLL
WITH A SPIRIT,
YOU'LL TAKE CONTROL OF IT,
AND THEN I'LL CLOSE ITS GATE.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasping )
- ( groaning )
- IT'S LIKE WE'RE
PLAYING CAT AND MOUSE.
I LOVE THAT GAME.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO,
LITTLE MOUSE.
YOU THINK YOU CAN
BEAT MY ROCK DOLL?
- NOW I'M IN TROUBLE.
I DON'T THINK I HAVE A SPIRIT
STRONG ENOUGH TO
DESTROY THAT THING.
- ( groaning )
- ( screaming )
( pants )
( screams )
BAD!  BAD!  BAD!
OH, SO VERY BAD!
- DON'T LET HER GET AWAY,
ROCK DOLL.
LET'S TEACH THAT FOOLISH
LITTLE GIRL A LESSON.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A LITTLE GIRL?!
WE'RE THE SAME AGE.
I MIGHT EVEN BE A LITTLE OLDER!
- IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA
TO KEEP BABBLING LIKE THAT.
UNLESS YOU WANT US
TO CATCH YOU.
- OKAY, WHAT
SPIRIT DO I HAVE
THAT CAN HELP ME OUT
IN THIS SITUATION?
- ( buzzers sound )
- YOU'D BETTER HURRY.  IF YOU
DON'T START MOVING FASTER,
WE'RE GONNA
CATCH UP WITH YOU.
- ( screams )
( panting )
( screams )
- I COMMAND YOU
TO CRUSH HER FLAT.
- OW!
HOLD ON.
ISN'T THIS A...
A CLIFF?!
( screaming )
- FINISH HER, ROCK DOLL!
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
- ( laughing )
THERE'S NOWHERE
TO RUN, BLONDIE.
- THE SEA.
I COULD SUMMON AQUARIUS
FROM HERE.
- ( groaning )
- ( laughs )
IT LOOKS LIKE THE CAT'S FINALLY
GOING TO CATCH THE MOUSE.
- WATER CAN'T
DESTROY THAT THING.
BESIDES, AQUARIUS WOULD JUST
WASH ME AWAY WITH THEM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
- ( laughs )
I'M GOING TO CRUSH YOU
LIKE A LITTLE BUG.
SORRY, NO LOVE FOR YOU.
- WASH ME AWAY,
THAT'S IT.
OPEN, GATE OF
THE WATER BEARER.
- ( doorbell rings )
- AQUARIUS.
- AQUARIUS?
HOW DOES A WEAKLING LIKE YOU
HAVE A SPIRIT WITH
THAT KIND OF POWER?
- THAT GIRL IS OUR ENEMY.
YOU HATE HER KIND.
SO GO GET HER!
- ( scoffs )
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO DEAL WITH YOUR BAD ATTITUDE.
GET OVER THERE
AND TAKE HER DOWN.  NOW.
- WELL, I SEE YOU'RE JUST
AS ANNOYING AS EVER.
NO WONDER YOU STILL
DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
- JEEZ, WHY DO YOU KEEP
RUBBING IT IN LIKE THAT?
- MARIONETTE ATTACK!
YOU WILL NOW DO AS I COMMAND.
- WHAT?
- SHE'S UNDER MY SPELL,
SO SHE WON'T DO
YOUR BIDDING ANYMORE.
MIGHT AS WELL SEND HER BACK.
- NO WAY.
AQUARIUS IS STILL
MY ACE IN THE WHOLE.
- I BET YOU WON'T
STILL THINK THAT
WHEN THE SEA WASHES AWAY
YOUR PITIFUL EXISTENCE.
NOW, AQUARIUS, GET RID OF THIS
STUPID GIRL ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- WHAT?!
I WAS ALREADY
PLANNING ON IT!
( screams )
- ( screams )
- SAY GOOD-BYE, LITTLE--
UH...
( screams )
WAIT!
- ( both scream )
- ( smirks )
AND I THOUGHT
THE BLONDE GIRL WAS STUPID.
I CAN CLOSE MY OWN GATE,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BUH-BYE.
- ( weak laughter )
LEAVE IT TO AQUARIUS
TO HURL HER WAVES AGAINST
FRIEND AND FOE ALIKE.
- ( groans )
I HATE MYSELF FOR ALLOWING
YOU TO TRICK ME AGAIN.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
BECAUSE SHE WASN'T
STRONG ENOUGH
TO DESTROY MY ROCK DOLL.
- AND SO WHAT? THAT PUPPET
OF YOURS CAN'T DO ANYTHING
IF YOU'RE NOT THERE
TO CONTROL IT.
I KNEW THAT ALL I HAD TO DO WAS
GET YOU AWAY FROM THAT THING.
AND IT WORKED BECAUSE
NOW YOU'RE TOO DIZZY
TO EVEN WALK
IN A STRAIGHT LINE.
- ( both growl )
- THAT'S WHAT YOU
GET FOR MESSING
WITH A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE WE ENDED UP
IN A STALEMATE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, STALEMATE?
I'M OBVIOUSLY THE WINNER HERE.
- YOU CAN'T JUST
DECLARE YOURSELF
THE WINNER OF A FIGHT.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN I'M THE WINNER.
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- NO!
HOW'D THIS HAPPEN TO ME?
I NEVER LOSE.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU JUST DID...
TO A WIZARD FROM FAIRY TAIL.
- ALTHOUGH THE BURNING
FLAME OF MY LIFE
HAS BEEN EXTINGUISHED
FAR TOO SOON,
MY LOVE FOR YOU WILL
BLAZE ON ETERNALLY,
COLD EMPEROR.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE,
SO LET'S TONE DOWN
THE DRAMA, OKAY?
- ( gasps )
ANGELICA,
AVENGE YOUR
MASTER'S DEATH.
- HUH?
- BUT I THOUGHT THAT RAT
WAS ONE OF HER PUPPETS.
- ( screams )
- ( growls )
- I CAN'T MOVE MY LEGS
FOR SOME REASON.
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- ERZA!
WHOA.
I FORGOT.  SHE'S MAD AT US
BECAUSE WE BROKE GUILD RULES
AND TOOK AN S-CLASS REQUEST
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
- LUCY.
I ASSUME YOU KNOW
WHY I'M HERE.
YOU DO, DON'T YOU?
- TO TAKE US BACK?
PROMISE YOU WON'T HURT ME?
( echoing )
- ( laughs )
- HEY, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE OKAY.
I WAS WOR--
( gasps )
( whimpers )
- NOW WHERE IS NATSU?
- LISTEN.
I'M SORRY WE CAME HERE
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
BUT SOME REALLY AWFUL THINGS
HAVE BEEN HAPPENING
ON THIS ISLAND.
THERE'S THIS GUY
AND HIS MINIONS
WHO'RE TRYING TO
REVIVE A FROZEN DEMON.
AND THE ISLAND'S VILLAGERS
ARE SUFFERING
BECAUSE OF THIS MAGIC SPELL
THEY'RE USING.
THEY'VE TURNED INTO MONSTERS.
WE JUST THOUGHT THAT
IF WE WORKED TOGETHER,
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO HELP THEM.
- NONE OF THAT
IS MY CONCERN.
- PLEASE, ERZA,
LET US FINISH THIS JOB.
WE CAN'T LEAVE
THINGS THIS WAY.
( gasps )
- I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND.
THE THREE OF YOU HAVE
BETRAYED MASTER MAKAROV.
YOU'LL BE LUCKY IF YOU
WALK AWAY WITH YOUR LIVES.
- OKAY, NOW I'M SCARED.
- Gray: WHERE AM I?
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE AWAKE.
- WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- IT'S A STORAGE AREA THAT'S
NOT TOO FAR FROM THE VILLAGE.
EVERYTHING WAS DESTROYED
IN THE ATTACK LAST NIGHT.
SO WE DECIDED
TO COME HERE FOR SHELTER.
- THE WHOLE VILLAGE?
THAT'S HORRIBLE.
- THEN DESTROY THE VILLAGE.
- YES, SIR.
- UNDERSTOOD.
- IT'S A SHAME THERE HAS
TO BE BLOODSHED.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY ACTUALLY WENT AND DID IT.
- Boy: DAD, I'M HUNGRY.
- Girl: YEAH, ME TOO.
- Father: I KNOW.
- ( groans )
- YOU KNOW, IT WAS A MIRACLE
THAT NATSU AND LUCY WERE HERE.
THANKS TO THEIR BRAVERY,
EVERYBODY WAS ABLE
TO MAKE IT OUT ALIVE.
- SO ARE THEY STILL
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE?
- YES, THEY ACTUALLY WANTED ME
TO SHOW YOU TO THEIR TENT
ONCE YOU'D
FINALLY WOKEN UP.
- WHICH TENT?
- THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU
IN THAT BIG ONE
RIGHT OVER THERE.
- YOU MADE ME WAIT.
NOT SMART.
- ERZA!
WHY ARE THEY TIED UP?
- LUCY'S GOT ME UP TO SPEED
WITH EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SENT HERE TO STOP NATSU
AND THESE TWO FOOLS.
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
I'M DISAPPOINTED.
- WHERE IS HE, ANYWAY?
- THAT'S SOMETHING
WE'D ALL LIKE TO KNOW.
- THE LAST TIME I SAW HIM,
HE WAS FIGHTING AGAINST
THE COLD EMPEROR'S LACKEYS.
BUT WHEN WE WENT BACK
TO WHERE THE VILLAGE WAS,
THERE WASN'T ANY SIGN OF HIM.
WHEREVER HE IS,
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
ANYWAY, SINCE WE
COULDN'T FIND HIM,
ERZA DEMANDED THAT
WE TAKE HER TO YOU,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
WHERE YOU ENDED UP.
- SO I DID SOME SCOUTING
FROM THE AIR.
AND FROM UP THERE,
I COULD SEE THAT THE VILLAGERS
HAD MOVED INTO
THIS STORAGE AREA.
- OKAY, WE'RE GOING
TO SEARCH FOR NATSU
AND THEN WE'RE GOING BACK
TO THE GUILD.
- BUT WE CAN'T LEAVE
THE ISLAND JUST YET.
IF LUCY FILLED YOU IN,
THEN YOU KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT THESE VILLAGERS
ARE GOING THROUGH RIGHT NOW.
- AND WHAT WOULD
BE YOUR POINT?
- ( yawning )
MAN, I FINALLY COME UP
WITH THE PERFECT PLAN
AND THEN
I GO AND OVERSLEEP.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S DO THIS.
- I CAME HERE SOLELY
TO APPREHEND THESE FOOLS
FOR BREAKING
THE RULES OF THE GUILD.
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN ANYTHING
OTHER THAN THAT.
- RULES?  HAVE YOU EVEN SEEN
WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO THE PEOPLE
ON THIS ISLAND?
- I HAVE.
- AND YOU'RE STILL
JUST GONNA
TURN YOUR BACK ON 'EM?
- THEIR REQUEST
IS POSTED ON THE BOARDS
OF EVERY GUILD HALL.
THE VILLAGERS WOULD BE
BETTER SERVED
BY WIZARDS WHO ARE CLEARED
FOR S-CLASS.
YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED.
- HOW CAN YOU
BE SO HEARTLESS?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- THAT'S NO WAY TO SPEAK
TO THE GREAT ERZA.
- YOU SUCK-UP.
- HAVE YOU CHOSEN TO DEFY
THE GUILD'S RULES AS WELL?
YOU'LL FACE
THE SAME PUNISHMENT.
- DO WHAT YOU MUST.
FOR ME, THERE'S NO OTHER
CHOICE TO BE MADE.
I CAN'T WALK AWAY
FROM WHAT I KNOW IS RIGHT.
I'M SEEING THIS
THROUGH TO THE END.
AND YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
- ( screams )
PLEASE DON'T GET MAD AT US.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY
CONTROL OVER GRAY!
- HE'S NOT FEELING
LIKE HIMSELF RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE HE LOST A FIGHT
TO HIS OLD FRIEND!
- ( both gasp )
- THESE EVENTS
ARE INTOLERABLE.
WE'LL DEAL WITH THE IMMEDIATE
PROBLEMS FOR NOW.
- Both:
THANK YOU.
- THIS DOESN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING.
YOU'RE STILL GOING
TO FACE PUNISHMENT.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HOW PATHETIC.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
STILL STANDING, TOBY.
- ( groans )
- THOSE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS,
THEY'RE QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
- ( screams )
HEY, CAN WE KEEP THAT WHOLE
SHOCKING-MYSELF THING A SECRET?
- THIS UNFORTUNATE
TURN OF EVENTS
COULD PUT THE RESURRECTION
OF DELIORA IN JEOPARDY.
- ZALTI, YOU'RE
STEALTHY AS EVER.
- IF ALL GOES AS PLANNED,
THE DEMON SHOULD AWAKEN
AT SOME POINT TONIGHT.
BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP AN EYE
ON THOSE WIZARDS.
IF THEY WERE TO INTERRUPT
THE MOON DRIP CEREMONY,
THEN DELIORA WOULD
FOREVER REMAIN ENTOMBED IN ICE.
SALAMANDER AND TITANIA
ARE QUITE POWERFUL.
THEY COULD EASILY
FOIL OUR PLANS.
- AS ALWAYS, YOU SEEM
REMARKABLY WELL INFORMED.
NO MIND.
I CAN'T SAY I'M WORRIED.
THOSE FOOLS MAY BE STRONG,
BUT THEY'RE NO MATCH FOR ME.
- I WAS HOPING
YOU'D SAY THAT.
SO IT'S VERY
REASSURING TO HEAR.
BUT STILL,
ALLOW ME THE HONOR
OF JOINING YOU IN BATTLE
FOR OLD TIME'S SAKE.
- HOLD UP, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE A WIZARD TOO.
- YES, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE USED IT.
BUT I'VE DABBLED IN
A PARTICULAR FORM OF LOST MAGIC.
- SURE.  WE COULD USE
ANOTHER WIZARD.
- ( rumbling )
- IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE!
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- IT'S ALL COMING DOWN.
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
- WHAT IS
THE MEANING OF THIS?
- ( shivers )
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN SALAMANDER
WOULD MAKE THE FIRST MOVE.
IT APPEARS WE HAVE
A VISITOR, SIR.
- ( laughs )
YOU KNOW, I USUALLY END UP
BREAKING STUFF BY ACCIDENT.
IT'S KIND OF FUNNY
HOW HARD IT IS
WHEN I'M TRYING
TO DO IT ON PURPOSE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I'M KNOCKING
THIS PLACE OVER.
THEN YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO SHINE MOONLIGHT
ON THAT DEMON
YOU'VE GOT UNDERGROUND.
- ( rumbling )
- INSOLENT FOOL.
JUST WHO DO
YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU DARE CHALLENGE ME?
- OKAY, WOULD SOMEONE PLEASE
EXPLAIN WHAT'S GOING ON?
BECAUSE I'M LOST.
- EVIDENTLY, THIS BOY
IS THE REASON THE TEMPLE
IS NOW TILTED.
I ASSUME THAT HE DESTROYED
THE SUPPORT PILLARS ON ONE SIDE.
DOING SO CAUSED THE TEMPLE
TO SHIFT IN THAT DIRECTION.
THIS, IN TURN,
WILL PREVENT
ANY MOONLIGHT FROM SHINING
DIRECTLY ONTO DELIORA.
IT'S AN INGENIOUS PLAN.
I'M ACTUALLY QUITE SURPRISED
THAT DOLT WAS THE ONE
WHO CAME UP WITH IT.
- SO YOU'RE GONNA
FIGHT ME OR WHAT?
- FLAMES SHOOT
FROM HIS FEET?
- WHEN WE FOUGHT THAT GUY,
HE WAS ABLE TO SHOOT FIRE
FROM ALL OVER HIS BODY.
- ( screams )
WHAT THE-- HE'S FAKE?
- ICE MAKE: EAGLE.
YOU CAN'T DODGE THEM
IN MIDAIR.
WHAT KIND OF RIDICULOUS
MAGIC IS THIS?
- FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
HUH?
( yelps )
- VERY FORTUNATE,
COLD EMPEROR.
LUCK IS ON YOUR SIDE.
- CAN WE KEEP THE WHOLE
TOBY-GOT-CHARRED THING
A SECRET TOO?
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
- WHATEVER DO YOU MEAN?
- DON'T PLAY DUMB WITH ME.
YOUR MAGIC HAD TO HAVE
CAUSED THAT HOLE IN THE FLOOR.
- DON'T YOU HAVE
EVER THE WATCHFUL EYE?
PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO EXPLAIN MY ACTIONS, SIR.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
STRONG ENOUGH TO DEFEAT DELIORA.
SO IT'S IMPERATIVE
THAT YOU REMAIN SAFE
UNTIL ITS RESURRECTION.
- ARE YOU SUGGESTING
THAT I COULD FALL VICTIM
TO SUCH PALTRY MAGIC?
LEAVE ME.
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF THIS MYSELF.
ONCE I FINALLY
DEFEAT THE DEMON,
EVERYONE WILL
WORSHIP MY NAME,
COLD EMPEROR LYON.
I'VE WORKED TOO HARD TO LET
A BRAT LIKE HIM TARNISH IT.
- AS YOU WISH.
- SO YOU WANT TO
TRY TO DEFEAT DELIORA?
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
HE SERIOUSLY WANTS
TO FIGHT THAT DEMON?
- THE THING LOOKS
HALF-DEAD ALREADY.
SO LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
TO MELT THAT ICE
JUST SO YOU CAN FIGHT IT?
THAT'S PRETTY MESSED UP
IF YOU ASK ME.
- I MUST RISE ABOVE
UR'S LEGACY.
I WILL NOT REST UNTIL
I'VE FULFILLED MY DREAM.
- WHY GO THIS FAR?
CAN'T YOU JUST CHALLENGE HER
AND BE DONE WITH IT?
- WELL, I WOULD IF I COULD,
BUT UR HAS BEEN DEAD FOR YEARS.
- Gray: THE WOMAN WHO TAUGHT ME
HOW TO USE MY MAGIC,
MY MASTER UR, SACRIFICED
EVERYTHING TO SEAL IT AWAY.
- I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT SHE ENDED UP DYING
WHEN SHE SEALED IT.
- YES.
BUT SHE'D STILL BE ALIVE
IF IT WASN'T FOR GRAY!
- ( grunts )
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU IN THE PAST,
BUT I DO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING IN THE PRESENT.
AND IT'S HURTING
A LOT OF INNOCENT PEOPLE.
AND SINCE YOU DON'T SEEM
TO REALIZE THAT YOURSELF,
I'LL HAVE TO KNOCK
SOME SENSE INTO YOU.
- Gray: EVEN BACK
WHEN WE WERE KIDS,
LYON'S ALWAYS DREAMED OF
SURPASSING UR'S MAGIC ABILITY.
BUT SINCE SHE'S GONE AND
HE CAN'T CHALLENGE HER DIRECTLY,
HE'S DECIDED THAT IT'S UP TO HIM
TO KILL DELIORA
'CAUSE IT'S THE ONE THING
THAT SHE COULDN'T DO.
- WELL, YEAH.  I GUESS
THAT'D BE THE ONLY WAY
TO CHALLENGE SOMEONE WHO'S DEAD.
- AYE.
- LISTEN, THERE'S SOMETHING--
SOMETHING I NEVER
GOT TO TELL HIM.
I KEPT IT SECRET.
UR MADE ME PROMISE
TO NEVER LET HIM KNOW.
BUT I HAVE TO.
UR MAY NOT BE WITH US,
BUT SHE'S STILL ALIVE.
- ( all gasp )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- PROFESSOR HAPPY'S CLASS
ABOUT FAIRY TAIL.
TODAY I'M GONNA
LET YOU GUYS IN
ON A COUPLE OF MY SECRETS.
I'M A WIZARD WHO
PRACTICES AERA MAGIC,
WHICH GIVES ME
THE ABILITY TO FLY.
I CAN ALSO SPEAK
JUST LIKE A HUMAN
EVEN THOUGH I'M A CAT.
AND BEFORE YOU
EVEN BOTHER ASKING,
YES, I AM A CAT.  YAY!
OH, YEAH, AND MY FAVORITE FOOD
IN THE WORLD IS FISH.
WELL, THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED!  AYE!
- Natsu: SO GRAY'S MASTER UR
WAS THE ONE WHO
SEALED AWAY DELIORA, RIGHT?
- AYE.
AND SHE WAS ALSO THE WIZARD
WHO TAUGHT HIM ALL
THE COOL ICE MAGIC
THAT HE USES.
- WOW.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
AN AWESOME TEACHER
IF SHE WAS ABLE TO TEACH
A MORON LIKE HIM ANYTHING.
- ALL THIS TALK
MAKES ME WONDER
WHAT HE WAS LIKE BEFORE
HE JOINED THE GUILD.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Natsu: DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO KNOW WHAT HE WAS LIKE
BEFORE FAIRY TAIL?
- Happy: IT'D BE NICE
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT HIM,
LIKE WHY HE STRIPS ALL THE TIME.
- UGH, I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.