[KYOKA]
I will.
And your spirit will
always be by my side.
Hold on, who told her she could
just absorb Seilah's life force?
I mean, how much energy
did she have left?
She coulda shared some.
After all, that's my technique.
The Faces are about to detonate!
Any ideas on what
we should do?
We're gonna stop
them, of course.
Destroy Kyoka.
She's the last Demon Gate and
all that Tartaros has left!
I know you can do it, Erza.
[BOTH]
I will.
I swear, I will stop the Faces.
I swear, I will destroy
the Fairy Tail guild.
[ERZA yelling]
You will not prevail!
You're too late, darling.
Then prove it!
Be safe. Please.
[FRANMALTH whimpering]
[KYOKA yelling]
She's a sight to behold.
Make her cry, Erza!
[HAPPY]
Mira? Are you okay?
[MIRAJANE]
I'll make it.
I think Lisanna and Elfman
were looking for ya,
didja get to see 'em or--?
They're fighting the most
obnoxious foe we've faced.
Lucky us.
You all right?
Yeah, but what just happened?
Whoa. Look over there!
It's the enemy!
[LUMMYS laughing]
[LUMMY A]
Tsaa!
[LUMMY B]
Doon!
So freaky!
So scary!
Have any idea what
they're trying to say?
[ELFMAN]
Dude, you're the psychic.
[LISANNA]
Make it stop.
[JET, DROY screaming]
So, does your guild have
any hot boys or what?
Yeah, what do you think
you're lookin' at?
First the ears, now she
can multiply like a bunny.
[LUMMYS laughing]
That's Seilah.
[LUMMYS screaming]
We can handle this,
go after that one.
And make sure to
send her our regards.
Do you think they need backup?
No, they should be fine.
They're with Jet,
Droy, and Warren.
Guess Warren can
use Droy as a shield
while he screams in everyone's
head that Jet ran away.
[KYOKA chuckles]
I'm glad you made it, Erza.
I was hoping I'd get
to finish you off myself.
[rumbling]
What is this?
[KYOKA gasps]
I don't like it.
It sounds like an earthquake.
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
I'm nervous.
Uhh, I'm sure it's nothin' pal.
Don't forget to pick me up
if you have to run, Kyoka!
I know this is hard on you.
Do you wanna take a break?
I'm fine.
Tartaros' base is in pieces.
Doesn't look like that
fight's been going too badly.
[WENDY] Yeah, but wasn't
everyone inside of it?
They're all okay, aren't they?
Wendy!
[heart beating]
Say something! What's wrong?
Talk to me, Wendy!
Hang in there!
[rumbling]
That's not the wind I hear.
He's fading. It was bad
already, but now...
[NATSU]
You crazy idiot.
You pushed yourself too far!
True enough, but he got us this.
Now we can cure everyone.
[LUCY]
Demon blood.
That's right.
Take it to Porlyusica,
Levy, see what she can do.
I'm on it. Be back
as soon as I can.
Hopefully she's with the others.
So, um, have you seen Gray?
Yeah, but to be honest,
I could barely recognize him.
Whaddaya mean by that?
[GAJEEL]
He's powered up somehow. A lot.
You'd have to see it.
He's got this frozen aura around
him that chilled me to the bone.
What's happening to
the Bane Particles?
[JUVIA]
Please forgive me, my darling.
It was all for
your sake. I swear.
[SILVER]
You released me. Thank you.
[JUVIA]
Sir, I...
[SILVER]
That's quite a day, kiddo.
You ended my suffering and saved
all the magic in the world.
[JUVIA]
I don't know what to say.
[SILVER]
You don't need to say anything.
Just take care of my boy.
I wonder what happened to him.
No idea, he didn't stick
around long enough to say.
He's hunting.
So do ya think we
should go after him?
Hey, what is it?
Something wrong?
[GAJEEL]
He's prob'ly just freakin' out
'cause he knows the next
time him and Gray fight,
he's gonna get
handed a new one.
Gajeel.
[GAJEEL]
Hm?
You can hear it too, right?
[GAJEEL]
Huh?
[distant howling]
[gasps]
That growling.
[distant growling]
[GAJEEL gasps]
[LEVY gasps]
What's up?
[gasps]
[howling]
Now that's a sound.
Kinda unsettling.
Yeah, it is.
I certainly didn't
expect him to show up.
One can only plan so far.
[LUMMYS laughing]
[CROWD chattering]
[GRAY gasps]
[HAPPY whimpers]
Was he attracted by
the concentration of power?
Or does he know?
Perhaps he comes to find Zeref.
That sound! There's
no mistaking it!
[roaring]
[NATSU]
It's Acnologia!
[IGNEEL]
So, the time has come at last.
[ACNOLOGIA growling]
[roars]
Acnologia's here!
That's him?
he thing that took out
Tenrou? No way. It can't be!
Just 'cause you won't look
doesn't mean it isn't here!
First Master! Save us! Please!
We don't stand a chance.
We barely made it
last time. What now?
Acnologia.
A dragon?
[FROSCH whines]
[CARLA]
C'mon, Wendy! Snap out of it!
Please! You're scaring me!
[heart beating]
[CARLA whimpers]
It can't be.
[DORANBOLT]
No. He's coming.
[gasps]
[heart beating]
[NATSU groaning]
Natsu?
Are you gonna be okay?
What's wrong?
[LEVY]
You're hurt too?
It's because they're
Dragon Slayers.
Their bodies are
reacting to Acnologia.
Natsu. Gajeel.
I wonder.
Just what does his
arrival foretell?
It's quite the quandary.
Not even I can say.
[growls]
[roaring]
He's here!
He'll eat us!
What do we do? We can't
fight that thing!
We sure can't.
He'll roast us alive!
He will if we give up now.
But I don't plan to. Not ever!
[ACNOLOGIA roaring]
[WIZARD A]
Everyone run!
[WIZARD C] Don't clump up,
it gives him a target!
[WIZARD B] Make sure
we have all the wounded!
[WIZARD D]
Find shelter wherever you can!
[VIJEETER]
He looks mad.
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[roaring]
[CROWD screaming]
[ROMEO]
This is crazy.
[WAKABA] He can do that much
damage just by flying by?
[MACAO]
I think we may be done for!
We're all gonna die.
We gave it all we had, but how
are we supposed to beat this?
Damn it!
I think I see it now.
You've come for E.N.D.
To hunt him down.
[roaring]
[MARD GEER] Then it's fear
that cracks your whip.
You know that once he's been
reborn, he'll be unstoppable.
So you'll kill him now,
before he grows.
[MARD GEER]
How amusing.
[groaning]
[GAJEEL groaning]
[IGNEEL]
Natsu.
It's been too long, my boy.
[NATSU gasps]
[LUCY]
Huh?
Igneel?
[IGNEEL] It must be
you who defeats E.N.D.
But I have absolute faith
you're up to the task.
[NATSU]
Igneel.
How can I hear your voice?
[gasps]
Igneel?
No one else is here.
Who're you talking to?
[IGNEEL] Fear not.
I will deal with Acnologia.
[NATSU gasps]
[LUCY whimpers]
[NATSU screaming]
[NATSU laughing]
[MIRAJANE]
When he was a little boy,
a dragon found him
wandering the forest.
He took Natsu in
and taught him all about
language, culture, and magic.
But...
[LUCY gasping]
[NATSU groaning]
[NATSU]
Why, Dad?
Why'd you go 'n why
didn't you take me?
[groaning]
He's not gone.
He'd never leave me!
Not on purpose! No!
I'll find him.
One of these days.
[NATSU screaming]
[LUCY yelps]
[IGNEEL] I'm sorry, son,
but I never did leave you.
[IGNEEL]
In fact,
I've been closer than you
ever could've guessed.
[IGNEEL] Please trust that
all will be explained in time.
Right now,
I must wipe the blight of
Acnologia from this world!
[IGNEEL]
Fight, Natsu! Fight to live!
[roaring]
I'm dreaming. I have to be.
[NATSU crying]
You're back.
[LUCY] Igneel,
King of the Fire Dragons,
rises up to stop Acnologia
and his wings of darkness.
We humans can do
nothing but stare in awe
at a battle that goes far
beyond our comprehension.
Till Natsu jumps into the
fray, his fists giving voice
to emotions far too
strong for words.
Once again, a promise is made
between father and son.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Fire Dragon Iron Fist."
His flames will burn
away the darkness.