[NARRATOR] It all
happened on this day.
December sixteenth,
seven-hundred-and-eighty-four.
On Tenrou Island.
♪
[deep, booming sound]
[MAKAROV] That ungodly sound.
What could it be?
[ERZA] Master.
The ship will be ready to
take us back to the mainland
very shortly.
Also, regarding Laxus...
[MAKAROV] I've nothing to
discuss with or about that boy.
[ERZA] Yes, I understand.
Except to say, he's
got quite a pair on him.
Daring to set foot on The Fairy
Tail guild's most sacred ground.
He no longer enjoys
that privilege.
But what he's
done for us.
Yes.
I heard all about his
heroic fight with Hades.
How he saved your lives
by putting himself
directly into harm's way.
My appreciation for
what he did is more than
words could convey.
But as far as
Fairy Tail's concerned
he is still an outsider.
Albeit one to whom
we owe our gratitude.
So your position
is firm, is it?
[LAXUS] Of course it is.
That's how the guild's stayed
strong over the years.
You can't buy your way
in with a single good deed;
it takes a lot more.
[ERZA] That's true.
You guys
were in a jam.
So I did what any decent
passing stranger should do
and tried
to help out.
There wasn't any
kind of ulterior motive
behind my actions.
[LAXUS] Hey, old man!
Yeah, that's the look.
Classic.
Probably the last time
I'll see that scowling face
for a long while.
Later.
Hold on!
[deep, booming sound]
No.
[CANA] What's up?
Is something the matter?
God I hope not.
Something seems off.
Smells off,
that's for sure.
There's a strange odor.
Whoa, that
reminds me.
Maybe somethin' yummy
will settle your tummy.
That sound and smell
have nothing to do
with my tummy, cat!
[HAPPY] Let's hold hands!
Will somebody feed
Lucy so her belly
will stop rumblin' for a while?
The Lucy in Edolas
had a big appetite,
but this is crazy!
You shouldn't
listen to Gajeel,
he's just being his usual
"big-time-jerk" self.
Oh dear, I hope that
there's still enough
food left to tide her over
'til we get back home.
Geez!
Don't ya know a joke
when ya hear one?
Yeah.
Well, all kidding aside.
What in the heck
was that noise?
Whoa!
Now it sounds like there's some
kinda animal-in-heat panting.
The latter could
possibly be the sound
of your chair.
My chair?
Is it squeaking
or somethin'?
What the-?.
What're you doing?
You won't spank me, so serving
as your chair should be
a fitting punishment
for my failure
I almost smacked you
for scaring me,
but I'm afraid you'd
get the wrong idea!
Here ya go, I bet
you're pretty thirsty.
You don't have
to do all that
when you're not
feeling well.
It's fine.
Helping out makes
me feel better.
Workin' through
the pain!
Just like a real man!
[CARLA] I don't think so!
Please tell me that ya
didn't mean to do that!
Oh, I meant
it alright.
And if I hear you say "real
man" in the next five minutes
you're gonna be
turned to stone!
[ELFMAN] Why do you care?
[EVERGREEN] It's
driving me crazy!
[ELFMAN] Oh yeah?
Well that's an awfully
short trip for you, ya know?
[EVERGREEN] A real man would
never talk that way to a lady!
[MIRAJANE] You two
shouldn't fight so close
to your wedding day!
[ELFMAN and EVERGREEN]
That was a lie!
[thunderous roar]
What is that?
It sure is manly!
That's definitely
a dragon's roar!
A dragon?
Are you sure it's
not a thunderstorm?
[LUCY] Hey,
is everyone all right?
[HAPPY] Do you guys
hear that crazy noise?
Yeah, What is it?
[CANA] Are You okay?
My wounds are startin'
to burn like hell.
There's no doubt.
That dragon...
he's gettin' real close.
Look up in the sky!
Something's coming this way!
[HAPPY] Natsu!.
What's the matter?
Holy crap!
That thing's humongous!
Oh, no.
It is a dragon!
I don't believe it.
You gotta be kiddin'!
I don't think
it's a friendly one.
I knew it.
I was right all along.
They still exist.
[MAKAROV] I'm afraid
that's Acnologia.
The black dragon
of the apocalypse.
Yeah.
It's definitely him.
That sounds bad.
What the heck are we gonna do?
[NATSU] Hey, dragon!.
You know where
I can find Igneel?
Tell me!
Grandeeneh and
Metallicana, too!
[GILDARTS] Stop it, Natsu!
You don't wanna provoke him!
Did you forget
what happened to me?
How I lost my arm and my leg?
Hell!
I'm lucky I didn't
lose my life that day!
[GILDARTS] Natsu look at me.
It was over before
I even knew what hit me.
It ripped off my arm
and leg, and gutted me.
[GILDARTS] Igneel may be
a different kind of creature,
but I'm telling you this black
one is no friend to anyone.
There's not a man
that could beat him.
It's coming down!
[HAPPY] I don't think this
is the same kinda dragon
that raised Natsu and Wendy!
This one seems evil!
[GILDARTS] You're certainly
right about that!
It's the most
evil thing there is!
[NATSU] So are we gonna
fight it, or what?
We can't, Natsu.
You don't understand
the situation.
It's not about winning
or losing a fight.
This is about
getting away with our lives.
And I'm not sure that
all of us are even gonna be
lucky enough to do that.
[NATSU] Whaddaya mean?
Are you tryin' to say that this
thing's gonna kill some of us?
Come on.
Everyone run, now!
What's it doing?
No way.
[NATSU] I don't believe it.
The entire forest has
completely disappeared!
[ELFMAN] That's crazy.
[LEVY] How can it
be so destructive?
It wiped out those trees
with just a single roar!
How strong is that thing?
Not just strong.
He's evil.
Pure and simple.
That just now was
nothin' more than
his way of gettin' warmed up.
Listen up!
If you wanna stay alive!
You can't waste time
freakin' out!
Pull yourselves together
and let's get outta here.
Are you okay, dear?
Hurry!
Everyone get to the ship!
It's this way!
Just through those trees!
Now get moving!
Wendy!
You know how to communicate
with dragons, don't you?
Can you talk to it for us?
Anyone can communicate
with a dragon,
but this one didn't
come here to talk to us!
[PANTHERLILY] He's attacking!
No, Fried!
Bixlow!
He cut off our
escape route!
But, why us?
Why are you doing this?
Answer me!
[ZEREF] He refuses
to speak to them.
Which means he views them
as nothing more than insects.
Men don't engage
vermin in conversation.
This is no different.
And men certainly
don't battle pests the same
as actual threats.
Those poor souls don't
have a prayer of surviving.
[EVERGREEN] Elfman!
[ERZA] Be careful!
[ZEREF] Mankind
will soon learn who's
at the top of the food chain.
Ever.
Thank you.
[LEVY] No.
We're trapped.
What'll we do?
[ZEREF] It seems.
I find myself at the
crossroads once again.
At the end
of yet another era.
So farewell.
Natsu.
You jerk!
C'mon gramps!
[MAKAROV] Get to the ship!
[GRAY] He's crazy!
He can't fight that thing!
Master!
Please don't
play the hero!
The guild needs
you to stay alive!
[MAKAROV] Get out of here!
I will fight
by master's side!
No lizard is gonna
tear this guild apart!
I'll stay with you
'til the bitter end!
Me, too!
[EVERYONE agreeing]
Will you brats
just shut up and honor
your master's final wish?
Get out of here now!
[MIRAJANE] Final wish?
I am a Dragon
Slayer wizard, Gramps!
This is what I was born to do!
So let me--
[LAXUS] Not
today, kid!
Let go.
Laxus!
Best of luck.
Now, run!
[MAKAROV] What good children.
It may be hard to believe now,
but this is for the best.
It's times like these that
teach you important lessons
for your future.
Like knowing that tears
are wasteful things,
nothing to trouble over.
Is death caused by sadness?
Or is sadness caused by death?
The answer is in your hearts.
My dear children, you
must learn and grow, and live!
You foul creature!
I don't know
what your goal is here.
But I'm not letting
you get any further.
I won't let you
hurt my children!
This is what a father
does for his family.
I have no regrets.
I can die a happy man.
[NATSU] We're
getting gramps back.
ya hear me?
[MAKAROV] Natsu!
[MAKAROV]
Erza. You, too?
[LAXUS] I was down
with the plan to evacuate.
I'm sure there are plenty
of folks out there who'd let
an old guy take the fall.
But not your guild.
Now attack!
You damned
stupid bunch of kids.
[LAXUS] Alright, you guys!.
Let's get ready to hit
this overgrown lizard
with everything we've got!
[LAXUS] If you let loose
on him and I blast him
with a million
watts of lightning.
he'll learn to never mess
with Fairy Tail again!
[ALL] Laxus!
[WENDY] Please Be careful!
Laxus?
[LAXUS] You'd better
get out of the way Natsu,
'cause here it comes!
Hold on just
a second, man!
No, do it
now, Laxus
I haven't
moved yet!
Raging Bolt!
Heaven's Wheel.
Scattered Petals!
Super Freezing.
Arrow!
Water Nebula!
Solid Script: Fire!
Now Sagittarius!
Get him!
Evil Explosion!
We'll use the full
power of the Thunder Legion!
Come on, babies!
Time to Rock!
[LAXUS] Seriously?
We just totally unloaded on this
bastard and he's still smiling?
Let's see what you
Dragon Slayers can do!
You hear me, Natsu?
I still owe Laxus a
serious butt kickin'.
[HAPPY] Maybe later.
[GAJEEL] Iron Dragon.
Roar!
[WENDY] Sky Dragon.
[NATSU] Fire Dragon.
Roar!
[ERZA] Did that work?
[GILDARTS] Of course not.
What do you mean?
[GILDARTS] He's not even
using half as much power
as the time he fought me.
He's playing with us!
He's back
in the air!
All our attacks
didn't even
put a single
scratch on him!
His power's
unbelievable!
We gave it
everything we had.
Three Dragon Slayers
all at the same time.
Our whole guild went against
him, and it still wasn't enough.
This shouldn't happen!
I'm supposed to be
a freakin' Dragon Slayer,
so why the hell
couldn't I beat him?
[PANTHERLILY] What do
you think he'll do now?
Maybe he'll just
decide to go back home.
We can't let
down our guard.
Breath attack!
Is he gonna try and wipe
out the whole island?
My god.
He's that strong?
[LUCY] No.
Isn't there
anything we can do?
Is this it?
Are we all just
gonna die here?
Defense magic
users, bring out your
most powerful spells!
But I don't have time
to write an Enchantment!
Script magic has plenty
of other defensive spells
that we can use right now.
Yes, you're right, Levy!
Think of one real quick!
Everybody concentrate
all your magic power
on Fried and Levy!
Let's hold hands!
[NATSU] Come on, Lucy.
We are not gonna go out crying.
Fairy Tail never
gives up the fight!
We've gotta all face
our fears together!
We'll show him we have a bond
that can never be broken!
Okay, kids.
Let us all go home together!
[ALL] Back home to Fairy Tail!
I guess it's over now.
Natsu.
[NARRATOR] It all
happened on this day.
December sixteenth,
seven-hundred-and-eighty-four.
On Tenrou Island.
The day Acnologia
wiped it off the map.
His work completed.
he disappeared into
the wild blue yonder.
Search crews spent
nearly half a year scouring
the nearby waters for survivors.
Unfortunately,
none were ever found.
Time marches on.
And seven long years have
passed since that fateful day.
♪
[HAPPY] Natsu, what in the
heck happened to us out there?
[NATSU] I'm not sure.
I remember getting attacked by
that big, black dragon and then
seeing blinding white light.
[HAPPY] Do you
think it's possible
that we're all dead now?
[NATSU] Don't be ridiculous!
You and I both know
there's no way Fairy Tail
would ever go out like that!
[HAPPY] If we're all alive,
where is everybody?
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time: Fairy
Tail, year seven-ninety-one!
[NATSU] I don't know,
but we need to find 'em
and get back to the guild!
[HAPPY] Yeah, you're right.
Let's all go back
to Fairy Tail together!