[KAGURA] The man
whose will I speak of?
It turns out you
knew him very well.
His name was Simon
and Jellal killed him.
He was my brother.
[ERZA] Simon...
[ERZA] You're his sister?!
[ERZA] I can see
why you thought Jellal
was responsible for
your brother's death.
It would be easy to let you
go on believing that, but...
...I'm the one to blame.
[MAKAROV] I can feel
the bloodlust from here!
[screaming]
[CROWD chattering in awe]
I'm sorry, but I
can't afford to die here.
[NARRATOR]
After successfully defeating
the Hungry Wolf Knights,
Natsu and the others
came face to face
with another Lucy,
who had come from the future.
How did this Lucy manage
to travel back in time?
For what purpose?
What sort of future
has she come from?
And what does Princess Hisui
of Fiore hope to achieve
by opening the Eclipse
door and using its power
over the passages of time?
[NARRATOR] At this point,
everything remains
shrouded in mystery.
[HAPPY]
A Future Racing Toward Despair!
[NATSU]
Oh, come on! Another door?!
How many more 'exits'
are we gonna go through?
For that matter,
how do we know
we haven't been making
circles this whole time?
[WENDY]
There are wind drafts blowing
from almost every direction.
I can't tell
which one goes outside.
[LOKE] The big guy isn't
gonna last much longer...
If we could get in
touch with the others,
none of this would be a problem.
Just our luck.
I'd give anything to
hear Warren in my head,
and I don't say that very often.
We just have to hope
our luck will change
and keep looking
for a way out of here.
[PANTHERLILY]
And if it doesn't change,
we could all be stuck
wandering down here forever.
I'm sorry.
We wouldn't be stuck down here
if I was more acquainted
with the layout of the castle.
Hey, don't sweat it!
No one here blames you.
Whatever, let's just
keep on moving.
This place sure ain't helping
Future Lucy feel better.
[WENDY] You're right.
[LUCY] Forward... March!
[LOKE]
Hey Natsu, wanna trade wounded?
[HISUI] Believe me,
I completely understand
your apprehension.
I realize
how absurd it sounds.
We're deciding
the fate of this world
based on the
outcome of the games.
Truth be told,
I would prefer if we had more
time to study the situation
in detail.
[HISUI] The lives and futures
of everyone in this kingdom
hang in the balance.
And yet,
I have nothing
to base my decision on
but the word of a single person.
At first, I thought
they were insane
claiming to be from the future.
But as I began to listen,
the pieces came together.
And now, there is
just one more thing
that will validate
their predictions.
And if it comes to pass,
we will face certain doom.
I pray that their claims
will prove to be untrue,
or else calamity may
soon be at our doorstep.
[WENDY] How does it look, Lucy?
I think the coast
is clear. Let's go.
Right!
How do you think the
Grand Magic Games are going?
I'm sure our guys are
pulling their own weight.
Sucks that we're
down here missing it.
I bet it's a heck of a show.
[CROWD in awe]
But how did she block
Kagura's Archenemy?!
Don't know.
That can't be good.
Simon saved my life.
[ERZA] As did Grandpa Rob.
[ERZA] And so many
of my dear friends.
If I throw it all
away here and now,
I would dishonor everything
they've done for me.
[KAGURA]
Running away like Jellal?
Then I'll kill you both!
[shouting]
If that's what drives
your life, then so be it!
It's not my place to
tell you what to think or feel.
[ERZA] But I will not lose!
[CROWD cheering]
[MALE 186A] That was awesome!
[CHAPATI] It's Erza!
What incredible fortitude!
Despite being battered and
bruised, she turned the tables!
Most impressive!
[MATO] That was amazing!
She finally
unsheathed her sword.
And she still lost.
But how?
I can't believe it.
Well done!
Not even my eyes could keep up
with that quick attack!
[CHAPATI]
Kagura is getting back up!
Neither of them wants
to throw in the towel!
I will avenge him!
Look out!
Oh no...
But why?
[ERZA]
It's because I... remember...
Your face...
[ERZA]
I know you.
Not personally,
but we've at least met.
[ERZA] All I can recall
is meeting Simon's sister
on that night.
You... can't be...
It's true. Just like you.
I grew up in Rosemary Village.
[ERZA] I was there
when we lost everything.
[VILLAGERS screaming]
Grab all the children!
Slaughter any adults you find!
[YOUNG KAGURA] Big Brother!
Where are you?!
You've gotta hide or
they're gonna find you!
Let go! I have
to find my brother!
[MALE HUNTER 186A]
I heard some kids over there!
Let's go and check it out!
[YOUNG ERZA] Stay quiet.
But what about you?
[YOUNG ERZA] I'll be fine!
I'll find another spot!
Stay alive.
[MALE HUNTER 186A]
There! I found 'em!
[MALE HUNTER 186A] Grab her!
[KAGURA] You were the one...
[ERZA] Simon was
always talking about you,
hoping that you
were healthy and safe.
But he wasn't the
only one who worried.
I kept you in my
thoughts as well.
Even now.
[sobbing]
I need some time
to take all this in.
[KAGURA] For now, though,
I hand over this victory to...
[CROWD gasping]
[MINERVA]
You won this fight, Erza,
but the points
belong to yours truly.
[CHAPATI]
Minerva has struck down Kagura!
Sabertooth scores five points
for defeating a team leader!
That puts them ahead of
Fairy Tail by four points!
And with Erza badly
hurt on the battlefield,
Fairy Tail may lose
one of its best!
[MINERVA] Didn't I tell you?
This is the manner in
which a queen does battle.
A queen only
dines on delicacies,
such as the severed
head of a mermaid
with a wing-plucked
fairy for dessert.
How scrumptious.
[MINERVA laughing evilly]
You'll pay for that.
I'd like to see you make me,
especially when you're
so obviously wounded.
That'd be an amusing trick.
[KAGURA] Millianna... Please...
You have to... save her.
I will.
Who's Millianna?
Oh, the little kitten.
As you can see, she's
already down and out.
I believe I've
earned another point!
Sabertooth's total
just jumped to fifty-five!
[MATO] Fairy Tail keeps falling
further and further behind!
A five-point gap.
That'll be difficult
to come back from.
Please, talk to me!
Erzy? S'that you?
Stay with me! Millianna!
[ERZA] What the hell is this?
Frankly, the two of you
were beginning to bore me.
I needed to do something
to entertain myself.
Her screams were quite lovely.
Bad move.
They're both down.
This is horrible!
We gotta do something, quick!
They need medical help! Hurry!
[CHAPATI] All of
Mermaid Heel's competitors
are now out of the match,
leaving Erza and Minerva
to battle it out,
one on one!
[MATO] It'll be tough.
Erza's covered in
wounds from head to toe!
And Minerva's come out
of this as fresh as a daisy.
[CHAPATI] It's down to
the Queen of the Fairies
versus the Queen of the Tigers!
[NARRATOR] Erza and Minerva
aren't the only combatants
still in the final match.
While many have fallen,
there are other
intense wizard battles
erupting over every corner
of Fiore's capital city.
[groaning in pain]
[yelling]
Well, this got
boring in a hurry.
You're just wasting
my time, kid.
I'm outta here.
[ROGUE] You don't scare me.
You aren't even as
strong as Natsu Dragneel.
The hell you say?
'Lightning God Slayer'
Olga, s'that right?
Catchy name.
[OLGA chuckling]
Am I supposed to be
flattered or something?
Come on.
What? I thought all you
Saber-punks liked lip service.
I mean, with a name like that,
your lightning's gotta
be something to behold.
Sorry, but second-best
is all it's ever gonna be.
[OLGA]
Are you saying yours is best?
That's some bold talk,
coming from a Fairy.
There's always
someone better than you.
Having your face
shoved in the gravel
is a good way to learn that.
Bring it on!
Let's see whose
lightning comes out on top.
Grit your teeth!
'Cause here comes
the first strike!
What's the matter?
Don't tell me the great Laxus
is so terrified he can't move.
Come on, we both know
you weren't really gonna hit me.
You've got a lot to learn about
the art of intimidation, pal.
[yelling]
That was pretty impressive.
Now who's being flattering?
Are we doing this
sometime today?
I can't be stuck playing
grab ass out here forever.
[yelling]
[JURA] My, my...
I was hoping to come across
some capable warriors.
The Wizard Saint, Jura!
The monster's here...
This should be good.
I won't let you snare
Lyon with your wiles!
I told you,
I only have eyes for Gray!
[LYON] To think that she's
giving Shelia this much trouble.
That's my Juvia!
[GRAY] Man, Not this
crap again! Come on!
--[SHELIA] Hi, Lyon!
--[JUVIA] Darling!
What happened to you, Gray?
You're looking a little rough.
I was just taking care
of some unfinished business;
you know how it is.
Juvia.
Yes?
[GRAY]
Let's take 'em out together!
Let's take 'em out together.
[GRAY] Together, my love...
[GRAY]
We'll be together forever.
I've got just the spot
for our honeymoon, my darling.
What crazy nonsense
are you on about now?!
Damnit! I've got to bring
dear Juvia to her senses!
You're the one who needs
to come to his senses, Lyon.
This is so lame.
It's just one
maze after another.
It's quite a dilemma...
If I had only known
this was going to happen,
I could have memorized
the castle's floor plan.
You shouldn't feel bad.
Master Makarov and
the rest of the guild
must be worried sick by now,
so we need to get out quickly.
Aye.
We need to tell them
about the Eclipse
and the Lucy from
the future, too!
Why don't we
just charge through
all their soldiers
and be done with it?
We can't!
We have injured with us.
I bet the rest of us
could pull it off
if we work together!
No, there's more
to it than that.
Don't forget,
Fairy Tail's still competing
in the Grand Magic Games.
And it's a
kingdom-sponsored event.
If we go taking out
their Royal Army,
they might disqualify our
guild from the tournament.
Considering we took
out their execution squad,
it might be too late...
She does have a point.
Maybe we should have gone
a little easier on them...
I mean, when you take
time to think about it,
they weren't actually bad guys;
they were just doing their jobs.
Still, given the circumstances,
we didn't really
have another choice.
The fact of the matter is
that they were sent
down there to kill us...
I'd say just taking them
outta commission for a while
was going easy on 'em.
Hey there.
Don't look so worried;
it'll be fine.
Even if there
are two of you now,
I'm enough of a man to share
my love with both of you!
You're as clueless
as the tomcat...
[HAPPY] Hey, Lucy.
You feeling any better?
Where are we?
Not sure.
[MIRAJANE] It looks like
the castle's dining hall.
[FUTURE LUCY]
We're still inside the castle?
From what I
remember from last time,
after we escape
the Palace of Perdition,
we end up getting caught
by the royal army again.
That's why I rushed here
as soon as I was able to.
I was hoping that I could
warn you beforehand.
But luck abandoned me.
Just like it always does.
[FUTURE LUCY]
To make matters worse,
we're going to be stuck
behind bars until it happens.
[HAPPY] Whaddya mean "it"?
So these events are
in our immediate future?
Quite ominous indeed.
Don't be a downer!
Now that we know, there's
no way they'll catch us.
Yeah!
I can't see them
being a problem for us.
While we were making
our escape last time,
we got too close
to the Eclipse gate.
As a result, we lost
all of our magic power.
We were thrown into
a dungeon soon afterward.
Our future selves
sound like total morons.
So, uh...
What made you decide
to risk your life
and come here from the future?
For real.
What's this all about?
Why'd you come back
in the first place?
[FUTURE LUCY] To change
the horror that is my past.
[NATSU]
What happened that was so bad?
Tell us.
Maybe we can help,
and at least you won't
have to do it alone.
Okay...
I haven't disclosed
all the details to you yet.
It's almost too much
for me to comprehend.
Pure terror...
[HISUI] A swarm of over
ten thousand dragons
will assail the kingdom.
[DRAGONS roaring]
The city will burn,
the castle will fall,
and countless lives
will be lost.
Are those words true?
I don't know.
Regardless...
[HISUI] The decision rests
squarely on my shoulders.
And the echoes of
this one decision
will reverberate
throughout the rest of time.
[NATSU] Ten thousand dragons?!
I guess something serious
goes down in the future.
[HAPPY] What do we do, Natsu?!
[NATSU] Oh! Oh! Happy!
I just figured out
how we'll fix this!
[HAPPY] Yeah?
Well, forgive me,
but I don't have very high
hopes about your plan.
[NATSU] Just hear me out!
This is legit! Seriously!
The best plan ever!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Next time: Frog!
[HAPPY]
So tell me, whatcha thinkin'?!
[NATSU] I betcha the
dragons are super strong,
so I'll beat 'em up with
magic instead of my fists!
[HAPPY] How's that any
different than your usual plan?