[FRIED]
Uh!
Whoosh.
[screams]
[BIXLOW screams]
[EVERGREEN gasps, screams]
Whirr.
[YAJIMA gasps]
What is this guy?
Yajima, no!
[BIXLOW, FRIED grunt]
[BIXLOW, FRIED groans]
Ka-boom!
[screams]
[FRIED screams]
[YAJIMA groans]
Fwoosh.
[YAJIMA screams]
Mr. Yajima!
Fairy Machine Gun. Leprechaun!
You're helpless.
[CROWD shouts]
[EVERGREEN groaning]
Ever!
He creamed us.
[YAJIMA wheezes]
Who the hell are you?
[STRANGER]
I have no name.
Though humans
have a word for me.
They call me disaster.
A force of nature.
[BIXLOW grunting] What's with
his magic? I can't move!
And he's barely even touched us.
[STRANGER]
The netherworld gate has opened.
--Humanity will be judged.
--[YAJIMA groaning]
Netherworld gate?
He's from Tartaros.
No doubt about it.
[FRIED] So, that means
it wasn't just the nine.
They're going after former
members of the Council, as well.
But why? What could
Tartaros be after?
Say your prayers.
Let him go!
--[STRANGER] Too late.
--[YAJIMA screams]
Yajima!
[STRANGER growls]
[YAJIMA]
Uh.
[FRIED]
Uh!
[BIXLOW]
Mm.
[STRANGER]
[LAXUS] Those are my
pals you're messin' with.
If you thought you're
getting away with this,
you're in for a real shock.
'Bout time, Laxus!
[BIXLOW chuckles]
Now it's his turn.
This guy. Who is he?
He's with Tartaros! He
came here to kill Yajima!
That so?
[LAXUS grunts]
[STRANGER growls]
[STRANGER roars]
[gasps]
[STRANGER pants]
[LAXUS gasps]
He's not human!
[STRANGER growls]
Whoosh.
[STRANGER yells]
I missed?
[STRANGER roars]
[LAXUS grunts]
[TEMPESTER groans]
Stand still. Coward!
Is this still enough for ya?
[LAXUS]
Lightning Dragon Jaw!
Nicely done, Laxus!
I'll say!
No one's as manly as you.
[ELFMAN sneezes]
[LAXUS] So what should
we do with him now?
I'm all ears, Yajima.
Well, I would say
that we should take
him to the Council.
If there still
was one, that is.
The HQ's gone, sure,
but they've got other
outposts, don't they?
He has quite a few
questions to answer.
Why not take him
back to the guildhall?
Just leave him in
a room with me,
and I can guarantee he'll talk.
[EVERGREEN chuckles]
Moving along. They might've
gone after the current council
for any number of
reasons, but retirees?
I don't understand the motive.
Me neither.
Enhanced interrogation time?
Enough with the
sausage, okay?
[STRANGER groans] So, you're
with Fairy Tail, are you?
[BIXLOW, FRIED]
Uh?!
[EVERGREEN gasps]
[YAJIMA]
Hm?
[STRANGER] I misjudged you.
Never imagined I'd encounter
your kind of power
on the surface.
No matter though.
All I have to do is die.
Shut up. Nobody's
gonna die, all right?
[STRANGER] A great number
of people are about to die,
and we'll be the first.
[LAXUS]
Uh.
He blew up?
But why?
[BIXLOW, FRIED]
Uh!
Strange. He left
some sort of mist.
It looks like it's spreading.
[STRANGER]
Mankind cannot escape disaster.
[LAXUS]
Tsch.
[STRANGER] The mist is
rife with Bane Particles.
As it spreads, they will destroy
any ether-nano they can find.
But Ether-nano's inside
all living things! [coughs]
[YAJIMA coughs]
[STRANGER] Right you are.
Which is why this mist causes
Magic Deficiency Syndrome
and bane sickness.
[BIXLOW coughing]
[STRANGER] First, you'll
be stripped of your powers.
And then you'll be
stripped of your lives.
[BIXLOW choking]
[STRANGER] I would've
begun with this attack,
but, I have to go
back to Tartaros
and get reborn
every time I use it.
[LAXUS choking]
[STRANGER] That means I'll see
you soon. In the Netherworld.
[FRIED]
Try not to breathe it in!
[EVERGREEN]
It's everywhere. What do we do?
[BIXLOW] The whole town'll
be infected soon!
[YAJIMA]
We can't just stand around here!
Our only hope is to run for it!
[YAJIMA grunts]
[EVERGREEN]
Yajima! Hang in there!
[groans]
[FRIED grunts] Bixlow! Ever!
You have to resist!
[LAXUS] No one else is gonna
die here! Not while I'm around!
[FRIED]
Laxus, shield your mouth!
[LAXUS inhales]
[FRIED]
What are you doing?
[inhales]
[LAXUS inahaling]
[LAXUS] That's twice you've
misjudged me, "Disaster".
First, you underestimated
the strength of my magic.
Now you've done the
same with my lungs.
[FRIED] Please Stop.
You'll kill yourself!
[LAXUS inhales]
No way you're talkin'
me outta this,
but you can make sure
they get home safe.
[FRIED]
Laxus!
What happened to them?
Whatever it is, tell
me you can fix it!
They'll be okay! Won't they?
[PORLYUSICA]
They've been heavily exposed
to Bane Particles.
I'll do what I can.
But far smaller exposures
than theirs have proven
lethal in the past. Recovery is
possible, but not guaranteed.
Or even likely.
[panting]
[PORLYUSICA] Loxus's case is
many times worse than the rest.
It's a miracle he's
lasted this long.
[FRIED]
Master.
[ALL]
Uh?!
[FRIED grunting]
[MAKAROV]
I'm here.
Be proud, sir. Laxus
saved the whole town.
Mist...
Mist everywhere. Would've
killed us all. If he hadn't...
You'll tell me later.
You did well getting them back
home, now get some rest.
[gasps] So much poison, and
Laxus breathed all of it in.
So it wouldn't reach the town.
[MAKAROV]
Mm...
[LAXUS groans, pants]
[WIZARD 235A]
Quarantine in effect!
Keep your distance, the air here
is polluted with bane particles.
[WIZARD 235B] The west side
is especially contaminated.
No one gets in!
[WIZARD 235C]
Medic! Four new victims!
[WIZARD 235D] If it's
this bad for non-wizards,
what could it do to us?
[WIZARD 235E] Same thing. The
death toll's over a hundred now.
[WIZARD 235F] I don't get it.
What the hell happened here?
The people. They're fine,
aren't they?
They are safe?
[GRAY growls]
[LUCY]
Mm.
[ERZA grunts]
[NATSU growls]
Yeah.
Then it was worth it.
[ELFMAN growls]
[WENDY cries]
[ERZA] From the Gate of the
Netherworld, came Tartaros.
They're after former
Council members now.
Which means Jellal
will be a target.
This is awful.
[NATSU]
Well, Gramps.
You realize this means war.
Sorry for the trouble.
Thank you.
It's fine, Tempester.
No trouble at all.
Tempester. That's
my name, is it?
[KYOKA]
Yes.
[TEMPESTER] I'll forget it again
before this body is complete,
but no matter.
That name will mean nothing
to me in my next life.
How much longer until
I'm fully regenerated?
[KYOKA]
Under normal circumstances,
you'd be out of there in a day.
But there's another vat
in use at the moment.
This slows the process down.
Another vat you said. Was
someone else defeated as well?
So far, the others are fine.
It's my child in there.
[KYOKA] This is Minerva.
My demonic fledgling.
[FRANMALTH laughs]
Well I certainly hope
she doesn't come out
as screwed in the head as
that failure, Doriate, did! Ha!
Surely not.
That little mishap must've cost
this guild a little fortune!
[laughs]
[FRANMALTH] Putting Temphumpsty
Dumpsty back together again
isn't free either, by the way.
Hope ya had a good reason
for blasting off this time.
[TEMPESTER]
This I remember.
I was driven to it by
a Fairy Tail wizard.
I've heard of this guild.
Reyur! Something seems to have
your little lady riled up!
It's members stopped the guilds
of Brain and Hades both.
But they won't stop us.
[KYOKA chuckles]
Knowing that as I do,
I can't help but be excited.
This means war!
Oh, I'll thrash every last one
of those Tar-tar mother--
You don't wanna say that!
We all know what you're feelin'!
Then lemme go before I have
to bash your heads in!
Wish you'd made that
threat a bit sooner.
[NATSU] They hurt our friends,
so we hurt them!
Stop actin' like
it's complicated,
and help me kick their butts!
I'd like nothing better, Natsu,
but we don't have nearly
enough information yet.
They're called Tartaros.
But aside from that,
their objective, their location,
all of it's a mystery.
Listen to Erza, Natsu!
How do you expect us to
attack them right now if we
don't even know where
their base is?
I'll beat down some other dark
guilds and make them tell us!
Okay, and where exactly
are we gonna find these
other dark guilds?
How the heck would I know?!
You don't, so calm down
and help us make a plan!
[NATSU growls]
We do know on thing for sure.
They're targeting members
of the Magic Council.
And not just current
members, either.
Anyone who's been on
the Council is at risk.
Then all we gotta do
is hang out around
some former council members,
and Tartaros'll come to us.
A good plan. Problem is,
the addresses of all former
council members are kept secret.
How come?
The council's imprisoned
quite a few people,
most of whom
would like revenge.
Looks like yet another dead end.
[LOKE]
Actually, no. It's not.
[CANA]
Why's that?
I don't know where every
former council member lives,
but I can point you to a few.
Whoa, really?
How do you even find
out that kinda thing?
So I'm hot-tubbin'
with this librarian type:
stern in the streets,
crazed in the sheets.
--You know what I mean.
--[LUCY] Oh.
[PORLYUSICA] Hm. Thanks to
Loke's tramping around,
we have the addresses of four
retired council members.
We need to send a
team to each location.
Our main objective is to protect
these people from Tartaros.
But our second goal is
to find out everything
these wizards know about
the nature of Tartaros,
the whereabouts of other
former council-members,
and why they might've
been targeted.
Should you find the thing
that poisoned Laxus,
know that we need
a sample of its blood.
I won't be able to make
an antidote without it.
This is no time to be rash,
so avoid exposure at all costs!
[EVERGREEN whimpering]
Don't worry. I'll do whatever
it takes to make you well.
[LAXUS panting]
The jig's up. Fried told on you.
[BIXLOW groaning]
[MIRAJANE] Now we all know
what you did for those people.
You've come such a long way.
[LAXUS panting]
Rest up, ya hero.
You've certainly earned it.
Today, we go to war!
Our foe is a pillar
of the Baram Alliance.
As strong as Grimoire heart
and the Oración Seis.
But they should've learned
from their allies' mistakes.
For by the time
our work is done,
the bloodied remnants
of their guild
will look back on
this day and rue it.
For this is the day they made
an enemy of Fairy Tail.
They've attacked our brethren.
The pain they've caused
is mine and yours. The blood
they've spilt is our blood.
Now it is time for the
blood not shed to boil.
For our pain to feed
our burning rage.
Let us fight not for justice,
but for the thunder
in our souls.
I make this oath upon
the honor of our guild.
Fairy Tail will
destroy this foe!
[FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS cheer]
[MICHELLO]
Mm...
So if we may, we'd
like to stay around
for a little while
to protect you.
We'll keep ya safe.
So you should feed us well.
I appreciate the sentiment, but
frankly, you'd be a nuisance.
How did you find
where I live, anyway?
If you gotta problem, I'm sure
we can work it out cat-to-cat.
Who are you callin' a cat?
I know all about your
troublesome guild,
and I would like nothin'
to do with it.
Good luck. I hope
your plan succeeds.
But you'll have to find
someone else to use as bait!
Tartaros would've come for you
regardless of whether we showed
up to help or not, so I
wouldn't call you 'bait'.
Oh, and by the way,
you're welcome.
Think I'm stupid? Well I'm not
stupid enough to stick around
here after what
you just told me.
I'm gonna hit the bricks,
and don't follow me.
[MICHELIA] Hey! They came a
long way to see you, Grandpa.
Don't be rude.
[MICHELLO]
You're not my boss.
[WENDY] She's the one that
did the things with Loke!
We should do what
we can to help.
The entire council
was wiped out.
[MICHELLO]
Hmph.
You used to be a
part of that Council.
You can't just ignore
what happened!
[MICHELLO]
Mm...
Also, any guesses
as to why this guild
is targeting
council members?
Could be a number of reasons.
Council's ticked off
a lot of wizards.
More'n this old mind
can keep track of.
This isn't about some grudge.
Their process is too methodical.
They're doing this
to achieve a goal.
I'm Sorry, but I've no
idea what that might be.
No, wait. There is something.
Some awful thing.
Called "Face".
[LUCY, WENDY grunt]
[NATSU]
Uh! Everyone down!
[WENDY, LUCY grunt]
What is it?
That goes for you too!
--[MICHELIA screams]
--[MICHELLO grunts]
Get ready.
For what?
[NATSU grunts]
No! Please, not my
beautiful house!
--[LUCY groaning]
--I think we're under attack!
Is everybody okay?
--[HAPPY] Aye.
--[MICHELLO, LUCY, WENDY grunt]
That explosion was massive.
How are we alive?
[NATSU grunts] Haven't eaten
that fast since Tuesday.
[MICHELIA]
E-Eaten?
[belches]
Nice one!
[LUCY gasps]
[JACKAL]
And here I was,
thinkin' you'd be too
blown up to tell apart.
Who're you?
That's how it was with the
magic council. [laughs]
--[WENDY] Uh...
--[HAPPY, CARLA gasp]
You're with Tartaros, aren't ya?
[JACKAL]
Yeah. Who's askin'?
[NATSU]
Natsu of Fairy Tail.
Brace yourself.
I'm gonna hurt ya.
[LUCY] Jackal the demon Gate
is intent on killing Michello.
But thanks to Natsu,
his surprise attack failed.
Now Fairy Tail's pyro faces off
against Tartaros' bombardier,
while the rest of us take cover.
What is Tartaros' goal here?
Why are they hunting down
old members of the council?
And what about this "Face"
that Michello mentioned?
Why is he so scared of it?
Next time: Tartaros Chapter,
Prologue - The White Legacy
It will be the fireworks
show that started a war.