- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- Natsu: NATSU! - Wendy: WENDY!
- Gajeel: GAJEEL!
- Happy:
AND THE THREE OF THEM ARE--
- Gajeel: DRAGON SLAYERS!
- Wendy: THREE BEST FRIENDS!
- Natsu: FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS!
- Happy:
WOW, YOU GUYS REALLY NEED
TO GET YOUR ACT TOGETHER.
- Natsu: WHATEVER, WE WERE
TOGETHER ENOUGH
TO KICK THE KING'S BUTT!
- Wendy: EVERYTHING WORKED
OUT IN THE END.
- Gajeel:
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED TO MY CAT?!
- Lucy:
I HATE TO BUST YOUR BUBBLE,
BUT THINGS JUST GOT
A WHOLE LOT WORSE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTACY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP WITH
A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- LISTEN, THIS LOOKS BAD
BUT WE'VE GOT TO STAY COOL.
LET'S HEAD INTO THE ROYAL CITY
AND SEE WHAT'S UP FOR OURSELVES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
SEE WHAT?
- IT'S OUR FUTURE.
LET'S LOOK IT STRAIGHT
IN THE EYE.
- ( gasp )
- Mystogan:
TAKE ME BEFORE THE POPULACE
AND EXECUTE ME FOR MY CRIMES.
AS A CAPTAIN IN THE ROYAL ARMY
AND A MEMBER OF THE EXCEED RACE,
YOU CAN QUELL THE CHAOS.
BECOME THEIR SAVIOR!
YOU ARE THE RULER THEY NEED,
LEAD THE PEOPLE INTO A WORLD
WITHOUT MAGIC.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
THE ONLY WAY TO SAVE
THIS KINGDOM
IS FOR YOU TO DIE?
- ( Happy speaking )
- ( screaming )
- ( rumbling )
- YOU MAY THINK
THAT THIS IS MADNESS,
BUT IT'S OUR ONLY CHOICE.
- ( groans )
- BUT PRINCE,
THIS FOOLISH PLAN--
HOW COULD YOU ASK THIS OF ME?
- Pantherlily:
I SIMPLY CANNOT DO IT!
- Mystogan:
I THINK YOU CAN.
- THEN YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T KNOW ME.
- DESPITE THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE AN EXCEED,
YOU CHOSE TO SAVE THE LIFE
OF A HELPLESS HUMAN CHILD.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT LIFE HAS
VALUE FOR EVERY LIVING CREATURE,
REGARDLESS OF WHAT FORM
THEY TAKE.
- AND STILL YOU'D BURDEN ME?
MAKE ME CARRY THE WEIGHT
OF THIS WORLD ON MY SHOULDERS?
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD BEAR THAT WEIGHT.
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE.
AND I'M AFRAID THERE IS
NO OTHER WAY.
- YOU ARE PRINCE OF THIS WORLD.
THE ONE MOST SUITED TO RULE.
- I AM THE DESTROYER
OF THIS WORLD.
- YOU'VE TAKEN
EXTREME MEASURES TO SAVE IT.
YOU'RE EVEN WILLING TO PUT
YOUR OWN LIFE ON THE LINE.
WE NEED SOMEONE WITH THAT KIND
OF HEART TO TAKE THE HELM.
STEER US OUT OF THIS DARKNESS!
YOU CANNOT BREAK THIS WORLD,
AND THEN LEAVE IT TO OTHERS
TO PICK UP THE PIECES.
YOU MUST MAKE IT WHOLE AGAIN.
IT'S YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE IT IN DEATH!
- Mystogan: THIS STORM
CANNOT BE QUELLED BY ME.
- WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
TO US, MOMMY? I'M SCARED!
- WE'RE GOING TO BE OKAY,
I PROMISE WE WILL.
- ( running )
- COME ON, EVERYBODY.
JUST CALM DOWN!
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
IN A TIME LIKE THIS?
I'D START RUNNING NOW
IF I WERE YOU, LADY.
THIS PLACE IS HISTORY!
- IS HE SERIOUS?
- WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
- DADDY!
- OH, THERE YOU ARE!
- KEEP YOUR EYES ON YOUR KID,
OKAY?
- Pantherlily:
I'LL DO IT.
I WILL PLAY THE ROLE OF VILLAIN.
- ( explosion )
- THE WHOLE THING'S
BLOWN TO PIECES!
- OUR POOR, LITTLE HOUSE
IS GONE.
- NOW THE BOY HAS NO PLACE
TO COME HOME TO.
IT'S AN OUTRAGE!
AN OUTRAGE!
- Pantherlily: WHEN I
WAS EXILED BY MY HOMELAND,
THE KINGDOM TOOK ME IN.
BUT NOW, I'VE RUN AFOUL
OF THE KINGDOM AS WELL.
I'M A MAN WITH NOWHERE
TO CALL HOME.
IF I'M TO BE SACRIFICED,
THERE'S NO ONE TO MOURN ME.
- PLEASE, STOP.
YOU GAVE ME THE GIFT OF LIFE.
I COST YOU YOUR COUNTRY!
I CANNOT ASK YOU
TO SACRIFICE ANYMORE.
- I FEEL THE SAME AS YOU.
PLEASE, DO NOT THROW
YOUR LIFE AWAY.
MORE DEATH WILL ONLY LEAD
TO MORE SORROW.
AND MUCH MORE SUFFERING.
- PERHAPS.  THEN HOW DO YOU
SUGGEST WE MAKE THINGS RIGHT?
I'VE ONLY CAUSED MORE PAIN.
- PANTHERLILY, SIR.
THE SITUATION'S MUCH WORSE.
- I'M AWARE OF THAT.
AS YOU CAN SEE, WE'RE DEALING
WITH THE ANIMA, HERE.
- HAVE YOU STOPPED IT?
- NO, NOT EXACTLY.
- THERE'S BEEN MASSIVE RIOTING
IN THE ROYAL CITY.
THE DESTRUCTION IS BEYOND
OUR CONTROL.
- THE CHAOS IS FAR WORSE
THAN I HAD ANTICIPATED.
WE MUST DO WHAT WE CAN
TO STOP IT.
- Pantherlily: CONTROLLING THE
CROWD IS THE FIRST PRIORITY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. WE CANNOT
LET IT SPREAD. WE SHOULD GO.
- Soldier #1:
- UM, SIR?  WHO MIGHT HE BE?
- ( screaming )
- ( whispering )
- HOW MANY ARE THERE?
- Soldier #2:
THREE, SIR.
- AND YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN
THEM OUT?
EXPLAIN YOURSELF!
- Soldier #2: YES, SIR.
UH... THEY'RE REALLY STRONG.
- ( evil laughing )
- I AM THE DEMON
THEY CALL DRAGNEEL!
AND I'VE COME HERE TO THIS WORLD
TO STEAL ALL
OF YOUR MAGIC POWER!
- WHAT?!
- NATSU?
- Man #1:
OH, NO!  THIS IS HORRIBLE!
- Natsu:
HAVE YOU GONE INSANE, OTHER ME?!
NEVER MIND!
- ( evil laughing continues )
- FAUST AIN'T YOUR KING
ANYMORE!
'CAUSE I KICKED
HIS SORRY, OLD BUTT!
- ( evil laughing )
BUT I DECIDED TO SPARE
HIS LIFE, FOR NOW!
- YOUR MAJESTY!
- OH, NO!
- POOR KING FAUST!
- HOW DARE HE HURT HIM!
- COME ON, RED FOX.
HEY, MARVEL!
NOW, MY FAITHFUL SERVANTS,
IT'S TIME TO TRASH THE CITY!
- HE'S GOT A SWORD FOR AN ARM!
- IT'S ANOTHER DEMON!
- WE'RE DOOMED!
- THESE VILLAINS WON'T STOP
UNTIL THEY'VE DESTROYED
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT!
THE CITY IS UNDER ATTACK
BY DEMONS FROM ANOTHER WORLD!
- YOU BETTER RUN!
- UH...
- ( screaming )
- I'M SORRY.
- JUST LOOK AT THEM, THEY'RE
AN UNSTOPPABLE FORCE OF EVIL.
- ( chuckling )
- ( crowd murmuring )
- JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?  STOP THIS!
- NOW, MY LOYAL SERVANTS
OF LORD DRAGNEEL--
DON'T STOP DESTROYING STUFF!
- KEEP GOING
WITH THIS SERVANT CRAP
AND I'M COMING UP THERE FIRST.
- Natsu: JUST DO WHAT
I TELL YOU TO, SLAVE!
- I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE SPECIFIC.
- ( thinking)
HOLD ON.
- THEY'RE TO BLAME FOR THIS!
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO STOLE
EDOLAS' MAGIC POWER!
- IT'S ALL THAT
DRAGNEEL'S FAULT!
- Gajeel: THAT'S RIGHT, THE DARK
LORD DRAGNEEL'S THE BRAINS
BEHIND THE WHOLE OPERATION.
- UNFORGIVABLE!
- GIVE US OUR MAGIC BACK, NOW!
- BETTER BE CAREFUL,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU PLAY WITH FIRE.
- Man #2: OH, NO!
- Man #3: HE REALLY IS A DEMON!
- NATSU,
STOP THIS, NOW!
- HUH?
- IS SOMEBODY CHALLENGING HIM?
- HE'S OVER THERE,
IN THE CASTLE TOWER.
- DO YOU KNOW WHO IT IS?
- ( sighs )
- ARE YOU TELLING ME WHAT TO DO,
YOU LITTLE PUNK?
- STOP THIS FOOLISHNESS,
THE KING HAS BEEN DEFEATED.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO ATTACK INNOCENT PEOPLE.
- Natsu:
OH YEAH?
- NO, DON'T!
- IF YOU'RE TRYING TO SCARE ME,
IT AIN'T GOING TO WORK.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU ARE
THE PRINCE.
- HE'S THE PRINCE?
- COULD IT REALLY BE HIM?
- BUT THE PRINCE MYSTERIOUSLY
VANISHED SEVEN YEARS AGO.
PRINCE JELLAL IS BACK!
- Man: I DON'T BELIEVE IT,
HE'S RETURNED?
- Man #2:
JUST IN TIME.
- Man #3:
IT'S A MIRACLE!
- Pantherlily:
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- Nadi:
I'M RESPONSIBLE, SIR.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- I HAPPENED TO OVERHEAR
YOUR CONVERSATION EARLIER.
- LET'S FIGHT.
OR YOUR PRECIOUS CITY IS GOING
TO GET BURNED TO THE GROUND.
- IT SEEMS WE HAVE
OUR VILLAIN, DON'T WE?
- WHY ISN'T THE ARMY
DOING ANYTHING?
- SOMEONE HAS TO SAVE THE KING
OR THEY'LL KILL HIM!
- IS ANYBODY EVEN SURE THAT
THAT GUY IS REALLY THE PRINCE?
- I DON'T CARE WHO HE IS,
AS LONG AS HE CAN BEAT
THAT MONSTER.
- Panther Lily: THE CITIZENS DO
NOT BELIEVE IN THE PRINCE YET.
- NATSU, STAY RIGHT THERE.
- DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
I AM THE GREAT AND POWERFUL
LORD DRAGNEEL.
- Pantherlily: IT'S OBVIOUS HE
WANTS TO MAKE JELLAL PLAY
THE ROLE OF HERO.
BUT IF HE THROWS THE FIGHT
AND THE PUBLIC FINDS OUT,
THE CONSEQUENCES COULD
BE TRAGIC.
- ( thinking ) IS HE WILLING
TO PAY THE ULTIMATE PRICE?
- SIR, I'D ADVISE YOU TO BE
READY FOR SOME MAJOR SURPRISES.
THERE'S QUITE A BIT MORE
IN STORE FOR TONIGHT,
TO SAY THE LEAST.
- OH, MY.
I FEEL MYSELF AGAIN.
EXCEPT FOR THIS CRUSHING WEIGHT!
I'M BEING SQUASHED BY MY MEN!
WHAT THE DEVIL
IS HAPPENING HERE?
IS THAT MAGIC POWER?
THE QUEEN,
I MUST PROTECT THE QUEEN!
- Nichiya:
( roars )
- Gajeel:
THERE GOES THE PRINCE,
IS HE REALLY GOING TO FIGHT
THAT MONSTER BY HIMSELF?
WHAT UNBELIEVABLE COURAGE
HE HAS.
- Woman #2:
HE'S SO BRAVE.
- YOU IDIOT, I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
BUT YOU'RE JUST GOING TO END UP
MAKING THINGS WORSE
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW SLEEP!
THE ANIMA MUST HAVE
TAKEN MY POWER.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU SCARED WITHOUT
YOUR MAGIC, HUH?
- ( grunts )
- WELL YOU SHOULD BE.
'CAUSE CHECK THIS OUT,
I'VE GOT PLENTY!
- Man: EVERYBODY, RUN!
- I SAID, STOP!
- Wendy: NATSU, YOU'RE
GOING WAY TOO FAR.
- Gajeel:
NO, HE'S NOT.
THE MORE POWERFUL THE VILLAIN'S
MAGIC SEEMS TO EVERYONE,
THE STRONGER THE HERO LOOKS
WHEN HE BEATS HIM WITHOUT
USING ANY MAGIC AT ALL.
- LISTEN TO ME, NATSU.
YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MISTAKE
WITH ALL THIS,
THIS WHOLE SHOW
THAT YOU'RE PUTTING ON.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT
TO FOOL ALL THESE PEOPLE.
- HAH, I CHALLENGE YOU!
- Woman: PRINCE!
- Man: WATCH OUT,
HE'S DANGEROUS!
- YOU FOOL,
YOU CAN'T BRING THE PEOPLE
TOGETHER LIKE THIS--
THROUGH EVIL.
- FIGHT ME FOR REAL.
- YEAH!
- YOU GOT HIM, PRINCE!
- WE KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU'RE OUR ONLY HOPE!
- YEAH, NOW THEY'RE
REALLY GETTING IN TO IT.
- IDIOT!  YOU SHOULD HAVE
STAYED DOWN
SO WE WOULDN'T HAVE
TO STRETCH THIS OUT FURTHER.
- NOT MY STYLE!
- ( groans )
- OH, NO.
- GET UP!
- HOW DARE HE STRIKE
THE PRINCE LIKE THAT.
- ( crowd cheering )
- ( chanting )
GO, PRINCE!
- THIS IS IT, BUDDY.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
A REAL FAIRY TAIL SEND-OFF.
SINCE YOU'RE LEAVING FAIRY TAIL,
YOU'VE GOT TO SWEAR TO
FOLLOW THESE THREE RULES--
NUMBER ONE,
NEVER, EVER, SHARE SENSITIVE
INFORMATION ABOUT FAIRY TAIL
WITH ANYONE,
AS LONG AS YOU LIVE.
TWO--
HOW'D THAT ONE GO AGAIN?
- NUMBER TWO, YOU MUST NEVER
CONTACT ANY CLIENTS
YOU MAY HAVE WORKED
WITH FOR THE GUILD
FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL GAIN.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
AND DON'T FORGET NUMBER THREE.
ALTHOUGH OUR PATHS MUST STRAY,
YOU'VE GOT TO PROMISE TO LIVE
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
TO THE FULLEST.
THAT MEANS TO TREAT EVERY DAY
LIKE IT WAS GOING TO BE
YOUR LAST DAY IN THIS WORLD.
DON'T FORGET THE FRIENDS
YOU LOVED.
- YOU MUST TREASURE THEM
FOR AS LONG AS YOU LIVE.
- DID YOU GET ALL THAT?
- Natsu: WHEN A GUILD
WORKS TOGETHER,
THERE'S NOTHING THEY CAN'T DO.
NICE KNOWING YOU, PAL.
LATER.
- ( crowd cheering )
- THANK YOU.
- Man: THE PRINCE WON!
- Man #2: HE BEAT HIM!
- Man #3: AWESOME!
- Woman: PRINCE, YOU'RE MY HERO!
- NATSU.
- WHAT?
WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S STARTING.
- YEAH, I GUESS
OUR LITTLE SONG AND DANCE
AIN'T OVER JUST YET.
- Man: DO YOU SEE THAT?
- Woman: HIS BODY IS GLOWING.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO US?
- THE REVERSE ANIMA SPELL
IS BEGINNING TO CAST
EVERY REMAINING SHRED OF MAGIC
OUT OF EDOLAS.
AND BECAUSE WE POSSESS
INTERNAL MAGIC POWERS,
THAT INCLUDES ALL OF THE EXCEEDS
AND THE DRAGON SLAYERS AS WELL.
WE'LL ALL BE PULLED
INTO EARTH LAND.
- SAY WHAT?
- I BELIEVE THE
QUEEN IS PREPARING
FOR THIS OCCURRENCE AS WE SPEAK.
- I'M SCARED, YOUR HIGHNESS.
- I'M FEELING REALLY WEIRD.
- Chagot: DON'T BE AFRAID,
IT WILL BE ALRIGHT.
THEY DON'T NEED ANGELS NOW,
SO WE HAVE TO MOVE ALONG.
THERE'S GOING TO BE
A BIG CHANGE FOR US.
AND WE ALL HAVE TO WALK
TOWARDS IT WITH A BRAVE FACE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- THE ANIMA IS PULLING US
OUT OF THIS WORLD!
- ( gasping )
- Lucy: IT LOOKS LIKE THE ANIMA
IS STARTING TO WORK IN REVERSE
AND IT'S PUSHING THE MAGIC
OUT OF HERE.
THAT MEANS WE'VE
GOT TO GO, TOO.
- Natsu:
HEY, WHAT'S UP, YOU GUYS?
- Lucy: NATSU!
- Happy: NATSU!
- Gray: GOOD TO SEE
YOU, PAL. YOU'RE OK.
- THIS IS CRAZY!
- Alzack:
I GUESS IT'S FINALLY HAPPENING.
WE'RE LOSING
OUR MAGIC POWER, FOREVER!
- Bisca: DOES THIS MEAN WE'RE
GOING TO LOSE OUR GUILD, TOO?
- I'M SO SCARED.
WHATEVER WILL BECOME OF US, NOW?
- YOU'RE ASKING ME, LIKE I'VE
GOT SOME KIND OF ANSWER?
- TRY NOT TO WORRY ABOUT IT,
YOU GUYS.
IT TAKES A HECK OF A LOT MORE
THAN JUST MAGIC
TO MAKE A REAL GUILD,
TRUST ME.
IT'S ALL ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
THAT'S THE HEART OF A GUILD.
- IS THIS IT, SCARLET?
- I'M AFRAID SO, NIGHTWALKER.
NO. WE'RE BOTH--
- ( both )
ERZA.
- Lucky: WHAT IN TARNATION
IS GOING ON HERE?
- THIS FORCE IS PULLING US IN!
- THIS CANNOT BE!
JUST WHEN WE WERE REVIVED
AND READY TO PERFORM FEATS
OF UNIMAGINABLE HEROISM!
- SIR, YES, SIR!
- ( screaming )
- Mystogan: I KNEW
THE MAGIC WOULD BE EXPELLED.
BUT I HAD NO IDEA THE PEOPLE
WOULD BE AS WELL.
- WHOA, HE TOTALLY SENT
THE BAD GUYS FLYING AWAY!
- THE PRINCE JUST SAVED
THE ENTIRE KINGDOM!
- Man: OH, YEAH!
- HERO OF THE KINGDOM!
- Pantherlily:
PRINCE.
ALTHOUGH THINGS ARE
CHANGING RAPIDLY,
DON'T FORGET, ADAPTING
TO THEM CAN TAKE TIME.
DON'T RUSH.
LEAD YOUR PEOPLE WITH WARMTH
AND A CALM HEART.
TAKE THEM AT A PACE
THEY CAN KEEP UP WITH.
THEY WILL MARCH ALONGSIDE YOU
INTO THE FUTURE.
- I WILL.
- BYE-BYE, LUCY ASHLEY!
BYE, EVERYBODY IN FAIRY TAIL!
- LATER!
AND BEST OF LUCK TO ME!
I MEAN, THE YOU
THAT'S ALSO ME.
- GOOD LUCK TO YOU, TOO.
I MEAN GOOD LUCK TO ME, TOO.
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE IT'S
CONFUSING OR SOMETHING.
- BYE-BYE, PRINCESS.
TAKE CARE UP THERE.
- BYE-BYE, EVERYONE.
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- DON'T BE SUCH A FOOL, WE WON'T
BE SEEING THEM AGAIN. NEVER.
- WHAT?!
( crying )
I'LL MISS YOU!
- STOP BEING SO SENTIMENTAL.
IT'S JUST PATHETIC.
- Lucy: AND WITH THAT, WE
ALL WENT BACK TO EARTH LAND.
- FAREWELL, PRINCE.
- FAREWELL, LILY.
AND FAREWELL TO MY FAMILY
IN FAIRY TAIL.
I'LL CHERISH OUR MEMORIES
FOR AS LONG AS I LIVE.
I PROMISE I WILL.
- Lucy: YOU CAN'T HELP BUT
WONDER WHAT WENT DOWN
AFTER WE LEFT.
- THE MONSTERS
HAVE BEEN DEFEATED!
WHETHER WE HAVE MAGIC OR NOT,
OUR KINGDOM WILL LIVE ON
SAFELY AND PEACEFULLY
FOR ALL ETERNITY!
- ( crowd cheering )
- Lucy: I HAVE A FEELING
THINGS ARE GOING TO BE
A WHOLE LOT BETTER
FOR THEM.
AFTER ALL, THEY'VE LEARNED
THERE'S STILL MAGIC EVERYWHERE.
AS LONG AS YOU KNOW
HOW TO LOOK FOR IT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: MAN, I AM SO GLAD
TO FINALLY BE HEADING HOME.
- Happy: I HOPE EVERYONE
MADE IT BACK OK.
- Natsu: DON'T WORRY,
LITTLE BUDDY.
I KNOW THEY'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
- Happy: BUT HOW CAN
YOU BE SO SURE?
- Natsu:
'CAUSE OUR GUILD IS AWESOME!
PLUS, WE'VE GOT GRAMPS AROUND
IF THINGS GET TOO OUT OF HAND.
HE CAN TAKE CARE OF ANYTHING.
- Happy: WOW, I WAS EXPECTING
MORE OF YOUR USUAL CRAZY TALK.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu:
CRAZY TALK, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Happy:
WELL, I GUESS FOR YOU,
MAKING SENSE IS CRAZY.
- Natsu: PFFT, YOU'RE JUST
JEALOUS OF MY BRAIN.