How can you do this right now?
At a time like this?
Please stop.
[NATSU]
I had to do it.
'Cause she was crying.
[NATSU]
She looked so weak and fragile.
Her voice was
trembling with fear.
[NATSU] I don't wanna
see Erza like that.
I've always looked up to
her as a strong warrior.
[NATSU]
You made Erza cry!
And I'm not gonna let
you get away with that!
[GRAY]
All right, Erza! Bring it on!
You're the one who's
goin' down this time!
[GRAY]
I hope she knows...
...that her friends are ten
times better than any armor.
We'll make sure she
never cries again.
Look at the person in
front of you and tell me...
...is he your enemy,
or your friend?
[ERZA]
I don't know what happened,
but you can't let some fleeting
emotion consume you!
We've grown up together!
Have you forgotten our history?
[ERZA, MAKAROV] Put aside
your anger. Listen to me!
[MAKAROV] It's perfectly fine
to fight from time to time.
[GRAY]
Gramps.
[MAKAROV] If you're
being true to yourself
and following your beliefs,
conflicts are bound to happen.
And if it comes to
a clash of spirits,
make sure your actions
are rooted in respect.
Violence must not be
fueled by hate and spite
for those with whom
you share a bond.
That's what a guild
is all about.
[MAKAROV]
Never forget.
[ERZA]
I love you both unconditionally.
And I mean that from the
very bottom of my heart.
[JUVIA]
Gray, my darling!
[gasps]
[JUVIA]
You're not dreaming!
Wendy nursed me back
to health! I'm okay now!
"Okay" might be taking
it a little far.
Natsu and Erza seem fine, too!
Juvia.
[JUVIA]
My love!
No. What happened?
Clearly their recklessness
caught up with them.
I was so worried about you.
I'm sorry.
[HAPPY]
Oh, Natsu!
Hey, buddy.
Erza, do you know what caused
that bright light
in the sky earlier?
Huh?
What's the matter?
[JELLAL]
This is insane.
We don't even begin
to compare to him.
How can one man wield
so much power?
[COBRA] He's strong,
but I can hear his moves...
...before he makes them!
[AUGUST]
I can also hear your moves.
You can't disguise them!
[yells]
You're not fast enough!
[AUGUST]
Too slow.
Spiral Pain!
An interesting spell indeed.
That's why....
...I mastered it many years ago.
[groaning]
[JELLAL]
There must be a way.
We need to have Porlyusica
treat Natsu A.S.A.P.
[CARLA]
And Gray. And Juvia, too.
Aye.
Get down, now!
[HAPPY, CARLA scream]
[LUCY]
What the--?!
Where did that come from?
It's been such a long time.
Hello, Erza.
You know this person?
I don't. Tell me who you are!
[WENDY] It's weird.
They look really similar.
Who am I?
One could say I'm you, Erza.
And you are me.
Seems we've won.
They're disappearing.
[MINERVA] Honestly, they were
dead when the fight began.
So I'm not certain
if we beat them,
or the one controlling
them was defeated.
But either way, it's a victory.
[ROGUE]
That blinding light we saw,
do you know what it was?
It's Fairy Law. That's
Makarov's most powerful spell.
Its purpose is to
obliterate anybody
who the caster sees
as their enemy.
It's a good thing we made
amends with Fairy Tail
before all this happened.
I wonder how effective
the spell was.
[MINERVA] Well, I highly doubt
it got every last one.
But I'm sure it wiped out a
sizable chunk of their forces.
I hope you're right.
Because we've nearly exhausted
our reserves by now.
[LECTOR]
Whoa!
All those bad guys just
collapsed outta nowhere!
[FROSCH]
I think so, too!
I'm not sure who was
able to pull that off,
but it looks like we're
safe for now, big sister!
I thought I told you
I'm not your sister.
[LARCADE] That was quite
the spectacle to behold.
[YUKINO]
Who's there?
[LARCADE]
So many of our men gone
in one brilliant flash of light.
Therefore, if I ever want
to face my father again,
I must repay this in kind.
Is he, like, an angel?
Oh, yeah. I think so, too!
He's another one of the Twelve!
I'm absolutely positive.
That so?
You really think you can
take on both of us, do you?
Then you're a fool.
[LECTOR] Don't forget
I'm here for backup.
[FROSCH]
Me, too!
Perhaps I should clarify.
I intend to repay everyone.
Meaning, all who oppose us
will be subjected
to my punishment.
It's blinding!
May your spirits of pure white
into the heavens take flight.
What's wrong, Sorano?
[YUKINO]
Please, stay strong!
[MINERVA gasping]
What is this?
I can't take it.
M'lady!
[MINERVA]
No. Don't!
Please. Don't touch me.
[ROGUE]
What?
Oh, no. What's happening?
[ROGUE]
Well, this isn't good.
[WIZARDS groaning]
[WIZARD D]
Oh, wow!
[WIZARD E]
This is crazy!
No. We have to fight it!
I don't think I can.
What's happening to you?
[MAVIS] This magic is strange.
I don't understand it.
Only the adults are affected.
[MAVIS]
No. Wait.
Some people are perfectly fine.
What's going on here?
[gasps]
I feel so strange.
So good.
There's nothing I can do.
It's taking over.
[grunting]
[CANA]
Gildarts!
What the hell's happening
to you? Shake it off!
Ahh...
Well, whatever your creepy
thing is right now,
this is not the time!
I feel so good.
Larcade's doing that
godforsaken spell of his.
[IRENE]
You and I share quite a lot.
More than you
could ever imagine.
[IRENE]
Not now.
Damned Larcade.
You need to get all the wounded
to safety, right this instant!
Yeah! Right!
Aye, aye!
But what about you, Erza?
[ERZA]
I wanna know what she means.
I need to find out the truth!
[gasps]
I can help you fight.
[ERZA]
Wendy!
[IRENE]
Imbuement magic?
I find it hard to believe
that not a single one of you
was affected by Larcade's spell.
I'll have to fight through it.
Please stop, Larcade. Right now!
[ZEREF]
You're harming your allies, too.
[LARCADE] That was not my
intention. Forgive me.
What kinda magic is this?
[YUKINO]
Why did it only affect her?
Too much!
[YUKINO]
Just hang in there!
[LARCADE]
My magic is rooted in pleasure.
And all those who have tasted it
cannot escape its grip.
Relentless pleasure sounds
like a gift, doesn't it?
But too much is dangerous.
Open! Divine Gate
of the Two Fish!
In fact, it can be fatal.
[gasps]
It seems that you've been kept
in the dark of ignorance,
but I will share the light of
pleasure and pain with you.
[gasping]
What's happening?
I feel so bad all over!
Never mind, I'm feeling
real good now!
Yeah, I think so, too!
We have to keep
ourselves together!
Don't give in to it!
[gasping]
[screams]
[gasps]
[KAGURA] All this talk
about light and pleasure,
and yet, still you're
partnered with Zeref.
Kagura, you're here!
I'm afraid you don't understand.
He's much more than that to me.
My father.
[JELLAL]
How could this happen?
This is the end
for Crime Sorcière.
We've been annihilated.
[JELLAL]
By one man...
[AUGUST] I've heard that you
once worshipped His Majesty.
Knowing his power, why would
you ever choose to fight him?
[JELLAL]
Because I saw the light.
The radiance of a heart that
could brighten my darkness.
[AUGUST] So light is good
and darkness is evil?
How simple-minded.
His Majesty was once
blessed with a son.
The boy was born into this world
possessing a tremendous
power of light.
[JELLAL]
Zeref... had a child?
[AUGUST]
The lad was unloved.
With nary a soul to share
his gift, he walked alone,
traveling the path where
light and darkness meet,
until he reached a
state of nothingness.
Good and evil are not as
simple as black and white.
If we were to call one thing
"good" in this world, perhaps...
Perhaps that would be "love."
[JELLAL]
Come on.
I have to get up. Now!
Erza is in danger.
I have to find her.
You're telling me
you're Zeref's son?
Indeed, my father
is Zeref Dragneel.
And my name is Larcade Dragneel.
Did he say Dragneel? Wait!
That's Natsu's last
name, isn't it?
[FROSCH]
Huh?
As a matter of fact, it is.
Natsu is my father's
younger brother.
Which would, in turn,
mean that he's my uncle.
[gasps]
What?! That's insane!
[LARCADE]
I was rather looking forward
to meeting him
during this battle.
After all, Father seems to
care much more about him
than he ever has about me.
So naturally...
I want him to die!
They're blades of light!
You think you can talk
down to us from on high?
[KAGURA]
Get down here!
Holy--!
I think she's awesome!
[YUKINO]
Kagura!
[LARCADE] And now you must learn
the taste of pleasure and pain.
These primal instincts
you can't deny.
Try and resist it
with all your might!
I can't even stand up! Kagura!
[screams]
[gasps]
[yells]
[LARCADE]
She bit through her own tongue.
Escaped the pleasure by
inflicting pain on herself.
[gasps]
[LARCADE]
She's fast!
Your magic's incredibly vulgar.
I know what she's doing.
She's preparing her
unstoppable technique!
[KAGURA] You could say the
same for my Grudge Sword's
thirst for blood!
Archenemy!
[gasps]
[KAGURA] He stopped my sword
with his bare hands?
You have the wrong idea.
You can't hold all the Twelve
to the same standard
of the ones you've
defeated so far.
No. I, Irene, and August
aren't like the rest.
I love that look on your face.
It's rare to see someone
caught between defiance
and resignation.
[yells]
[LARCADE]
Fear not.
For eventually, this pain will
give way to ultimate pleasure.
You were fierce earlier.
And you referred to the
magic I wield as "vulgar."
I concede that may be true
to a certain degree,
but if you look, you'll
find there's love in it.
It allows you to die
without feeling any pain.
[LARCADE]
May your spirit of pure white
into the heavens take flight.
Kagura, no!
I'm scared, Lector.
Enjoy it for now.
Your pleasure will
become so intense
you'll be begging
for it to stop.
[gasps]
No!
And now, your death will
be filled with pure bliss.
His Majesty's child.
Perhaps the only one
who can beat him...
[AUGUST]
...is his mother.
[LUCY] Kagura struck at Larcade
with her invincible sword,
but ultimately failed
to reach her target.
Meanwhile, still unconscious
after his battle with Gray,
Natsu's body is being consumed
by a mysterious force.
He's left to wander
among the memories
scattered throughout his mind.
Memories that seem like
they may belong to another.
But are they merely from
a life he's forgotten?
Next Time: "Natsu's Mind."
In the search for answers,
hope can be found.