HEY, GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Erza:
PREVIOUSLY, ON FAIRY TAIL.
- Gray: JELLAL, ONE OF ERZA'S
OLD FRIENDS, IS PLANNING
TO RESURRECT THE EVIL WIZARD
ZEREF USING THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
WITH HELP FROM THE REST
OF HER OLD BUDDIES,
WE DEFEATED TRINITY RAVEN,
A TEAM FROM THE DARK GUILD,
DEATH'S HEAD ORDER, BUT NOW...
- HURRY, NATSU.
THE ETHERION IS ABOUT TO FIRE!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- Erza: WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOUR REAL GOAL IS, JELLAL?
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THAT THE R-SYSTEM
HASN'T BEEN COMPLETED.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I'VE BEEN DOING
SINCE I LEFT THIS PLACE
YEARS AGO?
RESEARCHING IT RELENTLESSLY.
AND I KNOW THAT EVEN THOUGH
THE TOWER ITSELF WAS CONSTRUCTED
EXACTLY LIKE THE BLUEPRINTS,
THERE'S STILL ONE THING
YOU DON'T HAVE--
A VITAL PART
TO ITS COMPLETION.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE, BECAUSE YOUR
SACRIFICE WILL COMPLETE IT.
- NO, SOMETHING EVEN
MORE BASIC THAN THAT.
MAGIC ENERGY.
I DON'T THINK YOU REALIZE
HOW MUCH MAGIC ENERGY
YOU'D HAVE TO ACCUMULATE JUST
TO ACTIVATE THE R-SYSTEM.
YOU COULD GATHER EVERY SINGLE
WIZARD ON THE CONTINENT
AND YOU STILL WOULDN'T HAVE
ENOUGH POWER TO PULL IT OFF.
THIS TOWER DOESN'T
HAVE THE CAPACITY
TO STORE THAT MUCH MAGIC ENERGY
WITHIN ITS WALLS,
AND YOU CERTAINLY CAN'T DO IT
ON YOUR OWN.
I FIND IT HIGHLY SUSPICIOUS THAT
YOU HAVEN'T TRIED TO ESCAPE,
DESPITE KNOWING THE COUNCIL'S
PREPARING TO ATTACK.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- ONLY THREE MORE MINUTES
UNTIL THE ETHERION FIRES.
- ANSWER ME.  YOU KNOW YOUR
DREAM WILL NEVER COME TRUE
SO WHY ARE YOU WILLING
TO RISK YOUR LIFE?
DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WE'LL GO TOGETHER.
I'LL STAY HERE
TO HOLD YOU DOWN,
AND I WON'T LET GO
TILL THE BITTER END.
- TO BE HONEST,
THAT DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD.
I NO LONGER HAVE CONTROL OVER
MY OWN BODY AND SOUL
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN POSSESSED
BY ZEREF.
I'M MERELY A PUPPET
HE'S MANIPULATING IN ORDER
TO BECOME FLESH AGAIN.
- YOU WERE POSSESSED BY HIM?
- I WASN'T ABLE TO SAVE MYSELF
AND NOT EVEN MY CLOSEST FRIENDS
WERE THERE TO COME TO MY RESCUE.
THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED
THERE IS NO HEAVEN, NOR DOES
TRUE FREEDOM REALLY EXIST.
ALL OF CREATION WAS FINISHED
BEFORE IT EVEN BEGAN.
- THE FINAL ETHERION FIRING
PHASE HAS BEEN COMPLETED.
- NOW DEPLOYING
THE SATELLITE SQUARE.
- DISPLACEMENT LACRIMAE SHOW
ALL SIGNS NORMAL.
- COORDINATES ARE LOCKED.
- MAGIC FUSION APPEARS
TO BE STABLE.
- START THE COUNTDOWN.
- LET US PRAY.
- FOR THE INNOCENT.
- FOR THE END.
- Lucy:
WHAT'S THAT BRIGHT LIGHT?
- Wally:
GOTTA BE THE ETHERION.
- OH, NO.
COME ON YOU GUYS.
HURRY UP AND GET OUT
OF THERE NOW.
- Jellal: DEEP DOWN I KNEW THE
R-SYSTEM COULDN'T BE COMPLETED,
BUT ZEREF KEPT PUSHING ME.
HE FORCED ME TO CONTINUE
THE TOWER'S CONSTRUCTION.
I WANTED TO STOP,
BUT I COULDN'T.
IT'S LIKE I WAS A FREIGHT TRAIN
WITH NO BRAKES.
I SURRENDER.
GO AHEAD AND FINISH ME.
ISN'T THAT WHY YOU CAME
LOOKING FOR ME?
- ( whimpering )
- THERE'S NO NEED FOR ME
TO SPILL YOUR BLOOD
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
THE SATELLITE SQUARE IS FOCUSED,
AND THE ETHERION WILL FIRE
ANY MINUTE NOW.
THAT MEANS THIS IS THE END
FOR BOTH YOU
AND ME.
- IT IS A GRIM FATE
THAT WE SHARE.
- SO ALL THIS TIME YOU WERE
JUST ANOTHER OF ZEREF'S VICTIMS.
- IT'S MY OWN FAULT.  I LET
MY WEAKNESS GET THE BEST OF ME.
THE RIFT BETWEEN MY DREAM
AND REALITY WAS TOO DEEP
FOR MY MIND TO COMPREHEND.
- THE ONLY PEOPLE CAPABLE
OF SAVING YOU
FROM YOUR FLAWS
AND YOUR INNER WEAKNESS
ARE THOSE WHO YOU CALL
YOUR FRIENDS.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- I APOLOGIZE FOR NOT BEING ABLE
TO SAVE YOU BACK THEN.
CAN YOU FORGIVE ME?
- ERZA.
YOU HAVE SAVED ME.
- WE PRAY TO THE SACRED LIGHT
FOR FORGIVENESS.
LET US FIRE THE ETHERION
AT ONCE.
- IT'S HEADED STRAIGHT
FOR THE TOWER.
- NATSU.  ERZA.
- THAT LIGHT.
WE DIDN'T MAKE IT IN TIME.
- ( panting ) ERZA!
- THIS IS THE END.
- ( all shouting )
- ETHERION HAS IMPACTED
THE TARGET.
- WAS THE TARGET SUCCESSFULLY
DESTROYED?  I NEED CONFIRMATION.
- THE DENSITY OF THE ETHER-NANO
FUSION IS INCREASING.
EXTREME WEATHER CONDITIONS
ARE EXPECTED.
- ( sighing )
- WHO KNOWS HOW MANY
INNOCENT PEOPLE
MIGHT HAVE BEEN INSIDE
THAT TOWER.
- BUT THEY WERE THERE FOR THE
SOLE PURPOSE
OF RESURRECTING ZEREF.
THEIR SACRIFICE HAD TO BE MADE
TO SAVE THE LIVES OF OTHERS.
- I UNDERSTAND THAT, MICHELLO,
BUT IT'S STILL HEARTBREAKING
ALL THE SAME.
I SINCERELY DOUBT THE VICTIMS'
FAMILIES WILL BE COMFORTED
BY THAT REASONING.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- OH, NO.  DID WE LOSE 'EM?
- WE'RE STILL ALIVE?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- ( cackling )
- ETHER-NANO NEUTRALIZERS
DETECTED AT THE EPICENTER.
NO, WAIT A MINUTE,
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- THERE'S BEEN A SUDDEN DROP
IN FUSION DENSITY.
- PICKING UP HIGH LEVELS OF
MAGIC ENERGY
FROM ANOTHER SOURCE.
- THE COUNTER CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH IT.
- WHAT COULD IT BE?
- RESTORING VISUAL FEED.
- A CRYSTAL?
- NO, NOT A CRYSTAL.
THAT'S A LACRIMA.
- SO YOU THINK THEY'RE OKAY?
MAYBE THEY SURVIVED THE BLAST
AND THEY'RE STILL INSIDE.
- WHAT IN THE HECK JUST HAPPENED
TO THIS PLACE?
- THE ETHERION WAS FIRED,
BUT I SHOULDN'T HAVE SURVIVED
THE BLAST.
- ( laughing ) IT'S HERE.
AT LONG LAST, MY HOUR
OF GLORY HAS ARRIVED.
- GLORY?
- THIS IS THE TRUE FORM
OF THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
A GIANT,
MAGICAL LACRIMA CRYSTAL.
THANKS TO THE COUNCIL,
IT'S READY TO ACTIVATE.
THE ETHERION'S MAGIC ENERGY
PROVIDED THE MISSING PIECE
OF THE PUZZLE,
WHICH MEANS THE R-SYSTEM
IS NOW COMPLETE.
- ( gasps )
- THE TARGET IS STILL STANDING.
- IT'S A GIANT LACRIMA.
- I THINK IT ACTUALLY ABSORBED
THE MAGIC ENERGY
OF THE ETHERION BLAST.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- SIEGRAIN, I THINK IT'S TIME
YOU START EXPLAINING YOURSELF.
HE DISAPPEARED.
- SO I WAS YOUR PAWN.
- YOUR EXPRESSION
WAS PRICELESS, ERZA.
- ( gasps )
- HE ISN'T CAPABLE OF PUTTING
FORTH HIS FULL POWER RIGHT NOW.
SO HE HAD TO MANIPULATE YOU
IN ORDER TO SAVE HIMSELF.
- SIEGRAIN.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THIS REMINDS ME
OF WHEN WE FIRST MET YEARS AGO.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
YOU ACCOMPANIED MAKAROV
TO THE MAGIC COUNCIL
TO SUBMIT A WRITTEN APOLOGY
FOR DESTRUCTION OF PROPERTY.
- SHE ATTACKED ME
OUT OF NOWHERE.
SHE MUST'VE MISTAKEN ME
FOR YOU.
- I CAN'T SAY I BLAME HER,
AFTER ALL WE DO LOOK ALIKE.
YOU REFUSED TO LET UP UNTIL
I CONFESSED TO YOU
THAT I WAS HIS TWIN,
BUT STILL, YOU WERE HOSTILE
TOWARDS ME
FROM THAT DAY FORWARD.
- WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?  IF YOU
TRULY CARED ABOUT YOUR BROTHER,
YOU WOULD'VE TRIED TO STOP HIM
INSTEAD OF HELPING HIM
COVER HIS TRACKS, AND I KNOW
YOU'VE BEEN SPYING ON ME
AND REPORTING BACK TO HIM.
- IS THAT SO?
- A MISTAKE ON MY PART.
IN RETROSPECT, PERHAPS I
SHOULD'VE SAID SOMETHING
THAT WOULD'VE CONVINCED YOU
I WAS GOING TO FIND JELLAL
AND KILL HIM, BUT MY BIGGEST
MISTAKE WAS RUNNING INTO YOU
IN THE FIRST PLACE, ESPECIALLY
AFTER THE TROUBLE I WENT THROUGH
TO BECOME A COUNCIL MEMBER.
- THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN
HAVING TO COME UP WITH EXCUSES
ON THE SPOT.
- I GET IT.
SO THE TWO OF YOU HAVE BEEN
CONSPIRING THIS WHOLE TIME.
- CONSPIRING?
- NOT EXACTLY.
- I'M AFRAID IT'S MORE
COMPLICATED THAN THAT.
- ( gasps )
- WE'RE NOT TWINS,
BUT TWO FACES OF ONE PERSON,
AND WE HAVE BEEN
FROM THE START.
- BUT HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
WAS HE JUST A PROJECTION?
- YOU NEVER SUSPECTED FOR A
MOMENT WE WERE ONE AND THE SAME.
- THEN YOU'RE THE
ONE RESPONSIBLE
FOR FIRING THE ETHERION.
DID YOU WORM YOUR WAY
ONTO THE COUNCIL JUST FOR THAT?
- I HOPE YOU ENJOYED
THE FREEDOM I GRANTED YOU
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.  YOUR
RELEASE AND EVERYTHING AFTER
WAS ALL PART OF MY PLAN
TO RESURRECT ZEREF.
- HOW CAN YOU LIVE
WITH YOURSELF
KNOWING THAT YOUR ENTIRE LIFE
HAS BEEN ONE BIG LIE?
- MAGIC ENERGY.
I CAN FEEL IT SURGING
THROUGH MY BODY.
- A HUGE AMOUNT OF MAGIC ENERGY
IS BUILDING UP
IN THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
- IF TOO MUCH POWER IS CONTAINED
IN ONE PLACE,
IT'S SURE TO EXPLODE.
- WE'VE BEEN HAD.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO THE BUILDING?
- IT'S LIKE IT'S STARTING
TO AGE AND COLLAPSE.
- THIS HAS TO BE
THE ARC OF TIME,
BUT THAT'S ONE
OF THE LOST MAGICS.
- ( shouting )
- NO, ULTEAR!
- THIS IS ALL
FOR MASTER SIEGRAIN.
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD SAY
MASTER JELLAL.
ALL OF HIS HARD WORK
HAS PAID OFF
AND NOW HIS LIFELONG DREAM
WILL BECOME A REALITY.
- Gray: THAT GIANT LACRIMA
IS THE R-SYSTEM?
YEAH, THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I SEEN IT IN ACTION,
BUT I THINK THAT'S WHAT JELLAL
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- OH, NO,
IT'S BEEN ACTIVATED.
- AND WHAT THE HECK
DOES THAT MEAN?
ARE YOU SAYING ZEREF'S ABOUT
TO BE RESURRECTED?
- WE DON'T KNOW.  WE MAY HAVE
HELPED JELLAL BUILD IT,
BUT WE'VE NEVER SEEN IT
ACTIVATED BEFORE.
- AND NOW NATSU AND ERZA ARE
TRAPPED INSIDE THAT THING.
- Sho: THAT'S RIGHT.
ALONG WITH SIMON AND JELLAL.
- ( grunting )
- LOOKS AS THOUGH SOMEONE'S
A LITTLE WORSE FOR WEAR.
DON'T TELL ME YOU USED UP ALL
YOUR MAGIC ENERGY
FIGHTING AGAINST IKARUGA.
- JELLAL, YOU'RE THROUGH!
- ( laughs ) THE MAGIC
COUNCIL'S HEADQUARTERS
IS LITTLE MORE THAN A PILE
OF RUBBLE BY NOW.
I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT
A BLESSING ULTEAR HAS BEEN.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT HER.
SHE HAS NO FEAR OF DEATH BECAUSE
SHE BELIEVES THAT ALL OF MANKIND
WILL BECOME ONE IN HEAVEN.
IN FACT, SHE TOLD ME SHE'D BE
MORE THAN HAPPY TO GIVE HER LIFE
IF IT MEANT MY DREAM WOULD COME
TO FRUITION.
THAT REMINDS ME.
I SHOULD THANK HER FOR BEING
AN IGNORANT FOOL
WHO'S EASY TO MANIPULATE.
- CURSE YOU!
I'M TAKING REVENGE FOR ALL
THE PEOPLE YOU'VE ABUSED.
THIS IS THE END, JELLAL.
I'LL KILL YOU!  AGH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO MY ARM?
- IT'S JUST A BIND SNAKE.
I SLIPPED IT ONTO YOU DURING OUR
HEARTWARMING EMBRACE EARLIER.
- ( screaming )
- NOW THAT I'VE COLLECTED
THE PRECISE AMOUNT
OF MAGIC ENERGY NEEDED
FOR THE R-SYSTEM, THERE'S ONE
MORE THING THAT MUST BE DONE
BEFORE ZEREF
CAN BE RESURRECTED.
THIS IS WHERE YOU
TAKE CENTER STAGE
FOR YOUR MOMENT
IN THE SPOTLIGHT, MY DEAR.
THE MAGIC ENERGY HELD WITHIN
THIS LACRIMA MUST BE FUSED
WITH THE BODY OF MY SACRIFICE.
ONCE THAT HAPPENS,
YOUR FLESH WILL BREAK DOWN
AND RECONSTRUCT ITSELF
TO CREATE ZEREF'S BODY.
- ( screaming )
- YOU KNOW,
I REALLY DID LOVE YOU, ERZA.
- NO.  STOP!
- OH GREAT AND POWERFUL ZEREF,
I CALL UPON YOU
TO OFFER YOU THIS WOMAN'S FLESH.
- DON'T DO THIS.
PLEASE, JELLAL!
- I GOT YOU.
ERZA'S AN IMPORTANT PART
OF OUR FAIRY TAIL FAMILY.
I WON'T LET YOU TOUCH HER.
- NATSU.
- JEEZ, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HANGING AROUND WITH THIS LOSER?
IF WE DON'T HURRY
AND GET BACK TO WORK,
LUCY'S NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO PAY HER RENT.
TRUST ME, YOU DON'T WANNA
MAKE HER ANGRY.
- SORRY, BUT I CAN'T MOVE.
- NO WAY. ( cackles )
TIME FOR SOME SERIOUS PAYBACK.
- ( laughing )
- THIS IS WHAT YOU GET
FOR ALWAYS TICKLING ME.
- THIS IS SERIOUS,
SO QUIT GOOFING OFF.  STOP IT!
NATSU, YOU'VE GOTTA GET OUT
OF HERE AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
- I AIN'T LEAVING.  IF YOU
CAN'T DO THE FIGHTING YOURSELF,
THEN I'LL JUST HAVE TO
DO IT FOR YOU.
- YOU CAN'T.
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
BESIDES, YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
- WHO SAYS I NEED TO KNOW
THE GUY TO BEAT HIM UP?
- PLEASE.
JUST THIS ONCE,
DO AS I ASK YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HONESTLY, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
YOU ALL THAT WELL, EITHER,
BUT I CAN STILL TAKE YOU DOWN.
- ( grunts )
- YOU'RE EVEN FOOLHARDIER THAN
THE RUMORS MAKE YOU OUT TO BE.
WHAT KIND OF SICK SATISFACTION
DO YOU GET
FROM STRIKING
A DEFENSELESS FRIEND?
- I HAD TO DO IT.
'CAUSE SHE WAS CRYING.
SHE LOOKED SO WEAK
AND FRAGILE.
HER VOICE WAS TREMBLING
WITH FEAR.
I DON'T WANNA SEE ERZA
LIKE THAT.
I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED UP
TO HER AS A STRONG WARRIOR.
AND WHEN SHE WAKES UP
FROM THIS NIGHTMARE,
I WANT HER TO FEEL LIKE
HER OLD SELF AGAIN.
IF YOU WANNA GET TO HER,
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO THROUGH ME.
- IS THAT A CHALLENGE?
CONSIDER MY INTEREST PIQUED.
I WOULD LOVE TO WITNESS
THE POWER OF A DRAGON SLAYER.
- ( screaming )
FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
FIRE DRAGON TALON!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- IS THAT THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
( laughs )
I EXPECTED MORE FROM YOU,
NATSU DRAGNEEL,
SON OF IGNEEL.
I WAS HOPING TO GET A TASTE
OF THE DESTRUCTIVE MIGHT
OF A DRAGON SLAYER BEFORE
I STARTED RIPPING YOU TO SHREDS
WITH MY BARE HANDS,
BUT IF THAT'S ALL YOU'VE GOT,
I WON'T WASTE MY TIME.
- I'LL SHOW YOU!
- YOU MUST BE PUNISHED
FOR DISRUPTING MY CEREMONY.
PREPARE TO BE DESTROYED
BY MY HEAVENLY BODY MAGIC.
METEOR!
- ( grunts )
MAN, THIS GUY IS FAST.
I'LL HAVE TO RELY
ON ALL MY SENSES TO FIGHT HIM.
SOUND, FEELING, HIS SCENT.
IF I CONCENTRATE I CAN PREDICT
HIS NEXT MOVE.  STAY FOCUSED.
GOT YA!
( grunting ) WHY DOES IT SEEM
LIKE HE'S GETTING FASTER?
- BE GLAD YOU GOT YOUR HITS IN
'CAUSE IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
AND NOW I'LL SHOW YOU
THE TRUE DESTRUCTIVE POWER
OF DARKNESS MAGIC.
MAY THE SEVEN STARS
BRING JUDGMENT UPON YOU.
SEVEN STAR SWORD,
GRAND CHARIOT!
- ( groaning )
- THAT SPELL PACKS AS MUCH
OF A PUNCH AS BEING HIT
BY A FALLING METEOR.
I'M SURPRISED HIS BODY'S STILL
IN ONE PIECE
AFTER BEING HIT WITH IT.
PERHAPS THAT WAS A LITTLE MUCH.
THE R-SYSTEM CAN'T AFFORD
TO SUFFER ANY MORE DAMAGE
OR IT'LL BE RENDERED USELESS.
I CAN FEEL THE MAGIC ENERGY
BEGINNING TO LEAK OUT.
I'LL HAVE TO HURRY.
IT'S TIME, ERZA.
- ( grunting )
YOU FEEL THAT?
IT WAS MY SNEAK ATTACK.
SO NOW THAT THE TOWER'S
A GIANT CRYSTAL,
I GUESS SHATTERING IT
WOULD SCREW UP YOUR PLANS.
THIS IS NOT YOUR DAY, BUDDY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COME ON, DIDN'T YOU KNOW
THAT DESTROYING STUFF
IS WHAT US FAIRY TAIL
WIZARDS ARE BEST AT?
NOW I'M ALL FIRED UP.
MORE THAN I'VE EVER BEEN BEFORE.
- YOU WON'T GET IN MY WAY!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: THE MAGIC ENERGY INSIDE
THE TOWER IS OUT OF CONTROL.
IF WE DON'T STOP IT,
IT'S GONNA EXPLODE.
- Natsu:
I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WAY TO STOP
IT.  WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ERZA?
IF YOU GO BACK INSIDE THAT THING
I'LL HAVE TO PULL YOU OUT AGAIN.
- Happy: ARE YOU TRYING TO FUSE
YOUR BODY WITH THE LACRIMA
TO ABSORB THE MAGIC ENERGY
AND KEEP IT FROM BLOWING UP?
- Natsu: NO, DON'T DO IT!
( - Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: THE TOWER JUST VANISHED
INTO THIN AIR.
- Natsu: THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
ERZA!