So, this August guy.
I gotta wonder what
kinda wizard he is.
Well, please, don't do
anything to test him.
The whole point is to negotiate.
You'd be obliterated before
you even knew what hit you.
So keep that in mind.
Aye, sir.
The August I know is
kind and warmhearted,
and I believe he's the most
reasonable member of the Twelve.
However, he's also quite loyal.
His support for the Emperor
will be hard to sway.
So how are you gonna get past
that major sticking point?
[BRANDISH]
No idea.
[LUCY yelps]
[NATSU]
Hm?
Ya can't hide, Mest.
I know you're there.
[LUCY, MEST gasps]
What do you expect?
I can't believe you'd put
all your trust in this girl.
Just get over it. It's not
like she's a bad person.
[MEST] But did you have to take
off her Magic Sealstone?
She's still our
prisoner, ya know!
Don't worry about
the details, man!
Natsu, is there
anything going on
inside that spiky
head of yours?
[BRANDISH] Are we really
gonna walk all the way there?
I'm not gettin' in a vehicle!
[HAPPY] And I can only
carry one person at a time.
I know what we can do.
[HAPPY]
Aye!
You're huge!
Ah, yeah! That is awesome!
Seems like we can ride him now.
So jump on this
big ball of fluff.
[LUCY]
Is she making a cutesy face?
Whoa! Hey, lady, can
you make me big, too?
[yelps]
Oh, wow! This rules!
I feel so freakin' cool
right now, you guys!
[NATSU]
Yeah, man! That is totally cool!
Please let me down!
I'm terrified!
[CANA panting]
Cana, come on.
Get serious and hit me
with all you've got.
But you're my friend.
I can't just attack you.
I get that you're only
a projection, but still.
You know, you're a lot
like my best friend.
She had long, brown hair, too.
[CANA] You think that
makes us "a lot" alike?
[MAVIS] She died when
she was very young.
But even after she
was gone physically,
she was still there for me.
Her spirit gave me the
strength to keep going.
[MAVIS]
If Zera had lived,
I think she probably would've
grown up to be like you.
Oh, yeah?
[grunts]
Actually, forget I said that.
Damn, that's so rude!
Zera's in my heart.
So even to this day,
she's with me.
But not inside of
this empty projection.
She lives in my real heart.
Cana, we both need your help.
You're the only one who
can free me and Zera
from this crystal coffin.
So please...
[MAVIS]
You aren't "attacking" anybody.
You're using your power
to save a friend.
[LISANNA, MIRAJANE yell]
[ELFMAN growls]
Man, there are a
lot of these jokers.
But... I got somethin'
for all of 'em!
[GAJEEL]
Karmic Demon... Iron God Sword!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[crying]
[ROGUE] Come on, Sting,
you have to snap out of it.
It's all my fault.
I'm nothing but a screw-up.
I'm supposed to be the
master of our guild.
[YUKINO]
You are our master, Sting.
And that means, when things
get as dark as they are now,
you lead us out of it.
Yukino.
You can do it. I know
you have what it takes.
I'm sorry. That
must've been painful.
[YUKINO]
No, uh.
I mean, I slapped you, so
wouldn't that hurt you more?
[STING]
Having to do something like that
because your master is pathetic
is the painful part of it.
Uh, you're not pathetic.
I'm sorry. I just didn't
know what to do.
Someone needed to knock
some sense into me.
We gotta learn from this
experience and grow stronger.
If you can still
walk, follow me!
We're Tigers, yeah?
We're hungry for a fight!
And right now,
it's feeding time!
[SABERTOOTH]
Yeah!
Let's do this!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
You win! Stop! Sorry for
lookin' at your panties!
We'll fight for Mister Ichiya!
Our hero! A man who was
way too young to die!
Ichiya's still alive!
[SOLDIER B]
Whoa!
[SOLDIER C]
What's happening?
[SOLDIER D]
We're floating!
Yi Ragdo!
[MINERVA] Those savages
made our master weep.
No mercy.
Feel better, Master Crybaby?
Call me whatever
you want. Who cares?
Don't you start!
[JULIET]
Hmmm.
The ones who were taken prisoner
seem like they're
doing better now.
Should we attack them?
What do you think, my lady?
Bloodman and Larcade
are drawing near.
They'll handle it.
[WIZARDS, SOLDIERS yelling]
Bill, no!
[WIZARDS groaning]
[WIZARD D]
Everyone's dying! What is this?
[WIZARD A]
Uh! The Grim Reaper!
[WIZARD E]
Run!
[WIZARD F]
The Grim Reaper's coming back!
[WIZARD G]
He's gonna crucify us again!
[WIZARD H] I don't think
I'd survive it this time!
[ALL gasp]
No way.
We'll get revenge for you.
They'll be pickin' their
teeth up off the ground.
[GAJEEL]
How do you like bein' crucified?
For me, this is just bringin'
up some bad memories.
Better than what
your future holds.
[BLOODMAN]
You have touched death.
There will be no reprieve,
and no escape.
You think so?
Which means this must
be my lucky day!
Because I was
gettin' pretty sick
of lookin' for a place to die.
Now, Juliet, Heine. Go join
them on the front line.
Yes, ma'am!
[JULIET]
What? How come?
You just said Bloodman and
Larcade would handle everything.
Show some respect.
When our lady gives an order,
we follow it. Idiot.
Our third guest will
be arriving shortly.
Our third guest?
Yes.
The Horses and Tigers,
those were our first guests.
The Fairies were
today's second guests.
Soon, we'll be meeting
a third group.
And this one could
be a bit of trouble.
[ANGEL]
Here we are!
The mobile temple Olympia
has joined the party!
Our lawless days are done.
And now we're a force for
justice. We're Crime Sorciere!
What the hell?
I thought this was
a snowy mountain.
[COBRA] I just wanna
be on solid ground.
[gasps]
Something wrong, Yukino?
Nothing. Don't worry about me.
[IRENE] But the most troublesome
of all will be our fourth guest.
Another one?
Seems like too many to me!
[IRENE] This guest is
neither friend nor foe.
I shall have to deal
with them personally.
I don't know who they are, but
they're already being stupid.
Yeah, Lady Irene's a
High Enchanter after all,
so they're in for it.
Sucks for them.
Bein' huge is pretty
awesome, huh?
[HAPPY]
Aye!
I've never felt this cool!
Could you turn him back?!
So fluffy!
[BRANDISH] Sorry, Lucy, I just
did what he asked me to.
But the way he looks is
really freaking me out!
[BRANDISH]
He seems to enjoy it.
[gasping]
[screams]
[growls]
Stop playing around with
people's bodies, would ya?
I'm not sure why,
but you're definitely the
most fun to mess with, Lucy.
Ain't she?
We don't have time to be
playing these foolish games.
[gasps]
Whoa, you feel that?
Magic power.
There's no mistaking him.
Wait. You can't be serious.
He's this strong?
That's why he's called
the Wizard King.
I'm fired up now!
Natsu, we're here to talk, okay?
I've got a bad feeling
about this guy.
[COBRA groans]
[COBRA]
Have we stopped movin' yet?
'Cause I still feel
like I'm gonna hurl.
You'll feel better soon. It just
might take a moment or two.
However, in the meantime,
I think we should start flexing
the Olympia's muscle
a little bit.
Mobile temple Olympia,
main cannon, engage! 'Kay?
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Be careful! They're
firing cannons!
Hang on! Looks like they're
targeting the invaders!
Does that mean it's
on our side? Awesome!
[WIZARD O] We've got some
serious backup now, guys!
[WIZARD P]
Yeah! But who is it?
Is something the matter?
You're not injured, are you?
Yukino, you can leave
the front line if need be.
[YUKINO]
No, it's nothing.
I'm sorry. I'll be okay.
[YUKINO] For some reason,
I've got this strange sensation.
Our fourth guest will
be arriving any moment.
We need to be prepared for them.
Seems his Majesty's little
strategy game has ended.
A more straightforward attack
would've already resulted
in victory, I'm sure.
But now, the game board
has been broken
by someone who doesn't
play by the rules.
Acnologia and his
wings of darkness.
A black dragon
coming to the spot
where the white
maiden prevailed.
As if seeking revenge.
But I know the last laugh
will belong to me.
The scarlet maiden.
After all, I'm known in some
places as the "Scarlet Despair."
There must be a more
charming name than that.
[IRENE chuckles]
My bane particles spell doom
for any wizard who inhales them.
Soon, you'll feel the sensation
of your organs liquefying.
Yeah, I don't think so,
'cause my lungs
are made of iron!
Excellent news.
It's been too long
since I've faced a truly
challenging opponent!
Iron Dragon Spear!
My body is made
of Bane Particles,
so touching me will
seal your doom.
I am a god of death! Dragging
all I face into the underworld!
[GAJEEL screaming]
Perhaps you can survive this.
But what about those
without your gifts?
Everyone get away, right now!
Don't come near him!
[BLOODMAN] My legion of the
dead will consume your soul!
All these bones. Ah, damn it!
[LEVY]
Solid Script Shine!
Some type of light? Holy magic?
[GAJEEL]
What the--?
[LEVY]
I'm not gonna leave you!
Levy! You gotta go!
Uh! Good thinkin'.
I don't wanna hear
you say things
like you're lookin'
for a place to die.
Uh, that was just fight talk.
I was trying to sound
cool and intimidating.
What's that look?
I didn't mean it!
This is serious.
Your life is important to me.
You can't die.
So watch what you say.
Those who oppose me
cannot escape death.
I'll drag your souls
through the gates of hell.
For I am death.
And this promise of life
you cling to will be broken
without any mercy.
Now what is this?
The magic energy of the
very land has changed.
Irene. Just what are
you planning to do?
[AUGUST] Tell me. What
is the meaning of this?
[BRANDISH] I've come here
to negotiate with you.
I assume the enemies
killed Jacob?
[BRANDISH]
He's been defeated.
However, instead of killing him,
they've taken him prisoner.
God Serena, where has he gone?
He's confined to our memory.
I thought Brandish's
magic power was crazy,
but August is on a
whole other level.
[NATSU growls]
It's like night and day.
[MEST] I think they're putting
that extremely lightly.
I mean, the power coming from
him is not even of this world.
[AUGUST] So then, what do
you mean by "negotiate"?
[BRANDISH]
I'd like you to walk away.
[AUGUST]
Hmm.
It doesn't appear to me
that you've been tortured,
which leads me to wonder...
What's brought about this
betrayal of our homeland?
I'm not betraying anyone.
I'm still devoted to Alvarez.
However, I feel like there's
no meaning to this war.
[AUGUST] So you'd dare
act in direct opposition
to his Majesty's wishes.
We've pledged our lives
in service to the Emperor.
If you cannot comprehend why
His Majesty wages this war,
then you are among the enemy.
[GAJEEL]
Hey.
That mask you made for yourself,
you positive it's gonna work?
It's Solid Script magic,
so of course I'm positive.
[BLOODMAN]
When the first seal is broken,
Bane Particles drain
your magic power.
The second opens a gate
to the underworld
beneath this field of corpses.
Upon breaking the third seal,
the god of death renders
judgment upon you.
And when that happens,
you are condemned down
to the land of the dead.
I get that you're
tryin' to be scary,
but your magic power is a joke.
You got nothin' on the
rest of the Twelve, do ya?
That's because I wield
the power of curses.
So does that mean
what I think it does?
I control what rises from
the depths of Tartaros.
Curse Power... Explosion Spiral!
[LEVY screaming]
[GAJEEL screaming]
Tenka Goken! Onimaru!
[roars]
[BLOODMAN]
Unleash, Dark Deluge!
Are you kiddin' me?!
This again?
[GAJEEL] Aw, man, can he use
all the Tartaros curses?
[LEVY]
Maybe.
But I'm not falling for
the same trick twice!
Solid Script Hole!
Nice one, Levy!
[GAJEEL]
Iron Dragon Roar!
[BLOODMAN]
Ice Demon Rage!
[BLOODMAN] Behold, a curse
beyond the Nine Demons.
To the underworld.
The dead begin to scurry.
Damn it!
The third seal breaks
as judgment is rendered.
[BLOODMAN]
Over Skelter!
[GAJEEL screaming]
[LEVY screaming]
Levy!
My death vortex... How
could they have escaped it?
[coughing]
[gasps] Oh, no! Your mask!
You gotta get it back on, now!
[LEVY]
I'm sorry. I was bluffing.
The truth is... it never worked
[gasps]
[LEVY] Bane Particles
don't just get inhaled,
they're absorbed
through the skin, too.
I guess I never had
a chance, huh?
Then why in the hell
did you even come here?!
I hoped I could save you...
[gasps] Levy!
[LUCY] As Levy succumbs
to the poisonous cloud
of Bloodman's Bane Particles,
Gajeel has to risk everything
to beat the god of death
and save her life.
He struggles against this
powerful, curse-wielding foe
in a battle which could
very well be his last.
With his iron fists swinging,
he fights to protect
everything dear to him.
Next Time: "Together, Always."
Gajeel holds tightly to
the dream of a future
filled with happiness.