[LUCY]
Open! Gate of the King!
[KING growls]
[CROWD murmurs]
A fallen star or king?
[KING]
You know who I am.
[JACKAL]
What the hell is goin' on here?
Hey, stop yer cryin'
and start talkin'!
No! No! No!
What could've taken
down Plutogrim?
Seems like the old flying beast
has finally been put to sleep.
Those vile fairies. What now?
It has been quite a while,
King of the Stars.
[KING]
Not long enough, Mard Geer.
[MARD GEER] I must say, I'm
very surprised to see you again.
Perhaps most surprised
at my miscalculation.
I didn't think anyone
here could summon you.
[KING]
I see you're still
lugging that battered
tome around with you.
Have you not yet fulfilled
your ambition?
[MARD GEER]
This holds the spirit of E.N.D.
The embodiment of Tartaros.
[KING]
Ah.
And you still seek to bring
life from those dead pages?
[MARD GEER] You know very
well what my goal is.
To revive E.N.D.
and return to Zeref.
Until it has been achieved,
I will not waver.
[KING] Mard Geer. You've always
been such a twisted fool.
Feet firmly planted in
the mire of avarice.
So blinded by your ambition
that you would plunge the
entire world into chaos.
Yes, I would. But I'm not blind.
I clearly see our journey's end.
We have come far in
our return to Zeref.
In fact, it's looming
on the horizon.
[LUCY cries]
[KING]
My old friend is on the ground.
Sobbing and twisted in pain.
Did she try to impede
your journey?
Yes, she did.
[LUCY cries]
[KING] The tears she sheds.
They anger me.
Are you the one who
caused them to flow?
[MARD GEER] I think the time
for discussion has long passed,
wouldn't you agree?
[KING]
Yes. Wholeheartedly.
In order to fulfill my
obligation to my old friend,
I will eliminate all
who would do her harm.
Will you?
[KING] You will pay dearly
for your transgressions!
[KING roars]
[KING] Is your only strategy
to flee, Underworld King?
[MARD GEER] You're exactly
the same as you've always been.
With the same glaring weakness.
It's quite a relief.
It means that I can remain
assured in my victory.
[KING] And you still
are nothing but talk.
Lulled into complacency and
false pride by your own words.
Curse of Thorns.
[KING grunting]
May these never ending briars
ensnare your ponderous bulk.
And bring about your ruin!
[MARD GEER]
Earlier, you chided me.
Indicted me for
my willingness
to throw the world into
chaos to achieve my goals.
Did you not?
It seems to me that your
memory is growing feeble.
Let me remind you
of recent events.
Not long ago you and your
"eclipse" spirits threatened
not only your own world,
but this one as well.
And now you barge
in here threatening
to harm me and my
demonic brethren.
How you reek of the putrid
stench of hypocrisy.
[KING]
You are mistaken.
I admit, we did
stray from our path.
We let misguided ambition
rule and paid dearly for it.
But our friends risked
everything they had
and set us back on course.
It is for that reason
I'm here today.
I owe it to them to render aid
when they need it most.
That is the true meaning
of friendship.
These brambles may set
me back momentarily,
but the pain they
inflict is nothing
compared to the suffering my
friends endured to help me.
You will not hold me back!
Is that so?
[KING]
I shall vow again and again!
To pay tribute to
the life of my friend,
and the sacred bond we share.
I will eliminate you!
You missed.
[KING]
Meteor Blade!
I'm impressed. However,
"Celestial Spirit King,"
as I said before, you
have a glaring weakness.
Even your title betrays it.
[KING]
What do you mean?
You're bound by
celestial law.
The rules that govern your
interaction in this world.
So although you may
tower over me now,
my ultimate victory
is set in stone.
Aw, damnit!
My tail's caught under
this friggin' boulder!
[JACKAL grunting]
So what happened? Why did
our fortress crash and burn?
Uh?!
[LUCY cries]
[JACKAL]
You did this? Didn't you?
[JACKAL] Stop with all
the pitiful blubbering
and answer me! Whenever
I see someone crying
like that, it makes me
wanna gouge out their eyes!
[LUCY cries]
I said enough!
[JACKAL]
What?!
[LUCY]
A force-field of water?
Aquarius?! Are you here?!
Please, talk to me!
[gasps]
The hell?
Hey, why are you glowing
like some kinda star?!
You tryin' to pull another
one of your freaky stunts?
I can feel it. Magic power.
[KING] Aquarius holds a
great deal of magic power
in her hands. And that is
now shared with you.
[LUCY]
Celestial Spirit King?
[KING]
Use it. Stand up!
[LUCY] This was her last
gift to me. Her power.
[KING] Rise and make use
of what you've been given!
[LUCY]
I will!
[KING]
My old friend.
May the radiance of
the stars be your guide.
[LUCY]
Thank you, your majesty!
[JACKAL growls]
You stupid girl!
[LUCY] You too, Aquarius.
For everything you've done.
You forget my curse?
Lemme remind you!
[JACKAL] Burn baby burn!
Explode into a million pieces!
[panting] That did it!
There won't even be
a body left to bury!
No way! That's impossible!
[LUCY]
You're right, Aquarius.
[JACKAL] Hey you!
How dare you ignore me!
You'll be sorry! I'll
make you burn for real!
[LUCY]
I can't keep on crying forever.
This'll get your attention!
Explosion Spiral!
[LUCY]
I have to save my tears.
[JACKAL grunts]
What the...? I don't get it!
[LUCY] Because right now,
I need to help my friends.
[LUCY]
I need to fight!
[JACKAL]
Huh?
[LUCY] Oh stars far and wide
that embody the heavens.
I implore you, Tetrabiblos.
By thy radiance,
reveal thy form to me.
Eternal ruler of the stars...
What is she babbling about?
[LUCY] Now that the
aspect is complete,
I ask that you to lend
your power to me.
Let your unrestrained rage flow.
Open the raging,
tumultuous gate!
[JACKAL]
I dunno what she's saying,
but I know that it's not
gonna be good!
With all 88 heavenly bodies.
Shining Uranometria!
[JACKAL]
No! Don't do it!
--[JACKAL screams]
--[LUCY yells]
Jackal's curse power is no more.
[SILVER]
That little cockroach.
What is this magic?
[KEYES] Conjury of the celestial
world. The maiden survived.
[KING yells]
You're not as spry as before.
Could it be that
something is ailing you?
[KING] It seems my old friend
has exhausted her strength.
[MARD GEER] A spirit,
however large and imposing
they may appear is inexorably
bound to its summoner.
So if that wizard's magic
power is depleted, well,
the spirit also loses its
potency. It really is a shame.
But regardless.
This is where you end.
[KING] I swore an oath
to eliminate you.
[KING]
Come to me.
May the starlight fantasy of
the 88 illuminated bodies
imbue this spirit with
celestial might.
[KING]
Galaxia Blade!
It's an omni-directional attack?
Your summoner is nearby, will
you "eliminate" her, as well?
[KING]
Smile!
[MARD GEER]
You wouldn't dare!
What could this
strange light be?
[laughs]
Erza!
[ERZA]
I will strike you down!
Yes! The fight I hunger
for! What I need!
[ERZA grunts]
The passion is electric!
It makes me feel alive!
[GRAY grunting]
What the hell just happened?
Hey, Pantherlily!
Where'd you go?
[JUVIA] Gray, my love!
Where are you?
Call my name and
I'll come running!
Well that sucked.
Is it over now?
Shadow Gear! Levy?
Are ya here?
[DROY] We're here. It's a
miracle that we're not dead.
Yeah, right. But I'm
getting crushed over here.
[JET, DROY]
Hang on! I'm comin'!
You're not playin hero, tubby.
That's cuz' I obviously am one.
Clean out your ears.
She clearly called for me!
Bullcrap, we both heard her
say "please save me, Droy!"
Manly!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks!
[JET, DROY]
They beat us to it!
[ELFMAN] So, uh? Can anybody
tell me what all that was?
[LEVY]
I'm not really sure,
but I think we're back
on the ground now.
[LISANNA] Yeah, you're
right. So did we fall?
[HAPPY]
Natsu! Where are you?
My head feels kinda weird.
Like it's heavier or something.
[MACAO]
Hey!
[ELFMAN, LISANNA]
Huh?
Are you okay?
Man, am I glad to see you!
I smoke too much to be running.
Does this mean we're all
up and moving around again?
[ELFMAN] I just know, that I
think we're alive.
[ROMEO]
What's the matter with Mirajane?
[LISANNA]
She's just exhausted.
She needs a little
time to recover.
All right! We gotta go
check on everybody else.
Now we're gonna find some
injured. They'll need our help.
Yeah!
Let's go get our guild mates!
It's crazy out here.
But we'll find them.
I wonder about
Natsu and Lucy.
[MACAO]
I'm sure they're fine, but...
[MARD GEER whimpering]
You've broken the Alegria curse.
[KING]
The cleansing light of the stars
has chased away the sinister
shadow you've cast.
My old friend and her comrades
will finish the job here.
They will send you back
where you belong.
[MARD GEER]
Curse you.
[KING] Once again, your lack
of understanding is glaring.
You saw my bond as a chain
tying me to a weight.
But this is not so. This bond
connects our hearts and minds.
It means we share in our goals.
It means we will finish what
the other has begun,
without question.
[KING]
It is far from a "weakness".
In fact, this bond is our
greatest strength.
Now your weakness is exposed.
Your ignorance of love,
trust, and friendship.
The concepts would
never enter your mind.
So you neglect them,
at your own peril.
But before I leave this place
for the celestial world.
And my old friend continues
the task we share.
There is one more thing I must
do to help my comrades.
My dear friend. I look forward
to our next meeting.
I know it will be under more
joyful circumstances.
[MARD GEER]
You're running away?!
No. What is this?
Does that starry-eyed old
fool think he can stop me?
I know that victory shall
be mine in the end.
If the humans and the
king truly share hearts.
I'll just have to make
them cease their beating.
They will share death.
[TORAFUZAR]
How is this possible?
That pitiful little girl took
out both Lummy and Jackal?
[TORAFUZAR] Her magic must be
more powerful than we thought.
I can't stop. They need
me. I gotta help them.
[TORAFUZAR]
He should've just killed her
when he had the chance!
But I'll do it now.
Gajeel.
This can't be.
I thought that the girl was
the only remaining survivor!
[GAJEEL]
Huh?
[KEYES]
It would appear
Mard Geer's Alegria curse
has been lifted.
But still. The fairies will
fall! It is their fate!
Water Nebula!
Juvia.
[JUVIA] I won't let
you harm my friends!
You should cool down.
[JUVIA gasps]
Not happenin'!
[LUCY]
Gray.
[KEYES] Mm. The boy
cancelled out Silver's ice.
Nice one.
Uh!
Fwoosh.
Fire?
[TEMPESTER] What is this?
He's eating my fire attack?
[NATSU] Wow, Lucy, I don't
know how you did it.
But you saved the day.
You are one tough little lady.
We'll work together and
finish what you started.
You deserve to take a break.
[LUCY]
Thank you.
[NATSU]
All right!
Looks like we've got
our work cut out for us.
These guys are serious!
I'm fired up now!
[LUCY] Fairy Tail is
finally back in action
and ready to spring
into battle against
the demon gates of Tartaros!
Meanwhile, Wendy and Carla
learn the disturbing truth
about the plan to use Face,
and it's not over yet.
Tension is building everywhere.
And as our members
pick up the pieces,
Erza and Minerva's rivalry
has exploded into a
life or death face off!
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
- Erza vs.Minerva"
[LUCY] Where does true
strength come from?