- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- Lucy: OUR COALITION FORCE
COURAGEOUSLY STOOD UP
TO THE ORACION SEIS.
THAT IS UNTIL THEY DESTROYED
OUR TRUMP CARD,
THE MAGIC BOMBER,
CHRISTINA.
- Hoteye: OH, YEAH!
- Gray: WE HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO HEAD-TO-HEAD
WITH THEM.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT DIDN'T GO SO WELL
AND THEY TOTALLY WHOOPED US.
- Hoteye: OH, YEAH!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
- MAN, THEY'RE WAY STRONGER
THAN WE THOUGHT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, BRAIN?
YOU GONNA CAST
THE SPELL OR WHAT?
- DO YOU KNOW HER?
- NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THAT'S WENDY.
THE MAIDEN OF THE SKY.
- WHAT?
MAIDEN OF THE SKY?
- WENDY?
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I WAS GONNA ASK YOU.
- ( crying )
- ( Happy speaking )
- TO THINK WE SIMPLY
STUMBLED UPON HER HERE.
WE MADE QUITE A FIND,
MY FRIENDS.
GRAB HER!
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- Both: WENDY!
- UNHAND HER NOW!
- HELP ME!
- I'LL SAVE YOU AS SOON
AS I'M ABLE TO CATCH UP!
- STRIKING WHILE WE'RE DOWN?
THAT ISN'T FAIR.
- ALL IS FAIR
IN MONEY AND WAR.
OH, YEAH.
- ( gasps )
AAH!
- CARLA!
- GRAB MY PAW!
- WHOA!  OHH!
- YOU'VE GOT THE WRONG CAT.
- ( screams )
- NATSU!
- WENDY!
- HAPPY!
- I HAVE NO USE
FOR THE REST OF YOU.
BE GONE!
DARK RONDO!
- GET DOWN.
- LUCY!
- ( grunts )
- I'VE GOT YOU.
- YES, HOLD ME IN
YOUR LOVING ARMS.
- IRON ROCK WALL!
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
- THAT WAS AWESOME!
- ( chuckles )
- YOU'RE THE BEST WIZARD EVER.
- I'LL SECOND THAT.
WE OWE YOU ONE.
- YEAH, WE WERE
ALMOST GONERS.
THANKS A MILLION.
- OKAY.
LET'S TAKE THEM DOWN.
HUH?
- Gray:
THEY'RE LONG GONE BY NOW.
- Natsu:
WHY'D WE LET THEM GET AWAY?
- OH, WENDY.
- THEY WIPED THE FLOOR
WITH US.
- WELL, THEY'RE A LOT
STRONGER THAN WE ARE.
WE NEVER STOOD A CHANCE
AGAINST THEM.
- Lyon: THE ORACION SEIS.
WHAT UNBELIEVABLE POWER.
- Hibiki: AND THERE ARE
ONLY SIX OF THEM.
THEIR MAGIC IS MUCH STRONGER
THAN THE RUMORS SUGGESTED.
- Sherry: JUST LOOK AT WHAT
THEY DID TO CHRISTINA.
- Jura: ACCORDING TO ANGEL,
THE WOMAN WHO PEERS INTO MINDS,
THEY KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT OUR MISSION.
WE'RE LUCKY
NO LIVES WERE LOST.
- WAIT A SEC.
WHAT ABOUT ALL
THE PEOPLE INSIDE?
- DON'T WORRY, PRETTY LADY.
- CHRISTINA'S EQUIPPED WITH
A REMOTE CONTROL FUNCTION,
SO THERE'S NO NEED
FOR A PILOT.
- WE WERE GONNA CLIMB ABOARD
ONCE WE FOUND THEIR BASE,
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE NEVER MADE IT THAT FAR.
- OH, GOOD.
THAT'S A RELIEF.
- GLAD TO SEE YOU
MADE IT OUT UNSCATHED.
- NOT QUITE. IN FACT,
I BARELY MADE IT OUT ALIVE.
- HM?  YOU'RE WOUNDED?
- THEIR POWER TERRIFIES ME.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT IF IT
WEREN'T FOR SIR ICHIYA'S
PAIN KILLER PARFUM,
I WOULD BE IN
UTTER AGONY RIGHT NOW.
- DETESTABLE ORACION SEIS.
INSTEAD OF BRAVELY
FACING YOUR FOES,
YOU DECIDED TO FLEE.
WHICH MEANS WE WIN
BY DEFAULT!
- THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS,
YOU WEIRDO!
- LOOK, PAL,
WE MAY BE BATTERED,
BUT WE ARE NOT BEATEN.
HERE, TAKE A WHIFF,
AND LET MY PAIN KILLER PARFUM
EASE YOUR DISCOMFORT.
- WOW.  WHAT A LOVELY SCENT.
- AND IT WORKS.
MY PAIN IS JUST FADING AWAY.
- MAN.
- IF ONLY HE COULD
CAST THE SPELL
WITHOUT ALL THE BIZARRE POSING.
- WAY TO GO, CHIEF.
- All: GO CHIEF!
- THEY CALLED HIM
SOMETHING DIFFERENT AGAIN.
- I BET THEY'RE DOING IT
JUST TO ANNOY US.
- WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
HOW DARE THOSE PUNKS
RUN OFF WITH WENDY AND HAPPY.
THIS SUCKS!
I GOT TO GO FIND THEM!
- HEY!  WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
- ( gasps )
( groans )
- YOU MUSTN'T BE RECKLESS.
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN
AND THINK THIS THROUGH.
- THOSE WINGS.
- WAS SHE HIDING THEM?
- YOU CAN FLY?
- THAT'S SO COOL!
- YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
AERA MAGIC BEFORE?
WELL IN THAT CASE,
I SUPPOSE IT'S ONLY NATURAL
THAT YOU WOULD
FIND IT SURPRISING.
- YOU'RE TRYING TO
COPY HAPPY, AREN'T YOU?
- AS IF, DIMWIT!
- NOW NOW,
WE CAN HAVE TWO FLYING CATS.
- THOUGH I AM CONCERNED
ABOUT WENDY AND THAT TOMCAT,
THIS IS NOT A FOE
TO BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.
WE CANNOT FACE THEM AGAIN UNTIL
WE'VE COME UP
WITH A PLAN OF ATTACK.
- I WHOLEHEARTEDLY AGREE,
LADY CARLA.
THE ENEMY IS FAR STRONGER
THAN WE ANTICIPATED.
- MAN.
- BUT FIRST...
- ( wincing )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( gasps )
- I'M NO DOCTOR,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
THE VENOM FROM HER
SNAKEBITE IS SPREADING.
- MASTER ICHIYA--
- I GOT THIS, MEN.
I KNOW WHAT YOU NEED,
MY HONEY.
A LITTLE PAIN KILLER PARFUM!
AROMA INCREASE!
- ( groans )
- SINCE WHEN ARE PAIN KILLERS
AN ANTIDOTE FOR SNAKE VENOM?
- HIS PARFUM DOES MORE
THAN EASE PAIN.
IT ALSO HAS A CLEANSING EFFECT
THAT'LL HELP HER BODY
EXPEL ANY TOXINS.
- OH, YEAH.
- ( groans )
- ERZA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S
IN EVEN MORE PAIN NOW.
- HUH?  YOU THINK SO?
- ( screams )
- OH, MAN.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I DON'T KNOW.
HIS PAIN KILLER PARFUM
HAS NEVER FAILED BEFORE.
- ERZA, HANG IN THERE.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- I'M SORRY, LUCY.
- HMM?
- I NEED TO BORROW YOUR BELT!
- ( yelps )
WAIT A MINUTE!
( screams )
- ( laughing )
- LOOK AWAY!
- ( grunts )
- JUST WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO WITH THAT?
- IT'S HARSH,
BUT IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN KEEP FIGHTING.
SOMEBODY CUT IT OFF.
- ( all gasping )
- AT LEAST GIVE US TIME
TO FIND AN ANTIDOTE.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME.
- VERY WELL.
I WILL DO IT.
- HOW KIND OF YOU.
- PUT DOWN THE SWORD.
- DO IT!
- NO, DON'T!
- UM, LYON,
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
GONNA DO IT?
- WE CAN'T LOSE
ONE OF OUR STRONGEST
WHEN WE'RE FACING
SUCH A POWERFUL FOE.
- YEAH, BUT--
- OH, COME ON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE GOT STUCK
WITH YOU WIMPY FAIRIES.
QUIT WHINING.
YOU'RE FRIEND'S GONNA DIE
IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING
TO HELP HER.
- YOUR FRIEND'S GONNA DIE
IF HE DOESN'T
PUT DOWN THAT SWORD.
- WHY IS THAT?
THIS IS JUST HIS WAY
OF SHOWING LOVE.
- JUST HURRY UP
AND CUT IT OFF!
BEFORE THE VENOM SPREADS
TO THE REST OF MY BODY!
- PUT THE SWORD DOWN!
- DON'T DO IT.
YOU WANT TO BE KNOWN AS THE GUY
WHO MAIMED ERZA?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
STOP.  WE'LL FIND A CURE.
- WE HAVE NO RIGHT
TO INTERFERE
WITH HER WISHES.
- READY?
- ( gasps )
- ( all gasp )
- HER ARM IS MORE IMPORTANT
TO YOU THAN HER LIFE?
WHERE ARE YOUR PRIORITIES?
- THIS'LL AFFECT HER
FOR THE REST OF HER LIFE,
SO WE CAN'T JUMP THE GUN.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
ANOTHER WAY WE CAN SAVE HER.
- YOU'RE JUST
AS SPINELESS AS EVER.
FIGURES.
- I REALLY THOUGHT
YOU HAD CHANGED,
BUT YOU'RE JUST AS
SHADY AS EVER.
- ( gasps )
- ERZA!
- OH, NO.
- THIS IS BAD, GUYS.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP THE VENOM FROM SPREADING
OR SHE'LL DIE.
- WE NEED WENDY.
SHE COULD SAVE YOUR FRIEND.
THIS IS NO TIME FOR US TO BE
BICKERING AMONGST OURSELVES.
WE NEED TO WORK TOGETHER
TO COME UP WITH A PLAN
TO RESCUE WENDY.
AND I SUPPOSE
THAT TOMCAT TOO.
- WAIT A SEC.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT LITTLE GIRL
HAS SOME KIND OF
ANTI-VENOM MAGIC?
- AMAZING.
- NOT JUST ANTI-VENOM.
SHE CAN CURE FEVERS,
RELIEVE PAIN,
AND HEAL WOUNDS.
- UM, EXCUSE ME.
I FEEL AS THOUGH MY
ROLE IN THE GROUP
IS BEING THREATENED, AND I
FIND THAT RATHER UNSETTLING.
- THAT'S CRAZY. EVERYONE KNOWS
HEALING SPELLS ARE LOST MAGIC.
THERE'S NO WAY
THE KID COULD USE THEM.
- DO THESE POWERS HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH
THAT WHOLE
"MAIDEN OF THE SKY" THING?
- YES IT DOES.
YOU SEE,
THAT LITTLE GIRL
IS THE SKY DRAGON SLAYER.
SHE'S WENDY, THE SKY DRAGON.
- ( all gasp )
- SHE'S A DRAGON SLAYER TOO?!
- I'LL GIVE YOU
ALL THE DETAILS LATER.
ALTHOUGH TO BE HONEST,
THERE'S REALLY NOT MUCH MORE
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
- ( exhales )
- WENDY IS THE ONLY WIZARD
CAPABLE OF SAVING YOUR FRIEND.
WE NEED HER RIGHT NOW.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THE ORACION SEIS
FEEL THEY NEED HER TOO
FOR SOME UNKNOWN REASON.
- IN THAT CASE...
- THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
FOR US TO DO.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
RESCUE WENDY.
- WE'LL DO IT FOR
ERZA'S SAKE.
- AND HAPPY'S TOO.
- OKAY!
ARE YOU WITH ME?!
- All: YEAH!
- Narrator:
DEEP INSIDE THE WORTH WOODSEA,
THERE IS A VILLAGE
THAT WAS ONCE THE CAPITAL
OF AN ANCIENT CIVILIZATION.
THIS WAS WHERE
THE VILLAGERS WORSHIPPED.
IT IS SAID A PRIESTESS
WOULD ENTER THIS CAVE
IN ORDER TO HEAR
THE WORDS OF THE GODS.
HOWEVER,
IN THIS DAY AND AGE,
THE SACRED CAVE SERVES
AS A HIDEOUT
FOR THE ORACION SEIS.
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- HEY!  DON'T BE SO ROUGH.
SHE'S JUST A LITTLE GIRL,
YOU KNOW.
- HAPPY.
- ( whimpers )
( muffled yelling )
- LET HIM GO!
- ( grunts )
- WHOA...
- YOU'RE NOT HURT
TOO BAD, ARE YOU?
- NO.  DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, LITTLE LADY.
I'M GONNA DO MY BEST
TO FIND US A WAY OUT OF HERE.
PROMISE.
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
I DON'T GET WHY
THIS GIRL IS SO IMPORTANT.
- DOES SHE HAVE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH NIRVANA?
- SHE DOESN'T SEEM
ALL THAT SPECIAL TO ME.
- IS SHE WORTH MONEY?
YOU'RE GONNA SELL HER TO
THE HIGHEST BIDDER, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH!
- YOU REALIZE THAT CASH
ISN'T THE ANSWER
TO EVERYTHING?
- WELL I THINK IT IS,
BECAUSE MONEY
CAN BUY EVERYTHING,
EVEN LOVE.
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
- SHE USES WHAT'S CALLED
"SKY MAGIC."
IT GIVES HER THE POWER
TO HEAL OTHERS.
- HOW'S THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
- ISN'T IT A LOST MAGIC?
- ONE OF MANY PRACTICES
FORGOTTEN LONG AGO.
- ( snores )
- OH, YEAH.
I CAN PRACTICALLY
SMELL THE MONEY.
- ( chuckles )
WHAT GOOD IS A HEALER TO US?
WAIT, YOU DON'T MEAN...
- SHE IS THE KEY.
WITH HER POWER,
WE SHALL REVIVE HIM!
- WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- LOOK, IF YOU'RE ASKING
ME TO HELP YOU, FORGET IT!
I'D NEVER DO ANYTHING
FOR JERKS LIKE YOU.
- YES, YOU WILL.
THERE'S NO DOUBT.
- ( exhales )
- ONCE YOU FIND OUT
WHO IT IS,
YOU'LL BE MORE
THAN HAPPY TO HELP.
- ( gasps )
- RACER,
BRING HIM TO ME AT ONCE.
- WILL DO, BOSS.
BUT IT'S SO FAR,
IT'LL TAKE ME AN HOUR
TO GET THERE AND BACK.
- NO MATTER.
- I SEE.
ONCE HE'S REVIVED...
WE'LL BE ABLE TO
FIND NIRVANA IN NO TIME.
YOU'RE DOING
YOUR NAME PROUD, SIR.
- COBRA, HOTEYE, ANGEL,
I WANT YOU TO CONTINUE
THE SEARCH FOR NIRVANA.
- BUT WHY?
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
WE SHOULD BEGIN THE SEARCH
AFTER HE'S BEEN REVIVED.
- COME ON.
YOU GUYS JUST TELL US
WHO YOU'RE TRYING
TO BRING BACK.
- I WOULD PREFER TO ERR
ON THE SIDE OF CAUTION.
MIDNIGHT AND I
WILL REMAIN HERE.
SOMETHING TELLS ME HE WON'T
MAKE VERY GOOD COMPANY.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
GUESS WE'D BETTER
GET GOING.
- YOU BOYS WANT TO RACE ME?
WHOEVER'S THE FIRST
TO FIND NIRVANA
WINS A PRIZE--
- IN THE AMOUNT OF
ONE MILLION JEWEL!
OH, YEAH!
COUNT ME IN.
- DON'T YOU THINK
A MILLION'S A BIT MUCH?
- BE HONEST WITH ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THESE CREEPS
ARE TALKING ABOUT,
DO YOU?
- UM, WELL NO.
NOT REALLY.
WHAT DOES NIRVANA DO?
PLEASE TELL US THAT MUCH.
- IT'S INCREDIBLY POWERFUL.
IT SWAPS LIGHT
FOR DARKNESS.
- UH...
- BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ME NEITHER.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
NATSU AND THE OTHERS
DECIDE TO SPLIT UP INTO GROUPS
SO THEY CAN COVER MORE GROUND
IN THEIR SEARCH FOR WENDY AND
HAPPY.
THE FIRST GROUP IS
NATSU AND GRAY OF FAIRY TAIL,
ALONG WITH CARLA
OF CAIT SHELTER.
THEN THERE'S JURA,
LYON, AND SHERRY
OF LAMIA SCALE.
AND THE BOYS OF
BLUE PEGASUS,
ICHIYA, REN, AND EVE.
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
I HAVEN'T HEARD
A SINGLE "MAN."
- I THOUGHT HE WAS
RIGHT BEHIND US.
- I GUESS WE MUST
HAVE LOST HIM.
- REN!
AND EVE!
WHERE ARE YOU, MAN?
- ( chuckling )
- Narrator: THAT LEAVES US
WITH LUCY OF FAIRY TAIL,
AND HIBIKI OF BLUE PEGASUS,
WHO'VE CHOSEN TO STAY
BY THE AILING ERZA'S SIDE.
- ( gasping )
- IT'S BAD.
COME ON, GUYS,
PLEASE HURRY.
- ( murmurs )
- YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
GONNA HELP, RIGHT?
INSTEAD OF SITTING
AROUND WORRYING,
WHY DON'T WE TRY TO
LEND THEM A HAND?
- AND HOW ARE WE
GONNA DO THAT?
- I KNOW WE DON'T REALLY
CONSIDER OURSELVES A TEAM
SINCE OUR COALITION WAS
KIND OF THROWN TOGETHER,
BUT WE NEED TO START
THINKING THAT WAY
IF WE WANT TO DEFEAT
THE ORACION SEIS.
- ARCHIVE MAGIC.
THAT'S THE NAME FOR WHAT YOU'RE
WORKING WITH NOW, ISN'T IT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT SURE COMES IN HANDY
WHENEVER I NEED TO
KEEP TABS ON PEOPLE.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO
JOIN THE OTHERS, LUCY?
- NO, I NEED TO
STAY WITH ERZA.
I CAN'T LEAVE HER.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'D BE
ANY HELP ANYWAY.
I'M OBVIOUSLY THE WEAKEST
FIGHTER IN THE GROUP.
- YOU'RE JUST BEING MODEST.
I'VE HEARD RUMORS
OF YOUR STRENGTH.
THERE WAS THE TIME
YOU BEAT UP 19 VULCANS
THAT STOOD 10 FEET TALL.
AND THEN THERE WAS FAIRY TAIL'S
BATTLE AGAINST PHANTOM
I HEARD YOU KNOCKED OUT
THEIR INFAMOUS MASTER JOSE
WITH YOUR BARE HANDS.
AND THE TIME IN ACALYPHA
WHEN YOU SINGLE-HANDEDLY
TOOK ON A DARK GUILD THAT HAD
OVER A THOUSAND MEMBERS.
- THAT'S STRETCHING THE TRUTH.
- UH-HUH.
- SO, HIBIKI, HOW COME YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO JOIN THE OTHERS?
- WHAT KIND OF MAN WOULD I BE
IF I LEFT YOU LADIES ALONE?
- THANKS.  GUESS YOU'RE
NOT SO BAD AFTER ALL.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY A LOT NICER
THAN "SORCERER WEEKLY"
MADE YOU OUT TO BE.
- GOOD TO KNOW.
THANKS TO ARCHIVE,
I CAN KEEP TRACK
OF THE OTHERS.
AND I CAN MAKE THEM AWARE
OF OUR CURRENT POSITION TOO.
THAT WAY ONCE THEY'VE
RESCUED WENDY AND HAPPY,
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO LOCATE US,
AND SAVE ERZA.
- OH, WOW. YOU'VE GOT ALL THE
BASES COVERED, DON'T YOU?
- WELL, YOU CAN THANK
MASTER ICHIYA.
I'M JUST DOING
WHAT I WAS TAUGHT.
- ( chuckles )
- HERE WE GO.
I FOUND NATSU'S GROUP.
- SO IF SHE'S
A SKY DRAGON SLAYER,
WHAT DOES SHE
EAT FOR POWER?
- AIR, OF COURSE.
- DOES IT TASTE ANY GOOD?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I DON'T SEE HOW THAT'S
ANY DIFFERENT FROM BREATHING.
- YOU KNOW, THE ONLY REASON
SHE APPLIED FOR THIS MISSION
IS BECAUSE SHE WANTED
TO GET THE CHANCE TO MEET YOU.
- WHY ME?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE A
FELLOW DRAGON SLAYER.
THERE'S SOMETHING SHE
WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT.
- DID SHE TELL YOU?
- YES.
APPARENTLY, THE DRAGON WHO
TAUGHT HER DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
MYSTERIOUSLY DISAPPEARED
SEVEN YEARS AGO.
SHE WAS HOPING THAT YOU
MIGHT BE ABLE TO TELL HER
ITS WHEREABOUTS.
- I NEED MORE INFO.
WHAT'S THE DRAGON'S NAME?
- I BELIEVE WENDY CALLED HER
THE SKY DRAGON GRANDINA.
- SKY DRAGON GRANDINA.
SEVEN YEARS AGO.
( grunts )
- HMM.
- HOLD ON!
MAYBE LAXUS KNOWS.
- THAT GUY'S NOTHING
BUT A LOSER.
GRAMPS SAID HE'S NOT A REAL
DRAGON SLAYER, REMEMBER?
- ( Carla gasps )
- HUH?
- WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE?
- ( gasps )
- THE TREES...
THEY'RE BLACK.
- OH, MAN. THAT'S CREEPY.
- ( gasps )
- WORD ON THE STREET IS
IT'S CAUSED BY NIRVANA,
AIN'T THAT RIGHT,
BIG BRO ZATOU?
- OH, YEAH.
MAGIC SO POWERFUL,
THE PLANET CAN'T TAKE IT.
EVERYTHING IT TOUCHES
WITHERS UP AND DIES, BIG BRO.
- ( laughing, cackling )
- OH, DEAR.  THIS IS BAD.
THEY'VE GOT US SURROUNDED.
- WORD ON THE STREET IS
IT'S CAUSED BY NIRVANA.
- WOULD YOU STOP REPEATING
YOURSELF, BIG BRO GATOU?
- OH, MAN, I DIDN'T
EVEN NOTICE, BIG BRO ZATOU.
- WHOA, AWESOME.
THOSE TWO HAVE GOT TO BE THE
DUMBEST MONKEYS I'VE EVER SEEN.
- HEY!  YOU BLOCKHEADS ARE
MEMBERS OF THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
YOU'RE FRIENDS WITH
THAT BLONDE GIRL.
- YEAH, I REMEMBER THEM NOW.
THEY'RE FRIENDS WITH THAT GIRL
WHO RUINED OUR PLANS
IN ACALYPHA, AIN'T THEY?
- OHH!  THAT ONE THERE
IS AN ANGRY MONKEY.
- DON'T GO MESSING
WITH NAKED MUMMY.
WE'RE WITH THE ORACION SEIS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GOT A DEATH WISH, PAL?
- WHAT'S THIS
NAKED MUMMY BUSINESS?
- ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
THAT STUPID?
THEY'RE THE DARK GUILD THAT LUCY
TOLD US ABOUT THE OTHER DAY.
- IT WAS A TRAP.
THEY TRICKED US INTO THINKING
WE'D BE FACING SIX WIZARDS.
- WELL I SAY
THE MORE THE MERRIER.
- NO KIDDING.
BRING ON THE MONKEYS.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD HAS
GOTTEN INTO YOU TWO?
WE SHOULD RUN WHILE
WE HAVE THE CHANCE.
- NO WAY.
THAT WOULD BE RUDE.
ESPECIALLY AFTER THEY WERE
KIND ENOUGH TO COME TO US.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING UNTIL THEY
TELL US WHERE THEIR BASE IS.
- WHERE ARE YOU HIDING
OUR FRIENDS HAPPY AND WENDY?
- YOU THINK A LITTLE FIRE'S
GONNA SCARE US?
- DON'T GO MESSING
WITH NAKED MUMMY.
WE'RE WITH THE ORACION SEIS.
- YOU ALREADY SAID THAT, DUMMY!
- ( chuckles ) THIS IS THE END
OF THE LINE FOR YOU FAIRIES.
- ( rhythmic chanting )
- ( Natsu and Gray chuckle )
- I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THESE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS
ARE COMPLETELY INSANE.
DO THEY HONESTLY THINK
THEY STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THIS ENTIRE GUILD?
- ( chanting continues )
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
IN ANOTHER PART OF THE FOREST,
REN AND EVE OF BLUE PEGASUS
FIND THEMSELVES
SURROUNDED BY
AN ENEMY AS WELL.
- JUDGING BY THEIR HAIR,
I'D SAY THEY'RE IN
THE BLACK UNICORN GUILD.
- THESE FUNNY LOOKING CREEPS
REALLY WANT TO GET IN OUR WAY?
- YOU GONNA CRY,
SILKY HAIRED LOSERS?
- DUMB PRETTY-BOYS.
- GAME OVER, SISSIES.
- Narrator: AND NATURALLY,
JURA, LYON, AND SHERRY
HAVE ALSO FOUND
THEMSELVES SURROUNDED.
- THEY'RE MEMBERS OF
THE RED HOOD DARK GUILD.
- I HAD NO IDEA
WE WERE BEING FOLLOWED.
- I DON'T THINK THEY KNOW
WHO THEY'RE DEALING WITH.
- IT'S JURA,
THE WIZARD SAINT.
- IF WE CAN DEFEAT HIM,
IT'LL MAKE US FAMOUS.
- AAH!
- Narrator:
AND LET'S NOT FORGET HIM.
- I'M JUST A SIMPLE TRAVELER
WHO GOT SEPARATED FROM
THE REST OF HIS PARTY.
SO PLEASE, DON'T MAKE A MESS
OF MY HANDSOME FACE.
MAN!
- Racer:
SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG.
THING'S SO HEAVY, IT WAS HARD
FOR ME TO BUILD UP ANY SPEED.
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT I WAS FAST,
BUT AFTER THAT TRIP
I'M STARTING TO
DOUBT MYSELF.
- LET ME ASSURE YOU, RACER,
THERE IS NO ONE WHO
CAN COME EVEN CLOSE
TO MATCHING YOUR SPEED.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- Happy: IT'S A COFFIN.
- IT'S TIME, WENDY. ARE YOU
READY TO USE YOUR HEALING MAGIC
TO RESURRECT THE MAN INSIDE?
- NO!  I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT,
AND YOU CAN'T MAKE ME.
- YEAH, YOU HEARD THE LADY.
- I'M SORRY.
PERHAPS I FORGOT TO MENTION
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE
IN THE MATTER!
- ( gasps )
- WHOA!  WHAT THE--?
- ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE YOU TO JELLAL.
A BRILLIANT WIZARD
WHO ONCE INFILTRATED
THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
- IT'S NOT HIM.
IT CAN'T BE.
- BUT IT IS.
ONCE HE'S REVIVED,
HE WILL LEAD US TO NIRVANA.
- REVIVE HIM?
BUT HOW?!
WHAT DO YOU EVEN
MEAN BY THAT?
LIKE BRINGING HIM
BACK FROM THE DEAD?
- IT'S REALLY HIM.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW JELLAL?
- OVEREXPOSURE TO ETHER-NANO
CAUSED HIM TO GO INTO
A CATATONIC STATE.
THOUGH HE'S BEEN
RENDERED UNCONSCIOUS,
HE'S STILL FAR FROM DEAD.
YOU ARE THE ONLY WIZARD
CAPABLE OF REVIVING HIM.
ISN'T THAT THE LEAST
YOU CAN DO
AFTER ALL HE'S
DONE FOR YOU?
- ( gasps )
- ( exhales )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WHOA! ALL OF A SUDDEN
THE BAD GUYS
ARE COMING OUT IN DROVES.
- Happy: WATCH OUT!
THEY'RE NOT JUST ANY BAD GUYS.
THEY'RE FROM THE DARK GUILDS!
- Natsu: I AIN'T SCARED OF THEM.
I'LL KICK THEIR BUTTS
AND THEN I'LL FORCE THEM TO TELL
ME WHERE THEY'RE HIDING WENDY.
- Happy: AREN'T YOU
FORGETTING SOMEONE?
YOUR LIFE WOULD BE
MISERABLE WITHOUT ME.
- Natsu:
I GOTTA SAVE BOTH OF YOU?
IN THAT CASE, I SHOULD WARM UP
BEFORE THE BIG FIGHT.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Happy: DON'T GET TRIPPED UP,
'CAUSE YOU WON'T BE
SAVING ANYBODY.
- Natsu: COME ON.
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH, WOULD YOU?
- Happy: I DON'T KNOW.
MY CHANCES MIGHT BE
BETTER WITH GRAY.