[NARRATOR] While Natsu and the
Dragon Slayers of Sabertooth
continue their intense battle
with the demons of Tartaros,
Erza and the others fight with
everything they have left
to try to keep the
Faces from detonating.
As the wizards struggle to
end this war once and for all,
Mard Geer shares
his ultimate plan.
[MARD GEER]
Don't you know?
I'd think you could've
put it together.
That tome your friend wants
to steal contains E.N.D,
and it's magic that seals him.
You wanna bust him out?
Now you see.
Despite how it may appear...
I'm not our leader.
That title belongs to E.N.D.
There are none among us
who can rival his strength.
Once E.N.D. has finally
been released,
we can fulfill our true purpose,
and return to Zeref.
Damn! It won't budge!
Come on, Man! Use your fire!
Ah! Crap, I'm stuck.
It froze.
[NARRATOR]
But when all hope seemed lost,
an old friend returned
to save the day.
[NATSU]
My scarf.
I thought I'd lost it for good.
[GRAY]
You're welcome.
[NATSU]
Uh...
If it means so much to you,
then take better care of it.
Will do.
[GRAY]
Ice Demon: Zero Long Sword!
Don't let this jerkwad freakshow
get under your skin!
Keep fighting! Ah!
[MARD GEER] Behold, I
am Mard Geer Tartaros.
Absolute Demon, and
King of the Underworld.
[GRAY]
Natsu.
[NATSU]
Don't say it. I know.
We don't care what you
call yourself king of!
We're gonna take you out!
[MARD GEER]
Come. Give me your all.
For this battle
shall be your last.
Now it's time for you to Freeze!
Right After you Burn!
[GRAY, NATSU gasp]
Hey! You better let
go of me right now,
you weird gargoyle
lookin' freak!
[MARD GEER]
At last, the time has come
for you to see what lies
beyond the Netherworld Gate.
[NATSU groans]
[GRAY groans]
[NATSU, GRAY groaning]
[NATSU screams]
[MARD GEER]
I will savor every last moment
of tearing your soul to shreds
and erasing your existence.
[ERZA groaning]
[ERZA] There's a light
you'll never take from me.
[ALL gasp]
No way.
She's back on her feet.
But how does she know what
to do without any senses?
She's amazing!
Truly impressive.
How was she able to
sense the attacks?
Cause Erza can do anything.
Keep your guard up!
You're beaten.
Lay down.
[ERZA]
Sight.
Sound.
These are luxuries, both.
All that's needed
is the light within.
You would understand
that if you had one.
[ERZA] It would've led you
to protect your comrades!
[ERZA grunts]
[ERZA] You were created
to live in darkness!
With pain your only guide,
it's you who must be frightened!
I guess we better head to the
guild hall to meet Makarov.
Hey, Lucy.
Could you give him
a message for me?
Let him know I've got his back.
And I have faith this
secret weapon's gonna work.
You got it.
[WARREN]
Man, she is workin' that outfit.
Lookin' good.
Come on man.
You gotta get your
head in the game!
For real, we've got way
more important things
you could be thinking
about. Get a grip!
I really gotta work
on my filter...
Okay, let's get going.
We don't have time to waste.
[CARLA] Her looks aren't the
only thing that's changed.
She's so strong
and confident now.
Are you sure you
wanna stay behind?
Yeah, I'll be fine here,
but you better get moving.
Okay. We'll be back
before you know it.
[yells]
[STING, ROGUE grunt]
It was your fault.
You're the one who
dragged her into this.
That pitiful excuse of a girl
was completely useless.
I had such high hopes
of utilizing the power
of the demons to strengthen
the intensity of her magic.
But she wasn't ready
and that weakling chose
to remain a weakling.
The years I've spent teaching
you have been wasted.
But a place may do
what I could not.
These woods are filled
with vicious beasts.
Either it will strip you
of your tears, your heart,
and your weakness.
Or they will strip
you of your life.
Once your tears have dried
for good, you may return.
But she is your own child!
[JIEMMA]
Hm... Child, you say?
But how? No!
You should be out of power!
How can you still be standing?
[ERZA]
I told you.
I'll keep standing until
I've put you in the dirt.
[MINERVA]
No.
Stop.
I will have revenge!
Stay back! You've won this!
Let me go!
Nakagami...
Starlight!
[yells]
[MINERVA groaning]
[JIEMMA]
She's nothing!
[ROGUE]
Uh.
[STING]
Uh...
[JIEMMA] The only thing she
was ever going to be good for
was continuing my bloodline.
Take that back!
[JIEMMA grunts]
[JIEMMA]
Is that all you've got?
[STING groans]
[ROGUE groaning]
[ROGUE whimpers]
[JIEMMA]
You'll never beat me.
You need to accept the fact
that as long as I'm alive
you'll never have my guild.
[ROGUE]
We don't want your guild back,
we want our guild back.
The way it was.
When we were a team.
The way a guild
is supposed to be.
Only the weak believe that crap!
[ROGUE groans]
A real leader knows that the
only thing Sabertooth needs
is to be the strongest
guild there ever was.
But you ruined that.
With your "weakness"
and "teamwork."
I know you might
see it that way,
but I don't.
Showing compassion
isn't weakness,
it's strength.
With a power unlike
anything else.
[JIEMMA]
Nonsense.
Weakness is abandoning
your comrades
when they need you the most.
[yells]
[LECTOR whimpers]
[gasps]
[LECTOR]
Help me, Sting.
No!
Lector!
Lector is gone.
Master killed him!
Frosch!
Why did he do that?
[JIEMMA]
It got what it deserved.
If you're smart you'll
remove your emblem
before you join
the fleabag.
[screams]
Would you stop your
damn blubbering?
[STING]
What have you done?!
What the hell have you done?!
[JIEMMA] Silence!
It was just a lousy cat!
[STING growls]
--[STING yells]
--[JIEMMA groans]
[FROSCH, ROGUE whimper]
We're through with
that kind of guild.
We wanna be part of something
we can believe in.
We know it's not
going to be easy,
but that's what
we're gonna build.
A true guild.
And we aren't gonna
give up no matter what.
Which means...
We don't need you anymore!
Your reign is over!
[STING yells]
[JIEMMA laughs]
You two believe you can
create some perfect guild?
There's no way you can
because there's no such thing.
And that's just the way it is.
Sabertooth is about brute
strength and nothing else!
Why are you trying
to change that?
Because.
You're wrong.
I know the truth now.
There are guilds
who have it all.
[ROGUE]
They're strong and kind.
They respect each other.
And they fight for
the good of humanity.
And what a tragic
creature you are.
For you've never known
the light you lack.
Way to go!
Take her down!
[ROGUE] That's what it
means to be a true guild!
How dare you mock me!
[STING, ROGUE groaning]
One individual strength
is everything!
Teamwork is just
a clever fallacy.
It's made to manipulate the
mind and encourage dependence!
And nobody's gonna drag me down!
What don't you understand?!
Things aren't like
they used to be!
The world is in trouble!
We can fix it, together!
That's how Fairy
Tail does things!
[ROGUE]
As a team.
[JIEMMA]
Never!
This is your last chance before
we shut you up for good!
Let's show him what
teamwork can do!
[STING, ROGUE]
White Shadow Dragon Silk!
[JIEMMA groaning]
It's impossible!
How?!
[BOTH panting]
[ROGUE]
Natsu.
Gray.
[STING]
It's all... up to you now.
[GRAY grunts]
[NATSU, GRAY grunt]
[IGNEE roars]
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[IGNEEL roars]
[GAJEEL]
Get down!
[LEVY screams]
[GAJEEL grunts]
Uh. Thanks for saving me.
It's fine. Just try
to be more careful.
[PORLYUSICA]
Is everyone all right?
[BOTH gasp]
[LEVY]
Porlyusica!
[GAJEEL] This should
help with the antidote.
Here.
Wait, how did you get the blood
from the demon with
the Bane Particles?
He did it.
I'm just the one
lugging him around.
And he was willing
to die to get it.
[GAJEEL] Ha, ha. He's seriously
one tough bastard.
I don't think he'll ever grow
out of this reckless behavior.
After all,
his Grandfather
certainly didn't.
Hurry!
We haven't got time to waste.
But, thanks to Loxus,
I can save them all.
[GRAY, NATSU yell]
[GRAY, NATSU gasp]
[NATSU]
Uh.
[GRAY growls]
[NATSU grunts]
Fire Dragon Roar!
[NATSU growls]
[GRAY]
Ice Demon Rage! Ah!
[MARD GEER]
Dea Yggdrasil!
[NATSU yells]
[GRAY yells]
[BOTH yelling]
All right. Ice Make...
Guungneer!
[MARD GEER]
Hm?
Man, that's cold!
[MARD GEER]
He was inside the ice?
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame!
What is up with him?
Is he immortal or somethin'?
I just have to get a clear
shot to hit him with my magic.
[MARD GEER]
Well, humans, I must admit,
I have been quite entertained by
your attempts to vanquish me.
[MARD GEER] And now it's
my turn to entertain you,
with a story about the one
and only Primordial Magic.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[MARD GEER]
From that origin point,
magic grew to form
various distinct paths.
E.N.D. studied this
evolution and realized
the immense potential
for a new kind of power.
[MARD GEER]
Curses.
[MARD GEER] A power fueled
by the most dismal emotions:
woe, spite, envy, and hatred.
[MARD GEER]
Each of these negative feelings
gave us an incredibly
powerful energy.
And we channeled
this essence of life
to manifest our darkest desires.
Do you even know
what you're saying?!
If that's true than Magic
will always be stronger!
[NATSU, GRAY gasp]
[NATSU gasps]
Gray! What is this?!
[GRAY]
Is it fog?
No.
I can barely move!
What are we gonna do?!
[MARD GEER] The Era of Magic
is coming to an end.
It's time for the true
supreme power to rule.
Welcome to the Era of Curses.
[NATSU, GRAY groaning]
[MARD GEER] Prepare
yourselves for purgatory.
For I will invoke
the ultimate curse,
designed to destroy
Zeref himself!
[NATSU screams]
[GRAY gasping]
[MARD GEER]
The memory... of death.
[NATSU groaning]
[GRAY groaning]
[MARD GEER]
Memento Mori!
To kill Zeref
one must destroy the concept
of both life and death.
Those afflicted by
the Memento Mori
no longer belong with the
living or with the dead.
They simply cease to exist.
[GRAY]
This can't be the end.
[NATSU groaning]
[MARD GEER] You are now, and
forever will be... nothing.
The moment has arrived.
The ultimate curse has finally
been perfected and invoked.
Once E.N.D has been revived,
I'll fulfill my promise.
And then...
You will be destroyed,
Lord Zeref.
[LUCY] Even Fairy Tail's
duo of fire and ice
is decimated by Mard
Geer's ultimate curse.
Is there no other wizard
that can stop Tartaros
and the Memento Mori?
As the Faces' countdown reaches
zero, tensions run high.
Will Magic really disappear
from the world forever?
Or will humanity be saved
in the final moments
by an ancient and
spectacular intervention?
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Soaring Above Ishgar."
High in the sky,
a miracle appears.