It's hot.
[JUVIA] And completely deserted.
C'mon, Aries!
Where are you?
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Fairy Tail
Cult Quiz, question number ten!
During Miss Levy's seven-year
stint on Tenrou Island,
who would've been Droy of
Shadow Gear's rebound?
That is, if she
hadn't rejected him.
[CAPRICORN whimpers]
[LEVY]
I think I've got it!
Araña, of Mermaid Heel!
[ringing]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Correct!
How did you come by that juicy
bit of gossip, Miss Levy?
I don't imagine that
he told you himself!
No, it was just
an educated guess.
Mira mentioned that the two of
them worked the same job once.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Well done!
And now it's time for
Mr. Capricorn's punishment!
Wait! No!
Can we talk this out?
Put it back down,
before I lose my grip!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
We've cracked the case, folks.
Capricorn is not
a Mountain Goat!
[CAPRICORN whimpers]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Ten
questions in and we are tied,
five to five!
Therefore, our eleventh
question will be the final one!
[grunting]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] But first,
let's chat with our contestants.
Are we having fun yet?
Do I look like I'm
having fun to you?!
Do you mind just getting
to the question already?
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
You heard it folks,
our participants
are definitely slipping!
If either of them
miss this question,
they'll be dropped
into the "fun zone!"
Then what was the point
of all the questions
you made us answer earlier?!
Please, anything
but the "fun zone"!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Alright then! Final question!
Miss Levy likes
one of her guildmates.
Which one is it?
[LEVY gasps]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Alright then! Final Question!
Miss Levy likes
one of her guildmates.
Which one is it?
What the heck?
That seems a little
personal to me.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] By the way,
when I say "like"
I don't mean as a friend
or respected colleague.
I mean "nudge, nudge,
wink, wink," like.
[LEVY whimpers]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
We're talking attraction:
emotional and physical.
Who does she pine for
late at night?
It's no secret to anyone,
even I could answer it.
Aw, fine, I'll say it!
[inaudible]
[LEVY sobs]
[ringing]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
That is... correct!
Give it up for Miss Levy, the
Fairy Tail Cult Quiz champion!
I was sure you'd be too
embarrassed to say it out loud!
[CAPRICORN screams]
Oh, please don't drop
me in the fun zone!
[CAPRICORN screams]
[LEVY] Now then.
Solid Script: Thunderbolt!
Glad that's over.
I've been beaten.
As of today, you are
the cult quiz queen.
[LEVY sighs]
There's no way that
anyone but Capricorn
could've heard me say it.
Right...?
[HAPPY]
Juvia vs. Aries!
Desert Death Match!
[LUCY grunts]
Oh, it's torture.
My entire body hurts.
And I'm sticky too.
So tell me, have you enjoyed
this particular punishment?
[LUCY] No! No more
watermelons, please!
You can whip me all day,
just don't use fruit!
You look rather
adorable when you beg,
but that won't help you now.
Once you see what's up next,
you'll wish I'd
stuck with melons.
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY screams]
What the heck you gonna
do with that stuff?!
You can't know
what torture is
until you've been
slathered in condiments.
Ready to learn?
[LUCY] Nope!
[VIRGO laughs]
Think you can run from me?
Look, you're my friend and
I don't want to fight you.
I came here to talk!
I don't intend to fight you,
Lucy, my plan is to punish you.
They're quite different.
[LUCY] They sound pretty
fricking similar to me!
If I keep running like this
then I'll never close her gate!
I've got to find
a place to lay low
so I can come up with a plan.
[LUCY grunts]
Well that sucks.
It's just another hallway!
[footsteps grow louder]
[LUCY gasps]
[VIRGO laughs]
You can't hide here!
These are my halls and they
conceal nothing from me.
You know I'll catch you
eventually, so why put it off?
[LUCY grunts, gasps]
[VIRGO laughs]
[VIRGO] If you
don't stop running,
you'll be too tired
to scream later.
Where's the fun in that?
[LUCY] I'm sorry, but the
entertainment of my torturer
is not my top priority!
[VIRGO laughs]
Who wants mayo?
I have lots of it!
This is bad.
There's no window!
[VIRGO] Where have
you run off to now?
Stop teasing me,
we have too much to do.
She's closing in.
I guess I'll have
to try the door.
[LUCY gasps]
[VIRGO] If you don't come
out, I'll use tartar sauce too!
You'll reek of
pickles for weeks.
[LUCY] She was right.
I wish she had stuck
with the melons.
[NATSU and WENDY sniff]
Are you positive that this
is the right way, Natsu?
There's no doubt about it.
Loke's scent is
all over the place.
I'm trying my best,
but I can't smell a thing.
Think you could train my nose
to be as sensitive
as yours someday?
Nonsense, you have far more
important skills to develop.
By the way, are the
rest of you certain
that we're still in
the lion's domain?
It might just be me, but
this place feels different.
Now that you mention it,
I guess that tunnel we found
could've been an exit.
But Astral Spiritus
should have twelve rooms,
one for each zodiac sign, right?
If this isn't Loke's domain,
then which spirit
does it belong to?
[NATSU] Hey.
[GROUP] Huh?
Something's coming.
Take cover!
[WENDY and CARLA yell]
Hey! What are
those things?
They look like
thermometers!
It's Loke!
Let's do this!
[NATSU gasps]
[OPHIUCHUS chuckles]
Who could that be?
I dunno, but she's
got a big syringe!
Identify yourself at once.
There are twelve zodiac spirits
and you aren't one of them.
If you can't be quiet
in your ignorance,
I'll give you a hemiglossectomy.
I am Ophiuchus
the snake charmer:
thirteenth spirit of the zodiac.
Welcome to Ophiuchus'
Study Corner:
the cure to your confusion!
Here we have
the celestial plane
as it's viewed from Earthland.
The sun is centered of course,
and all around it,
we see the twelve primary
constellations of the zodiac.
But, upon
closer inspection...
Right here, between
the constellation
of the Scorpion and the Archer,
we find the sign of
the Snake Charmer.
It's a fairly tight fit between
those two, but I make it work.
Incidentally, the sign
of the snake charmer has
a distinctly medical focus.
Between the nurse
outfit and the syringes,
I feel like I could've guessed.
So that's how it works.
I thought you celestial spirits
had something to
do with sky stuff!
But you didn't know
for sure until now?
[NATSU] Hey.
If you're a member
of the zodiac,
then I bet you work with Loke.
Correct. I didn't plan
to confront you yet,
but in light of
recent events,
we thought it best to make
some last minute change-ups.
Enough chat. It's time
for me to give each of you
an incredibly
thorough examination.
Like, you'll check
our heart-rates?
I'll cut your
hearts to pieces!
[GROUP screams]
Now then, If you could all
just turn your heads and cough.
These things feel super
weird. I don't like it!
[CARLA] Just what kind of
demented examination is this?!
[HAPPY] I think that she's
been breeding stethoscopes
with boa constrictors!
My position as caretaker
of Astral Spiritus
comes with some perks.
One being I can manipulate
every single thing around us.
Forget bedside manner.
I've got stethoscopic
straight-jackets!
I can barely even wiggle!
You got nothing!
I'll burn straight
through these things!
As if I'd allow you to
do something like that.
[WENDY gasps]
[HAPPY and CARLA]
Eh?!
Wha...?
Heh. Aaaaaahhhh!
[GROUP yells]
What a terrible sound!
I'm no nurse,
but I think you might
be doing this wrong!
Nonsense, this is exactly
how you're meant
to use magic stethoscopes.
Trust me.
I'm a nurse.
[GROUP screams]
Now that the belligerents
have been subdued...
...we can proceed with the exam.
I'll be checking out
your throats next.
Just say "ah" if you'd
like to volunteer.
There's no way that thing
will fit in our mouths!
This bad boy will fit
just about anywhere
if you shove hard enough.
[OPHIUCHUS yells]
[HAPPY grunts]
See? Mouths are stretchy!
[NATSU grunts]
Oops! I forgot
to disinfect!
I think my throat's broken.
Sometimes even
strong women cry!
Ow, my dignity!
Frigging psycho!
Oh no! My torture
victims think I'm crazy.
Whatever shall I do?
Ooh, I know just the
way to patch things up!
[OPHIUCHUS laughs]
[NATSU grunts]
[WENDY groans]
[OPHIUCHUS]
Okay, tough guy.
Show me where it hurts.
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU yells]
[HAPPY squeals]
[WENDY grunts]
[CARLA] My fur!
[HAPPY]
I don't want to go bald!
[NATSU] It hurts
so freakin' bad!
[OPHIUCHUS] My.
This is almost too much!
I've got loads of fun
procedures planned,
so try and stay
conscious, will you?
[WENDY screams]
I'd say that this was for
your own good, but it isn't!
[CARLA] Ah! There's nothing
wrong with that tooth!
[HAPPY groans]
[HAPPY] Why am I the only one
who got the shovel?
Hey, wait.
Shouldn't you be struggling,
or begging for me to stop?
Yeah, but I've never been
to see a dentist before,
and I always wanted to
know what it was like.
My teeth are crazy strong so
I never had to go and see one.
I remember having teeth.
I swear I'll never take mine
for granted again after this.
Unless we can beat Ophiuchus,
you won't even get a chance to!
[OPHIUCHUS] Mmm...
Dragneel, I'm impressed.
Between your stoic outlook
and that ultra-fit bod',
you've pushed my sadism
right into overdrive.
A nurse is supposed
to heal people,
so why call yourself one
if you make them hurt instead?
And by the way, didja
finish up my cavity thing?
There's more than one
kind of nurse, kid.
Some just really dig the toys.
Others use the nurse's
toolkit to inject their foes
with a double dose
of irony and pain.
Here, let me show
you what I mean!
I've had enough of this!
[NATSU growls]
[WENDY grunts]
[HAPPY gasps]
It's a liquid explosive!
Why put something like
that into a syringe?!
What the-? Don't like
the look of that guy.
You don't? Well,
that's just too bad.
'Cause in case you didn't
notice, he has a few friends.
Looks like it's time
for us to get serious.
[JUVIA pants]
[JUVIA] I've been
walking for miles,
but everything looks
exactly the same.
[JUVIA] When I got here, hours
ago, the sun was right overhead.
It hasn't budged.
[JUVIA] It seems time
flows differently here.
Perhaps it's a place where
it doesn't move at all.
[JUVIA] This realm
belongs to Aries.
I suspect that defeating her
is my only chance of
getting out of here alive.
But where could she be?
For that matter.
I'm a water wizard.
And I'm already dehydrated.
She could wait for the desert
to take care of the hard part,
then finish me off
once I'm weak.
Come on, little ram.
You've go to be nearby.
Show yourself!
Stop playing the coward.
Let's fight!
[ARIES laughs]
[ARIES] Looks like you're
about to run out of juice.
I wonder, can you
fight on fumes?
That'd be kind of badass!
[JUVIA pants]
[JUVIA] If she heard my
challenge, she ignored it.
And I can't get back
to Gray without her.
It's so hot...
I wish I could take
my clothes off.
But if I did that,
then there would be
nothing to protect me
from the glare of the sun.
So thirsty...
If I could only
find some water...
[gasps]
Amazing!
An oasis, I'm saved!
Water!
And right when I
needed it most, too!
[JUVIA laughs]
[JUVIA sighs]
It was only a mirage?
This is the end for me.
I can't go on like this.
[engine revving]
[JUVIA gasps]
A magic-mobile?
[JUVIA coughs]
[ARIES laughs]
You look awful!
Desert's a crappy place
for a water wizard to
hang out, isn't it?
What's up?
Going to say something back
or are you too tuckered out?
You're not going to be
any sport at all like this.
[ARIES laughs]
Are you really
the new Aries?
That's right, you're looking at
the one and only Aries the Ram.
I'm still pretty new to
the Earthland circuits,
but in the celestial world,
I'm the fastest thing on wheels.
Check this out!
[ARIES] Made this place
so I could get my tan on.
And show off these
hella cool shades.
Badass, right?
What a tragedy.
The Eclipse has turned you
into a phony little poser.
How dare you
call me a poser!
I am legit.
I don't care what you think!
This wouldn't be so sad
if you hadn't once been such
a gentle, loving spirit.
I won't even get into
your breast size.
That'd be a pretty low blow
if I gave a crap.
Now take it back before
I casually break your legs.
[JUVIA] So are you and
Loke still very close?
Or did his interest disappear
along with your Double D's?
[ARIES growls]
I am parched!
Glad I brought
my trusty canteen.
Uh-huh.
Water!
[ARIES gulps]
[JUVIA] Gulp...
Ah! Now that's the stuff!
Gee, I'd offer you some, but I'm
not supposed to aid the enemy
unless they've surrendered!
Some things are more
important than water.
You wouldn't understand this,
but I'd rather be baked alive
than betray my beloved Gray.
That was beautiful.
I'm sure he'll appreciate
your sacrifice.
[JUVIA]
Wait, no! No!
It's gone.
[ARIES chuckles]
[ARIES]
Whelp, now that I've broken
your precious little spirit,
this feels like a
pretty good time
for me to kick your
sun-dried little tush.
You ready?
[JUVIA gasps]
[ARIES]
I'll take that as a yes!
Golden Horn Bomber! Yeah!
[JUVIA grunts]
There's still some
spring in your step!
Never would've guessed
you had it in you.
This might be kind of fun!
[JUVIA grunts]
I'm at the end
of my strength.
Either I end this fight now,
or she's going to tear me apart.
C'mon. Water Slicer!
Too dry.
I couldn't even attack her once.
You might have that
fighting spirit on lock,
but you're outta your element.
Just stand still and
let me put you to bed.
What the--?
[SHEEP 212A] One sheep!
Two sheep! Three sheep!
Four sheep!
Five sheep! Six sheep...
How am I supposed
to fall asleep like this?
[SHEEP 212A] Ten Sheep!
That was just to prep
you for my next move.
Here goes!
[JUVIA gasps]
[JUVIA grunts]
I know you're kind of
distracted back there,
but hey, what do you
think of my driving?
[ARIES laughs]
[JUVIA grunts]
What's the matter,
are you finished already?
Bet you wish you'd taken
that water now, huh?
Well, if you're too
weak to talk back,
I should put you
out of your misery.
Need... Water...
Just a bit...
Sorry, but that
ain't happening.
This is a desert, and you won't
find a drop of water in it!
There isn't a nice way
to put this, babe:
you're going to die thirsty.
Water... Water...
[JUVIA gasps]
[ARIES gasps]
I've located some water.
[ARIES] Oh yeah?
So where is it?
Right beneath you.
Underneath your feet.
Say what?
I have enough power...
for a Water Whip!
[JUVIA yells]
[ARIES yells]
You're really going to
drink outta my radiator?
[JUVIA] That's right.
Without water
pumping through it,
your magic-mobile would
overheat for sure.
Ah! Wow!
Talk about a recharge!
Yeah?
Well you let your
guard down, stupid!
[ARIES gasps]
Yeah, now that
I'm hydrated,
I'm pretty much impervious
to physical attacks.
Water Jigsaw!
[ARIES screams]
[ARIES] Aw, man!
Time for you to go home.
Got to say, beating
me with my own ride
like that was pretty badass.
I made it.
At last I can return to
my polar paramour's side.
Now...
...I just have to
figure out how to get back.
[LIBRA and YUKINO yell]
[YUKINO yells]
Within your soul
there must be balance.
Find your inner symmetry
and push it outwards,
or else you'll fall
into a bottomless hell.
There's no way you
can knock me off
without putting
yourself in danger.
You'll fall.
[LIBRA]
You're wrong about that.
Once I've knocked you off,
I'll leap towards the
center of the stone.
Balance may be
restored from there.
This is a battle
of endurance.
Whoever loses equilibrium
first, is defeated.
[YUKINO] She's intimidating,
but if I lose my nerve,
then it's over for me.
Remember that
balance is everything.
[YUKINO growls]
[ARCADIOS] This passageway
seems endless.
How far do you suppose
it will take us?
[HISUI]
I can't say for sure.
It could lead us to
the celestial world.
Or perhaps to a place
we've never heard of.
[ARCADIOS] Leo's whereabouts
are still unknown.
I fear that he may be planning
something we've not foreseen.
What do you make
of all this?
The last we saw of Leo,
he was fighting Natsu.
Something seemed off, though.
Leo didn't bring
the celestial globe.
So, where did he leave it?
Good question.
He can't have
left it unprotected.
We can only guess.
Wherever Leo's gone,
I bet the globe is near.
I think you're right, Arcadios.
He may be planning
something new.
It's quite possible.
[HISUI] Hmm...
The first to win two out of
a total of three matches
shall be declared the victor.
Is this agreeable to you?
[ERZA] Yes, It is.
But before we begin in earnest,
allow me to compliment
your stagecraft.
The extra context makes me all
the more determined to win.
[SAGITTARIUS] We are
warriors, the both of us.
It's been my experience that a
warrior only fights at his best
when taken by
the mood of battle.
[ERZA] Intriguing.
My experience has been the same.
Well then.
It seems we're more
alike than I knew.
[SAGITTARIUS]
I appreciate that.
If all else is settled,
then tell me:
are you prepared for battle?
[ERZA] A good warrior is
always ready for battle.
A small part of me does wish
we had an audience, though.
I considered
bringing one in,
but I don't have the heart
to destroy you so publicly.
This is my way of
showing you mercy.
Ooh, I hope your sword's
as sharp as your tongue.
Erza Scarlet,
I challenge you!
I accept!
[HAPPY] Hmm.
If we could see his
halves separately...
[NATSU]
What's up, Happy?
[HAPPY] I'm trying to figure
out if this Sagittarius guy
is a human or a horse.
[NATSU]
He's a human, no doubt!
Horses can't talk, dummy.
[HAPPY] Remember those yucky
winged fish? They talked!
They kept on shouting
"I can fly."
[NATSU] Good point.
[HAPPY] And besides,
I am a talking cat.
[NATSU] Oh yeah!
Crap, now I don't know
which one he is either!
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: Erza vs. Sagittarius!
Horseback Showdown!
[HAPPY]
Know what? I say human.
Pretty sure the head decides.
[NATSU] Wait a second.
Why does it matter?