[RUFUS] What happened?
Where am I?
It's as if I've blocked
it from my memory...
Ah yes, there it is.
This is the Royal
Library in Crocus.
And today is the final day
of the Grand Magic Games...
But, this place, filled
with the wisdom of ages,
is where they ended for me.
For this is where
I was defeated
by the wizard from Fairy Tail.
[CHAPATI] The underdogs
from Fairy Tail have made
a thrilling rally and
are now leading the pack...
With an impressive fifty points!
And all five members of
their team are still in play.
[CHAPATI] But nipping at their
heels are both Sabertooth and
Lamia Scale, who each
have forty-nine points!
[YAJIMA] With forty-three
points, Mermaid Heel needs
to kick it into high gear
if they want to catch up.
Things are looking
a little grim, chicas.
We're still
in this...
but it's gonna be real tough.
Aw, quit yer
cryin', you two.
We still got Kagura
on the field,
and Milliana's one
tough kitty herself.
Never underestimate
us mermaids!
Yeah, I guess.
But I still got something
kinda stuck in my craw...
What's bothering you?
[BETH] Well, I've been
watchin' the screen up there,
and they haven't shown
Millianna in a long time.
Is that so?
[LISLIE] You worry too much.
I bet she's just found
a sweet hiding spot
and she's waiting for the
perfect time to pounce.
[ARAÑA] Sounds like her.
Well, I hope
you're right...
But I can't say
I'm sure about it...
I just gotta gut feeling
she's in some kinda trouble.
[MINERVA giggles]
[HAPPY] The Kingdom
'til Tomorrow!
[LUCY] No matter where we go,
it all looks exactly the same.
It's impossible to
know if you're going
the right way or not.
Well, this is just the way
we're goin' right now.
I'm pretty sure this is
gonna lead us outta here.
I can kinda sense a breeze.
Do you know, Loke?
How'd you get down here anyway?
I just jumped.
[WENDY] But you really
didn't pay attention
to how you got here?
[LOKE] I live by the "leap
before you look" philosophy.
[NATSU] Wow, you're actually
kinda cool sometimes.
[LOKE] Thanks.
What about
Colonel Arcadios?
Do you think he'll be okay?
He's doing great
considering what
he just went through.
[HAPPY] After jumping
into the lava like that,
I'm surprised he's still alive.
[CARLA] It's extraordinary...
Did he have help
from Horologium?
No. He jumped
in before anyone
had the chance to help.
What an amazing
warrior. And so noble.
Check out
his necklace.
That's no ordinary
piece of jewelry.
The jadestone is a
strong protection charm.
There's jade
again. Like Zirconis.
He called himself
the Jade Dragon.
[NATSU] And he was
kind of a jerk.
[LUCY] Well, he certainly
talked a lot, didn't he?
It's strange.
Princess Hisui's name
translates to 'Jade.'
[CARLA] And we're to talk to
her about this Eclipse project.
To decide whether
or not it's right.
[NATSU] She threw
Lucy down here,
so we definitely got
something to talk about.
That may be true,
but let's not lose focus.
First and foremost,
we need to get out of here
and let the rest of the
guild know we're safe.
You're right.
[PANTHERLILY] We still
may have a ways to go.
[MIRAJANE] Yeah, there's no
telling how deep this cave is.
[LOKE] You could probably
fit an entire city in here.
[LUCY] Tell me about it.
[NATSU] Whoa! I smell somethin'!
[WENDY] That probably means
we're almost to the exit.
[YUKINO] Perhaps the head
of the execution squad
was telling the truth after all.
Don't you think it's kinda
weird that the rest of
them told us their names.
but the leader never
said what his was?
Yeah, that's true.
We gotta call him
something, I guess...
How 'bout Scythe?!
[LUCY] That's original.
Hey!
Look over there!
[NATSU] It's a door!
[HAPPY] Heck yeah it is!
[LUCY] Maybe that's the way out!
[PANTHERLILY] It's huge.
[WENDY] It looks
really hard to open.
[YUKINO] Yes, it does.
[NATSU] Don't worry,
I got this...
Fire Dragon...
What the--?!
We're free!
[NATSU grunting]
But how?
Is it a trap?
[NATSU grunting]
Thanks, but...
who are you?
[SOLDIER A] Princess! Princess!
I bring terrible news!
[SOLDIER B] Calm down,
and tell us what it is.
[SOLDIER A] Okay. We
haven't received any
updates from the
palace of perdition.
so we sent a squad
to investigate.
They report that the
Hungry Wolf Knights
have been wiped out!
[SOLDIER D] What?!
Impossible!
By that tiny
group of wizards?!
[SOLDIER D] Any word
on the criminals?!
[SOLDIER A] It seems
they were able to escape.
[SOLDIER C] That
doesn't make sense!
[HISUI thinking] I knew it...
[DARTON] I wouldn't
celebrate just yet, Princess.
Your plan
is clear as day.
[HISUI] Darton!
I thought you were accompanying
my father to Domus Flau.
I couldn't shake
my suspicions.
So I decided to return... And
now they've been confirmed.
I won't stand for this
abuse! Not from you...
After all, you're the
one who sent Arcadios
to the Palace of Perdition
without a trial.
[DARTON] Which is precisely
why you decided to use the
Fairy Tail guild in order
to rescue him. Correct?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[DARTON] The truth of the
matter is, you're the one
who's really in charge
of the Eclipse Project.
Arcadios was
willing to play
the role of villain
to deflect suspicion...
He wanted to conceal the fact
that you're running the show.
Please. correct me
if I'm wrong, Princess.
No, you saw right
through our charade...
Impressive.
[DARTON] I implore you. You must
understand what is at risk here!
That device
is dangerous!
Changing history
could spell our doom!
[HISUI] Perhaps... But it
may be our only salvation.
[DARTON] It may be?
Listen... I swore
that I'd tell no one...
but I'm afraid that I
have no other options.
There's another
plan in the works.
Another way the
device can be used...
The Eclipse Two.
Two?
[HISUI] It is the true
purpose of the Eclipse.
[HISUI] And if this plan
should fail. tomorrow.
our kingdom will
be wiped off the map.
[CHAPATI] With all five
members still in the game,
team Fairy Tail is looking
like an unstoppable force.
No surprise there.
After all, my dear friend
Laxus is among their ranks.
We're all called
the Thunder Legion
for a reason, ya know?
Well, I just wish
he'd stop holding back
and put the hurt on
those other guilds!
Savoring the
moment before victory.
That's my Laxus!
[EVERGREEN] We're a team!
Laxus! Time to show
the world your power!
[BIXLOW, EVERGREEN, &amp; FRIED]
Go, Laxus! Go, Laxus!
Put a sock in it!
So Master Mavis...
what's next in your plan?
Although Laxus
is hanging back,
the others seem
to be on the move.
Don't worry, everything
is falling into place.
[JUVIA thinking] I've hit my
mark, precisely when I was told.
[SHELIA] Sky God... Boreas!
[JUVIA thinking] It's just as
Master Mavis predicted!
[MAVIS] Juvia and
Shelia will collide.
Widdle Shelly-welly!
Yeah, yeah...
You're the girl Lyon's
in love with, right?
Yes, and it's
definitely NOT MUTUAL!
[SHELIA] Oh yeah? Then get lost!
[EVERGREEN] That's Shelia,
the God Slayer...
She doesn't look
like a huge threat,
but she can heal herself.
Then how in the heck is
Juvia supposed to beat her?!
She just needs
to keep her busy.
That'll give Erza the
opportunity to take on Minerva.
[BIXLOW, EVERGREEN, &amp; FRIED]
You seem pretty darn confident!
[FRIED] Master Mavis,
this Minerva...
she's the one
from Sabertooth
who brutally attacked
Lucy in the water round.
[BIXLOW] She's serious trouble.
[EVERGREEN] I'm sure she's
nothing "Titania" can't handle.
[ERZA] There it is...
According to the plan, I'll
encounter Minerva here soon.
[CHAPATI] Here comes Kagura!
What?
[ERZA thinking] The First
Master was wrong?!
[ERZA thinking] Her skill!
[KAGURA thinking] Let's
see if she's deserving
of her reputation as a warrior!
[MAKAROV] Kagura?!
That's not in the plan!
I thought Erza was scheduled
to go up against Minerva,
was she not?
It would seem the
renowned Fairy Tactician.
has made an error
in her calculations.
[BIXLOW &amp; EVERGREEN] Shh!
[FRIED] Hmm?
I made a mistake?
How could this happen?
I'm... so... ashamed.
[MAKAROV] Oh... Uh! It's okay!
No... I'm not
gonna cry about it.
These things just
happen sometimes.
[MAKAROV] Aw, damnit!
Quick! Somebody!
[EVERGREEN] This is
all your fault, Fried!
[FRIED] What?!
[MAKAROV] Calm her down!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Now this is
one heck of a matchup!
It's the ultimate
swordswoman showdown!
This should prove to be
one of the better fights.
[ERZA thinking] Even her
sheathed sword is deadly.
[CHAPATI] Wow!
These two blade-wielding
beauties are literally
locked in combat!
[BOTH gasp]
[ERZA &amp; KAGURA grunting]
[MINERVA] Ha...
[ERZA &amp; KAGURA grunt]
[MAKAROV &amp; MAVIS gasp]
[CHAPATI] Holy cow!
If you don't mind,
I'd love to join you.
[CHAPATI] What an entrance,
Minerva jumps in
from seemingly out of nowhere!
Oh no... I never
saw this coming!
[CHAPATI] Amazing!
This one-on-one battle has
turned into a three-way brawl!
The tournament's trio
of feminine power is now
facing off in what will
surely be an epic showdown!
[FRIED] They are all
immensely powerful...
How could anyone
predict this outcome?
Erza should make
easy work of them!
Yeah, well...
I wouldn't say "easy".
Kagura. You've
got this one!
She's prolly
gonna win, right?
I told you not
to worry, didn't I?
[BETH] I know, but. I'm scared.
As long as I've known
her, she's never let me down.
You know how much
strength she has inside.
Don't lose faith in her.
[RUFUS] Erza... and Kagura.
Their strength has been
burned into my memory.
But still...
M'lady will claim victory.
Not only is she the most
powerful fighter in our guild,
she has our master's
blood in her veins.
Sting and Rogue are
more widely known,
but in reality can't
hold a candle to her.
No matter
whom I'm up against.
I will win.
[KAGURA thinking] I can't seem
to understand how she thinks.
From what Millianna has told me
she underwent unimaginable pain
at the hands of Jellal.
So, why does she protect him?
[MINERVA] My guild's
image is tarnished...
These last few matches
have been, problematic...
But ...
I have an opportunity.
Your guilds have inflicted
the most damage...
Fairy Tail and Mermaid Heel.
It's up to me
to reclaim
Sabertooth's rightful
place on top...
I think eliminating
both of you at the same time
should make that
abundantly clear.
Right?
How very
ambitious of you.
Enough talk
for now... Fight!
[CHAPATI] Uh-oh! You feel that?
The surge of power emanating
from our competitors
is totally off the charts!
Yes.
Even from this far away, I can
feel the waves of intensity.
And this is only the beginning.
They have strength!
But they'll never
match your spirit!
Take 'em down!
[yelling, grunting]
[ERZA] Haa!
[grunting]
Victory is mine!
[MINERVA groans]
Yi Ragde!
[KAGURA] No!
[ERZA] What is this?!
[MINERVA] Neir, wilg, mion...
Derus erkantia!
What kinda
crazy talk is that?
Some kind
of incantation.
But I don't know it.
Erza! Run away!
That magic!
What is it?
It's the Eighteen
Battle Gods of Yakuma?!
Yagde Rigora!
[ERZA &amp; KAGURA grunt]
[CROWD gasping &amp; murmuring]
[ALL gasping]
Yep. That's m'lady.
That power. It's
unmistakable...
and unforgettable.
Whoa...
Crazy!
[BOTH] Take this! And this!
And that! And that!
[CHAPATI] How can
they still be standing?!
[MALE A] They're incredible!
[MALE B] That's the
understatement of the year, man!
[FEMALE A] They're so cool!
Wow...
That one made my
heart skip a beat!
I can't believe she's
mastered that magic!
Those are three chicks
ya don't wanna mess with.
You think this means
their magic power is equal?
I honestly can't say.
[MINERVA] How fascinating...
I'm afraid I may have
underestimated your strength.
Engaging
you two personally
has taught me many things...
You both have so much power
raging beneath the surface.
Continuing on like
this will take us nowhere...
So let's change up
the game just a bit.
Do you see that?
It's her!
Yes...
[MILLIANNA groaning]
[ERZA &amp; KAGURA gasp]
I found
a stray kitten.
[ERZA &amp; KAGURA] Millianna!
[MILLIANNA groaning]
[ERZA] What is the
meaning of this?!
[MINERVA chuckles]
[MINERVA] Look at that
face, twisted with pain.
The sphere she's in constantly
drains her magic power...
It's excruciating.
Erzy!
Oh, a kitty
of my very own!
It's been a while,
Erzy-Werzy!
She's taken her hostage.
How could
she stoop so low?!
I told y'all.
She's in trouble!
But why?
Why would she
wanna kidnap Millia?
Surrendering
won't save her...
Rest assured, I have a much
more entertaining plan in mind.
I told you that I wanted
to change the game.
[KAGURA growls]
[ERZA growls]
Oh yes... Those scornful
looks speak volumes.
[DARTON] Are you sure of this?!
If what you say is true,
then we must act at once!
That means calling off
the games this instant!
Not just yet...
It's too soon.
First, we must verify that this
person's claims are accurate.
Princess. We may not
have that kind of time.
We're putting the lives of
countless citizens at risk!
[HISUI] This person claims
to know the future...
which includes the outcome
of the Grand Magic Games.
They told me that a
certain guild would win
in a way that no one imagined.
But what does
that mean?
[HISUI] It's unexpected
enough that no one could
ever see it coming...
So, if this outcome does indeed
come to pass, it's proof...
I will believe their
other dire predictions.
This is the future
of our kingdom...
You'd bet it solely
on the final results
of the Grand Magic Games?!
I have a hard
time believing it.
That's why we must wait.
We must be absolutely
certain in their words.
What then?
What if the games end exactly
as this mysterious advisor
claims they will?
Then we can put
our trust in them.
We can heed their warning
and act accordingly.
And that means...
I'll have no choice
but to activate Eclipse.
But how?
Is it a trap?
[NATSU grunting]
Thanks, but...
Who are you?
[NATSU sniffing]
Hey, wait!
I recognize that smell!
No doubt about it.
Natsu...
[quietly sobbing]
[NATSU gasps]
[sobbing continues]
[NATSU] What the hell?
[GIRL] Please...
You have to help me.
What? It's her voice...
I don't understand.
Neither do I.
What's happening?
Don't know.
Show us who you are!
[LUCY gasps]
They told me...
No!
[HISUI] That they
came from the future.
Lucy?!
It's me?!
Two Lucys again?
Is she the Edolas one?
She's not.
And I'm afraid it's not
gonna be simple as that.
[thinking] Oh no...
[CARLA] That means
my premonition...
Could it be coming true?
[FUTURE LUCY] I'm
begging you. Please help...
The whole kingdom...
is doomed...
[HAPPY] What?! How
could there be two Lucys?!
[NATSU] Aw, calm
down. It's no big deal!
People get copies of
themselves all the time.
[HAPPY] Nuh-uh, liar! You're
just making that up!
[NATSU] No, I'm not! Trust me!
It's, like, the hot
new thing to do!
[HAPPY] How would you know?
[NATSU] Cuz. Uhh... Oooh!
Erza's got a big fight,
let's cheer her on!
[HAPPY] You're just trying
to change the subject.
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
Erza vs. Kagura
[HAPPY] Come on, tell me!
Where did you hear about it?
[NATSU] None of
your business, dude.