- ( humming )
- AH, JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE THINGS
ABOUT BEING BACK HOME.
- Cana:
THE TUB IS PRETTY GREAT.
- YEAH, IT'S THE BEST.
- IF YOU EVER WANT A ROOMMATE,
I WOULDN'T MIND LIVING
HERE AT ALL.
- IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE MAKING
YOURSELF RIGHT AT HOME TO ME!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP WITH
A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO HAVE
ANY ADULT BEVERAGES
HIDDEN AWAY IN THIS PLACE,
WOULD YOU?
- THIS IS MY HOUSE, YOU KNOW!
- Lucy: MY UNEXPECTED
GUEST IS CANA ALBERONA.
OF THE YOUNGER GENERATION
OF FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS
SHE'S BEEN IN THE GUILD
THE LONGEST.
- ( sighs )
- Lucy:
WHAT'S UP?
IS SOMETHING BOTHERING YOU?
- Cana: NO, I'M OKAY.
BUT I'VE GOT TO ASK,
DO YOU LIKE, MAKE A HABIT
OF BATHING WITH OTHER PEOPLE?
- DO YOU MAKE A HABIT OF
BREAKING INTO HOUSES? SERIOUSLY.
- SO HOW HAVE THINGS BEEN GOING
BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR DAD
THESE DAYS?
- UM...I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, I GUESS.
BUT I HAVEN'T ACTUALLY HEARD
FROM HIM IN A WHILE.
- HMM.
- ( sighs )
- JUST SPILL IT ALREADY.
I'LL ALWAYS LISTEN IF YOU
WANT TO TALK.
- ALRIGHT THEN. I'VE BEEN
SERIOUSLY CONSIDERING
QUITTING THE GUILD.
- Lucy:
WHAT?!
- ( Happy speaking )
- Chico: CHEERS!
- Wang: CHEERS!
- Lucy:
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I MEAN, I THOUGHT CANA
WAS IN FAIRY TAIL FOR LIFE.
I TRIED TO GET HER TO TELL
ME WHY, BUT SHE WOULDN'T SAY.
- I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SHE ALWAYS STARTS TALKING
ABOUT QUITTING
WHENEVER THIS TIME OF YEAR
ROLLS AROUND.
- SAY WHAT?!
OH, NO.  IS SOMETHING BAD
GOING TO HAPPEN?
- Lucy:
IT SEEMS WAY LONGER,
BUT IT'S BEEN LESS THAN A YEAR
SINCE I JOINED FAIRY TAIL.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF MAJOR EVENTS
AND TRADITIONS
THAT I'VE NEVER BEEN A PART OF.
AND LITTLE DID I KNOW,
ONE OF THE BIGGEST WAS GOING
TO BE TAKING PLACE VERY SOON.
- LET'S GET TO WORK, HAPPY.
-AYE!
- HEY, IF YOU'RE GOING ON A JOB,
TAKE ME WITH YOU!
- IT'S SOLO-MISSION SEASON,
SORRY.
- WE'LL HANG OUT WITH YOU
WHEN WE GET BACK.
- YOU BETTER WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
GOING, YOU PINK-HAIRED FREAK!
- AND YOU BETTER TRY TO STAY OUT
OF MY WAY, MR. GRUMPY PANTIES!
- YOU GUYS REALLY HAVE TIME
TO STAND AROUND AND ARGUE?
- ( both )
YEAH, GOOD POINT.
- I'M BACK.
- Mirajane:
FORGET YOUR CLOTHES AGAIN?
- NO TIME TO WORRY ABOUT IT,
I'M GOING TO TAKE THIS JOB,
SEE YA!
- Mirajane:
BYE-BYE, GOOD LUCK.
- HE'S ON A SOLO GIG, TOO?
- HEY, THIS IS A JOB
FOR A REAL MAN.
- Mirajane:
ALRIGHT, BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
- I'M GOING TO PULL THE TRIGGER
ON THIS JOB OVER HERE, OKAY?
- GOT MY SIGHTS ON THIS ONE.
- I CALLED DIBS ON THAT JOB,
WARREN!
- I'M SORRY, PAL.
BUT IT'S FINDERS KEEPERS.
- ( both ) THE GREAT AND
MIGHTY TEAM SHADOW GEAR
IS SPLITTING UP FOR NOW.
- WHY IS EVERYONE GOING CRAZY?
- Mirajane:
YOU'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH.
- Wendy: HUH?
- ( both )
YOU CAN SEE INTO THE FUTURE?
- YES, A TRAIT THAT THE
EXCEED QUEEN AND I SHARE.
BOTH OF US WERE BLESSED WITH
THE RARE GIFT OF CLAIRVOYANCE.
I WASN'T AWARE OF IT
UNTIL RECENTLY,
BUT I BELIEVE I HAVE A SMALL
DEGREE OF CONTROL OVER IT.
- WOW, THAT'S TOTALLY AMAZING.
- SO CAN YOU TELL ME WHICH GUY
IS GOING TO BE
MY FUTURE HUSBAND?
- I'M AFRAID I'M NOT ABLE
TO SEE THAT FAR AHEAD.
BUT MAYBE, SOMETHING SOONER?
OKAY, KEEP AN EYE
ON MACAO OVER THERE.
I PREDICT THAT ANY MOMENT NOW,
WAKABA WILL WALK UP TO HIM
AND START DISCUSSING
THE YOUNGER FOLKS IN THE GUILD.
- ( both )
LET'S SEE.
- WHAT'S SHAKING, OLD TIMER?
- HEY, PAL.
- YOU WERE RIGHT, HE WALKED UP
JUST LIKE YOU SAID!
- BE QUIET SO WE CAN HEAR
WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- WE'RE GETTING TO THAT TIME
OF YEAR AGAIN, BUDDY.
- YEAH, IT REALLY TAKES ME BACK.
- Wakaba: THOSE WERE THE
GOOD OLD DAYS, WEREN'T THEY?
- Macao: WE WERE FULL
OF SPUNK BACK THEN.
- Wakaba: TELL YOU WHAT, THIS
NEW CROP IS SOMETHING ELSE.
ESPECIALLY THEIR DERRIERES!
- WHAT, NO WAY!
- YOU MORE OF A BREAST MAN?
- LOOK, I'M TRYING
TO RAISE A KID.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO GO AROUND
CHECKING OUT BUTTS.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU'RE A LEG MAN, AREN'T YA?
- Macao:
NOW YOU'RE SPEAKING MY LANGUAGE.
I'LL STAND BEHIND
A PAIR OF LEGS ANY DAY.
- THAT IS SO COOL!
- YEAH, YOU HIT IT ON THE NOSE.
YOU DIDN'T TELL US IT WOULD BE
SO CREEPY, THOUGH.
- QUITE HONESTLY, WE SHOULD HAVE
ALL SEEN THAT ONE COMING.
- STILL, I'M SUPER IMPRESSED.
- MM-HM.
- THANK YOU.
BUT I STILL HAVE
MUCH MORE TO LEARN
ABOUT HOW
TO PROPERLY CONTROL IT.
- HEY GUYS, YOU SHOULDN'T
BE DOING THAT INDOORS.
- HAD ENOUGH?
- IT SEEMS I CAN'T STAY IN MY
ORIGINAL FORM FOR VERY LONG.
- STILL, I FIND YOU
QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
YOUR BLADE SKILLS
ARE TOP-NOTCH.
- YOU FLATTER ME.
I THINK I SHOULD BE THE ONE
COMPLIMENTING YOU.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, ERZA?
MY CAT IS A FORCE OF NATURE,
AIN'T HE?
- I ASSUME THIS IS
WHAT THE GUILD REFERS TO
AS AN S-CLASS SKILL LEVEL?
- ( humming )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
SO MANY PEOPLE
ARE FREAKING GUNG-HO
ABOUT GOING OUT ON JOBS,
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE IS
JUST GOOFING OFF
LIKE THERE'S NOTHING HAPPENING.
- IT WILL ALL MAKE SENSE
TO YOU TOMORROW.
- Male Narrator:
THE FOLLOWING DAY,
ALMOST EVERY MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL
HAS GATHERED IN THE GUILD HALL
AWAITING A MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT.
- WHAT'S ALL
THE COMMOTION ABOUT?
- BEATS ME.
- I THINK THE MASTER IS
GOING TO TELL US
ABOUT SOMETHING BIG HAPPENING.
- CAN'T SAY I'M EXCITED.
- WHAT'S HE GOING TO SAY?
THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING ME!
- WE WORKED
OUR LITTLE TAILS OFF, RIGHT?
DON'T WORRY.
- JUST CALM DOWN, NATSU.
YOU'VE GOT THIS.
- THE TENSION HERE IS HUGE,
VERY MANLY.
- I'M DYING TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- THIS IS
SO UNBELIEVABLY EXCITING.
- Juvia:
GRAY IS ALMOST WITHIN REACH.
- Lucy:
YEAH, BE STILL MY HEART.
- ( crowd cheering )
- HERE WE GO!
- PLEASE DON'T MAKE US
WAIT ANY LONGER!
- YEAH, JUST TELL US ALREADY!
- I'M STILL SO LOST.
TELL US WHAT NOW?
- AHEM, IN ACCORDANCE
WITH THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD'S
TIME HONORED TRADITION,
I WILL NOW ANNOUNCE
THIS YEARS ENTRANTS FOR THE
S-CLASS WIZARD PROMOTION TRIAL!
- ( crowd cheers )
- THIS IS WHY EVERYONE'S
BEEN ACTING CRAZY LATELY.
- I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW!
- Erza:
PLEASE BE QUIET, EVERYONE.
- SHUT UP AND LET THE MASTER
FINISH TALKING.
- THE TRIAL THIS YEAR WILL
TAKE PLACE ON TENROU ISLAND.
OUR GUILD'S SACRED GROUND.
- ( crowd talking excitedly )
- DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT HE'S
GOING TO MAKE THEM DO?
- WELL, IT'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT
EVERY YEAR.
- IT'S BASICALLY
A SERIOUSLY TOUGH JOB.
- BUT IF YOU'RE ABLE
TO PULL IT OFF,
HE'LL BUMP YOU UP
TO AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
- THE STRENGTH THAT YOU
POSSESS INSIDE, YOUR CHARACTER,
AND YOUR HEARTS.
THESE ARE WHAT I CONSIDERED
WHILE MAKING MY SELECTION.
AND I HAVE CHOSEN
EIGHT PARTICIPANTS.
- Makarov:
NATSU DRAGNEEL.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- YOU'VE GOT THIS
IN THE BAG, BUDDY.
- Makarov:
GRAY FULLBUSTER.
- IT'S FINALLY MY TIME
TO  MOVE UP.
- Makarov:
JUVIA LOXAR.
- REALLY?
THE MASTER CHOSE ME?
- Makarov:
ELFMAN.
- S-CLASS DESERVES
A REAL MAN LIKE ME.
- BEST OF LUCK, BIG BROTHER.
- Makarov:
CANA ALBERONA.
FRIED JUSTINE.
- SO I'LL BE FOLLOWING
IN LAXUS' FOOTSTEPS.
- Makarov:
LEVY MCGARDEN.
- I'M SO STOKED ABOUT THIS.
- ( both ) LEVY IS TOTALLY
GOING TO WIN THIS ONE!
- Makarov:
AND MEST GRYDER.
- Guild Member #1:
MEST!
- Guild Member #2: HE ALMOST
MADE S-CLASS LAST TIME.
- I WORKED SO HARD, SO WHY
DIDN'T HE PICK ME THIS YEAR?
- IT'S BOUND TO HAPPEN
SOME DAY, BUCK UP.
- Droy and Jet:
LEVY'S GOING TO BE--
- Max: WELL, MASTER
FINALLY CHOSE NATSU.
- Warren:
DON'T FORGET GRAY.
- I'M SO PROUD OF THOSE KIDS.
- I BET THEY'RE PRETTY EXCITED.
- WHEN I GROW UP, I'M GOING
TO BE AN S-CLASS WIZARD, TOO.
YOU JUST WATCH ME.
- Lucy:
I GET IT NOW,
EVERYONE WANTED MASTER
TO PICK THEM FOR THE TRIAL
SO THEY WORKED THEIR BUTTS OFF
TO IMPRESS HIM.
- I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT,
YOU GUYS!
- Lucy:
I WONDER...
IS THIS WHY SHE WAS TALKING
ABOUT QUITTING?
- ALTHOUGH EIGHT WIZARDS
HAVE BEEN SELECTED,
ONLY ONE WILL EMERGE VICTORIOUS.
THE TRIAL WILL BEGIN
IN ONE WEEK'S TIME.
SO YOU'D BETTER STEP UP
YOUR PREPARATIONS.
- HE'S ONLY GOING TO CHOOSE ONE?
- I'D PUT MY MONEY
ON FRIED THIS YEAR.
- I'VE GOT TO GO WITH MEST.
- NATSU AND GRAY ARE
NO SLOUCHES.
- HOW COME HE PICKED JUVIA,
BUT I GET PASSED OVER?
I THOUGHT THE OLD MAN
LIKED ME MORE THAN HER.
- YOU SEEM TO HAVE
A SHADY REPUTATION
IN THE GUILD FOR SOME REASON.
I GET THE FEELING THEY DON'T
TRUST YOU VERY MUCH.
- THAT'S CRAZY!  THEY CAN ALL
TRUST ME JUST FINE!
- Gajeel:
I JUST CAN'T TELL THEM
WHAT I'M REALLY DOING
AROUND HERE.
- Pantherlily:
TAKE IT UP WITH ERZA.
- SORRY, BUT YOU'RE
NOT READY YET.
- THIS WHOLE THING SUCKS!
- AND AS USUAL,
EVERYBODY LOSES CONTROL.
- HEY, IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG,
CARLA?
- NO, I'M FINE.
SO STRANGE, WHAT WAS I SEEING?
WHO WAS THAT?
- Lucy: LITTLE DID I KNOW,
EVEN THOUGH I WASN'T CHOSEN
BY THE MASTER TO PARTICIPATE,
I WOULD STILL PLAY A ROLE.
AND SOMETHING ELSE UNEXPECTED
WOULD TAKE PLACE.
- Makarov: FOR THE BENEFIT
OF OUR NEWCOMERS,
LET'S GO OVER THE RULES
OF THE CHALLENGE, SHALL WE?
- THE EIGHT PARTICIPANTS
WILL EACH CHOOSE A PARTNER.
THIS PERSON WILL ALSO
BE ALLOWED TO TRAIN WITH THEM
DURING THE WEEK LEADING UP
TO THE EVENT.
- A PARTNER?
- YEAH, ULTIMATELY IT'S A BATTLE
BETWEEN TWO-PERSON TEAMS.
- A BIG PART OF IT IS PUTTING
THEIR FRIENDSHIPS
TO THE TEST AS WELL.
- OBSERVE THESE TWO RULES
WHEN CHOOSING YOUR PARTNER--
NUMBER ONE, THEY MUST BE
A MEMBER OF FAIRY TAIL.
AND NUMBER TWO, YOUR CHOICE
CANNOT BE AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
- HUH.
- BUT THAT ONLY RULES OUT
A HANDFUL OF PEOPLE.
NEITHER ERZA, MIRAJANE,
NOR GILDARTS CAN BE CHOSEN.
- GUESS A TEAM WITH
THOSE GUYS ON IT
WOULD BE PRETTY HARD TO BEAT.
- WE'LL REVEAL
ALL THE PARTICULAR DETAILS
OF THE TRIAL ONCE WE'VE ARRIVED
ON TENROU ISLAND.
BUT KNOW THAT YOU'LL HAVE TO GET
PAST ERZA TO CLAIM VICTORY.
- ( gasping )
- AND I'LL BE DOING MY VERY BEST
TO HELP WEED OUT THE REST OF YOU
RIGHT BESIDE HER.
- ( gasping )
- SO THE ONLY WAY SOMEBODY
CAN BECOME AN S-CLASS WIZARD
IS BY DEFEATING ERZA
AND MIRAJANE?
- BUT THE RUMOR HAS IT,
THEY'VE BEEN ORDERED
TO HOLD BACK A LITTLE BIT.
- I STILL DON'T ENVY ANYBODY
THAT HAS TO TAKE THEM ON.
- QUIT YOUR BELLYACHING.
THE THREE OF US
HAD TO GO THROUGH THIS TRIAL.
IT'S ONLY FAIR YOU DO, TOO.
- NO WAY, HE SAID,
"THE THREE OF US?"
- SWEET TUNA!
- I'M FINALLY GOING TO GET
TO FIGHT OLD MAN GILDARTS!
- THAT'S NOT GOOD NEWS!
- THE EIGHT PARTICIPANTS
I NAMED EARLIER
AND THEIR CHOSEN PARTNERS
ARE ASKED TO MEET
AT THE PORT OF HARGEON,
ONE WEEK FROM TODAY.
SO GET TO WORK.
- MAN, THEY SET THE BAR
CRAZY HIGH THIS YEAR.
- I'M KIND OF SURPRISED NONE
OF YOU HAVE EVER BEEN CHOSEN
FOR THIS THING BEFORE.
- Natsu: I'M READY FOR THE
BIG TIME. S-CLASS, HERE I COME!
- I KNOW I'M THE MANLIEST GUY
IN THE GUILD,
BUT I'M AS SCARED
AS A LITTLE GIRL RIGHT NOW!
- Wendy:
IT SURE SOUNDS TOUGH TO ME.
- Lisanna:
GOOD LUCK, EVERYBODY.
- I'LL BE COUNTING ON YOU.
- DON'T WORRY.  I'VE GOT
YOUR BACK, OLD BUDDY.
- Tommens:
THAT'S RIGHT.
- WE NEED AN S-CLASS MAN
IN OUR RANKS
NOW THAT LAXUS AIN'T AROUND.
HE'S GOT BIG SHOES TO FILL,
BUT I CAN'T THINK OF ANYONE
WHO COULD DO IT BETTER.
BESIDES, WE'VE GOT
TO SHOW EVERYONE
THE THUNDER LEGION'S
STILL GOT IT!
- Tommens:
REPRESENT!
- Lucy: WELL, IT
LOOKS LIKE FRIED'S PARTNER
IS GOING TO BE BIXLOW.
I THINK THEY'LL PROBABLY BE
A PRETTY TOUGH TEAM TO BEAT,
DON'T YOU?
- JEEZ, LUCY,
WAY TO BE ENCOURAGING.
- SPEAKING OF PARTNERS,
DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHO YOU'RE
GOING TO CHOOSE YET?
- I'M GOING WITH MY LITTLE
BUDDY, OF COURSE. - AYE!
- HEY, NOT SO FAST THERE PINKY.
IF THIS THING ENDS UP BEING
SOME KIND OF RACE,
HAVING A PARTNER THAT CAN FLY
IS AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE.
- WELL, IT SEEMS FAIR TO ME.
- Gray:
I'M COOL WITH IT TOO.
IF THIS ENDS BEING A BATTLE,
IT WILL BE A DISADVANTAGE.
- I'M SITTING RIGHT HERE,
YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS BECAUSE YOU
KNOW I'M GOING TO MAKE NATSU
AN S-CLASS WIZARD!
- WELL, YOU BETTER GET OVER IT.
'CAUSE THERE AIN'T NO WAY
YOU'RE BREAKING UP OUR TEAM.
- LET'S GO, PAL!
- SCREW A BUNCH
OF SITTING AROUND,
WE'VE GOT TRAINING TO DO!
- Happy:
AYE, SIR!
- I KNOW I'VE BEEN GONE
FOR TWO YEARS, BUT STILL--
I CAN'T BELIEVE NATSU'S
GOTTEN STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE IN THE RUNNING
FOR AN S-CLASS RANK.
- Lisanna: HE'S ALWAYS BELIEVED
THAT IF HE CAN BECOME
A MORE POWERFUL WIZARD, HE'LL
BE ABLE TO SEE IGNEEL AGAIN.
HE PROBABLY HAS TWICE
THE MOTIVATION FOR MOVING AHEAD
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
- MAYBE SO.
(thinking )
GOOD LUCK, NATSU.
YOU'LL SEE HIM SOMEDAY.
- I THINK I MIGHT
PREFER TO WITHDRAW
FROM THE TRIAL THIS YEAR.
- HUH? BUT, WHY?
- IT'S JUST...
I'D MUCH RATHER BE
SOMEBODY'S PARTNER THAN RIVAL.
- SAY WHAT?
- WELL, I MEAN, IF I--
IF IT WERE MY CHOICE...
- IT'S OBVIOUS SHE'D RATHER
BE YOUR PARTNER. - YOU THINK?
- DON'T YOU DARE TRY
TO STEAL HIM AWAY FROM ME!
- I WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
- Juvia:
BE HONEST WITH ME GRAY,
WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE
THIS BLONDE BIMBO ON YOUR TEAM?
- SIMMER DOWN, OKAY?
I'VE ALREADY GOT SOMEONE
LINED UP. - YOU DO?
- LONG TIME NO SEE, YOU GUYS.
- YOU'RE USING
ONE OF MY SPIRITS?!
- SERIOUSLY?
- WE WORKED THIS WHOLE THING OUT
A YEAR AGO.
- PLEASE DON'T TAKE THIS
TOO HARD, LUCY.
BUT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO PUT
A HOLD ON OUR CONTRACT
WHILE I TEAM UP WITH GRAY.
JUST IN CASE YOU'RE WONDERING,
I USED MY OWN POWER IN ORDER
TO PASS THROUGH THE GATE.
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT RUNNING OUT
OF MAGIC BECAUSE OF ME.
- 'KAY.
BUT I KIND OF WISH YOU WOULD
HAVE RUN THIS BY ME FIRST.
- ALRIGHT HAPPY, IT'S TIME
TO GET STARTED...
- ( both )
...ON SOME HARDCORE TRAINING!
- Natsu:
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO START WITH.
- Happy:
WELL, IT'S SNOWING RIGHT NOW
SO THE CHOICE IS
PRETTY CLEAR TO ME.
- RIGHT YOU ARE, OLD PAL.
LET THE TRAINING BEGIN!
WAIT, HOLD ON!
- FOR THE FIRST EXERCISE,
YOU'LL BE WORKING ON
DEFENSE TECHNIQUES
BY STOPPING THESE GIANT BOULDERS
USING ONLY YOUR BODY.
- CAN'T WE TRY
SOMETHING ELSE INSTEAD?!
- Elfman:
WAIT A MINUTE, LOKE.
ARE YOU STILL A FULL-FLEDGED
MEMBER OF THE GUILD?
- Loke:
MM-HMM.
SEE?  I'M STILL
A PROUD FAIRY TAIL WIZARD.
AND AS SUCH, IT'S MY
DUTY TO HELP GRAY
REACH HIS FULL POTENTIAL
AND MAKE IT TO S-CLASS.
- I APPRECIATE THE HELP, BUDDY.
- I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
- I DON'T REMEMBER THESE GUYS
BEING EACH OTHER'S "BFFs"
BEFORE TODAY.
- SO FEEL FREE TO COME AT ME
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
WE'LL GET HOT AND HEAVY LIKE
WE DID THE FIRST TIME WE MET.
- ( gasps )
HOT...
AND HEAVY?
WOW-WW.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN HANDLE IT.
- EASY THERE, GIRL.
- HEY, I'LL BE
ON YOUR TEAM, JUVIA.
- YOU BARELY EVEN KNOW HER.
- ACTUALLY, ME AND THE JUVIA
BACK IN EDOLAS
CAME TO BE REALLY GOOD FRIENDS.
NOT THAT YOU'RE ANYTHING
LIKE HER.
YOU'RE A LOT SWEETER.
- YOU WOULD CHOOSE ME?
- SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- I SUPPOSE SO. BUT I HAVE A
FEELING YOU'RE JUST USING ME
TO GET TO GRAY... - Lucy:
WHY IS SHE ALWAYS SO PARANOID?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WOULD
DO THIS TO ME, LITTLE SIS!
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE
YOUR OWN FLESH AND BLOOD
GO THROUGH THE TRIAL
WITHOUT A PARTNER?!
- NO.  YOU'VE BEEN GETTING
SUCH AN INTENSE STARE
I THOUGHT YOU ALREADY HAD
SOMEONE. - HUH?
( gasps )
- I THINK SHE MIGHT BE
A LITTLE UPSET
THAT FRIED TEAMED UP
WITH BIXLOW INSTEAD OF HER.
- SHE'S LOOKING RIGHT AT ME.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- Elfman: HER INTENSE STARE
IS ACTUALLY MORE LIKE...
...PETRIFYING!
- Happy:
HERE WE GO!
SPECIAL EXERCISE NUMBER 15
WILL DEFINITELY PUMP UP
THOSE SKINNY LEG MUSCLES!
HEY, YOU WANT TO TAKE
A BREAK, BIG GUY?
- INTENSE PAIN AIN'T
STOPPING ME!
LET'S MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT ONE, 'KAY?
- Happy:
SPECIAL EXERCISE NUMBER 16.
- GUESS I'D BETTER BE
HEADING TO TENROU ISLAND.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE, NATSU.
- THOSE S-CLASS HOTSHOTS
THINK THEY'RE GOING TO BE
ABLE TO STAND IN MY WAY, HUH?
I'D LIKE TO SEE THEM TRY!
- Happy:
AYE, SIR!
- Jet:
MASTER CHOSE YOU!
- Droy: YOU'RE GOING TO BE
AN AMAZING S-CLASS WIZARD.
YOU'RE GOING TO PICK ME
TO BE YOUR PARTNER, AREN'T YOU?
- YOU? INSTEAD OF ME?
I'M A HUNDRED TIMES FASTER.
- Droy: BUT LET'S FACE IT,
I'M THE BETTER FIGHTER.
- Jet: WHATEVER, YOU'VE JUST
GOT A THING FOR LEVY.
- Droy:
OH, AND YOU DON'T?
- IF YOU REALLY WANT TO MAKE
IT TO S-CLASS,
YOU SHOULD PICK ME INSTEAD
OF THOSE TWO CLOWNS.
- SERIOUSLY?
- I GET CHANCE TO BEAT UP
ON ALL THOSE OTHER IDIOTS
IF WE DO THIS, DON'T I?
- I GUESS THERE'S GOING TO BE
SOME FIGHTING INVOLVED.
BUT I'M SO PUNY AND WEAK.
WE'LL PROBABLY JUST LOSE
RIGHT AWAY.
- DON'T GO WIMPING OUT
BEFORE THE WHOLE THING
EVEN GETS STARTED, YOU HEAR?
- HEY, LET GO!
PLEASE, PUT ME DOWN!
- I'LL MAKE YOU BIGGER THAN
YOU'VE EVER BEEN, LITTLE GIRL.
- Wendy: HOW COME YOU'VE
BEEN SO QUIET TODAY?
I WISH YOU WOULD TELL ME
WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU.
- I'M NOT SURE.
I KEEP HAVING
THESE STRANGE VISIONS--
SOMETHING GOING WRONG
AT THE TRIAL.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE
ANY PART OF IT, UNDERSTAND?
- Wendy: DON'T WORRY, I DON'T
THINK ANYONE'S GOING TO PICK ME
TO BE THEIR PARTNER.
- Mest:
I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE
ABOUT THAT, SKY MAIDEN.
- OH, IT'S YOU.
WHO ARE YOU, AGAIN?
- MY NAME'S MEST GRYDER.
I WAS MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL.
- SOUP'S ON!
YOU READY TO EAT?
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG, NATSU?
- I'M FINALLY GETTING
MY BIG CHANCE.
AND I WILL BE
AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
- Happy:
AYE.
- Lucy:
WHOA, CHECK IT OUT PLUE.
I DIDN'T THINK IT EVER SNOWED
IN MAGNOLIA.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
PASSED OUT IN THE ALLEYWAY?
- Cana:
AH-HH.
I OWE YOU ONE.
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED ME
I WOULD HAVE FROZEN MY BUTT OFF
OUT THERE TONIGHT.
- NO JOKE, NOW YOU WANT TO TELL
ME WHY YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
LIKE SUCH A LUNATIC LATELY?
- YOU MEAN MIRA HASN'T
ALREADY TOLD YOU ABOUT IT?
I GET KIND OF CRAZY
AROUND S-CLASS TRIAL TIME.
IT HAPPENS EVERY YEAR.
- DOES THIS HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH YOU SAYING THAT YOU WANT
TO QUIT THE GUILD?
- THIS WILL BE MY FIFTH TRIAL.
THAT MEANS I'VE TRIED
FOUR TIMES,
BUT I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO GO ALL THE WAY.
BECAUSE I SUCK.
- OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
IS THAT ALL?
JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
MADE IT YET
DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN'T.
- I'M THE ONLY PERSON
WHO'S FAILED FOUR TIMES.
THAT'S WHY THIS WILL BE
MY LAST ONE.
IF I DON'T PASS IT THIS TIME,
I'M GOING TO LEAVE FAIRY TAIL.
- HEY, NOW. THERE ARE PLENTY OF
GUILD MEMBERS
WHO AREN'T S-CLASS.
- WELL, I DON'T WANT TO BE
ONE OF THOSE LOSERS, OK?!
I HAVE TO BE AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
OR I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO LOOK HIM IN THE EYE.
- ( melancholy music plays )
- ( music continues )
- DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THAT'S WHY IF I DON'T
MAKE IT THIS TIME,
I'M QUITTING FAIRY TAIL
FOR GOOD.
MY MIND IS MADE UP.
- CANA, WILL YOU PLEASE
LET ME BE YOUR PARTNER?
FAIRY TAIL JUST WOULDN'T
BE THE SAME WITHOUT YOU.
I PROMISE, I CAN HELP YOU
BECOME AN S-CLASS WIZARD!
- ( trembling )
- THANK YOU.
- Male Narrator:
ONE WEEK LATER,
OUR CONTESTANTS GATHER
AT THE PORT OF HARGEON.
WITH THEIR HEARTS RACING
AND THEIR DREAMS ON THE LINE,
THEY BEGIN THE S-CLASS WIZARD
PROMOTION TRIAL.
BUT WHO WILL ADVANCE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( laughing )
- Natsu: WHOA, WHAT'S
WITH THE CREEPY LOOK?
- Happy:
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
- Natsu:
EH, PROBABLY NOT, REALLY.
- Happy: THE STARS
HAVE ALIGNED IN MY FAVOR
AND TODAY I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
EXTREMELY LUCKY IN LOVE!
CANA READ MY FORTUNE EARLIER.
- Natsu: HUH.
- Happy: IF I CAN PULL OFF SOME
MAJORLY COOL STUFF IN THE TRIAL,
CARLA WILL FALL
HEAD-OVER-HEELS FOR ME!
- ( giggling )
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: YOU KNOW CARLA ISN'T
EVEN GOING TO BE THERE,
DON'T YOU?
- Happy:
WHAT-TT?!
OH, MAN!
- Natsu:
I GUESS ALL THAT GOOD LUCK
IS GOING TO GO TO WASTE, PAL.