HEY GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV!
- Mirajane:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy: SOME BIG THINGS HAPPENED
IN THE BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL.
ERZA BEAT EVERGREEN
AND ALL OF US GIRLS
THAT WERE TURNED INTO STATUES
ARE FINALLY BACK TO NORMAL.
BUT BEFORE WE HAD THE CHANCE
TO CELEBRATE,
THAT JERK LAXUS
CAST HIS THUNDER PALACE SPELL
AND TOOK
THE WHOLE TOWN HOSTAGE.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO JOIN THE FIGHT!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- AHHH!
- WOW!
- HE PUNCHED HIM
WITH A LION MADE OF LIGHT!
- IT'S TOTALLY POINTLESS.
THESE ARE SOULS, MAN.
YOU CAN'T HURT 'EM.
YOU CAN DESTROY THEIR BODIES,
BUT I'LL JUST MOVE 'EM
ON TO SOMETHING ELSE.
THAT MEANS
I GET NEW BABIES!
- All: YEAH!
- YOU COULD SEND A MILLION
OF THOSE THINGS,
I WON'T LET
ANY OF 'EM TOUCH HER!
- COME ON!
- AYE, SIR!
- WHOA!
YOU'RE A FEISTY
LITTLE CHEERLEADER, AIN'T YA?
- I AM NOT A CHEERLEADER!
- LUCY,
GO ON AND TAKE HIM OUT!
HE'S NOTHING!
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN HIM!
- HEY, MAN,
TAKE THAT BACK!
AW, CRAP.
TIME FOR THE BIG GUNS.
- BIG GUNS?
- UH-OH!
- ( neck cracks )
- ( Happy speaking )
- FIGURE EYES.
- Happy: DON'T LOOK INTO 'EM.
EACH ONE
OF THE THUNDER LEGION MEMBERS
HAS SPECIAL POWERS
THEY CAN USE IN THEIR EYES.
EVERGREEN CAN TURN YOU
INTO STONE WITH HERS.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT BIXLOW,
HE'LL TURN YOU INTO ONE
OF HIS CREEPY DOLLS.
HE'LL CONTROL YOUR SOUL.
- REALLY?
- NO WAY!
- WELL, AREN'T YOU SMART?
- All: SO SMART!
- Happy: WHATEVER YOU DO,
KEEP YOUR EYES CLOSED!
- ( Bixlow laughing )
MY POSSESSION AND FIGURE
EYES COMBO IS UNBEATABLE
AND YOU GUYS WON'T EVEN
GIVE IT SO MUCH AS A LOOK?
COME ON!
- LUCY, CLOSE MY GATE
AND HIDE INSIDE OF HOROLOGIUM
FOR A WHILE!
- YEAH, GREAT IDEA,
BUT MY KEYS WERE STOLEN
SO I CAN'T SUMMON HIM.
NOW COME ON!
I KNOW YOU CAN HELP ME,
SO JUST DO IT ALREADY!
- ALL RIGHT,
IT'S THE MOMENT OF TRUTH.
WHEN I GIVE THE SIGNAL,
OPEN YOUR EYES
AND HIT HIM
AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
- BUT I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO KEEP 'EM CLOSED.
- YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO TRUST ME.
- I TRUST YOU.
- THE ZENITH OF REGULUS!
LION BRILLIANCE!
- AH!  MY EYES.
- NOW, LUCY!
- OKAY!
( grunting )
- NO!  THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LET YOU BEAT ME!
- Loke: I'M NOT THE MAN
I USED TO BE.
WHEN I MET LUCY,
MY TRUE POWER AS A CELESTIAL
SPIRIT WAS AWAKENED.
I'M STRONGER
THAN I'VE EVER BEEN BEFORE
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO HER.
WE SPIRITS ARE NOT
LIKE YOUR LITTLE DOLLS.
LOVE MAKES US STRONGER.
REGULUS IMPACT!
AHHH!
- ( screams )
- KAPOW!
- THANKS, LOKE.
- I DID IT FOR THIS.
LOVE'S DAZZLING BRILLIANCE.
- Lucy: UH, COOL.
- WHEN'S THE WEDDING?
- YEAH,
DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH, CAT.
OH, MAN.
I'M SO BEAT.
- OPENING UP TWO ZODIAC GATES
WOULD TAKE A LOT OUT OF SOMEONE.
- I'LL BE THERE ANYTIME
THAT YOU NEED ME.
- AW, THANKS.
- WHOA, LUCY KICKED HIS BUTT.
- NO WAY!
THAT LITTLE PRINCESS
CAN ACTUALLY FIGHT?
- YEAH, SHE'S TOUGH AS NAILS.
- SHE'S JUST A CHEERLEADER!
- WAY TO GO, LUCY.
- WELL, THEY CAN BE TOUGH.
- I AM RIGHT THERE WITH YA.
- YEAH RIGHT,
I'VE NEVER HEARD THAT BEFORE! -
REALLY? YOU'VE NEVER HEARD
THE STORY OF THE TORTOISE
AND THE CHEERLEADER?
- IT WAS A HARE, YA MORON!
AND THE DUMB BUNNY LOST,
REMEMBER?
- I STILL DON'T GET THIS PART
AT ALL.
IF ONLY I COULD
JUST REWORD IT. ( groans )
COME ON LEVY, THINK.
AH!  THAT'S IT!
- Both: WHAT'S WHAT?
- I NEED TO LOOK
AT THESE TWO GRAMMAR STYLES
LIKE THE TORTOISE
AND THE HARE
AND TRANSLATE THEM
AT TWO DIFFERENT RATES.
IF I TAKE THE INTEGRAL NUMBER
OF SYNCHRONIZED LETTERS
IN A SINGLE PASS AND TRANSFORM
THEM INTO GEEL GRAMMAR,
AND THEN TRANSLATE THAT
INTO LOGUE...
IT WORKED!
- Both: YEAH!
- JUST GIVE ME A SECOND, I NEED
TO REWRITE THE ENCHANTMENT.
-YOU BET.
- THIS IS IT, YOU GUYS.
WHEN I'M THROUGH HERE,
YOU TWO'LL JOIN
THE BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
- YEAH, I'M ALL FIRED UP!
- IT'S TIME
TO TAKE OUT THE TRASH.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- MIRA.
- YOU'RE HURT PRETTY BAD.
- I'LL BE FINE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE BACK
TO NORMAL.
- I'M SORRY FOR EVERYTHING.
I REALLY AM.
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU APOLOGIZING FOR?
- BECAUSE I'M JUST USELESS NOW.
IT'S THE TRUTH.
I'M NEVER ABLE TO HELP YOU.
I'M SORRY.
- NO ONE THINKS YOU'RE USELESS.
I PROMISE.
YOUR SMILE
LIFTS EVERYONE'S SPIRITS.
IT MAKES US THINK
OF THE GOOD THINGS
AND FORGET
ABOUT THIS FIGHTING CRAP.
- ( whimpering )
- COME ON, SIS.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
- Cana: JUVIA.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG
WE HAVE
BEFORE THE THUNDER PALACE
ACTIVATES?
- AT THIS POINT, I'D SAY
IT'S ABOUT 30 MINUTES.
- MAN, WHAT A COWARD.
THE BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL, HUH?
EVERYONE ELSE FIGHTS
WHILE HE HIDES IN A CORNER?
- THE QUESTION
IS WHICH CORNER?
- Fried: LAXUS IS SAVING
HIS MAGIC ENERGY.
IT WOULD BE FOOLISH OF HIM
TO FIGHT MASTER MAKAROV
AT LESS THAN FULL POWER.
- Cana: FRIED.
- Juvia: SO HE'S THE ONE
WHO'S BEHIND THE ENCHANTMENTS.
- GET BACK HERE!
WHERE'D HE GO?
- OH, GREAT.
ANOTHER ONE?
- WE'RE TRAPPED.
- IT SAYS, "ONLY THE WIZARD
WHO PROVES HERSELF
TO BE THE STRONGEST--"
- "--WILL BE PERMITTED TO LEAVE
THIS BARRIER."
- THE VICTOR WILL THEN GO ON
TO BATTLE ME.
YOU MAY BEGIN.
- COME ON, FRIED!
IF YOU'RE REALLY LOOKING
FOR A FIGHT,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE,
'CAUSE I'LL TAKE YOU ON
RIGHT NOW, YOU HEAR?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
ARE YOU SCARED?
DON'T THINK YOU'RE MAN ENOUGH
TO HANDLE THE BOTH OF US?
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN MUCH
OF A REAL MAN, HAVE YOU?
- THE TRUTH OF THE MATTER
IS I'D PREFER
NOT TO SULLY MY OWN HANDS.
- YOU'RE SUCH A RAT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D MAKE YOUR
FRIENDS FIGHT EACH OTHER
LIKE THIS.
- "FRIENDS", YOU SAY?
TO BE PERFECTLY CANDID,
I'D RATHER SEE CANA
EMERGE THE VICTOR.
AS FOR JUVIA,
YOU STILL BEAR THE STAIN
OF PHANTOM LORD.
YOU CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHEN YOU MAY CHOOSE
TO TAKE UP ARMS
AGAINST FAIRY TAIL AGAIN.
- WHAT, LIKE YOU ARE NOW?
- FORGIVE ME.
BUT I'VE NO OTHER CHOICE.
- HOLD ON.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- Juvia: TELL ME SOMETHING,
MR. FRIED.
IF ONE OF US FALLS,
WILL YOU KEEP YOUR WORD
AND FIGHT THE ONE THAT REMAINS?
- I ASSURE YOU,
I'LL STAND BY MY WORD.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
- ARE YOU NUTS?
YOU'RE JUST GIVING
THIS CREEP WHAT HE WANTS!
- Fried:
GO AS HIGH AS YOU WANT!
THE ONLY WAY TO ESCAPE
IS BY STEPPING
OVER YOUR FALLEN OPPONENT.
IF ONE OF US MUST FALL
FOR THIS SPELL TO BE LIFTED,
I WILL BE THE ONE
TO MAKE IT SO!
- SHE WOULDN'T.
- STAY AWAY FROM THAT THING!
- I'LL NEVER HARM A FRIEND!
- JUVIA!
- ( screaming )
- I BROKE
THE ENCHANTMENT SPELL.
YOU ARE FREE NOW.
- BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
GO AND DO THAT.
- I WANTED
TO PROVE TO THE GUILD
THAT THERE'S NO REASON
TO DOUBT ME.
I LOVE ALL OF YOU.
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD
WILL ALWAYS BE MY HOME.
- I NEVER DOUBTED YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF US NOW.
AND YOU ALWAYS WILL BE.
WE LOVE YOU
JUST LIKE FAMILY.
FAIRY TAIL'S LUCKY TO HAVE SUCH
AN AMAZING WIZARD IN ITS RANKS.
- DO YOU MEAN IT?
THAT MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
- JUVIA!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
SHE CHOSE TO SACRIFICE
HER OWN LIFE
IN ORDER TO SAVE HER FRIEND?
- LET'S GO!
- AW, MAN.
THERE'S WAY TOO MANY PEOPLE.
I CAN'T PICK UP LAXUS' SCENT
WITH THEM AROUND.
- NOW, GUYS,
I WANT YOU TO LISTEN CLOSELY.
WE CAN'T RISK
THE TWO OF YOU
GETTING CAUGHT UP
IN ONE OF FRIED'S ENCHANTMENTS,
SO YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO SEPARATE.
GOT IT?
- Gajeel: I WANNA SETTLE
THE SCORE WITH SALAMANDER
SO BAD I CAN TASTE IT.
BUT THAT LIGHTNING IDIOT
HAS REALLY BEEN
WORKIN' MY LAST NERVE LATELY,
SO HE'S MY PRIORITY FOR NOW.
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU,
MASTER IVAN?
- Ivan: OF COURSE, MY BOY.
EARNING THE TRUST OF MAKAROV
AND THE OTHERS IS PARAMOUNT.
WE MUST NOT LET SUSPICION
CREEP INTO THEIR MINDS.
REMEMBER TO ALWAYS ACT
AS THOUGH
YOUR HEART AND SOUL
BELONG TO FAIRY TAIL.
- Gajeel: AS FAR AS THEY KNOW,
I'M A TEAM PLAYER.
- WE HAVE AMPLE TIME
BEFORE THE HAMMER DROPS
ON THAT SORRY EXCUSE
FOR A GUILD.
- YES, SIR.
- OH, COME ON, MIRA.
I'M STILL A MAN.
I CAN WALK ON MY OWN,
YOU KNOW.
- IT'S OKAY, IF MY BABY BROTHER
NEEDS A HAND,
I DON'T MIND HELPING AT ALL.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU SEEM TO BE FORGETTING
A BASIC RULE OF COMBAT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- EVEN THE MOST POWERFUL SPELLS
ARE ULTIMATELY WORTHLESS
IF THEY FAIL
TO HIT YOUR TARGET.
- CARD MAGIC!
HEAVEN!  REVERSE DEATH!
MOUNTAIN!
SUMMONED LIGHTNING!
- DARK ECRITURE REPEL!
- AHHHH!
- Elfman: WHAT IN THE--
- OH NO, CANA!
- YOU'RE TOUGH.
A TRUE TESTAMENT TO YOUR MANY
YEARS OF SERVICE TO THE GUILD.
- LISTEN TO ME, FRIED.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE BACK ALL THAT
GARBAGE YOU SAID ABOUT JUVIA.
AHHH!
- CANA!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT DID HE DO TO HER?
- ( Cana moaning )
- THIS HAS GONE TOO FAR!
- HOW DARE YOU?
- I'M SORRY, ELFMAN, BUT YOU'VE
ALREADY LOST TO EVERGREEN.
THEREFORE, YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO REJOIN THE GAME.
- OH, YEAH?
- WE'RE IN THE SAME GUILD!
WE SHOULDN'T BE FIGHTING
EACH OTHER.
- WE WERE ONCE.
HOWEVER, THE ULTIMATE PURPOSE
OF THIS GAME
IS TO RESTRUCTURE THE GUILD,
TO BREAK OUR MEANINGLESS BONDS.
LAXUS' ENEMY
IS MINE AS WELL.
- I'M READY
TO TAKE ON BOTH OF YA!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- THOSE WHO HAVE BEEN DEFEATED
ARE STRICTLY PROHIBITED
FROM RE-JOINING THE GAME.
ANYONE WHO DARES ATTEMPT
TO DO SO
WILL RECEIVE A PUNISHMENT
FAR WORSE THAN DEATH.
DARK ECRITURE PAIN!
THOSE RUNES REPRESENT
UNIMAGINABLE PAIN
WHICH WILL BECOME
THE TOTALITY OF YOUR EXISTENCE.
- OH! AHHHH!
- ELFMAN!
YOU HAVE TO STOP THIS!
HE'S NOT AS STRONG
AS HE USED TO BE, FRIED!
- DARK ECRITURE TERROR!
SUFFERING!
- AHHHH!
- ( crying )
I'M BEGGING YOU.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
PLEASE, JUST SPARE HIM!
- ( screaming )
- NO!
- THE FINAL DARK ECRITURE.
DEATH.
- DEATH?
- ( growling )
- DON'T BE AFRAID,
BIG BROTHER.
WE STILL LOVE YOU.
- LISANNA!
- Lisanna: I FEEL SO STRANGE.
IT'S LIKE I--
I CAN'T MOVE.
- DON'T WASTE YOUR STRENGTH.
- WHERE'D YOU GO?
MIRA?
- I'M RIGHT HERE.
- MIRA-- I--
I JUST...
WANT YOU TO KNOW--
- LISANNA?
LISANNA?
LISANNA!
- WHAT'S THIS?
SO MUCH POWER.
HOW IS SHE--
- ( wailing )
( wailing continues )
- DARK ECRITURE WINGS!
- DIE.
- THIS IS HER TAKE OVER POWER.
THE SHE-DEVIL:
SATAN SOUL.
- DARKNESS STREAM!
DARK ECRI--
I KNOW A FEW FORBIDDEN SPELLS
OF MY OWN.
EVIL BATTLES EVIL!
DARK ECRITURE!
DARKNESS!
( growling )
- EVIL SPARK!
- IT'S TRUE.
HER POWER'S UNCANNY.
I'D HEARD TALES
OF HER ABILITIES,
BUT I NEVER WOULD'VE THOUGHT
MIRAJANE WAS CAPABLE OF THIS.
YOU'RE STRONG,
BUT I CAN'T AFFORD
TO LOSE THE GAME TO YOU.
AHHH!
DARKNESS BREATH!
DARKNESS FLASH BOMB!
IS SHE FINISHED?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
SHE'S CONTROLLING THE WATER.
JUST HOW POWERFUL IS SHE?
- EVIL EXPLOSION!
SOUL EXTINCTION.
- ( screaming )
- FRIED!  DIE!
- THERE'S NO WAY.
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST SUCH A FORCE.
- Lisanna: WE STILL LOVE YOU.
- ( panting )
- Fried: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID YOU STOP?
- BECAUSE THIS BATTLE
IS MEANINGLESS.
- YOU CAN SPARE ME
YOUR FALSE PITY, MIRA.
JUST FINISH ME OFF.
- I WON'T DO THAT
BECAUSE WE'RE ALLIES.
WE'RE BOTH MEMBERS
OF FAIRY TAIL.
THAT MEANS WE WORK TOGETHER,
WE CELEBRATE TOGETHER,
AND WE GROW TOGETHER.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
LAXUS IS MY ONLY TRUE ALLY!
- IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE THAT WAY.
LISTEN, WE'VE BEEN YOUR FRIENDS
SINCE THE VERY BEGINNING.
IT'S PERFECTLY FINE
TO HAVE THAT ONE PERSON
WHO YOU TRUST
MORE THAN ANYBODY ELSE.
IT'S HUMAN NATURE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE
TO SHUT OUT THE REST OF US.
WE'RE ALL PART OF SOMETHING
BIGGER. WE'RE LIKE FAMILY.
IF YOU'LL JUST REACH OUT,
I PROMISE THERE'LL ALWAYS
BE SOMEONE THERE FOR YOU.
ONCE YOU'RE FINALLY ABLE
TO SEE THAT CONNECTION,
YOU'LL NEVER FORGET
THAT IT'S THERE.
YOU'RE SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE
WHO CARE FOR YOU.
- I NEVER WANTED IT
TO COME TO THIS.
- YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
HOW ABOUT NEXT YEAR,
WE ENJOY
THE HARVEST FESTIVAL TOGETHER?
- MY SIS.
- SHE'S AMAZING, HUH?
"FRIED VERSUS MIRAJANE.
BOTH WIZARDS FORFEIT."
- THIS GAME
JUST GOT INTERESTING.
- NOW, THERE'S JUST ONE.
I'M COMIN' FOR YA, LAXUS!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japenese )
- SO IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO FIGHT LAXUS, HUH?
- YEAH.
AND I'M ALL FIRED UP!
- UM, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
SIT THIS ONE OUT.
I MEAN, ISN'T IT
USUALLY SUPPOSED TO BE
UP TO THE MAIN CHARACTER
TO BEAT THE FINAL BOSS?
- WHAT DO YA MEAN? IF I'M NOT
THE MAIN CHARACTER, THEN WHO IS?
YOU?
- I AM A NATURAL.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- HEY, MAN,
THIS IS MY SHOW TOO!
YOU CAN'T JUST GO DECIDIN'
YOU'RE THE MAIN CHARACTER.
- Happy: I'M SORRY BUT THE FANS
HAVE SPOKEN
AND EVIDENTLY I HAVE
MORE OF THEM THAN YOU DO.