- LILY, LONG AGO,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
I'M GLAD THAT I COULD RETURN
THE FAVOR TODAY.
- YES, AND I COULDN'T
BEGIN TO THANK YOU,
MY PRINCE.
- ( gasps, screaming )
- NO, NOT MY CAT.
LILY!
- ( theme music plays )
- ( man sings in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP
WITH A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- PRINCE.
- LILY!
- ( gasping )
- YOU PATHETIC TRAITOR.
YOU'RE NOT A NOBLE EXCEED.
YOU'RE JUST A LOUSY FALLEN.
TO THINK YOU WOULD FORGET
YOUR DEBT TO OUR KING
AND DARE BETRAY HIS ORDERS.
- IT'S THE EDOLAS ERZA.
THE ONE CALLED "KNIGHTWALKER."
- LILY!
- HEARTLESS BROAD,
YOU'RE GONNA PAY.
- NO, WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING TO HELP LILY.
- IT'S TOO DANGEROUS, CHAGOT.
- DON'T WORRY, YOUR HIGHNESS.
I'LL GO DOWN THERE
AND TAKE CARE OF HIM FOR YOU.
- SCARLET.
IT'S KNIGHTWALKER.
- Mystogan: LET ME HANDLE THIS.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR
INSOLENCE, CAPTAIN KNIGHTWALKER.
HOW DARE YOU POINT YOUR SWORD
AT ME,
THE ROYAL PRINCE OF EDOLAS.
- THE PRINCE?
- ( laughing )
YOU, THE ROYAL PRINCE
OF EDOLAS?
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
YOU DON'T DESERVE THE TITLE
BECAUSE I NEVER THOUGHT
OF YOU AS MY SON.
- THAT'S THE KING'S VOICE.
- YEAH, WHERE THE HECK IS HE?
- YOU HAVE SOME NERVE.  YOU
CAN'T RUN OFF FOR SEVEN YEARS
AND THEN SUDDENLY WALTZ BACK IN
AS THOUGH NOTHING HAPPENED.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FOOL ME?
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
IN EARTH LAND
SEALING ALL OF THE ANIMAS.
YOU'RE A TRAITOR.
AND AS SUCH, YOU MUST BE
PUNISHED FOR YOUR ACTIONS.
- WHERE'S THAT VOICE
COMING FROM?
I HAVE NO IDEA BUT HE CERTAINLY
SOUNDS ANGRY, DOESN'T HE?
- COME ON.
SHOW YOURSELF, BUCKO.
- COME OUT AND FACE US.
- YOUR ANIMA PLAN HAS FAILED.
PLEASE SURRENDER PEACEFULLY.
YOU'VE NO REASON
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
- RIDICULOUS.
WHO SAYS I NEED A REASON
TO FIGHT?
- DO YOU GUYS HEAR THAT?
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S COMING
FROM UNDERGROUND.
- FEEL THE MAGIC POWER
BUILDING UP IN THE AIR?
- THIS IS NOT A SIMPLE FIGHT.
NO, THIS IS RETRIBUTION.
THE EXTERMINATION OF ALL WHO
WOULD DARE TO OPPOSE THEIR KING.
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- SOME KIND OF MAGIC WEAPON?
- SINCE YOU AND YOUR MEDDLESOME
FRIENDS INSIST
ON STANDING IN MY WAY,
I'VE NO CHOICE BUT TO OBLITERATE
EACH ONE OF YOU,
REGARDLESS OF WHO YOU ARE.
- FATHER, PLEASE.
- I'M NOT YOUR FATHER.
I AM THE KING OF EDOLAS.
IF I DISPOSE OF YOU HERE
AND NOW,
I'LL NO LONGER WORRY ABOUT YOU
SEALING MY ANIMAS IN EARTH LAND.
I'LL BE FREE TO CREATE ANOTHER
GIANT LACRIMA
AND FUSE IT
WITH THE EXCEEDS.
LIMITLESS MAGIC POWER
WILL BE MINE!
- OH, NO.
- ( laughing )
TRY AS YOU MIGHT,
THERE IS NO STOPPING ME.
I AM THE KING.
MY POWER IS ABSOLUTE.
- ALL OF THAT MAGIC
CAN YOU FEEL IT?
- I CAN AND I RECOGNIZE
THAT FORM.
- NO, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
- IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?
- DORMA ANIM.
- THE DORMA ANIM.
FROM OUR OLD LANGUAGE,
IT MEANS DRAGON KNIGHT.
IT'S ENHANCED DRAGON ARMOR.
- Natsu: A DRAGON?
- CERTAINLY LOOKS LIKE ONE.
DON'T YOU GUYS THINK SO?
- IS IT MAGIC ARMOR?
- IT'S UNLIKE ANY
I'VE EVER SEEN BEFORE.
- Coco: IT'S AN ENHANCED ARMOR
MADE FROM AN ANTI-MAGIC LACRIMA
CALLED "WIZARD CANCELLER."
IT'S BAD NEWS FOR US,
BECAUSE OUR ATTACKS
WON'T HAVE ANY EFFECT ON IT.
THE KING MUST BE INSIDE OF IT.
HE'S CONTROLLING
THE DORMA ANIM'S EVERY MOVE.
- AS YOUR KING, I ORDER YOU
TO CAPTURE THE EXCEEDS AT ONCE.
- All: YES, SIR!
- HURRY.
FLY FOR YOUR LIVES.
- ( screaming )
- THEY'RE GETTING AWAY.
- MAGICALIZING CANNON.
CHARGED AND READY.
- FIRE!
- FLY AWAY.  HURRY.
- WE MUST FLEE, MY QUEEN
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS HERE.
EVERYONE, TRY TO STAY STRONG.
- AFTER THEM.
- YES, CAPTAIN.
- DO YOUR BEST TO PROTECT
THE EXCEEDS FROM THE ROYAL ARMY.
I'M GOING TO TRY
TO TAKE DOWN KNIGHTWALKER.
- YOU GOT IT.
WELL, LOOK AT YOU.
GOOD JOB.  I THOUGHT RIDING THIS
LEGION WOULD MAKE YOU NAUSEOUS.
DID WENDY CAST A SPELL TO HELP
YOU WITH YOUR MOTION SICKNESS?
- OH!  JEEZ!  WHY WOULD I BE
NAUSEOUS WHEN I'M NOT EVEN
RIDING ON A VEHICLE?  THIS GUY'S
LENDING US A HAND AS OUR ALLY.
MAN, YOU'RE CRUEL.
- I'M SORRY.  THAT'S MY MISTAKE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA BARF,
BUT IT'S JUST YOUR UGLY FACE.
- WE'VE GOTTA STOP THAT MONSTER.
HELP ME OUT, LOSERS.
- HEY,
WHO YOU CALLING A LOSER?
- I WOULDN'T GO NEAR THAT THING
IF I WERE YOU.
YOUR MAGIC IS USELESS
AGAINST IT.
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
DODGE ITS ATTACKS.
WE MUST DO WHAT WE CAN
TO PROTECT THE EXCEEDS.
THEY'RE COMPLETELY
DEFENSELESS RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT, HERE GOES.
- THINK YOU CAN DODGE ME?
WE'LL SEE.
( laughs )
I WILL OBLITERATE ANYONE
WHO GETS IN MY WAY.
I WON'T LET A SINGLE HUMAN
ESCAPE MY WRATH.
BE GONE!
- OH!
- MYSTOGAN.
- MYSTOGAN.  DON'T TELL ME
THAT'S THE NAME YOU CHOSE
TO BE CALLED IN EARTH LAND?
YOUR NAME'S JELLAL.
- ERZA, GET OUT OF HERE
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- FORGET ABOUT ME.
- WILL HE BE OKAY?
- YEAH, HE'S GOT THIS.
THREE-LAYER MAGIC CIRCLE
MIRROR WATER!
- WHAT?
HE REFLECTED MY ATTACK.
- THINK THAT GOT HIM?
- OH, WOW.
MYSTOGAN'S SO POWERFUL.
- ( laughs )
GOODNESS.  THAT TICKLED.
- WHOA.
IT'S NOT EVEN SCRATCHED.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
- BEHOLD.
THIS IS THE POWER
OF THE GREAT WIZARD CANCELLER.
YOU CAN ATTACK WITH ALL YOUR
MIGHT BUT IT WILL NOT STOP ME.
THE DORMA ANIM IS IMPERVIOUS
TO ALL FORMS OF MAGIC.
- ( gasping )
- ( screams )
- MYSTOGAN.
- THE MIGHTY PRINCE HAS FALLEN.
I'M SURE HE'LL FEEL RIGHT
AT HOME CRAWLING ALONG
THE GROUND WITH THE OTHER PESTS.
- ALL RIGHT, ICE MAKE LANCE.
- MAN, TALK ABOUT A ROUGH RIDE.
- IT'D MAKE ANYBODY SICK,
NOT JUST NATSU.
- ( screaming )
- FLY FASTER!
- OH, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT.
- I'M GOING TO TURN EVERY LAST
EXCEED INTO A SPARKLING LACRIMA.
- LEAVE IT TO THE HUMANS.
- ( crying )
- ONLY THEY WOULD COME UP WITH
SUCH A HORRIBLE CONTRAPTION.
- THE ONE WHO TURNS
THE HEAVENS BLACK
AND BRINGS WITH IT DESTRUCTION.
- THE STUFF OF NIGHTMARES.
DORMA ANIM
OR THE "DRAGON KNIGHT. "
- LEGEND HAS IT THAT LONG AGO
IT WAS USED TO ATTACK EXTALIA
AND IT NEARLY DESTROYED ALL
OF EDOLAS IN THE PROCESS.
- THE HUMANS WERE HORRIFIED
THEY CHOSE TO BAN ITS USE
AND SEAL IT AWAY FOREVER.
AND YET, HERE IT IS AGAIN.
- HOW WAS IT "NEARLY DESTROYED"?
YOU CARE TO ELABORATE?
- I'M AFRAID WE DON'T
KNOW THE DETAILS.
- BUT THE LEGEND SAYS THE MOMENT
THIS WORLD LOST MOST
OF ITS MAGIC POWER WAS
WHEN DORMA ANIM
FIRST TURNED
THE SKY BLACK.
- ( laughing )
- Gray: THIS SUCKS!  HOW ARE WE
TO FIGHT DODGING THIS THING?
- Coco: HANG IN THERE, LEGGIE.
- WE'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
- LET'S USE LUCY AS A DECOY
TO DISTRACT THE DRAGON THINGY.
- SHUT YOUR FACE, FISH BREATH.
- JUST SAYING.
- NOW, NOW.
WE HAVE TO STAY FOCUSED YOU TWO.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
WHO'S ATTACKING?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE DORMA ANIM SHOULDN'T BE
AFFECTED BY THEIR MAGIC ATTACKS.
- SKY DRAGON ROAR!
- UGH!
YOU LITTLE BRAT!
- PRETTY IMPRESSIVE JOB, KIDDO.
- THANK YOU.
THE TWO OF YOU CAN CAUSE
A LOT MORE DAMAGE THAN I CAN.
- GEEZER, YOU'RE GONNA
REGRET HURTING MY CAT.
- IT WAS YOU.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
- NATSU!
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- YOU CAN DO IT.
- WE'RE GOOD.
JUST KEEP THE CATS SAFE.
- IN THAT CASE,
I'LL LEAVE IT TO YOU.
- Lucy: YOU SURE THEY'RE GONNA
BE ABLE TO HANDLE THAT MONSTER
ALL BY THEMSELVES?
- Gray: DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
OF COURSE THEY CAN.
WHO BETTER TO FIGHT A DRAGON
THAN THOSE WHO WERE TRAINED
TO DEFEAT THEM?
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO STAND A CHANCE.
THE DRAGON SLAYERS.
- Girl: LOOK UP THERE.
THEY'RE LACRIMAS.
HAS EVERYONE BEEN TRANSFORMED?
- WHEN THE DRAGON CHAIN
WAS SEVERED,
THE KINGDOM LOST TEN YEARS'
WORTH OF MAGIC POWER.
EVEN IF THEY WERE TO MAGICALIZE
ALL OF THE EXCEEDS,
THEY WOULD NEVER BE ABLE
TO RECOVER THAT MUCH.
THEY'VE RESORTED
TO USING THE DORMA ANIM.
IF THEY'LL GO TO THAT EXTREME,
THEN WHO KNOWS
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN NEXT?
- TRY NOT TO MOVE TOO
MUCH 'CAUSE IT'LL HURT.
- LILY,
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE ALIVE.
- PRINCE.
- Man: GIMME A BREAK.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
THREE SCRAWNY HUMANS ARE
TAKING ON THAT BEAST?
- THEY MUST BE CRAZY.
- MAYBE THEY'RE SUPER STRONG.
- NOW COME ALONG, CHAGOT.
- WE NEED TO GET YOU AS FAR AWAY
AS POSSIBLE, DEAR.
- IF YOU STAY YOU'RE BOUND
TO GET CAUGHT UP IN THE BATTLE.
- LET'S DO THIS, SALAMANDER.
- GREAT.
I HAVE TO TEAM UP
WITH YOU AGAIN.
- QUIT YOUR WHINING, WILL YOU?
- WE CAN SETTLE OUR SCORE
AFTER WE'RE DONE
KNOCKING THIS OLD GUY'S
TEETH IN.
- I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW.
- I WOULD LOVE TO SEE YOU TRY.
- I'LL LEND A HAND.
SWIFT WINGS
THAT SPEED THROUGH THE HEAVENS.
- WHAT THE--
- THAT IS CRAZY.
MY BODY FEELS SO MUCH LIGHTER.
- VERNIER!
- HOW DID THEY DODGE MY ATTACK?
- WHOA!  WE'RE REALLY FLYING.
- I CAN'T LOCK MY TARGETS
ON THEM.
- FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST.
- IRON DRAGON CLUB.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
THEIR ATTACKS SHOULDN'T
AFFECT ME.
WHY IS THE DORMA ANIM
TAKING DAMAGE?
- COME ON.
IT SHOULD'VE FALLEN BY NOW.
- THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH.
- LET ME HELP.
I CALL UPON THEE,
THE STALWART MIGHT
TO CLEAVE THE HEAVENS.
- OH!
- WHAT'S SHE DOING NOW?
- ARMS!
- THAT'S AWESOME.
I FEEL WAY STRONGER.
- 'CAUSE IT'S AN ATTACK
ENHANCEMENT SPELL.
- YOU READY
TO CRUSH THIS OLD GUY?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW IT.
- NONSENSE.
WHY IS THEIR MAGIC POWER
INCREASING ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- FIRE DRAGON BRILLIANT FLAME.
- IRON DRAGON SPEAR, DEMON LOG.
- IT'S HER.
YOU'RE DONE FOR, BRAT.
LAUNCH DRAGON RIDER MISSILES.
- OH, NO,
LOOK OUT, WENDY!
- DON'T WORRY.
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
VERNIER!
- THEY'RE TRACKING HER?
- ( wincing )
- ( screaming )
- YOU SAVED ME.
- I WON'T LET HIM HURT YOU.
- TRY AND STOP ME.
- YOU AIN'T SHOOTING NO ONE,
YOU HEAR ME, OLD MAN?
- ( growls )
YOU'RE GRATING ON MY NERVES!
- THERE'S STILL
TWO MISSILES LEFT.
- HOW CAN THAT BE?
NO, WAIT, NATSU.
THOSE ARE DIFFERENT
THAN THE OTHERS.
- ( screaming )
- ( laughing )
IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU LOWLY
WIZARDS LEARNED YOUR PLACE.
YOU COULDN'T SLAY A DRAGON
IF IT LAID DOWN BEFORE YOU.
HUH?  IMPOSSIBLE.
HE'S EATING THE FLAMES
FROM THE DRAGON RIDER MISSILES?
IS HE INSANE?
WHY IS HE EATING
THE DORMA ANIM'S TAIL?
- MAN, THAT WAS SOME SERIOUSLY
NASTY TASTING FIRE.
DON'T THINK I'VE EVER TASTED
A FLAME THAT GROSS BEFORE.
- ( spits )
THE IRON, TOO.
BAD STUFF, BUT EVEN SO...
- I'M STARTING TO FEEL LIKE
I GOT A REAL FIRE IN MY BELLY.
- ARE YOU TRYING
TO COPY ME, METALHEAD?
- IT WAS JUST A COINCIDENCE,
NUMB NUTS.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
ARE ALL EARTH LAND WIZARDS
THIS POWERFUL?
- MAN, THIS THING'S HARDCORE.
NO WONDER THEY CALL IT A DRAGON.
- THAT AIN'T A DRAGON.
IT'S JUST A DUMB, OLD MAN HIDING
INSIDE A BIG HUNK OF JUNK.
- HE'S OUT HERE ALONE WITHOUT
ANY GUARDS TO PROTECT HIM.
SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS TAKE
THAT THING DOWN.
- I'M FIRED UP NOW.
- SO THESE ARE
THE DRAGON SLAYERS.
( panting ) SUCH POWER.
I WILL NOT REST UNTIL
I HAVE IT FOR MYSELF.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- THIS IS BAD, YOU GUYS.
IT'S GAINING POWER,
PULLING IT FROM THE AIR.
AND IT'S FLOWING
INTO THE ARMOR.
- ( laughs )
IF I CAPTURE THE DRAGON SLAYERS,
I'LL BE ABLE TO START
MY ANIMA PLAN OVER AGAIN.
THEY'RE THE KEY TO EVERLASTING
MAGIC POWER FOR EDOLAS.
WAIT.
WHAT AM I THINKING?
THEY'RE WEAPONS.
I SHOULD SECURE THEM FOR MYSELF.
IF THEY HAPPEN TO GET DAMAGED
IN THE PROCESS, SO BE IT.
I SHALL ROB YOU
OF THE WILL TO FIGHT.
YOU'LL BE BEGGING ME
FOR MERCY.
WITNESS THE POWER
OF DORMA ANIM.  BLACK HEAVEN!
I GOT YOU NOW.
- ( screaming )
- YOU'LL HAVE TO
DO BETTER THAN THAT.
- NO, NATSU.
- HE HIT THE THING WITH ARMS
ATTACK AND IT DIDN'T FLINCH.
- ( laughs )
CAN YOU FEEL IT,
THIS ABSOLUTE MAGIC POWER?
IT'S SPECTACULAR.
DON'T BOTHER FALLING TO YOUR
KNEES, BEGGING FOR YOUR LIVES.
STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE,
SO I CAN WATCH YOU TREMBLE
IN FEAR.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
I'M THE ONE DRAGON
YOU CANNOT SLAY.
- ( screaming )
- FORGIVE ME, NATSU.
- YOUR HIGHNESS,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I SAW WHAT HAPPENED.
WHY DID YOU LET HIM HIT YOU?
DON'T TELL ME THAT YOU DID
IT TO SAVE ME.
- I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- I'M FINE.
IT'S BARELY A SCRATCH.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE IN A LOT OF PAIN
RIGHT NOW AND YOU KNOW IT.
- WE'VE NO CHOICE BUT TO LEAVE
THE DORMA ANIM TO NATSU
AND THE OTHERS.  WE HAVE
ANOTHER MATTER TO ATTEND TO.
- WHAT MIGHT THAT BE?
- I HAVE ONE FINAL TASK,
AND I KNOW I WON'T BE ABLE
TO DO IT WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
- THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- I CAN HEAR THEIR SCREAMING.
- THE ROYAL ARMY,
THEY'VE ALMOST CAUGHT UP.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THERE'S SO MANY OF 'EM.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- ONLY ONE THING WE CAN DO.
STOP THEM BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
THE EXCEEDS ARE COUNTING ON US.
- I WANNA HELP YOU FIGHT, ERZA.
- ME, TOO.
WE HAVE TO DO WHATEVER WE
CAN TO PROTECT OUR HOMELAND.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU,
SCARLET.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
- ( laughs )
- OH, NO.  IT'S A TRAP.
- WE'VE BEEN AMBUSHED.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE, LEGGIE.
- ( screaming )
- LEGGIE, NO!
- HAPPY.
- AYE, SIR.
- THOSE WHO DARE TO THREATEN OUR
KING CANNOT BE ALLOWED TO LIVE.
WE MUST MAKE SURE NONE
OF THEM ESCAPE.
HEAD TO THE SURFACE.
- YES, CAPTAIN!
- PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT TO STOP
FLAILING, CHILD,
UNLESS YOU WANT ME TO DROP YOU.
- WE HAVE TO RESCUE LEGGIE.
- THANKS A LOT, CARLA.
HEY, YOU HEARD HER.
NOW QUIT SQUIRMING OR ELSE.
- AW, MAN.
YOU'RE SO HEAVY.
- YOU'RE SO DEAD
IF YOU DROP ME, CAT.
- HOLD ON.
DID WE FORGET SOMEONE?
- YEAH, WHERE'S ERZA?
- TRYING TO SNEAK UP ON ME?
- I'M READY TO FINISH
THIS ONCE AND FOR ALL
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU.
- GET TO THE SURFACE, MEN.
I CAN HANDLE THIS ONE MYSELF.
- YES, CAPTAIN!
- RUINS OF THE WRETCHED
CATS' ANCIENT CITIES.
THIS SEEMS LIKE THE PERFECT
PLACE FOR YOUR GRAVE.
- WISHFUL THINKING.
I WILL NOT DIE BY YOUR HAND.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE WITH MY FACE
COULD EVER CAUSE FAIRY TAIL
SO MUCH PAIN.
- WELL, I CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE WITH MY FACE
WOULD BARE THEIR FANGS
AT THE KING.
- COME GET ME.
- I WOULD BE MORE THAN HAPPY TO.
- Both:
I WILL NEVER STOP FIGHTING,
NOT UNTIL I'VE RID
THIS WORLD OF YOU.
- ( theme music playing )
- Happy:
HEY, NATSU, I'VE BEEN WONDERING.
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF LIFE?
- WHOA, WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
YOU DIDN'T EAT ANY WEIRD
MUSHROOMS, DID YOU?
- NO WAY.  I HATE MUSHROOMS.
ARE YOU GONNA ANSWER ME OR WHAT?
- HOLD ON, LET ME THINK
I'D SAY THE MEANING OF LIFE IS
EATING, SLEEPING AND FIGHTING.
- YOU'RE NEVER GONNA BE A
PHILOSOPHER, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- FINE, WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
- FISH.
CATCHING FISH, COOKING FISH,
EATING FISH.  THEY'RE SO YUMMY.
- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO CRITICIZE ME, PAL.