- HEY GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- DON'T WORRY LITTLE BUDDY,
I'M COMING FOR YOU. HAPPY.
- IF I STAY IN THIS CRAZY
CAT ROOM MUCH LONGER,
I'M GOING TO GO INSANE.
I GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE RIGHT NOW.
- Toy cat: PRETTY KITTY,
PRETTY KITTY, PRETTY KITTY.
- HEY, I KNOW THEY PUT
YOU HERE TO DISTRACT ME,
BUT I DON'T HAVE TIME TO PLAY
WITH YOU RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
- MEOW. MEOW. MEOW.
- WELL, MAYBE JUST
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- Happy: VOICE OF DARKNESS!
- SO WE TOOK A STAND
FOR OUR FREEDOM.
WE HOPED TO SAVE
OUR DEAR FRIEND, JELLAL.
- DON'T GO MESSING
WITH MAD DOG WALLY.
- ALL OF THAT MANUAL LABOR
HAS MADE US STRONGER.
- YOU BRATS.
( moans in pain )
- ( clamoring )
- Budi: THIS KID'S NO FUN.
HE HASN'T MADE A PEEP
THIS WHOLE TIME.
- DROP THE TOUGH-GUY ACT
OR WE'LL GO TO MORE
EXTREME MEASURES
LIKE WE DID WITH
YOUR LITTLE GIRLFRIEND.
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT. YOU AND
YOUR BUDDIES DON'T REALIZE
HOW LUCKY YOU ARE TO BE
BUILDING THE R-SYSTEM, DO YOU?
- IT'S A SPECIAL HONOR AND ONCE
THE TOWER'S BEEN COMPLETED
EVERYONE WHO WORKED
ON IT GOES TO HEAVEN.
- WE'RE GOING TO USE THE
R-SYSTEM TO RESURRECT OUR GOD.
- SHUT UP, YOU FAT PIG.
- WHAT'D YOU JUST CALL ME?
- FORGET HIM.
WE'RE WASTING TIME HERE.
WE HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THE RIOTERS.
- REST UP KID, 'CAUSE WE'RE
GOING TO KEEP ZAPPING YOU
UNTIL YOU START BEGGING
OUR GOD FOR MERCY!
- ( both laugh )
- GOD. I DON'T BELIEVE
THERE IS SUCH A THING.
IF THERE WAS THEN WE WOULDN'T
HAVE TO SUFFER LIKE THIS.
I HATE IT.
- IS THAT SO?
- ALL OF IT. I HATE
THEM AND THEIR GOD.
EVERYTHING ABOUT
THIS LOUSY WORLD.
- EMBRACE YOUR
FEELINGS OF MALICE
AND SHARE THEM WITH ME.
I THRIVE ON DARK EMOTIONS,
THEY MAKE ME STRONGER.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHAT AMUSING CREATURES.
I'M RIGHT HERE
WITHIN THEIR TOWER,
SO VERY CLOSE TO THEM,
YET THEY'VE GONE TO ALL THIS
TROUBLE TO RESURRECT ME.
JUST TO MAKE ME
FLESH AND BONE.
- SHOW YOURSELF.
- THEY MAY HAVE ALL
THE FAITH IN THE WORLD
BUT IT'S YOUR HATRED THAT ALLOWS
YOU TO SENSE MY PRESENCE.
- JELLAL, YOU ARE
A FORTUNATE CHILD
FOR YOU HAVE MET THE
GOD THEY SO REVERE.
( laughs )
MY NAME IS ZEREF
AND HATRED IS MY
VERY EXISTENCE.
- Erza: WE HAVE TO FREE
EVERYONE IN SECTOR 8 TODAY.
COME ON, WE CAN DO IT.
- Simon: NO WE CAN'T.
WE COULD NEVER TAKE DOWN
ALL THOSE GUARDS.
- WE HAVE TO.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY WE'LL
BE ABLE TO SAVE JELLAL.
- I GUESS SHE'S INTO HIM.
SORRY, OLD BUDDY.
- ERZA, UM, DO YOU...
YOU DON'T HAVE A CRUSH
ON JELLAL, DO YOU?
- WHAT? WHY WOULD YOU ASK ME
SOMETHING LIKE THAT RIGHT NOW?
WE NEED TO FOCUS.
- SORRY. BUT I JUST WANTED
TO MAKE SURE BECAUSE...
- WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
- LOOK, UP THERE.
- MAGIC SOLDIERS.
- SIMON.
- HE'S HURT. WHAT WILL WE DO?
- ( growls )
- ( people screaming )
- NO, YOU CAN'T GIVE UP
LIKE THIS.
WE HAVE TO FIGHT
TO BE FREE.
- OUT OF THE WAY.
- PLEASE COME BACK.
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
WE HAVE TO SAVE JELLAL.
- WATCH OUT.
- ERZA.
- GRANDPA ROB.
- MY MAGIC MAY NOT BE
AS STRONG AS IT ONCE WAS
BUT IT'S STILL ENOUGH
TO PROTECT MY FRIENDS.
I WILL NOT LET YOU TAKE
THE LIFE OF AN INNOCENT.
- WHOA, DID YOU SEE THAT?
- YEAH.
- HE REFLECTED THEIR MAGIC BACK.
- ( Grandpa Rob groaning )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YES. I MAY BE
A DECREPIT, OLD MAN,
BUT DEEP DOWN I'VE STILL
GOT SOME FIGHT LEFT IN ME.
AS A WIZARD, MY MAGIC
HAS ALWAYS BEEN INTERTWINED
WITH THE VERY
ESSENCE OF MY LIFE.
BUT I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW MUCH SO UNTIL
I LOST IT AND SOON FOUND
MYSELF IN THIS SORRY STATE.
DON'T END UP LIKE ME, ERZA.
YOU HAVE SO MUCH POTENTIAL,
DON'T LET IT GO TO WASTE.
- GRANDPA.
- YOU'LL FIND IT DEEP
WITHIN YOUR HEART.
- IN MY HEART?
- YES MA'AM. THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN BELIEVE IN SOMETHING
IS IF YOU FEEL IT IN YOUR HEART.
THINK ABOUT THIS,
MAGIC IN IT'S TRUEST FORM
IS VERY SIMILAR
TO RELIGIOUS FAITH,
FORTUNE-TELLING, HEALING
AND EVEN PRAYER.
YOU SEE, ALL OF THESE THINGS
WORK MIRACLES THAT CAN ONLY
BE EXPERIENCED BY BELIEVERS.
- SO, I JUST HAVE TO BELIEVE?
- THAT'S RIGHT. AS LONG
AS YOU BELIEVE IN IT'S POWER,
HAVE FAITH IN YOURSELF
AND STRIVE TO LIVE IN
HARMONY WITH NATURE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO USE MAGIC.
THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
TO BECOME A WIZARD.
DOESN'T SEEM SO HARD,
NOW DOES IT?
- I WANT TO USE MAGIC.
IT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
GRANDPA, IF I BECOME A WIZARD,
DOES THAT MEAN I'LL BE ABLE TO
FLY THROUGH THE SKY ON A BROOM?
- I CAN'T GUARANTEE THAT,
BUT YOU WILL GAIN MAGICAL
POWERS OF SOME SORT.
- I PROMISE I'LL GIVE YOU
A RIDE ON MY BROOM SOMEDAY.
- YOUR BEAUTIFUL SMILE IS THE
ONLY THING THAT'S KEPT ME GOING
WHILE I'VE BEEN STUCK
IN THIS WRETCHED PLACE.
- YOU'RE HURT, AREN'T YOU?
- REMEMBER THIS, YOUR FREEDOM
LIES WITHIN YOUR HEART, CHILD.
- Urtear: THERE'S NO
FREEDOM IN THIS WORLD.
- FOLLOW YOUR HEART AND
YOUR DREAM OF BECOMING
A WIZARD WILL COME TRUE.
- Urtear: I WILL MAKE
YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE.
- GRANDPA, NO.
- Urtear: TRUE FREEDOM
LIES WITH ME.
- ERZA, WE GOT
TO RETREAT. HURRY UP.
- Sho: SISTER, COME ON.
- Millianna: ERZY.
- ( sobs )
( screams )
- ( screams )
- Man: WHOA.
- Man 2: HOW'D SHE DO THAT?
- Man 3: SHE DEFEATED
ALL OF THEM.
- OH, WOW. SHE USED MAGIC.
- YOU KNEW ALL ALONG, GRANDPA.
YOU KNEW I HAD THIS POWER.
NOW THAT I'VE FOUND IT
I CAN USE IT TO SAVE JELLAL.
I'M AFRAID LEARNING HOW
TO FLY A BROOM HAVE TO WAIT.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE.
WE HAVE TO FIGHT
FOR OUR FREEDOM.
FOLLOW ME.
- ( people cheering )
- THEY'RE REVOLTING.
WHAT'RE WE GOING TO DO?
- RUN FOR IT.
- LET'S NOT DO ANYTHING HASTY.
- IT'S NOT OUR FAULT. WE
WERE JUST FOLLOWING ORDERS.
- OUT OF MY WAY.
I'M HERE TO SAVE YOU.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
WE FOUGHT THEM JUST
LIKE YOU SAID WE SHOULD.
EVERYONE WAS SO BRAVE.
SIMON ENDED UP GETTING
HIMSELF HURT PRETTY BAD
AND GRANDPA ROB SAVED MY LIFE,
BUT HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
BUT WE BEAT THEM. WE FOUGHT FOR
OUR FREEDOM AND WE WON.
COME ON, WE GOT TO MEET
WALLY AND THE OTHERS.
THEY FOUND SOME BOATS
SO WE'RE GOING TO LEAVE
THIS PLACE FOR GOOD.
- ERZA.
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO LEAVE THE TOWER.
BECAUSE TRUE FREEDOM
IS RIGHT HERE WITH ME.
- OH, WOW, I FOUND
A MOVIE LACRIMA.
- UH, WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S A LACRIMA WITH
A MOVIE IN IT, SILLY.
- OH, WHAT'S A MOVIE?
- YOU KNOW, MOVING PICTURES.
IT'S SOMETHING PEOPLE WATCH THAT
SHOWS ACTORS ACTING OUT A STORY.
TO BE HONEST, I'VE NEVER
SEEN ONE MYSELF.
- ( screaming )
- IT'S TOO BAD THINGS HAD
TO END THIS WAY, TONY JOE.
BUT FROM THE FIRST
MOMENT YOU MET ME,
YOUR FUTURE WAS SEALED.
- HE'S SO COOL.
- DON'T YOU THINK
HE'S KIND OF EDGY?
- 'CAUSE BEING EDGY IS DANDY.
- Millianna: THAT DOESN'T
EVEN MAKE ANY SENSE.
- SISTER, WHERE ARE YOU?
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
TO GET OUT OF HERE, TOO.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE AT FREEDOM.
- DON'T YOU SEE? THERE'S NO
FREEDOM IN THIS WORLD.
THOSE FOOLS WHO BUILT
THIS TOWER MAY NOT HOLD
YOU PRISONER ANYMORE,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T
EXPERIENCED TRUE FREEDOM.
BECAUSE THAT CAN
ONLY BE FOUND
IN ZEREF'S WORLD.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND WHY THEY MADE
US WORK SO HARD ON THIS TOWER.
THEY BELIEVE THEY CAN USE
IT TO RESURRECT ZEREF.
YOU CLAIM TO BE SUCH
DEVOUT FOLLOWERS
BUT YOU COULDN'T EVEN SENSE
YOUR GOD'S PRESENCE HERE,
COULD YOU?
- THIS TOWER
BELONGS TO ME NOW.
I WILL FINISH
IT'S CONSTRUCTION
AND BRING ZEREF
BACK TO LIFE.
- THAT'S MAGIC.
- SOMEBODY PLEASE HELP,
- STOP IT. YOU'RE HURTING
HIM, JELLAL.
- SO WHAT?
WHY DO YOU CARE?
I THOUGHT YOU HATED THEM.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, I DO,
BUT YOU'RE BEING CRUEL.
- IF YOU WANT TO SENSE
ZEREF'S PRESENCE,
YOU HAVE TO FOCUS
ON YOUR HATRED.
- NO.
- ( laughs )
- YOU KILLED HIM.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- I HAVEN'T CHANGED ONE BIT.
I'M RENAMING THIS PLACE
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
ERZA, YOU AND I WILL STAY
HERE AND FINISH IT TOGETHER.
- WHAT?
- ONCE IT'S COMPLETED,
WE'LL RESURRECT ZEREF.
- WHY WOULD ANYBODY
WANT TO STAY HERE
WHEN WE FINALLY
HAVE A CHANCE TO LEAVE?
- (laughs ) FINE, IF YOU WANT
TO LEAVE SO BADLY
THEN I'M NOT GOING
TO STOP YOU.
BUT YOU'LL HAVE
TO GO ALONE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THERE'S NO WAY I COULD FINISH
THE TOWER'S
CONSTRUCTION BY MYSELF
SO I'M GOING TO KEEP
THE OTHERS HERE WITH ME.
BUT DON'T WORRY, I PROMISE
I WON'T MISTREAT THEM.
I'LL MAKE SURE EVERYONE'S
FED AND CLOTHED
AND THEY GET PLENTY OF REST
BETWEEN THEIR SHIFTS.
I'M SURE ZEREF WOULD
PREFER I BUILD MORE HATRED
BY RULING WITH AN IRON FIST.
BUT WEAK AND UNHAPPY PEOPLE
DON'T MAKE VERY GOOD WORKERS.
- THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO AGREE TO THAT.
EVERYBODY'S ON
THE BOATS READY TO GO.
THEY'RE JUST WAITING
FOR US TO JOIN THEM.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD
CONVINCE THEM TO STAY HERE
AND WORK FOR YOU NOW.
- OH, I DON'T THINK I'LL HAVE
ANY PROBLEM CONVINCING THEM
BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO GIVE THEM A PURPOSE.
ONCE THEY LEARN
OF ZEREF'S POWER,
THEY'LL HAPPILY WORK
TO RESURRECT HIM.
- BUT NONE OF THEM WOULD
WILLINGLY BECOME A SACRIFICE
- IT DOESN'T MATTER. ZEREF TOLD
ME SACRIFICES AREN'T NECESSARY.
HE'S SUCH A BENEVOLENT
GOD, ISN'T HE?
- PLEASE JELLAL, YOU GOT TO TRY
TO COME TO YOUR SENSES.
- I COULD ASK THE SAME OF YOU.
I DON'T NEED YOU ANYMORE,
BUT SINCE YOU TOOK CARE OF
THE FOOLS WHO WERE IN MY WAY,
I'LL LET YOU LIVE.
ENJOY YOUR NEW FOUND FREEDOM.
BUT, I HAVE SOME RULES
FOR YOU BEFORE YOU GO.
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
- I DEMAND YOU NEVER
TELL ANYONE OF THIS PLACE.
IF THE GOVERNMENT FOUND OUT
ABOUT THE TOWER OF HEAVEN,
I'D BE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
IF WORD WERE TO GET OUT,
THEN I'D HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO DESTROY THE TOWER
AND EVERYONE INSIDE IT.
YOU'RE FORBIDDEN FROM
EVER RETURNING HERE AGAIN.
SET ONE FOOT ON THIS LAND
AND I'LL KILL YOUR FRIENDS.
I FIGURE SHO WOULD
HAVE TO BE THE FIRST TO GO.
- NO. YOU WOULDN'T.
- ONE FALSE MOVE
AND YOUR FRIENDS WILL DIE.
I'LL ENJOY TRUE FREEDOM
WHILE YOU SUFFER,
BURDENED BY YOUR GUILT.
( laughs )
- ( sobbing )
NO. NO.
I HAVE TO FIGHT JELLAL.
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I HAVE TO DO IT.
- Siegrain: THE TIME
FOR ACTION IS NOW.
WE MUST USE THE
SATELLITE SQUARE
TO FIRE AN ETHERION BLAST
DIRECTLY AT THE TOWER.
- THE R-SYSTEM IS FORBIDDEN
MAGIC WE CANNOT ALLOW
TO BECOME PART OF
OUR RECORDED HISTORY.
THEREFORE, IT HAS
TO BE DESTROYED.
WHY CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
- ETHERION WOULD OBLITERATE
EVERYTHING IN IT'S PATH,
INCLUDING ANY INNOCENT
CIVILIANS WITHIN THE TOWER.
- NOT TO MENTION, YOUR OWN
BROTHER'S LIFE IS AT STAKE.
IF YOU FIRE THE ETHERION,
HE'S SURE TO DIE.
WOULD YOU BE ABLE
TO LIVE WITH THAT GUILT?
- IF IT'S FOR THE GREATER GOOD.
- ALTHOUGH LIVES OF INNOCENT
CIVILIANS WILL BE LOST,
WE MUST STOP HIM.
IT'S A SACRIFICE THAT
MUST BE MADE NOW.
- HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
CAN YOU IMAGINE
HOW WE'D BE VILIFIED
IF WE ATTACKED KAH ELM
WITHOUT WARNING?
WE'D GO DOWN IN HISTORY
AS MASS MURDERERS.
- I WILL SACRIFICE MY
REPUTATION IN ORDER
TO SAVE COUNTLESS LIVES.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS?
- THINK OF HOW THE R-SYSTEM
WILL AFFECT FUTURE GENERATIONS.
HOW CAN WE TEACH OUR
CHILDREN THE VALUE OF LIFE
IF THE DEAD CAN BE RESURRECTED?
- Belno: WE HAVE TO PUT
AN END TO THIS.
I WOULD LIKE TO VOTE IN
FAVOR OF AN ETHERION ATTACK.
- WE NEED ONE MORE.
- JUST A SINGLE VOTE.
THAT'S ALL IT WILL TAKE
AND THEN IT'S GAME OVER.
( laughs )
- MAN, OH, MAN,
WE PLAYED SO MUCH
THAT I'M COMPLETELY
WORN OUT NOW.
- SO, WHERE THE HECK
ARE WE, ANYWAY?
- I DON'T KNOW
MAYBE IT'S JUST ME
BUT FOR SOME REASON THE
NAME ZEREF SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
- I'M SURE. HE WAS
A LEGENDARY BLACK WIZARD.
- Lucy: WAIT A MINUTE.
I REMEMBER SOMEONE SAYING
THE MONSTER THAT CAME OUT
OF THE LULLABY FLUTE
WAS ONE OF ZEREF'S DEMONS.
- Erza: I NEVER MENTIONED IT,
BUT I SUSPECT DELIORA
WAS A DEMON FROM
THE BOOK OF ZEREF AS WELL.
- IF THIS WIZARD
IS AS EVIL AS YOU SAY,
THEN WHY WOULD JELLAL
WANT TO RESURRECT HIM?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HIS MOTIVES EITHER.
HOWEVER, MY OLD FRIEND
SHO SAID SOMETHING TO ME
ABOUT ZEREF GETTING
THEM TO HEAVEN
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS
THE WORLD WILL BE REBORN
AND THEY'LL BECOME IT'S RULERS.
- OKAY, THERE'S ONE THING THAT
CONFUSES ME ABOUT THESE PEOPLE
WHO CLAIM TO BE
OLD FRIENDS OF YOURS.
WHY'RE THEY ACCUSING
YOU OF BETRAYING THEM?
DON'T THEY REALIZE
JELLAL'S THE BAD GUY HERE?
- IT'S NOT THEIR FAULT.
I'M SURE HE FED THEM
ALL SORTS OF LIES
ABOUT ME ONCE I LEFT.
THAT DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT I ABANDONED THEM
SO LONG AGO.
IN THE END, I GUESS YOU
COULD SAY I DID BETRAY THEM.
- BECAUSE HE THREATENED TO KILL
THEM, IF YOU EVER CAME BACK.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE SAVED THEM...
- NONE OF THAT MATTERS ANYMORE.
IF I CAN DEFEAT JELLAL,
IT'LL ALL BE OVER.
LEAVE IT TO ME, OKAY?
- WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
SHE'S HIDING SOMETHING?
- BUT YOU CAN'T HELP ME NOW, THE
ODDS ARE STACKED AGAINST ME.
WIN OR LOSE THIS BATTLE,
I'M STARING DEATH IN THE FACE.
- WHY WOULD SHE SAY THAT?
WHAT DOES IT EVEN MEAN?
- SISTER, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WHY? WHY ARE YOU LYING TO THEM?
- SHO.
- YOU THINK BY MAKING
YOURSELF THE MARTYR,
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
SYMPATHY FROM YOUR FRIENDS?
TELL THEM THE TRUTH. THAT'S NOT
HOW IT HAPPENED AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU BLEW UP THE BOATS WE WERE
GOING TO USE TO ESCAPE,
AND THEN YOU LEFT ON YOUR OWN.
WE WOULD HAVE ENDED UP
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SEA
IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR
JELLAL. HE SAVED US.
HE WARNED US NOT TO
TRUST WIZARDS LIKE YOU
WHO HAVEN'T LEARNED
TO USE THEIR MAGIC PROPERLY.
HE SAID THAT YOU HAD BECOME
DRUNK WITH MAGICAL POWER
AND YOU DIDN'T WANT
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH YOUR PAST OR THE
PEOPLE YOU LEFT BEHIND.
- DID YOU EVER THINK
HE MIGHT BE LYING?
- IF YOU TRULY KNEW
ERZA THEN YOU'D KNOW
SHE'D NEVER DO
SOMETHING SO HORRIBLE.
- Sho: YOU ONLY THINK
YOU KNOW HER.
YOU WEREN'T THERE BACK THEN, YOU
DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT US.
AFTER YOU LEFT, JELLAL'S WORDS
WERE MY ONLY SALVATION.
AND THAT'S WHY I'VE SPENT
ALL THESE YEARS WORKING
TO FINISH THE TOWER FOR HIM.
I DID IT FOR HIS SAKE.
NOW YOU'RE TRYING TO TELL
ME THAT IT WAS ALL A LIE?
YOU REALLY EXPECT
ME TO BELIEVE
YOU'RE TELLING THE TRUTH
AND JELLAL'S BEEN LYING
TO US THIS WHOLE TIME?
- Simon: THAT'S RIGHT.
- WHY, YOU...
- WAIT. HE DOESN'T POSE
A THREAT, MY DEAR.
HE NEVER MEANT
YOU ANY HARM.
AT THE RESORT, HE KNEW HE
WAS ATTACKING YOUR ICE DECOY.
- Gray: BUT HOW?
- SINCE IT WAS HE WHO CAST
THE DARKNESS SPELL,
IT HAD NO EFFECT ON HIM.
I CAME ALONG IN THE
HOPES OF DISCOVERING
WHY HE'D CHOSEN TO SPARE YOU.
- I'D EXPECT NO LESS FROM A
MEMBER OF PHANTOM'S ELEMENT 4.
- Sho: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- I HAD TO FOOL YOU
AND THE OTHERS
INTO THINKING I'D KILLED HIM
BUT I'D HOPED OUR ATTACK
WOULD LURE THEM HERE.
- SO YOU WERE LYING, TOO?
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT TO ME?
- I'M SORRY.
JELLAL HAD YOU UNDER
HIS SPELL
AND I COULDN'T
CONVINCE YOU OTHERWISE.
SO, I PLAYED ALONG UNTIL
THE TIME WAS RIGHT.
- SO YOU KNEW ALL ALONG.
- I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED
IN YOU, ERZA.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
THAT COULD CHANGE THAT.
I MEAN THOSE WORDS FROM
THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
- SIMON.
- I NEVER KNEW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I BLINDLY
FOLLOWED HIM ALL THESE YEARS.
I DOUBTED YOU.
'CAUSE YOU LEFT ME
ALL ALONE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW MUCH THAT HURT.
( grunts )
( sobbing )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHICH ONE OF
YOU I SHOULD BELIEVE ANYMORE.
- I KNOW IT MUST BE DIFFICULT
TO TAKE ALL OF THIS IN AT ONCE.
BUT SHO, THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
THOUGH IT'S BEEN MANY YEARS,
I HAVE NEVER ONCE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT ANY OF YOU.
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T
STAND UP TO HIM,
BUT I WAS SO WEAK
BACK THEN.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- NOW YOU'RE STRONGER
AND READY TO FACE HIM.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
I'VE WAITED ALL THESE
YEARS FOR THIS VERY MOMENT.
WHEN A GROUP OF POWERFUL
WIZARDS WOULD GATHER HERE.
- SO, WHAT DO
YOU HAVE PLANNED?
- Simon: WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE DOWN JELLAL.
WE CAN DO IT IF
WE WORK TOGETHER.
BUT FIRST, WE MUST
KEEP SALAMANDER
AND WALLY FROM CLASHING.
- GEEZ, WHAT'S UP
WITH THIS ROOM?
THERE'RE CATS
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I LIKE THAT GIANT,
GREEN KITTY HEAD.
OH, WOW, IT'S SOME KIND OF MASK.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO, HAPPY.
AYE, SIR.
I'D MAKE A GOOD CAT.
( laughs )
( grunting )
MAN, IT'S STUCK ON
MY GIANT NOGGIN.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
Ah, WELL, IT LOOKS COOL
SO WHO CARES, RIGHT?
- AIN'T THAT DANDY.
- ( theme song )
- ALL RIGHT, IT LOOKS
LIKE I BEAT YOU AGAIN.
THAT MAKES IT NINE WINS
IN A ROW FOR ME.
- ONE MORE GAME. I'M TOTALLY
GOING TO WIPE THE FLOOR
WITH YOU THIS ROUND.
- GIVE ME A BREAK,
THAT'S WHAT YOU'VE BEEN SAYING
FOR THE LAST EIGHT GAMES.
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING
THE SAME OLD THING.
- THAT MEANS I WIN
BY DEFAULT. WOOHOO.
I JUST KICKED
YOUR FELINE BEHIND.
- Natsu and Happy:
NEXT TIME, HEAVEN'S GAME
- Happy: YOU CAN'T JUST
GO AND CHANGE THE RULES
WHENEVER YOU WANT, YOU CHEATER.
- Natsu: OH, YES I CAN.
- Happy: THAT'S IT.
HE'S COMPLETELY LOST IT.