- HEY, GUYS.  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy:
GRAY, ARE YOU CRYING?
- Happy: WE FOUND OUT
GRAY'S MASTER UR
USED A SPELL THAT
TURNED HER BODY INTO ICE
TO SEAL AWAY
THE DEMON DELIORA.
HE DEFEATED
HIS CHILDHOOD RIVAL LYON
WHO'S DETERMINED
TO RESURRECT THE DEMON.
BUT IS IT TOO LATE?
- Gray: THEY DID IT.
THEY ACTUALLY REVIVED IT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( roars )
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps )
- FINALLY!
THE MOMENT IS HERE.
- WHAT THE HECK
WAS THAT NOISE?
IT SOUNDED LIKE SOME
KIND OF MONSTER GROWLING.
- IT WAS PROBABLY
JUST YOUR STOMACH, LUCY.
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT HALF
AS FUNNY AS YOU THINK YOU ARE.
- SO DO YOU THINK THAT SOUND
MIGHT HAVE BEEN DELIORA?
- OH, NO.  YOU MEAN...
THEY BROUGHT IT
BACK TO LIFE?!
( gasps )
- SEE THAT PURPLE LIGHT?
THAT'S THE MOON DRIP.
- ( Deliora roars )
- IT MUST BE.
- HEY, YOU NEED
TO EAT SOMETHING.
- AND YOU NEED TO SHUT
YOUR TRAP BEFORE I HURT YOU.
- THAT MAY BE
THE DEMON GROWLING,
BUT SOMEONE'S
STILL PERFORMING
THE MOON DRIP CEREMONY UP THERE.
WHICH MEANS THEY HAVEN'T
FULLY REVIVED IT YET.
SO WE STILL HAVE
A CHANCE TO DO SOMETHING.
COME ON.
- DELIORA'S BELOW US.
- PUTTING A STOP
TO THE CEREMONY
IS OUR ONLY HOPE.
WE'VE GOT TO HURRY!
- ( chuckles )
- OH, MAN.
I'M WASTING MY TIME ON YOU.
LET'S FINISH THIS
RIGHT NOW.
( grunts )
- READY WHEN YOU ARE.
GO AHEAD AND DO YOUR WORST,
LITTLE SALAMANDER.
- WHY YOU!
( shouts )
( grunts )
BUT I BROKE IT, RIGHT?
- I HAVE THE ABILITY TO
CONTROL AN OBJECT'S TIME.
MEANING I CAN TAKE
THE CRYSTAL BACK IN TIME
TO BEFORE IT WAS BROKEN.
- WHAT KIND OF MAGIC
GIVES YOU THAT POWER?
- I PRACTICE ONE OF
THE LOST MAGICS
CALLED THE ARC OF TIME.
IT'S EXTREMELY RARE
AND QUITE POWERFUL.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO
SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN I THROW THIS
CRYSTAL BALL INTO THE FUTURE?
- ( shouting )
( grunts )
AAH!
- YOUR FIRE WON'T HELP YOU.
- OH YEAH?
IT STOPPED IN MIDAIR.
- YES.  I ALSO
HAVE THE ABILITY
TO FREEZE
AN OBJECT IN TIME.
- NICE TRICK.
BUT I'D BE MORE IMPRESSED
IF IT WORKED ON PEOPLE.
- AH, THAT'S THE RUB.
IT'S POWERLESS ON LIVING THINGS.
SINCE UR TURNED HERSELF
INTO THE ICE
THAT ENCASES DELIORA,
I CANNOT SIMPLY TURN BACK
THE TIME ON THAT ICE
TO ITS PRE-FROZEN STATE.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE
USING MOON DRIP.
- LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS DOING THIS?
IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE
YOU'RE WORKING HARD
TRYING TO
REVIVE THIS DEMON
JUST SO LYON CAN KILL IT
TO BOOST HIS EGO.
THAT'S GREAT
FOR HIM AND ALL,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA GET OUT OF IT?
- I CAN'T SAY.
I'VE ONLY
RECENTLY JOINED THEM
SO I DON'T KNOW ENOUGH
TO SPEAK ON THE OTHER'S BEHALF.
- OKAY, WHAT ABOUT YOU THEN?
WHAT'S YOUR GOAL
IN ALL OF THIS?
- YOU CERTAINLY KNOW HOW TO
GET STRAIGHT TO THE POINT.
( laughs )
THE COLD EMPEROR LYON
IS AN ARROGANT TWIT.
HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST DELIORA.
THAT'S WHERE I COME IN.
- IF HE CAN'T KILL IT,
WE'RE IN MAJOR TROUBLE.
UNLESS YOU'RE GONNA
DEFEAT IT YOURSELF.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I WANT TO CONTROL THE DEMON.
YOU SEE, THERE ARE SPELLS
THAT GIVE THE CASTER
POWER OVER IMMORTAL MONSTERS
LIKE THIS ONE HERE.
WITH A SINGLE SPELL,
I'D BECOME THE MOST
POWERFUL
MAN IN THE WORLD,
BECAUSE I'D HAVE A DEMON
AT MY BECK AND CALL.
- TALK ABOUT A LAME ANSWER.
I'M SORRY I EVEN ASKED.
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE AFTER?
YOU THINK JUST
HAVING A MONSTER'S
GONNA MAKE YOU TOUGH?
NO WAY.
- ( laughs )
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE TOO YOUNG
TO UNDERSTAND RIGHT NOW,
BUT ONE DAY YOU'LL REALIZE
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
TO HAVE POWER ON YOUR SIDE.
- WELL I'VE ALREADY GOT
PLENTY OF POWER ON MY SIDE.
'CAUSE ALL OF MY FRIENDS
AT FAIRY TAIL HAVE GOT MY BACK.
- IF YOU LET YOUR COCKINESS
GET THE BEST OF YOU,
YOU WILL FALL EXACTLY
LIKE THE CEILING ABOVE YOU!
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH
OF YOU AND YOUR BUDDIES
SCREWING THINGS UP FOR
THE PEOPLE ON THIS ISLAND.
IT'S TIME I PUT
A STOP TO IT!
- YOU DON'T SERIOUSLY BELIEVE
YOU CAN STOP MY ARC OF TIME
WITH YOUR PUNY FLAMES,
DO YOU?
- I DON'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT YOUR STUPID MAGIC.
I JUST WANT YOU
OFF THIS ISLAND!
I MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO CONTROL TIME,
BUT I CAN SEE THE FUTURE.
AND I SEE...
ME KICKING YOUR BUTT
AND SENDING YOU FLYING!
- ( screams )
- OHH!
- AWESOME.  THE MOON DRIP
SHOULD STOP ANY MINUTE NOW.
- YOU MEAN THIS GUY WAS
DOING IT ALL BY HIMSELF?
- TOO LATE!  IT'S OVER.
THE CEREMONY'S
ALREADY BEEN COMPLETED.
- HUH?
- ( roars )
- WHOA.  NO WAY.
- WHAT'S THIS?
SOMETHING TRULY TERRIBLE
HAS HAPPENED.
- WE HAVE TO GET
OFF THE ISLAND, CHIEF.
- I'M STAYING.
YOU AND THE OTHERS CAN GO,
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO
LEAVE THIS PLACE BEHIND.
-  ( roars )
- THANK YOU.
- HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- NATSU?
- THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
WE CAN DO NOW.
WE GOTTA TAKE
THAT THING DOWN.
- ( groans )
NEITHER ONE OF YOU
ARE STRONG ENOUGH.
BUT I AM.
I WILL DEFEAT IT.
- LYON.
- I'M GOING TO
SURPASS UR FINALLY.
( laughs )
- YOU CAN'T FIGHT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN GET UP
OFF THE FLOOR.
- ( roars )
- I'VE WAITED SO LONG
FOR THIS MOMENT.
- YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
THE MOST POWERFUL WIZARD?
WELL, I'D SAY UR'S GOT TO BE
THE STRONGEST AROUND HERE.
SHE'S BEEN HOLED UP
IN THE MOUNTAINS
EVER SINCE SHE LOST HER
DAUGHTER A FEW YEARS BACK.
BUT I SWEAR I'VE NEVER
MET ANOTHER WIZARD
AS SKILLED AS SHE IS.
- WOW.  UR.
DO YOU THINK SHE'LL
TEACH ME MAGIC?
SHE WAS STRONG.
BUT STILL NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO KILL THAT DEMON.
( grunts )
I'M GOING TO DO THE ONE THING
UR NEVER COULD.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH
YOU TOOK THAT PUNK IN,
BUT NOW YOU'RE
TEACHING HIM MAGIC TOO?
- HE TOLD ME
HE WANTED TO LEARN.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
YOU'VE ALREADY GOT ME
TO TAKE THE PLACE
OF YOUR DAUGHTER.
( gasps )
- LYON,
LET'S GET SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
I'VE NEVER ONCE
THOUGHT OF YOU
AS A REPLACEMENT
FOR MY DAUGHTER.
YOU ARE WHO YOU ARE.
YOU'RE MY ADORABLE STUDENT.
- FINALLY.
MY DREAM WILL BE FULFILLED!
- YOU'VE CAUSED
ENOUGH TROUBLE.
I'LL CLEAN UP
THE MESS YOU'VE MADE.
I'LL SEAL THE DEMON MYSELF.
ICED SHELL!
- DON'T DO IT, GRAY!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW LONG IT TOOK ME
TO MELT THAT ICE?
SEALING IT AGAIN
ISN'T GOING TO STOP ME.
I WILL NOT REST UNTIL
I'VE FINALLY DEFEATED DELIORA!
- I CAN'T WORRY
ABOUT THE FUTURE.
I HAVE TO DO THIS
TO KEEP IT FROM
KILLING US ALL RIGHT NOW!
NATSU!
- ( gasps )
- WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME HANDLE THIS?
- DON'T BE STUPID.
JUST GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- IF I DIDN'T
LET YOU DO IT BEFORE,
WHY WOULD I
LET YOU DO IT NOW?
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
GO OUT LIKE THAT.
GO AHEAD AND CAST THE SPELL.
BUT I'M NOT MOVING.
- ( gasps )
NATSU...
- ( roars )
- IT'S SO LOUD!
IT'S GONNA BUST MY EAR!
- ( both scream )
- NATSU!
- I'M NOT GIVING UP
TILL THE BITTER END!
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- ( roars )
WHAT THE--?
I'M STRONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
- WHAT?  NO WAY.
BUT THAT CAN'T BE!
- ( gasps )
- DELIORA...
WAS ALREADY DEAD.
- WHOA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- FOR 10 YEARS...
UR HAS GRADUALLY DEPLETED
THE DEMON'S LIFE FORCE.
AND WHAT WE JUST SAW
WAS NOTHING MORE THAN
ITS LAST DYING BREATHS.
( crying )
MY DREAM IS DEAD.
THERE'S NO HOPE NOW.
I WILL NEVER SURPASS UR.
- MAN.
YOUR TEACHER WAS
PRETTY AWESOME.
- Ur: I'VE FREED YOU
FROM THE DARKNESS, GRAY.
I'VE SEALED IT
AWAY FOREVER.
- ( crying )
YOU'VE SAVED MY LIFE AGAIN.
THANK YOU, UR.
- ( chuckles )
- Lucy:
THE ICE THAT WAS ONCE UR
MELTED AND BECAME WATER
THAT FLOWED INTO
THE OPEN SEA.
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S NOT
PHYSICALLY WITH US,
GRAY SAYS SHE'S
STILL ALIVE.
AND I THINK HE'S RIGHT.
FROM THE SEA,
SHE'LL BE ABLE TO
WATCH OVER HER
BELOVED STUDENTS FOREVER.
I CAN ALMOST
HEAR HER SAYING...
"PLEASE DON'T FIGHT ANYMORE."
- OH YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT.  WE WON!
- AYE, SIR!
- YOU KNOW,
I WAS KINDA WORRIED
FOR A WHILE THERE.
BUT IT ALL WORKED OUT
THANKS TO YOUR AMAZING TEACHER.
- WE TOTALLY FINISHED
AN S-CLASS QUEST
ALL BY OURSELVES!
- ( all laughing )
- YOU THINK MASTER MAKAROV WILL
LET US IN THE SECOND FLOOR NOW?
OH NO!
YOU'RE STILL GONNA
PUNISH US, HUH?
- ISN'T THERE SOMETHING THAT
YOU'RE ALL FORGETTING ABOUT?
YOU CAME TO THIS ISLAND
TO HELP THE VILLAGERS.
THE REQUEST WAS
FOR YOU TO RETURN THEM
TO THEIR ORIGINAL FORMS.
- ( gasps )
- YOU STILL HAVEN'T COMPLETED
YOUR S-CLASS QUEST YET.
- BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE CURSE SHOULD BE LIFTED NOW
'CAUSE DELIORA'S DEAD.
- WRONG.  THIS CURSE
YOU KEEP TALKING ABOUT
NEVER HAD ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE DEMON.
THE VILLAGERS HAVE BEEN
AFFECTED BY THE INTENSE
MAGIC ENERGY RELEASED
FROM THE MOON DRIP SPELL.
IN OTHER WORDS, DELIORA'S DEATH
ISN'T GOING TO CHANGE
THEIR CURRENT SITUATION
WHATSOEVER.
- WHAT-- OH NO.
- WELL, THEN WE'D BETTER
GO AND CHANGE THEM BACK.
- AYE, SIR!
- YEAH, BUT WE
DON'T KNOW HOW.
LYON.  DO YOU KNOW?
- TO BE QUITE HONEST,
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
- YOU DON'T KNOW?
- WHAT?
- BUT THEY TOLD US
THE CURSE STARTED
ABOUT THE SAME TIME
YOU GUYS GOT HERE.
- WHEN WE FIRST ARRIVED
THREE YEARS AGO,
WE WERE AWARE THAT THERE WAS
A VILLAGE SOMEWHERE
ON THIS ISLAND.
BUT WE HAD
ABSOLUTELY NO REASON
TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE VILLAGERS,
SO WE LEFT THEM ALONE.
AND THEY NEVER
CAME TO THE TEMPLE
TO SEE WHAT WE WERE UP TO.
- IN THREE YEARS
YOU'VE NEVER ONCE MET?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE LIGHT FROM THE MOON DRIP
IS SO BRIGHT
YOU CAN SEE IT FROM PRACTICALLY
ANYWHERE ON THE ISLAND.
IT'S KINDA WEIRD THAT
THEY SAW IT EVERY NIGHT
AND NEVER WENT
TO INVESTIGATE.
- THE VILLAGERS WEREN'T
TRANSFORMED BY THE MOON DRIP.
IT DOESN'T AFFECT
THE HUMAN BODY.
- WHAT?
- YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT
SO YOU AND YOUR LACKEYS
WILL BE OFF THE HOOK.
- JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
I'VE BEEN EXPOSED TO IT
AS LONG AS THEY HAVE
AND MY APPEARANCE
HASN'T CHANGED ONE BIT.
- OH YEAH.  THAT'S TRUE.
- I WOULDN'T TRUST THEM.
THOSE VILLAGERS ARE
HIDING SOMETHING.
BUT I'M SURE YOU
GUILD WIZARDS CAN HANDLE IT.
- WE'RE NOT DONE WITH YOU.
YOU DESTROYED THE VILLAGE--
- THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH,
NATSU.
- YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
WHY WE ALL JOINED LYON?
ALL BECAUSE ALL OUR FAMILIES
WERE KILLED BY DELIORA.
AND WE WANTED TO
GET REVENGE.
HE CONVINCED US THAT
IF WE HELPED HIM
RELEASE THE DEMON,
HE WOULD KILL IT.
THAT IT WOULD BE
GONE FOREVER.
- THEY WERE SIMPLY DOING
WHAT THEY BELIEVED TO BE RIGHT.
SO THERE'S NO NEED
TO CRITICIZE THEM FOR IT.
LET'S GO.
- BUT...
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
TO LIFT THE CURSE?
- Erza: I HAVE NO IDEA.
- Lucy: OH, GREAT.
- ( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- I KNOW YOU DON'T
WANT TO HEAR IT,
BUT YOU REALLY SHOULD
JOIN A GUILD.
YOU MAKE NEW FRIENDS,
MEET NEW RIVALS,
AND MAYBE EVEN FIND
A NEW DREAM TO LIVE FOR.
- ( gasps )
WHATEVER.
JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
- ARE YOU SURE
THEY CAME HERE?
- YEAH, THIS HAS
BEEN THEIR CAMP.
I WONDER WHERE
THEY COULD HAVE GONE.
- HELLO?!
- SINCE WE'RE HERE,
I'M GONNA GRAB BANDAGES
AND SOME MEDICINE.
- YOU FINALLY MADE IT BACK.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO SEE.
PLEASE, FOLLOW ME
TO THE VILLAGE.
- ( excited chatter )
- WHOA. ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- YESTERDAY IT WAS
A TOTAL MESS,
BUT NOW IT LOOKS PERFECT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
EVERYTHING'S BACK
TO HOW IT WAS.
IT'S LIKE THE VILLAGE
WENT BACK IN TIME.
- NOW THAT IT'S FIXED,
YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
TOUCH ANYTHING,
'KAY, NATSU?
- ARE YOU SAYING
I DESTROY EVERYTHING I TOUCH?!
- WELL, KINDA.
- BACK IN TIME.
- ( laughs )
- WAS IT HIM?
NAH, IT COULDN'T BE.
UNLESS HE HAD
A CHANGE OF HEART.
AH, WHO CARES.
- NOT ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OH, I FORGOT
ABOUT OUR STUFF.
Lucy:
BOBO'S GRAVE IS BACK.
I'M SO GLAD.
AND I'M SURE THE CHIEF
MUST BE RELIEVED.
- YOU AND YOUR
WIZARD FRIENDS USED MAGIC
TO RESTORE OUR VILLAGE,
DIDN'T YOU?
- UH WELL, SIR,
THAT'S NOT--
- I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW MUCH I APPRECIATE IT.
HOWEVER, I MUST KNOW
WHEN ARE YOU WIZARDS
FINALLY GOING TO
DESTROY THE MOON FOR US? WELL?!
- UH...
- DESTROYING THE MOON
IS A SIMPLE TASK, SIR.
- HUH?
- WHAT THE--?
DID SHE JUST SAY THAT
WITH A STRAIGHT FACE?
- AYE.
MAYBE SHE'S GONE CRAZY.
- Erza: BUT BEFORE I DO THAT,
I NEED TO ASK YOU ALL
A FEW QUESTIONS.
WOULD YOU BE SO KIND
AS TO CALL EVERYONE TOGETHER
FOR A MEETING?
LET ME MAKE SURE
I HAVE MY FACTS STRAIGHT.
THE FIRST TIME
EVERYBODY IN THE VILLAGE
TOOK ON THESE DEMONIC FORMS
IS WHEN THE MOON
BEGAN TO TURN PURPLE.
IS THAT CORRECT?
- YES.
DURING THE DAY, WE'RE FINE,
BUT WHEN THE MOON COMES OUT
WE TRANSFORM INTO
WHAT YOU SEE NOW.
- AND THE MOON
FIRST TURNED PURPLE
ABOUT THREE YEARS AGO,
RIGHT?
- WOW, HAS IT REALLY
BEEN THAT LONG?
- YEAH.
- WE'VE LEARNED THAT
THE MOON DRIP CEREMONY
HAS BEEN PERFORMED
ON THIS ISLAND EVERY NIGHT
FOR THE LAST THREE YEARS.
AND EACH NIGHT IT PRODUCED
A BEAM OF LIGHT SO BRILLIANT
THAT YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
HAVE MISSED IT.
( yelps )
- WHOA.  EVEN LUCY'S
PITFALL TRAP IS BACK.
- SHE SCREAMED
LIKE A GIRL.
- YEAH.
AND IT WAS CUTE.
- I'M SO GONNA BE
DEAD MEAT WHEN SHE GETS OUT.
- SERIOUSLY.
DIDN'T YOU EVER WONDER WHERE
THAT LIGHT WAS COMING FROM?
- SHE GOT UP LIKE
NOTHING HAPPENED.
- SHE MUST BE PRETTY TOUGH.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DIDN'T ANYONE
INVESTIGATE?
- ( all murmuring )
- WELL, WE WOULD HAVE
LOOKED INTO IT,
BUT ACCORDING TO
VILLAGE LORE,
OUR PEOPLE MUST NEVER
GO NEAR THAT TEMPLE.
- BUT WHO CARES ABOUT
VILLAGE LORE
WHEN YOUR OWN PEOPLE
ARE DYING?
YOU OBVIOUSLY KNEW
THERE WAS A PROBLEM
'CAUSE YOU CONTACTED
THE MAGIC GUILDS.
- OH WELL...
- WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON HERE?
- TO BE HONEST, WE DON'T EVEN
KNOW THAT OURSELVES.
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
WE'VE TRIED TO INVESTIGATE
THE LIGHT MANY TIMES.
WE'D TAKE UP WEAPONS
WE'VE NEVER HAD TO USE.
I'D TRIM AND STYLE
MY SIDEBURNS,
AND THEN WE'D VENTURE INTO
THE JUNGLE TOWARDS THE TEMPLE.
BUT WE COULD NEVER
GET NEAR IT.
WE'D GET CLOSE ENOUGH THAT WE
COULD SEE IT THROUGH THE TREES,
AND THEN SUDDENLY WE'D
FIND OURSELVES BACK
AT THE VILLAGE GATES.
- BUT HOW'S THAT POSSIBLE?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- WE GOT INTO THE TEMPLE
WITHOUT ANY PROBLEM AT ALL.
HOW WEIRD.
- WE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
TO YOU EARLIER,
BECAUSE WE WERE WORRIED
THAT YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE US.
- WE'RE TELLING YOU
THE TRUTH.
WE'VE TRIED TO GO BACK
TO THE TEMPLE MANY TIMES.
- BUT NOT A SINGLE VILLAGER
HAS EVER BEEN ABLE
TO GET INSIDE.
- I GET IT.  YES.
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
IMPRESSIVE, TITANIA.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
IT WOULDN'T TAKE YOU LONG
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
( chuckles )
- Erza: NATSU?
COME WITH ME.
I'LL NEED YOUR HELP
TO DESTROY THE MOON.
- ( laughs )
- ( all gasp )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: PROFESSOR HAPPY'S
CLASS ABOUT "FAIRY TAIL."
YAY! TODAY I'M GONNA TEACH YOU
ABOUT CELESTIAL SPIRITS.
THE NUMBER OF TIMES
A CELESTIAL WIZARD
CAN SUMMON A SPIRIT
DEPENDS ON THEIR CONTRACT
AND THE AMOUNT OF
TRUST BETWEEN THE TWO.
ALSO, WHENEVER
A WIZARD GETS STRONGER,
THEIR SPIRITS BECOME
MORE POWERFUL AS WELL.
NEW CELESTIAL SPIRITS
SHOW UP ALL THE TIME,
SO BE ON THE LOOKOUT.
THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED!  AYE!
HEY, NATSU, DID YOU KNOW
THERE ARE ACTUALLY CATS
LIVING ON THE MOON?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'VE NEVER HEARD THAT.
- IT'S TRUE.
AND IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY HAVE A LOT OF FUN TOO.
THEY SPEND ALL DAY
PLAYING IN CRATERS
AND EATING FISH.
I REALLY WANT TO
CHECK IT OUT.
- SORRY, PAL,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY FISH
ON THE MOON.
- WHAT?!
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THE MOON DOESN'T HAVE FISH?
YOU'VE BEEN THERE?
- NO,
BUT YOU CAN'T HAVE FISH
WITHOUT WATER.
- AW, MAN. I WAS LOOKING
FORWARD TO SOME MOON FISH.