- HEY, GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Natsu: WE'RE READY
FOR THE BIG TIME.  S-CLASS!
- Happy: NATSU AND I
WERE DRAGGED TO GALUNA ISLAND
BY A POWER-HUNGRY LUCY.
IT'S A SCARY PLACE
BECAUSE IT'S BEEN CURSED.
- Lucy: DON'T LIE!
THIS WAS ALL YOUR IDEA.
- Happy: ON OUR ADVENTURES,
WE CAME ACROSS A DOG,
HUGE EYEBROWS,
SOME CRAZY SIDEBURNS
AND A GIANT MONSTER
FROZEN IN ICE!
- Natsu:
PRETTY WEIRD SO FAR, HUH?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Gray: DELIORA...
- YOU SURE THIS IS THE DEMON
YOUR MASTER SEALED AWAY?
- THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- I WONDER WHY
IT WAS TRANSPORTED ALL THE WAY
FROM THE NORTHERN
CONTINENT TO GALUNA ISLAND.
- YOU DON'T THINK THIS DEMON
COULD HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE ISLAND'S CURSE,
DO YOU?
- I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF IT DID.
IT MAY BE ENCLOSED IN ICE,
BUT THAT THING'S STILL ALIVE.
- SWEET!
GIVE ME A GO AT IT!
I AIN'T AFRAID OF
NO STUPID DEMON!
- YOU KNOW, BRUTE FORCE
ISN'T THE ONLY WAY
TO SOLVE A PROBLEM, NATSU.
- A LITTLE FIRE
OUGHTA DO THE TRICK!
- GRAY JUST PUNCHED NATSU!
- WELL, THIS WOULDN'T BE
THE FIRST TIME HE'S DONE THAT.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?!
WHAT'D YOU HIT ME FOR, GRAY?!
- I DON'T WANT YOU AND
YOUR FLAMES ANYWHERE NEAR IT.
IF THAT ICE MELTS
AND DELIORA IS REVIVED...
THERE'S NO WAY WE'D BE
ABLE TO STOP IT.
- COME ON. DO YOU REALLY
THINK A HUGE CHUNK OF ICE
WOULD BE THAT EASY TO MELT?
- NO...
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M THE ONE WHO GOT HIT
FOR NO GOOD REASON!
WATCH YOUR TEMPER, MAN!
- PLEASE, YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
- MANY YEARS AGO,
MY MASTER UR
CAST A SPELL CALLED ICED SHELL
ON THIS DEMON...
ENCLOSING IT IN A FORM OF ICE
THAT CAN'T BE MELTED.
IT'S SO STRONG THAT EVEN
THE MOST POWERFUL FLAME SPELLS
HAVE NO EFFECT ON IT.
IF THEY KNEW THAT THE ICE
COULDN'T BE MELTED,
THEN WHY DID THEY
BRING IT HERE?
- WELL, MAYBE
THEY DIDN'T KNOW.
THEY MIGHT'VE BROUGHT IT HERE
TO TRY TO MELT IT SOMEHOW.
- BUT WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT?!
- UM, I HAVE NO IDEA.
- ( sighs )
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
WHO WOULD BRING DELIORA HERE,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY, WHY?
- WE NEED ANSWERS.
LET'S GO FIND THOSE GUYS.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- NO!
WE'RE GONNA STAY HERE
AND WAIT.
- WAIT FOR WHAT?
- FOR THE MOON TO COME OUT.
- THE MOON?!
BUT IT'S THE MIDDLE OF
THE AFTERNOON!
FORGET THAT!
IF I HAVE TO HANG OUT HERE
ALL DAY, I'LL DIE OF BOREDOM!
- BUT GRAY,
WHY DOES THE MOON MATTER?
- I HAVE A FEELING
THAT THE CURSE ON THIS ISLAND
AND DELIORA ARE SOMEHOW
CONNECTED TO IT.
AND I HEARD THOSE GUYS
WE SAW EARLIER
SAY SOMETHING ABOUT
COLLECTING MOONLIGHT.
- I HEARD THAT TOO.
I GUESS WAITING TILL NIGHTFALL
IS THE ONLY WAY WE'RE GONNA
FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
- I'M NOT WAITIN'!
WE GOT WORK TO DO!
( snoring )
- WELL, THAT WAS FAST.
- AYE.
- ( rock music playing )
- ( Happy speaking )
- MUST BE NICE...
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING
BUT EATING, FIGHTING
AND SLEEPING.
- AYE.
THAT'S NATSU FOR YA.
- I GOTTA ADMIT,
I'M A LITTLE BIT JEALOUS.
- UR...
( panting )
- ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE
TO KEEP UP, GRAY?
I WARNED YOU,
TRAINING WITH ME CAN BE TOUGH.
- ( panting )
YEAH, BUT I'LL DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
- ( groans )
I KNOW I AGREED TO WAIT,
BUT THIS IS SO BORING.
- AYE.
- OH, I KNOW!
OPEN-- GATE OF
THE HARP CONSTELLATION!
LYRA!
- OH, WOW!  I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN FOREVER, LUCY!
- HEY, LYRA!
- SAY...
HOW COME YOU NEVER
CALL ME ANYMORE?
IT'S NOT FAIR.
I WOULD LOVE TO HELP YOU OUT,
BUT YOU IGNORE ME, MEANIE.
- "MEANIE," HUH?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOLD ME
YOU WERE ONLY AVAILABLE
THREE DAYS A MONTH.
- UH...
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- GREAT.  ANOTHER WEIRDO.
- ( snoring )
- SO WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HEAR ME SING?
ANY REQUESTS?
- NOPE, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- DO YOU KNOW ANY SONGS
ABOUT FISH?
- 'KAY.  I'VE GOT A SONG I THINK
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE, LUCY!
- LYRA HAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
SINGING VOICE!
- WELL, MIRA'S A SINGER TOO,
YOU KNOW?
AND SHE SINGS SONGS
ABOUT FISH FOR ME.
- ( playing soft melody )
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
- ♪ WORDS ARE BORN INTO AIR ♪
♪ AND QUICKLY FADE OUT
IN THE WIND ♪
♪ BUT THEY FIND THEIR WAY
INSIDE YOU ♪
♪ WHERE THEY LIVE ON
FOREVER MORE ♪
♪ WHEN THE SKIES ARE DARK
AND FULL OF RAIN ♪
♪ LOOK INSIDE YOUR HEART ♪
♪ LIGHT, SO WARM AND ALL AGLOW ♪
♪ SHINING JUST LIKE THE SUN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SEE JUST HOW MUCH
YOU'VE GROWN ♪
♪ HOW STRONG YOU ARE ♪
♪ A PATH WILL OPEN UP TO YOU ♪
♪ AND IT STARTS FROM THE DAY
THAT YOU... ♪
♪ FIRST HEARD THOSE WORDS. ♪
- ( grunts )
- ♪ OOH OOH. ♪
- GRAY?  WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING.  I'M FINE.
- YOU SEEM UPSET.
- WELL, ONE OF LYRA'S TALENTS
IS SINGING SONGS
THAT RELATE TO WHAT
HER AUDIENCE IS FEELING.
- DID HER SONG MAKE YOU CRY?
- I WASN'T CRYING.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD SING
SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE UPBEAT.
- YOU SHOULD'VE JUST SAID THAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- ( Gray sighs )
I THINK WE SHOULD SKIP THE SONG.
WE NEED TO STAY QUIET.
WE DON'T WANNA BE FOUND OUT.
- ( rumbling )
- ( Natsu snoring )
- WHAT'S THAT WEIRD NOISE?
- IS IT NIGHT YET?
- IT'S A BEAM OF LIGHT!
- SHINING DOWN FROM THE CEILING!
- BUT WHY IS IT PURPLE?
IT MUST BE MOONLIGHT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M GETTING SCARED, GRAY.
- IT'S SHINING ON DELIORA!
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A COINCIDENCE.
- LET'S GO.
WE HAVE TO FIND OUT WHERE
THE LIGHT'S COMING FROM.
- AYE!
- WHY WOULD SOMEONE CAST A MAGIC
CIRCLE INSIDE THIS OLD TEMPLE?
- LET'S FIND OUT.
- All:
ZERAM, SEN, DIOLUNA...
KOO-NAH, KOO-RAH-KAH...
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
- ...ZERAM, SEN, DIOLUNA,
KOO-NAH, KOO-RAH-KAH.
- THE MOON...
- IT LOOKS LIKE THOSE ROBED
FREAKS ARE CHANTING SOME SPELL
TO COLLECT THE MOONLIGHT.
- AND SHINE IT ON DELIORA.
BUT WHAT FOR?
- IT'S A BELIANESE SPELL
CALLED THE MOON DRIP.
- WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?!
- I SEE.  THAT'S WHAT
THEY'RE TRYING TO DO...
- OKAY, TEASE,
FILL US IN.
- THEY'RE USING THE MOON DRIP
SPELL TO MELT THE ICE
SURROUNDING THAT DEMON
UNDERGROUND
SO THEY CAN RESURRECT IT.
- Natsu: WHAT?!
- THEY CAN'T!
THE ICE USED IN AN ICED SHELL
CAN'T BE MELTED.
- I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT THAT'S NOT ENTIRELY TRUE.
WHILE THE ICED SHELL
IS STRONG,
IT CAN BE MELTED
USING MOON DRIP.
FOCUSED MOON ENERGY CAN BREAK
ANY MAGICAL SPELL.
- OH, NO.
- IDIOTS.
THEY'VE NEVER WITNESSED
THE WRATH OF DELIORA.
- I THINK WHAT THE ISLANDERS
BELIEVE IS A CURSE AGAINST THEM,
MAY ACTUALLY BE SIDE EFFECTS
OF THE MOON DRIP.
CONCENTRATED MOON ENERGY
CAN CONTAMINATE YOUR BODY.
I'M AFRAID
THOSE POOR ISLANDERS
HAVE BEEN EXPOSED TO WAY
TOO MUCH OF IT.
- I'LL MAKE 'EM PAY!
- HOLD IT!
SOMEONE'S COMING THIS WAY.
- WHAT A WASTE, I LOST SO MUCH
PRECIOUS SLEEP FOR NOTHING.
- ( snoring )
- WE SEARCHED ALL DAY
FOR THE INTRUDERS,
BUT NEVER FOUND A TRACE OF THEM.
- MAYBE THERE WASN'T ANY!
- I'M AFRAID I HAVE
SOME SAD NEWS, COLD EMPEROR.
WE THOUGHT WE HAD INTRUDERS
DURING THE DAY,
BUT IT SEEMS THEY GOT AWAY
SOMEHOW.
I CANNOT SPEAK OF LOVE
IN THIS SITUATION.
- INTRUDERS?
- ( exhales )
- SO THAT GUY'S THEIR LEADER.
- HE'S TRYING TO ACT
ALL HIGH AND MIGHTY,
WEARING THAT
STUPID-LOOKING MASK!
- I DON'T KNOW,
I THINK IT LOOKS KINDA COOL.
- HAS DELIORA BEEN AWAKENED YET?
- IT SHOULD BE LATER TONIGHT
OR TOMORROW, SIR.
- WHICH ONE, GIRL?!
- THE TIME HAS ALMOST COME.
IF YOU SEE THOSE INTRUDERS
AGAIN, KILL THEM.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE
GETTING IN MY WAY.
- THEY MUST HAVE BEEN VILLAGERS.
THEY'RE THE ONLY OTHER PEOPLE
ON THIS ISLAND.
- THEN DESTROY THE VILLAGE.
- YES, SIR!
- UNDERSTOOD!
- WHAT?!
- BUT THE VILLAGERS DIDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
- YEAH.
WE GOTTA STOP 'EM.
- IT'S A SHAME
THERE HAS TO BE BLOODSHED.
- THAT VOICE...
NO.  IT CAN'T BE.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS
SNEAKING-AROUND BUSINESS!
IT'S NOT THE VILLAGERS!
WE'RE THE INTRUDERS
YOU'RE AFTER!
- ( all gasp )
- ( chuckles )
- JEEZ!  I GUESS THERE'S
NO TURNING BACK NOW, HUH?
- I WANNA HELP OUT TOO!
WANT ME TO SING?
- NO, I WANT YOU TO GO BACK.
- AWW, YOU'RE NO FUN.
- I KNOW THAT MARK.
THEY'RE FROM FAIRY TAIL.
- INTERESTING.
THOSE VILLAGERS MUST'VE GONE
TO THE MAGICAL GUILDS
FOR HELP.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THEM.
GO ERADICATE THE VILLAGE.
- WHAT?!
- BUT WHY?!
- ANYONE WHO STANDS IN MY WAY,
WHETHER DELIBERATELY OR NOT,
IS MY ENEMY!
- SAY WHAT?!
( panting )
- WHY, YOU!
STOP THIS CRAZY CEREMONY
RIGHT NOW!
- ( grunting )
- HE'S AN ICE WIZARD TOO?
- LYON!
- HUH?
- LYON?
- HOW COULD YOU?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
- OH, GRAY.
IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE,
HASN'T IT?
- ( both gasp )
- WHY WOULD YOU
REVIVE DELIORA?
- TO THINK THAT YOU WERE
ONE OF THE WIZARDS
CALLED TO THIS ISLAND
TO HELP THOSE POOR VILLAGERS.
DID YOU COME
KNOWING YOU WOULD FIND ME?
OR IS THIS JUST
MERE COINCIDENCE?
NOT THAT IT MAKES ANY
DIFFERENCE TO ME.
- AN ACQUAINTANCE OF YOURS,
COLD EMPEROR?
- ( barks )
- DO AS YOU WERE ORDERED.
I CAN HANDLE THE INTRUDERS
ON MY OWN.
- YES, SIR!
- HEY, WAIT!  COME BACK HERE!
- NO, NATSU DON'T GO NEAR HIM!
- AAH!
- NATSU!
- HAPPY, GET LUCY OUTTA HERE!
- AYE!
- WAIT!
- ( grunting )
- HA!
- WHAT?!  NO!
I CAN'T MOVE!
- HOLD ON, WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
NATSU LIKE THAT.
- HE WAS HIT WITH A TYPE
OF ICE MAGIC
THAT INSTANTLY
FREEZES THE AIR.
IF WE HAD STUCK AROUND THERE
ANY LONGER,
WE PROBABLY WOULD'VE
BEEN FROZEN TOO.
- WHO CARES?
WE GOTTA SAVE HIM!
- BUT WHO'S GONNA
SAVE THE VILLAGE,
IF ALL OF US HAVE BEEN
TURNED INTO ICE?!
( cries )
- AW, I'M SORRY, HAPPY.
IT MUST'VE BEEN HARD FOR YOU
TO LEAVE HIM BEHIND.
DON'T YOU WORRY,
I'M SURE HE'LL BE FINE.
ICE IS NO MATCH FOR
A SALAMANDER, RIGHT?
- AYE!
- YOU DISTRACTED ME
LONG ENOUGH
FOR THE GIRL
AND THE CAT TO ESCAPE.
CHIVALROUS,
BUT ULTIMATELY POINTLESS.
THERE'S NO WAY THOSE TWO
CAN STOP MY MINIONS.
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE THE POWER
OF FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS!
NOW!
AAH!
OH, AAH!
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA, GRAY?!
- I SEE YOU'RE AS RECKLESS
AS EVER.
WAS HE NOT ONE OF YOUR ALLIES?
- YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THAT WITH ONE SPELL
YOU COULD BLOW UP THAT ICE
AND HIM WITH IT.
- SO YOU CHOSE TO SEND HIM
SAFELY
OUTSIDE THE RANGE OF MY MAGIC.
THAT WAS A VERY CLEVER MOVE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU'RE TRYING TO PULL THIS
SUPERIOR ACT WITH ME, LYON.
YOU'RE NOT!  WE'RE NOT
UR'S STUDENTS ANYMORE!
- I'M WELL AWARE OF THAT.
PAINFULLY AWARE.
OUR BELOVED TEACHER
IS NO LONGER OF THIS WORLD.
- HER FINAL ACT WAS SEALING
THAT MONSTER AWAY.
ARE YOU REALLY SO CALLOUS
THAT YOU WOULD TRY TO DESTROY
OUR MASTER'S LEGACY?
- DON'T DELUDE YOURSELF.
WE BOTH KNOW YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KILLED UR.
AND YET, YOU DON'T SEEM
TO FEEL ANY GUILT.
HOW CRUEL.
- ( muffled groaning )
AAH!
( chuckles )
GRAY, YOU PUNK!
OH, YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS!
MY FIRE POWER ISN'T MAKING
A DENT IN THIS ICE.
MAN, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
( panting )
I'VE GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE VILLAGE.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO RUN.
AW, MAN, THIS IS HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE!
UH, AAH!
- ( all moaning, groaning )
- UH, WHY DO YOU WANNA GO
TO GALUNA ISLAND?
AH, IT'S SCARY.
- JUST SHUT UP AND STEER.
- OKAY, OKAY...
- ( all moaning, groaning )
- IF YOU DROP US OFF SOMEWHERE,
YOU CAN HAVE THE BOAT.
PLEASE, I'M BEGGING YOU, LADY!
I'VE HEARD
THAT ISLAND IS CURSED,
AND ANYONE WHO STEPS FOOT ON
ITS SOIL TURNS INTO A DEMON!
- I WILL TAKE THAT CHANCE.
- BUT WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO GO THERE?
- WHEN RULES ARE BROKEN,
THE GUILTY MUST BE PUNISHED.
AND THAT IS ALL
I CAN TELL YOU.
- SHE'S SO COOL!
- AND HOT TOO!
- WE DON'T LIKE RULE-BREAKERS
EITHER!
- WE'LL HELP YOU CATCH 'EM
IF YOU WANT!
- SURE.
NOW LET'S HURRY.
- AYE-AYE, SIR!
- I WANNA JOIN YOUR TEAM TOO!
I'LL BRAVE THAT SCARY ISLAND
FOR YOU!
LISTEN UP,
YOU SCALAWAGS,
RAISE THE SAILS,
AND SET COURSE
FOR THE CURSED ISLAND
OF GALUNA.
- ENOUGH WITH THE GAMES, GRAY.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
MURDERED UR, SO JUST ADMIT IT.
I'M SURPRISED YOU HAVE THE GALL
TO EVEN SPEAK HER NAME!
- AAH!
LYON...
- WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T TELL ME THE GUILT IS
FINALLY GETTING TO YOU.
I'M WARNING YOU,
DON'T TRY TO INTERFERE.
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
I'M RESURRECTING DELIORA.
- I WON'T LET YOU.
- IT'S LIKE OLD TIMES.
BUT I'VE GROWN MUCH STRONGER
SINCE THEN.
ICE MAKE: EAGLE!
- ICE MAKE: SHIELD!
AAH!
- WHILE YOUR SPECIALTY IS
CREATING INANIMATE OBJECTS--
STATIC ICE MAKE MAGIC--
MINE IS CREATING
LIVING CREATURES.
ACTIVE ICE MAKE MAGIC.
DID YOU FORGET MY ICE
HAS THE ABILITY TO MOVE?
- ICE MAKE: HAMMER!
- ICE MAKE: APE!
HOW PATHETIC.
YOU STILL USE TWO HANDS WHEN
CASTING YOUR ICE MAKE SPELLS.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
UR TAUGHT US.
SINGLE-HANDED SPELL CASTING IS
INCOMPLETE AND UNBALANCED.
- WELL, I'M THE EXCEPTION
TO THAT RULE.
I SURPASSED UR'S SKILL LEVEL
A LONG TIME AGO.
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
- REGARDLESS, EVER SINCE
WE WERE CHILDREN,
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO LAND A SINGLE HIT ON ME.
- ( growls )
I'M A LOT STRONGER NOW
THAN I USED TO BE.
ICE MAKE: GEYSER!
- ( all screaming, clamoring )
- NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
I WAS ALWAYS
THE SUPERIOR STUDENT,
AND I'M STILL
STRONGER THAN YOU.
I WAS ABLE TO MASTER
SINGLE-HANDED ICE MAKE MAGIC,
WHILE YOU STILL HAVE TO
RELY ON TWO HANDS.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
WE MAY HAVE CHOSEN
DIFFERENT PATHS,
BUT WE'RE FROZEN IN TIME.
OUR RANKINGS AS WIZARDS
NEVER CHANGE.
- AAH!
- THAT'S WHY
I'M RESURRECTING DELIORA--
TO PROVE THAT I AM
MORE THAN UR'S STAR PUPIL.
AS A CHILD, I ONLY EVER DREAMT
OF ONE THING...
THE DAY I WOULD SURPASS UR'S
ABILITIES AS A WIZARD.
BUT YOU RUINED IT FOR ME,
GRAY.
AFTER SHE DIED,
I THOUGHT MY LIFELONG DREAM
OF SURPASSING HER
HAD BEEN DASHED...
UNTIL I REALIZED,
THERE WAS ONE WAY.
IF I CAN DEFEAT DELIORA,
A DEMON SO STRONG THAT
NOT EVEN UR COULD VANQUISH IT,
THEN I WILL HAVE
SURPASSED HER POWER.
MY DREAM WILL FINALLY
BECOME A REALITY.
- LISTEN TO ME.
THAT THING DESTROYED
EVERYTHING WE CARED ABOUT!
AND YOU WANNA BRING IT BACK JUST
TO PROVE HOW STRONG YOU ARE?!
THAT'S INSANE!
PLEASE!  YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
AAH!
"PLEASE.  YOU CAN'T DO THIS"?
REALLY?
FUNNY YOU SAY THAT.
THOSE WERE THE EXACT WORDS
WE SAID TO YOU THAT FATEFUL DAY.
SURELY,
YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN?
IT'S BECAUSE YOU CHALLENGED
DELIORA...
THAT UR LOST HER LIFE!
I CAN'T STAND YOU
EVEN SPEAKING HER NAME
IN MY PRESENCE!
BE GONE!
THIS IS THE END, GRAY!
- ( grunts )
( screams )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- PROFESSOR HAPPY'S CLASS
ABOUT FAIRY TAIL!
TODAY, I'M GONNA
TEACH YOU GUYS
ALL ABOUT
NATSU THE FIRE WIZARD.
YAY!
NATSU WAS RAISED BY
A DRAGON NAMED IGNEEL,
WHO TAUGHT HIM
RARE DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC.
SO HE CAN EAT FIRE,
BREATHE FIRE
AND ATTACK WITH FIRE.
HIS ONLY WEAKNESS,
AS YOU'VE PROBABLY
ALREADY NOTICED,
IS A REALLY BAD CASE
OF MOTION SICKNESS.
WELL, THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED!  AYE!
- MAN, THAT DELIORA THING
IS GIGANTIC, HUH?
- YEAH, IT'S PROBABLY BIGGER
THAN A PILE OF 1,000 FISH.
- HUH, I WONDER WHAT KIND OF
FOOD YOU'D HAVE TO EAT
TO GET THAT BIG.
- I BET LOTS AND LOTS
OF FISH WOULD WORK,
'CAUSE THEY'RE
FULL OF CALCIUM,
AND OTHER STUFF THAT'S
GOOD FOR YOU.
- EH, FISH IS OKAY,
BUT I'M MORE OF
A MEAT MAN MYSELF.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: IF YOU EVER GOT
THAT BIG,
I BET YOU'D GET ARRESTED
ALL THE TIME.
- HEY, WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
- 'CAUSE IT'D BE THAT MUCH
EASIER FOR YOU
TO DESTROY A TOWN.