[CANA] Way to
suck it up out there!
Losers!
Seriously, how could members of
the great Fairy Tail
be so pathetic?
It was embarrassing!
[ELFMAN] Maybe you
should have been there
to cheer us on
instead of hitting
every pub within
walking distance.
[CANA] I did cheer for you guys.
All the pubs
have lacrima-vision
and the booze is
a helluva lot cheaper!
[MAKAROV] Less
shouting, more drinking!
We've got a horrible
defeat to celebrate here!
[LEVY] Master's wasted!
♪
This has certainly
been an eventful day, hasn't it?
No kidding.
I think it's safe to say
our work's cut out for us.
Tomorrow's when
it's all gonna change!
I'll jump in there and
set that scoreboard on fire!
That's right!
Natsu's gonna burn some booties!
If Salamander's takin' part,
I might have to step in myself.
Talk about the
perfect opportunity
to show him the
fruits of your labor.
[LEVY] Hey.
I don't see Lucy or Gray.
Did they leave?
I haven't seen them
since today's match.
Well, yeah, can
you blame 'em?
You saw how badly
they lost today.
They'll show up once
they're done licking
their wounds.
[ROMEO] They looked fine to me!
But do ya think we should
check on them or something?
[JUVIA THINKS] Oh Gray.
[GRAY] You're still
angry about today?
[LUCY] Are you
saying you aren't?
[GRAY]
Well, everyone else is
drowning their
sorrows at the bar.
I know it's a pain,
but you should drop
in once you've got
your stuff worked--
Please stay a bit.
I don't wanna be alone.
Fine, I'll stay.
What's up?
[LUCY] The truth is.
I love you!
I always have!
I can't! My heart
belongs to Juvia!
Give me a chance!
That's all I ask!
She could
be confusing my
beloved and taking
him all for herself!
We're right here, Juvia.
Her imagination must
not have an off switch.
Neither does her mouth.
Hey Lu!
How're you feeling?
[LUCY] I'm good now.
For real!
Matter of fact, I'm more
fired up than ever!
[GRAY] How are
Wendy and Carla?
They're both
still pretty weak.
Porlyusica hasn't
left their side.
Listen up!
Now that all you brats are here.
I'd like to make a toast!
[MAKAROV] Today we lost!
And you know that
means, don't you?
Tomorrow we
climb to the top!
Because Fairy Tail never backs
down and we're not startin' now!
The greatest
guild in Fiore is us!
[ALL] Yeah!
What gives?
Did they drink so much they
forgot they're bottom
of the barrel?
Don't look at me.
[HAPPY] Chariots!
[ARCADIOS] Your Majesty.
I'm pleased to
report that the first
day of the games
ended without incident.
[MATO] The magic
battle was quite good.
If your Majesty has
any requests concerning
tomorrow's battle portion,
I will happily arrange it.
[MATO] I would like to
see Bacchus, for sure.
Make certain to
include him in the matchup.
[ARCADIOS] Any preference
on his opponent?
[MATO] How about
that Fairy Tail member?
The one who can transform!
Darn it, what was the name?
[MATO]
El--
But of course,
Your Majesty.
I promise a magic
battle you won't forget.
[MATO]
I'm looking forward to it.
[ARCADIOS] If you
have no other requests,
I shall take my leave.
[MATO] Thank you
for your stalwart service.
Rest well, Colonel.
[ARCADIOS]
Sleep is the furthest
thing from my mind.
There's work to do.
I can't afford to rest when
it's so close to being finished.
[NATSU] Who wants some?
Don't chicken out now!
I was startin' to enjoy myself!
[MACAO] Another K-O!
[WAKABA] What happened, Max?
Lose your footin'?
A seven year
training gap and
this guy catches
up in three months?
Have you ever felt
completely out-classed?
Not bad, kid.
You wanna try
your luck against me?
Aw, leave it alone.
If you chumps go at it we'll
be footing the repair bill.
What's the deal,
Thunder Dolt?
Tryin' to impress grand-dad
with your 'good-guy' routine?
[LEVY] Are you
trying to get fried?
Hey!
Stop it, Gajeel!
I won't allow you to
mistreat him like this!
Mess with Laxus,
and you're messing
with the Thunder Legion as well!
Assemble,
Laxus Bodyguard Corps!
Our leader needs us!
[CANA] Someone
can't hold their liquor!
[BACCHUS] Now this looks
like a party worth joinin'.
[CANA] Oh, yeah?
How about a couple
drinks to pass the time?
So we're skipping
the introductions
and going straight
to the fun part?
Ya got something
ta prove, do ya?
Hey, pal.
Take some free
advice and walk away.
Her alcohol tolerance is
about as strong as her daddy!
[MACAO AND WAKABA]
You gotta be kidding me!
I don't believe it!
He literally just drank
her under the table.
I've never seen Cana
drink until she drops before!
[BACCHUS] Thanks
for the trophy, hot stuff!
[MACAO] Do you
have a death wish?
[WAKABA] If Gildarts finds
out, he's gonna be pissed!
Hand it over!
Mocking our guild
won't help you either!
This guy's out
of his mind!
Get up, Dad!
[ERZA] Is that you, Bacchus?
Well, well! If
it isn't Erza Scarlet!
Still a drunk.
And when I'm sober
you'll still be smokin' hot.
You know how
to flatter a girl.
[LUCY] You know him?
I heard you'd gone
into hiding a while back.
It seemed like such a shame.
Something like that.
What about you?
I hear you're actually
competing in the magic games.
At first I saw this
little trip as an excuse
to get hammered and
sample the local color.
[BACCHUS] But after watching
Warcry make a fool out
of himself and
our guild, my manly
spirit got thirsty
for vengeance.
So I'm enterin'
the games as a reserve
member and I plan to
cause all kinds of trouble!
My soul is
shaken and stirred.
[BACCHUS]
Maybe we'll have our own
little party in a battle round.
It'd be nice to
settle the score.
[BACCHUS] You know
what we say in our guild.
You will always be.
Wild.
At least you're still
good for a chuckle, Erza!
[Bacchus laughs]
[LUCY] Who was
that walking distillery?
[ERZA] A member
of Quatro Cerberus.
He's one of their
S-Class wizards.
I've run into
him on jobs more
than a few times
over the years.
And I know his
strength all too well.
[ERZA] Drunken Hawk
Bacchus, master of
the Drunken Chop-Hanging Palm.
We've fought
on many occasions,
but there's never
been a clear winner.
What?
Y'mean he's as strong as you?
What's it matter?
That's all ancient history now.
There's no way Erza would
lose to a cocky wino!
Who said Erza's even
gonna fight him, nerd?
If she won't, then
I call dibs on him!
Tell me more about
this vision of yours.
What, exactly, did you see?
[CARLA] It was confusing because
it was only bits and pieces.
They're never very clear.
There was
a white knight,
an enormous magic circle.
Can you recall any more?
[CARLA] I saw something
that defied all reason.
[PORLYUSICA]
What do you mean by that?
[CARLA] I saw Mercurius
come crashing down.
And, as it happened, I thought
I heard someone singing.
[CARLA] Lucy.
[CHAPATI] Its day two of
the Grand Magic Games
and the stands are
exploding with excitement!
Joining me once
again is Mr. Yajima,
and our new special guest,
Sorcerer Weekly's Jason!
[JASON] So cool!
[CHAPATI] Let's get back
to the action already
in progress, as our wizards
take on the Chariots!
[CHAPATI] The point
of this game is to reach
the final goal
without falling off.
Simple, right?
Wrong!
[CHAPATI] The chariots
are constantly in motion.
And though it's
at a snail's pace,
one false move could cost you!
[CHAPATI] Which team
will survive this rough and
tumble sight-seeing
tour through Crocus
and be the first to
cross the finish line?
[CHAPATI] For those of you
here with us at Domus Flau,
we'll be showing the race in
crystal clear lacrima-vision!
[JASON] Cool!
You've seen a lot in
your days. But would you
have ever predicted
anything remotely like this?
Well.
Why in the hell
did we pick him?
Yeah, you'd think
the name "Chariots"
would be a big clue,
even for Natsu.
He was absolutely
insistent on participating.
[ELFMAN] Maybe he
thought he was gonna
get to fight chariots
or something.
[CHAPATI] Uh, oh!
I don't know what's wrong
with Fairy Tail A's Natsu,
but he can barely put one
foot in front of the other!
That's it; the world's
against us.
[CHAPATI] But that's not all!
Mere feet away are
Fairy Tail B's Gajeel, and
Sabertooth's Sting, who seem
to be in the same boat!
Huh?! Why am
I feeling sick?
I can't imagine
what could
be causing them to
slow down like this.
I could be wrong,
but I'd say they
share a common weakness
for moving vehicles.
No, this is Salamander's
stupid weakness!
So why do I wanna throw up?
I don't understand.
What is happening to Gajeel?
I'll tell you what!
He's stealing Natsu's shtick!
Even the Sabertooth
guy's ill.
Talk about a text-book
case of rotten luck.
This game is all about Sting's
one and only weakness,
so those other guilds have
no clue how easy they got off.
Yeah, Sting would
rock their face!
[CHAPATI] Now let's take a look
at the group leading the pack!
This race is as neck
and neck as it gets, folks!
[CHAPATI] At the front is
Blacksnake from Raven Tail!
Followed closely by
Blue Pegasus' Ichiya,
Lamia Scale's Yuka,
and Mermaid Heel's Lislie!
Feel the burn!
I'm surprised someone with
your figure can
run for this long.
Don't underestimate
chubby power, short stuff.
[CHAPATI]
Coming in behind them is
Quatro Cerberus'
reserve member Bacchus!
Man, that guy's loud.
Can't you let a man work off
last night's booze in peace?
[YUKA] Feel my Wave Boost!
Good luck using any magic
while you're inside
my shockwave!
Weren't you
listening before?
Chubby power rules!
There it is!
Lislie's gravity change magic!
She dodged Yuka's
wave and is now
making her way
towards the leaders!
A magic-neutralizing
wave, huh?
In that case!
Watch my
Swiftness Parfum!
Point-Blank Absorption style!
Wow.
They're really goin'
all out, aren't they?
Gets my soul all
stirred up, y'know?
Welp, guess I
might as well put
a little effort
into this race, too!
[BACCHUS] Check this out!
[CHAPATI] I don't believe it!
Bacchus demolished the
chariots with brute force!
Amazing.
He's even stronger than before.
[ELFMAN] What's with this guy?
[BACCHUS]
Catch ya later, losers!
Try not to fall
off before the finish!
That was a dirty trick!
You said it!
[LISLIE] No one
makes chubby fly!
[CHAPATI] What
happened to Lislie?
[JASON] A gravity change!
So cool!
[BACCHUS] WILD!
[CHAPATI] We have a winner!
I'm shaken and
stirred, baby!
[CHAPATI] Quatro Cerberus
scores 10 points!
I didn't know Cerberus had
someone like him in their guild!
That's what I call wild.
[ALL] Wild!
[CHAPATI] In second place is
Raven Tail's Blacksnake!
[CHAPATI] Lislie's in third,
Yuka takes fourth,
and Ichiya comes in fifth!
[CHAPATI] That just leaves the
three-way battle for last place.
[GAJEEL] This is embarrassing.
I used to be able to ride
on vehicles just fine!
[STING] Hey, that just means
you've finally become one.
You're the
real deal now...
...a card-carryin'
Dragon Slayer.
[STING] I guess
congrats are in order.
Welcome, newbie.
[GAJEEL] Newbie?
What's up?
Where did all of
my strength go?
Come on!
This blows!
Okay?
He thinks puking in
slow-mo is entertaining?
This a common affliction
amongst your kind Rogue?
I had thought that
only Sting and I had trouble
with motion sickness,
but it seems I was wrong.
[ROGUE THINKING] I'm glad
that's not me out there.
Does it affect
you too, Laxus?
Just don't
let Natsu know;
I'll never live it down.
I probably wouldn't have
admitted that if I were you.
Gotta keep movin'!
I'm not gonna lose like this!
[STING] Talk about uncool.
Anyone can see ya
got no strength left.
You're just making
fools of yourselves.
[STING] Fine, whatever.
I didn't need this win,
so I'll just let
you guys have it.
Sabertooth's
just gonna keep
rackin' up the
points after this.
In the end,
one measly little point
isn't gonna change the outcome.
One point is nothin'
to scoff at, kid.
Don't you forget that!
[STING] I don't get it.
Can you explain somethin' to me?
Why'd you even bother
entering the tournament?
Seriously.
[STING] I mean,
you're nothin' like
the Fairy Tail I
knew growin' up.
[STING] You're obsessed
with how tough you
are and what the rest of
the world thinks of you.
[STING] What happened to the
Fairy Tail of my childhood?
The guild that did whatever the
hell it wanted
whenever it wanted?
[STING] They never
cared what anybody
else said or thought of them!
The reason we're here
is for our friends!
[NATSU] The ones who waited for
us for all the
years we were gone!
[NATSU] Who fought through
the pain and the heartache.
[NATSU] They were humiliated,
but even so, they stayed strong!
[NATSU] And they kept
our guild together!
[NATSU] We're doing
this for all of them!
And we're gonna make
sure that everyone here knows.
The Fairy Tail
guild never gave up!
Not for an instant!
So there's no way I'm
gonna give up now!
[ALL] Oh, Natsu!
[CHAPATI] He did it!
Fairy Tail A's Natsu nabs sixth
place and scores two points!
'Bout time we got
some points on the board.
[CHAPATI] Gajeel from
Fairy Tail B takes
seventh place
and scores one point!
Now those boys
have some moxie.
Yeah, that was awesome!
Well, they're gutsy,
I'll give 'em that.
They're from Fairy
Tail, aren't they?
Maybe their guild's
not so bad after all.
He got me right
in the feels, man.
You know, I just might start
rooting for those guys now.
[MALE SPECTATOR 161G]
Way to rock, Fairy Tail!
[MALE SPECTATOR 161H] You
just earned yourself a new fan!
[CHAPATI] Crowd
favorite Sting forfeited
the race, so Sabertooth
gets zero points!
You're doing
this for your friends?
That's a load of crap,
and you know it.
[CHAPATI] And Raven Tail
jumps ahead to first place!
[JASON] Cool!
[CHAPATI]
Which leaves Sabertooth tied
for second with Lamia Scale!
Wait, we're not first?
How did we fall behind?
Sting was feelin'
pukey and didn't finish.
Ugh, my stomach wants to
jump right out of my body.
[LUCY] So you're sure
Natsu will be okay?
Why wouldn't he?
It's just motion sickness.
Stop worrying and let
him get some rest.
[LUCY] What about Wendy?
[PORLYUSICA]
She's coming along nicely.
At least you're up now,
Carla. How're you feeling?
[CARLA] Fine.
I'm so glad to hear that.
The others are waiting,
so I'll check back later 'kay?
You're not going
to say anything to her?
I just don't think
that it would do any good.
They'd never believe me.
Not about a future
like that, anyway.
I suppose it's just as
well that you don't, then.
Besides, you don't seem
to believe it yourself.
You're right!
I don't believe it!
How can I? It's too
bizarre to be true!
It wasn't a premonition.
Just a silly dream.
[CHAPATI] And now for
the part you've all
been waiting for:
the battle portion!
[CHAPATI] Today's first
match pits, Blacksnake,
the dark python of our first
place guild, Raven Tail...
...against Lamia
Scale's own Toby Olorta!
[Toby howls]
[CHAPATI]
It's serpent vs. hound!
Which one of them
will end up top dog?
I expect to see a clean
fight out there, understand?
Toby is so ferocious!
Bad, dog!
Hey guys!
Did I miss anything?
They've been
takin' their sweet time.
It's just about to start.
That dog dude's gonna
be goin' in for Lyon's guild.
It's the Raven Tail
wizard you should watch.
Ya know
he won't play fair.
Yeah. I see
you too, Blondie.
[LUCY THINKS]
She's covered in bruises!
[ALEXAI (IVAN)] Flare.
I won't tolerate any
more embarrassment.
You do realize who you
owe your victory to, don't you?
Yes, sir.
But that Blonde bimbo
won't stop staring at me!
[ALEXAI (IVAN)] Are you
asking for another beating?
[FLARE] No.
I won't argue again!
Please have mercy on me.
[TOBY] Ultra-Poison Nails!
Mega-Mega Jellyfish!
[TOBY] He just vanished!
You fool!
He's using mimic magic!
[BLACKSNAKE] Sand Rebellion!
That freak stole my spell!
He must be able
to mimic different
types of magic or something!
Mimic magic.
I haven't seen that
in a long time.
Come on, dog guy!
Tear him up!
Obliterate that
Raven Tail scumbag,
and I'll pay your
weight in gold!
[Toby howls]
You're stronger
than I thought you were!
[BLACKSNAKE]
You're not so bad yourself.
[TOBY] I wish I had a
cool name like Blacksnake!
It's just my wizard name.
You mean you lied to me?
[BLACKSNAKE] What
are you talking about?
[TOBY] Alright!
Then, if I beat you,
you gotta tell
me what your real name is!
Deal?
[BLACKSNAKE] I'm fine with that.
But what if I win?
[TOBY] Then I'll tell
you my super-special
secret that nobody knows!
[BLACKSNAKE] Sounds intriguing.
It's a deal!
Our competitors
seem to have
struck a friendly wager.
I wouldn't consider
their secrets a prize.
Cool!
A little gambling?
This could make
things interesting.
[TOBY] Nails! Nails!
Fangs! Psyche!
[ELFMAN] Great idea!
♪
[NATSU] Elfman's up next,
fighting the drunk-fu master!
[HAPPY] He's no "master"!
He's only as strong as Erza!
[Happy howls]
[NATSU] And he
rocked the Chariot game.
Dude's tough!
[HAPPY] Elfman can
take him down, no prob!
What's the matter?
Don't you have
faith in your friends?
Huh?
[NATSU] Geez, chill out!
And why are you yelling
everything like the dog guy?
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Elfman vs. Bacchus!
[HAPPY] I can't believe
I actually howled!
I've lost my kitty pride!
[NATSU] What exactly do
cats have to be proud of?