Guess what!
Hungry?
I've got something you
might wanna nibble on.
I didn't know you had a
little friend with you.
It's nice, huh? Having friends.
[MAVIS]
Being in nature...
[MAVIS] ...reminds me the
world is full of kindness.
[MAVIS humming]
Could there be a more
beautiful day?
[ZERA] Here you are, sitting
around daydreaming, as usual.
Hey, Zera!
So I guess you
conveniently forgot
all about
cleaning the library.
Oh. Whoops, I didn't mean to!
My point is, you forgot!
Well, there's no time
like the present!
Honestly, Mavis! You're
not wearing shoes again?
Of course not!
I love going barefoot!
I know.
Hey, Mavis. You've
forgiven me, right?
For how I used to treat you?
For what? Being super mean
to me all of the time?
Come on, we're way
over that stuff.
You're my best friend forever!
Aw, really?
You are just the
sweetest little thing!
I'm not half as
sweet as you are.
Let's go.
[ZERA]
Okay.
[MAVIS] Seven years ago,
tragedy struck Tenrou Island.
Wizards from Blue Skull
invaded our home.
They slaughtered
everyone in sight,
wiping out the entire Red Lizard
guild, and villagers alike.
But Zera and I survived
that horrible night.
And for all these years,
we've lived in isolation,
with only each other
to keep us company
and to share our thoughts.
Just us on that island.
Alone, but not alone.
[YURI]
You ready, boys?
Let's go snag ourselves
that Tenrou Orb!
So ya know where it is, do ya?
I think he means, "Let's
split up and look for it."
Yup! And I call this way!
Well, I reckon I'll head east.
[PRECHT sighs]
[PRECHT]
Give the signal if you find it.
[YURI]
You bet!
So where should I
put this stack of books?
Put 'em in that bookcase.
What about these?
In that one over there.
There's still more.
Those go over...
[ZERA]
They're all completely full!
Calm down, silly.
We just have to organize
them a little more neatly.
Oh, wow! A book all about
ancient battle strategies!
Reading that sounds even
more boring than cleaning up.
Just put it away! Or we're
never gonna get done in here!
[YURI]
Hey. I recognize that.
It's the Red Lizard guild mark.
Or at least, it used to be.
I should set aside
a little space here
to store my absolute
favorite ones.
Quit slacking off already!
You must've read that book
over a thousand times by now!
Yeah, I know,
but every time I discover
something new!
That's really interesting.
What am I doing?! I won't let
you drag me down with you!
First we do our chores,
then we relax!
Okay!
[ZERA]
Hm?
Huh? What's the matter, Zera?
I think someone's here.
There's somebody else
on the island? But why?
No, no, no, this
can't be happening!
[MAVIS]
Don't freak out!
I'm so scared.
I haven't talked to anybody
in over seven years!
I don't know what to do!
Do I not count as "anybody"?
They're here!
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
[ZERA]
Okay!
Be careful.
[chuckles]
Everything'll be fine.
It's a massive library.
You mind telling me why
you've come to this island?
[YURI]
Whoa! You scared me!
They told me this place
was completely deserted!
[YURI]
Oh, man.
Gonna answer?
Uh, yeah. It's because I--
I came here to study
the island's ecosystem.
[MAVIS]
You're lying.
If you're truly a biology
expert, as you claim,
then tell me this:
How did you protect yourself
against the poisonous Yaktrinca?
What's she talking about?
I guess you don't get out much.
But there's a place near
the port of Hargeon
that sells a Yaktrinca antidote.
So why did you actually
come to the island?
[YURI]
I told you already.
That was a good story,
but Yaktrinca isn't
the least bit poisonous.
Even an amateur biologist
would know that.
You're not a very
convincing liar.
[grunts]
You nailed him. Way to go!
[YURI] You must think
you're really smart, huh?
I have read thousands
and thousands of books!
I'm a treasure hunter,
and I came here to find a jewel
called the Tenrou Orb.
Bet'cha didn't know that.
[MAVIS]
The Tenrou Orb?
Now don't act like you haven't
heard of it, smarty-pants.
It's the only S-class
treasure on this island.
Of course I've heard of it.
Because it's Tenrou Island's
most sacred artifact.
So I can't let anyone just
waltz in here and take it.
You're spunky, but I don't think
you're gonna be much
of an obstacle for me.
[ZERA]
Huh?
Aw, who am I tryin' to kid?
I'm not fightin' a little girl.
[sighs]
Well, you're obviously
a sharp little tack,
so are you willing to take
me on in a game of wits?
[MAVIS]
You wanna play a game?
[YURI]
Yeah, and if I win,
you have to tell me where
to find the Tenrou Orb.
If you win, I'll leave the
island without any more fuss.
[YURI] All right,
I'll sweeten the deal.
If you beat me, I'll take
you to meet a fairy.
A real fairy?
[YURI]
Yeah.
It's a deal!
But only if you win, okay?
She's so gullible.
The rules are pretty simple.
All we do is point out some
facts about each other.
[MAVIS]
Can you give me an example?
Yeah, sure.
So on my first turn,
I could say something like,
"You are a girl."
If that fact is true,
then you'd be up next.
And I could say
that you're a man.
[YURI] Yeah, that's pretty
much the gist of it.
[MAVIS]
Hm...
[YURI] The first to
get one wrong loses.
I assume lying's not allowed.
[YURI]
Naturally.
However, there is one
more important rule.
We can't state any fact
that we both have in common.
What kind of things do
we have in common?
Obvious statements like,
"You have eyes."
Things that'd be
true of anybody.
If we pointed out
stuff like that,
the game would never end.
Yes, I see.
The whole game is
basically an exercise
in deductive reasoning.
Oh, and there's one more thing,
the key words can
only be used one time.
I get it. You mind if
we do a practice run?
[YURI]
Not at all.
I'm positive that you
are not a biologist.
[YURI] Correct.
I'm positive you love books.
You're right about that!
I can clearly see that you are
wearing a leather jacket.
Right again.
But you can only point out
your opponent's
appearance one time, too.
Else there'd be no end to it.
Makes sense to me.
[YURI]
You are a teenager.
Yes, just barely.
And I'd say you...
...are in your 20s.
Ha! Incorrect!
Despite my obvious maturity,
I'm still in my teens.
[YURI laughs]
[YURI]
I win that round!
But that was just
a practice run.
Here comes the real thing.
And there's no backin'
outta this one, okay?
Oh, no. This is such
a horrible idea.
Mavis can be such an airhead.
If she gets distracted,
she's gonna blow the
whole thing for us.
[YURI]
Ready?
Ready.
Let the game begin!
[YURI]
Now the trump card.
Hm? What in the world is that?
[YURI] An A-class treasure,
the Judgment Field.
Anyone standing inside it
has to tell the truth.
If you lie, this magic
item will know
and you will be
deemed the loser.
Pretty cool little
gadget, isn't it?
It really uses magic?
[YURI]
Yep.
And because you can't
lie, that also means
you can't break the promise
you made to me earlier.
[MAVIS]
What promise?
That you'd tell me where
I could find the Tenrou Orb
if I beat you at this game.
Ah, I'd forgotten about that.
I got so wrapped up in
everything, it slipped my mind.
And remember if I win,
I get to meet a real fairy!
This'll be fun.
And your magic field will
guarantee my victory.
How?
[chuckles]
Beacuse you're gonna have
to stick to the rules.
I was the winner of the
practice round, after all.
Whaddaya mean?
According to the rules,
we can't state anything
that we have in common.
I'm a teenager.
But as you admitted, so are you.
Since you stated something
that we both have in common,
you lost the round.
Now that we have
this magic field,
you can't break the rules.
So are you ready?
[YURI] This brat is way smarter
than I thought she'd be.
But even so, I have
a clear advantage.
I'm gonna meet a fairy!
[YURI]
Tons of information.
In sports, they talk about
a "home field advantage."
This game has
the exact opposite.
There's info about
her everywhere I look.
The books she's reading.
What she ate today.
Her hobbies and interests.
It's all out in the open.
On the other hand, she's
got almost nothing on me.
This'll be over in no time.
[YURI]
Whaddaya say we get started?
First thing is deciding
who goes first.
It doesn't really matter to me.
[gasps]
What?
You heard me.
It makes absolutely no
difference what order we go in.
Because I'm going to
win it in one round.
[MAVIS] And that's the story
of how Yuri and I first met.
Who could have imagined
that in 95 days
we'd create Fairy Tail?
[YURI]
Hold on a second,
you understand how this
game works, don'tcha?
Yes, of course I do.
Whatever we say, your
magic field will determine
whether it's true
or false, right?
[YURI]
That's right.
And you said you'll
win the first round,
so if we go to round two,
you'll automatically lose.
[MAVIS] I know, because
we've already established
that lying means
forfeiting the game.
[YURI]
Okay.
This is ridiculous.
I've been playing this game
practically my entire life.
Nobody's ever won it in just
one turn. It's impossible!
She must be bluffing.
Trying to ruffle my feathers.
[YURI]
I've got this in the bag.
She sealed her fate
by being so cocky.
So you think it doesn't matter
which one of us goes first?
[MAVIS]
Nope.
Then allow me to do the honors.
[YURI] Here's an
undisputable fact for ya.
You're a bird owner.
Try and deny that,
ya little know it all!
Here goes.
You are a bird--
No, I'm not!
Uh!
[ZERA]
Uh?
Since you got that one wrong,
I win the round
and the entire game!
That's totally unfair!
You didn't even give me a
chance to finish my sentence.
So what?
We went over all the rules
and I don't remember
there being one about
not cutting off your opponent.
The first thing you said
was, "you're a bird,"
but all evidence clearly
shows that I'm human,
so your statement was
false and you lose.
Why, you... You tricked me.
I didn't know she was so sneaky.
That doesn't count!
You cheated! I call do-over!
No! I will not accept it!
Okay, then new rule!
We have to let the other
person finish talking!
That's fine by me.
All right, ya little cheater,
that means it's your turn now.
[MAVIS]
Okay.
I'll go if you insist, but this
will still be the final round.
Are you ready?
Don't forget that you have
to keep your promises.
The first one being that you'll
leave the island immediately.
And more importantly that
I can meet a real fairy!
[YURI] How the heck does
she think she can win
in one turn again?
Besides, there's absolutely
no way she can pull it off.
It's impossible for the
questioner to win.
The game doesn't work that way.
I don't think you understand.
If you get it right,
that just means it's my turn
and we keep on playing.
But if you happen
to get it wrong,
you lose and the
whole thing is over.
[MAVIS]
I know.
[YURI] Well, if you understand
that, you should be able to see
the person stating
the facts can never win.
You're just making
that assumption
based on your limited personal
experience and understanding
of how you think the game works.
Which is precisely why
you're going to lose.
Here goes.
[YURI]
Bring it!
[YURI] Why does she think
she can win like this?
Ever since we first
began playing the game,
you have blinked your eyes
a total of 57 times.
Huh?
What'd you say?!
I said, you've blinked
a total of 57 times
since the game began.
Now is that statement
true or false?
How can anyone
possibly know that?!
[YURI]
That's completely insane!
There's no way she could've
been counting my blinks!
Hold on!
Since blinking is something
that we have in common,
you broke the rules.
[MAVIS]
No, I didn't.
Actually, ever since
we started the game,
I haven't allowed myself
to blink a single time.
I think my eyes are
about to explode!
[YURI]
What? No! She can't be serious!
Wait. Don't freak out.
Just think. I've still
got a 50% chance at this.
Is she right or wrong?
Oh, man! She got me!
Whatever I say, I won't know
the truth! I'll be lying!
There is no way in hell
anyone could ever answer
a crazy question like that!
How come I never
thought of that?!
[cries]
[YURI] She did it.
I hate to admit defeat.
Oh, my poor, aching eyes.
[YURI] But this girl
is really something!
[PRECHT]
Yuri!
Do you mind explaining
what's going on in here?
Whoa. This library's
unbelievable!
We almost got rid of him
and his friends show up?
Oh, man. It's Precht and Warrod.
[PRECHT] Our work is done.
Let's get going.
[YURI]
What?
Did you guys find the orb?
I said I wouldn't tell.
[PRECHT]
We've located it, yes.
[MAVIS, YURI] You mean that
whole game was pointless?
[PRECHT] This is where
it should be, at least.
But it's been taken.
[PRECHT]
Somebody beat us to it.
I guess some other
treasure hunters
must've gotten to the thing
before we had a chance.
[PRECHT]
Let's head back to the mainland.
We're not givin' up on it.
Just gonna see if we can get
more intel back home.
Wait a minute.
I'm almost positive I can
tell you who's responsible
for the orb's disappearance.
[PRECHT]
Who's that?
[MAVIS]
Seven years ago, a wizard guild
by the name of Blue Skull
invaded the island and
plundered the village.
You're the first ones
to come here since then,
so they must've taken it.
[PRECHT]
It was a wizard guild?
That's not good news for us.
[PRECHT] Even still, we'll
have to pay them a visit.
Listen. Yuri, Precht,
and Warrod, right?
My name is Mavis Vermillion.
And for the past seven years,
I've been studying strategies
for taking on wizard guilds.
Together, we can beat them.
No, Mavis. You've got
to be kidding me.
I humbly ask you
take me with you.
The Tenrou Orb is the
symbol of this island.
My people have protected this
sacred relic for generations.
I must fix this.
The treasure belongs
to the island,
and it's my duty to
see it's returned.
Please don't.
Just to be clear,
we're treasure hunters.
Even if we do find the thing,
there's no guarantee we're just
gonna give it back to you.
Then you and I can have
another game of wits
whenever that time comes.
But right now, we share a
common goal of finding it.
Not to mention you
still have to make good
on the promise you made.
I wanna meet a real fairy!
[YURI]
Huh?!
That damned Yuri.
Is he seriously considering
letting that girl
tag along with us?
It may not be such a bad idea.
She's obviously one
smart little cookie.
It's kinda sad.
Living in solitude on
this island for so long...
It's quite fascinating.
So why don't you tell me why
you're really coming with us.
[MAVIS] To bring the Tenrou Orb
back to its rightful place.
I mean, you didn't even notice
it was stolen for seven years.
So it can't be all that
important to you.
We're just after it because
it's an S-class treasure.
Of course it's important.
I just never realized it before.
And to be totally honest,
this is a great chance to
finally see the outside world.
For me and Zera.
Who is that?
[MAVIS] C'mon, Zera. Stop
skulking around and say hello!
Please?
I guess I have to now.
She's a little on the shy side.
You don't have to make
excuses for me.
[YURI]
Uh...
Well, aren't you going
to pack your suitcase?
I never said I was
going with you!
And I'm definitely not leaving
with some creepy
treasure hunter.
Uh. That's all right.
This is probably the
most important decision
we've ever made.
It's a huge deal.
Whaddaya mean by that?
There's a whole world
waiting out there,
and we're never gonna
see it if we stay here.
It's scary, but we can't
hide from it forever.
[ZERA]
Fine. I'll go too.
Then it's settled.
We're both going with you!
[YURI]
Okay...
Hey, Mavis.
How old is Zera anyway?
He should know to never
ask a lady her age!
She's a teenager, just like us.
I don't really think I want this
guy to know very much about me.
Okay.
Very nice meet you, Zera.
This is going to be so much fun!
You don't have to worry.
Okay! Let our adventure begin!
[YURI]
I must admit,
I was charmed by this
mysterious little girl.
But if I knew then
what I know now,
I would've never agreed
to let her come along.
That one decision would've
changed everything.
Prevented all of this
heartache and pain.
[MAVIS] We sailed away from
the comfort and security
of the only home
I've ever known,
across the sea and
into the waiting world.
Creatures I'd only
read about in books
were right before my eyes.
I finally experienced what
life is like on the outside.
It's a place full
of incredible joy!
But when I learned
about the troubles
plaguing my new friends,
I had to do something.
It was finally time
for me to take action.
Next Time: "Treasure Hunt."
Adventure awaits right
below the surface!