[CHAPATI] It's over!
The winner of the Grand
Magic Games is Fairy Tail!
[ALL cheering]
Man, that sound
is incredible.
We can hear it
all the way from here.
This is awesome.
If they start cheering
any louder for us
I think the ground'll
start shaking.
Geez, would somebody
shut 'em up?
This noise is makin'
my wounds itch.
Now don't be like that.
They're cheers of celebration.
I'll bet you the master's
beside himself with excitement.
Auh.
Puttin' the old geezer aside.
This makes up for
seven years of humiliation
our guild mates endured.
My darling Gray.
We just have to go
on a victory date, okay?
Take me out!
You mean right now?
[LECTOR sobbing]
[CROWD cheering]
Just listen to this
crowd roaring its approval!
The mightiest guild
in Fiore, Fairy Tail,
is back with a vengeance!
Congratulations Maky.
[MATO] Oh wow!
They finished the final battle
without losing anyone! Huh?
[CHAPATI] Fairy Tail
has clawed its way from
a last-place start
to a first place upset!
[CHAPATI] And don't forget,
the upstart guild was
originally split into
two separate competing teams!
[YAJIMA] Even without the
participation of Natsu Dragneel,
an amazing sense of
solidarity allowed Fairy Tail
to triumph in the end.
[CHAPATI] I certainly agree!
Tell us, Mato,
what are your thoughts?
[MATO] Me? Well, yeah,
they really put on a show!
[FROSCH] Fairy Tail
is super cool, huh?
[ROGUE] Yeah. Heh.
I know we just lost,
but I feel happier now
than I ever have before.
That's good, Rogue.
Hey, Frosch. Listen.
[FROSCH] Yeah?
I want to change
and become the kind of man
who treasures his friends.
[FROSCH]
That's how I feel, too!
[HAPPY] The One
Who Closes the Gate!
[YAJIMA] This year's
games had too many
impressive battles to count!
[CHAPATI] Which fight did you
find most memorable, Mato?
Uh...
[YAJIMA] He's gone. Well,
maybe he had to take a leak.
[CHAPATI] Oh. Uh.
Well in that case,
what was your favorite
bout, Mr. Yajima?
[YAJIMA] Mirajane and
Jenny's sexy pose-off!
I haven't felt
that young in years.
[CHAPATI]
Well, this is awkward.
[GAJEEL] Guess it's over.
All that's left
is the celebration!
Hey Erza,
how's that leg?
It should be good as
new in a few days.
[LAXUS] Can't believe I'm sayin'
this, but, it's kinda strange
not havin'
"you-know-who" around,
hollerin', and makin' noise.
[GRAY] Yeah, I don't mind it.
[GAJEEL] He'd be extra
annoying after all that.
[ERZA chuckles]
Sounds about right.
By the way, did anyone see
their signal flare?
Nope. And I've been
keeping an eye out for it
this entire time,
well, except for when
Jura knocked me flat.
I didn't see one either.
I ain't worried.
Knowin' our Salamander,
he probably just
forgot to shoot the thing.
Signal flare?
[LECTOR] Whadaya think
they're talkin' about?
Tell me somethin'.
[GAJEEL grunts]
Oh, I know you ain't
talkin' to me, punk. Scram!
Calm down!
[STING] Sorry, but--
[GAJEEL and JUVIA] Huh?
Where's Natsu? Why wasn't
he in the fight today?
What's the deal?
Is Natsu hurt?
Is he gonna be okay?
[GRAY]
We're countin' on you guys.
You'd better
make it out of there.
Fire Dragon Roar!
Gravity zone!
It'll take a lot more than that
if you wanna
haul in this catch!
--Aah!
--Ya ok?
I am way too
hungry for this!
Paper Blizzard.
Purple Dance!
[LUCY] This again?
C'mon I'm getting bored here!
Okay then,
let's spice things up.
How about I start
by shredding your clothes?
Hey, wait a sec.
Let's not get crazy!
[yells]
I'm very sorry
about that, Princess,
but I felt I had to intervene
to preserve your dignity.
That was way too close.
Now die! Ugly brute!
Wow, the rage in your eyes
is utterly intoxicating.
Whaddya say we ditch
this fight and go get
a bite to eat
somewhere romantic?
Ugh. I asked you to die.
Why don't you
dissolve? Sploosh!
Please let us pass.
We've gotta find our friends!
[laughs] Sorry, no can do!
You and me are
gonna be hangin' out
for the rest
of your short life.
Your time is up!
Surrender now!
Just let us pass through!
[KAMA] Never! Not a single
one of you will escape.
Can you at least hear us out?
I am a peacekeeper of Fiore.
Those who threaten
the peace must die!
We aren't
threatening anything!
We're trying to help
Fiore and time is short.
[PANTHERLILY] Why do you
refuse to understand that?
A criminal will say
anything to escape justice.
[KAMA]
Your words are meaningless!
Oh, no. This is bad!
We can't let them
trap us in here like this.
If we don't do something
soon it'll be too late.
It'll happen again!
Oh Lucy,
are you feeling okay?
[FUTURE LUCY]
We're running out of time.
[CARLA] This future Lucy
said that in her time,
we were in the castle
when the disaster happened.
We've escaped
our prison, but...
...even if we
aren't behind bars,
we're still
trapped in the castle.
So we're in
just as much danger.
[MALE SOLDIER 190A]
Go men! Show them no mercy!
[MALE SOLDIER 190B]
Surround them!
[LOKE] More reinforcements?
We need to wrap this thing up!
Stay still for a sec.
And I will end
your miserable life.
A group of men are here
to punish us, Princess.
[LUCY] Yeah, I can see that!
Oh, no. My battle form!
Look at that. Now it'll be
easier to execute you!
[PANTHERLILY laughs nervously]
Err! You want an execution?
Well I'll give ya one!
[NATSU] I'll burn every
single one'a'ya to a crisp!
[MALE SOLDIER 190A] Steady men!
Hm?
What is it?
Did you see something?
Thought so.
Must've been my imagination.
Happy! Carla!
Get outta here and
find the rest of the guild!
[PANTHERLILY] Tell them
what's happened to us!
Aye, Sir!
We're on it!
[BOTH yell]
[UOSUKE] Nuh-uh!
Y'all gotta stay put, ya hear?
[HAPPY]
It's that weird guy again!
Nobody's gettin' outta
this castle, understand?
Huh?
Hey. Y'all? I'm caught
in someone's net!
[MALE SOLDIER 190E]
I can't move a muscle!
[MALE SOLDIER 190F]
Me neither! What's happening?
It's holdin' 'em down!
Is that some
kind of shadow magic?
[MALE SOLDIER 190G yells]
[MALE SOLDIER 190H]
What in the hell is going on?
[MALE SOLDIER 190I]
I dunno but it's bad!
What the heck?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What's happening?
That shadow is
swallowing our men!
Yeah. Is it a spell?
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS scream]
Neppa? This shadow is
haulin' me in!
We'll pull through,
just hang on!
[UOSUKE yells]
Why is this happening to us?
Please! Help!
Hold on! I'll save you!
No! This cannot be!
We, the Hungry Wolf Knights,
bested by a shadow?
How? Princess, I've failed you!
That... shadow.
[FUTURE LUCY] I've never
seen anything like it.
It didn't happen like this!
What's the heck's
goin' on here?
[JELLAL] I've got it!
Everything makes sense now.
[ULTEAR] What do you mean?
All of this time,
and the truth has been
right under our noses.
What is it, Jellal?
This Lucy from the future said
she arrived on July fourth.
But it was actually just
before midnight on the third.
Then she can't be
the source of the power
we've been sensing for years.
She only got here
a few days ago.
[JELLAL] Agreed. The taint
of Zeref we've sensed
for the past seven years
came from the Eclipse.
There's no doubt in my mind.
But this is different.
It's a person.
Because the Eclipse is a
product of the Book of Zeref,
its use comes with a price.
[JELLAL] All those who use it
bear the trace of his power.
Zeref.
[ULTEAR] The indomitable
wizard of darkness.
You guys are freaking me out.
I'm just as uneasy.
But right now we have to
put our focus elsewhere.
There's simply
too much at stake.
[MELDY] Right.
[JELLAL] If we assume that
this future Lucy has been
completely honest with us,
then she came into
our time on the third,
just before midnight.
If that's true,
then who did I see
earlier that evening?
Uh.
[DARTON] Hm?
Princess.
[HISUI gasps]
Arcadios, it's you!
I'm so glad you're all right!
[grunts] Colonel.
[DARTON] Please forgive
me for throwing you
into the Palace of Perdition.
It was a misunderstanding
on my part.
[ARCADIOS] You did
as you thought right,
I hold no grudge. The men
you have assembled here.
Have you already
informed them of
the Eclipse's
secondary purpose?
[HISUI] I have.
The rest of the garrison
is being informed of
the plan as we speak.
Hopefully that means
word will soon reach
the Hungry Wolf Knights as well.
The time traveler's
prediction about
the end of the games.
It came true.
We've no choice.
We'll switch to Eclipse Two.
It's our only chance
against what's coming.
Princess, am I to
understand that
you've abandoned our original
plan to go back in time
and defeat Zeref?
No, but right now
we have to focus on
the more imminent threat.
[HISUI gasps]
Colonel!
Huh?
A true knight must always
trust his master's words.
This is part of the code
I've sworn to live by.
I am duty-bound
to put my faith in you.
Which is why, I ask you
to slay me, Princess.
Huh?
[ARCADIOS] Since I cannot
repress the doubt within me,
there is but one recourse.
I must die.
For I've dishonored you.
[DARTON]
Arcadios! Have you gone mad?
[ARCADIOS grunts]
[DARTON gasps]
[ARCADIOS] Princess. There is
something I must ask you.
What is it, Arcadios?
What happened?
[HISUI]
What are you talking about?
[ARCADIOS] I have spoken
with your contact
that came from the future.
That person clearly has
no knowledge of Eclipse Two!
[HISUI gasps]
[ARCADIOS] They knew about
the impending apocalypse
but they shed tears
because they did not
know how to stop it!
That can't be.
They're the one who gave me
explicit instructions
on how to activate it.
So, you're claiming that this
person was feigning ignorance?
[ARCADIOS] I don't see
how that's possible.
I cannot think of a single
thing she'd have to gain
by lying to her friends!
[HISUI]
What? Did you say "she"?
The traveler from
the future who advised me.
That person was a man.
[ARCADIOS] Uh!
Whoever I saw on the evening
of the third wasn't her!
She didn't arrive until later!
[JELLAL] Which can
only mean that someone else
has used the Eclipse!
[HAPPY] All of
those royal soldiers.
[CARLA] They were
pulled into that shadow!
[PANTHERLILY] But why
didn't it target us?
Someone's inside.
Keep your guard up.
[MAN chuckles]
Okay, and who are you?
[MELDY] You seriously think
there's another person
from the future here?
[JELLAL] Yes, and they should
be easy to find because
they'll be swathed in that evil
power from using the Eclipse.
We know Lucy came back
to try and save us.
Question is...
why's the other person here?
[MAN] Shadows can
reach beyond the present
to both the past
and the future.
And into the hearts of men.
[MAN] It seems we meet again,
Natsu Dragneel.
[NATSU gasps]
I've traveled quite a ways
from the distant future.
I'm Rogue.
No way. How can you be Rogue?
The same one from Sabertooth?
[scoffs]
You came from the future too?
So I'm not the only one.
Why're you here?
[ARCADIOS] There are two who
have come from the future.
One of them is Lucy.
She came back in time
to warn her friends
of the impending doom.
And then there's another,
who came to tell the Princess
how to avert that disaster.
Both had the same
objective at heart.
They did what they could
to try and save the kingdom.
It's their only chance.
And if the future's
as bad as they say,
there could still be more.
[ARCADIOS gasps]
[HISUI] Take back your sword.
You'll need it
for the battle ahead.
I'm going to open the Eclipse.
I intend to save this kingdom.
That means drawing
a blade of my own.
The second time traveler.
What could be their goal?
[JELLAL] We have to hurry!
[LOKE] You took out
all of the royal soldiers.
Are you tryin' to help us?
[NATSU] You seem pretty
different than you were before.
[FUTURE LUCY huffs]
So why did you come back?
Just what do you want?
All I want...
is to use the Eclipse.
But what's that gonna do?
It can save us all,
if we tap into
its hidden power.
[FUTURE ROGUE] As you know,
it can be used for time travel.
But it can also
serve as an offensive weapon
known as the Eclipse Cannon.
That is the only chance
you have of defeating
the ten thousand dragons.
So then it's really possible.
We can win.
Well that sure makes
things nice and simple!
Glad we gotcha on our side.
Aw yeah! Let's go and
kill ourselves some dragons!
Does this mean
everything's gonna be okay?
'Fraid not. You see,
I've come from seven years
in the future.
A time when the
world as you know it
will have ceased to exist.
[FUTURE ROGUE] The dragons
will have destroyed everything
and rule over the ashes.
They're gonna take over?
But, what happened to the
people who survived the attack?
In my time not even ten percent
of the human race remains.
Furthermore...
[FUTURE ROGUE] Our Eclipse has
but a fraction of the power
that yours can wield.
Which means that this is
humanity's last chance.
We stop them now or die.
Seems pretty simple,
all we gotta do is
open the gate, and blow 'em up!
[NATSU] Let's get to it!
[FUTURE ROGUE] Seven years in
my past something happened.
Someone prevented
Eclipse Two from activating.
But how come?
Why would they do that?
[FUTURE ROGUE] Because of
that one person's actions,
the gate remained shut.
And humanity was left
defenseless against
ten thousand raging dragons.
[FUTURE ROGUE] This person let
ninety percent of humanity die.
So I've come back
to save those lives,
by eradicating theirs.
[CARLA] How barbaric!
Why don't you try explaining
the situation to them
before you resort to violence?
[PANTHERLILY] She's right.
There's no need for bloodshed.
A person's destiny is immutable.
Even if I did
persuade them somehow,
[FUTURE ROGUE] they would
still end up stopping Eclipse.
Fate has stolen
that choice from them.
Their future is set in stone.
They don't have a choice?
[FUTURE ROGUE] None of us
are stronger than fate.
The living remain,
and the dead are gone.
The one who
closed the gate before,
will always do the same.
As long as they're alive,
it's bound to happen again.
[NATSU] I don't have a clue what
you're talkin' about, buddy.
Spill it! Who's this person
you're after anyway?
[FUTURE ROGUE]
It's you...
Lucy Heartfilia!
[gasps]
[NATSU] Lucy!
[LUCY gasps]
[slow lub-dubs of a heartbeat]
Oh no! Are you okay?
No!
What? There's two?
How could this be?
[coughs]
Just hang on!
[HAPPY] Lucy!
I didn't do it.
I didn't close the gate.
I would never do that!
I know you didn't!
I promise, I won't either,
no matter what!
[LUCY] But why? Why didn't
you protect yourself?
[FUTURE LUCY]
You're part of my past.
If you were to die,
then I would die too.
In a way, dying is
the only way I can live.
It's so strange.
I never thought that
I'd die in my
own arms, you know?
It's kind of comforting.
No, don't talk like that.
You're gonna make it.
We won't let you die!
Can't we help? We could
use healing magic.
I'm afraid that
wound's too severe.
[CARLA]
There's nothing we can do.
[FUTURE LUCY]
Don't cry. It's okay.
I thought that
I'd never get to see
my friends again.
But I did, one last time.
And that's enough...
to make up for the hell
that I've been through.
Oh, Lucy. Please,
just try to hang in there,
we need you!
[FUTURE LUCY]
I'm not the Lucy you know.
I'm from a different time.
A whole other world.
There's no reason
for you to cry.
The me who lives in this time,
she gets to keep on
living with her friends.
So you don't need to be sad.
[HAPPY] But we are sad!
We don't care what world
you come from 'cause
no matter what anyone says
you're still our Lucy!
You're our friend
and we love you!
We don't ever wanna lose you!
So, of course we're sad,
how could we not be?
[HAPPY sobbing]
Hey. Could you let me
see your guild mark?
[FUTURE LUCY sobbing]
Where's yours?
What happened?
[LUCY] Hey Natsu, look!
Mirajane just put the official
Fairy Tail mark on my hand!
[grunts]
I just wish... I could've...
[FUTURE LUCY]
...had more adventures.
[LUCY sobbing]
[FUTURE LUCY]
Please. Protect the future.
How could she have forgotten
that she closed the gate?
I don't care about your gate!
I would never shut it
but you still--
How could you?
[FUTURE ROGUE] You say
that now, but you will.
You've done it before and
I know you will do it again.
[LUCY] I'm not gonna
shut the damn gate!
Why do you keep accusing me?
Cut it out! I haven't
done anything to you!
The gate will be closed.
There's no way to prevent it.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Not while you're still alive.
You heard my future self say
that she did no such thing.
Tell me, why would
I lie to myself?
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Her delusions are irrelevant!
Every choice you think you
have has been decided by fate!
Then I'm gonna turn fate
into a pile of ashes!
[NATSU] I ain't lettin'
anybody steal Lucy's future.
Not while I'm alive!
[FUTURE LUCY]
Please. Protect the future.
I will, I promise!
[HAPPY] Hey Natsu,
are you seein' this?
It looks like
there's a ton of wizards
grouped up in the city square!
[NATSU] Oh yeah. Apparently
a bunch of the guilds
decided to hook up and
go kick some dragon butt!
[HAPPY] Good luck, everybody!
[NATSU] Whaddya say we leave
'em to those guys for now,
'lil buddy? We've got
other butts to kick!
Like this guy's!
[HAPPY] Let's do it!
We made a promise to Lucy
and we're not gonna break it!
[NATSU and HAPPY] Next time:
Natsu versus Rogue!
[NATSU] We will
protect the future!
You just watch us, Lucy.
[HAPPY] Yeah, there's no way
future Rogue gettin' past us!