[NATSU]
Previously on Fairy Tail...
[LUCY] Somehow, I fell asleep
and lost Cana. When I woke up,
I had one of the Seven Kin
of Purgatory standing over me.
[HAPPY] Natsu and I
rushed in to save her,
but he couldn't
really do that much.
I gotta say, it was pretty lame.
[NATSU] Hey watch it, pal!
I still managed to make up
a sweet, new technique to fry
that big dumpling to a crisp!
[LUCY]
Yeah, by frying me first!
♪
[NATSU] Come on guys, put your
backs into it, would ya?
[LUCY] I'm afraid I'm gonna
pull your stupid head off!
[HAPPY]
Aye!
Natsu... Do ya think maybe
you can just blast the rocks
away with your fire?!
Oh yeah!
Jeez!
[NARRATOR] Once again,
light and darkness collide
in their eternal struggle
for the future of mankind.
Which one will fill
the skies of tomorrow?
The warm glow of fairies...
Or the cold gloom of demons?
Blades of magic power?!
She can summon weapons
just like I do?!
Go.
Nice try but your attacks
will have no effect on me...!
My body's made entirely of--
[ERZA]
Juvia!
[JUVIA] I don't understand...!
How was she able to injure me?!
When my blades
strike they stimulate
the enemy's pain receptors...
One might say they're
"blades of sensation."
Such power...
I see... You're one of the Seven
Kin of Purgatory, aren't you?
[MELDY] I was not sent here
to answer questions...
Just eliminate the enemy... That
is the mission I was given.
[HAPPY]
Dead-End of Despair!
[running]
[NATSU]
He's gone!
Are you sure Zeref
was right here?
Then they must've
gotten to him already.
They were definitely here...
But she must've done
something to mask the smell,
so I can't tell
which way they went.
Don't forget about Cana...
she's gone, too.
[NATSU] And high-kicking's
gonna help us, how?
[LUCY]
Gimme that doll, fleabag!
This is gettin' old...
I'm takin' a nap.
We don't have time
for that right now,
and as much as I'm
worried about Cana...
We need to deal with
this Zeref creep first.
I'm sorry Lucy...
I'll never do it again!
[LUCY] From what I understand...
Grimoire Heart's plan for
taking over the world completely
revolves around Zeref.
Why do the bad guys always
wanna take over the world...?
It sounds like such a huge pain
in the neck if you ask me.
If I took over the world,
I'd make sure there were
yummy fish everywhere!
[LUCY] Well, I don't think
that's what these guys
are planning.
Let's go find 'em...
We gotta settle the score
for what they did to Gramps.
When I get my hands
on those scumbags...
they're gonna wish
they never set foot
on Fairy Tail's sacred ground.
How did they get here...?
Hey, wait...
They must've traveled on some
kind of ship to get here, right?
And that dark-haired woman said
she was planning to take Zeref
back with her to see
her master, didn't she?
I'll bet whatever ship they came
in on is anchored somewhere
near the island.
That's gotta be where
she's taking him...
Happy... do you think you can
fly around and look for it?
You know I would... But now...
I'm kinda out of power... sorry.
You're all out...? So you're
nothin' but a talking cat?
Well, in that case...
I guess we should head back and
check on Gramps and Wendy...
Maybe Carla and Lily can look.
[NARRATOR]
One of the many tunnels
that wind through
Tenrou Island...
Also known as Route E.
[CANA] If Lucy was right...
then I should be able to find
Mavis's grave
somewhere down here.
I'm gonna be
the first one to find it...
I'm gonna be the one who
passes the trial this year...
I'll finally make S-Class rank.
Then I can look him
in the eye...
and I can tell him the truth...
But I can't do it until
I'm an S-Class wizard.
Is that it?
Oh yeah... Splitting up was
an absolutely brilliant idea.
I haven't run into a single
person yet, friend or foe.
I wonder what
Cana's problem is anyway,
I've never seen her
in such a rotten mood...
I guess she could really
use a drink or something.
Wait a sec...
Ya know, I honestly don't think
I've seen her touch a drop
of anything the entire time
we've been on this island...
Maybe she's goin' cold turkey.
[leaves rustling]
[GRAY]
Someone's coming.
[ULTEAR] It won't be long
before you're restored
to your rightful place
as ruler... Lord Zeref.
[GRAY]
That's Zeref...?!
He looks like he can't
even stand up on his own.
[GRAY]
What?!
No... She's with Grimoire Heart.
But she looks just like her.
Just like my master... Ur.
What's her story...?
Who in the hell is she?
[evil chuckling]
[HADES] This is truly
entertaining indeed.
[BLUENOTE] I'm pleased to find
you in such high spirits...
my Lord.
[evil chuckling]
[HADES] Of my elite Seven Kin,
three have already been bested.
It would appear that Makarov...
has trained all of
his children well.
[BLUENOTE]
Should I go down there?
[HADES] Not now...
I'm afraid that this is not
your battle to fight.
Stand down, Bluenote.
[BLUENOTE] I can't let those
beneath me have all the fun,
can I...?
After all, I can't risk
my body going soft.
[HADES]
That is quite enough!
[BLUENOTE]
What's the matter...?
If we submerge the ship,
they'll have no hope finding us.
Makarov's followers will
surely try to come aboard,
unaware of the horrors
that await them...
Never suspecting they've
ventured into the Devil's heart
until it's too late.
[BLUENOTE] You'd rather
have your prey fling itself
into your gullet?
I prefer the thrill of the hunt.
Some other time perhaps...
I don't want you throwing
my plans into disarray...
So you'll remain here.
[BLUENOTE] Almost half of
your "prized" fighting force
are down.
If one more of them
should fall... I'm going in.
I'm ready to fly.
Bluenote Stinger is with them?!
[LAHAR] Legend has it,
that during the Cabria War,
he singlehandedly wiped
out Commander Gohra's
Blue Dragoon Regiment.
It's said his power
is so terrifying...
every single blade of grass
he treads upon dies.
They've got someone
that strong...?
This is going to be
even worse than we feared.
I'm afraid so... And we
have no hope defeating them
on our own...
Neither does Fairy Tail.
[LAHAR]
I'll contact HQ immediately...
They will advise
on our next move.
Give me some time first!
Look here!
Doranbolt's vanished!
Not only that, but he took the
communication lacrima with him!
How are we gonna contact
headquarters now, sir?
What exactly are you planning to
do...? Whose side are you on?
[NARRATOR] In a secluded
spot on Tenrou Island,
Fairy Tail's master,
Makarov, lies motionless...
Gravely wounded
from his fierce battle
with Grimoire Heart's
master, Hades.
Unable to heal him,
Wendy and the others anxiously
await Natsu's return.
[NATSU]
Wendy!
You made it back...!
Did you find anything?
[LUCY]
Is Master doing any better?
[CARLA] I can't say his
condition has improved.
[PANTHERLILY] Although it would
seem that the master's wounds
are quite serious, for some
reason I don't feel as though
his life is truly in danger.
[CARLA] Perhaps it has something
to do with this island
being considered sacred ground.
The traitor's returned!
Where'd you run off to,
whoever-you-are?
That's Mest, the spy
from the Magic Council.
To be quite honest,
my name is Doranbolt.
What are you doing here?
[DORANBOLT]
Please don't be afraid, Wendy...
I guess you could say
I'm on a rescue mission.
[DORANBOLT]
I can use my magic
to transport your guild
members somewhere safe.
I'll get you as far away from
this island as possible!
But first I need to
know where everybody is
in order to do that.
We don't need
your help, okay pal?
What makes you think
we'd trust anyone who's acting
in the interest of
the Magic Council?
This is our problem, not yours;
and we are more than capable of
taking care of it by ourselves.
Listen to me...
I guarantee once the council
finds out what's going on here,
they'll do whatever it
takes to neutralize the threat!
You mean they'll blast us
with Etherion again?!
Once was enough...
Like, seriously.
What's Etherion...? Do you know?
I don't have any firsthand
experience with it...
but apparently, it's extremely
powerful destruction magic.
Yeah, and the Magic Council
used it on us before when we
were in the Tower of Heaven.
[PANTHERLILY] Really? How
did you manage to survive?
[HAPPY] Well, it's kind of
a long story, actually...
A bunch of other
crazy stuff happened,
and it was all absorbed
inside this huge lacrima.
[CARLA] Yet another example
of this guild running into
major trouble wherever they go.
But if they decide to fire it
while we're all on the island...
Who knows what kind of damage
it might cause this time?
Then we'll have to take care of
business before that happens.
Your master's been defeated...!
And Grimoire Heart's got
incredibly powerful wizards
on their side...!
There's no way
you can beat them!
Oh yeah...? So we should just
blow up the whole island, huh?!
We can't let that happen!
Our guild considers this
sacred ground because our
first master is buried here!
We have to try to protect it!
Here's a message for the
council... Tell them they had
better back off... If they
don't, they're gonna be sorry.
Yeah...! Tell 'em Fairy Tail
can always take care of itself!
Are you threatening the Magic
Council...?! Some lowly wizards?
[NATSU] You've got
a lot to learn, man...
Whether it's Grimoire Heart
or the Magic Council,
Fairy Tail doesn't back down.
You attack us, it's gonna
be your last mistake...!
We'll put you deep
in the ground!
[WENDY] The sky... It looks
like there's a storm coming.
Juvia!
[ERZA] Although we don't have
much magic energy left after
the S-Class trials...
we have the advantage...
A two-on-one battle
shouldn't be this difficult.
Number thirteen.
Don't worry... I can handle her!
The wizard known
as Erza Scarlet...
You're assigned number four.
And what does this ranking mean?
Your priority...
It is the order in which
you should be eliminated!
Utter nonsense.
It is necessary.
Tell me why you're
going after Juvia!
Number thirteen
is worthless trash...
so I want to get her
out of the way.
[JUVIA]
I won't last much longer...
Please stay strong...! Juvia!
[MELDY]
Number three is Gildarts...
But it appears he's
no longer on the island.
Number Two is Makarov...
But Master Hades has
already defeated him.
Master Makarov is number two?
You mean to tell me there's
a higher priority target
than the master of our guild?
Number one, is that man...
Gray Fullbuster.
Why him?
Why choose Gray?
[MELDY] Because... he has
her blood on his hands.
Ultear's mother... died
because of him...! That man...
Can never be forgiven for
the pain he caused Ultear!
When I find him, I'll
tear him limb from limb!
[ERZA]
She's gone insane!
[JUVIA]
Now you've done it...
If you dare carry out that
threat... I swear to you...
You will never live
to speak of it.
What's wrong with her...?
She's only number thirteen.
Wait... Try to calm down Juvia.
How can I do that...? She
plans to kill my beloved
over pure nonsense... And you
think I should remain calm?
[ERZA]
No... But I, uh...
I'm afraid there's no way
that's going to happen; not now.
You're gonna pay for even
thinking of hurting him!
[JUVIA]
Water Nebula!
[ERZA] Amazing... She's a
completely different woman
from the one I faced before.
She's able to channel her
emotions into a massive
flow of strength.
That... is her true power...
Erza, listen...! go ahead; I can
handle this battle on my own.
Find the others and
make sure they're all safe,
especially my darling Gray.
I certainly will...
Best of luck to you.
[MELDY]
Get back here, number four!
Maguilty Rays!
[JUVIA]
Water Slicer!
The storm is intensifying.
[GRAY] Where's she taking
him...? Back to their base...?
To Grimoire Heart's master?
[RUSTYROSE] The sky's tears
wash away my own desires...
Its eyes turn cloudy with
the looming darkness.
[AZUMA] Are those the lyrics
of a song... Rusty?
In a way... Music to
accompany my drum.
So... Speaking of drums,
it looks as though
you've taken a beating.
Proof that I battled
with a skilled warrior.
Oh, did you now...? I find
that hard to believe...
There doesn't appear to be
a single one in the bunch.
My war drum beats a strong
and steady rhythm.
You'd be wise
to take them seriously...
They are quite formidable.
Their power doesn't
rely solely on magic...
Their hearts and conviction
are weapons enough.
They use Conviction
as a weapon...?
Well... That's not unlike
our blossoming flower.
[MELDY]
I find it strange...
We both speak of the
same Gray, and yet...
One is boiling with hate...
And the other one with love.
Although it's the same person...
You'd think we were
discussing two different men.
It's natural... Not
everyone feels the same...
That's part of being human.
This is an amazing
stroke of luck.
I've come here on a mission
to kill Gray Fullbuster...
And right away,
I've encountered a person
who harbors
strong feelings for him.
What do you mean?
Your deep feelings of love for
Gray... will be what kills him!
Now, Juvia... Enjoy your
brief journey to heaven...
before you descend into
the depths of hell.
Picture your beloved...
Feel him inside your heart.
[JUVIA]
My darling Gray...
Just like that...!
My Sensory Link will bind you!
What is that...?
It's hurting my arm!
This is Lost Magic...
Maguilty Sense.
[JUVIA]
What have you done to me?
I've linked your sensations to
those of your 'beloved Gray.'
It can only be accomplished
between those who have
strong feelings.
You really mean it...?!
My darling Gray and I
are finally living
our lives as one?!
Only your senses.
What's happening to me?
Why does my face feel
so flushed all of a sudden?!
Doesn't it feel nice...?
your senses are now
completely intertwined.
Oh yes, it does...!
It feels so amazing I can
hardly contain myself...!
[MELDY] However... This means...
he also shares your pain!
[GRAY yells]
He too, will experience all
of the pain that I'm prepared
to put you through.
[JUVIA] What...?! You would use
my love to cause Gray... Pain?!!
[JUVIA]
Sierra!
But how...?! Her magic
power has increased!
I underestimated her ability...
She can channel her
feelings into strength.
[MELDY]
Then I'll do the same...!
I'll show her the
power of what I feel!
Now...! I'll add one more with
three-spread sensory link!
Why is my attack
hurting me, too?
[grunting]
Damn...! Where is all
this pain coming from?
[MELDY] For Ultear's sake...
I would gladly give my life...
I would make that sacrifice.
You are the link
between me and him...
You've allowed me
to connect to my target...
With the spell I've cast,
me, you, and your dear,
beloved Gray...
are all one...
all our senses have merged.
And if one of us were
to die in this battle...
Gray will die as well.
It'll be the end
to all of our lives...
No... The end to all
of our suffering.
♪
[HAPPY] Love is caring for
someone... Sharing your heart
and making a cozy place for them
to curl up in your soul...
Love is like a river filled with
fish that feeds your spirit,
with lots of yummy mackerel...!
Or like a warm saucer of milk,
filled with the creamy goodness
two people share when they're
crazy for each other...!
Two drums beating in rhythm!
Or the loudest band in
the world, rockin' out!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next Time:
Tears of Love and Vitality!
[NATSU]
You kinda went nuts there, pal!
[HAPPY] No I didn't! I'm just
full of all this poetry
and it needs to get out.
[NATSU] Oh yeah...?
Well if you ask me,
that's not all you're full of.