- Zero:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy: IT TOOK ALL
OUR MAGIC ENERGY.
BUT AFTER COUNTLESS BATTLES,
WE FINALLY DEFEATED EVERY LAST
MEMBER OF THE ORACION SEIS.
- Happy: LITTLE DID WE KNOW THAT
WOULD UNLEASH BRAIN'S ALTER EGO,
MASTER ZERO.
WISH WE COULD REPLENISH
OUR ENERGY SOMEHOW,
'CAUSE THIS GUY'S GONNA
BE HARD TO BEAT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HOW LONG?
I SIMPLY CAN'T HELP
BUT ASK MYSELF
HOW LONG MUST I CONTINUE
TO FIGHT THE UNENDING WRONGS
IN THIS WORLD?
- IS THAT ERZA?
- I FOUND YOU.
- LOOK WHO'S HERE.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- DO I KNOW YOU?
- I KNEW IT.
HE DOESN'T REMEMBER ME.
- IT ISN'T PERSONAL.
HE'S JUST NOT HIMSELF.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT SEEMS HE'S UNABLE
TO REMEMBER EITHER OF US.
- HE'S LOST HIS MEMORY.
I SEE.
SO THAT'S WHY.
- ( Happy speaking )
- YOUR NAME IS WENDY MARVEL?
I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW YOU.
- YOU'VE LOST YOUR MEMORY?
IF THAT'S THE CASE, THEN YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN HOW TO STOP NIRVANA,
HAVEN'T YOU?
- NO, I TRIED.
I FAILED.  MY SELF-DESTRUCTION
MAGIC CIRCLE DIDN'T WORK.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE
I CAN DO NOW.
I'M SORRY.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- YOU CAN'T GIVE UP THAT EASILY.
OUR GUILD IS IN DANGER OF BEING
DESTROYED AT ANY MOMENT.
DON'T TURN YOUR BACK
ON OUR COMRADES.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WE CAN DO.
- ( explosion )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- I ASK THAT YOU
PLEASE REMAIN CALM.
DON'T YOU SEE, THERE'S NO
ESCAPING THE FATE BEFORE US?
ON THIS DAY,
WE SHALL BE PUNISHED
FOR OUR NABURA HEAVY SINS.
- ( laughing )
DESTROY JUSTICE AND DECENCY.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- THAT'S CAIT'S SHELTER.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
SO MUCH LIGHT AND MAGIC POWER.
HE'S GOING TO FIRE NIRVANA.
- NO.  THE GUILD.
- PLEASE, NO!
- ( Zero laughing )
- WHAT?
- ( clamoring )
- IT FLEW RIGHT BY.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( shouting ) MAN!  MAN!  MAN!
MAN!  MAN!  MAN!  MAN!  MAN!
( winces )
- SOMETHING STRUCK NIRVANA'S
LEG, BUT WHAT WAS IT?
- ( gasps ) NO WAY.
- OH, WOW.
- THE MAGIC BOMBER
CHRISTINA SAVES THE DAY.
- IS IT AN ALLY?
- Hibiki: DO YOU READ ME?
SOMEONE ANYONE, RESPOND.
PLEASE LET ME KNOW
THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
- I KNOW THAT VOICE.
IT'S HIBIKI.
- YEAH.
- ERZA AND WENDY,
GOOD TO KNOW YOU'RE
ALIVE AND WELL.
- IN CASE YOU WERE WONDERING,
I'M ALIVE BUT NOT QUITE WELL.
- MASTER ICHIYA,
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I NEVER EXPECTED TO SEE
THE MAGIC BOMBER FLY AGAIN.
- Carla: NOR DID I.
CERTAINLY NOT, AFTER WE WATCHED
THE ORACION SEIS SHOOT
HER DOWN.
- Wendy: HOW'D YOU GET
HER FLYING AGAIN?
- HARD WORK
AND LOTS OF IT.
FOR A GROUP OF WIZARDS
WHO BARELY KNOW EACH OTHER,
WE'RE PRETTY GOOD AT WORKING
TOGETHER TO GET THE JOB DONE.
CHRISTINA LOST ONE OF HER
WINGS WHEN SHE WAS SHOT DOWN,
SO LYON'S USING HIS
ICE MAKE MAGIC TO REPLACE IT.
- ( grunts ) THIS IS HARDER THAN
I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
- YOU'LL SEE ON THE BOW,
SHERRY'S COMBINING HER
MARIONETTE MAGIC
WITH REN'S AIR MAGIC TO KEEP
THE DAMAGED HULL INTACT.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT I'VE EVER
WORKED WITH ANYTHING
QUITE THIS BIG.
- RIGHT? I'M JUST GLAD
IT'S NOT AS HEAVY AS IT LOOKS.
- OUR ATTACK ON NIRVANA
WAS THANKS TO
EVE'S SNOW MAGIC.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- I USED IT TO FUSE A COUPLE
OF CHRISTINA'S MAGIC BOMBS
TOGETHER.
WHEN FIRED, THEY DID VERY
LITTLE DAMAGE TO NIRVANA.
EVEN THOUGH,
THEY'RE SO POWERFUL.
THAT TOOK THE LAST
OF MY MAGIC ENERGY.
( groans )
- Hibiki: EVE.
- WE'VE GOTTA STAY STRONG.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
I CAN KEEP THIS UP.
- DON'T CRACK.
JUST A LITTLE MORE.
WE OWE YOU ONE.
- BECAUSE OF YOU,
MY GUILD IS SAFE.
THANK YOU.
- I'M SURE YOU CAN TELL
THAT EVERYONE HERE
IS RUNNING LOW ON MAGIC ENERGY
RIGHT NOW.
I'M AFRAID WE CAN'T ATTACK
FROM THE SHIP ANYMORE.
POWER'S TOO LOW.  JUST FLYING
THIS FAR WAS HARD ENOUGH.
- DON'T WORRY,
WE'RE GONNA BE FINE.
LISTEN UP.
THERE'S ONE LAST THING.
A LITTLE BIT OF GOOD NEWS.
I FINALLY FOUND WHAT I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR IN THE ARCHIVE.
I KNOW HOW TO STOP NIRVANA.
- Erza:
PLEASE. TELL US.
- YOU KNOW THE SIX APPENDAGES
WE THOUGHT WERE LEGS?
WELL, THEY AREN'T.
THEY'RE PIPES.
APPARENTLY, THEY SUCK MAGIC
ENERGY OUT OF THE EARTH,
WHICH THEN IS USED
TO POWER NIRVANA.
AT THE BASE OF EACH LEG IS
A LACRIMA THAT CONTROLS
THE SUPPLY OF MAGIC ENERGY.
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
IF ALL SIX LACRIMA ARE
DESTROYED SIMULTANEOUSLY,
IT WILL WREAK HAVOC
ON NIRVANA'S CONTROL SYSTEM
THEREFORE FORCING IT
TO SHUT DOWN.
THEY MUST BE DESTROYED
AT ONCE.
OR THE OTHER FIVE WILL
SIMPLY REPAIR THE DAMAGED ONE.
- SIMULTANEOUSLY DESTROY
SIX LACRIMA?
HOW DO WE DO THAT?
- IF I COULD,
I'D MAINTAIN TELEPATHY
TO TIME OUT THE STRIKE.
TRY THIS.
I'LL GIVE EACH OF GUYS YOU
A SYNCED TIMER.
I'M UPLOADING IT TO YOU NOW.
BUT LISTEN, GUYS,
IT HAS TO BE PRECISE.
- TWENTY MINUTES?
THAT'S WHEN NIRVANA WILL
BE FULLY CHARGED
AND READY
TO FIRE AGAIN.
- WE HAVE TO DESTROY ALL SIX
AT ONCE.
- MAN.
- IF ANYBODY CAN DO IT,
IT'S YOU GUYS.
I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
- CARE TO WAGER A BET?
- WHO'S THAT?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- IT'S THAT CREEPY BRAIN GUY.
- HOW WAS HE ABLE
TO HIJACK MY TELEPATHY?
- I AM ZERO.
MASTER OF THE ORACION SEIS.
BRAIN IS NO MORE.
- I DIDN'T KNOW THAT THOSE
BONEHEADS HAD A MASTER.
- FIRST OF ALL,
ALLOW ME TO COMMEND YOU.
YOU FOOLED ME.
I NEVER SUSPECTED THERE MIGHT BE
OTHER WIZARDS CAPABLE
OF ARCHIVE MAGIC LIKE BRAIN.
- HE USED ARCHIVE?
THAT MUST'VE BEEN HOW HE FOUND
OUT ABOUT NIRVANA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- NOW HEED MY WORDS,
WIZARDS OF LIGHT.
I AM GOING TO OBLITERATE
EVERYTHING YOU HOLD DEAR.
I'VE ALREADY BEGUN BY DESTROYING
THREE OF YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS,
A DRAGON SLAYER,
AN ICE WIZARD
AND A CELESTIAL WIZARD.
( laughing ) AND A CAT.
- HE GOT NATSU AND THE OTHERS?
- WHAT'D THEY EVER DO TO YOU?
DID I HEAR YOU SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT DESTROYING NIRVANA'S
LACRIMA SIMULTANEOUSLY?
WELL, YOU CAN TRY.
BUT I'M STANDING RIGHT IN FRONT
OF ONE OF THEM,
AND I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF LEAVING.
( laughs )
AS LONG AS I'M HERE,
IT'LL BE IMPOSSIBLE
TO DESTROY ALL SIX AT ONCE.
- ( grunts )
- OW!
OUR TELEPATHIC CONNECTION'S
BEEN CUT OFF.
- THOUGH IT SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE,
WE CAN DESTROY ALL SIX AT ONCE.
WE MUST SPLIT UP
AND ATTACK INDIVIDUALLY.
AND HOPE THAT WE ALL STRIKE
AT THE SAME TIME.
EACH WIZARD HAS A ONE-IN-SIX
CHANCE OF RUNNING INTO ZERO.
UNFORTUNATELY,
ERZA'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS ANY REAL CHANCE
AGAINST HIM.
- EXCUSE ME, I THINK YOU'RE
FORGETTING SOMETHING,
LIKE BASIC MATH.
WE DON'T HAVE SIX WIZARDS
WITH ENOUGH MAGIC ENERGY
TO GO THROUGH
WITH YOUR PLAN.
- ( gasps )
BUT THAT MEANS.
OH, NO!
I CAN'T FIGHT.
I'M SORRY.  I CAN'T HELP YOU.
- WE CAN'T DO IT ON OUR OWN.
IS THERE ANYONE ELSE
STRONG ENOUGH TO HELP US?
- Ichiya:
YES, MY HONEY.
I'M ABLE-BODIED
AND AT YOUR SERVICE.
ALTHOUGH I AM TIED UP RIGHT NOW.
- MASTER ICHIYA.  THAT'S THREE.
WHO ELSE?
OH, NO.
HEY, I'M ALMOST OUT OF ENERGY.
WE GOTTA HURRY, YOU GUYS.
- WE NEED THREE MORE PEOPLE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMEONE ELSE.
CAN ANYONE HELP?
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
CHRISTINA'S LOSING ALTITUDE.
- ( grunts )
NO, I'M COMPLETELY
DRAINED OF ENERGY.
I'VE FAILED.
- ( grunts )
I CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE.
I'M SORRY.
( panting )
- SHERRY!
- CHRISTINA'S LOSING ALTITUDE.
- GRAY, GET UP.
YOU MUST.
THINK OF UR.
DON'T LET HER DOWN.
YOU MUST KEEP FIGHTING.
DON'T LET THESE GUYS
GET THE BEST OF YOU.
- I'VE ALWAYS HATED YOU,
LUCY.
YOU THINK YOU'RE SO CUTE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU'LL NEVER COMPARE TO ME.
YOU'RE AN AIR-HEADED CRYBABY.
THERE'S ONE THING I CAN SAY.
YOU ALWAYS GIVE IT YOUR ALL.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD REALLY
CARE WHETHER YOU DIED.
BUT I WAS WRONG, LUCY.
PLEASE, YOU HAVE TO RESPOND.
- ( loud bang)
- ( shudders )
- NATSU.
- RESPOND, TOMCAT.
- Erza: NATSU.
- ( grunting )
- CAN YOU HEAR OUR VOICES?
IF YOU CAN, PLEASE RESPOND.
- YEAH, WE HEAR YOU.
- NATSU.
- DESTROY ALL SIX
LACRIMA AT ONE TIME.
- MAN.
- SO WHO'S FIGHTING ZERO?
'CAUSE WE'D LIKE ANOTHER
CRACK AT HIM.  RIGHT, BOYS?
- EIGHTEEN MINUTES LEFT.
WE'VE GOTTA HURRY.
WE OWE IT TO CARLA AND WENDY
TO PROTECT THEIR GUILD.
- GUYS, MY TELEPATHY'S
ABOUT TO CUT OUT.
A WHILE AGO, I UPLOADED A MAP
TO EACH OF YOUR MINDS.
I NUMBERED THE LACRIMA
SO YOU COULD FIND THEM.
EVERYBODY CHOOSE A NUMBER,
OKAY?
THEN SPLIT UP--
- ( explosion )
- ARE YOU OKAY?  SHERRY!
YOU'VE PUSHED YOURSELF
TOO HARD.
- I'LL TAKE ONE.
- TWO.
- GUESS I'LL TAKE THREE.
PLEASE DON'T LET ZERO BE THERE.
- THEN I SHALL TAKE NUMBER FOUR.
I CAN TELL IT'S CLOSEST TO ME,
THANKS TO THE SMELL
OF ITS PARFUM.
- YOU MEAN, BECAUSE YOU
SEE IT ON THE MAP?
- MY HONEY, WHY DO YOU INSIST
ON MAKING A FOOL OUT OF ME?
- I CAN TAKE NUMBER FIVE.
ERZA, GUESS YOU'RE
FEELING BETTER, HUH?
YEAH, IT'S ALL THANKS
TO YOU GUYS.
- THAT LEAVES ME WITH--
- YOU'RE LEFT WITH NUMBER SIX.
- WHOSE VOICE DID I HEAR JUST
NOW? IS SOMEONE THERE WITH YOU?
- NATSU HASN'T BEEN MADE AWARE
OF YOUR SITUATION YET.
HE STILL THINKS YOU'RE
THE ENEMY.
SO TRY TO KEEP QUIET.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- WE LOST OUR CONNECTION.
- THAT MEANS WE LOST HIBIKI.
- ( crying )
- WE'VE SIX WIZARDS NOW.
LET'S GET THE BALL ROLLING.
- OKAY GUYS, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE
GOT THE SIX PEOPLE WE NEED.
LET'S GO AND IF YOU RUN INTO
ZERO, TAKE THAT JERK DOWN.
'CAUSE WE'RE ALL GONNA BE TOO
BUSY DESTROYING THOSE LACRIMA.
- ( grunts )
MAN!  MAN!  MAN!  MAN--
UGH!  OW!  COME ON, ICHIYA.
GOTTA STAY SMOOTH.
I HAVE TO MAKE IT
TO LACRIMA NUMBER FOUR.
( panting )
EVERYBODY'S COUNTING ON ME.
THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO
IS LET MY NEW COMRADES DOWN.
( panting )
I'M NOT OUT OF BREATH.
I GOT THIS.  I MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT I'M STILL A YOUNG MAN, MAN!
- FANCY MEETING YOU HERE,
BRAT.
YOU LOOKING FOR A FIGHT?
YOU FOUND ONE.
- I WONDER WHICH ONE OF US WILL
MAKE IT OUT OF HERE ALIVE.
ME OR YOU?
- I BET ZERO'S
AT LACRIMA NUMBER ONE.
- THAT'S WHERE NATSU'S HEADED.
- HE'S GOT A NOSE LIKE NO OTHER.
HE MUST'VE CHOSEN KNOWING ZERO
WOULD BE THERE.
- WE GOTTA GET OVER THERE
AND HELP HIM.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER MAYBE--
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE NATSU.
TRY NOT TO WORRY.
HE CAN HANDLE IT ON HIS OWN.
- NATSU.
- LET'S SPLIT UP
AND GET TO OUR POSTS.
I'VE GOT NUMBER FIVE
AND YOU'VE GOT NUMBER SIX, OKAY?
- ( shudders )
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, I-- ( grunts )
I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
( groans ) NATSU...
DRAGNEEL.
- IMPRESSIVE.  YOU'RE MUCH MORE
AGILE THAN THE LAST TIME WE MET.
DARK CAPRICCIO!
AS YOU CAN SEE,
I'M TWICE AS STRONG AS BRAIN.
- UGH!
- ( laughing )
( continues laughing )
YOU WERE WONDERING
WHO WILL MAKE IT OUT ALIVE.
I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT IT'LL BE ME.
- FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
( grunting )
NO.
- HMM...
I MUST SAY I'M SURPRISED
YOU WERE ABLE
TO STOP A PIERCING SPELL.
WHO'S THERE?
- JELLAL!
- WELL, HELLO.
I TAKE IT YOUR MEMORY
HAS RETURNED?
- ( growling )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: NOW THAT WE KNOW HOW
TO STOP NIRVANA,
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME WE GO
ON A RAMPAGE, DON'T YOU?
- Happy: AYE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PROBLEM:
EVERYBODY'S USED UP
THEIR MAGIC ENERGY
AND NOW THEY'RE
ALL TOO WEAK TO RAMPAGE.
- Natsu: THEY'VE GOTTA HAVE SOME
FIGHTING SPIRIT LEFT IN 'EM.
AW, YEAH.
I'M ALL FIRED UP.
- Happy: YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES I'M JEALOUS OF
YOUR SIMPLEMINDEDNESS.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: THIS MIGHT BE YOUR ONLY
CHANCE TO SHOW OFF FOR CARLA.
- Happy: OH, YEAH!
NOW I'M ALL FIRED UP.
- Natsu: WHAT WERE YOU SAYING
ABOUT SIMPLEMINDEDNESS, HAPPY?