- HEY, GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
WE WERE ATTACKED
BY A RIVAL GUILD
CALLED PHANTOM LORD.
AND THEY TOTALLY DESTROYED
OUR MEETING HALL.
WE'VE NEVER BEEN
ON GOOD TERMS WITH THEM,
BUT THEY WENT TOO FAR
WHEN THEY ATTACKED
LEVY'S TEAM
AND KIDNAPPED LUCY.
NOW THE MASTER'S ANGRY.
HE'S DECLARED WAR AGAINST
THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( man groans )
- FAIRY TAIL'S COME CALLING!
- LET'S GET 'EM!
- ( all shouting )
- ( Happy speaking )
- ( all screaming )
- ( grunting )
- CARD MAGIC!
LIGHTNING!
REVERSE TOWER!
LOVERS!
FATE OF LIGHTNING!
- RING MAGIC!
TWISTER!
- AAH!
COME ON, MAN UP!
DON'T YOU WANNA BE
LIKE ME?!
- WHOA, THAT GUY'S A BRUTE.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO HIS ARM?
- IT'S TAKE OVER MAGIC.
- WHY WOULD ANYONE LET
A MONSTER TAKE OVER THEIR ARM?
- YOU GUYS, THAT'S ELFMAN!
- I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
HE KILLS MONSTERS,
THEN ABSORBS THEIR POWER. THEY
CALL HIM "BEAST ARM" ELFMAN.
- ( cackling )
- ( crashes )
- WHO'S THAT?
- THAT'S GOTTA BE...
- ( chuckles )
- IT'S THE IRON DRAGON SLAYER.
BLACK STEEL GAJEEL.
- YOU ATTACKED LEVY!
AAH!
( groans )
- AW, MAN.
- WHAT THE--?
HE JUST KNOCKED OUT HIS OWN
GUILD MATES WITH THAT ATTACK.
- ( chuckles )
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.
UNLESS YOU SCUM ARE
TOO SCARED
TO FACE THE GREAT
IRON DRAGON SLAYER.
- TOO SCARED?!
REAL MEN HAVE NO FEAR!
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE ELFMAN, RIGHT?
AHH, NOT BAD, BIG GUY.
- WELL, THAT'S 'CAUSE
I'M A REAL MAN.
- YEAH?  THEN LET'S SEE
HOW A REAL MAN HANDLES THIS!
- ( all grunting )
( screaming )
- THEY'RE PHANTOM!
YOU ATTACKED YOUR OWN MEN?
- 'CAUSE I KNEW
IT'D DISTRACT YOU.
- NATSU?
- HIYAH!
- WHOA, THAT KID
SENT HIM FLYING.
- NOBODY'S EVER
DONE THAT BEFORE.
- ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M FAIRY TAIL'S DRAGON SLAYER.
ELFMAN, LEAVE THIS GUY TO ME.
- COME ON. FIRST YOU USE
ME AS A SPRINGBOARD,
AND NOW YOU WANNA STEAL
MY MAN-TO-MAN FIGHT?
- IRON DRAGON CLUB!
- ( grunts )
- NATSU!
- YOU DESTROYED
OUR GUILD HALL...
AND YOU ATTACKED LEVY
AND HER TEAM.
- ( gasps slightly )
- I'LL MAKE YOU PAY!
- AAH!
- WHOO, THE KID'S
FIRED UP NOW.
- YEAH, I'D HATE TO BE
THAT OTHER GUY.
- HMM!
- HE'S QUITE A WIZARD.
- ALL RIGHT, FINE,
YOU'RE MANLIER THAN I THOUGHT.
I'LL LET YOU HAVE THIS ONE,
BUT YOU GOTTA PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'RE GONNA--
- YOU BET. I'LL BEAT
HIM TO A PULP.
- NICE TRY,
BUT I'M STILL STANDING.
- TRUE.  YOU WON'T BE
FOR MUCH LONGER, THOUGH.
- OH, YEAH?
- UH-OH.
AAH!
- THAT HURT.
- THIS IS PRETTY CRAZY.
- AW, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU CAN DISH IT OUT,
BUT YOU CAN'T TAKE IT?
- ( laughs ) IT'S GONNA TAKE
MORE THAN THAT TO KEEP ME DOWN.
- YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
YOU CAN BEAT ME, YOU PYRO?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "THINK"?
I KNOW THAT I CAN.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
- YOUR STEEL BEAMS
CAN'T EVEN TOUCH ME.
YOU BETTER START
STEPPING UP YOUR GAME!
- THE RUMORS ARE TRUE.
YOU'RE WAY MORE POWERFUL
THAN YOU LOOK.
THAT ACTUALLY BURNS A LITTLE.
SO, IS THAT ALL YOU GOT...
SALAMANDER?
- THAT WAS MY WARM-UP.
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHING YET,
YOU METAL FREAK.
MAN, HE'S TOUGH.
- ( laughing )
- ( grunting )
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT, PUNK?
- DON'T GET COCKY,
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- EVERYTHING'S SHAKING.
- I GUESS THEY'RE
GOING AT IT.
- I DON'T LIKE
THE SOUND OF THAT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
MASTER MAKAROV'S ANGRY.
- IT'S CALLED THE GIANT'S WRATH.
- NOBODY WILL BE ABLE
TO STOP HIM NOW.
- ( whimpers )
- HE'S GONNA MAKE
THE GUILD HALL COLLAPSE.
- WHEN HE GETS ANGRY,
THE MASTER'S EVEN MANLIER.
- PREPARE TO FIGHT!
WE CANNOT LOSE
AS LONG AS MASTER MAKAROV
IS WITH US.
- ( chuckles )
- JOSE!
- LOOK WHAT THE CAT
DRAGGED IN.
- WHY ARE YOU ATTACKING
FAIRY TAIL?
TELL ME!
- I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN QUITE A WHILE, MAKAROV.
SIX YEARS AGO AT
A GUILD MASTERS CONFERENCE.
I REMEMBER THAT DAY.
I WAS A COMPLETE MESS.
I CAN'T HOLD MY LIQUOR
AS WELL AS THE REST OF YOU.
- AAH!
I DIDN'T COME HERE
FOR SMALL TALK.
I WANT ANSWERS, JOSE.
- ( laughs )
- A PROJECTION?
YOU COWARD.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN YOU'D FLEE
WITH YOUR TAIL
BETWEEN YOUR LEGS.
- IT'S NOT COWARDICE.
I'M SIMPLY TRYING
TO AVOID A FIGHT
BETWEEN TWO OF
THE WIZARD SAINTS.
IN LIEU OF THAT MESS,
I PREFER A SENSIBLE VICTORY
WITHOUT ALL THE COMMOTION.
- WHY ARE YOU HIDING?
COME AND FACE ME LIKE A MAN!
LUCY?
BUT WHY?
- WHY, YOU ASK?
YOU MEAN SHE'S A MEMBER
OF YOUR GUILD,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW?
I'M SURPRISED THAT
MISS LUCY HEARTFILIA
NEVER TOLD YOU THE TRUTH.
- ( grunts )
NO, DON'T!
WHERE'D HE COME FROM?
I COULDN'T EVEN
SENSE HIS PRESENCE.
- IT'S SO SAD!
SO SAD!
- AAH!
- WHAT THE--?
- SOMETHING FELL
FROM THE RAFTERS!
- ( gasps )
- ( all murmuring )
- IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
WHY AM I SUDDENLY
FEELING MELANCHOLY?
( cries softly )
IT MUST BE BECAUSE
THE WORLD HAS JUST LOST
A GREAT WIZARD.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
I FEEL WEAK.
MY MAGIC...
IT'S GONE.
- IT'S GRAMPS!
- IS HE OKAY?
- MASTER!
- Aria:
SUCH SORROW.
- MAKAROV IS POWERLESS NOW.
THANKS TO ARIA OF THE HEAVENS,
A MEMBER OF PHANTOM'S
ELEMENT FOUR.
HE HAS THE ABILITY TO MAKE
OTHER WIZARDS' POWERS
DISAPPEAR INTO THIN AIR.
I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
WE'VE WON THIS ROUND,
FAIRY TAIL.
- ( groaning )
MY POWER IS...
MY MAGIC POWER IS--
- MASTER, CALM DOWN.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I DON'T SENSE
ANY MAGIC ENERGY
COMING FROM HIM AT ALL.
- GRAY, ARE YOU SAYING HE'S
JUST AN ORDINARY OLD MAN NOW?
- NO, THAT CAN'T BE!
- COME ON, GRAMPS!
YOU CAN PULL THROUGH THIS.
- GUESS THE FUN'S OVER.
AND JUST WHEN THINGS
WERE STARTING TO GET GOOD.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
GRAMPS IS SO POWERFUL.
HOW'D THEY BEAT HIM?
- ONLY WAY TO FIND OUT
IS TO GO UP THERE.
- THE MASTER'S BEEN DEFEATED!
- FOR REAL?
- WHAT?  HE'S OUT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- YOU GUYS, WE CAN BEAT 'EM.
- THEY'RE NOT HALF AS STRONG
WITHOUT THEIR MASTER.
- AND WE'VE GOT GAJEEL AND
THE ELEMENT FOUR ON OUR SIDE.
- ( gasps )
THIS IS BAD.
- NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
- LET'S GET 'EM!
- ( Phantom Lord Guild
shouting )
- DON'T YOU START
GETTING COCKY!
- AW, CRAP, WHAT NOW?
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
FIGHT HARDER.
- TAKE THIS!
TRI-ELEMENT COMBO ATTACK!
- AAH!  OH, NO!
( screams )
- CANA!
- ( groans )
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
- MACAO...
- ( all groaning )
- Cana: YOU SHOULDN'T
PUSH YOURSELF SO HARD.
YOU'RE TOO OLD FOR THIS.
- ( groaning )
- ( chuckles )
WELL, I CAN SEE
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
- WE CAN'T DO THIS.
WITHOUT THE MASTER
WE AREN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
AND OUR MORALE'S
DANGEROUSLY LOW.
WE MUST RETREAT!
EVERYONE, BACK TO
THE GUILD AT ONCE!
- ERZA?
- NO WAY!
WE CAN'T JUST GIVE UP.
- REAL MEN NEVER RETREAT.
- I STILL GOT FIGHT IN ME.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
LET'S STAY.
- WE CAN'T.  WE DON'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST JOSE.
NOW RETREAT!
THAT'S AN ORDER!
- ( all clamoring )
- THERE THEY GO...
I KNEW IT WOULDN'T BE LONG
BEFORE THOSE GUTLESS COWARDS
GAVE UP
AND STARTED RUNNING
FOR THEIR LIVES.
- THEY'RE RETREATING
WITH SORROW IN THEIR HEARTS.
- HUH?  ARIA?
I SEE YOU'RE JUST
AS CREEPY AS EVER.
I GOTTA COMMEND YOU ON TAKING
DOWN THAT FAIRY TAIL GEEZER.
I JUST FOLLOWED
MASTER JOSE'S ORDERS.
BUT THANK YOU!
- WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS CRYING?
JEEZ, CUT IT OUT.
SO, WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THAT LUCY GIRL?
- ( exhales )
- SHE'S BEEN CAPTURED.
THE POOR WRETCH IS BEING HELD
IN A GLOOMY CELL
AT HEADQUARTERS.
- SO MUCH FOR GIVING HER
A WARM WELCOME, HUH?
- NO WAY.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- GAJEEL!
- WE'LL FINISH THIS SOMEDAY...
SALAMANDER.
- THOSE JERKS KIDNAPPED LUCY.
- AAH!
- EVERYBODY OUT!
LET'S GO!
- I'M NOT GOING BACK YET.
I WON'T LEAVE TILL
I GET REVENGE.
THEY GOTTA PAY FOR
WHAT THEY DID TO US.
- PLEASE...
- ERZA...
- I'M SORRY.
IT'S OUR ONLY OPTION.
WE NEED HIM.
WE'RE COMPLETELY HELPLESS
WITHOUT THE MASTER.
- ( all shouting )
- YEAH-- AAH!
NO.  THE SALAMANDER...
AND THAT CAT!
- YOU GOT IT, BUDDY.
AND WE NEED TO CHAT.
- PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
- ( chattering )
- SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO NOW?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
WE'RE GONNA GO SAVE LUCY.
- ( man groans )
- ALL RIGHT, PAL,
WHERE IS SHE?
TELL ME.
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW A LUCY.
( screaming )
THIS HURTS SO BAD!
- START TALKING.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU, DUDE.
I DON'T KNOW NOTHING.
I'M SERIOUS, DUDE.
NOW PUT OUT THE FIRE!
- IF YOU PHANTOM GUYS HURT
ANOTHER ONE OF MY FRIENDS...
I SWEAR I'LL BURN EVERY
ONE OF YOU INTO A PILE OF ASHES.
- AAH!
I TOLD YOU, MAN,
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
THIS LUCY CHICK.
IF I KNEW WHO SHE WAS
I WOULD HAVE TOLD YOU BY NOW!
- FUNNY YOU SHOULD SAY THAT,
'CAUSE I WAS JUST THINKING
I SHOULD HAVE BURNED YOU
TO A CRISP BY NOW.
- AYE!
- OUR HEADQUARTERS
IS UP AHEAD.
IF I HAD TO GUESS,
I'D SAY THEY PROBABLY
GOT HER LOCKED UP THERE.
OKAY?!
- YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID THAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
- AYE!
- ( gasps )
WHAT THE--?
HOW DID I GET HERE?
- SO YOU'RE FINALLY AWAKE.
I WAS GETTING WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, LUCY.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- ( door opens, closes )
- I AM MASTER JOSE PORLA
OF THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD.
- YOU'RE WITH PHANTOM?!
THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS CAPTURED BY TWO
OF THE ELEMENT FOUR.
- I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THIS DINGY CELL.
AND BEING TIED UP
MUST BE DEGRADING.
BUT I'M AFRAID
I HAD NO CHOICE, MY DEAR.
THAT IS HOW YOU TREAT
A PRISONER, AFTER ALL.
- YOU'RE THE JERKS WHO ATTACKED
MY FRIEND LEVY!
YOU'D BETTER LET ME GO.
MY FRIENDS ARE GONNA COME
LOOKING FOR ME.
- DEPENDING ON YOUR WILLINGNESS
TO COOPERATE,
I'M FULLY PREPARED
TO TREAT YOU
AS PHANTOM LORD'S
ESTEEMED GUEST,
RATHER THAN
A LOWLY PRISONER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
( screams )
YUCK!
THAT BUG CRAWLED ON ME!
- SEE?
YOU DON'T WANT TO
STAY IN HERE, DO YOU?
I HAVE A BEAUTIFULLY DECORATED
SUITE WAITING FOR YOU,
IF YOU'LL PROMISE TO BEHAVE.
- WHY DOES YOUR GUILD KEEP
ATTACKING US?!
- WHO IS "US"?
OH, I'M SORRY, ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT FAIRY TAIL?
IT WAS A MEANS TO AN END...
AND THAT'S ALL.
- WHAT?
- YOU SEE, WE WERE WORKING
TOWARDS OUR MAIN OBJECTIVE
OF ACQUIRING
A CERTAIN SOMEONE.
THEY HAPPEN TO BE A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL,
SO IF WE HAVE TO DESTROY
THE GUILD TO GET A HOLD OF THEM,
SO BE IT.
- WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- OH, MY MY.
YOU'RE SUCH A NAIVE
YOUNG LADY.
NOT AT ALL WHAT I'D EXPECT
FROM A DEBUTANTE.
- ( gasps )
- I'M TALKING ABOUT
YOU, OF COURSE.
LADY LUCY,
THE PRIVILEGED DAUGHTER
OF THE WEALTHY
HEARTFILIA FAMILY.
- BUT HOW DID YOU
FIND OUT ABOUT THAT?
- YOU KNOW, I'M SURPRISED
YOU NEVER TOLD
YOUR FELLOW GUILD MEMBERS
THE TRUTH.
AND I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THE DAUGHTER
OF A WEALTHY TYCOON...
WOULD STOOP TO SUCH CHEAP
AND DANGEROUS WORK,
AS WIZARDING FOR SUCH
A LOW CLASS GUILD, DO YOU?
- I'VE BEEN KIDNAPPED?
- NO, MY DEAR.
I PROMISE
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
WE'RE NOT LOOKING
FOR RANSOM MONEY,
WE'RE JUST
DOING OUR JOB.
WE WERE HIRED BY YOUR FATHER
TO BRING YOU HOME TO HIM.
- ( gasps )
NO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULD HE WANT ME BACK?
- WHY DO YOU SEEM SO CONFUSED?
ANY FATHER WOULD GO
LOOKING FOR A DAUGHTER
WHO RAN AWAY FROM HOME.
- ( exhales )
NOT HIM.
HONESTLY, I'M SHOCKED HE EVEN
NOTICED THAT I WAS GONE.
I'M NOT EVER GONNA GO BACK
TO THAT HOUSE!
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH HIM!
- OH, DEAR.  I SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN THAT YOU'D BE PROBLEMATIC.
- WELL, YOU MIGHT AS WELL
JUST LET ME GO.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT.
- PLEASE.
I NEED TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU DON'T THINK I'D FALL
FOR THE OLDEST TRICK
IN THE BOOK, DO YOU?
- NO.  FOR REAL.
I'M DYING HERE.
- FINE THEN.
- UH--
- GO AHEAD.
- A BUCKET?!
- ( laughs )
I'M READY FOR ANY OLD TRICK
YOU MIGHT THROW MY WAY.
- ( sighs )
GUESS IT'LL HAVE TO WORK.
- YOU'RE GONNA USE IT?!
( groans )
WELL...
I HAVE NEVER MET
SUCH A VULGAR YOUNG LADY.
I'LL TURN AWAY
BECAUSE I'M A GENTLEMAN.
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
- YOU KNOW, THERE'S A REASON
OLD TRICKS ARE STILL AROUND.
'CAUSE THEY WORK!
BYE!  TAKE CARE, 'KAY?
( gasps )
( exhales )
- ( groans )
OOPS, I FORGOT TO MENTION...
THIS CELL IS SEVERAL
STORIES HIGH.
( groaning )
I MUST ADMIT, YOU REALLY DID
A NUMBER ON ME, YOUNG LADY.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO GET AWAY WITH IT.
YOU WILL BE PUNISHED.
I'LL SHOW YOU JUST HOW
TERRIFYING PHANTOM LORD CAN BE.
( gasps )
( groans )
- I HEARD HIM
IN THE DISTANCE.
I KNOW HE'S HERE.
NATSU!
- LUCY!
AAH!
- WHOA, IT'S RAINING LUCYS!
- I MADE IT JUST IN TIME.
- YEAH.  THANK YOU.
I KNEW YOU'D SAVE ME.
- ( grunts )
THERE YOU GO.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- I THINK SO.
- THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
OKAY, WE'D BETTER
HEAD BACK TO THE GUILD.
- WHAT?!
THAT'S THEIR HEADQUARTERS.
LET'S GET 'EM!
- WE CAN'T!
ERZA TOLD US TO RETREAT.
- 'CAUSE SHE'S A WIMP.
I'LL FACE THOSE GUYS
BY MYSELF IF I HAVE TO.
- BUT YOU SAW WHAT THEY DID
TO THE MASTER.
- EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHY I WANNA GET REVENGE!
- YOU'RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO FIGHT THEM ON YOUR OWN.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- I SAID YOU CAN'T!
- I HEARD YOU THE FIRST TIME.
- EVERYBODY'S HURT.
- I'M NOT HURT!
- NO, BUT NAB'S
GOT A BROKEN ARM.
- SO WHAT?
I'M STRONGER THAN HIM ANYWAY.
- MACAO'S BEAT UP TOO.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE HE'S AN OLD MAN.
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
( crying )
ALL OF THIS,
EVERYTHING...
IT'S MY FAULT.
BUT I DON'T WANNA LEAVE.
I WANNA STAY
WITH YOU GUYS.
'CAUSE I LOVE
BEING IN FAIRY TAIL.
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'RE CRYING.
WHY ARE YOU UPSET?
- YOU CAN TELL US.
- ( crying )
- YOU'RE ONE OF US.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LEAVE.
- COME ON, LET'S GO BACK
TO THE GUILD.
- YEAH, OKAY.
I GUESS WE OUGHTA.
TIME TO GET UP.
LET'S GO, LUCY.
- DON'T BE SO ROUGH WITH HER.
REMEMBER, GIRLS ARE DELICATE.
- HOW ABOUT I CARRY YOU
ON MY BACK?
IS THAT COOL WITH YOU?
- ( Lucy crying )
- Happy:
AW, LOOK WHAT YOU DID.
YOU MADE THE POOR GIRL
CRY AGAIN.
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO HELP!
- ( groaning )
SHE'S MADE ME ANGRY!
HER FATE IS SEALED!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- JEEZ, WHAT'S TAKING HIM
SO LONG TO GET HERE?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO MEET
A WHILE AGO.
- WHAT'S UP, HAPPY?
WOW, YOU'RE EARLY.
- NUH-UH!  I GOT HERE ON TIME!
YOU'RE LATE, YOU BIG DUMMY.
- SERIOUSLY? I COULD HAVE
SWORN I WAS RIGHT ON TIME,
'CAUSE IT'S A QUARTER
TILL HUNGRY IN MY STOMACH.
- WAIT, YOU TELL TIME
WITH YOUR STOMACH?!
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Natsu: HUNGRY O'CLOCK!
WANNA GRAB A BITE TO EAT?
- Happy: I THOUGHT
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO RUN ERRANDS.
- LATER!  THERE'S AN AWESOME
FISH SPECIAL ON THE MENU.
- FORGET THE ERRANDS.
LET'S EAT IT UP!