- Natsu: EDOLAS?
- Carla: THAT'S CORRECT.
A WORLD THAT EXISTS,
INDEPENDENTLY FROM
THE ONE WE KNOW.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, A WORLD
THAT'S BEGUN LOSING ITS MAGIC.
- THEY'RE RUNNING OUT OF
MAGIC THERE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- UNLIKE HERE, IN EDOLAS,
MAGIC IS A FINITE RESOURCE
WITHOUT LIMITS ON ITS USE, IT
WILL ONE DAY DISAPPEAR FOREVER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- IN AN ATTEMPT TO RESTORE
THEIR RAPIDLY DIMINISHING
MAGIC POWER RESERVES,
THE KING OF EDOLAS
DEVELOPED A SPELL THAT WOULD
ABSORB IT FROM ANOTHER WORLD,
OUR WORLD.
IT IS A VERY POWERFUL SPELL
INDEED. HE CALLED IT ANIMA.
THAT IS WHAT OPENED THE HOLE
IN THE SKY.
- SO, THAT'S IT.
- ANIMA?
YOU CAN'T.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS, ALL RIGHT?
- Happy: EDOLAS
- Carla: SIX YEARS AGO, THEY
BEGAN SETTING UP ANIMA VORTICES
ALL ALONG THE BARRIER
BETWEEN OUR WORLDS.
BUT THE EXPERIMENT DID NOT
GO AS THEY PLANNED.
IT SEEMS SOMEONE HAD
MADE IT THEIR GOAL
TO CLOSE THEM, ONE BY ONE.
MY SUSPICIONS WERE RAISED
WHEN WENDY TOLD ME
WHAT HAPPENED WITH JELLAL.
BUT, THE STORY MAKES MORE SENSE
IF HE IS ACTUALLY MYSTOGAN.
I'M SURE HE MUST'VE BEEN
THE ONE CLOSING THE ANIMA.
BUT THIS ANIMA WAS SIMPLY
TOO LARGE.
NO ONE WAS STRONG
ENOUGH TO CLOSE IT.
AND THUS, THE GUILD AND
EVERYTHING SURROUNDING IT
WAS ABSORBED.
- Natsu: WHY WOULD THEY GO AFTER
FAIRY TAIL LIKE THAT?
- I TOLD YOU. TO PROVIDE MORE
MAGIC POWER TO THOSE IN EDOLAS.
- SO THEY CHOSE FAIRY TAIL
BECAUSE IT HAS
A LOT OF TOP CLASS WIZARDS?
BECAUSE THERE WAS MORE
POWER TO TAKE?
- THAT'S CORRECT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT'S A SERIOUSLY SELFISH MOVE.
YOU'D BETTER GIVE US BACK
ALL OF OUR FRIENDS RIGHT NOW!
- ( lightening crackling )
- WHOA.
- YOU MEAN IT, CARLA?
THIS HAPPENED BECAUSE OF YOU
AND ME? IT'S OUR FAULT?
- INDIRECTLY, YES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"INDIRECTLY?"
- THE KING ENTRUSTED US
TO COMPLETE ANOTHER
MISSION ENTIRELY.
SOMETHING THAT WAS
TOTALLY INDEPENDENT
FROM THE ONE INVOLVING
ANIMA AND MAGIC ABSORPTION.
- BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
HOW CAN THAT BE TRUE WHEN
YOU WERE BORN IN THIS WORLD?
HATCHED OUT OF AN EGG.
- AND HAPPY WAS, TOO.
IT WAS ME THAT FOUND HIM.
- INDEED WE WERE.
TO BE PERFECTLY
HONEST, I MYSELF,
HAVE NEVER PERSONALLY
SET FOOT IN EDOLAS.
I WAS BORN IN THIS WORLD
AND HAVE SPENT MY
ENTIRE LIFE HERE.
IT'S EXACTLY AS WENDY SAID.
BUT WE WERE IMPRINTED
WITH THIS KNOWLEDGE.
THE DETAILS OF OUR
MISSION AND OF EDOLAS
ARE PART OF WHAT MAKES
UP OUR VERY BEING.
HE AND I, WERE BORN TO CARRY OUT
THIS MISSION, FOR OUR KINGDOM.
SO WHY...
WHY DON'T YOU KNOW THE
FIRST THING ABOUT IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- ( scoffs )
ANYWAY, THAT'S WHAT I
MEANT BY INDIRECTLY.
THE ANIMA THAT DID THIS
ORIGINATED FROM OUR HOMELAND,
SO THAT'S WHY WE'RE PARTIALLY
TO BLAME.
- BUT, WHAT IS THE MISSION
THAT YOU'RE ON, CARLA?
- I CAN'T TELL YOU.
I'M SORRY.
- PLEASE TELL US.
I WANNA KNOW MORE ABOUT WHERE
I CAME FROM AND WHY I'M HERE.
- I SAID I CAN'T TELL YOU
AND THAT'S FINAL.
YOU KNOW IT, BUT YOU JUST
DON'T REMEMBER.
- ( sighs )
OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN, NOW THAT THE
CAT'S BEEN LET OUTTA THE BAG,
WE SHOULD HEAD OUT.
WE GOTTA GET TO EDOLAS!
- HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- YOU MEAN IT?
- ( Natsu and Wendy laughing )
- UH. I'M SCARED.
AND BEIN' SCARED ALWAYS
MAKES ME HUNGRY.
- IT'S GOOD TO HAVE A
HEALTHY APPETITE.
IF ALL OF OUR FRIENDS ARE
UP IN EDOLAS,
THEN WE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO AND HELP 'EM OUT.
- Wendy: ARE THEY REALLY THERE?
- Carla: I WOULD ASSUME SO.
BUT EVEN IF WE FIND THEM,
I'M NOT ENTIRELY SURE
WE CAN SAVE THEM.
AND WHAT'S MORE. IF WE CAN,
IN FACT, REACH EDOLAS,
I CAN'T GUARANTEE THAT
WE WILL BE ABLE TO RETURN HERE.
- OH WELL. IF NONE OF OUR
BUDDIES ARE IN THIS WORLD,
WHAT WOULD BE THE POINT
OF COMING BACK HERE ANYWAY?
EXCEPT FOR LOOKING
FOR IGNEEL, MAYBE.
- I FEEL THE SAME.
- WE SHOULD AT LEAST
TRY TO SAVE ALL OF THEM.
THEY'D DO IT FOR US.
- Carla: I MAY HAVE ONLY
RECENTLY STUMBLED INTO
BEING A MEMBER OF FAIRY TAIL,
BUT I AM INDEED
A PART OF THE GUILD.
AND LIKE I SAID,
I'M INDIRECTLY RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
SO I'M NOT COMPLETELY AGAINST
TAKING YOU THERE.
BUT, IF I AM TO DO THIS,
I WILL NEED TO LAY DOWN
A FEW VERY FIRM GROUND RULES.
BY RETURNING TO EDOLAS,
I WILL BE ABANDONING MY MISSION,
ONE HANDED DOWN
BY THE KINGDOM ITSELF.
A TRAITOR. I CANNOT RISK
BEING SPOTTED BY ANYONE
WHO WOULD KNOW MY IDENTITY.
WE WILL ALL NEED TO
BE IN DISGUISE.
- EVEN ME?
- YOU SURE YOU WANNA DO
THIS, CARLA?
- I AM. I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
AND LISTEN, TOMCAT,
ANOTHER RULE IS
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
NOT TO PRY INTO THE DETAILS
OF OUR MISSION.
- AYE.
- THIRDLY, ASIDE FROM
THE INFORMATION
I WAS GIVEN AT BIRTH,
I KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT THE LAYOUT OF EDOLAS.
I CANNOT BE THE NAVIGATOR.
- GOT IT!
- AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
SHOULD I OR THE TOMCAT DO
ANYTHING THAT WOULD CONSTITUTE
A BETRAYAL TOWARDS YOU,
KILL US WITHOUT
ANY HESITATION.
- ( stomach growling )
- BUT THAT'S CRAZY.
I WOULD NEVER DO ANYTHING TO...
- STOP THAT DISGUSTING
BODILY NOISE.
LET'S GO.
TOMCAT, HOLD ONTO NATSU.
- WE'RE GONNA FLY THERE?
- WE HAVE WINGS
FOR THAT REASON
SO WE COULD ONE DAY RETURN TO
OUR HOMELAND IN EDOLAS.
- ALL RIGHT THEN, LITTLE BUDDY.
YOU'RE GONNA SHOW ME
WHERE YOU CAME FROM.
- AYE, SIR!
- TOMCAT, DON'T HOLD BACK
YOUR MAGIC POWER.
- AYE!
- ( Wendy and Natsu screaming )
- WE'LL ENTER EDOLAS THROUGH
WHAT REMAINS OF THE ANIMA.
WHEN I GIVE THE SIGNAL,
GIVE IT EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
- ( both grunting )
- ( screaming )
- NOW!
- ( gasping )
- ARE WE THERE YET?
( gasping )
( Natsu laughing )
- WE'RE ACTUALLY HERE.
WE MADE IT.
- MY ROOTS. MY HOMELAND.
- LOOK AT ALL THESE
FLOATING ISLANDS.
- YOU COME FROM A PRETTY COOL
PLACE, HAPPY. DON'T YOU THINK?
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
- IT'S SO STRANGE
AND WONDROUS.
- I'VE NEVER EVEN SEEN
TREES LIKE THESE.
- OH, WOW! CHECK IT OUT,
HAPPY. YOU SEE?
THERE'S A RIVER IN THE SKY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
- OKAY. EVERYONE GET A GRIP
ON YOURSELF.
REMEMBER WE'RE NOT
HERE ON A SIGHTSEEING TRIP.
SO BE SURE TO KEEP YOUR WITS
ABOUT YOU.
- ( chuckles ) I KNOW,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
- SORRY, SORRY.
- ( all screaming )
- ( Natsu grunting )
- MY WINGS DON'T WORK.
- HOW COME YOU CAN'T
FLY ANYMORE?
- I TOLD YOU, MAGIC IS A
LIMITED RESOURCE IN THIS WORLD.
- OH YEAH, CARLA, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I GUESS I DO FEEL A
LITTLE STRANGE.
- LET'S GO. WE GOTTA FIND
WHERE THEY TOOK ALL OUR FRIENDS!
- HOW WILL WE FIND 'EM IF
NO ONE KNOWS THEIR WAY AROUND?
- PIECE OF CAKE.
JUST FOLLOW MY NOSE.
( sniffing )
UH, WELL, THIS IS CRAPPY.
THERE ARE SO MANY CRAZY
NEW SMELLS HERE,
MY NOSE IS CONFUSED.
- YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
THE AIR IN THIS PLACE
IS LIKE NOTHING I'VE
EVER TASTED BEFORE.
- Natsu: OH, DOES THAT MEAN THE
FIRE WILL TASTE DIFFERENT?
- Carla: HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
- Happy: ALL THIS TALK ABOUT
TASTING MAKES ME EVEN HUNGRIER.
- Wendy: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE COULD EAT HERE.
- Carla: WE'RE IN
A STRANGE WORLD
AND ALL YOU CAN THINK
ABOUT IS FOOD?
- Wendy: SO, WHERE ARE WE
GOING, ANYWAY?
- Natsu: BEATS ME. WE GOTTA
WALK SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
SO WHY NOT THIS WAY?
- Happy: I WAS AFRAID YOU WERE
GONNA SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- Carla: SURPRISING AS IT IS,
THE FIRE BREATHER IS RIGHT.
- ( stomach growling )
- Carla: STOP THAT!
- Natsu: OH, MY BAD.
- THERE'S NO ONE HERE.
WE HAVEN'T RUN INTO
A SINGLE PERSON.
- IS IT SOME KINDA
FOREST WORLD?
- SURELY NOT. WE'LL STILL
NEED DISGUISES.
- BUT FROM WHERE?
THERE'S NOTHING.
- HEY!
- Happy: UH, NATSU.
I'M NOT SO SURE ABOUT THIS.
- ( Natsu and Wendy laughing )
- Happy: BOO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT EXACTLY
WE'RE BEING DISGUISED AS.
- Natsu: WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU LOOK LIKE A THING THAT
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HAPPY.
RELAX, NO ONE'S GONNA
RECOGNIZE YOU.
- IT'S SO EMBARRASSING.
- FASHION SENSE ASIDE, I DO FEEL
QUITE A BIT MORE AT EASE NOW.
- YOU DO? NOT ME.
IT'S HOT AND ITCHY
IN THIS GETUP.
I THINK I'M ALLERGIC TO IT.
- PLEASE TRY TO TOUGHEN
UP, TOMCAT!
- AYE.
- ( gasps ) IT'S THAT
FLYING RIVER.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT BEFORE.
- THIS JUST REMINDS ME HOW
HUNGRY I AM.
- I SAID, TOUGHEN UP.
- ( stomach growling )
I BET THERE'S TONS OF
YUMMY FISH SWIMMING
IN THAT FLYING RIVER.
- THERE'S A MAN OVER THERE!
- HE MUST BE AN
EDOLAS NATIVE.
- Wendy: THANK GOODNESS.
HE LOOKS LIKE A NORMAL PERSON.
- Happy: WHAT DID YOU EXPECT
PEOPLE HERE TO LOOK LIKE?
HE'S GOT THE RIGHT IDEA, THOUGH.
WE SHOULD BE FISHING RIGHT NOW.
- Wendy: HEY, WHERE DID
NATSU GO?
- Natsu: YO!
- ( all gasping )
- LEMME ASK YOU SOMETHIN'!
- ( man screaming )
- OF COURSE.
- WHAT IS HE DOING?
- SCARING THE LOCALS.
- I'M LOOKIN' FOR A
BUNCH OF WIZARDS
FROM THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
YOU SEEN THEM AROUND ANYWHERE?
- ( screaming ) PLEASE.
DON'T HURT ME.
- WAIT. HOLD ON.
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
I JUST WANTED A LITTLE HELP.
- THINK BEFORE YOU ACT.
YOU WALKED UP TO SOMEONE MINDING
THEIR OWN BUSINESS,
WHILE WEARING THAT
RIDICULOUS OUTFIT
AND THEN STARTED TALKING
ABOUT FAIRY TAILS.
OF COURSE YOU SCARED HIM.
- OKAY, THEN HOW DO YOU
SUGGEST THAT WE FIND EVERYONE?
- YOU DIDN'T MEAN TO...
- LISTEN. IF THAT MAN
REPORTS US TO THE AUTHORITIES,
WE'RE THROUGH.
- LET'S DITCH THE COSTUMES
THEN, PLEASE.
- Carla: NOW WE'RE IN EVEN MORE
OF A HURRY TO FIND THEM.
- Happy: ( sighs ) THIS FEELS
A MILLION TIMES BETTER.
BUT I REALLY WISH THAT GUY
HADN'T RUN OFF
WITH HIS FISHING ROD.
- Natsu: OH, DID I MESS
THAT UP, TOO?
- Wendy: HEY, DID ANYONE
ELSE HEAR A WEIRD NOISE
JUST A SECOND AGO?
- Natsu: OH, ANOTHER FISHERMAN?
THIS GUY'LL KNOW
SOMETHING, FOR SURE.
- Carla: IS THERE A BRAIN
IN YOUR HEAD?
- Happy: WHOA, BIG FISHY ALERT!
- Natsu: AWESOME! NOW STAND BACK
WHILE I GRAB US DINNER.
- ( growling )
- All: IT'S HUGE!
- ( all exclaiming )
- TOO HUGE!
- WE WON'T GO HUNGRY
ATLEAST. I'M ALL FIRED UP.
- NATSU. WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH TIME TO CATCH HIM.
- ALL I NEED IS JUST
A COUPLE OF SECONDS.
( grunting )
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST.
WHAT?
- Wendy: NATSU.
- Happy: NATSU.
- ( groans ) MY FIRE'S PUT OUT.
- HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
YOU CAN'T USE MAGIC IN EDOLAS
LIKE YOU CAN IN OUR WORLD.
- ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO DO.
- LET'S RUN FOR IT!
- IT CAN RUN ON LAND?
- THIS PLACE IS
REALLY GONNA SUCK
IF WE CAN'T USE OUR MAGIC HERE!
- AND IT TOOK ALL THIS TO
MAKE YOU REALIZE THAT, NATSU?
- HEY, GUYS, I'M AFRAID
THAT RUNNING AROUND SCREAMING
AND BEING CHASED BY
THIS MONSTER IS GONNA ATTRACT
A LOT OF UNWANTED ATTENTION.
- WELL, THIS WAS THE MONSTER'S
GENIUS IDEA, SO DON'T BLAME ME.
( exclaims ) OH, JUST GREAT.
- IT'S A DEAD END.
- PLEASE, HAPPY, YOU GOTTA
FLY US OUTTA HERE.
- I CAN'T USE MAGIC, EITHER.
- ( all screaming )
- HOLY CRAP. NOT HAVING
MAGIC IS SUPER HARD.
- I'M JUST GLAD THAT
EVERYONE'S OKAY.
- I'D BE A HECK OF A LOT BETTER
WITH A BUNCH OF
FISH IN MY TUMMY.
- WELL, I'VE HAD MORE THAN
MY FILL OF FOOLISHNESS TODAY.
- HUH?
- THIS WOULD BE MUCH EASIER
IF YOU DIDN'T CAUSE A RUCKUS
EVERYWHERE YOU GO.
- NOW BE NICE.
- SO IT'S MY FAULT. REALLY?
- YOU CERTAINLY PLAY A
LARGE PART IN OUR TROUBLES.
WE NO LONGER HAVE DISGUISES.
IF PEOPLE FROM THE KINGDOM
DISCOVER US ROAMING AROUND,
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT THEY'LL DO.
AND IF WE GET TAKEN
INTO CUSTODY,
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT
SAVING THE OTHERS.
WE'LL HAVE OUR WORK CUT OUT FOR
US TRYING TO SAVE OUR OWN SKINS.
- OKAY. I DON'T REALLY GET IT,
BUT I GUESS IT'S ALL
MY FAULT SOMEHOW.
- HOW DOES ANYTHING
EVER GET THROUGH
THAT THICK SKULL OF YOURS.
- PLEASE TAKE IT EASY
ON HIM, CARLA.
NATSU'S A NICE GUY,
AND HE DIDN'T MEAN
TO DO ANYTHING WRONG.
- MY WHOLE POINT IS HE
HAS NO CONTROL.
- ( stomach growling )
- LIFE CAN GET PRETTY WEIRD
SOMETIMES. DON'T YOU THINK?
- WHAT, IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MAKE ME
FEEL BETTER OR SOMETHING?
AND SINCE WE'RE SNEAKIN' AROUND,
TELL YOUR STOMACH TO BE QUIET.
- UH-OH.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- WE'VE BEEN SPOTTED AGAIN.
- WELL. WHAT SHOULD WE
DO NOW?
- I, UH... HELLO, WE'RE
NOT FROM AROUND THESE PARTS
AND WE SEEM TO HAVE GOTTEN
A LITTLE LOST IN THIS FOREST.
- WE'RE SORRY.
IT'S NOT OUR FAULTS, WE SWEAR.
- UH...
- MIGHTY EXCEED,
PLEASE FORGIVE US
AND LET US LEAVE WITH OUR LIVES.
- EXCEED?
- I WONDER WHO THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
- HMM.
- YO!
- DON'T SCARE 'EM, NATSU.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE WE
CAN AVOID THEM NOW, HUH?
I GOT SOMETHIN' IMPORTANT
TO ASK YOU GUYS
SO LISTEN CLOSELY, OKAY?
SOME OF OUR FRIENDS
ARE HERE IN EDOLAS AND...
- ( screaming )
- All: PLEASE DON'T HURT US!
- WELL, EXCUSE ME.
- IT'S STRANGE. BUT I THINK
THOSE PEOPLE SEEMED TO BE
AFRAID OF HAPPY AND CARLA.
- RIGHT? I KNEW IT WASN'T
ALL MY FAULT.
- TELL ME THE TRUTH. AM I
REALLY THAT SCARY LOOKING?
- YOU LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE
GONNA EAT 'EM.
- NO, I DIDN'T.
- WHOA!
- NOW WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- I DON'T THINK THIS IS
GONNA BE GOOD GUYS.
- ( all screaming )
- Wendy: I DON'T WANNA
FALL ANYMORE.
- Carla: THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH
FOR ME.
- WHERE ARE WE NOW?
- IT'S LIKE SOME KIND OF
WEIRD WAREHOUSE.
- ALTHOUGH I BELIEVE WE'RE
WELL BEYOND THE POINT
OF TAKING PREVENTIVE MEASURES,
LET'S SEE IF THERE ARE ANY
CLOTHES IN HERE
THAT WE COULD USE TO
DISGUISE OURSELVES.
- ( Natsu grunting )
WHOA! THEY'VE GOT LOADS
OF COOL STUFF HERE.
- NATSU, WOULD YOU PLEASE
NOT LOOK THIS WAY FOR A MINUTE?
- AWESOME HEADGEAR!
- I SUPPOSE THIS'LL DO
FOR NOW.
- OH YEAH. YOU LOOK
BEAUTIFUL, MY FINE FELINE.
- ( scoffs )
- ( gasping )
- YOU SEE SOMETHING
OUT THERE?
- ( exclaims ) IT'S FAIRY TAIL!
IT'S IN DISGUISE, TOO,
BUT I'D RECOGNIZE IT ANYWHERE.
THAT'S WHERE THEY ARE.
- HOLD ON!
- WAIT FOR US!
- HONESTLY!
- THIS DISGUISE IS WAY
TOO HEAVY!
- ( all gasping )
- ( people chattering )
- THEY'RE OKAY!
- AND IT WASN'T EVEN THAT
MUCH TROUBLE TO FIND 'EM.
- IS IT JUST ME, OR DOES
SOMETHING SEEM KINDA DIFFERENT?
- WHO CARES ABOUT THAT,
THEY'RE HERE.
- YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- NO, HE'S NOT. THERE IS
SOMETHING WRONG HERE.
- Happy: HEY, LOOK.
HERE'S THE REQUEST BOARD.
- Natsu: SEEMS NORMAL
ENOUGH TO ME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
WE HAVE TO TRY TO PRETEND
LIKE WE'RE NOT REALLY HERE.
- LOOK AND YOU'LL SEE.
- Natsu: YEAH. SEE WHAT?
- WELL, I'M OFF. I JUST TOOK
ON A PRETTY MAJOR JOB.
- TAKE CARE.
- JUVIA, MY BELOVED.
PLEASE, WAIT.
IF YOU'RE GONNA GO OUT,
PLEASE TAKE ME WITH YOU.
PRETTY PLEASE?
- YOU'RE SUCH A WET BLANKET
AND TAKE TAKE SOME OF THOSE
CLOTHES OFF FOR A CHANGE.
- WHAT?
- GIVE ME A SHOUT WHEN YOU
HAVE YOUR SUMMER WARDROBE.
- I JUST GET REALLY COLD.
- HE NEEDS TO LEARN
A THING OR TWO
ABOUT BEIN' CLINGY.
- THE POOR GUY IS HEAD OVER
HEELS IN LOVE WITH HER
AND JUST DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH HIMSELF.
- WHAT THE HECK IS
GOING ON?
- I'M TIRED OF YOUR
EXCUSES, ELFMAN.
- YOU ACTUALLY
BUNGLED UP ANOTHER JOB?
- IT'S SO EMBARRASSING.
- JET AND DROY MAY BE OUR
STRONGEST MEMBERS,
BUT THEY DON'T ALWAYS HAVE TO
SCOLD THE WEAKER ONES.
ELFMAN'S JUST NOT THAT CAPABLE.
- LAY OFF HIM, YOU TWO!
- GOT A JOB TO DO.
- MAN, DOES THAT GUY EVER
TAKE A BREAK?
- HIM? NEVER.
- MISS CANA, WOULD YOU CARE TO
JOIN US FOR AN ADULT BEVERAGE?
- YEAH, TIP ONE BACK AND RELAX!
- OH, DON'T BE SO
SILLY, YOU TWO.
I'VE NEVER HAD A DROP OF ALCOHOL
IN MY LIFE, SO WHY START NOW?
- HEY, MY HOT BISCUIT.
- ALLEY CAT.
MY LITTLE GUNSLINGER.
- ( Wendy exclaiming )
- YOU HAVE REALLY GOTTA
MAN UP!
- ( crying ) I KNOW, I'M SORRY.
- AND QUIT SAYING THAT
YOU'RE SORRY ALL THE TIME.
- I WANNA DECLARE MY LOVE
HERE AND NOW FOR JUVIA.
- I SWEAR, GRAY, YOU'RE GONNA
SMOTHER THAT POOR GIRL.
- YEAH. SOMETHING IS
DEFINITELY WRONG HERE.
- EVERYBODY IS ACTING
CRAZIER THAN NORMAL.
- HEY, WHAT THE HECK
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOIN'?
- ( all gasping )
- WHAT?
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA WITH YOU
SNEAKIN' AROUND
OUR GUILD LIKE THIS?
- LUCY.
- SERIOUSLY?
- I'M SCARED, CARLA.
- DON'T WORRY, CHILD,
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
BUT WHAT THE DEVIL
IS GOING ON HERE?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WHAT GIVES.
EVERYBODY'S PERSONALITIES
HAVE GONE TOTALLY
WHACK-A-DOODLE!
- Happy: MAYBE EDOLAS
HAS SOME KINDA
PERSONALITY REVERSAL SPELL
ON IT LIKE NIRVANA.
- Natsu: GRAY'S WEARING
A MILLION LAYERS,
ELFMAN'S ACTING LIKE
A GREAT BIG WEENIE,
AND LEVY IS SOME KINDA STREET
THUG? THIS PLACE IS THE COOLEST.
- Happy: I JUST THOUGHT
OF SOMETHING,
I WONDER WHAT THE BIZARRO
ERZA'S GONNA BE LIKE.
- Both: NEXT TIME FAIRY HUNTER!
- Natsu: YEAH, ME TOO.
LIKE WHAT WOULD BE THE OPPOSITE
OF SUCH A HARDCORE CHICK?
- Happy: SHE'S PROBABLY ALL
SWEET AND SAYS THINGS LIKE,
"WELCOME HOME, MASTER!"