[ROCKER] These things
are too hot to handle!
Let's get outta here, man!
[BACCHUS] There's no way!
I still owe the Fairy Tail guys
a few rounds of drinks
to celebrate their victory!
We can't just bail on 'em!
There's one right
behind ya! Move!
[BACCHUS yelling]
Come on, man!
Hang on! Someone!
We gotta get some
help here! Please!
Please, just breathe, big guy!
You can't go dyin' on me!
[MACAO groaning]
[ROMEO]
Dad, no!
[WAKABA]
Slow down kid!
He's hurt!
I got him. I'm comin', Macao!
[MACAO] Forget about me!
Just keep my boy safe!
Please, Dad!
[ROMEO]
No!
[WAKABA grunts]
[HAPPY]
Time of Life!
[LYON] Shelia! Where are
you? Shelia! Shelia!
We need you.
You're the only one
who can save him.
Please come. He'll die.
[MELDY] I'm sorry.
I think it's too late.
The time has finally
come for you to die.
Now finish him!
[MOTHER GLARE roaring]
[NATSU panting]
[MOTHER GLARE] What has
gotten into you, Atlas Flame?
You'd turn your back on
your own kind for this human?
[ATLAS FLAME]
Didn't you hear me?
He may have been born human,
but was raised by Igneel,
King of the Fire Dragons.
Therefore he is my family!
[MOTHER GLARE]
Such unbelievable hubris!
But if you insist, I will not
back down from this fight!
[ATLAS FLAME]
Nor will I!
[NATSU munching]
[FUTURE ROGUE] You fool!
You don't know when to give up.
Death is still your only future!
I will never give up!
And this fire's
got me feelin' good!
That being said, you've still
sustained multiple injuries.
You can't continue buying time!
Once you've been fatally
wounded, you're done for!
[NATSU grunts]
[ATLAS FLAME growling]
[NATSU grunting]]
[FUTURE ROGUE yells]
[NATSU] I told ya
that I never give up!
It just ain't my style!
[NATSU] Besides, there's a
promise that I gotta keep!
What promise?
Eat my Raging Bolt!
[ZIRCONIS cackling] Ridiculous!
After all your bluster,
is that really the
best you can do, punk?
I'm just startin'
to get warmed up.
[PANTHERLILY]
I thought Laxus would have
more of an effect than that.
Is Zirconis really
that powerful?
[CARLA] It's true, he possesses
Dragon Slaying magic.
But nobody ever said
that it would be
an easy task to accomplish.
[WENDY] If one's not
enough. How about two?
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
Nice hit, Wendy!
Give 'em hell!
[ZIRCONIS groans]
Did that work?
I think that it may have!
He's eating dirt now!
[ZIRCONIS groans]
[LAXUS] Tch! So, I seem
to recall that you were
flapping your gums earlier
about bluster, weren't ya?
[ZIRCONIS] You have the nerve
to hit my handsome face?
You're trying to make
me angry aren't ya?
[PANTHERLILY]
Impossible! That did nothing?
[CARLA] It seems that
all it did was get him
riled up even further.
[ZIRCONIS] I've had
just about enough of this.
I can play all night
with these little girls.
But I don't have much interest
in messing around with guys.
So I'm gonna eat this
little morsel right up.
Clothing and all.
[WENDY gasps]
[ZIRCONIS] That man is all
tough and stringy looking.
Not appetizing. But you...
[LAXUS]
Wendy! Run!
What are you doing?
[LEVIA] Accept your fate,
and come with me!
[ROGUE]
Never!
[LEVIA] You can't
escape your destiny!
You heart will
become black as night!
That's not gonna happen!
Not as long as I have him!
This thing is a
pain in my ass!
[LEVIA]
Stop getting in my way!
If you refuse to help me,
then go somewhere else at once!
[SCISSOR RUNNER]
I will not! I'm trying to
kill this human and you're
preventing me from doing so!
[STING]
Let's hit 'em, Rogue!
[ROGUE]
Right!
[STING, ROGUE grunting]
[STING, ROGUE]
We did it!
[LEVIA] Ha! Your feeble
magic has no effect on us!
[SCISSOR RUNNER]
It's insulting.
Prepare to die
for your arrogance!
[STING yelling]
No! Sting!
[LEVIA]
Rogue. I am through with asking.
I have no choice but
to take you by force.
Iron Dragon Sword!
[GAJEEL grunts]
[GAJEEL growls]
The right or the left?
[GAJEEL]
Which is it gonna be? Oh crap!
[COBRA yellig]
[ROCK DRAGON] My scales
are made of solid rock!
Your poison will
never penetrate them!
[ROCK DRAGON]
Now get off me, you pest!
[COBRA yelling]
[ROCK DRAGON]
Time to die!
[COBRA grunts]
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY] I've gotta hurry.
I need to tell everybody
about what I've found!
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
No!
[ULTEAR sighs]
[ULTEAR] I've lived my
entire life in the shadows.
Ruled by darkness.
[ULTEAR] I thrived on deception,
contempt, rancor, and death.
And still, I received
forgiveness and compassion.
Gray allowed me a
second chance at life.
I wanted to atone for my sins
so I founded Crime Sorcière.
The "witch's crime."
But I will never find salvation.
At my core, I'm still the same.
A witch crumbling under
the weight of her own crimes.
One who'd take the life
of an innocent.
Perhaps that's because
I myself don't deserve to live.
[YOUNG ULTEAR gasps]
[HADES]
Oh my. All these books.
I see that you've
developed a keen interest
in time magic, have you not?
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Yes, Master Hades.
It's quite fascinating, sir.
You needn't be
so formal, child.
Please, get on your feet.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Master Hades.
You once sparked my
curiosity when you spoke of
a magic that can
retrieve lost happiness.
Do you remember, sir?
You're referring to
Arc of Time magic?
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Yes, I've finally been able to
track down some information!
This book contains some notes
that I believe may
teach me how to use it.
[HADES]
The Last Ages spell.
I absolutely forbid its use.
[YOUNG ULTEAR] But why?
This is exactly the spell
that I was hoping to discover.
It turns back time!
It lets you do things
over again. This magic.
I would do whatever it takes
of me to master it someday.
[HADES] The price of
mastering the Last Ages spell
is quite a heavy one, indeed.
It does, in fact,
turn back time.
But the caster must forfeit
their time in return.
"Their time?"
In other words, their life.
[HADES] Time will travel back
for the world at large,
but, for the wizard
who casts the spell,
they'll lose the rest
of their remaining time.
[YOUNG ULTEAR gasps]
Oh. I see. Thank you.
[ULTEAR] At this point,
I will gladly pay.
If giving up this life
of sin and sorrow,
if that can truly set
the world as it was,
then so be it.
Arc of Time Last Ages!
[ULTEAR groaning]
[ULTEAR]
I must endure it! This pain.
It's nothing compared to what
I've brought into this world.
All the suffering
I've inflicted upon others.
Their pain. Their deaths!
Every cell in my body
feels like it's on fire!
The very fabric of my
existence ripped to shreds.
My life is being
torn from me!
All as payment for
the lives of others.
This is what
I give to the world!
[ULTEAR] I will take this
pain and tenfold more!
Whatever the cost.
I will pay it!
I will sacrifice
my life. My future!
[ULTEAR screaming]
[ULTEAR] I ran through
the valley of death
reveling in sin
to escape my demons.
My loneliness.
Never truly realizing
that I was no longer alone.
Gray. Jellal.
And sweet Meldy.
[ULTEAR] I never
deserved their forgiveness.
Their warmth was wasted on me.
I was blind to it.
Obsessed with my past,
I could never live in the
present, much less the future.
But now I can
find redemption.
I can give the time I would've
wasted in this world,
so the ones I love can
live and be a part of it.
I ask the hands
of time to reverse!
To return the world
to what it once was.
If only briefly.
Before it was thrown into
chaos by that damned gate!
Let my life be enough!
[ULTEAR gasps]
[ULTEAR]
It worked. I've done it.
I've turned back time.
[ULTEAR gasps]
What? One minute?
Is that what my life was
worth? Just one minute.
No. This can't
be all they get.
It's not enough.
I've failed them!
[GRAY]
Get down!
[LYON]
Stay focused!
This is a war-zone!
[MELDY]
Sorry!
[JUVIA gasps] I can still
feel the warmth of Gray's hand
on my tushie!
Juvia!
[MELDY, GRAY gasp]
[LYON]
What just happened here?
I died? I don't get it!
A dream?
But I saw it as well.
The hell? What was that?
I'm starting to get totally
creeped out here you guys.
Some of the little ones
were climbing over
that rubble there.
[LYON grunts]
[LYON] They came just
like we knew they would!
[GRAY grunts]
[LYON]
What the hell is going on?
That was exactly
what we just saw!
We all knew. But how?
[JET] Whoa!
[DROY] That was way too close.
[DROY]
But it's like I saw it coming.
I could see that
far in the future.
[JET] Premonition?
Let's make sure
it doesn't come true! Come on!
[DROY]
Yeah!
[ROMEO]
It was like a dream.
[WAKABA]
But we were all wide-awake.
[MACAO]
It's dangerous to stay here.
[WAKABA, ROMEO gasp]
[NARRATOR] That night,
people all over the world
caught a glimpse
one minute into the future.
But much like a dream,
it quickly slipped
from their memories.
Leaving behind a faintly
eerie sensation for those
who experienced it firsthand.
So this phenomenon,
although miraculous,
went largely unnoticed.
However, for the
wizards doing battle,
that minute they peered into
the future was worth a lifetime.
It was the difference
between life, and death.
[WENDY]
What was that?
We can figure it out later!
[WENDY gasps]
Sky Dragon Roar!
Lightning Dragon Roar!
[ZIRCONIS groaning]
That vision. Or premonition.
Was that your doing, Carla?
I swear it wasn't me.
And it definitely wasn't me.
[PANTHERLILY, CARLA]
Nobody thought it was.
Oh.
I'm seein' things.
[BACCHUS yelling]
Get wild on 'em,
brother! Kick his butt!
[NARRATOR]
Such a brief time.
[GAJEEL]
Which is it gonna be?
I got ya now!
[NARRATOR] But that one minute
bought humanity countless years,
and secured its future.
[GAJEEL]
That was weird.
It's like I knew
what it was gonna do!
[COBRA]
Eat this!
[ROCK DRAGON roaring]
[STING]
Here goes!
[LEVIA] You cannot hide
forever, Rogue! Show yourself!
[ROGUE] I control
my own destiny, not you!
[LEVIA]
Huh?
[ROGUE yells]
[LEVIA groaning]
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY]
Wait a second...
If I turn around that corner...
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY gasps]
Not goin' there.
What is this? It's like time
has been disrupted somehow.
Has something happened
to the Eclipse gate?
[NATSU] You'd better keep
your head in the fight, pal!
[FUTURE ROGUE groans]
[NATSU] I gotta promise
that I intend to keep!
[FUTURE ROGUE] What promise?
What do you mean?
[NATSU] I made a
promise to the Lucy
that came from the future.
[NATSU grunting]
[LUCY panting]
[ZIRCONIS groaning]
Princess. The wizards
can handle things
from this point on,
so we should leave.
I can escort you.
For now, it is my
duty to remain here.
I cannot desert my people
in a time of crisis.
[YUKINO]
But Princess. It's dangerous.
[LUCY]
Hey, I've got something!
You need to look at this! Now!
[HISUI]
What do you want to show us?
[LUCY]
It's my future self's diary!
[YUKINO]
What does it say?
[LUCY huffs]
Read it!
[YUKINO] "Our one hope...
is that the Eclipse gate
in this time period
gets destroyed.
If that happens, the one
that exists in the future
will disappear as well.
And none of the horrible
things will ever happen."
[ARCADIOS]
But can that be true?
[LUCY] Yes, it can't still
be around in the future
if we destroy the
gate in our time!
There will be an entirely
new future where the eclipse
was destroyed in the past.
It'll be gone forever.
Just a part of ancient history.
And if it's not around,
Rogue won't have a way
to travel back in time.
[HISUI] But all of that has
already happened in our time,
so is it still
possible to change it?
[HAPPY]
Yeah, and if we're lucky,
Rogue and the dragons will
get out of our time for good.
Well, it's certainly
worth a try!
[ARCADIOS] You're right. But it
is a rather daunting task.
How can we destroy
that massive structure
when our resources
are spread so thin?
[PANTHERLILY] It won't be
an easy job, that's for sure.
[LUCY] Easy or not
we have to find a way!
The future of the
entire world is at stake here.
Let's take it down. I made
a promise to myself,
and there's no way
I'm gonna break it.
[NATSU] Hey man!
Did ya get a load of
that awesome news?
[HAPPY] All we gotta do
is destroy the Eclipse gate
and all our problems
will be solved!
[NATSU] I mean, could
the job be any more
perfect for us, or what?
[HAPPY] I know! Destroying
stuff is what we do best!
[NATSU] Aw yeah,
I'm fired up now!
[HAPPY] That thing
is pretty big though.
It's gonna take some kinda
plan to bring it down.
[NATSU]
Come on, isn't it obvious?
[HAPPY] Oh. I think
I know what to do!
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next Time: Fields of Gold!
[NATSU] There's only
one thing to do!
[HAPPY]
That's right!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Blast it
with all the magic we've got!