I'm guessing we're here.
Yes, and it took no time at all,
thanks to Sir Warrod's magic.
It beats walking,
that's for sure.
A Wizard Saint's power
is nothing to scoff at.
[retches]
Seriously?
Look there! Those boulders!
[GRAY] It's all frozen,
just like the old man told us.
[ERZA]
The Village of the Sun
must be on the other
end of this trench.
All right! Chow time!
Here's hoping they got more
than cold dishes to serve.
Natsu.
I really don't think you
understand the situation.
[WARROD] These days my
allegiance is to nature.
Every retired man needs a hobby,
mine is turning
deserts into forests.
As you can imagine, I've
seen many peculiar things
traveling about the
deserts of this land.
Most recently, I came
across a village
hidden in the Mountains.
As it turned out, I had
read about this place before.
Known as the Village of
the Sun, its people worship
an ever-burning flame
as their guardian deity.
They've got a fire
that never goes out?
[WARROD]
They do.
But when I got there, the
whole place had frozen over.
[grunts]
[WARROD] Be it by nature,
or the folly of man.
Every person,
plant, and creature.
All the buildings too.
The river was solid ice.
Even the sacred flame
of the village was frozen,
though it burns on, even now.
It's possible to freeze a flame?
Oh, that poor village.
I have no idea what happened
to the people there.
However, one thing
that was clear to me
is that they're still alive.
[HAPPY] I thought you said
they were all frozen?
[CARLA]
None of this makes sense.
The people of that village
are in dire need of help.
They must be restored,
that is why I called on you.
Break the curse of ice.
That is your task.
I leave this task in your hands,
youngsters of Fairy Tail.
Should you face yourselves
in this journey,
I ask you to look closely.
Do this and you shall overcome
whatever obstacles
may fall before your paths.
[ALL yelping]
[ALL laughing, cheering]
This is amazing!
That it is. He can make
a tree fly like a dragon.
[ERZA] The power to
control nature itself.
[GROUP gasping]
It's hard to believe something
could freeze an entire city
and everything
around it so perfectly.
[GRAY grunts]
Strange, Warrod said all
the people were frozen,
but I don't see anyone around.
I wonder where they are.
[NATSU]
Hm?
[BOTH gasping]
[ERZA gasping]
[GRAY grunts]
[BOTH]
Giant!
[NATSU]
Giant! Giant! Giant!
Tiny.
Giant!
[WENDY]
For some reason,
I feel like I was just
the butt of a joke.
[NATSU] That old tree didn't
say anything about giants!
I'm sure he must have
done that on purpose.
You know, I can't
help feeling I kept
a colossal piece of information
from those youngsters.
Oh-ho, that's because I did!
Oh well. Perhaps
he's got dry rot.
[LUCY grunts]
[GRAY grunting]
[UR] Now get outta here
and let me do this.
No! I won't leave!
This is my fault. I'm the one
who should fix it, not you!
Let me do it, Ur!
[UR]
No one's at fault here.
Understand?
This is just something we have
to do in order to be happy.
[GRAY]
Uh.
[UR]
Absolute freeze! Iced shell!
[gasps]
I'm begging!
Please, don't do this!
I promise I'll do whatever
you tell me to from now on!
[UR]
Please, don't cry for me.
I'll live on in the ice.
I may not be with you, but I
will protect you from Deliora.
Be strong. Make me proud.
Please, Ur!
I've sealed it away.
You're free from the darkness.
[grunts]
[GRAY grunts]
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Seeing these giants frozen
in ice, just... ya know.
Oh, that's right. Deliora.
They're quite impressive.
I never knew people
like this existed.
I think I found his dog!
[CARLA]
Hello, nightmare fuel.
All right, then. It's time to
give these oversized popsicles
a wake up call! Ha-ha.
A major case of hot foot
will get him moving for sure!
[HAPPY]
You can do it, Natsu!
[NATSU yelling]
[HAPPY] Go hotter!
Make 'im feel the burn!
This ice is crazy! I'm pooped.
[HAPPY]
Me too.
Oh, right. You did
so much, tomcat.
Remember what Warrod told us?
We're not dealing with
garden-variety ice here.
This is weird. I've never
felt ice like this before.
The magic power
it has is bizarre.
[ERZA] So, we can't melt it from
outside or crack it from inside?
Well, we already knew
this wouldn't be easy.
No way.
[LUCY]
Uh.
I think I recognize the
source of this magic power.
[ALL gasp]
Well, well, well.
Some uninvited guests.
Every job has its shockers.
I didn't expect it to be
kids and their pets, though.
Get lost! Ya dig?
[ALL gasping]
[ERZA]
Who're you?
A treasure hunting trio, baby!
The Sylph Labyrinth guild!
Ya dig?
[ERZA]
Very well.
Why are you all so calm?
Aren't you surprised that
another guild's here?
Nah, this stuff
happens all the time.
Yup.
I've never heard of a
treasure hunter guild.
The title probably tells us
everything we need to know.
Well, I guess it
only makes sense
that even people like these guys
would wanna be
part of a guild too.
Sorry, kids, but we've had dibs
on the treasure here
for a while now.
Why don't you go find your own?
Not interested.
I think we're just
fine staying here.
Oh, ya think so?
I think you should leave, unless
ya wanna be target practice.
Not looking for treasure?
There's gotta be something
that got you to come
all the way out here!
Spill it.
We came to free all
of the villagers.
So we're going to melt
this crazy ice!
[ALL grunt]
Then you're totally
here to get in our way!
Ya dig?
[WENDY, CARLA whimper]
[DRAKE] I'm sure you've heard
about the Eternal Flame
that's burned in this
village for centuries!
[HIROSHI] Even among the most
novice treasure hunters,
the flame is considered
an S-Class treasure!
It's totally legendary!
[RALA]
Ya dig?
[BOTH whimper]
However, thanks to the giants
that guard the
Village of the Sun,
no one's ever been
able to get near it.
[RALA] But, the big guys
were frozen solid,
and good hunters
know opportunity
when it knocks, ya dig?
So, now, we're taking
the Eternal Flame
and getting out while
the getting's good.
You can't!
It's their guardian, the most
sacred part of their village!
If you take it away,
it could destroy them!
Sounds like you aren't treasure
hunters, just common thieves!
[ALL grunt]
We're totally treasure hunters,
and we're gonna leave
here with our treasure!
Finder's keepers is
the law of the land
and we live by it,
whether you like it or not!
Ya dig? Now, scram!
We don't have time
for playing around!
Let's just swipe the treasure
and get outta here,
before these wizards
decide to butt in.
Hm. Totally.
Yeah!
Hate to break it to ya,
but that flame you're after
is frozen solid, just like
everything else in the village!
[DRAKE chuckles]
Underestimating a treasure
hunter on a mission
is never a good idea.
Yeah.
The ice won't be any trouble.
We can melt it all on our own,
with our secret treasure.
Ya gonna make us
guess? What is it?
Heh. Liquid Moon Drip.
[BOTH screaming]
That's a blast from the past!
And it's just what we need!
Lyon used it to free Deliora!
[NARRATOR] Moon Drip is an
incredibly strong and rare magic
that's harvested from the
natural power of the moon.
When used, it can nullify
even the most potent
of spells with ease.
--[LUCY gasps]
--[footsteps]
[DRAKE]
It's been fun!
[HIROSHI]
See ya, losers!
[RALA]
Ya dig?
I never knew it
could be a liquid.
Catch 'em!
If we had that bottle,
we could free the whole village
and be done with this job!
[GROUP]
Oh!
Let's move! They're going
to use all of the Moon Drip!
Not if I can help it!
[NATSU yelling]
These wizards are pretty
light on their feet!
Don't look back, just run!
[RALA yelling]
[NATSU]
Someone steal it!
[GRAY] Beat 'em senseless
if you have to!
[HIROSHI]
And you called us thieves?
Way to be a bunch
of total hypocrites!
[RALA]
No kiddin'!
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
[MAN] Looks like our
work's cut out for us.
It'll be annoying, but we should
deal with these pests first.
S'part of the job, after all.
[WOMAN]
The thieves are irrelevant.
We should focus on
the wizards first.
They're the greatest threat.
[MAN] I guess you
got a point there.
[WOMAN]
Fairy Tail.
[MAN]
Who? You mean those wizards?
[WOMAN]
You've never heard of them?
Just how big is that
rock of ignorance
you've been living
under? I'm curious.
[MAN] The outside world
doesn't concern me.
[WOMAN]
It doesn't matter.
What does is that my
chance for vengeance
came even sooner than I'd hoped.
The underworld has its perks.
[MAN]
Whatever. We got work to do.
Let's go, newbie.
[WOMAN]
M'lady.
Call me anything else, and
it'll be your head that rolls.
[MINERVA chuckles]
[HIROSHI]
The ice won't be any trouble.
We can melt it all on our own,
with our secret treasure.
[NATSU] Ya gonna make
us guess? What is it?
Heh. Liquid Moon Drip.
[BOTH screaming]
I never knew it
could be a liquid.
Catch 'em!
If we had that bottle,
we could free the whole village
and be done with this job!
[GROUP]
Oh!
[NATSU]
Hold it! That means stop!
--[NATSU growls]
--Don't you care
about the giants that are
frozen alive back there?
[DRAKE]
Shut up!
You don't know what
we had to go through
to get this much Moon Drip!
Back off and get your own!
Yeah, you can face the island
of totally terrifying demons
and harvest the magic
for yourselves!
And besides, I don't wanna
give those giants a chance
to get in a good nibble.
I like living too much, ya dig?
Hey, guys? I think we lost Erza!
She's gonna stay in the village
to learn more about the giants
and how we can help them.
Am I the only one who
thinks that's a bad idea?
What are you frozen for? Well?
Mmm. No point worrying now.
Let's focus on what's ahead.
[NATSU]
Get back here, ya thieves!
[DRAKE]
Stop calling us that!
[HIROSHI]
We're treasure hunters!
[RALA]
Ya dig?!
You're takin' from others!
'Scuse me for callin'
it like I see it!
This is getting annoying!
Any bright ideas?
Yeah, let's totally waste 'em.
Drake! Time to get elevated!
Make it quick! Don't be picky.
[DRAKE]
Yeah, yeah!
[ALL grunting]
You spell-slingers wanna
trade insults? That's fine.
But you'll regret
getting in our way.
Now that you have,
you've dug your own grave.
Treasure hunting's dangerous,
and so are treasure hunters.
Ya dig?
Oh, you're about to find
out what real danger is.
We prefer a good fight
to all this runnin' around.
So bring it on!
That's cool with us!
We can totally throw down!
Ya dig?
Ha! Show me what ya got!
[RALA yelling]
[NATSU yelps]
'Kay, that's new!
What's with the hammer hand?
[RALA]
Meet my custom,
face-smashing powerhouse,
the Stronger.
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
[yelping]
[NATSU screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSU grunts]
Natsu!
Are you okay? Say something!
Now I'm mad.
He's fine!
Ice Make Freeze Lancer!
[GRAY yells]
Total Cut!
[yelling]
[GRAY grunts]
How do you like my Chain
Blade? Have another taste!
Total Thrust! Heads up!
[BOTH yelp]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH sigh]
[WENDY grunts]
[BOTH yelp]
A Sniper?
[HAPPY]
Where'd it come from?
I can't tell!
Heh. Aww. You're quicker
than I expected.
But, don't worry. The next shot
will find its mark for sure.
His voice is coming
from all over!
Where's he hiding?
My 74's been aching
to meet her kill quota.
[sniffing]
I smell gunpower.
[grunts]
[WENDY]
Lucy, he's up there!
[LUCY]
Good eye, Wendy!
I'll handle him.
Open, Gate of the Archer!
[bell tolls]
[LUCY]
Sagittarius!
[horse whinnying]
Leave the sharpshooting
to me, my lady!
I'll teach this naïve
foal some manners!
Think so?
[LUCY whimpers]
No way!
What just happened?
Things got a lot harder.
Such skill.
Sorry. but once I've got you
in my sights, you're done for.
Tired?
Not on your life.
We've got a fight on our hands.
Okay, what do I see here?
[ERZA] They're all facing
the same direction
and their weapons are drawn.
But why?
What was happening in this
village before it was frozen?
It's puzzling.
[ERZA]
Then there's the Moon Drip.
There's no way to know
whether that meager amount
will be enough to
free everyone or not.
[gasps]
[ERZA] An army, weapons ready,
frozen by strange magic.
A warzone? And, if so,
what were they fighting?
Or, rather, what were
they all protecting?
Their families? A leader?
The village itself?
Or something intangible?
[gasps]
The Eternal Flame.
[ERZA] The flame is frozen, but
still active. How can I find it?
Pretend you're a giant.
You worship the eternal flame
as your guardian deity.
What would you do
if it were threatened?
[ERZA]
Of course!
I'd keep my back to it
and face the threat head on!
The flame is this way!
A mountain? The flame
must be at the summit!
Second round. Let's see
you deflect this one!
[RALA grunts]
Fire Dragon Wing Attack!
[roaring]
[RALA chuckles]
[grunts]
Ice Make.
Total Cut!
[HIROSHI yells]
All right. I'll play
another round with ya.
[WENDY, LUCY gasp]
[SAGITTARIUS]
On my honor as a spirit,
I shall not fail in this task!
[gasps]
[ERZA panting]
[ERZA]
Nothing. Nothing at all.
I thought if I could
find the Eternal Flame,
I might find a way
to return the village
and its people to normal.
Then again, it's supposed
to be frozen as well.
Even if I found it, I wouldn't
be able to get to it.
I can't give up.
It's here somewhere.
I just have to find it.
[ERZA gasps]
[ERZA]
What sort of madness is this?
[ERZA gasps]
It can't be. This has to
be some kind of illusion.
[LUCY] We've got another
mystery on our hands!
For some reason,
Erza has changed
into a child version of herself.
Why would that happen?
Did the Eternal Flame cause it?
Or is it part of
someone's sinister scheme?
And is there a way to turn her
into her full-grown self again?
On the other side
of this mystery,
a crisis like we've
never faced lies in wait.
Next time: "Art of Regression"!
Watch out, Natsu! I don't
think this guy's here to help.