Finally found you.
Millianna, I--
Listen to me!
It's okay, Erza. Leave it be.
No it isn't.
[ERZA] I've forgiven
Jellal, and so should you.
How could you ever
defend a monster like him?
Did you forget
he murdered Simon?
He has to pay. He's a
liar and a murderer.
I can't forgive that!
I'll kill him or die trying!
[ERZA] I know where that
path leads. A dark, empty place.
Killing him won't
bring back the dead!
[MILLIANNA] So I should just
pretend everything's okay?
I won't do it! This is wrong!
[ULTEAR]
Yes, I agree.
[JELLAL gasps]
[MILLIANNA gasps]
[ULTEAR]
This is wrong.
[HAPPY]
Sin and Sacrifice!
[JELLAL]
Ultear. It's you.
You can't blame
Jellal for the things
he did back then.
He wasn't in control.
Wait, who are you?
I'm the girl who was pulling
the strings the entire time.
[MILLIANNA gasps]
[YOUNG ULTEAR] I feed off
the suffering of others,
and I have gained
much power from you.
You're such a fortunate boy
to have the honor
of speaking with a god.
Yes?
[YOUNG ULTEAR] The most
nefarious wizard in history.
I am Zeref.
I am hatred incarnate.
[YOUNG JELLAL]
We need to stay here, Erza.
[YOUNG ERZA] But we're slaves.
We'll be free once we escape!
[YOUNG ERZA shrieks]
[YOUNG JELLAL]
Fine then, I'll let you leave.
Go on, have a good time
pretending to be free.
However, I swear that I'll
kill everyone you care for
if you ever come back here.
That's the price
of your freedom!
So go on! That is,
if you can stand
with the weight of their
lives on your shoulders.
[MILLIANNA gasps]
[ERZA]
Leave her be, Ultear.
See, that's the kind of
person that I really am.
[ERZA grunts]
[MILLIANNA gasps]
[ULTEAR] Heh. There's no
point in fighting it.
No matter how hard
I try to play the hero,
the truth of it is, I'll
always be rotten at the core.
And what makes you say that?
[ULTEAR] It's a fact.
Anyway, now isn't exactly
the time for us to
stand around chatting.
This area's still crawling with
that mother dragon's offspring.
We should split up
and wipe them out.
And one more thing, kitten.
I alone am to blame
for your friend's death.
As a matter of fact,
I was the architect
of the Tower of Heaven.
[ULTEAR] I'll give you a shot
at revenge once this is over.
So if that's what you want,
you'll have to survive.
[ERZA] Believe it or not,
she's a victim herself.
She was raised as
a test subject,
and taught of nothing but pain.
Honestly, I dunno what
to make of all this.
[JELLAL] We live in a
chaotic and damaged world.
[ERZA] Even so, we have
to keep fighting.
To strive for something better.
[ULTEAR] There's only one way
for me to make things right.
And that is to kill Rogue.
We would just be killing a
completely innocent person.
It's wrong. So, no.
Think of our futures.
Just who would we
be if we did this?
[ULTEAR grunts]
[ULTEAR]
This is who I really am.
[LEVIA roaring]
[STING] Why the hell are
you just sittin' there?
[ROGUE]
Sting, what're you doing?
[STING] Thought I'd drop
by and save your butt!
Let's do this!
Wait, so have you already
beaten your dragon?
[SCISSOR RUNNER roaring]
[STING] Nope! Figured I'd
just bring him with me!
You what?!
No worries dude,
he's super slow!
[ROGUE]
This isn't time for jokes!
[STING]
We're a team, aren't we?
Figured we should
take 'em on together!
[LEVIA] Scissor Runner.
This human has proven
difficult to subdue.
Give me your aid.
[SCISSOR RUNNER] I'm not
interested in taking one alive.
I plan to kill every
single human I can find!
We're the Twin Dragons, right?
So let's kick
their asses. C'mon!
[ROGUE gasps]
Let's go.
[ROGUE] That's right.
As long as I have Sting
watching my back,
nothing can touch me.
[ROGUE] If I'm destined
to be tainted by evil,
then at least I'll have his
light nearby to strike me down!
[SCISSOR RUNNER, LEVIA roaring]
[JUVIA, GRAY, LYON grunting]
Try and beat this.
Ice Make: Snow Tiger!
[LYON grunts]
Ice Cannon!
My studly snowflake's
Ice Cannon. They beat it?
[GRAY] I don't know 'bout
you man, but I'm gettin'
sick and tired of
this underdog crap.
Let's take 'em out together!
Sounds good to me!
Ice Make: Freeze Lancer!
Ice Make: Snow Dragon!
[LYON, GRAY grunt]
They just keep coming.
Come on, we should
fall back and take cover.
Gray, we have to go!
Yeah I get it!
[GRAY, LYON grunting]
Know what these
bastards have in common
with my wife? They're annoying!
[MACAO] I need you to
hang in there, okay buddy?
I know, Dad. I'm fine!
[MACAO] Damn it. Those things
are way tougher than they look.
[WAKABA]
And there's more comin'!
So what're we
gonna do about it?
What can we do?
They've got us surrounded.
You aren't really giving
up on us, are ya?
What?
[ROMEO] I asked you
if you're giving up!
Of course not! Don't be
foolish, listen to me!
Hey! I'm never gonna let
anything hurt you, son!
I don't need your
protection. I've grown up.
I'm strong. Just like you. I'm a
Fairy Tail wizard. I can fight!
[MACAO grunts]
[WAKABA]
Hate to interrupt guys!
But they tracked
us down. Incoming!
[ROMEO, MACAO grunting]
Are you okay?
I'm not finished yet.
I can keep this up
all day if I gotta.
I sure wish I could
say the same but...
I'm old.
[WAKABA]
Stop your whinin'.
Ya know, I'm gettin'
a little old for this too.
Damn it.
[ROCK DRAGON]
Is this Dragon Slayer Magic
you've been tickling me with?
[COBRA] I'm gonna
need ya to keep that
ugly mouth of yours shut.
You sound like a pack
of dying Vulcans,
and I have sensitive ears.
See, I'm in a great
mood now that
I've been busted out of prison.
And I'd like to take in as
many voices as possible.
Problem is, this lame
excuse for a boulder
keeps makin' noise!
[ROCK DRAGON]
Petulant insect!
[COBRA] Heard that comin'
from a mile away!
Better luck next time.
You shall not face
this threat alone!
[COBRA] Keep back where
you belong! Sideliner!
[COBRA]
Poison Dragon Gouge Horn!
[ROCK DRAGON roaring]
What did you call--?
[ICHIYA groaning]
My patootie! You have disfigured
my most beautiful asset! Man!
[COBRA] And that's why I told
ya to keep to the sidelines.
[ROCK DRAGON roaring]
This ain't good. It doesn't
seem wounded at all.
[NATSU] I gotta admit,
you're tougher than I thought.
Bring it on!
[FUTURE ROGUE] You can't
stop me. My will is iron!
That ain't enough. 'Cause my
flames have shattered iron!
[ULTEAR]
I stopped just short of murder.
I didn't go through with it.
But that isn't the problem.
The fact is that
I would've done it.
Without a second thought, I
would've killed an innocent man!
Why would that be the first
place that my mind turns?
Unless some part of
me still craves it.
[ULTEAR] Who am I fooling?
I haven't changed a bit.
[ULTEAR]
Crime Sorcière? What a joke.
I could never atone
for the sins of my past.
Is anyone here? Hello?
[LUCY] I've gotta find the
others. They need to know--
[LUCY screaming]
[LUCY grunting]
That hurt.
[LUCY gasps]
[ROCK DRAGON roaring]
[LUCY] Little dragons!
They're everywhere!
I'm completely surrounded.
No. I won't make it in time!
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
What's happening?
[LUCY shrieks]
Flare?
[LUCY] Uh. Okay then.
Thank you! Sorry. Gotta run!
[FLARE grunts]
Let's see how ya like this!
[ZIRCONIS groaning]
Damn you!
[LAXUS] You're goin' up
against the wrong guy,
ya old pervert!
[ZIRCONIS]
That cocky attitude will only
get you so far, little insect.
[LAXUS gasps]
[ZIRCONIS roars]
[ALL grunting]
[LAXUS groans]
[ZIRCONIS cackling]
[LAXUS] If you're gonna go
around callin' people insects,
then you'd better be ready
to face the consequences!
[ZIRCONIS grunts] That's good.
Keep it coming, you little brat!
Bastard.
[ERZA grunts]
[JELLAL grunts]
[ERZA]
There's way too many of them!
[JELLAL]
You're feeling overwhelmed?
Well this is a first.
I wouldn't call it that.
[JELLAL]
Good then.
Because if the two
of us come together...
[JELLAL] ...I know we
can take on anything!
[ERZA] Of course we can!
Now get to work!
[JET] Just keep on
tryin', ol' buddy.
We gotta get you back up
on your feet, alright?
Aw. Man. You're really
heavy, ya know that?
It's no use.
My legs are shot.
[DROY] There's no way
I can walk like this.
Damn it! Pull yourself
together, let's go!
Y'know, This is why
I'm always naggin' you
about goin' on a diet!
I'm finished, okay?
Don't let me weigh you down.
You have to get out
of here, right now!
No! We're in this
together, ya' hear?
Both of us are gonna make it!
[DROY] That hurt even
worse than the last one.
[JET]
They almost got us that time.
It's now or never, you big
lug. Just get up, please.
[DROY] Listen man.
My legs won't even move.
I'm really worried
about Levy right now.
You gotta go and
find her for me.
One of us has to look after her.
I won't leave!
Man, I'd like to
lay down myself.
My side's killin' me.
They got me good all right.
But I ain't about to run off
and save Levy
without ya, buddy.
You're comin' with me, Droy.
We'll save her together.
[JET coughing] She needs both
of us. So you gotta get up!
I'm sorry, Jet.
I know I'm too heavy.
Don't you dare give up! It
ain't over while we've still got
the will to fight, okay bud?
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY]
I have to tell them.
I have to tell everyone
as soon as I can!
[HAPPY]
Hello! Is anyone there?
Where are you guys?
This can't be for real.
It might be the worst
nightmare I've ever had, but,
it's too horrible to be real!
[ELFMAN yelling]
[ELFMAN grunts]
Big Brother, you okay?
I'll help you fight them!
[ELFMAN] Stay back, Lisanna.
It's too dangerous!
If we take them on together,
we may have a shot at this!
[ELFMAN]
I don't think so.
You'd better get out of here and
support the rest of the guild!
There're too many of 'em
gathered for us to beat.
I'll rush in and distract 'em.
That'll be your chance to run!
Damn you! I'm gonna
show you bastards
what Fairy Tail is made of!
Don't be stupid, come back!
[ELFMAN yelling]
Manly attack!
[LEVY]
This way! Keep moving!
There's no guarantee
that this spot'll stay safe.
[LEVY]
Gajeel...
Have a taste of my
Iron Dragon. Roar!
[DARK DRAGON maoning]
[GAJEEL] Alright. Now let's
see if you can still crawl.
What the hell? I didn't
even leave a scratch!
Yeah, that's it!
Good job, Uncle!
Attack from above!
[NATSU groaning]
[FUTURE ROGUE] That's the
price of underestimating
Dragon Tamer magic.
You ain't seen nothin'!
We're only gettin' started!
Is anybody here?
[HAPPY grunts]
[WAKABA groaning]
[ROMEO]
How ya holdin' up, Dad?
[MACAO]
I'm alright. But I won't lie.
We're in a tough spot.
[WAKABA] Yeah. And I
thought fightin' in the games
seemed hard. That was nothin'!
[ROMEO gasps]
[HAPPY] I'm so glad
that you're okay! Romeo!
[ROMEO]
Happy!
[HAPPY]
Wakaba! Uh. And let's see.
[MACAO] Macao. I've
known you for years.
Aw, c'mon! Did you
seriously forget that?
[ALL grunting]
[ROMEO grunting]
Crap! Something hit my shoulder.
[WAKABA] Stay tough,
buddy. Agh, my back.
[MACAO] At least, it looks as
though you're alright, Happy.
I'll go get you guys some
help, okay? Just wait here!
[HAPPY]
Is there a problem?
[WAKABA] No need for all that.
We'll be just fine on our own.
[HAPPY]
But you're hurt.
I've gotta find a way
to get you help!
[WAKABA]
Don't worry about us, Happy.
We old timers have been
in way bigger jams
than this one before.
You heard the man.
We don't need
anybody rescuin' us,
so get on outta here.
[HAPPY] No way! I'm not just
gonna ditch you guys!
We're Fairy Tail wizards.
And that means we can
take care of ourselves.
My dad knows what
he's talkin' about.
Are you sure, Romeo?
We're glad to be
a part of this.
[ROMEO] Natsu's giving it all
he's got. So is everyone else.
We wanna help!
If there ever was a time
to fight, it's now!
I understand.
Alright then, I'll go!
But you have to
make me a promise!
[WAKABA]
What kinda promise?
[HAPPY] The kind where
all of you stay alive!
That's the only way I'll leave!
Well, you drive a real
hard bargain, cat.
You've got yourself a deal.
Sure hope I wasn't lyin'.
What'd you say?
You just had to put
on the tough guy act
'cause your son's watchin', huh?
[ALL groaning]
[MELDY panting]
Juvia!
Meldy, it's you!
[MELDY] I lost track
of Ultear a while back!
Have you seen her?
[JUVIA]
I can't say I have.
[GRAY]
Get down!
[LYON]
Stay focused!
This is a war-zone!
[MELDY]
Sorry!
[JUVIA gasps] I can still feel
the warmth of Gray's hand
on my tushie!
[GRAY]
Juvia. Listen for a sec.
There's somethin'
I've been meaning
to tell ya for a while now.
Um. Whatever "something"
is, I'm ready to hear it!
[GRAY] I mean it's not
that big of a deal, but...
You never know. It might be
a really big deal for me!
Looks like this is about
to get really awkward.
[JUVIA] Could this be the
moment I've always dreamed of?
Will he confess his
love to me at last?
Oh my goodness.
What will I say?
Juvia! Move!
[JUVIA gasps]
[GRAY groans]
[LYON gasps]
[MELDY gasps]
[GRAY]
I'm hit.
[JUVIA screaming]
[LYON] Gray!
[ULTEAR]
I'm unfit for this world.
I don't deserve to live.
[NATSU] Damn! We haven't
taken down a single dragon yet!
[HAPPY]
We can't give up now, Natsu!
All our friends from
Fairy Tail and the other guilds
are riskin' their tails
to protect the kingdom!
We can't let 'em show us up!
[NATSU] Well yeah, I know!
Plus if I gave up now,
it would destroy
Fairy Tail's reputation!
[HAPPY] Yeah! We can't afford
to show any weakness
at a time like this!
[NATSU] We ain't givin' in,
no matter what!
[HAPPY] I'm gonna fight
my hardest just like you!
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next time: Time of Life!
[NATSU]
We're almost there, Happy!
Let's give it one last push!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!