Darkness, we beseech thee.
Envelop our light and swallow
us into your infinite shadow.
Sever the bonds that
shackle us to the heavens.
Release us from our perpetual
enslavement and set us free!
[GROUP]
Liberam!
[NATSU] Geez, are we
ever gonna get there?
Eventually, but I'm afraid
it's still a ways off.
My feet are killing me.
[YUKINO] I suppose I'd have
dressed differently
if I knew we'd be climbing
mountains today.
[HAPPY] Well, I got no
complaints. This is a breeze!
[HISUI pants]
[ARCADIOS]
Princess, are you alright?
[HISUI]
Yes, I'll be fine.
[NATSU]
Whoa.
[HISUI] It's said fog is the
doorway to the Astral Spiritus.
[NATSU]
You mean the fog itself?
[HISUI]
That's right.
Throughout the course
of human history.
Numerous legends were
born from this place.
The sacred site
of Astral Spiritus.
Countless souls
have journeyed here
seeking the origin
of celestial magic.
But those who entered this fog
were never heard from again.
This spot is where all quests
for Astral Sprirtus have ended.
So this is the
point of no return.
No one's made it
through alive?
So the legends say.
But forward is our only option.
[HISUI]
Now, take your keys.
These will carry us through
the rest of our journey.
So let's go.
[HAPPY]
Astral Spiritus!
[LOKE]
O, Lord of Darkness.
O, Lord of Stars.
O, Lord of Eternity!
We beg thee hear our solemn
prayers and grant us liberation.
Release our spirits into
infinite time and space.
[LOKE]
O, my star-bound brethren.
Let the flames of darkness
burn away our celestial prison.
Let the holy black
light of the Liberam
guide us down the path
of true freedom!
They will purify us, and cleanse
us of our miserable fates.
Their light will merge with ours
and grant us divine radiance!
The time has come.
[ALL grunting]
[TAURUS grunting]
Moo.
[ALL grunting]
[NATSU]
Party's over guys!
[LOKE grunts]
[NATSU growls]
[LOKE grunts
[NATSU gasps]
[NATSU grunts]
You'll pay for this...
...with your life!
[grunting]
[NATSU groans]
[NATSU]
You're really serious.
[LUCY]
We found 'em!
[YUKINO]
And just in time.
[NATSU gasps]
[LOKE grunts]
[gasps]
[NATSU growls]
[NATSU panting]
Where is the globe?
[LOKE grunts]
[NATSU grunts]
It seems we'll have to
locate it ourselves.
[LUCY]
Please! You have to stop this!
I know that you don't
want to believe me.
But even if the Liberam spell
does what you want it to,
you'll only be
free for 12 days!
And then it'll all be over.
[LOKE]
We know.
[LUCY gasps]
Huh?
You're aware of
the true cost?
So why are you going
through with it?
12 days isn't really
that much time, you know?
Hmph. That's more than
enough time for us.
[GROUP gasps]
Whatever the cost for freedom,
we will gladly pay it.
Seriously?
[LOKE] The only birthright
we spirits can claim
is our enslavement to humans.
We exceed them in
every possible way,
but still that is
our fate in life.
Or should I say
that was our fate.
What we do here
will change that.
Even if it costs
us our lives!
I would never consider any
of you to be my slaves!
You've always been my
most treasured friends.
You're like family!
I can't bear the thought
of losing you!
I don't care
what you think!
These losers are
nothin' but talk anyway.
'Cause I got all of their
Closure Keys right here with me!
Uh! What the?
Where'd they go?
[LOKE gasps]
[PISCES BOY, MOM gasp]
Hate to break it
to ya, fish face,
but those ain't the real things.
What you stole from us
were just a bunch of fakies!
We have the real ones!
That's so smart!
Good job kids!
Don't compliment 'em
for it. Crazy hag!
[PISCES MOM]
How can you be so cruel?
Do you want to see your
dear, sweet mother cry?
Will that finally
make you happy?
Not this crap again.
Piri, piri!
Forgive me, Leo.
I totally screwed that up!
Time for punishment!
No, I'm the one who raised him,
so it's all my fault!
[TAURUS]
Moo. We've been punished enough.
What do you suggest we do, Leo?
I think the use of force
may be necessary.
I'm totally down with that!
There're way more of us
then there are of them.
Let's rip 'em to shreds!
That sounds like a whole
lot of fun to me! Yeah!
You know I wanna!
The time to
strike is now.
They're powerless against us.
Tell me, humans.
Do you wish to rob us of
what little freedom we have
and force our gates to close?
It's not like that at all!
The only thing I want
is to save your lives!
[LOKE]
I've heard enough.
No more lies from you!
[TAURUS]
Moo!
[VIRGO cackles]
[PISCES BOY growls]
[ARIES grunts]
[CANCER laughs]
[ARCADIOS] Are you ready
to take them on, Natsu?
Yeah!
[ARCADIOS grunting]
[VIRGO, LUCY grunt]
Solid Script Magic.
Thunderbolt!
[TAURUS]
My, my.
It seems the young lady
does not have the courage
to attack us directly.
How lame!
Well that's just too bad.
Because we are gonna
rip you a new one!
What do we do?
Any ideas, Lucy?
We gotta talk some
sense into 'em.
We didn't come all this way to
start a fight with you guys!
We came to save you!
You think we don't
know what we're doing?
We're getting our freedom,
and you won't stop us!
[NATSU growls]
Natsu!
You're gonna regret that!
[NATSU yelps]
[VIRGO cackling]
[HAPPY]
I got ya!
[VIRGO cackling]
[NATSU yelling]
[VIRGO grunts]
[NATSU yelps]
[NATSU groans]
You guys!
How in the heck
did you find us?
These monsters haven't
hurt you, have they?
We're fine.
[TAURUS] What an udderly
unfortunate turn of events.
This totally sucks, man!
It's infuriating.
[LOKE grunts]
[CANA] You guys can
thank Warren for this.
[LUCY]
He found us?
[HAPPY]
What a cool guy!
[MIRAJANE]
Yeah.
He was able to use his
telepathy to track you.
So all of us followed
the signal up the mountain
and into the fog.
I'll be sure to
thank him later!
You can do something nice
for him when you get home!
Can't say I'd want to
read anyone's mind,
but it comes in handy.
[ERZA] So this is
the Astral Spiritus?
And the Liberam
was not done?
That's right.
[GAJEEL] Heh, heh. I've always
wanted to go a couple of rounds
with some celestial spirits!
[PANTHERLILY]
That's great,
but we didn't come
here to fight them.
Yeah, I know that!
I'm just saying!
This ain't a freebie.
You're going to owe me big
time for saving your butt.
I thought you were
just being a bro!
Oh my bold,
bare-chested, brawler!
I'm all ready for you Loke,
so step up and get some!
Do you really have to say
that after you strip down?
[LOKE growls]
You're a dead man!
[NATSU growls]
[growling]
[NATSU panting]
[LOKE] If you really wanna
stop us, follow us in!
We'll show you just how far
we'll go for true freedom!
Loke!
Where're they goin'?
[HISUI]
No, wait!
Why?
I will give a key
to each one of you.
[HISUI]
By using them,
you will be able to close
the spirits' gates by force.
This is the only hope
we have to stop them now.
Then give me Loke's!
Please, let me deal with him.
I know you mean well, Lucy,
but there is no way
he's gonna listen to you.
But this might just
change his mind.
I know that he's lost his way.
But he's still my friend,
so don't take it too far.
[NATSU]
I won't, I swear.
Take this.
It's the lion's key.
We're in the rift between
our world and theirs.
It's uncharted territory.
So please be careful.
I will.
Let's go, Happy!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
Thank you, Princess.
I give you my solemn word
that we will not let you down.
We can't afford to fail.
Alright, are you ready?
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[LUCY grunts]
[LUCY]
Where am I?
[LUCY grunts]
[whip cracks]
[LUCY]
There you are!
[VIRGO]
It is you.
But it's hardly a surprise.
I had a very strong feeling
that you would be the one to
come for me, Lucy Heartfilia.
[ERZA]
Is this some kind of joke?
[SAGITTARIUS]
I've recreated a battle scene,
reminiscent of days long past.
Is that so?
[ERZA]
These are just paper-mache.
[SAGITTARIUS]
I'm a firm believer in creating
an appropriate atmosphere.
Best two out of three takes it.
[ERZA]
We're to shoot down the targets?
[YUKINO gasps]
[LIBRA]
Balance is essential.
Between our kind and yours.
I'm sorry.
But I don't understand
what you mean by that.
[SCORPIO]
Battle coliseum, open.
[CANA]
Huh? What the hell is this?
[SCORPIO] I hear that you're
quite skilled with cards.
So how about the two of
us play a little game?
[CANA]
What?
[SCORPIO]
We'll begin with six cards each.
[CANA]
Sounds fun, but...
[SCORPIO]
Do it!
[CANA]
Fine, here I go.
But, they're all blank.
Guild Battle, begin!
Huh?
The scorpion goes first!
Draw sequence!
So are you ready
to duel with me?
[CANA]
Wait a sec!
Why don't you tell me
the rules first?
[SCORPIO]
I am the rules.
That doesn't make any sense!
[GRAY]
Not what I was expecting!
[CANCER] Bum, bum bum,
bah dum bah dum, yeah!
[GRAY]
Alright let's do this!
[CANCER] I thought the
cool one would wanna dance.
So let's get down and
set this floor on fire!
[GRAY]
Huh?
[CANCER]
Yeah!
Let's boogie, man!
It's hot.
[JUVIA]
And completely deserted.
C'mon Aries!
Where are you?
What the?
Is there something
stuck to my head?
Uh, what the heck is going on?
[CAPRICORN] We're about
to begin our contest.
What contest?
[CAPRICORN]
A quiz!
Worthy of a Zodiac Spirit!
A game show?
[CAPRICORN]
I suppose.
Each contestant
will be presented
with a series of questions
they must answer.
There are ten in all.
Once the final score is tallied,
the winner will then be
granted complete freedom.
And the loser will suffer
a truly horrible fate.
Oh... I don't like
the sound of that.
But why are we playing
a trivia game?
Well, because I'm rather
fond of them, that's why.
Now then.
[FEMALE HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Fairy Tail Cult Quiz,
Question Number One!
[NATSU] Uh, so, is this just
some big stack of rocks?
[HAPPY] Uh, they're
called ruins, genius.
[NATSU grunts]
[HAPPY screams]
[LOKE growls]
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU]
Let's get one thing straight.
There's no way I'm gonna let
you guys forget about Lucy.
I just couldn't stand to see her
go through that kind of pain.
[LOKE chuckles]
[WENDY] It looks like we're
in an amusement park, Carla.
[CARLA]
Well, I'm certainly not amused.
[WENDY, CARLA gasp]
[AQUARIUS giggles]
Hey there!
This spoiled child
needs a spanking!
Aw. Let's play!
[MIRAJANE] This is definitely
nicer than I expected.
Hm?
[MIRAJANE groans]
[MIRAJANE gasps]
[PISCES MOM] Very good!
You're a great swimmer!
[PISCES BOY]
What's up, girl?
Come on. Let's have
some fun in the water!
If you're looking for us,
we're over here!
It's hide and go seek!
We didn't come here to play
silly children's games!
[GAJEEL]
Especially not with these two
annoying little rugrats.
[GEMI]
Piri, piri.
These guys aren't
any fun at all.
[MINI]
Yeah, they're really boring.
[BOTH gasp]
[GEMI, MINI]
Piri, piri, pikkiri!
[BOTH grunt]
It's blinding me!
Well, I gotta say, this
seems like an excellent spot
for a little man on man action!
[TAURUS]
Moo.
You should know, referring to
me as a man is a big mistake.
Well, whatever you are,
I came here to school
you on your manners,
so let's get to it.
[TAURUS] Indeed,
we shall make this quick.
I have a quite a few things
I need to do today.
[ELFMAN yells]
[ELFMAN]
Hey. What gives?
I can't land a hit!
[TAURUS] Moo. It would seem
your muscles are just for show.
Oh, so that's what
you think, is it?
In that case, let me
give you a show!
[ELFMAN]
Beast Soul!
[TAURUS] First, you talk
about being a man,
then you turn into
a filthy animal?
You're nothing
but a talking cow!
[ELFMAN growls]
[TAURUS]
Change into whatever you like,
it will make no difference.
[ELFMAN growls]
[ELFMAN yells]
[TAURUS] Now, let me have
some peace and quiet.
[ELFMAN] You think
you can just ignore me,
and read your little book?
Well, I'll just have
to knock that thing
right outta your hooves, pal!
[TAURUS]
Moo.
It's no wonder a dullard like
you would attack a book.
[ELFMAN groans]
[TAURUS] Your low
intelligence is reflected
in your fighting style.
That's why you revert
to beastly forms. You can't
expect to win that way.
It's just all brawn
with no brains.
Perhaps you can inscribe
that on your tombstone.
[TAURUS]
Moo.
What a farce.
We've got serious beef now.
[TAURUS]
Moo!
Moo?
[ELFMAN growls]
[TAURUS whimpers]
[ELFMAN]
Huh?
[TAURUS]
How completely disgusting!
So unclean!
And it's all over my
nicely pressed suit!
Huh? My sweat.
[TAURUS] It's revolting.
And it smells so foul!
That's the sweat of a man!
Now taste it, cow!
[TAURUS moaning]
I think I'm gonna be sick!
Eat this!
[TAURUS]
Moo!
[ELFMAN grunts]
[TAURUS whimpers]
[ELFMAN laughs]
[TAURUS] Moo! No moore!
I can't take any moore of this!
So get lost!
[TAURUS]
No! You're forcing my gate!
Moo!
Oh, boy.
But that got the job
done. Manly style!
[ARCADIOS] It seems the bull
was the first to fall.
[HISUI]
Wonderful!
I was confident that Fairy Tail
would never let us down.
Now 11 remain.
Good luck.
We're counting on you.
[NATSU grunts]
[HAPPY] They get to go
to an amusement park?
No fair!
[NATSU] It makes me sick
just thinkin' about it.
[HAPPY]
Yeah, you can't go on rides
without tossing
your cookies, huh?
[NATSU retches] Oh man,
I'm so going to hurl.
[HAPPY] Wait a second, I can
use my hypnosis to cure you!
[NATSU]
You can really do that?
[HAPPY] You're not gonna barf.
You're not gonna barf.
[NATSU]
What do you know? It's work--!
Never mind.
[HAPPY]
I tried!
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: Wendy vs. Aquarius.
Let's Have Fun in
the Amusement Park!
[HAPPY] You'd think
your little pea brain
would be easy to hypnotize.
[NATSU] You don't
have to be so mean.