- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON FAIRY TAIL...
- Happy: SCARY LUCY
SAVED THE DAY!
- Natsu: DEEP DOWN,
THE REAL LUCY AND THE SCARY ONE
AREN'T SO DIFFERENT AFTER ALL.
- Lucy: QUIT CALLING US "REAL"
AND "SCARY," WOULD YOU?
- Happy: BUT THREE LUCYS
TOGETHER WAS JUST WAY TOO MUCH.
- Lucy: I HAVE TO AGREE.
- Natsu: THE THREE OF
YOU SHOULD COMBINE INTO
ONE GIANT MEGA LUCY!
- Happy: THERE'S ENOUGH MONSTERS
IN THE WORLD ALREADY.
- Lucys: WATCH IT, CAT!
- CAN WE PLEASE JUST
GET BACK TO THE STORY?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I DON'T KNOW WHY. I'M SORRY!
PLEASE, DON'T HURT ME!
- All: HUH?
- Natsu: WHAT THE...
ARE YOU THE SAME OTHER ME
FROM JUST A MINUTE AGO?
- YES! OF COURSE
I'M THE EXACT SAME GUY!
BUT PEOPLE SAY I'M LIKE A
DIFFERENT PERSON
BEHIND THE WHEEL!
- THIS WORLD'S NATSU
IS A TOTAL SCAREDY-CAT!
- ( whimpers ) PLEASE,
YOU GUYS ARE FREAKING ME OUT!
DON'T SCREAM.
- IT'S JUST LIKE LOOKING
INTO A MIRROR, ISN'T IT, NATSU?
- ( Happy reading out
on screen text )
- I'M SORRY!
I'M REALLY, REALLY, SORRY!
BUT THIS IS AS FAR AS
I CAN TAKE YOU!
- HOW COME?
- THE ONLY REASON I CAME
IN THE FIRST PLACE IS
BECAUSE MY LUCY TOLD ME
I HAD TO!
- AWW, WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO ANYTHING THAT SCARES YOU.
- WE DEFINITELY DON'T HAVE
ROOM FOR A BLUBBERING COWARD
ON OUR TEAM.
- DON'T BE RUDE!
- HMM.
HEY, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I BET IT'S WENDY, RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- OH, WOW.
YOU'RE SUCH A CUTE LITTLE GIRL.
AND YOU'RE EARTH LAND'S VERSION
OF ME?
- ARE YOU JUST NOW
FIGURING THAT ONE OUT?
- WELL, MY NAME IS HAPPY.
AND THIS BEAUTY IS CARLA.
- AND I'M LUCY. BUT YOU
ALREADY KNOW MY NAME, DON'T YOU?
- ( exclaims ) I'M SORRY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO MAKE IT UP TO YOU!
- GEEZ, LUCY, GIVE "SCARED ME"
A BREAK, WOULD YOU?
- THE LUCY THAT
I KNOW FROM HERE
TOLD ME I NEEDED TO BRING YOU
THIS FAR. SO, I DID.
- IS THAT THE PLACE?
- I THINK IT'S THE ROYAL CITY.
- IT'S SO BIG!
- ( laughs )
YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD US
WE WERE HERE SOONER!
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SO SORRY!
- THIS IS AWESOME.
WE'LL BE BUSTIN' OUT
OUR FRIENDS IN NO TIME!
- THEY'RE ALL DOWN THERE,
TRAPPED INSIDE OF
SOME GIANT LACRIMA.
- WE MUSTN'T WASTE TIME.
- HOLD ON A SECOND!
- THANKS A MILLION, BUDDY!
- Lucy: SAY HI TO ME FOR ME!
- HEY, WAIT!
YOU'RE REALLY DOING IT?
FIGHTING THE KINGDOM?
- I DON'T KNOW. WE'RE JUST GONNA
TRY TO GET OUR FRIENDS BACK.
BUT IF THE KINGDOM DECIDES
IT WANTS TO GET IN OUR WAY,
I GUESS WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO FIGHT 'EM.
- ( gasps )
- ( wind whooshing )
- WELL, I HATE TO BE SAYIN'
THIS, BUT YOU CAN'T BEAT THEM.
- ( laughs )
- ( festive music playing )
- ( people chattering )
- ( men laughing )
- ( children laughing )
- THEY'RE SO HAPPY.
- IT'S NOT WHAT I EXPECTED.
I THOUGHT THIS PLACE
WOULD BE DARK AND SCARY.
- NOT EXACTLY MY IDEA OF A
DICTATORSHIP, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- AND WE GOT INTO THE CITY
WITHOUT HAVING TO FIGHT
A SINGLE GUARD.
- COMPARED TO ALL THE OTHER
TOWNS WE'VE BEEN TO,
IT'S LIKE A FAIR.
- I'M SURE IT'S BECAUSE THEY
STEAL MAGIC FROM EVERYWHERE
AND HOARD IT ALL HERE.
THEN THEY TRY TO
GLOSS OVER THEIR CRIMES
TO MAKE IT MORE PALATABLE
TO THE GENERAL PUBLIC.
- WELL, IT'S NOT WORKING FOR ME.
- HEY, GUYS, IT LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON OVER HERE!
- ARE THEY HAVING
A PARADE OR SOMETHING?
- Natsu: OOH! LIKE THEIR VERSION
OF FANTASIA?
- Happy: AYE, SIR!
- Carla: WE'RE HERE
FOR BUSINESS,
NOT PLEASURE, REMEMBER?
- Natsu: WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHY'S EVERYONE CHEERING?
- Lucy: HOLD ON, NATSU!
- Happy: WHOA!
IT'S SUPER CROWDED OVER HERE!
- GEEZ.
HEY! IF YOU'RE GONNA STOP
IN FRONT OF ME LIKE THAT,
WARN ME!
( gasps )
- NO. THAT'S A LACRIMA.
- A GIANT ONE. WHICH MEANS...
- ALL OF OUR FRIENDS
ARE INSIDE OF THERE.
- AND IF YOU LOOK CLOSELY,
YOU CAN SEE THAT THERE'S
A MISSING PIECE.
- WHAT? YOU MEAN THERE'S MORE
OF THAT THING SOMEWHERE?
- ( crowd cheering )
( loud cheering )
- ( sobbing )
- CHILDREN OF EDOLAS,
IT BRINGS GREAT JOY TO MY HEART
TO TELL YOU
THAT OUR ANIMA PROGRAM
HAS PRODUCED ENOUGH MAGIC POWER
TO LAST ANOTHER DECADE!
- YOU DIDN'T PRODUCE
A DARN THING.
ALL YOU DID WAS BREAK INTO OUR
WORLD AND STEAL IT FROM US!
- PLEASE CONTROL
YOUR TEMPER, TOMCAT.
- LET US REJOICE TOGETHER!
LET US SING AND DANCE!
LET LAUGHTER ROAR
THROUGH OUR SACRED KINGDOM!
- ( cheering )
- THE POWER WITHIN THIS LACRIMA
BELONGS TO ALL LOYAL SUBJECTS
OF OUR FAIR HOMELAND!
TODAY WE HOLD OUR FUTURE
IN OUR HANDS
TO ENSURE ITS PROSPERITY
INTO TOMORROW AND BEYOND!
THEREFORE WE MUST SWEAR
TO PROTECT THIS GIFT FROM HEAVEN
WITH OUR VERY LIVES!
MY DEAR CHILDREN,
TODAY I SHALL MAKE
A MOST SOLEMN PLEDGE TO YOU
AS YOUR BENEVOLENT RULER.
I WILL BRING YOU MORE POWER.
SO MUCH MORE THAN
YOU COULD POSSIBLY IMAGINE.
- ( cracking )
- ( crowd chanting )
EDOLAS! EDOLAS!
- MAN, WHAT A JOKE.
THE PEOPLE HERE
ARE A BUNCH OF SUCKERS.
THEY WENT FOR HIS WHOLE ACT,
HOOK, LINE, AND SINKER.
NOW WHAT AM I GONNA DO
ABOUT THIS?
- ( Natsu grunting )
- STAY STRONG!
- IT'S THEM, OUR FRIENDS.
WE GOTTA GET THEM OUT OF THERE!
- ( sobs )
WE WILL! JUST WAIT.
WE'LL GET THEM ALL BACK.
NATSU, PLEASE.
- ( laughing )
- I CAN'T JUST SIT AROUND
LIKE THIS FOREVER.
I'M STORMIN' THE CASTLE!
- Carla: THAT WON'T DO ANY GOOD!
- OH, YEAH, WHY NOT?
- WITHOUT A SOLID
STRATEGY IN PLACE,
YOU DON'T HAVE A PRAYER
OF SAVING ANYONE.
- ( guttural groan )
- BUT STILL, THEY WERE
TURNED INTO THAT CRYSTAL.
AND WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO CHANGE THEM BACK.
- HMM. THE KING WILL JUST
HAVE TO TELL US THAT HIMSELF.
- BUT HE'D NEVER DO THAT!
- HE WILL
IF WE BEAT IT OUT OF HIM!
- HEY, YEAH!
DO YOU THINK THAT THE KING
ACTUALLY DOES KNOW
HOW TO REVERSE THE SPELL?
- PROBABLY.
- THEN WE STILL HAVE A CHANCE!
IF WE GET CLOSE TO THE KING,
WE CAN PULL THIS OFF.
- FOR REAL?
- BUT HOW DO WE SAVE THEM?
- WITH GEMINI!
REMEMBER, NOT ONLY DO THEY
HAVE THE POWER
TO TURN INTO THE
PEOPLE THEY TOUCH,
THEY CAN ALSO READ THE MINDS OF
WHOEVER THEY TURN INTO.
WHICH MEANS IF THEY'RE ABLE
TO TRANSFORM INTO THE KING,
THEN THEY'LL ALSO BE ABLE
TO TELL US EVERYTHING HE KNOWS.
- OH!
- TIMING IS GONNA BE
A MAJOR ISSUE WITH USING THEM,
BECAUSE THEY CAN ONLY
TRANSFORM INTO SOMEONE
FOR NO MORE THAN FIVE MINUTES
AND THEY CAN ONLY REMEMBER
A COUPLE OF PEOPLE AT A TIME,
LITERALLY, JUST TWO,
SO THERE'S THAT.
BUT THE REAL QUESTION IS,
HOW ARE WE GONNA
GET CLOSE ENOUGH TO HIM?
THAT'S TOUGH.
- YEAH, NO JOKE. HE ALWAYS HAS
A LOT OF GUARDS SURROUNDING HIM.
- I'VE COME UP WITH A PLAN
FOR GETTING WITHIN RANGE.
- ( all gasp )
- AS WITH ANY HOME
OF A PARANOID RULER,
WHEN THE CASTLE
WAS CONSTRUCTED,
THERE WAS A TUNNEL BUILT
AS AN ESCAPE ROUTE,
WHICH LINKS UP WITH A MINE SHAFT
JUST OUTSIDE OF THE CITY WALL.
- THERE IS?
BUT HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
- IT'S JUST IN MY HEAD, COMING
TO ME IN LITTLE BITS AND PIECES.
FROM THE MOMENT
WE FIRST SET FOOT IN EDOLAS,
IT'S AS THOUGH
I HAVE A MENTAL MAP
THAT'S SLOWLY BEING FILLED IN.
- WELL, MY HEAD IS STILL EMPTY.
- IF WE CAN FIND THAT TUNNEL,
THEN WE MAY HAVE A REAL SHOT
AT GETTING CLOSE ENOUGH
TO THE KING.
- ALL RIGHT! LET'S GET INSIDE
THAT GEEZER'S HEAD!
- LET'S GO!
- AYE-AYE, SIR!
- NOT YET!
- WHY YOU ALWAYS STOPPIN' ME?
- WE'LL GO
UNDER THE COVER OF NIGHT.
UNTIL THEN, WE SHOULD TRY
TO GET SOME REST.
WE SHOULD BE ARRIVING AT
THE ENTRANCE
TO THE TUNNEL ANY MOMENT NOW!
- IS THIS IT?
- YES. I'M POSITIVE.
- IN WE GO.
- WAIT.
- AGAIN WITH THE STOPPIN'?
- I UNDERSTAND THAT TIME
IS OF THE ESSENCE, TRUST ME.
BUT WE WILL NEED
A SOURCE OF LIGHT IN THE TUNNEL.
- I GOT THIS!
ONE TORCH! COMIN' UP!
HUH?
- YOU SEEM TO HAVE
FORGOTTEN AGAIN.
YOUR MAGIC POWER SIMPLY
DOESN'T WORK HERE IN EDOLAS.
- ( groans )
AW, MAN!
- I CAN'T EXACTLY SAY THAT
LUCY BEING THE ONLY ONE OF US
THAT CAN STILL USE MAGIC
IS A VERY COMFORTING THOUGHT.
- GIVE IT A REST, HAPPY,
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS.
- I'M SORRY,
DID I SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
- WHAT ARE YOU
HOLDING THERE, LUCY?
- ( laughing )
I GOT US TORCHES!
I TOOK SOME WOOD
FROM OVER THERE,
WRAPPED 'EM WITH CLOTH
and DIPPED 'EM IN OIL.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS LIGHT THESE BABIES UP
AND WE'LL HAVE
NO PROBLEMS SEEING.
- AND HOW WILL WE DO THAT?
- GOOD QUESTION.
- THIS HAS GOTTA BE
THE MOST HUMILIATING THING
I'VE EVER DONE IN MY LIFE.
- WE'VE GOT NO OTHER CHOICE.
BUT IT REALLY DOES ILLUSTRATE
HOW CONVENIENT MAGIC CAN BE
FOR EVEN THE LITTLE THINGS.
- OLD-TIMEY PEOPLE MUST
HAVE BEEN SUPER IMPRESSIVE
IF THEY COULD MAKE FIRES JUST
BY RUBBING
A COUPLE OF STICKS
TOGETHER LIKE THAT.
- ( groaning with frustration )
MAN! I SUCK AT MAKING FIRE!
- ( sizzling )
- WHOA! I DID IT!
- YAY! LUCY MADE FIRE!
- GOOD JOB!
- AWESOME! I KNEW
YOU HAD IT IN YOU!
- I FIND IT IRONIC THAT
THE FIRE WIZARD
COULDN'T EVEN MAKE A SPARK.
- WE GOT FIRE NOW,
SO JUST DROP IT, WOULD YOU?
- I'M ALL FIRED UP!
- THIS'LL BE PERFECT!
- GO, LUCY!
- ( sighs )
NOW THAT THAT'S OVER,
CAN I REST FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
- HMM.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
( gasps )
YEAH, MAYBE EATING FIRE
WILL BRING YOUR MAGIC BACK.
- THAT'S RIGHT. SO DID IT WORK?
- FEEL IT YET?
- HMM.
( swallows )
DEFINITELY FEELING HOT
RIGHT HERE.
- WELL, DOES IT FEEL LIKE MAGIC?
- UH, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'M STARTIN' TO THINK
IT DOES!
- YOU GOT A FIRE IN YOUR BELLY.
GO AHEAD AND LET IT OUT
BY GIVING US THE OLD FIRE DRAGON
IRON FIST MOVE!
- YOU BET! COMIN' RIGHT UP!
SORRY, I GOT NOTHIN'.
- I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU
THAT WOULD HAPPEN.
- I THOUGHT
MAYBE ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS EAT THIS WEIRD WORLD'S FIRE!
- Lucy: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
THANKS TO MY TORCHES,
WE'RE ALL SET.
- Happy: BUT THEY'RE NOT MAGIC.
- LOOKS LIKE NOBODY'S BEEN HERE
IN A WHILE.
- PUT THE LIGHT RIGHT OUT
IN FRONT OF US.
THAT'S OUR LINK.
- IT SEEMS PRETTY THICK,
AND I THINK IT'S BEEN FORTIFIED
BY SOME SORT OF MAGIC.
- DOES THAT MEAN
THIS IS A DEAD END?
- WE'LL HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO GET THROUGH IT.
I'M SURE THE PASSAGE LEADING TO
THE CASTLE IS ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- GUESS WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
BREAK IT DOWN.
- THAT'LL BE NO PROBLEM.
'CAUSE I KNOW SOMEBODY THAT
CAN BUST RIGHT THROUGH IT.
OPEN, GATE OF THE GOLDEN BULL!
- ( bell tolls )
- TAURUS!
- ( grunting )
( growling )
- BRING ON THE MUSCLE COW.
- IF YOU'RE LOOKIN'
FOR BRUTE STRENGTH,
TAURUS IS DEFINITELY THE
CELESTIAL SPIRIT
YOU WANNA CALL ON.
NOW PLOW THROUGH THAT WALL
FOR US, WILL YOU?
- OF COURSE, MISS LUCY,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
I'M ALWAYS IN THE PLOWIN' MOOD.
- KNOCK THAT THING
OUT OF OUR WAY!
- I'LL MAKE IT VAMOOSE!
MOO! MOO!
MOO!
- MAJOR HOOVES OF FURY!
- YEAH, YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN!
HEY, LOOK!
- THERE'S A PASSAGEWAY!
- LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
CARLA'S GOT THE ONE-TWO PUNCH
OF BRAINS AND BEAUTY!
- THAT WALL WASN'T SO HARD
TO MOVE, MISS LUCY.
- THANKS FOR
ALL YOUR HELP, TAURUS!
- DON'T YOU THINK
I DESERVE TO GET A SMOOCH?
- UH, GET OVER IT ALREADY.
- AW, COME ON, MISS LUCY.
A KISS FROM YOU
WOULD SEND ME TO THE MOOD.
- HOW ABOUT I JUST SEND YOU
HOME INSTEAD?
- WHETHER OR NOT THIS PASSAGE
LEADS TO THE CASTLE
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
- YOU'VE BEEN RIGHT
ABOUT EVERYTHING ELSE SO FAR.
I'M SURE
THIS IS WHERE WE WANNA GO.
- ( Happy groans softly )
- WHAT'S WRONG, BUDDY?
- HEY, WHY DO YOU THINK
THAT I'M NOT GETTING
ANY KINDA MAP
INSIDE OF MY HEAD?
I MEAN, I'M FROM EDOLAS
JUST LIKE SHE IS.
AND SUPPOSEDLY WE BOTH GOT
SENT AWAY ON THE SAME MISSION.
SO HOW COME
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING?
- WE AGREED NOT TO TALK
ABOUT THAT, REMEMBER?
- AYE.
- I CAN'T GIVE YOU
AN EXPLANATION,
THAT'S JUST HOW IT SEEMS
TO BE WORKING OUT.
- FOR NOW,
WE GOTTA KEEP MOVING FORWARD.
- RIGHT.
- YEAH.
I HOPE THIS THING
DOESN'T CAVE IN ON US.
- SHUT UP, NATSU,
OR YOU'RE GONNA JINX US.
- THIS MINESHAFT IS PRETTY OLD
AND RUNDOWN, ISN'T IT?
- I REALLY HOPE
IT'S NOT HAUNTED.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
PLEASE DON'T LET THERE BE
SOMETHING SCARY DOWN THERE!
- JUST HOLD THIS THING
FOR ME, OKAY?
- WHY? JUST TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON!
DO YOU HAVE TO
FIGHT SOMETHING?
- BE QUIET
AND DON'T MOVE A MUSCLE.
( malicious laughter )
WE'VE FOUND THE LAIR
OF THE SHADOW MONSTER!
( laughs )
- ( all exclaiming )
- THIS IS NOT THE TIME
FOR GOOFING AROUND!
- Carla: LET'S SEE.
NOW IN ABOUT FIFTY PACES
WE'LL TAKE A LEFT.
WE SHOULD TURN HERE.
- THIS IS MORE LIKE A CAVERN
THAN A TUNNEL.
- YES, AND I
BELIEVE THIS CAVERN
IS LOCATED DIRECTLY
UNDERNEATH THE CASTLE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU'RE DOING ALL THIS,
BUT I'M SO GLAD
THAT YOU'RE ON OUR TEAM.
- I'M PERPLEXED AS WELL,
BUT LIKE I SAID,
THE MAP JUST KEEPS GETTING
MORE AND MORE FILLED IN.
- YOU'RE AMAZING, CARLA.
- WELL, BEING ABLE TO FIND
OUR WAY THROUGH HERE
IS SURE TO BE THE EASY PART.
BUT WHAT WILL BE TRULY AMAZING
WILL BE SNEAKING IN AND OUT
OF
THE KING'S ROYAL
CHAMBERS UNDETECTED.
AS DEFENSELESS AS WE ARE NOW,
THIS MISSION'LL BE OVER
THE MOMENT WE'RE SPOTTED.
- NOW, DON'T FORGET,
WE CAN ALWAYS USE MY MAGIC
IF WE GET INTO A PINCH!
- SO YOU'RE GONNA SAVE US?
I DON'T THINK SO.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
TAURUS GOT US THIS FAR,
AND THE WHOLE PLAN
RELIES ON USING GEMINI!
- YEAH, YEAH.
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY, HAPPY?
- AYE!
- ( yells )
- LUCY!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- OH, NO, I'M STUCK.
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- CAN'T REACH MY KEYS.
- ( gasps ) ROYAL TROOPS!
- WHY ARE THERE
SO MANY OF THEM DOWN HERE?
- HOW IN THE HECK
DID THEY FIND US?
- SO THESE ARE THE MAGIC USERS
FROM EARTH LAND?
- ( gasping )
- Lucy: ERZA!
- IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH
YOU RESEMBLE THE OUTLAWS,
NATSU DRAGYON AND LUCY ASHLEY.
TAKE THEM AWAY.
- Soldiers: YES, MA'AM!
- ( screaming )
- ERZA!
PLEASE LISTEN TO US! WAIT!
- Carla: WENDY!
- Happy: NATSU! LUCY!
- GREAT EXCEEDS.
- Both: HUH?
- I'M HONORED
TO WELCOME YOU HOME.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WHO ARE YOU, HAPPY AND CARLA?
I THOUGHT THAT
YOU WERE OUR FRIENDS.
- WE'RE MOST GRATEFUL FOR YOUR
HELP IN CAPTURING THE INTRUDERS.
- ( sobbing )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: CHECK IT OUT, NATSU!
THERE'S AN ENTIRE LAND
THAT'S MADE UP OF CATS!
- Natsu: WHOA! THAT'S CRAZY!
DO YOU THINK THAT MEANS
THERE ARE PLACES OUT THERE
FULL OF OTHER ANIMALS LIKE THIS?
- OOH! IF THERE IS, I'M GONNA
GO TO THE LAND OF FISH!
THAT'S A KITTY PARADISE!
- I THINK YOU'D
BE IN BIG TROUBLE
IF YOU WENT TO THEIR LAND
AND STARTED EATING
ALL OF 'EM.
- Both: NEXT TIME, EXTALIA.
- Natsu: I GUESS IF I COULD,
I'D VISIT THE LAND OF DRAGONS!
- WHY? YOU DON'T THINK DRAGONS
WOULD BE SUPER TASTY
OR SOMETHIN', DO YOU?
- EW! NO WAY!