Sorry, guys.
I wish I had happier news.
I promise I'll find him.
For you and the rest of us.
We're gonna get
everyone back together.
And I ain't stoppin'
until we're a guild again.
I don't know. Are you
positive Gray's in there?
[NATSU]
Yep. I'd bet my scarf on it.
We gotta get him
back to Juvia soon.
So let's not waste
any more time.
[NATSU] Ugh. This place is
creepy, so I'm all for that.
[HAPPY] Who builds a church in
the middle of a spooky forest?
[LUCY] Somebody I'd rather not
meet, to be honest with ya.
All right, let's
take it by storm!
Aye-aye, Sir!
Hold it right there, guys!
[NATSU, HAPPY grunt]
That's gonna leave a mark.
Well, at least my
head broke the fall.
We have no idea who or what
might be waiting
for us inside there.
Just charging in blindly
isn't the smartest idea.
[NATSU]
Tch.
Well, all I know
is Gray's in there
and we need to get him out.
[LUCY] Which is exactly why
we have to think this through.
We can't afford to mess it up.
Yeah, okay.
So I think I should give
Miss Virgo a ding-dong
and have her tunnel
us in underneath.
Good idea!
Okay, let's go!
Open. Gate of the Maiden!
Vir--
...go?
[HAPPY, NATSU yell]
[HAPPY]
I think she needs help.
[LUCY] Whoa! What happened?
Are you okay?
[NATSU]
Who do I beat up for this?
Don't mind me.
[LUCY]
Uh.
I wasn't busy, so I
thought I'd punish myself.
[LUCY]
You gotta be kidding me.
[NATSU] There's a lot I don't
know about celestial spirits.
[HAPPY]
Aye.
It's a pleasure to see you.
I hope that you gentlemen
are doing well.
All right, anyway...
Let's get back to work!
[LUCY]
Star Dress: Virgo Form!
She transforms now?
I'm getting flashbacks
of a scary armor wizard!
That outfit grants some
of my special abilities,
increases her magic power,
and boosts her sex appeal.
Okay, Virgo, you ready to rock?
I live to serve,
Princess, so let's go!
[hammering]
And with that, we're in.
Looks like the basement to me.
[NATSU]
Great!
Now would you move
your big ol' butt?
[HAPPY]
Yeah. Please, Lucy.
We're kinda sick of
seein' your undies!
I can't help but wonder
what kinda stuff
the Avatar guys do down here.
[NATSU]
Who knows?
Probably just a bunch
of fartin' around.
Let's see if we can dig
up anything on Gray
before anyone finds
out we're here.
Gray! Come out, come
out, wherever you are!
Who's screaming?
That's not a voice I recognize.
[D-6] It definitely came
from inside the church.
We've got company.
Finally, some excitement!
I'm ready to play!
Natsu's here?
You idiot!
The plan was to move
around undetected,
not tell the entire world
we broke into the place!
Princess, I believe this
calls for punishment.
Feel free to use this on me.
I swear I'll behave.
Now is not the time!
[VIRGO]
Always time for punishment.
What did I do to deserve this?!
All right, you two, stop!
Yep, he's here.
[LUCY]
Huh?
I know the guy's scent.
Place reeks of 'im.
We can always trust your nose.
Well, I guess there's no reason
for us to hide anymore.
[ABEL]
Hey!
[NATSU]
Hm?
[ABEL]
Wanna tell me what you guys
are doing inside our hideout?
I hope you came to play,
'cause that's my favorite
thing in the world.
[LUCY]
Is that who we're fighting?
Wait, I know that doll!
Mr. Cursey!
Oh, man, it's all
coming back to me now.
It belonged to that big pasty
guy we fought on Tenrou.
[HAPPY] Yeah, you and him had
a whole lot of fun with it.
[LUCY]
I would never call that "fun"!
[ABEL]
So, you've already had a chance
to play with Mr. Cursey, huh?
He's one of the best
presents I ever got.
From one of the heavyweights
of Grimoire Heart.
This little guy's magic power
is so awesome, it's scary!
Just looking at the thing
makes my skin crawl.
Be careful, Princess.
He's small, but he's an
extremely strong wizard.
[ABEL]
Huh?
[gasps]
[NATSU]
Sorry, squirt.
Bring me Gray or
get outta my face.
Abel!
[wails]
Oh, you foolish intruders
have got my blood
boiling over with rage!
You won't leaf here!
Because in this room, I keep all
my instruments of cruel-TEA!
Is he serious?
I bet he's talkin'
about your novel, Lucy.
Prepare to experience
brew-tal torture
the likes of which
you've never seen!
I'm thirs-TEA for punish-mint!
[LUCY]
That's not a good thing!
[GOMON] Tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-
tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-
tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-tea-
tea-tea-tea-tea-tea...!
Don't let him give you
any crazy ideas, please.
[HAPPY yelling]
[LUCY]
Especially that one!
Triangle Dummy Dragon!
Callin' this thing a
dragon is an insult!
Well, if that's not
your cup of TEA...
...try the Iron Maiden!
Natsu!
This seems like somethin'
Gajeel'd be into!
Now steep tight.
Oh, no!
[LUCY]
That's brew-tal.
The punish-mint's
completed to a TEA.
[GOMON]
Huh?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[GOMON]
The iron is melting? How?
[gasps]
Pour me.
That's two down.
[D-6]
You're mine now!
[NATSU]
And that's three.
[groaning]
[D-6 grunting]
[VIRGO]
He's so strong.
That's our Natsu!
Always ready to
serve up some punch!
No, what a bitter end.
I'm having a hard time
swallowing all of this.
We're the top tier
wizards of Avatar.
[GRAY] It's obvious you
were in too deep, Gomon.
[gasps]
[GRAY]
Leave him to me.
Hey! Long time no see, man!
[JUVIA]
Oh. Gray darling.
Please come back, my love.
I need you here.
It'll be okay. I just need
to dry you off a little.
[gasps]
So wobbly.
[CARLA]
Huh?
[WENDY]
And big.
[JUVIA]
These belong to my sweet Gray.
[WENDY, CARLA yelps]
You can't take his fish.
[CARLA] What in the world
is she dreaming about?
[CARLA]
Tell me, Wendy.
[WENDY]
What is it?
Do you think the
others have been able
to track down Gray yet?
[WENDY]
Yeah.
I imagine that they have by now.
[CARLA]
I hope they're not quarreling.
[WENDY] In a weird way, that's
kinda how they get along.
They're like best friends
who love to fight.
[CARLA chuckles]
You certainly do have a point.
No, please don't. No fighting.
You'll make Erza mad.
And she'll beat
you both to a pulp.
[WENDY]
That's what usually happens.
[CARLA]
A believable dream.
[yelling]
[chuckles]
[LUCY]
Stop it!
Would you guys
cut it out already?
You made a stupid mistake
comin' to this place.
That's funny!
'Cause I was about to say
the exact same thing to you.
[GRAY] I can do whatever
the hell I want!
[NATSU]
You're wrong!
Juvia's waiting for you!
[NATSU]
As a matter of fact, we all are!
[NATSU] We're gonna get
Fairy Tail back together!
And we can't do it without you!
[LUCY, HAPPY gasp]
You're such an idiot.
Don't you realize
Fairy Tail is gone?
[NATSU]
No, it's not!
All the memories we share and
the friendships we've made,
they haven't gone anywhere!
Fairy Tail's still here.
It lives on in our hearts.
Always has... and always will.
Sure, okay. If that
works for you.
But it seems to me like
that should be enough,
so leave me out of it.
Let me follow my own
path from now on.
[HAPPY]
Gray.
[GRAY]
Fairy Tail is in my past,
and that's where
it's gonna stay.
We used to be friends,
but everything has changed.
I can't pretend that it hasn't.
[slap]
[LUCY]
Nobody is pretending!
We're your friends, Gray.
And we always will be.
Whatever it is you're going
through, we're here to help.
Hearing you say all this,
it's breaking my heart.
After all we've been through--
[gasps]
I don't... feel so good.
What's happening?
All of a sudden, my stomach
started hurting really bad.
I can't--
It must be you, Mary.
Oh, am I interrupting
something, Gray?
Looks like you're catching
up with some old friends.
Probably from that guild that
went belly up, aren't they? Ha!
No! Princess!
What the hell are
you doing to Lucy?
Simmer down!
I think these chains
are made with Sealstone!
I'll help you!
[yells]
Mr. Cursey loves to play!
Yeah. I know.
We were having a
little difficul-TEA!
Now, I wouldn't even bother
trying to fight away the pain
if I were you.
'Cause you're weak. I'm like
so totally stronger than you.
And my black magic
power is the bomb.
All right, Gray!
[GOMON]
Nuh-uh!
These chains are blocking
his magic power.
How strong is he?
Stop right there.
It hurts so bad.
Princess!
[HAPPY]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, owie!
This is what happens
when you don't
mind your own business, Natsu.
You're not yourself, man!
It's obvious there's some kinda
demon that's taken over you!
[GRAY]
No. I'm in control of myself.
The Fairy Tail emblem's gone.
I made the choice
to get rid of it.
So I could find my own answer.
I can't believe he'd do that.
He erased his guild mark!
You'll regret that!
[PANTHERLILY]
Hm?
I can hear somebody
approaching the camp.
Yeah, I hear 'em, too.
I know that scent.
[LEVY]
I'm back.
Thank goodness!
Glad you made it!
Job well done!
[KNIGHT B] Infiltrating the
cult must've been tough.
[KNIGHT AA] I bet being
petite came in handy.
I just wish I could've
done it more quickly.
I didn't have too hard
of a time sneaking in
among all the real cultists.
But sneaking out, that was a
little bit more of a challenge.
[LEVY gasps]
So, were you guys able to dig
up any information on Gray?
Yeah.
I wonder what happened to him.
It's unsettling. Like his heart
was consumed by darkness.
Doesn't really matter.
Our only mission here is to
stop the Purification Plan.
[PANTHERLILY] What do you
mean "it doesn't matter"?
Come on. Gray was our friend.
[GAJEEL]
Well, he's not anymore.
And if they can somehow pull off
what they're tryin' to do,
then a lot of innocent
people are gonna die.
Anyone that would
willingly play a role
in that kind of evil plan
is no friend of mine.
Do you think you could do it?
Strike down an old guild mate?
[GAJEEL] The way I see it,
he's our enemy now.
We have to stop that
plan no matter what.
Yummy fish. Yummy fish.
Don't burn it to a crisp,
Natsu. It's my fishy.
Oh, wait.
You okay, Happy?
[HAPPY]
Mh-hm. Guess so.
Is your tummy feeling better?
Yeah. It doesn't hurt anymore.
Where's Virgo?
I think these Sealstone chains
forced her gate closed.
Gray is such a jerk.
What in the hell
is wrong with him?
And without the Fairy Tail guild
mark, he looks totally stupid.
As crazy as this might sound,
I believe Natsu's theory.
Something's taken him over,
or he's being manipulated.
Bet you're right.
The Gray we know would never
do anything like this.
[footsteps]
Hear that?
[LUCY yelps]
What kind of lunatic
bows to empty air?!
Scary!
[growls]
[NATSU]
Where is Gray?
Bring him down here right now!
Gray and the other
mighty ones had to leaf
to begin the mission
we've been brewing up.
What's that?
[GOMON] Our Purification Plan
for the unclean masses.
Our exalted leader
asked that I stay behind
to snuff out who sent you here.
Under strain of
brew-tal torture.
What is this Purification Plan?
[GOMON]
The purification of souls.
Only one thing will beckon the
return of our Dark Lord Zeref.
The deaths of
countless innocents.
There's no way Gray
would be involved
in some evil plan like that!
[GOMON] Why have you
not mentioned my outfit?
[LUCY]
Huh?
[GOMON]
Well, I mean,
I'm obviously cosplaying
as our Dark Lord Zeref,
and I think I nailed
it to a TEA!
Yeah, so?!
[HAPPY]
Whoa.
[GOMON] I'm such a major
fan of Lord Zeref
I even got this
awesome face tattoo.
It's spelled in some
kinda foreign alphabet,
but I was told that it
says "Zeref Rules."
[LUCY] Uh, it actually
says "powdered tea."
[LUCY] Probably shouldn't
have done that.
Say what?!
You bergamot be
telling the truth!
[gasps]
[screaming]
He can control his torture
stuff without touching it?
[GOMON]
You just noticed?
You let her go, round boy!
Shut up. You should realize
I have the power here.
[yells]
Ah!
[GOMON]
Time to get started.
And I will show no pi-TEA!
No, Lucy!
I can't get it off!
[GOMON]
Magic doesn't work on Sealstone,
that's the point!
[gasps]
[GOMON humming]
I can use a whip.
Or a candle.
Or water. Or rope!
How about some
foot-licking torture?
So, what's your cup of TEA, huh?
It all sounds so perverted.
And would you stop with
the whole ridiculous
"bowing to nobody" thing?!
It's creepy!
I would go with foot-lickin'
stuff if I were you.
I mean, how bad can that be?
Just the sound of it gives
me the heebie-jeebies.
It seems that you
fail to comprehend
the barbari-TEA of that
particular method of torture.
Wait, what does salt water
have to do with anything?
[GOMON]
I'll tell you.
First, I slather your
feet in salt water,
then I bring in a goat.
The goat licks your
feet to get the salt.
The thirsty goat's tongue gets
scratchier and scratchier,
peeling off your skin and
eventually the flesh beneath it.
The beast, never satisfied,
will keep on licking
for eterni-TEA.
That is some freaky,
messed up stuff!
[HAPPY]
You mean that poor goat
has to lick her
nasty feet forever?
[LUCY screams]
[GOMON]
Gimme that footy!
[LUCY screams]
No!
Chai!
Now, you had better
get real chatty, kid,
or she's gonna be
walking on stumps.
You bastard! I told ya
everything I know!
So listen!
The only reason we came
to this creepy dump
was to get our friend Gray!
I cannot believe such falsity!
Gray is one of our most
prestigious members.
[LUCY grunting]
[LUCY screams]
[NATSU growls]
[NATSU]
He is our friend!
No matter what the hell
he might be saying now,
we'll never stop
believing in him.
[growls]
Hold your tongue!
[squeals]
Lucy, no!
What are you doin' to her now?
[grunting]
[squeaks]
This situation calls for
far more severi-TEA!
Cutting her in half is
guaran-TEA-d to make you talk!
I won't let you!
[GOMON]
You might have faith in Gray,
but he won't be
coming to save her!
[LUCY]
Huh?
Gray.
[GRAY]
Ugh! So typical!
How can you guys
always ruin everything?
Listen up, it's Code Blue.
I just hit a snag here.
[ALL]
Huh?
[GRAY]
No, no. Not that kind.
Mm-hmm.
[sighs] Hell if I know.
You should probably
ask him yourself.
Yeah, he's right here.
All that stuff on
him just faded away.
[NATSU]
Uh.
Hold it up to your ear, man.
What's it supposed to do?
[ERZA]
Natsu. This is you, right?
[NATSU gasps]
[GRAY]
Mh-hm.
Congratulations. Your antics
blew Gray's covert operation.
[LUCY] The stage has
been set for Avatar
to unleash their heinous
Purification Plan.
They want to summon
their Dark Lord Zeref
by killing scores of innocent
people as a sacrifice.
There's barely any time left
before the plan
kicks into action,
so we're going to
have to move quickly.
Five strong, the members of
Fairy Tail's mightiest team
rides again to take down
this murderous cult.
Next Time:
"The Purification Plan."
The bond we share is
our strongest weapon
in the fight against evil.