[LUCY]
I can't believe it.
They're all gone.
[NATSU] Sorry to
keep you waiting, Lucy.
Cocky lizards.
Listen up, ugly!
You just picked a fight
with the wrong guy!
I'm Natsu Dragneel
of the Fairy Tail guild.
I'm a Dragon Slayer!
And I'm here
to do just that.
Say that to my face!
Turn around, you coward!
[GRAY] All right, fine.
I said I'm sick and tired of
you screeching like a banshee!
It's seriously harshing
my mellow here.
You lookin'
to fight, Ice-lips?!
Anytime, anyplace, chump!
You can do it, Natsu!
Those two butt heads
more than a couple
of goats in heat...
It's embarrassing.
I understand that
they're polar opposites,
but I don't really get how two
friends could fight so much.
Wait...
Fire and Ice are going at it
and you find that surprising...?
Give me a break.
Oh, Gray...!
Even when you act like a savage,
you're the epitome of hot!
Hold on...
Shouldn't he be 'cool' as ice?
[LUCY] Cut it out, you two!
You destroyed the
place once already!
Isn't that enough for one week?
[NATSU, GRAY] Killjoy!
We have a day off,
so if they get hurt
they'll have time to heal...
I say let them have their fun.
Uh, Mira...
I think you might be
missing the point a little.
Hey Master...!
Are you just going
to ignore them?!
I suppose this does
call for a stern talking-to...
[MAKAROV]
Natsu!
Is that fighting
or a love squabble?!
Show the same spirit
you did in the arena today!
Seriously?!
Damn straight...!
And you call yourself a master
of Dragon-Slaying magic...?!
Be a man!
I agree!
You're not helping!
[NATSU] You heard
the old man, Gray!
Get ready to cry!
[GRAY] Oh yeah...?
Let's see if you can make
good on that little threat!
Down the hatch!
--My bad.
[HAPPY] Bullies!
What did I do to deserve this?!
[NATSU] Sorry 'bout that!
[GRAY] Ya Shoulda dodged.
[HAPPY] You're so mean!
I'm a Fairy Tail wizard, too!
Show me some respect!
Um, I think she's gonna blow!
[WENDY] I'll fix you up, Happy.
Think you could
use some of that
to de-charcoal my fish?
That's not even a word.
[MIRAJANE]
Wendy's really something else...
She's kind, and gentle,
and a very skilled healer,
but it's crazy
because on the flip side,
she's been trained to fight
and even slay dragons!
No kiddin'...
But it kinda makes you wonder
where the dragon that
raised Natsu went wrong.
Hey!
That's enough!
[NATSU, GRAY]
Sorry, ma'am.
[groaning in pain]
Listen, you two.
We're here to prove
that Fairy Tail
is the best guild
in all of Fiore.
That's why we're competing
in the Grand Magic Games.
And the final matchup
is right around the corner.
It took all of our strength
to snag the first place spot.
Now all of the other guilds
will be gunning for us.
We should be focused
and level headed,
so what exactly was the point
of ruining my cake?!
[NATSU, GRAY, LUCY] Huh?
On your feet...
Die with dignity!
[screaming]
[ERZA]
Quit running like cowards!
[CARLA, HAPPY, PANTHERLILY]
Gajeel?!
If I ever see
another mine car,
it'll be too soon.
Where you been?!
You missed all the cake!
Yeah, jerk!
Why'd you take off
in the middle of our match?
Here we go...
For real...?!
I just spent half the day
crawling out of
a hole in the ground
'cause the lava-brained
tool in front of me
put me down there!
Ohh. S'that true, Gray?
I seriously worry about
your lack of brain cells.
That must've been
real rough for ya!
What's your deal?!
Ugh, just forget it.
Anyway...
You two come with me... Now.
Got something to show ya.
[HAPPY] King of the Dragons!
[CROWD chattering]
[MALE 176B]
Fairy Tail is kickin' tail!
[FEMALE 176A]
They just might win this thing!
[MALE 176C] In their dreams!
[FEMALE 176B] Was it me,
or did Sabertooth kinda suck?
[MALE 176D] Yeah, totally!
[MALE 176E] Sabertooth ain't
giving up without a fight.
Just you watch.
They'll own the final!
[JIEMMA] Well, Sting... Rogue...
What should I do with you two?
[JIEMMA] No answer, huh?
I thought you were
"true" Dragon Slayers.
You used to love reminding us--
Always telling us you're
the epitome of strength.
Isn't that right?
So imagine my surprise
when you shamelessly got
your asses handed to you
by another Dragon Slayer!
[JIEMMA] What do you have
to say for yourselves?!
You spelled it out clearly...
We were defeated.
Natsu was somehow
able to subdue us
without using the
full extent of his power.
[ROGUE] He possesses strength
far beyond what we imagined.
He may be unbeatable.
That sounds like the
whining of a weakling to me.
Is that what I'm hearing? Well?!
I don't recall asking
to hear your pitiful
excuses, Rogue,
and I never asked you
to embarrass me like this!
You've disgraced our name
as the mightiest guild!
[LECTOR] Sting!
[FROSCH] Rogue!
Worms like you aren't
fit to call themselves
members of Sabertooth!
Get out!
I don't want to see
your faces here again.
Our guild has
no room for losers.
That's how we remain strong.
Aw, come on, Master...
Sting and Rogue
tried their best;
isn't that what
matters the most?
I know Sting lost,
but that's okay...!
He still gave the fight
his all, and I'm proud of him!
Lector...
[LECTOR]
If you want my opinion,
you gotta lose sometimes,
or you'd never
grow as a person!
This defeat gave Sting a chance
to learn a lot about himself
and his opponent!
So why not just let it slide?
[JIEMMA] Who the hell are you?
[LECTOR]
What do you mean, Master?
I'm a bonafide member!
I've even got the
Saber crest to prove it...!
Don't ya see?
This is a total abomination!
Who defiled our
guild's sacred crest
by placing it on this
mangy little creature?
[growling]
Help me... Sting...
No...! Lector!
Lector is gone...
Master killed him!
[ROGUE] Frosch!
Why did he do that?!
[JIEMMA]
It got what it deserved.
If you're smart,
you'll remove your emblem
before you join the fleabag.
[hysterical crying]
Would you stop
your damn blubbering?
[STING] What have you done...?!
What the hell have you done?!
[JIEMMA] Silence!
It was just a lousy cat!
So be it.
[JELLAL] Stop right there!
Reveal your identity.
I have already revealed mine.
[JELLAL] A woman?
There's no way!
[ULTEAR] Are you serious?
I don't believe it.
If this is some joke,
then it's in very poor taste.
I'm afraid that
we gravely mistook
the gravity of the situation.
If there is a joke in this,
it's that our fate
was already sealed.
[JELLAL] The gate that
will change the world...
The Eclipse...
[JELLAL]
The Dragon King Festival...
[WENDY] So, um...?
What did you find down here?
[GAJEEL] Pipe down and keep up.
[NATSU] Why'd you only bring us?
I wonder if
he found something
that has to do
with Dragon Slayer magic.
Possibly.
So, then...
Why did the gawkers tag along?
Excuse us for being gawkers.
We can't help being curious!
[GAJEEL] This is it.
[WENDY] Look over there!
[GRAY] What are those things?
[LUCY] They look like...
...giant bones...
[NATSU]
Those aren't just any bones--
These are all dragon remains.
[HAPPY] All these
used to be dragons?!
[CARLA] There are so many!
[PANTHERLILY] If you ever
wanted proof that they existed,
here it is.
[GRAY] But what
are they doin' here?
[GAJEEL] Who knows?
[NATSU] Well I'd like to,
that's for sure.
Why would there be piles
and piles of them like this?
Something bad
must've happened here.
Who knows, maybe we'll
find Igneel somewhere.
Happy!
[HAPPY] My bad.
No... He ain't here.
[GAJEEL] Yeah, it's
only been fourteen years
since our dragons
up and vanished...
Lookin' at these bones,
I'd say they've been here
for a lot longer than that.
That might work.
[LUCY] What was that, Wendy?
[WENDY] The Milky Way spell...
It's one of the new
Dragon Slayer secret arts
that Grandeeney
had passed down to me.
[WENDY] "Hear the voices
of the dragon spirits
that lead to
the River of Heaven."
[WENDY]
When I was first learning it,
I assumed it was
some kind of attack.
But I just had a thought.
What if...
...it's something else entirely?
[WENDY] It's possible
that the spell could
allow us to hear the voices
of dragons who have passed on.
You think?
Seriously?
If we can somehow commune
with the spirits
of these dragons...
then one of them might be able
to tell us what happened here.
[WENDY]
And we might finally be able
to find out why
our dragons vanished.
[MALE GUARD 176A] Hey, you...!
This area is off-limits...!
Halt!
Looked like they were writing
something down in here...
Huh.
[MALE GUARD 176A]
"July seventh...
The Eclipse project"?
[MALE GUARD 176A]
"The Dragon King Festival?"...
What is this?!
[WENDY] Just as I thought.
I got these
characters wrong before
because I assumed that they
were used for an attack spell.
[LUCY] A magic circle?
Yeah, what are
you trying to do?
If you'd been paying
attention, you would know that.
She's casting the Milky Way!
There we go...
I need everyone to step
away from the circle.
[WENDY] O wandering spirits
of dragons long past--
Reveal yourself,
and share your wisdom with me.
Milky Way!
It's workin'!
[LUCY] Beautiful!
[HAPPY] Look at the stars!
[LUCY]
The bones!
Talk to us, Wendy!
What's happening?!
I'm trying to contact
a dragon spirit.
But the residual thought energy
lingering down here is weak...
It's incredibly old,
and it's fading.
[WENDY] I found one!
[PANTHERLILY] Are you sure
that's a dragon spirit?!
[HAPPY] Wendy?!
[CARLA]
Quiet! She's concentrating!
What the hell?!
[roaring]
[screaming]
[laughing sinisterly]
[DRAGON]
Even in death,
scaring the pants off
humans is hilarious!
[ZIRCONIS]
My name is Zirconis.
They called me the
Jade Dragon back in my day.
I'm impressed you were able
to conjure my spirit...
Seems like the handy-work
of the Sky Dragon Grandeeney.
[ZIRCONIS]
Which one of you was it?
Oh, how adorable!
[ZIRCONIS] So it was this tiny
Dragon Slayer who woke me, eh?
[NATSU] Back off, creep...!
Don't even think
of touchin' her!
[ZIRCONIS]
Then I'll eat her...!
And she's just the appetizer!
I won't let you!
[ZIRCONIS]
Geez, lighten up, dummy.
Did you honestly think
I could eat any of you?
That'd be pretty hard to pull
off when I can't even touch you.
[laughing]
What did you call me?
All these bones,
and we get the crazy person.
Dragon... It's not a person.
Got another word
I could call him.
[ZIRCONIS]
My name is Zirconis...
They called me the
Jade Dragon back in my day.
You already told us that!
[CARLA] Can you tell us
what happened here?
[HAPPY] We were wondering
why there are so many
dragon bones lyin' around.
[PANTHERLILY] Learning
their fate was the reason
we decided to summon you
in the first place.
[ZIRCONIS] I have no interest
in talking with you humans!
Okay, what about cats?
[ZIRCONIS] Let's see...
It must have been over
four hundred years ago...
[GRAY] Guess he's got
no problem talkin' to cats.
[ZIRCONIS] Dragonkind once
ruled over every corner
of the globe.
We soared through the skies,
raced over the land,
and swam the great oceans.
[ZIRCONIS] Everything in the
world belonged to dragonkind.
Including humans.
[ZIRCONIS]
Your race was plentiful.
And an excellent
source of protein.
[ZIRCONIS] But,
there was one dragon who
felt our reign was unjust...
What a fool.
[ZIRCONIS]
It zealously spread the idea
of a world in which
we coexisted with humans.
Well, as with any fanatic idea,
there were some who fully agreed
and some who
opposed it outright.
It wasn't long
before war broke out.
[ZIRCONIS] I, myself,
fought against the fanatics.
[LUCY] Huh?!
So does that mean...
...you're against humans?
[ZIRCONIS] True, I am
not fond of your kind...
Unless you've
been properly cooked.
Medium rare, of course.
[NATSU]
Didn't your parents tell ya
not to talk to your food?
[ZIRCONIS] Hey!
Show some respect to the dead!
Anyway...
you were starting to tell us
about your civil war?
[ZIRCONIS] Both sides were
fairly evenly-matched...
The fighting was so brutal
that entire continents
were left barren and scarred.
[ZIRCONIS] Until finally
the dragons
supporting coexistence
came up with a plan
that doomed us all.
[ZIRCONIS] They granted humans
what would come to be known as
Dragon Slaying magic.
And with this new power in hand,
mankind joined the war.
[HAPPY]
So the first Dragon Slayers
were some kind
of ancient warriors?
[ZIRCONIS] Mm-hmm. The Dragon
Slayers' immeasurable power
quickly turned
the tide of the war.
We were so overwhelmed
that victory seemed certain for
the dragons on the other side.
[ZIRCONIS] But no one
predicted the travesty
that would come to pass.
[ZIRCONIS] The Dragon Slayers
became so powerful
they eventually turned
on the very dragons
that had given
them their strength.
[ZIRCONIS] It was a massacre.
[ZIRCONIS] There was one man
whose power was so terrible
he bathed the countryside
in the blood of my kin.
[ZIRCONIS] The very mention
of his name still scares me.
[ZIRCONIS] This man
slayed countless dragons
and soaked in their blood.
He used his power so often that
his skin turned to scales,
his teeth sharpened into fangs,
and he stopped
being human altogether.
Are you saying...
...that he turned into a dragon?
[ZIRCONIS] That is the fate
that awaits all who
practice Dragon Slayer magic.
[ZIRCONIS]
All the bones you see here
belong to the
victims of that monster.
[ZIRCONIS]
Despite his human origins,
he became the
King of all dragonkind.
[ZIRCONIS] And the war
that he gave rise to
came to be known as the
"Dragon King Festival."
[ZIRCONIS] His name...
...was Acnologia.
Once a human being,
now a dragon, cloaked
in wings of darkness.
[LUCY] Acnologia...
[LUCY] That's the dragon
we fought on Tenrou Island.
Fairy Tail's strongest members
threw everything
they had at it...
But that monster
just kept coming...
We couldn't even faze it!
[GRAY] You're saying
it used to be human?!
[GAJEEL] Impossible!
[ZIRCONIS] Most of my race
now rots in the ground
thanks to Acnologia.
All of this happened
in the distant past.
[ZIRCONIS]
But you and I have already--
[NATSU] What happened?!
[GRAY] He's gone.
[GAJEEL] Hey!
We weren't done with you yet!
[HAPPY, CARLA] Wendy!
I'm sorry...
Any thought energy he had
left is completely gone now.
[WENDY] But wherever he is,
I'm sure he'll finally
get some long needed peace.
Looks like we got ourselves
into another situation.
Let's pretend we
didn't hear anything.
[NATSU] There's only
one thing I wanna know...
Does this mean that we're gonna
turn into dragons, too?!
How should I know?!
But I don't wanna!
[ARCADIOS]
That's not very likely.
[WENDY] Who's there?!
[ARCADIOS] I took the
liberty of eavesdropping...
It would appear our research
is in line with historical fact,
after all.
[ARCADIOS] Tell me...
Have you heard of the
demons of the Book of Zeref?
[GRAY] Deliora...
[ARCADIOS]
Acnologia is similar to them...
For it was Zeref himself
who turned the Dragon Slayer
into that creature of death.
[HAPPY] Really?
[ARCADIOS] That means...
If you wish to conquer
the black dragon...
You must first find a way
to subdue the
black wizard, Zeref.
Who are you?!
How do we beat Zeref?
Yukino...?!
Is that you?!
[CARLA] In my visions,
I saw a white knight...
The castle crumbling...
And... Lucy singing.
[roaring]
[NATSU]
Sorry to keep you waiting, Lucy.
Cocky lizards...
Listen up, ugly...!
You just picked a fight
with the wrong guy!
I'm Natsu Dragneel
of the Fairy Tail guild.
I'm a Dragon Slayer!
And I'm here to do just that.
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame...!
Roar!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon...
...Crushing Fang!
[LUCY] Natsu...!
It's no use...!
Please stop!
[NATSU] I ain't givin'
up that easily!
[shouting]
[LUCY] Natsu!
[NATSU] I ain't quittin'...
I refuse!
[NATSU] I won't run.
And I won't turn back.
Do you hear me?!
You're dead meat!
Natsu!!!
[NATSU] Man, that ghost
dragon was intense, huh, Happy?
[HAPPY] Yeah, we got lucky...
If it was a real dragon it would
have gobbled us up in one bite!
[NATSU] So who are these chumps
and why are they
actin' like big shots?
[HAPPY] Natsu...
I don't think they're
acting like big shots...
I'm pretty sure
they are big shots.
[NATSU] I don't care
if they're freakin' royalty,
if they mess with my pals,
they're gonna roast!
[HAPPY, NATSU] Next time:
The Eclipse Project!
[NATSU] Just try
messin' with Fairy Tail!
You'll be eating
lava for breakfast.
[HAPPY] All right Natsu,
we get it!