[NARRATOR] As Natsu and
friends are locked in battle
with the Black Magic
Cult, Avatar,
Erza, Juvia, and Wendy swoop in,
giving them an advantage over
the force of thousands.
Arlock, the high
priest of Avatar,
calmly greets the force
from Fairy Tail,
revealing he'd
expected their arrival.
Meanwhile, something weighs
heavily on Natsu's mind:
How to prevent Rogue's
tragic message
from the future
from coming true.
[ROGUE] Gray Fullbuster
will kill Frosch.
[NARRATOR] If this prophecy
does come to pass,
darkness will infect Rogue
completely, and the whole world
will be thrown into
chaos and destruction.
It's up to Natsu and the
remaining members of Fairy Tail
to not only stop Avatar's
plan of annihilation,
but also prevent the future
Rogue warned them of
from becoming reality.
The rear forces have been
completely eradicated,
Your Eminence.
And the vanguard can't
advance any farther!
These foes, the magic they use,
it's just too strong.
We'll never defeat them!
The enemy's come
to finish us off!
Ah! This can't be real!
We have over 2,000
fighters on our side!
Yeah, that's true. And there's
only a handful of them.
[NATSU] Doesn't matter
how many you got.
The odds are against you.
Chumps like you will
never beat Fairy Tail.
[ARLOCK] And when Ikusatsunagi
begins to tremble the ground
beneath us, the
purification will begin.
How 'bout I make you tremble?
[AVATAR A]
Your Eminence!
Forgive me, but we
may need to postpone
the Purification
Plan's sacrifices.
We're about to lose every
single one of our branches!
[NATSU] He's right, so you
should give up now!
[ARLOCK] Heh, the optimistic
ignorance of youth.
I myself remember those days.
But that optimism
dies with age.
Worn down by one's journey
through the sorrows of life.
That voyage always
ends in suffering.
[ALL gasp]
He deflected it?
[ARLOCK] It would appear that
you are a highly skilled wizard.
But will you be able
to deflect this?
[ALL yelp]
[ARLOCK]
Impressive.
Alas...
[NATSU yelling]
Why the heck can't I break it?
[NATSU] Ugh. Oh, of course
your attacks go right through!
That's cheating!
Here goes!
[yells]
He thinks he can just
push his way through?
Dream on, kid!
There's not a wizard alive
who can break through
Master Arlock's magic walls!
[ALL gasp]
--[AVATAR yelling]
--[ARLOCK gasps]
Nice try, pal! These walls
ain't gonna stop me!
[ARLOCK]
Impossible!
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon...
...Iron Fist!
[AVATAR screaming]
[HAPPY, LUCY gasp]
Now. The creepy
ol' boss is down.
So that means,
all their plans are over.
[ARLOCK laughs]
[NATSU]
What's so funny?
[ARLOCK]
You'll still suffer defeat.
[NATSU]
What?
[ARLOCK] I burned away the flesh
from my own face for this day.
It was worth every
last morsel of pain.
If it were possible,
I would do it all again.
What's with all
the crazy talk?
[ARLOCK]
O terrifying god of battle!
Remember our covenant.
I made the requisite sacrifice,
now unleash your fury!
Ikusatsunagi! I summon thee!
What the--?
[AVATAR gasping]
Not good.
[HAPPY]
Uh-oh.
My fur's tingling!
What's going on?
I sense a vortex of
magic power forming!
Can you feel it?
The air around us has changed.
Grandfather's spell
is starting to work.
[giggles]
Everybody's gonna die and
I'm so totally psyched.
It's finally happening!
The sacrifice has started,
and soon, we'll meet
our dark lord, Zeref!
[AVATAR yells]
Stop that woman at once!
Kill her!
[AVATAR screaming]
Something feels wrong.
[AVATAR B]
Your Eminence?!
[AVATAR C]
It's gonna kill us too!
[gasps]
[AVATAR shouting]
Huh?
Whoa! It's a big 'ol foot!
Outta the way! That gigantic
monster's gonna crush you!
[ABEL whimpering]
[AVATAR screaming]
Those are his men.
Awful.
Call that thing off!
Don't you see it's
stompin' on your guys?
[ARLOCK laughs]
This the how the
Purification Plan works!
What do you mean?
[ARLOCK] The true
sacrifices are the souls
of every last devoted
follower of Avatar.
The townspeople
are just a bonus.
[ARLOCK] They have pledged
their lives to Zeref,
and now, they are
giving their very souls!
Their gifts will entice our
dark lord to appear to us.
He will guide us into
a grand new age!
Say what?
[ARLOCK laughs]
[ARLOCK]
The god of war, Ikusatsunagi,
will not be stopped until
he takes every life
that dares remain here!
Hold on. Is Grandfather actually
trying kill all of us, too?
WTF?!
[JUVIA gasps]
That thing's terrifying.
Where'd it even come from?
It's one of the Eighteen
Battle Gods of Yakuma.
How is that possible?
[NATSU]
I can't believe it.
They don't give a damn
about their friends.
I'll show them!
[AVATAR yelling]
It's unreal. A god.
Here to purify.
[ABEL]
So enormous!
[D-6]
Victory will be ours.
[BOTH gasp]
He's beginning to attack!
[AVATAR D]
The ground's being torn apart!
[AVATAR E]
This is crazy!
No. I wanna live.
[LUCY gasps]
Hang on! You see what I see?
[gasps]
Somebody's up there!
Running on the sword!
No way.
It can't be!
Oh, yeah. There he goes!
Natsu!
[yelling]
Natsu.
[ARLOCK]
Your efforts will be in vain.
You cannot stop a god.
His power is far beyond
your understanding.
It's time, my loyal brethren.
Offer up your very souls to him.
Sacrifice yourselves.
Do it in the name of Zeref.
[NATSU]
How can you do this?!
Don't you care about them?!
This is not how you
treat your friends!
[ARLOCK laughs]
[ARLOCK]
Fool.
Your youthful inexperience
has left you so naive.
Time teaches us that friends
are but a means to an end.
You're wrong!
Friends are people that
share the same goal.
Who come together 'cause that's
the only way to move forward!
They might not all look
alike, or think alike,
but they make a pledge
to grow together.
Laugh and cry together.
Help each other.
And put their faith
in each other!
[ARLOCK] What you're talking
about is just dependency.
[NATSU] I don't give a
crap what you call it!
But what I'm talking
about is the bond
that's always been my salvation!
Friendship is what
gives me power!
It's what fires me up!
[yells]
You cannot hurt a god!
[NATSU] I made a promise to
protect those dear to me.
[NATSU] I will never stand by
and watch when someone needs me.
Not again.
That's why....
I'll get even stronger!
[NATSU] My father Igneel
gave me this flame!
Fire Dragon King...
...Destruction Fist!
[NATSU] My father Igneel
gave me this flame!
Fire Dragon King...
...Destruction Fist!
[yells]
[gasps]
My friend. You have
grown so strong.
[BOTH chuckling]
[WENDY giggles]
[AVATAR F]
I don't believe it.
[AVATAR G] That wizard
completely annihilated
the battle god.
[ARLOCK]
Impossible.
How could this have happened?
[ALL whimpering]
An entire army and a god...
defeated by this ragtag bunch?
Monsters.
It's not fair. Who do
they think they are?
[AVATAR H]
Please, don't hurt us!
[AVATAR I]
Run!
[D-6]
You fools!
The Purification
Plan isn't over yet!
We're just gonna have
to do it ours-- Ah!
[D-6]
Abel, no!
[gasps]
[GAJEEL] You know this
is forbidden magic,
so I'm gonna need
to confiscate it.
[D-6]
How dare you!
[grunts]
You left yourself
completely open.
Don't let anyone escape!
Arrest all of these scumbags!
It's Gajeel!
And Lily, too!
I don't understand.
Obviously, they work
for the council now.
It's bizarro world!
[LUCY]
Levy, wait up!
[LEVY gasps]
Hey, Lu-lu.
[LUCY] Wow. I guess
the rumors were true!
You're really working
for the council now!
[LUCY giggles]
I missed you so much!
This is such a nice surprise!
I never expected to
run into you here!
I thought you were a reporter.
[NATSU]
Huh?
Good to see you guys!
Natsu!
Been a long time.
Hey there!
[NATSU]
Whoa! You look just like Gajeel!
[growls]
Are you trying to get
under my skin already?
Nah, man, I just thought you
were too much of a rebel
to work for the council
Money doesn't grow
on trees, ya know.
But that old tree
did offer me a job.
You mean ol' Warrod
hooked you up?
[WARROD]
Oh, that metallic young man?
That's really something.
He's the head of the Custody
Enforcement Unit now?
And he joined because
of the advice I gave him?
Honestly, I was only joking.
[GAJEEL]
That means any guild wizard
has to do what I tell 'em.
So I'm gonna be puttin' you
under arrest, Salamander!
For makin' that
stupid, ugly face!
And you're goin' down
for indecency!
[gasps]
[GAJEEL]
Juvia. Uh.
You're too clammy!
I am?
[GAJEEL]
Yep!
Happy! You're eatin'
way too much fish!
Yumminess isn't a crime, okay?
[GAJEEL]
And Wendy Marvell.
You're under arrest because,
um, because reasons!
What? But I didn't do anything!
That leaves you.
I shouldn't have to explain
to you what you did, Gray.
Don't expect me
to go easy on ya.
[GAJEEL yells]
Hey, Erza!
No, she's angry!
Yeah! I'm so scared, Natsu!
Listen up, just because
you look like Gajeel,
that doesn't give you the
right to behave like him.
The hell are you sayin'?!
I am Gajeel!
No way.
The Gajeel I know would
never work for the Council.
Is that so?
This man, is in fact
the real Gajeel.
[NATSU, ERZA]
He is?!
You weren't joking? You really
didn't believe it was him?
I'm glad that's
been cleared up.
[KNIGHT A]
We've got Arlock!
[KNIGHT B]
Bring him into custody!
Let me go!
[D-6]
Well, this is embarrassing.
I'm so bummed.
This is my worst nightmare.
As I'm sure you can tell,
we were ultimately able
to bring Avatar's
Purification Plan to a halt.
But I can't take the credit.
I know who to thank.
It was clear when we
stormed their hideout.
Doesn't look like
anybody's here.
Check this out.
[PANTHERLILY]
"The ultimate elimination
will be held at Malba."
This looks a lot
like Gray's magic.
Sure does.
We never would've been
able to find this place
without your help, Gray.
Thank you.
No problem, but I'm sorry
for the trouble I caused.
I know it was a pain.
Don't worry, dear.
The only thing that really
matters is you're okay!
[LEVY] Not gonna lie,
you had me fooled.
Wish I could say
the same for you,
but you gotta do some
work on your disguises.
Oh. You knew that was me?
I'm lost. I have no idea
what they're talking about.
[CARLA] And where
did Erza come from?
[LUCY]
I'll explain later!
So that's them.
Gray's former guildmates.
Their bond still seems
extremely strong to me.
[PANTHERLILY] The important
thing is, the city is safe.
[LEVY] No thanks to us,
unfortunately.
[GAJEEL]
Eh...
We kicked some butt
Fairy Tail style!
It feels so good to work as
a team with all of you again!
You look like you've gotten a
little taller. Am I right?
Sorry. I'm exactly
the same as before.
It feels like we're back
at the ol' guildhall.
I have to admit,
I feel the same.
[giggles]
I've really been missing
times like these.
[ERZA]
All right! Victory is ours!
Let us raise a
shout of triumph!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Of course, we come
all the way out here
because we were worried...
...and instead, they've
somehow managed to take down
an entire army all
by themselves.
[STING] Not to mention
that huge monster. Heh.
Wow. I mean, you
gotta hand it to 'em.
Yeah, those crazy
Fairy Tail guys
really don't take crap
from anybody, do they?
I bet you "think so
too," huh, Frosch?
What the--?!
Where'd Frosch run off?!
Aw, man!
Hey. Frosch! Where are you?
Uh!
[ROGUE yelps]
[ROGUE] Did Frosch have
to go mingle with them?
Hold on. I think that's
Frosch from Sabertooth.
Yep. I think so, too!
[gasps]
What are you doing so
far away from home?
[FROSCH]
Good question.
[NATSU screams]
That big jerk! He broke
his promise to me!
What do you mean?
[ROGUE] Gray Fullbuster
will kill Frosch.
[NATSU] I want you to
swear you'll stay put.
You and Frosch can't leave
town until I get back.
[GRAY]
All right, you.
[gasps]
Get closer so I can see
your cute widdle face!
Awww.
[NATSU]
Huh...?
Just looking at you
makes me happy!
[FROSCH chuckles]
[NATSU]
Uh... I...
[ERZA]
Yes, Frosch is adorable,
but you still need to try
to get control of yourself.
[GRAY chuckles]
[GRAY]
I know, but I can't help it.
[JUVIA] Gray, should I
be worried, darling?
I'm cute, too!
[LUCY chuckles]
Oh, no! Is he trying to
take away my Frosch?!
You do realize everyone
loves Frosch, right?
[LECTOR]
Yeah. Sting's gotta point.
It's just one of those
things ya kinda can't deny.
[STING] Well, let's go
mingle with them too.
[ROGUE grumbles]
[ALL chattering]
Hey! Natsu!
We just wanted to come
and congratulate you
on a job well done!
I'm gonna be right
there, Frosch!
Oh, wow! It looks like Sting
and Rogue are here, too!
It's good to see you again!
Hey there, Lector!
You gotta give Frosch
back to me now!
Okay, sorry about that.
There's no reason
for you to get upset.
I think so, too!
[LUCY gasps]
[ROGUE]
Come on, Frosch.
You should know better
than to run off like that.
[FROSCH]
I'm sorry!
[LECTOR]
Calm down, Rogue.
No need to be all harsh.
[STING]
What?
Gajeel? You're working
for the council now?
This is just a joke, right?
[PANTHERLILY] I had a
feeling he'd say that.
[GAJEEL] Oh, you think
it's a joke, huh?
Well, you can laugh
about it plenty in jail!
[LECTOR] Hey. Relax.
He was just being friendly.
Gray, my love!
How come you've never
once treated me with
the same affection
you're giving Frosch?
[GRAY]
Jeez.
Give me a break and stop
being so freaking clingy!
[chuckles]
[LUCY]
Around 400 years ago,
a powerful Dragon Slayer bathed
in an overabundance of blood
from his prey, which turned
him into a terrifying creature.
The black king of the dragons.
Elsewhere, a solitary
magical prodigy
haunted by the family he lost,
immersed himself in the
study of forbidden magic.
Little did he know,
this would draw
the wrath of the god Ankhselam.
Next Time: "Memoirs."
And thus, the sorrowful
gears of fate begin to turn.