[NATSU]
Previously, on Fairy Tail!
[NARRATOR] The Grand
Magic Games continue...!
And although they got
off to a rocky start,
the wizards of Fairy Tail
have turned it around.
They've taken the lead after
winning day four's team battle
against the Twin
Dragons of Sabertooth.
This loss greatly displeased
Master Jiemma,
and a dramatic clash ensued.
Meanwhile, in a dragon bone yard
far beneath the
Domus Flau coliseum,
the spirit of the
Jade Dragon, Zirconis,
told Natsu and
the others the truth
behind the Dragon King Festival
and Aknologia himself.
[ARCADIOS]
I am Colonel Arcadios,
leader of the
Sacred Cherry Blossom Knights...
The Crocus garrison force
of the Royal Fiore Army.
And I am Yukino Aguria,
acting-Sergeant in the
Cherry Blossom Knights.
So what business does the
military have down here anyway?
I don't get it...
You're in the army?
But you were with
the Sabertooth guild
just a couple
of days ago.
Did you join the army after
those guys kicked you out?
Yes, in a manner
of speaking.
Please allow
me to clarify...
For the past
several years
I have been working on a
highly classified project...
But its success
required the power
only a celestial
wizard can provide.
Luckily, Sargent Yukino
is able to lend her assistance
in this undertaking.
[LUCY]
A celestial wizard?
[HAPPY]
The Eclipse Project!
[WENDY]
Excuse me...
So you specifically needed
that type of magic power...?
To do what, though?
Get to the point,
would ya...?!
I'm runnin'
really low on patience!
So skip the formal crap and tell
us what you're doing down here!
The one and only
Natsu Dragneel...
It's an honor to make
your acquaintance...
I applaud your recent
victory in battle.
[NATSU growls]
[NATSU stomps]
I said skip
the formal crap
and tell me
what you're doing...!
While you're at it,
tell me why the hell
you were trying to get your
hands on a celestial wizard!
And when I ask
somebody a question...
I expect an answer right away!
Calm down.
Idiot.
[HAPPY] This should probably
go without saying...
But he's kind of
an important dude.
[PANTHERLILY] I don't really
think that calling him "dude"
is a very good idea either.
[CARLA]
A white knight...
[ARCADIOS]
Follow me, please.
[NATSU]
Hold on a minute!
Don't just walk away!
[YUKINO]
You too, Lucy.
You should come along with us.
If our plan is
indeed successful...
Both Zeref...
And Acnologia will be
defeated as a result.
[NATSU growls]
[WENDY] Do you really
think you can do that?
[NATSU]
Holy cow!
[GRAY]
It's huge!
[WENDY] It's Mercurius,
the luminaria palace!
[ARCADIOS]
This is his majesty's home.
It certainly is
fit for a king.
Are you really sure it's
okay for us to go inside?
[ARCADIOS]
Yes, but before we do...
I'd like to give Miss Lucy
my most humble apology;
my misguided actions put her
directly in harm's way.
[NATSU]
What do you mean by that?
[CARLA]
Hold on...
Are you talking about
that bunch of goons
that accidentally kidnapped
Wendy and I?!
You were the one that
was behind all of that?
My intention was never to
put you in any real danger...
But I was far too aggressive
with my orders.
I falsely believed that
you were our only hope
for the celestial wizard
we so desperately needed.
It was a lapse of judgment...
I ask your forgiveness.
[BOTH grunt]
[ARCADIOS] In truth,
the Grand Magic Games is a ruse.
Or rather a mechanism
for siphoning magic power
from the participants.
[GRAY]
So you've been stealing power
from wizards for years now?
[HAPPY]
It's all a big cover up?!
[CARLA]
How deplorable!
[GAJEEL]
That's messed-up.
[PANTHERLILY]
You can say that again.
[ARCADIOS] You're certainly
entitled to your opinions
on the matter,
but I firmly believe
that the end justifies
the means in this case.
[ALL gasp]
[HAPPY]
Whoa...
What's that?
[ARCADIOS]
Eclipse...
The door that will
change the world...
Without massive amounts
of magic power,
it never could've
been constructed.
[LUCY]
It's a door?!
[NATSU]
To where?
[ARCADIOS] When the sun
and moon intersect...
We will then use the
Celestial Zodiac keys
to open this door.
[NATSU AND LUCY gasp]
What lies beyond it
is time itself...
It will allow us to travel four
hundred years into the past,
and slay Zeref before he gains
the power of immortality.
His destruction is
our ultimate goal.
[NATSU growls]
[WENDY gasps]
[GRAY gasps]
[GAJEEL grunts]
[ALL gasp]
But... how's that even possible?
[YUKINO]
Tell me something...
is it true that
time flows differently
in the celestial world
than it does in ours?
[LUCY]
Yeah, it does, actually.
We'd like to
utilize the unique
dimensional properties
their world possesses...
Therefore, to open
up this door...
...we need celestial magic.
[ARCADIOS] Since celestial
wizards are scarce these days,
we thought we'd have to resort
to a substitute
source of power...
But now that we've
located the two of you
and all twelve Zodiac keys...
The plan can proceed
as it was intended.
The time for action
is almost upon us.
"When the sun and
moon intersect."
This will occur three days
from now, on July seventh...
We ask you for your help,
Miss Lucy.
[LUCY grunts]
The seventh of July?
That's the same day that all
of our dragons disappeared.
Pretty major coincidence.
This door's
supposed to open
when the sun and
moon intersect...
[DARTON]
The eclipse.
[SOLDIERS running]
[ALL gasp]
[MALE SOLDIER]
You there!
Stay right where you are!
[SOLDIERS growling]
[WENDY]
Royal soldiers?!
[CARLA] We're doing
nothing wrong!
Is there a problem?
What's going on?
[GRAY] Did you come here
looking for a fight?
[DARTON] It would be wise
of you to surrender quietly,
before things get messy,
Colonel Arcadios.
[ARCADIOS gasping]
Defense Minister Darton!
What is this meaning of this?!
It's you who should be
answering that question.
Why are you here...?
You are aware that revealing
state secrets to
outsiders is treason!
[ARCADIOS]
You're making a mistake!
These people are
not outsiders...!
They are an essential component
to the Eclipse Project!
[DARTON] You do not
have the authority
to make such reckless decisions
on your own, Colonel.
[ARCADIOS] I won't allow
your opposition
to jeopardize the safety
of the kingdom!
Call off your men and end this
ridiculous farce immediately!
You are way out
of line here...!
This plan of yours
will alter history!
Don't you realize
you're putting
our entire civilization
at risk?!
Now stand down!
[ARCADIOS growls]
What in the heck are
they talkin' about?
[LUCY] It sounds
like not everyone's
on board with this plan.
[GRAY]
I'll say.
They're gonna change history?
But if they go back
and change the past...
...the present and future
will change as well.
Quite a disturbing concept.
Colonel Arcadios,
you are under arrest
for treason against
the kingdom of Fiore!
Take the celestial wizards
into custody as well,
they are accessories
to this crime...!
Remove the others at once!
[MALE SOLDIERS]
Yes, Sir!
Say what?!
But I haven't
committed any crime!
[NATSU]
I'm warning you!
If you want her,
you gotta go through me!
No, stop!
You can't use magic here!
[NATSU]
Huh?!
[gate buzzing]
[NATSU gasps]
[NATSU]
What...?
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU] What in the hell's
happening to me?!
[LUCY]
Natsu!
[DARTON] Oh, did the Colonel
not inform you...?
The Games are just a way
of stealing magic power
to feed the Eclipse.
It is an extremely
effective tool... In fact,
if a wizard were to
activate a spell
this close to the device...
The Eclipse would completely
drain all of their magic power.
[NATSU collaspses]
I hope you won't cause
any more trouble...
After all, a wizard
incapable of using magic
is hardly a threat to a group
of royal soldiers.
Get your dirty
hands off me!
[YUKINO] If you're soldiers...
Then you serve under Colonel
Arcadios's command, don't you?
Lucy!
Please don't take them away!
Damn you, Darton!
I won't allow the Eclipse
plan to proceed.
Poor Natsu.
He's lost all
of his power...
It will take him quite
a while to recover.
[GAJEEL]
You bastards...
[DARTON]
Please, you must understand
that my intention was
never to harm anyone...
but there is simply
too much at stake.
However, I can offer you
somewhat of an olive branch
for your trouble.
I'll have you know
that his majesty is extremely
fond of the Fairy Tail guild.
If you can manage
to claim victory
in the Grand Magic Games,
I shall grant you
a private audience with him.
The king is a rather
kind-hearted man...
Who knows?
He may be even persuaded
to pardon your comrade.
I wish you
the best of luck.
[SOLDIERS marching]
Lucy...
[NARRATOR] The evening
of July fifth...
The Grand Magic Games
will come to a close tomorrow.
[LAXUS]
What the hell?!
[ERZA]
Lucy's been taken into custody?!
To think that she
would be involved
in some sort of top-secret
plot is utterly ridiculous.
[LAXUS]
Let me get this straight...
We take the top spot
we can ask for her back.
But that's only if
"his highness" allows it.
Personally, I have
a hard time believin'
anything that old guy told us.
I feel the same.
Are we just supposed to
put up with this crap
from those jerks?!
Untie me, and I'll go up there
and get her right now!
Just calm down and do
what master tells us.
No violence.
It'd be us against
the whole army, ya know.
[ERZA]
Master.
[MARKAROV grunts]
We can't afford to
take reckless action
against the kingdom...
And they surely wouldn't
want word to spread
that they mistreat
innocent civilians.
But I suppose we should
consider her a hostage
until this Eclipse Project
of theirs is called off.
Man...
They got us by the
you-know-what don't they?
She's a hostage...
There's one thing
I don't really understand...
If all of us know about this big
secret they're trying to hide,
why'd they let us
walk away free?
You expect them to make
any kind of sense?!
It was obvious that
Colonel Arcadios
was the primary target they were
after, so maybe they let us go
so we could testify
against him later.
Hm...
I dunno...
[CARLA] They'd still be risking
their secret getting out.
Perhaps they feel
it can't be kept
secret much longer.
It's still weird they
didn't keep us there...
Nobody would've
found out about it.
That's true.
I'm not so sure about that...
You're all on the first place
team in the games...
High profile.
It would be
pretty suspicious
if you all just didn't show up
for the final match tomorrow.
I can imagine the
kingdom doesn't want
to get on the bad side of every
wizard guild in the country.
[GRAY grunts]
The Royal Army isn't
known for acting rashly
and taking citizens
for no reason...
If we knew what the
real justification
for her capture was...
Perhaps we could use
that to help her.
[NATSU growling]
Hey...!
We all need to quit flappin'
our gums, and do somethin'!
[NATSU yells]
[MAKAROV]
Simmer down!
[HAPPY]
Whoa...
A member of our family
has been taken
against her will...
Believe me...
we all want justice right now.
[NATSU growls]
[MAKAROV]
That being said...
we can't just charge
headlong into conflict
like we usually do...
It's too risky...
However...
We are not cowards and we will
not let them get away with this.
We are Fairy Tail!
[YUKINO] I never wanted
you to get dragged into this.
I'm so sorry...
but I've always
been a bad luck charm.
Don't beat
yourself up!
Instead of feeling
sorry for ourselves,
let's figure out
how to get outta here!
[YUKINO]
You're right, but...
And the first order of business
when we blow this joint
is getting
our keys back.
[YUKINO] I'm sorry
I let this happen...
Seriously, it's totally
not your fault.
[YUKINO sighs]
[LUCY] It seems to me like
we got caught up in the middle
of some kind of power
struggle in the government.
Aren't they just fighting
over whether or not
that Eclipse Project or
whatever should be happening?
To be perfectly
honest...
I don't know enough to
have a real opinion on it.
It should...
They should go
forward with it.
[LUCY] Ah...
[YUKINO] A long time ago,
I had a big sister...
Her name
was Sorano.
I was always
messing things up
and getting
into trouble...
My parents were constantly
getting angry with me.
But time after time,
my sister stood up for me.
[SORANO] Leave Yukino alone;
it's not her fault!
She was so sweet...
and beautiful...
I was so lucky to
have a sister like her.
[LUCY sighs]
[YUKINO]
But then one night,
my village was invaded by a cult
that worshipped Zeref...
They killed our parents,
and took my sister away.
I wanted to help, but all
I could do was run for my life.
The Eclipse is the only hope
we have of defeating Zeref.
I just wanted to
have my family back...
That's all.
[YUKINO cries]
[LUCY]
So, if he was gone...
...they might never
have been taken away.
But there's
no guarantee
that the world would change
the way we want it to...
We don't have
that kind of control.
That's why it's such
a risky thing...
and why some people
are trying to stop it.
And nobody knows
if it's even possible.
Can you really go back
and change the past?
[birds chirping]
[wings flapping]
[NARRATOR]
July Sixth...
The final day of
the Grand Magic Games!
A day filled with jubilation!
[CHAPATI] This is what we have
all been waiting for, folks!
It has been an exciting week;
filled with incredible magic
and emotional moments
we may never forget!
But today,
one guild will be crowned
number one in Fiore
and the winner of
the Grand Magic Games!
[CROWD cheers]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
it has been an honor
to have spent this
time with you,
and with my fellow commentator,
the esteemed Mister Yajima!
My pleasure.
[CHAPATI] We have a very special
guest with us today...!
You all know and love
him as the official mascot
of the Grand Magic Games,
the always entertaining, Mato!
[MATO]
Heya!
[CHAPATI] Usually you're in
the arena acting as referee,
but not today!
[MATO] No sir!
That won't be necessary, because
today is extra special!
The final match!
[CROWD cheers]
[MATO] Now let's
get things started
and bring out
all the competitors!
[CHAPATI] Currently in sixth
place and hoping for an upset
are the hunting dogs
turned tail-chasers:
Quatro Puppy!
[CROWD cheering]
[YAJIMA] It's true the
"Drunken Hawk" Bacchus
has been on the losing side
this year,
but he's still a force
to be reckoned with.
Next up...
the guild that exudes class
and an intoxicating parfum.
With Ichiya Vandalay Kotobuki
at the helm, it's Blue Pegasus!
[CROWD cheering]
[MATO] They're currently
down in fifth place...
But today is their
chance to breathe in
the sweet smell of victory!
Good luck!
[CROWD gasping]
[CHAPATI] Here comes our
third place team: Lamia Scale!
Can Lyon Bastia, the ice wizard
who rivals Fairy Tail's
Gray Fullbuster, bring the heat
in today's battle?
Or will his team just get
frozen in their tracks?
[MATO] He doesn't
have to do it alone...
Don't forget the cute little
God Slayer, Shelia Blendi,
and the Wizard Saint Jura Neekis
are extremely powerful as well!
I agree; that team could
claim the title today!
[CHAPATI] Lamia Scale isn't
the only team in third place;
they are in very good company!
With Mermaid Heel!
[YAJIMA]
Beautiful ladies,
but don't fooled
by their sweet looks.
They are definitely not
delicate little flowers.
[MATO] Beneath the calm
exterior of their leader,
Kagura Meekazuchi,
burns a fire of intensity!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Let's hear it
for our second place team!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] What a shocker
to see this guild,
who's usually in the top spot,
playing catch-up!
Is this the end of an era?
[CHAPATI] Their Twin Dragons,
Sting and Rogue,
have a major bone to pick with
Natsu and Gajeel of Fairy Tail
after that crushing
defeat on day four...!
Can they settle the score?!
Let's give it up for returning
Grand Magic Games champions!
The mighty...
...Sabertooth!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Those are some
serious looks they've got today.
Surely they realize
there's a lot on the line.
[MATO]
Keeping cool under pressure!
Whoa, that's weird.
They usually have
two cats rootin' for 'em.
[MAN C]
Yeah, but one of 'em's gone.
[MAN A]
Wonder why?
[STING]
Lector...
[LECTOR]
Hey, Sting!
You've totally got this thing
in the bag, ol' buddy...!
They're only one point ahead,
that's nothin'
for a guy like you!
You're right about that, pal...
And I won't let you down.
'Cause...
I'm not losing.
[CHAPATI] And now,
in first place...
the guild that is making
a historical comeback
after literally falling off
the map seven years ago!
[crowd cheering]
[CHAPATI]
Let's welcome Fairy Tail!
[crowd cheering]
[ROGUE]
Well, this is it...
You ready?
[STING]
Yeah.
[LYON] Heh. They're definitely
getting a different welcome
from all that booing during
the games' opening ceremonies.
[LYON gasps]
[MATO]
Wait a minute!
Strange.
[MATO]
Uhhhhhh...
[DARTON] Hm.
[CHAPATI]
Unbelievable!
Team Fairy Tail is
keeping us on our toes
by this completely
unexpected roster change!
The man who
singlehandedly defeated
Sabertooth's Twin Dragons
has been replaced!
By Juvia?!
[ROGUE] Natsu is out
of the competition?!
That's alright with me...
In fact, that's the best
news I've heard all day.
[ROGUE]
I suppose you're right.
[CHAPATI] After such a strong
showing in the last round,
this decision is a real
head-scratcher.
What could be the reason?
[YAJIMA]
Hmmm...
Hopefully nothing
bad has happened.
[MAN E] But that
doesn't make any sense.
[MAN F] Aw man,
I wanted to see him fight again!
How interesting...
it would seem he hasn't
fully recovered yet.
[MAVIS]
Very clever, Sixth Master.
[MAKAROV] To be perfectly
honest with you,
it was the only real
choice that I had...
There is a chance that
winning the games would
get our poor Lucy back through
more "official" channels.
However...
In a situation like this,
we must explore every option...
We can't put all our
eggs in one basket.
[MAKAROV] Everybody is
focused on the games,
and we will cheer our
fighters on with gusto!
That's what the public
will be seeing.
[MAKAROV] But some of our
most capable wizards
will set out on a secret
rescue mission.
A two-pronged strategy...
Nicely done.
[MAKAROV]
Godspeed, my children!
We're counting on you!
[HAPPY]
This is horrible!
Lucy got kidnapped by
that royal army bigwig!
What are we gonna do?!
[NATSU] Relax, little guy.
It'll be fine.
We'll just go in and
bust her out, no prob!
[HAPPY] Yeah? But how
are we gonna do that?
[NATSU]
Come on...
Don't forget that we have a
plan-making genius on our team!
We got this!
[BOTH]
Next time: Fairy Tactician!
[HAPPY]
I know but I'm still worried...
I mean, can you actually
memorize a plan?
[NATSU]
Hmm...
I'm sure I can
wing it, at least!