[IGNEEL]
We haven't lost yet, humans.
Do not despair!
[gasps]
[REN]
We fired five volleys.
Why won't they break?
Christina's cannons are
the pride of Blue Pegasus,
and they didn't
even leave a mark.
So should we abort
the mission, sir?
Between the cannon shots and
the draining ether-nano,
we've used too much power.
We're about to fall!
[ICHIYA]
So this is how it ends.
[GRANDEENEY]
You need to move!
[JENNY]
Huh? Who was that?
Hey, look!
Evasive maneuvers!
[ALL gasp]
Hot damn! What was that?!
A bird?
I sense Grandeeney!
[GRANDEENEY roars]
Now there's a sight.
A dragon.
Thought they'd died out.
Come. We need to hurry.
Magnolia needs us.
[HAPPY gasps]
Those little Face thingies are
startin' to get crossed out.
Metalicana's back.
[METALICANA roars]
I know Weisslogia's dead.
But somehow I'm picking
up on his energy.
And I can feel Skiadrum as well.
[IGNEEL]
My kindred are free at last.
[IGNEEL] We soar through the
skies of Ishgar once again!
[IGNEEL roars]
[WENDY]
It's a miracle!
[LISANNA, LUCY gasp]
[MARD GEER whimpers]
[GAJEEL]
Ha, ha.
[MAKAROV]
Mm...
[HAPPY]
Ha, ha!
Incredible.
Damn these things!
Our magic's not
effecting them at all.
And I don't have much left.
[panting]
I'm exhausted.
What do we do now?
Mm? Hey, look up there!
Do you see it?
What is that thing?
Is it another demon?
[KAGURA gasps]
I don't think so.
[GRANDEENEY roars]
[BOTH gasp]
She really came back.
[MILLIANNA]
Meow!
That thing took 'em
all down with one hit!
What could possibly
be that strong?
Is it like a super kitty?
No. I don't know how,
but it's a dragon.
[JURA panting]
[JURA]
All those attacks.
And they're still
standing strong.
I fear our chance of victory
has disappeared with our magic.
No way. Is this someone's
idea of a joke?
[JURA]
What?
Is this really happening?
Am I dreaming?
[JURA] Only one creature has
that much effortless power.
The dragons are back.
And they're here to save us.
[gasps]
[IGNEEL roars]
[STING gasps]
I can feel his energy.
It's Weisslogia.
What is that?
I don't know, but it's
coming right for us!
[SOLDIER A]
It's a dragon!
[SOLDIER B]
Wait, now there's a dragon, too?
[SOLDIER C]
We're so dead!
[SOLDIER D]
Retreat!
Is that really him?
[SKIADRUM roars]
It destroyed them!
Is the dragon on our side?
Don't let your guard
down yet, men!
So, uh...
The "X's" are a
good thing, right?
I just don't understand
how the faces are being
wiped out so quickly.
[EVE]
Hey, boss!
We got our magic back!
Christina's up and running.
Any news from outside?
Sir, we're receiving messages
from guilds everywhere!
The dragons are back!
And they're destroying
the Faces!
[ICHIYA]
Uh?! Unbelievable.
Man.
Oh poo! Please, no!
How could such a perfect
plan go so off the rails?
The Faces are gone!
We're done for! We failed!
[laughs]
Way to go!
[IGNEEL roars]
[LECTOR]
Ha, ha, ha! We did it!
Take that ya stupid Faces!
What'd we do?
Don't ask me pal, I got no idea.
Me neither! Yay!
It's really over.
Yes.
At last.
We get to live in a world
filled with magic after all.
They saved our lives.
If it wasn't for the dragons,
Tartaros would've won.
Meow? I can feel it!
My magic power's back, baby!
We owe it all to them.
We had no hope.
No power.
Humanity was staring
into the void.
But they risked their
lives to protect us.
[MILLIANNA]
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I must admit.
I never imagined that a
dragon would save my life.
[IGNEEL]
We've done it.
The Revival of E.N.D.
has been stopped.
Victory is ours.
[FAIRY TAIL cheers]
[FRANMALTH]
Oh, this is worst thing
that could possibly happen.
What will I do without the
protection of my Master?!
Where will I go from here?!
Because... I can't stick
around this place, anymore!
[gasps] We were defeated.
I don't understand.
He was actually alive?
[IGNEEL]
We all were.
Skiadrum,
Metalicana,
and Grandeeney.
We lived within all of you,
the Dragon Slayers.
We used a very sacred art,
to allow our spirits,
and our powers to lie dormant
within each one of you.
Wait a minute, is that what
those heart palpitations were?
Your powers were awakening?
[NATSU]
Yeah!
You never gave me a
straight answer on that!
How exactly did you
get inside me, anyway?
I think I'd remember
eating a dragon.
[IGNEEL] We chose this course
of action for two reasons.
First of all, we wanted to
keep you Dragon Slayers
from ever physically
transforming into a dragon,
and therefore, suffering
the same fate as Acnologia.
Oh yeah.
I remember Zirconis
telling us about that.
He mentioned something about
Acnologia being human once.
[IGNEEL]
Yes.
And now for the second reason...
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
Hey wait!
[IGNEEL] We'll finish
this discussion later.
You just worry about
getting that book.
Dad, come back!
What does he want? A book?
Which one?
[GRAY]
This is what he wants, isn't it?
The Book of E.N.D.
Hand it over.
I made a promise, too.
That I would do whatever
it took to defeat E.N.D.
This ain't about you.
[ACNOLOGIA]
So that was the reason you chose
to stay with the humans.
You wanted to keep them
from turning into me!
[IGNEEL]
What do you want?
It's over now.
E.N.D. is gone!
You have no reason
to fear them anymore!
[IGNEEL]
Why don't you leave them alone?
[ACNOLOGIA]
Oh, come now.
You don't really think I feared
one of Zeref's pathetic
demons, do you?
That's ridiculous.
For I am Acnologia.
King of the Dragons!
[IGNEEL] But, don't forget,
you were once a human.
I will not stand by, and let
these other Dragon Slayers
meet the same fate.
[ACNOLOGIA] It doesn't
matter where you stand.
I'll still destroy you.
Just like I'll destroy them.
And the entire world!
C'mon, cut it out you guys.
Quit foolin' around.
These are the kinda fights
that hold Fairy Tail back.
Where'd it go?
You gotta be kiddin'!
It wasn't my fault!
[ZEREF] Thank you for
taking care of my book.
[GRAY gasps]
[gasps]
[ROGUE]
Uh..
[MARD GEER whimpers]
[ZEREF] But I think it's
best that I keep it.
It's rather important, you see.
Where'd it go?
You gotta be kiddin'!
It wasn't my fault!
[ZEREF] Thank you for
taking care of my book.
[GRAY gasps]
[STING gasps]
[ROGUE]
Uh...
[MARD GEER whimpers]
[ZEREF] But I think it's
best that I keep it.
It's rather important, you see.
I should've known.
Wait, is that Zeref?
[ROGUE whimpers]
[ZEREF]
Well, Mard Geer.
That was a valiant effort.
You came so very close
to reviving E.N.D.
[MARD GEER gasping]
You've earned the time
to rest in peace.
[MARD GEER]
Master...
Please, I... I only
wanted to fulfill
the promise I made to you.
It saddens me, but you failed.
[MARD GEER whimpers]
[NATSU, GRAY gasp]
[ROGUE, STING gasp]
[GRAY]
What the hell?!
Didn't you create him?!
[ZEREF]
I did, but, you see...
what I create, I destroy.
[STING growls]
[ZEREF]
When this all began,
I was only interested
in dealing with you.
[NATSU]
What?
[ZEREF] But then, Acnologia had
to come along and ruin my plan.
I can't help but wonder, will
he change history once again?
Or will there be a miracle?
[ZEREF] Not even I know
the answer to that.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just very interested
to see how you survive
this new era of darkness.
If you can, that is.
I'll show you despair unlike
anything you've ever imagined.
Well now what do we do?
That book could
destroy everything!
Not if I have it.
[IGNEEL roars]
[IGNEEL groans]
[ACNOLOGIA]
Is that all you've got?
I expected more from "Igneel,
The Fire Dragon King!"
[IGNEEL]
Thanks to you,
my powers have been dormant
for quite some time.
[NATSU gasps]
[IGNEEL]
Son.
[NATSU gasping]
Dad, where are you?!
[IGNEEL]
I owe you an explanation.
And I'm going to give it
to you while I still can.
So try not to interrupt
me this time.
As I mentioned before,
there were two reasons we stayed
inside the Dragon Slayers.
The first was to create
antibodies within you.
To keep you from ever undergoing
any physical transformation.
Thankfully, that process
was successful
and you will never experience
the dragon-ification
that Acnologia once did.
[GRAY]
Where are you going?!
[IGNEEL] The process of
creating these antibodies was
very delicate and required
all of our energy.
That's why we never made
our presence known to you.
And now the other reason.
We were waiting for the perfect
time to fix our mistakes.
It was our destructive legacy
that brought Acnologia
to this world,
and we wanted be the ones
to personally eliminate him.
[NATSU]
No!
This isn't how it
was supposed to be!
Just hang in there
a little longer!
We're gonna take him
down side by side.
[IGNEEL] No! This isn't
your fight, Natsu!
He's more powerful
than we imagined.
You must stay away.
That is an order!
[NATSU]
I don't care!
You left me once, and I'm not
gonna let you leave me again!
[IGNEEL roars]
[IGNEEL] I have waited for
this moment for so long.
Once I've slain you,
I can rest peacefully.
[IGNEEL]
Natsu...
Natsu.
Look what I caught, Dad!
[IGNEEL]
Good work.
Are you gonna cook it?
Well I would, but you
gotta make me a fire!
[IGNEEL]
Absolutely not.
You know how to do it yourself!
But it's so easy for you.
Do I really have to do it again?
[IGNEEL]
If you want to eat.
Come on now.
You're burning daylight.
[NATSU]
All... done!
My spelling's gotten pretty
near perfect, don't you think?
[IGNEEL]
What?!
Everything's spelled wrong.
Do it again!
You gotta be
kidding me, old man!
Do you know how long I've
been working on this?!
[IGNEEL] Complain all you want,
but it's still not right!
[NATSU]
You want me to redo it?
Fine.
It'll be so good you
won't know what to do.
[NATSU]
Whoa! This is awesome!
[IGNEEL]
Make sure you hold on tight!
[NATSU]
Huh?
[NATSU screams]
[NATSU]
Whoa! That was a close one, Dad!
[IGNEEL]
You better brace yourself.
Cause we're just
getting started!
Ya ready son?
Hey! We made it
and I didn't fall.
Let's go again!
[IGNEEL laughs]
You asked for it!
[NATSU] Hah! There's no way
you can knock me off!
[NATSU]
Hey, Dad, watch this!
Here goes!
Fire Dragon... Roar!
Whaddya think?
[IGNEEL]
You call that a roar?
You couldn't even
cook a fish with that!
Then let's see you do it!
[IGNEEL]
All right, then.
Fire Dragon... Roar!
[NATSU gasping]
[NATSU]
Thought you said
we weren't supposed to
wreck the mountains.
[IGNEEL] Sometimes it's okay
to go a little overboard.
[IGNEEL laughs]
Now it's my turn!
Will you teach me
how to do that, too?
[IGNEEL]
You already know.
The key is to always keep
a fire in your belly.
[NATSU]
That's easy!
[snoring]
[IGNEEL]
Natsu.
I'm so proud of the wizard
that you've become.
Driven, loyal, and strong.
Those years I spent with you
were the happiest of my life.
[IGNEEL] You might think
I was the one who taught
you everything, but you
were my greatest teacher.
[IGNEEL] Because you
taught me how to love.
Never forget that.
[whimpering]
[NATSU]
Dad, no!
[LUCY]
The battle is finally over.
And although Fairy Tail
has emerged victorious,
it comes at a great,
irreplaceable cost.
As the dragons reveal
the shocking truth
in the ruins of this
barren wasteland,
Natsu sheds what seems to be
an endless stream of tears,
etching his father's
unforgettable words
into his broken heart.
Next Time:
"Tartaros Chapter, Finale
Where the Power of Life Lies."
All that remains, is the
drive to keep living.