HEY GUYS! READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- HOW MANY TIMES
I GOTTA TELL YA?
WATCH OUT, BLONDIE!
- OH!
MAN, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
( sighs )
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND
A DECENT JOB LATELY.
IF I CAN'T PAY RENT,
I'LL GET KICKED OUT.
- ( cooing )
- WHAT?
YOU THINK IT'LL ALL WORK OUT?
- WELL, THAT'S A POSITIVE
ATTITUDE IF I'VE EVER SEEN ONE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ALONE
FOR ONCE.
I WISH I COULD JUST COME HOME
WITHOUT HAVING TO SEARCH
THE PLACE FOR WEIRDOES.
- ( cooing )
- YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN THROUGH
AN AWFUL LOT LATELY.
I THINK I DESERVE A NICE,
LONG BATH.
AH, BACK FROM THE DEAD.
PRETTY CUTE FOR A ZOMBIE,
DON'TCHA THINK?
IT'S A SHAME
THAT THERE'S NOBODY HERE
TO LAUGH AT MY JOKES.
- ( cooing )
- HEY, YOU GET ALL WRINKLY
IN THE TUB JUST LIKE I DO!
WHO WOULD'VE KNOWN?
AW, PLUE,
YOU'RE SO CUTE!
- ( Happy speaking )
- TIME FOR BED.
( squeals )
THIS BETTER NOT BE
WHAT I THINK IT IS.
AH!
- ( moaning )
- AHHH!
- G'MORNING.
- DON'T PLAY COOL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN MY ROOM
IN MY BED WITH YOUR CAT?
- AYE?
- GO AWAY!
- FIVE MORE MINUTES.
- YOU MUST BE DREAMING.
- GIVE NATSU HIS SCARF BACK,
YOU MEANIE.
- IS IT THAT IMPORTANT TO HIM?
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
WITHOUT IT.
HE NEVER
TAKES THIS THING OFF, HUH?
- NOPE, HE GOT IT FROM IGNEEL,
SO IT MEANS A LOT TO HIM.
- HM.
- ( Natsu moaning )
- HEY.  ARE YOU SURE
HE'S GONNA BE OKAY?
- AYE.  HE'S PROBABLY
JUST FEELIN' A LITTLE SICKLY
'CAUSE HE ATE
ALL THAT ETHER-NANO.
- OH, IS THAT BAD FOR HIM?
- AYE.
ONE TIME HE ATE
A BUNCH OF LAXUS' LIGHTNING
AND THE SAME THING HAPPENED.
- MMM.  SO EATING ANYTHING
OTHER THAN FIRE MAKES HIM SICK?
WAIT.  WHY WOULD HE EVER
WANNA EAT LAXUS' LIGHTNING?
- WELL, HE DIDN'T WANNA EAT IT.
THEY FOUGHT AND NATSU
GOT HIS BUTT WHOOPED PRETTY BAD.
- ( screaming )
- WOW, I HAD NO IDEA
HE WAS THAT POWERFUL.
- AYE.
HE'S SUPER DUPER STRONG.
WHO KNOWS? MAYBE ERZA OR
MYSTOGAN MIGHT BE ABLE
TO BEAT HIM NOW.
ACTUALLY, MIRA WAS PRETTY TOUGH
BACK IN THE DAY.
SHE EVEN HAD THE NICKNAME
"THE SHE DEVIL."
- BUT SHE'S SO SWEET.
- WE SHOULD HAVE
A BIG TOURNAMENT
TO DECIDE WHO'S THE STRONGEST.
IT MIGHT BE FUN TO FIND
OUT WHERE YOU STAND, HUH?
- I'M FINE NOT KNOWING.
AND BESIDES, I DON'T LIKE
THE IDEA OF RANKING MY FRIENDS.
- I WONDER HOW GRAY
AND ELFMAN WOULD DO?
GAJEEL AND JUVIA
ARE PRETTY AWESOME TOO.
- YEAH, I GET IT.
EVERYONE'S GREAT BUT ME.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO HEAD HOME, 'KAY?
- OKAY.
- WHAT'VE YOU GOT HERE?
- OH!  I FORGOT I WAS
SUPPOSED TO SHOW THAT TO YOU.
YOU NEED MONEY FOR RENT,
RIGHT?
FAIRY TAIL IS GONNA BE PART
OF THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
- HOW'S THAT HELP ME?
CHECK IT OUT AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE PAGE.
- "MISS FAIRY TAIL CONTEST"?
- AYE.
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE WINNER
GETS 500,000 JEWEL.
- OH MY GOSH, IF I COULD
JUST WIN THAT PRIZE MONEY,
I COULD COVER RENT
FOR THE NEXT SEVEN MONTHS.
- EVEN THOUGH MIRA AND CANA
ARE ENTERING THE CONTEST TOO,
YOU MIGHT STILL
HAVE A SHOT AT IT.
- IF MIRA'S COMPETING,
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
SHE'S A BIKINI MODEL
FOR "SORCERER WEEKLY."
AW, BUT WAIT.
I'M YOUNGER THAN SHE IS,
WHICH MAKES ME
THE EXCITING NEW MODEL!
I CAN DO IT!
YEAH!
BRING IT ON!
THAT PRIZE MONEY
IS AS GOOD AS MINE!
- SO YOU'RE AGAINST
RANKING YOUR FRIENDS
UNLESS THERE'S MONEY INVOLVED,
IS THAT IT?
- HAPPY, YOU WANNA
EAT SOME YUMMY FISH?
- I SEE. YOUR GUILTY CONSCIENCE
IS GETTIN' TO YA, HUH?
- MMHH!
- Narrator: THIS IS THE TOWN
OF SHIROTSUME.
IN ITS NORTHERN CORNER
LIES A DARK GUILD
KNOWN AS GHOUL SPIRIT.
- AHHH!
- YOU LAUGHED AT US,
DIDN'T YOU?  BIG MISTAKE.
- IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A FIGHT,
YOU GOT ONE!
- AHHH!
- TO THINK THAT A PACK OF RATS
WOULD HAVE THE AUDACITY
TO MOCK MEMBERS
OF A PROPER GUILD.
WHAT IS THE WORLD COMING TO?
- AHHH!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- THEY TURNED TO STONE.
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT!
- AHHH!
- C'MON, BABIES.
LET'S PARTY!
( laughing )
- Fried: I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH,
BIXLOW.
- WHAT?
Y'MEAN WE'RE DONE ALREADY?
- LET'S NOT WASTE OUR TIME
WITH THESE WEAKLINGS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY EVEN
BOTHERED TO FORM A GUILD.
- BUT WE CAN'T LEAVE JUST YET.
MY LITTLE BABIES ARE LOOKIN'
TO HAVE MORE FUN.
- MORE FUN!  MORE FUN!
- BE PATIENT.
I ASSURE YOU THEY'LL SEE
PLENTY OF ACTION SOON ENOUGH.
- SO WE'RE GOING THROUGH
WITH LAXUS' PLAN?
I SUPPOSE IT'S ABOUT TIME.
- YOU BETTER NOT
BE JERKING MY CHAIN,
CAUSE I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS.
MY BABIES TOO.
YAH HA HA!
- WHO THE HECK ARE THESE GUYS?
THERE'S ONLY THREE OF 'EM--
HOW COULD THEY TAKE OUT
OUR WHOLE GUILD LIKE THAT?
- HOLD ON.
THAT'S THE THUNDER LEGION.
SOME OF FAIRY TAIL'S BEST
AND LAXUS' PERSONAL GUARDS.
- ( chuckling )
THE THUNDER LEGION'LL
BE BACK SOON.
LOOKS LIKE MY TIME
HAS FINALLY COME.
YOUR LITTLE FAIRIES
ARE GONNA EAT EACH OTHER ALIVE.
HEAR THAT, OLD MAN?
YOUR ERA'S
ABOUT TO COME TO AN END.
- Makarov: THE WHOLE TOWN'S
GETTING INTO
THE HARVEST FESTIVAL SPIRIT.
- AND EVERYONE AT
THE GUILD'S GETTING READY
FOR THE FANTASIA PARADE.
- OF COURSE, PEOPLE COME
FROM ALL OVER THE COUNTRY
TO SEE OUR PARADE. WE CAN'T
LET OUR FANS DOWN, CAN WE?
- IT WOULD BE NICE IF LAXUS
WOULD JOIN US FOR ONCE.
- THE LESS SAID ABOUT THAT BUM,
THE BETTER.
- I HEARD FROM LEVY
THAT HE'S BACK IN TOWN.
EVEN IF HE SAYS NO,
IT WOULDN'T HURT TO ASK HIM.
- HE CAME BACK?  MMMHH.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- OF ALL TIMES,
WHY'D HE HAVE TO SHOW UP NOW?
- Young Laxus: HEY, GRAMPS!
GRAMPS!
HEY, WAIT UP!
- OH, HI, LAXUS.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA JOIN
THE FANTASIA PARADE
WITH EVERYONE ELSE?
- NOW WHY WOULD I DO THAT
WHEN I PROMISED I'D WATCH IT
WITH YOU THIS YEAR?
- ALL RIGHT!  HA HA HA!
YOU'RE GONNA LET ME
JOIN THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD
SOMEDAY, AREN'T YA, GRAMPS?
- SURE, WHEN YOU'RE
A LITTLE OLDER.
- ( giggling )
AW, MAN, I CAN'T SEE!
- WELL, THAT IS A PROBLEM.
WHOA, AH AHHH!
- THERE.
NOW YOU CAN SEE, RIGHT?
THE WIZARDS FROM FAIRY TAIL
ARE PRETTY COOL, HUH?
- OH, YEAH. THEY'RE THE COOLEST
WIZARDS IN THE WORLD.
YOU'RE THE BEST GUILD MASTER
EVER, GRAMPS.
- Boy: WHEN I GROW UP,
I'M GONNA JOIN FAIRY TAIL
AND BE IN THE PARADE TOO.
- Man: OH, ARE YOU NOW?
THAT'S GREAT.
- Narrator: AND SO, ON THE DAY
OF THE HARVEST FESTIVAL...
- ( vibrating ) FOOD.
- AYE!
- MUST EAT.
MUST EAT EVERYTHING IN SIGHT.
- CHOW TIME!  YEAH.
- NATSU STILL HASN'T RECOVERED,
HUH?
- HE DOES SEEM RATHER ILL,
DOESN'T HE?
- HE'LL BE FINE ONCE HE EATS.
TRUST ME.
- Warren: YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
A BIT, GRAY.
- HEY, WARREN.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
- DIDN'T THINK I'D MAKE IT BACK
IN TIME FOR THE FESTIVAL,
BUT HERE I AM.
- THIS GUY TAKES ON
SO MANY JOBS,
WE HARDLY EVER SEE HIM.
- WOW.
- HELLO, I'M A NEW RECRUIT.
MY NAME'S JUVIA.
- AH, SO YOU'RE THE ONE
I'VE BEEN HEARING ABOUT.
- MEET WARREN ROCCO.
HE'S A MASTER
OF TELEPATHY MAGIC.
- IT'S NICE TO MEET YA.
- THANK YOU,
THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
THIS FESTIVAL IS QUITE A SIGHT.
- Lucy: NO KIDDING.
WHAT A CROWD.
- Warren:
IT'S A PRETTY BIG DEAL.
PEOPLE COME FROM ALL AROUND
TO SEE THE FANTASIA PARADE.
- I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE IT MYSELF.
- YOU'RE IN THE PARADE,
REMEMBER?
- WASN'T THERE SOMETHING ELSE
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE IN?
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT
THE MISS FAIRY TAIL CONTEST!
MY RENT MONEY!
- A CONTEST?
I REFUSE TO BE OUTDONE
BY THAT BIMBO.
- SO I GUESS
YOU'LL BE ENTERING TOO?
- Max Alors: THE LONG WAIT
IS FINALLY OVER,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
WELCOME TO THE ONE AND ONLY
MISS FAIRY TAIL CONTEST,
WHERE YOUR FAVORITE FAIRIES
FIGHT IN A BATTLE OF BEAUTY.
I'M MAX ALORS--
SAND WIZARD EXTRAORDINAIRE,
AND I'LL BE YOUR HOST
FOR THIS EXCITING EVENT.
- ( all cheering )
- I EXPECTED TO SEE ELFMAN HERE,
BUT WHY YOU?
- 'CAUSE HE'S A MAN.
- NOW LET'S MEET
ENTRY #1!
THE EXOTIC BEAUTY WHO'LL
DRINK YOU UNDER THE TABLE
ANY DAY OF THE WEEK!
CANA ALBERONA!
NOW BUST OUT SOME MAGIC
AND SHOW US YOUR STUFF!
SHE SENT HER DECK SPINNING.
WHAT COULD SHE BE DOING
BEHIND ALL THOSE CARDS?
SHE CHANGED
INTO A SWIMSUIT!
- THE PRIZE MONEY
CAN COVER MY TAB.
- A SWIMSUIT?
NO FAIR.
- THAT'S A CLEVER IDEA.
MAYBE I SHOULD DO THE SAME.
- YOU'RE IN THIS TOO?
- WHENEVER I HEAR
THE WORD "CONTEST,"
I GET ALL WORKED UP.
- BYE BYE, RENT MONEY.
IT'S OVER FOR ME.
- ON TO ENTRY #2!
SHE MAY BE NEW TO THE GUILD,
BUT HER MAGIC IS S-CLASS.
A RADIANT BEAUTY IN RAIN
OR SHINE-- JUVIA LOXAR!
- PLEASE,
LET THESE FEELINGS
REACH YOU, MY BELOVED PRINCE.
- Max: AND THE LOVELY LADY
IS ALL SET
FOR A FABULOUS DAY
AT THE BEACH!
- LOOK AT ME, GRAY!
DO YOU LIKE WHAT YOU SEE?
- ANOTHER SWIMSUIT?
GIMME A BREAK.
- NEXT UP IS ENTRY #3,
FAIRY TAIL'S FAMOUS CENTERFOLD.
HER BEAUTY HAS STOLEN
THE HEARTS OF MEN AND WOMEN
ALL OVER THE LAND.
MIRAJANE!
- ( men cheering )
- NOW SHOW US YOUR STUFF!
- MY SPECIALTY
IS TRANSFORMATION MAGIC,
SO I'LL SHOW YOU A NEW SIDE
OF ME.
THIS IS MY HAPPY FACE.
AYE!
HERE'S MY GAJEEL FACE.
COOL, HUH?
- WELL, I'M GLAD AT LEAST
SOMEONE'S ENJOYING THIS.
- SHE'S A MAN?
- OH, WELL, LESS
COMPETITION FOR ME.
- MM-HMM.
- ENTRY #4!
THE FAIRY QUEEN
WHO NEEDS NO INTRODUCTION.
- THAT'S MY CUE.
- ERZA SCARLET!
- Man: IT'S HER!
- CHECK OUT THE ARMOR!
- Lucy:
WOW, SHE'S REALLY POPULAR.
- LET ME SHOW YOU A REQUIP
YOU DON'T GET TO SEE EVERY DAY.
AHHH!
- GOTHIC LOLITA?!
- LOOKS LIKE I WIN.
- NEVER THOUGHT I'D SEE HER
DRESSED LIKE THAT.
- OUI.
- AND HERE IS ENTRY #5!
PETITE AND CUTE, THIS FAIRY IS
AS SMART AS SHE IS CHARMING.
LET'S HEAR IT
FOR LEVY McGARDEN!
- LEVY!
- LET ME SHOW YOU
MY SOLID SCRIPT.
- LEVY!
- HERE WE HAVE ENTRY #6.
THE SNIPER WITH HER SIGHTS
ON YOUR HEART,
THE ONE AND ONLY BISCA MULAN!
- HA!
REQUIP TIME.
THE GUNNER!
YEE-HAW.
- THAT'S HOT!
- HOW CAN I TOP THAT?
- LET'S MOVE ON
TO ENTRY #7,
FAIRY TAIL'S RISING STAR.
- Lucy: HERE WE GO.
- SHE SHINES AS BRIGHTLY
AS THE SPIRITS THAT GUIDE
HER WAY. LUCY HEART--
AH! PLEASE DON'T SAY
MY LAST NAME OUT LOUD!
- WHO'S THAT?
- SHE'S CUTE.
- THERE'S NO WAY THEY'LL GIVE ME
THE PRIZE MONEY
IF THEY FIND OUT
WHO MY DAD IS.
- NOW SHOW US WHAT YOU GOT.
- ME AND MY CELESTIAL SPIRITS
ARE GONNA DO A CHEER
FOR YOU GUYS.
- ( all cheer )
- Evergreen: ENTRY #8.
- HEY, HOLD ON-- I HAVEN'T
EVEN STARTED TO DO MY CHEER YET.
- I AM THE VERY DEFINITION
OF "FAIRY."
NOT TO MENTION,
THE VERY DEFINITION OF BEAUTY.
I'M THE ONLY WOMAN HERE WHO
EMBODIES EVERYTHING MEN DESIRE.
THEREFORE, THE WINNER IS--
ME, THE LOVELY EVERGREEN.
NOW THIS IDIOTIC CONTEST
CAN END.
- AHHH!
- WHOA.  SHE'S BACK?
- THEN LAXUS MUST BE HERE TOO.
- Lucy: CAN'T YOU GO MESS UP
A DIFFERENT CONTEST?
GIMME A BREAK HERE.
I REALLY NEED THIS PRIZE MONEY!
- LUCY!
DON'T LOOK HER IN THE EYE.
- I'M SORRY,
WHAT WAS YOUR NAME?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- SHE TURNED TO STONE.
- IS THAT HER TRICK?
- Max: THIS IS BAD.
EVERYONE, GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
- ( all screaming )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, EVERGREEN?
YOU'LL RUIN THE FESTIVAL
FOR EVERYONE.
- ( laughs )
ON THE CONTRARY,
I THINK THINGS
ARE JUST GETTING INTERESTING.
- NO!  MIRA!
- SHE GOT ERZA TOO?
- DON'T BE A FOOL! RETURN THEM
TO NORMAL THIS INSTANT.
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE ALL YOUR FANS
DECIDED TO HEAD HOME.
- PITY, 'CAUSE THE PARTY'S
ABOUT TO START.
- I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
- Gray: FRIED?  BIXLOW, TOO?
- THE THUNDER LEGION.
- WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU GUYS
TRYIN' TO PULL?
- C'MON,
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!
- I'VE HAD ABOUT ENOUGH
OF YOUR NONSENSE.
TURN THEM BACK, OR ELSE.
- YOU'D BETTER PLAY NICE IF
YOU WANT THESE LADIES
TO JOIN THE PARADE.
- NO, STOP!
- IN OTHER WORDS,
I'M TAKING ALL OF THEM HOSTAGE.
BREAK THE RULES AND I'LL
SHATTER THESE CHICKS ONE BY ONE.
OR I COULD JUST SMASH 'EM ALL
RIGHT NOW.
- Makarov: I'M NOT AMUSED,
LAXUS. STOP FOOLING AROUND.
- I'M SERIOUS, OLD MAN.
- I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED WHO WAS
THE STRONGEST IN THE GUILD.
NOW IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT.
- YEAH, LET'S HAVE SOME FUN.
- FUN, FUN!
- THERE'S ONLY ONE RULE.
WHO'S EVER LEFT STANDING
IN THE END IS THE WINNER.
IT'S A FAIRY-TAIL
BATTLE ROYALE!
- NICE AND SIMPLE.
THAT'S JUST HOW I LIKE IT.
I'M FIRED UP NOW.
- GLAD YOU COULD SEE IT MY WAY.
IF NOTHING ELSE,
YOU GOT THE RIGHT ATTITUDE.
- NATSU.
- THIS IS A FESTIVAL,
RIGHT? LET'S PARTY.
- HAVE YOU ALREADY FORGOTTEN
HOW BADLY HE BEAT YOU
THE LAST TIME YOU GUYS
WENT AT IT?
- Natsu:
I WAS JUST A KID BACK THEN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT WAS LAST YEAR!
- YEAH, BUT SINCE THEN,
I'VE BECOME A MAN.
- ON THE OTHER HAND,
I THINK THAT ATTITUDE OF YOURS
IS GONNA GET YOU INTO A WORLD
OF HURT.
- WHY DON'T YOU SIT BACK DOWN?
- AHH!
- NATSU.
- I TOLD YOU SO.
- HE'S NO MAN.
- POOR GUY.  HE WAS FINALLY
FEELING BETTER TOO.
- NATURALLY, IF YOU WANT ME TO
TURN THE GIRLS BACK TO NORMAL,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DEFEAT US FIRST.
- BUT THOSE ODDS AREN'T BAD.
THERE'S FOUR OF US
AND LIKE A HUNDRED OF YOU GUYS.
- LOTS OF YOU.
LOTS OF YOU!
- YOU HAVE THREE HOURS
AND NOT A SECOND MORE.
AFTER THAT, THESE PRETTY STATUES
OF YOURS
WILL BE REDUCED TO DUST.
- YOU KIDDIN' ME?
- Laxus: ALL OF MAGNOLIA WILL
SERVE AS THE BATTLEFIELD.
THE FIGHT WILL BEGIN WHEN,
AND IF, YOU CAN FIND US.
- LAXUS, HOW COULD YOU?
I WON'T STAND FOR THIS!
- NOW NOW,
SIMMER DOWN, OLD MAN.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE FESTIVAL,
RIGHT?
IT'LL BE FUN!
- CAN'T SEE.
- Laxus: LET THE BATTLE
OF FAIRY TAIL BEGIN!
- Alzack: HE DISAPPEARED.
- Macao: SO IT'S HIGH-STAKES
HIDE AND GO SEEK, HUH?
- LET'S GO! WE GOTTA MAN UP
AND SAVE OUR GIRLS.
- ( all shouting )
- BISCA.
HOLD ON.
I'LL DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO SAVE YOU.
- YOU INSOLENT BRAT!
JUST WAIT!
I'LL STOP YOU
WITH MY OWN TWO HANDS!  AH!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- AN INVISIBLE WALL.
- DON'T BE SILLY, GRAMPS,
THERE'S NOTHIN' HERE.
MAN, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHAT'S THAT FLOATING ABOVE US?
LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND OF WRITING.
- MUST BE ONE OF
FRIED'S ENCHANTMENTS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"ENCHANTMENT"?
- IT'S A BARRIER FORMED
BY MAGIC RUNES.
ANYONE WHO STEPS INSIDE
IS BOUND BY ITS RULES
AND THE ONLY WAY TO ESCAPE
IS TO FOLLOW THEM.
- ANY IDEA WHAT IT SAYS?
- "STONE STATUES AND ANYONE OVER
THE AGE OF 80 YEARS
SHALL NOT PASS."
- WHOEVER WRITES THE RULES
WINS THE FIGHT, HUH?
- PERHAPS, BUT ENCHANTMENTS
LIKE THESE TAKE TIME TO WRITE.
AS SUCH, THEY WOULD BE USELESS
IN A ONE-ON-ONE BATTLE.
STILL, AS YOU CAN SEE,
THEY'RE QUITE EFFECTIVE
IF SET UP AS TRAPS.
- YOU'RE REALLY STUCK?
YOU CAN'T BREAK THROUGH?
- I'M AFRAID THE RULES
OF THE ENCHANTMENT ARE ABSOLUTE.
- WELL,
I GUESS THAT SETTLES IT.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO GO INTO THIS FIGHT
WITHOUT YA, GRAMPS.
- I'M SORRY.
- I WON'T SHOW MERCY,
EVEN IF LAXUS IS YOUR GRANDSON.
HE'S GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
- I DON'T KNOW IF GRAY
OR ANYONE ELSE IN THE GUILD
IS STRONG ENOUGH TO BEAT HIM.
ERZA PERHAPS.
BUT NOT
IN HER PRESENT CONDITION.
MMHH.
I SEE YOU.
- AH.
- WHAT'S WRONG, REEDUS?
- WELL, I'M AFRAID LAXUS
IS GONNA HURT ME.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU VISIT PORLYUSICA
IN THE EAST FOREST?
- OUI?
- SHE MAY HAVE A POTION
TO CURE PETRIFICATION.
- OUI.
- AHHH!
- YOU'RE AWAKE!
- HOLD ON.
WHERE'D LAXUS GO?
ACTUALLY, WHERE'D EVERYONE GO?
- NATSU.
IF HE GOT SERIOUS, HE MIGHT BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO PULL IT OFF.
- GRAMPS, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE EVERYBODY ELSE RAN OFF TO?
- I'LL HAVE TO PUT MY FAITH
IN HIS RAW TALENT.
NOW LISTEN UP--
THE FESTIVAL IS UNDER WAY.
LAXUS IS HIDING SOMEWHERE
IN MAGNOLIA.
FIND HIM AND BEAT HIM!
- ALL RIGHT!
JUST YOU WAIT LA--
- AH!
- UH, WHAT THE HECK?
- YOU FIND ANYONE, ALZACK?
- NOPE, NO LUCK HERE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- SORRY.
WE GOT NOTHIN'.
- DAMN IT!
HOW DARE THEY DO THAT TO BISCA?
- WHOA, JUST TRY
AND TAKE IT EASY, MAN.
- TAKE IT EASY?
WE ONLY HAVE THREE HOURS.
- WHAT THE--? A TRAP?
- Alzack: IT'S AN ENCHANTMENT.
- ARE YOU TELLING ME THEY PUT
THESE THINGS UP ALL OVER TOWN?
- IT MUST BE FRIED'S WORK.
- IT SAYS: "ONLY THE WIZARD
WHO PROVES HIMSELF TO BE
THE STRONGEST IS
ALLOWED TO LEAVE
THIS BARRIER."
- BUT WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I THINK HE'S TRYING TO MAKE US
FIGHT EACH OTHER.
- THAT'S A DIRTY TRICK, FRIED!
- ALL RIGHT.  SORRY.
BUT I GOTTA SAVE HER!
- Makarov:
WHY CAN'T YOU GET THROUGH?
OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE NOT
A STONE STATUE.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE OVER 80?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- "BATTLE OF FAIRY TAIL
STATUS REPORT."
- WHAT? IT SAYS "JET VERSUS
DROY VERSUS ALZACK."
IS THIS SOME KIND OF JOKE?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THOSE GUYS WOULD BE FIGHTING
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
- FALCON HEAVEN SOAR!
- KNUCKLE PLANT!
- GUNS MAGIC!
TORNADO SHOT!
"THE WINNER IS ALZACK.
JET AND DROY K.O.-ED."
- WHAT?
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- LET'S SEE HOW LONG
YOU CAN ENDURE
THIS GAME OF FAIRY-EAT-FAIRY,
OLD GEEZER.
- STOP THIS STUPID GAME
RIGHT NOW!  LAXUS!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THE THUNDER LEGION
IS FINALLY READY TO FIGHT.
EVERGREEN, BIXLOW, FRIED.
I'M TELLING YOU, THOSE GUYS
ARE CRAZY STRONG!
I'M GETTING ALL FIRED UP!
- WELL, I HATE
TO BURST YOUR BUBBLE,
BUT NO MATTER HOW BAD
YOU WANNA FIGHT THEM,
YOU CAN'T 'CAUSE YOU'RE
STILL STUCK INSIDE THAT BARRIER.
- YEAH.
I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
- Both: NEXT TIME, "DEFEAT YOUR
FRIENDS TO SAVE YOUR FRIENDS."
- Happy: I DON'T THINK GAJEEL
CAN LEAVE THE BARRIER EITHER.
WHY DON'T YOU GET TO KNOW
EACH OTHER BETTER
OVER A NICE CUP OF TEA?
- I AIN'T DRINKING TEA
WITH THAT GUY!