Where did Zeref go?
[STING] Well, don't forget we're
inside your mind, Natsu.
I imagine you subconsciously
replaced him with me.
You're not makin'
any sense, man!
[STING]
That's all right.
Follow me. We can find
the answer together.
To what?
Don't you wanna
know what that thing
growing inside you actually is?
And I hate the way you smell!
It's burning up the hair
in my nostrils!
The fact that a weak,
insignificant person
has the gall to challenge me
makes me wanna vomit.
Hey, Rogue!
Thanks for the power!
Now go, White Shadow Dragon.
I've got a fire in my belly.
On to the next desire.
One you will not
be able to resist.
This spell is known
as "Rest In Peace."
Call it whatever you want.
But you're still gonna lose.
Once I've ended your life,
Natsu Dragneel will be
the next one to perish.
[STING] Are you tryin'
to get me more fired up?
'Cause whether you like it or
not, that's what's happening!
I've spent way too many years
tryin' to get to Natsu's level,
so I'm not gonna let a bastard
like you get in my way.
My aim is to purify
Natsu's tarnished soul
with my own hands.
Your delusions of grandeur
won't be enough to stop me.
I've got real power,
and whenever I combine
it with Rogue's,
I wield the essence
of Sabertooth!
[chuckles]
Shattered.
White magic won't work
'cause Sting has the
power to cancel it.
I'm gonna knock
down your attack
and hit you with Rogue's shadow!
[STING yells]
[STING yelling]
[STING]
But wait.
[STING] Let's see what happens
when I use both at once!
[chuckles]
[yells]
[STING] So, you're the
stubborn type, huh?
[LARCADE]
Two powers together?
You're not strong enough
to fight the desire
all living creatures
must fall to.
Succumb to the eternal
sleep of death!
Now Rest in Peace!
[gasps]
What is this?
Mustn't sleep. No.
Death will be upon you the
instant you close your eyes.
Sleep... It's hard to resist.
But I cannot give in.
Listen, Frosch, you
can't fall asleep, okay?
I think so, too.
'Kay, good night.
Now is not the time
to say "good night."
Frosch! Listen to me.
Come on, Frosch.
Do you hear me? Wake up!
[screams]
[STING]
Snap out of it, damn it!
Don't sleep! Don't sleep!
Don't sleep!
Nobody can fully resist
their primal desires.
Not even mighty Acnologia.
And that weakness
gives me power.
I will use it to defeat him,
thus proving I am
the ultimate wizard.
What now?
Your shadow. Go into it.
[ROGUE] Your senses will be
sharper inside the shadow.
It won't last long,
but it will wake you up.
I'm not so sure I'm able to.
I don't know how to do that.
You must feel the gravity.
Focus on it until your feet
and the ground become one.
[STING]
Feel the gravity. Become one.
[KAGURA]
Gravity is a specialty of mine!
I can make you sink
into the earth!
What the--?
Kagura!
[gasps]
I feel so heavy!
Okay, okay.
I'm awake! For real!
Wait! Hang on!
Yeah!
[STING] Crazy. I'm really
inside my shadow.
He was right.
My senses are sharpening!
[STING]
Here we go.
I can still see you!
Fly Spirit! Into the heavens!
[STING]
Won't happen!
'Cause I'm using all of our
powers combined into one!
Mine, too, huh?
[gasps]
It's called White
Shadow Dragon Silk!
[LARCADE groans]
Close your eyes.
You need to sleep it off.
Nice! Now that's how
you do it! Yeah!
A nap doesn't sound
so bad, huh?
Father... I failed.
[groans]
[NATSU]
Jeez, Sting. How far we goin'?
[ROGUE]
What?
I'm Rogue, Natsu.
[screams]
When did that happen?
[ROGUE] Look, we're inside
your mind, remember?
[NATSU] Hey! Don't you blame
me for your tricks, man!
[ROGUE] It only serves
as further proof
that you need to focus.
Huh?
You know about your
scarf, don't you?
That it was crafted for you
using Igneel's scales.
'Course I know!
The scarf is white despite the
fact Igneel's scales were red.
Do you know the reason why?
[NATSU]
Hm?
[gasps]
Oh, wow. That's
a great question!
[ROGUE] So it never crossed
your mind until just now?
Once a dragon's scales fall off,
they begin to lose their color.
[NATSU]
Huh. Okay.
That's important, but not for
the reason you think it is.
Humans can't touch
dragon scales.
Not until they've lost
their color completely.
You don't actually
believe Igneel sat down
and knitted a tiny,
human-sized scarf, do you?
[NATSU] Are you tryin'
to tell me he didn't?
[ROGUE]
As a matter of fact,
your scarf was made
by a woman named Anna.
It's safe to assume you've
forgotten about that, though.
Wait. Lucy?
Striking isn't it?
Looks just like your friend.
[NATSU]
You again!
Anna was very kind and caring.
She was a truly
incredible person.
Now then, your death
is drawing near.
As is the answer we
had hoped to find.
[LUCY]
Natsu!
[PORLYUSICA]
It's dire.
His temperature is
getting dangerously low.
[HAPPY] Come on, Natsu!
Snap out of it!
Lucy, remove your clothing.
Huh? Why should I?
[PORLYUSICA]
To keep him alive.
He needs the warmth.
He needs to feel it.
Your love.
Honestly, we need
a miracle right now.
Right.
Zeref.
I'll beat him.
Zeref... must die.
He must die.
[HAPPY]
It's all right, Natsu.
You don't have to do it, okay?
Because if you kill Zeref,
you're gonna die too, remember?
[gasps]
[HAPPY]
I don't want that. So please...
Wait. Hold on, Happy.
What are you talking about?
Can you hear me, God?
Natsu can't die now!
So keep him alive, okay?
Please, God. Save him.
Don't take him away from me!
Natsu!
So if he kills Zeref...
Natsu's gonna die, too?
[HAPPY crying]
[STING]
Hm?
Hey, Sting! Rogue! We're here!
You okay?
We're fine. Really.
I'm sorry. Can't
stand up right now.
Isn't that the enemy?
[YUKINO] Thank you for
taking care of him.
Sting is the man!
Rogue, too!
We couldn't have done it
without your help, buddy.
Thank you.
We didn't actually do
any fighting, ya know?
Well, I did throw
a rock, but still.
[FROSCH]
Hey, Rogue.
I waited so I can eat with you.
Uh, sure. Are you
feeling hungry?
Yeah! I waited for you!
[ROGUE]
Okay, thanks.
[YUKINO chuckles]
[MINERVA] Kagura, I didn't know
that you would be here.
Well, I am.
[BOTH gasp]
If you don't mind,
I'd love to join you.
[yells]
[gasps]
[ERZA screams]
Victory is mine.
Yi Ragd!
No!
What is this?
[MINERVA]
Neir wilg mion.
Dels erkantias!
Yagd rigora!
[gasps]
I found a stray kitten.
[ERZA, KAGURA]
Millianna!
[ERZA]
What is the meaning of this?
[MINERVA] Look at that face,
twisted with pain.
The sphere she's in constantly
drains her magic power.
It's excruciating.
[ERZA]
What the hell is this?
Frankly, the two of you
were beginning to bore me.
I needed to do something
to entertain myself.
Her screams were quite lovely.
I hand over this
victory to-- Uh!
[MINERVA]
I need to apologize.
I treated you so poorly during
the Grand Magic Games.
It was wrong.
[KAGURA]
It's okay. I've let it go.
Honestly, I've decided
to live my life
without holding grudges.
Leave the past behind me.
Anyway... it seems this girl is
having some interesting dreams.
That's nice. Now don't
be in such a hurry.
--Seems that way. She, uh--
--Yeah. Kinda forgot about her.
Oh, you know, it's
sort of a long story.
Man, I am so beat.
You think you can take
things from here?
Sure thing. I'll get
us to Fairy Tail.
[KAGURA]
Erza. Please be safe.
[yells]
[IRENE]
Hm.
No, Erza!
Not bad.
[gasps]
Wait.
Heaven's Wheel!
Scattered petals!
Did that stop her?
No. Defeating her will
prove far more difficult.
[IRENE]
An attack of countless swords
all converging on your target.
I'm impressed you were able
to control that many at once.
It's quite a feat.
--[IRENE clapping]
--[gasps]
[IRENE]
For all your hard work...
You earned a flower.
She was able to block that
attack and do all this, too?
But how?
She's mocking me.
Come on, Erza, you had this
girl enhance your power
and this is the best you can do?
Shame. How disappointing.
Tell me. Who are you, really?
[IRENE]
Still haven't figured that out?
Ah. Deep in your heart,
you know exactly who I am.
But you don't
wanna believe it.
[ERZA]
I've never seen you before.
[WENDY] This woman doesn't
just look like Erza...
...she smells a lot
like her, too.
Now, now, Erza.
That's a rude thing
to say to your mother.
What? Is she really
your mother, Erza?
You liar!
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[ERZA]
I grew up in Rosemary Village
before it was burned
to the ground.
[ERZA]
I'm an orphan. I have no family.
You're wrong about that.
Because I am your mother, Erza.
I've only had one
parent in my life.
His name was Master Makarov!
Fine, if that's what you want.
And just because
I have a daughter
doesn't mean I care about her.
In fact, I thought you were
dead all these years.
[IRENE] I never would've dreamed
we'd meet on the battlefield.
Fate works in mysterious ways.
[ERZA]
No matter who you are,
you attacked Fairy Tail,
and that makes you my enemy.
[IRENE]
Mm.
Just as anyone who dares
oppose the Alvarez Empire
is my sworn enemy.
[IRENE]
Even my very own child.
But still, dying here
without ever learning
the secret of your birth...
[IRENE]
...that would be tragic.
A secret?
It means nothing to me!
I've held on to this
story for years now.
You could at least allow me
to share it with you, Erza.
Shut your mouth!
[yells]
My name is Irene.
Irene Belserion.
[IRENE] And once upon a time,
I was queen of the dragons.
[LUCY]
Four hundred years ago,
our peaceful world was attacked
by bloodthirsty dragons.
Their rampage threatened to
exterminate all of mankind.
But a lone queen rose up,
hoping to create a future
in which humans and
dragons could coexist.
Little did she know that
her plan would spell doom
for everything she so
desperately wanted to protect.
Next Time: "Dragon Seed."
Love will be blotted out by
a heart beyond redemption.