It would appear that
we all may have somewhat
underestimated the
power of your manly spirit.
Your tenacity and
uncanny ability to withstand
even the harshest of beatings
is unrivaled in our guild.
This was an
important victory.
And you've given us the
momentum to keep winning.
I don't know if I've
ever heard such
high praise from Erza before.
Well the big guy definitely
earned it, I'll say.
You were totally on
fire out there today, man!
Thanks guys.
But I'm startin' to
feel like I'm at
my own funeral or somethin'.
[LISANNA] I don't know
why anyone's surprised.
Takin' a beating's always
been your strong suit.
Sorry bro, but that's
a pretty lame strong suit.
[ELFMAN] Shut up Natsu,
you're the exact same way!
I think what you did out there
today was super
impressive, Elfman.
[ELFMAN] I really do appreciate
all the kind words, guys.
But Wendy's gonna
have to tag back in.
[WENDY] Right!
Now this is all very nice,
but you mustn't lose focus.
Get back to the games.
You have to study your opponents
if you want to beat them.
We definitely
wanna beat 'em!
See ya later.
Hey Elfman.
I'm sorry, but I kinda wanna
go and watch with them.
I would if I were you.
Mirajane's gonna be up next.
Go out there and
cheer extra loud for me.
You need to get some rest.
We'll hang out here for a while
and make sure
everything is cool.
I can set up an enchantment
to keep out any intruders.
The Thunder Legion
will be looking out for you.
Thanks, and sorry.
[EVERGREEN] It's fine.
But you might want to rethink
your strategy next time.
You should try to get
some sleep for now.
I'm sure Evergreen
will cuddle you if ya want!
Go on!
[EVERGREEN AND ELFMAN]
Hey, cut it out!
♪
[NATSU]
We've gotta do something
about those jerks in Raven Tail.
They can't just
get away with this.
[ERZA] It's as if they're trying
to take us out, one by one.
[CARLA] Actually.
I'm not entirely
convinced that's true.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
[ERAZA] How can you say that
after everything
that's happened?
The bandits from earlier
told Natsu that they were
hired by Raven Tail to
kidnap Lucy for some reason.
But their plan ultimately
ended in failure.
Not only did they choose
the wrong target,
but Natsu easily stopped them.
What's so strange
about that?
We don't know what
they were going to do
with Lucy if they had
caught her, either.
I don't wanna know!
The method they
used raises a red flag.
They have a wizard that can
instantly drain magic power.
That's the one who
attacked Wendy and I
before the games even began.
Yes, you're right.
And Master Makarov believes
it was this same wizard who
nullified Lucy's
magic power from
the sidelines during
her battle with Flare.
If Raven Tail has a wizard
who possesses
that kind of skill.
One would think that they would
choose to involve
him in the abduction.
Maybe they just thought
that it'd be too suspicious.
If they sent one of
their guys out right
before the battle,
people might notice it.
[LISANNA] The organizers
want everyone close by,
since they don't
announce who's fighting 'til
right before the match.
I think you're giving
them too much credit.
I don't know if they're
that concerned with how
they do things, as long as
somebody gets hurt in the end.
Well...
No matter what.
If they're targeting
us in and outside the
arena we must remain
on guard at all times.
No one should go
anywhere by themselves.
[CARLA THINKS] What troubles
me the most about this is
the fact that it was
Lucy they were going after.
[HAPPY] Mirajane vs. Jenny!
[CHAPATI] It's a lovely day
here at the games,
and it's about
get even lovelier!
Welcome to the
battle of the beauties,
which pits Fairy
Tail B's Mirajane Strauss.
Against Blue Pegasus' blonde
bombshell, Jenny Realite!
[LISANNA] Hey, we're back!
You're just in time.
So how's your
brother holding up?
[LISANNA] He's been a lot
better, but he'll pull through.
Let's hope your sister's
match is a little bit easier.
[CANA] Jenny's got
a lotta crowd support.
I hear she used to
be number one on
Sorcerer Weekly's
"hottest girls in magic" list.
Guys go a little nuts over her.
[LISANNA] Rumor has
it she idolized Mira.
So much that she actually
modeled her career after hers.
It's weird because now she's
technically older than Mirajane.
Since none of you aged
in the last seven years.
[PANTHERLILY] Oh, it seems
that someone's feeling better.
[HAPPY] Carla! You're back!
Wendy's fully
recovered as well.
So, apparently those of us
who aren't competing have
to stay over here
during the matches?
Oh! I was so
worried about you!
Knock it off.
You'll make me
miss the next battle.
[CARLA THINKS] I can't
keep worrying about
what I saw in my dream.
Right now, I need to support
my guild and cheer them on!
Come on Mirajane!
Fight with everything
you've got!
What's going on here?
You're not gonna like it.
Get a hold of
yourself, Master.
Do you like what you see?
[crowd goes wild]
[JENNY] Ooh.
[NATSU AND GRAY]
What kinda battle is this?
I don't know.
Huh?
It's weird.
I mean, I know they both used
to be pinup models and all.
But this is a place
for wizards to show
off their skills, not prance
around in teeny bikinis.
Disgraceful.
Hey, boys.
Hi!
[WENDY] They're not
gonna expect me
to do this kind of
nasty stuff are they?
[LUCY] I'm pretty sure
this is a special
arrangement for the two of them.
At least I hope so.
It's only the second day,
and we're already
having to dip into
our reserve members?
Yeah, kinda sucks.
But Ichiya's in bad shape.
Competing in
that Chariot race
earlier really took
it outta the old guy.
[JENNY]
You've definitely still got it.
Thank you.
It feels nice to
be doing this again!
I've gotta admit I
was actually a little surprised
that you agreed do
to a pose-off with me.
[MIRAJANE]
I don't really like slugging
it out with people,
so this is better.
[MIRAJANE] I much
prefer taking a more
peaceful approach
if it's possible.
[CHAPATI]
Two bodacious babes who are
both masters of
transformation magic?
This is truly the stuff
that dreams are made of!
Somebody pinch me!
Again I'm joined
by a real ladies'
man himself, Mr. Yajima!
And our cool guest,
Jason, has shot
dozens of centerfolds
for Sorcerer Weekly!
I'm really feeling
like a young man today!
This has gotta be the
coolest thing I've ever done!
I can't wait to see what
they'll change into next!
[LISLIE] Not so fast!
You don't expect
us to just let these
bubble-headed bimbos
hog all the attention?
[ARAÑA] We have strong
and beautiful chicas as well!
[ALL]
Team Mermaid Heel is
the ultimate in girl power!
[BETH] This is embarrassin'.
Well I definitely did
not see this one coming!
Mermaid Heel has
joined the party!
Even Lislie's ditched
the junk in the trunk
and brought the va-va-voom!
[SHERRY] Hold it!
All these girls are missing
the most important thing!
What good is skanking
around in your little
swimsuits if you don't
have the love to back it up!
If you want love,
then you gotta give love!
And we're both bustin'
at the seams with it!
And now the cute cousins
from the Lamia scale
guild have thrown their
bodies into the arena!
Wow.
That takes guts, I guess.
Why are you ladies just
watching from the sidelines?
What do you mean by that?
Do you think we should
go down there?
Are we supposed to just
always have a swimsuit handy?
No silly! But you
never know what
might happen, so you
should be ready for anything!
I have one for all of you!
[MAKAROV]
Pay close attention boys.
This is why we must
never, but never question
the infinite wisdom
of our first master.
Yeah, she really
seems to know
how to have a good
time, that's for sure.
You shouldn't
just stand here
like a bunch of party poopers!
Let's all go
down there together!
For real?
There's no reason that
we should stand idly by
while all our competitors
are taking the spotlight.
[LUCY AND WENDY] Huh?
[JUVIA] Since my body is
made of water. I can fill out
a bathing suit better than
any of these other girls.
[GAJEEL] Oh.
You're gonna do it too?
A woman must
do whatever
she can to fight
for her true love!
Well good luck with that.
This situation has gotten
pretty out of hand
wouldn't you say?
Oh yeah, but
it's all in good fun,
and the fans are
totally eating it up.
If you wanted a heaping
helping of fan service.
Then ladies and gentlemen,
Domus Flau is most
definitely the place you'd
wanna find yourself today!
And unless we want
an actual riot on our hands,
we have no choice but to
let this madness continue.
This is amazing.
Oh man!
The Sorcerer Weekly cover story!
I'll call it the Big Battle of
the Busty Bathing Bombshells!
It's so hot and cool!
[CHAPATI] But remember folks.
this is still a strictly
one-on-one affair so
Mirajane and Jenny will
be the only ones scoring!
Then why in
the heck are we
all down here
demeaning ourselves?
[MAVIS] Come on!
Lighten up, this is a
nice break from fighting.
Don't take this the wrong
way, but I just don't really
understand why a
ghost would be so into this!
Well, it makes total
sense coming from the
person who started this crazy
guild in the first place.
Ya know?
Is there a reason you're
standing so close?
As the rightful
queen of the fairies,
I simply can't be upstaged.
Wardrobe change!
School swimsuits!
This is starting to get
a little too creepy for me!
Wendy doesn't seem to
be that out of place in hers.
I feel out of place!
And now...
Bikinis and thigh highs!
That's weird.
It covers more skin,
but it's more embarrassing.
Who likes girls in glasses?
This is pretty much
the look I roll with every day.
[CHAPATI] Cat ears!
I feel absolutely
ridiculous in these.
[CHAPATI] Bondage gear!
Sometimes love
has to hurt a bit.
You're scaring me!
So "Titania!", Have you accepted
your place beneath me yet?
[ERZA] You dare speak to me?
[EVERGREEN] Sorry, ma'am!
Do you suppose
they're gonna make us
go down there and do
this in the next round?
Nah...
No way in hell.
How about a blushing
bride challenge?
So ladies, grab a
lucky guy and squeeze
into some wedding dresses!
I appreciate the help, master.
Thank you!
I will do whatever it takes
to secure a win for my guild.
Well you're not such
a bad match, are you?
Who knows, we
might be a whole
lot more compatible
than you think.
Not so fast there, buddy!
Levy is never gonna marry you!
[JET] Ya think she
wants you instead?
How come you're not
pairing up with anybody?
[GAJEEL] This is stupid.
I'm just gonna
take a nap instead.
[ROMEO] Why are you guys hiding?
[MACAO] Uh. I ain't
makin' that mistake again.
[WAKABA] And I'm afraid
my wife will see me.
[HAPPY]
How about you let me be
your partner
for this one, Carla?
[CARLA] Well, I suppose
it makes sense,
since we're both Exceeds.
My darling.
You and I are
meant to be together.
[JUVIA] Sorry.
But my heart belongs to another.
[GRAY] Hands off!
[JUVIA] Oh Gray!
She's not in your guild!
When the heck
are you gonna get
that through your
stupid spiky head!
[JUVIA] How bold!
Let's cuddle!
[SHERRY] I'm glad we can
finally show the world our love!
[REN] You're bein'
way too clingy.
And it's making me
fall for you even more.
So who's with me?
Hi!
Hey.
I've got a question for you.
Will you marry me?
[LISANNA] Hey!
Natsu!
[NATSU] Wow.
You look really nice.
[LISANNA] So do you.
Wait!
What the heck?
Remember when
we were kids.
We used to play
husband and wife.
[NATSU] Why did you do that?
[LUCY] Whoops, sorry!
[NATSU]
Get off, you're crushing me!
Now that the wedding is over,
let's get back to
another swimsuit round!
[OHBA] Stop!
This is an outrage!
I can't take any more of this!
[CHAPATI] What is this?
You foolish young people!
Let Ohba teach you a lesson!
So pay close
attention and learn
what it means
to be a real woman!
[CHAPATI] And with that
crash course in reality.
The mood in the arena has
been brought down to Earthland.
Party's over folks.
The other teams on the
field have begun to clear out.
[JASON] Cool. Down.
The circus is gone, and
it's just you and me again.
Aw, that's too bad.
It was fun while it lasted.
[CHAPATI] We need to wrap
this thing up, so let's move
on to the final round
of this exhilarating match!
[JENNY] Yes!
Sorry, Mirajane. But no matter
what the judges want us to do,
I have an air-tight
strategy for victory.
It all comes
down to this!
And I'm not gonna lose!
Why don't we
make things more
interesting and
have our own bet.
After all, everybody
else is doing it.
I'm game, so what
do you have in mind?
The loser will pose
for Sorcerer Weekly
wearing absolutely
nothing but her birthday suit.
That's crazy.
Sorry.
But I'm a little conflicted.
Who do I cheer for?
Don't know.
It's hard.
[MIRAJANE] You're on.
[CROWD]
Wha?
Unbelievable!
This might just be a bet
where everybody is a winner!
[JENNY THINKS]
She took the bait!
Mirajane has been the
apple of the public's eye
for a long time now,
so she may have
more fans in the
crowd than I do.
[JENNY] But those
judges up there are
the ones handing
out the scores.
[JENNY] So I did
a little digging to find
out what really turns them on.
And it seems like
they're into younger girls.
Which is perfect for me!
Mira may have been around
before I was, but she hasn't
aged in seven years, so now
she's actually the younger one.
[JENNY] And as an added
bonus a hot model coming
out of retirement, looking
exactly the same, and finally
getting naked will sell a ton of
magazines for Sorcerer Weekly.
It's obvious who they'll choose.
[CHAPATI] Now.
Our final theme will be.
Combat Gear!
[JENNY] So sorry
for being naughty,
but there is no way
I'm gonna lose this one.
It's just too perfect!
You really think you can
handle my combat form?
Yeah, I'm not
too worried about it.
And since we're making a bet
like everybody before us has.
[MIRAJANE] Why don't
we continue another trend,
and finish out this round with a
battle of strength
like they all did, too.
[JENNY] Uh.
What in the heck is that?
It's one of Mirajane's
She-Devil forms.
It is known as Sitri.
Her ultimate Satan Soul.
[MIRAJANE] I agreed to
the terms that you set.
So I'd appreciate it
if you would be a
good sport and agree to mine.
Wait, are you serious?
[MIRAJANE] Yes.
[CHAPATI] And like that, this
beauty battle becomes a brawl!
[YAJIMA] I suppose this
is more keeping with tradition.
[JASON] What a cute brute!
So cool!
[CHAPATI]
And Mirajane takes the big W!
Yay!
Way to go, Mira!
I'm okay with it!
Definitely a win-win!
am so ready for
next week's issue!
And that's how we do
things in the Fairy Tail guild!
But wasn't this supposed
to be a beauty contest?
Most of it was, anyway.
And no one ever said
they couldn't fight.
Mirajane just found a
way to bend the rules.
That seems to happen
quite a bit with this guild.
You said it, Wendy.
Sorry 'bout that.
But if this will make
you feel any better.
I'll buy an issue
when it comes out.
[CHAPATI]
That bold move nets another
ten points for Fairy Tail B!
Didn't know she had it in her.
Yeah, she's brutal.
That's why you always wanna
stay on her good side.
Understood.
Wow, that was
amazing. Nicely done!
Thanks you guys,
but that whole experience
was more than
a little embarrassing.
[GAJEEL] Yeah?
Well, I bet that last part
felt pretty damn good.
And now we're sitting
at twelve points.
Which ties us up
with Natsu's team.
[MIRAJANE] Is there
something wrong, Mystogan?
[JELLAL] No.
Give him a break,
isn't he supposed
to be the strong
and silent type?
[MIRAJANE] Yeah, you're right!
[JELLAL THINKS] The second day
is about to come to a close.
But there're still no answers.
[DARTON] Colonel Arcadios!
[ARCADIOS] Defense Minister
Darton, can I be of service?
[DARTON] You have got
some explaining to do!
[ARCADIOS]
Whatever do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
I want you to tell
me why the hell
you're trying
to get your hands
on a celestial wizard right now!
Don't you think you're
jumping the gun?
We need to have a trial run to
ensure everything is in order.
[DARTON]
But now is not the time!
We are not ready for that!
[ARCADIOS]
With all due respect sir,
I think you should
keep your voice down.
And truth be told, it has
been ready for some time.
[DARTON] You kept this from me?
[ARCADIOS] Don't be
offended, I kept it from
everyone in order
to shore up funding.
But once we are able to
secure a celestial wizard,
the Eclipse project will,
in fact, be fully operational.
[DARTON] That's ridiculous!
Do you expect me
to believe you've completed
a project of this
magnitude in seven years?
Whether you believe it or not,
the project is moving
on to Phase 4, Plan B.
Which means I will be obtaining
a celestial wizard if
I have to do it myself.
[ARCADIOS] I am aware
of your position on the matter.
Your opposition to Eclipse
has been well documented.
But at this point in time
there is no turning back.
Are you some kind of monster?
I can become one.
If it is necessary.
[ARCADIOS] I will
do whatever is required
to serve my king and country.
[ARCADIOS]
What lies beyond this door
will change the world forever.
If the key to open it is the
life of a young girl,
then so be it.
[CHAPATI] After an exciting
day, the final match of
day two of the Grand Magic Games
is about to take place!
[CHAPATI]
This one will test the skills
of Mermaid Heel's
Kagura Mikazuchi.
Against Sabertooth's
Yukino Aguria!
Once more we're treated to
two lovely ladies
going head to head!
Who do you think is
gonna win this one?
Are you really that
big of an idiot?
Obviously, Yukino is gonna
wipe the floor with this chick!
Then let's cheer her on!
We really gotta score
some points on this one,
since somebody screwed the
pooch on the Chariot game.
[YUKINO] I know.
But Sting is not
to blame for that.
The fact that the game involved
vehicles was unfortunate.
We can't change that now.
I just hope you
know what you gotta do.
We're counting on you.
Yes.
I will not tarnish
the name Sabertooth.
And I will achieve
victory without fail.
Do your best
out there, Kagura!
Go and fetch us a win!
Sabertooth isn't
the top ranked guild
for nothin' so
it's gonna be tough.
She would never let us down.
[KAGURA] Do not fear.
I see the path that
my sword must travel.
Something tells me that this
won't be another beauty contest.
[CHAPATI]
Well, personally, if they want
another one,
then I am all for it!
Come on you guys,
these chicks are way
too cool for something
that cheesy!
What's gonna happen?
Pay close attention.
Sabertooth is the
guild to beat this year.
You're right.
[CHAPATI] Kagura has made
quite a name for herself.
Not only is she considered
the strongest member
of Team Mermaid Heel,
she also was recently
named the top female
wizard by Sorcerer Weekly.
[CHAPATI] On the other hand,
not much is known about
her opponent, Yukino.
However, the simple
fact that she has been
chosen to represent the mighty
Sabertooth in the games,
would lead us to believe that
she will be a force
to be reckoned with!
[CHAPATI] The gong
has been struck!
Let the battle begin!
It is an honor to
cross swords with you.
For me as well.
[YUKINO]
So, shall we do as the others
before us and make a wager?
[KAGURA]
Silly bets do not interest me.
Is it because
you are afraid of losing?
[KAGURA] You're mistaken
if you believe that.
I fear no such thing.
But when I enter
into an agreement
I guarantee it will
be enacted without fail.
[KAGURA] Therefore, I never
gamble for entertainment.
Nor do I.
So let's raise the stakes.
Let's wager, our lives.
♪
[HAPPY] It looks like we've got
another girl-fight on our hands.
[NATSU] Ya think they'll
bust out the swimsuits?
[HAPPY] The audience
would probably love that,
but I really don't think
that's gonna happen.
[NATSU] They're not
the beauty queen types.
[HAPPY]
Yeah, they're super serious.
I get the feeling they're
both pretty into fighting.
[NATSU] So not so much
fan service next time, huh?
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next Time: Kagura vs. Yukino!
They said they're
gonna bet their lives,
do you think they'll go through
with it if one of them loses?
[NATSU] Nah, they'll
probably just get nekkid!
[HAPPY] Why would
you even think that?