[NATSU] It's been a long
time comin' friend.
I'm about to finish you off,
once and for all.
Once you were my friend.
But this is war, and war
has no place for mercy.
Ha! Ya got a big mouth
for such a little cat.
Come on then.
We're finally gonna find
out which one's stronger.
I'll end you.
[yells]
Yah!
[NATSU, HAPPY grunting]
[LUCY groans]
[NATSU grunting]
[HAPPY grunting]
[sighs]
[yelps]
[NATSU grunting]
[LUCY] Cut it out!
We're on a job ya idiots!
[NATSU]
What's with you?
[HAPPY] You really shouldn't
shout on a snowy mountain,
Lucy, you might start an a...
--[rumbling]
--[HAPPY] ...valanche
[LUCY yells]
Hey. Gimme a tug?
I'm kinda stuck.
Uh... Cold in all
the worst places.
Since I have your attention,
let's set something straight:
We're here to work!
But keepin' this uppity cat
in check is work, Lucy.
[HAPPY] She's got us between the
snow and a cold place, Natsu.
You bet your frozen butts I do.
Now you kids make peace
so we can get that ice
from Mt. Hakobe.
Whelp. Looks like
you've bought yourself
a little more time, Happy.
I'll just have to strip
you of your pride later.
[NATSU, HAPPY cackle]
Do you want out of there or not?
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Yes, ma'am!
[LUCY]
The name's Lucy Heartfilia.
My derpy companions?
They're Happy and Natsu.
The three of us have come
to Mt. Hakobe on a mission.
Our objective is a strange one.
We've been charged
to obtain some ice.
Magical Hakobe ice, named after
the only mountain in the world
on which it's
rumored to be found.
The job is for an
ice-manufacturer.
It's a kind that they
can't make themselves,
which makes sense, as Hakobe
ice is said to be unmeltable.
It's also so hard and so strong
that no ordinary
blade can scratch it.
That would make it
pretty tough to harvest.
But our client gave
us a magical pen,
designed for the sole
purpose of cutting it.
Why do you guys think
that people want this
Hakobe ice stuff
so badly anyway?
I've heard that if it's
applied to the skin,
it'll beautify the
wearer's complexion.
Throw it into a recipe,
and you'll come out
with a culinary masterpiece.
On top of that, the stuff's
an energy booster
that can cure minor illnesses.
Least that's the rumor.
The guys that hired
us must wanna make
some magic popsicles!
[LUCY] Somethin' tells me
this'll be a pain.
Wish we'd brought Gray and Erza.
[NATSU]
Well, It's too late for that.
They're probably out workin'
on their own jobs by now.
[HAPPY] Relax, all we gotta do
is nab some ice, right?
How hard can it be?
Good point, Happy.
The three of us have handled
way tougher jobs than this one.
That's the spirit!
By the way, I brought some
fish to eat, check 'em out!
Tadah! Travel snacks
of champions!
Whoa, so fresh
they're still wigglin'!
And since we've got
a fire wizard with us,
we can cook 'em any time!
Hey. Do what ya want with
yours but I'ma eat mine raw
Ah! It's getting way
too cold out here!
Oh yeah, that's all
kinds'a better.
My chest is not your personal
igloo. Get outta there!
[rumbling]
What's happening?
[LUCY]
Uh-oh. That looks bad.
[HAPPY]
You don't say!
That could'a been us.
Let's move!
[HAPPY, LUCY, NATSU scream]
--[LUCY] Everything is spinning!
--[NATSU, HAPPY yelling]
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY groaning]
[LUCY]
Have we stopped yet?
[HAPPY]
The Labyrinth of White!
You okay, Lucy?
[NATSU]
C'mon! Wake up!
And she got onto us
for not workin'!
You've left me with
no other choice!
Coochie, coochie, coochie, coo!
Coochie, coochie, coo!
[LUCY laughing] Please stop! I
can't take it. I'm begging you!
Uh, guys? What just happened?
Your shouting started
an avalanche,
and it knocked us
into this ravine.
On top of that, it feels
like this blizzard's
pickin' up strength,
so if we wanna get back,
we'd better hurry up.
Yeah, I agree, but I
really hate the idea
of tryin' to climb that cliff.
[HAPPY] That's cause climbin's
for monkeys and chumps!
I can fly you two back
up there lickety-split!
Sometimes I forget
how useful you are.
Yeah, well maybe I'll forget
to come back for ya!
Here we go!
--[HAPPY] Whoa!
--[LUCY yelps]
You sure you can fly in this?
[HAPPY] It's like my
wings are in a blender!
[LUCY, HAPPY yell]
[NATSU] Whoa, That crash-landing
looked frickin' awesome.
I want a turn! Let me try!
[LUCY, HAPPY]
This isn't a game, Natsu.
I nearly frickin' died!
[LUCY, HAPPY]
Such... bitter... cold...
[NATSU]
So, where are we now?
Have we caught up yet?
Probably not,
since we lost our map
in that stupid avalanche.
[HAPPY]
You're doin' real good, Lucy.
I'm gonna go look for that
map in my dreams, okay?
Heck no! That's not okay!
C'mon, you. Wake up!
If you fall asleep in this
blizzard, then you'll freeze
and you'll never wake up
and we'll get stranded here
and have to eat you.
Is that what you want?
Hey, do you think you
could you do somethin'
about this blizzard with your
fire so she'll stop shoutin'?
I can't sleep.
Guess it's worth a shot.
Fire Dragon... Roar!
[HAPPY yelling]
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame!
[HAPPY gasps, yelps]
[HAPPY] So hot!
The cold hurts just as much!
No, I take that back!
Freezin's way better!
Natsu is freakishly
strong, but I guess
a full-scale blizzard's more
than anyone can stop.
Well, ya know,
I bet Wendy's magic
would've had a better
chance than mine did.
And now that you mention it,
Gray's magic would've
been helpful too.
Here's an idea:
why don't'cha call up
one of your celestial spirits?
[LUCY] I normally would,
but I just sent them all
on vacation, so I
really can't right now.
I know they forgot
about the Liberam,
but I doubt that the stress
of it went the way
of those memories.
Those guys are in
serious need of a break.
[HAPPY]
All of 'em?
In that case, I guess we really
are on our own, aren't we?
This job sounded so
simple in the flyer.
Honestly, it didn't even occur
to me that we'd need their help.
It's all comin' back to me now.
We were fine until
one of you two said
"how hard can it be?"
and jinxed us!
It was you who said that.
We both heard you!
[LUCY] So, question.
Are you two as lost as I am?
[HAPPY]
Sure am. What do we do?
If we could tell
which way was south,
I'd say head that way.
But as things stand,
we just have to keep moving
so we don't freeze
[gasps] Look! Over there!
[HAPPY]
Wow! A cave!
Guess we beat the jinx!
That cave'll trump
a five star hotel
if it can get me
outta this blizzard.
Let's find out what it's
like in there! Natsu, mush!
[LUCY giggles]
--[HAPPY, LUCY gasp]
--[NATSU] Oh, ho-ho-ho!
Looks like it
goes pretty deep.
Let's take a look. We've got
plenty 'a time, right?
Maybe we should just
hang near the entrance.
because if this place is as big
as it seems, we might get lost.
It'll only be a
quick peek though.
Live a little, will ya?
Where do you boys get
all of this energy?
This cavern's even
deeper than it looks.
[HAPPY] How long d'ya
think it goes for?
Dunno, but I've been
lost enough for one day.
Let's head back while
we still know how.
[NATSU] No need to remember
how to get back.
I can still smell the
entrance, no problem.
[LUCY]
That's good to know and all.
But there's still
something about this place.
It's weirding me out.
[NATSU gasps, sniffs]
What's up, didja smell
somethin' tasty?
Nope, somethin weird though.
The air current
changed outta nowhere.
So, that's not normal?
What kinda shift was it?
To be honest,
I can't really tell ya.
[gasps] Get outta the way!
[HAPPY, LUCY yelp]
[yelps]
[NATSU grunting]
Ah! More of 'em inbound.
Look sharp!
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Roar!
[NATSU] There's no end
to these things! Let's go!
[LUCY, HAPPY yelp]
[NATSU] What in the heck
is up with this cave?
[LUCY] I said this place was
super-weird, but did you listen?
No!
[NATSU]
Whoa!
[LUCY, HAPPY, NATSU scream]
[NATSU, HAPPY grunt]
[NATSU, HAPPY screaming]
[LUCY screams]
So It's kinda awkward timing,
but I just remembered something!
[LUCY]
Oh yeah, what?
Right before we left
the guild, I talked to Levy!
She told me that she'd
read some stories about
this living cave that
moves around way deep
in the heart of Mt. Hakobe!
She read that no one
who's been lost down there
has ever made it out!
Thanks for letting us
know that we're screwed!
That would've been super
useful like three hours ago!
[LUCY, NATSU, HAPPY yell]
Well, we finally hit
the end of the line.
[HAPPY whimpers]
Sure is a lot colder down here.
It's every bit as bad as
it was in that blizzard,
so let's walk around
before we start to freeze.
[HAPPY] We've gotta find
that exit. Somehow...
[LUCY] Natsu, which way's
the exit? Are we there yet?
At this point, I'm clueless.
Can't even catch a whiff.
No.
I'm sorry guys, but that was
the last step I had in me.
Next time, let's just crawl.
So, hungry. I'll never
skip breakfast again.
I'm glad you're down
here with us, Natsu.
If you were anybody else then
we'd be stuck in the cold.
I'm sure that we've been
here for days, but how many?
Well.
I'd guess three days,
but it may well be four.
[HAPPY] Would we even know if
we were goin' the wrong way?
How could we?
[LUCY]
We couldn't.
That's why it feels like we've
been walking in circles.
--[stomach growlsx]
--[ALL gasp]
My tummy's eating itself.
I know we're trying
to make it last, but...
We've gotta eat sometime, right?
I guess so.
[HAPPY] Aw. I used to think
I'd always have fish.
This'll be the last
meal we get here,
so let's make the most of it.
I hear ya, Lucy.
I'm gonna roast
these fish with flair!
Please don't cook the left fish,
I wanna eat it raw.
Fire Dragon... Roar!
[HAPPY, LUCY yelp]
Natsu! Stop it!
Tell me that it's
just a bad dream!
Well, maybe they're still
good on the inside.
[HAPPY groans]
How could they be?
They're ashes now, you monster.
I told you that
they're better raw!
So much for making
our last meal count.
[HAPPY, LUCY groan]
[groans]
This sucks.
Do you think that maybe
somebody'll come lookin' for us?
Well If they do,
they'll have to get past
a mountain blizzard
and a shifting cave maze.
[ALL sigh]
All I can think about is food.
I'd kill for a bowl of
Mira's stew right now.
Would ya please stop
talkin' bout food.
It'll make us even hungrier
than we already are.
So sleepy...
[LUCY, HAPPY]
Oh, no you don't!
[NATSU grunting]
Get back up and turn on
my fire, you selfish lug!
It's cold in here. I need heat!
We've covered this, Natsu:
you fall asleep, we die!
Oww! That frickin' hurt!
Fine, I'll stay awake!
But first a quick nap.
[LUCY, HAPPY]
Oh, no you don't!
All right, I'm fired up!
Get off my back will ya?
So this is what happens
to people after three days
without getting any sleep.
It's like I'm a zombie.
There's a term for this feel.
They call it the
"breaking point."
All I want is to lay
down in an actual bed.
Forget the reward,
I'd pay every jewel
I have if it meant
I could sleep.
[HAPPY] Hold on. Me and Lucy
aren't makin' any fires,
so why can't we go to sleep?
Wow, when you put it like that.
there's nothing I can say,
you're just so persuasive.
No one's objecting?
'Kay, night, night.
Don't do this, guys.
It isn't any fair.
No sleeping allowed,
and don't you forget.
Uh.
[LUCY, HAPPY]
You had one job, ya jerk!
[sighs] You were totally
noddin' off, c'mon!
Uh. Sorry, I'll be good.
Well, that failed horribly.
so I guess we're all in
this together after all.
[LUCY, HAPPY, NATSU groaning]
If we all keep our
eyes on each other
it means they have to stay open.
[HAPPY]
I'd be scared of starvin'
if I weren't gonna freeze.
Well, If you do freeze,
I won't let Lucy eat you.
Ha... That was just a joke.
Well, not really, but you know.
[CROWD cheers]
[LUCY]
Thank you all so very much!
I can't begin to express
what an honor it is
to hold the Leaf-pen
trophy in my hands.
Since my first book did so well,
I plan to work even harder,
as writer and a--
[LUCY]
No. It can't be.
My award's a giant bathtub?
That's incredible! I've worked
so long for this moment!
Did I really though?
Well yeah, sure I did, look.
They don't give you
a hot tub like that
unless ya work for it, do they?
Showers are nice and all.
but nothing beats a
good ol' fashioned bath.
Ha... Mm...
[NATSU] I'm all...
fired up. Lots of fire.
Hey.
Check it out, a spicy treat!
This fire's a little bit
on the chilly side.
Like a minty sherbet,
wonder what it's burning off of.
Boy, I'll tell ya.
This warm water hits the spot.
[HAPPY]
Wow So many fish!
If only I had one more
mouth to eat them with.
[HAPPY]
Don't mind me you tasty morsels.
The ocean. An all
you can eat buffet!
Thar she blows, me matey!
[LUCY giggles]
[HAPPY]
Wait for me!
[NATSU] It really does
taste like someone
set a mint sherbert on fire!
Oh yeah, this is
the life, just me,
my blissfully hot bathtub
and the distant glow of--
[HAPPY]
Raw fish at last!
[yelps]
[LUCY]
What the heck is your problem?
Get off my head, you freak!
Why am I naked?
[screams]
So tasty.
Keep it down, or else!
I was tryin' to have a meal!
Now it's ruined!
We're screwed.
What the--?
Huh?
Now, that's a surprise.
[yelps]
Anyone get crushed by rubble?
I think I'm alive.
Yeah, I'll start
a flame and give--
Don't you make a single spark
until I've gotten dressed!
[NATSU, HAPPY groan]
Okay, yeah! I'm good to go!
[NATSU sniffs]
Whoa! Now that is a smell.
[LUCY] I'm cold, hungry,
tired, and a little crazy,
but I know that tunnel is new.
Surface air. No doubt about it.
Well sniffed!
So this thing might become
our ticket outta here, eh?
It's worth checkin' out!
Well, that's weird.
It's a massive wall of ice.
[NATSU] I see an exit,
but it's on the other side.
Go on then! You know
what to do, man!
Thanks for the pep talk!
Fire Dragon Talon!
Amazing. Not even a scratch.
C'mon Natsu, one more go!
Fire Dragon... Crushing Fang!
It's useless.
I haven't eaten anything
but ice in days.
That's a decent excuse,
but it's still weird
that it wasn't damaged at all.
Natsu might feel weak
by his own standards,
but that should've
done something. Unless...
Guys, I think that wall's
made of Hakobe ice!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Huh?
Which means that we can bust out
with nothin' but this magic pen.
Oh! Yeah, I think you're right.
About the pen or the wall?
They're kinda related, Natsu.
But It's only been four days,
so of course you forgot.
[LUCY grunts]
Hakobe Ice! Good work guys.
We got what we came for!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Oh!
--[rumbling]
--[HAPPY] What is it now?
I don't think we're
gonna like it.
Giant monster!
[LUCY] Um. Hello there,
distinguished sir or lady.
So is this your place?
It's really nice.
Uh, Lucy? I don't
think it's listenin.'
Okay, so we're gonna get
out of your hair now,
but we need to
take this with us.
It cures the sick and
gives people energy and
we can't get paid without it.
But look, it's just
a little bit,
so please don't
be too mad at us.
[MONSTER 221A roars]
[NATSU, LUCY grunt]
Don't think he's
feelin' generous!
[LUCY] Let's make a
run for it before he
knocks down something big!
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY yelp]
[NATSU, LUCY yelp]
Sorry 'bout that!
Ya smell that fresh air?
We made it!
Yeah, and we waited
out that big blizzard!
We can celebrate
once we're back home!
Ya don't have any ceilings
to crush me with out here.
Fire Dragon... Iron Fist!
[NATSU yelps]
What the heck was that, Natsu?
[HAPPY] I've seen you
beat up monsters like that
with one punch, what gives?
Cut me some slack.
I haven't eaten
or slept in days.
All right, we'll take
it together!
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU yelps]
I'm just as tired and
hungry as you are.
[MONSTER 221A roars]
Take this, ya big ugly.
My Fleuve d'étoiles!
[LUCY screams]
[LUCY] That was the
last of my strength.
At this point I can
barely move at all.
[gasps]
There's our escape raft,
Natsu. Get on, quick!
Ugh. Got nothin' to puke
Just hang in there
a little longer!
[MONSTER 221A roars]
Why is it so fast?
[HAPPY, LUCY yelp]
He's way too drained to fight.
But this ice can boost energy.
Natsu!
Huh?
Every brain-freeze
of my life just came
for seconds all at once!
You ate a crap-ton of ice, man.
What'd you think would happen?
What the--?
[yells]
That didn't just hit
the spot, it nailed it!
[HAPPY]
No way!
That ice even cured
Natsu's motion sickness!
Get ready, you two!
[NATSU yells]
[NATSU, LUCY, HAPPY scream]
--[MONSTER 221A roars]
--[NATSU yells]
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
[NATSU grunts]
[LUCY, HAPPY scream]
You kicked its ugly butt, man!
Hakobe ice definitely
lives up to the hype,
don't ya think?
Heck yeah it does.
I feel like I'm
on top of the world!
[LUCY, HAPPY giggle]
[NATSU]
All right.
I guess we'd better head
back to the guild-hall.
[HAPPY] If we're fast,
we might make it in time
for Mira's home-cooked dinner!
[LUCY] Never thought I'd be
this excited to get some sleep.
Oh. Hey, wait. We can't
go back to the guild until
we've delivered that ice.
Uh-- Hey, Natsu?
You ate that whole slab
of Hakobe Ice, so uh...
[NATSU, HAPPY gasp]
[HAPPY, NATSU, LUCY]
We've gotta go back in there?
[groans]
[ALL laugh]
[HAPPY]
And... transform!
[NATSU]
What are you shoutin' about?
[HAPPY] I'm practicin' that
awesome transformation spell
we learned from Mira!
[NATSU] Sweet, can you
turn into anything?
[HAPPY] Probably. What would
you wanna turn into?
[NATSU]
Hmm. How about a giant monster?
[HAPPY]
A monster. Really, why?
[NATSU] Because I wanna
go on a crazy rampage
and crush some buildings.
[HAPPY] Yeah, but. That's
exactly what you do right now!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Next time: Transform!
[HAPPY] Think I'd wanna
be a killer whale.
I'd get to eat
fish all the time!
[NATSU] You already do
that all the time!